Air Jordan
Nola.com
I have great respect for knowledge b b
Sick of them posing as if they're the good guy
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Little bit about Alex Jones
Jordan Jordan
What up
I'm listening to a little bit of old stuff that I haven't listened to in a long time
Stop
Play album
Non-stop when I was going to
Because of that
The better part of a decade probably since I have put one of those albums on exercising
Distance of not having made me able to listen to it again I appreciate
Is that okay
A little bit
Something that maybe I couldn't enjoy it as much as I originally gave you guys of overexposure grit
That's nice my bright spot is that the weather in Chicago is for the
The first time God damn nearly nine months
Great and then because we live in a cave Underground
Parking
That that's good
Episode to do
About May 12th and 13th
Of this week
I wanted to throw Thursday and but it was impossible because this episode infuriated the s*** out of here
Give you two pieces
Spoiler in advance
Is another round of my favorite game which is Alex
Says he's going
To prove something
No ever
Alex makes a reveal
Of one of the biggest f****** lies the funniest
There's no way that I could
Use it and it not live up to like being one of the most absurd thing you could ever imagine
Yuri Yuri
Things in the past
Check in with you or the seltzer
The first Kevin h
Serious
PRI aaas
Policy wonk
Blerg
Thank you so much you know about what they want
Thanks
I just want to not sure if it's a nips or snips
Knibbs
Heroin
Large
Druel
Ya think
A local charity
Appreciate
Yes sir Jordan
Are the Salford marches on we are in the week for now
Ugly at 4
Coming in on the end you know what you described as the first
We are officially at 65 South Thursday out
This week
Made a discovery of something I I remember liking from my childhood
Clearly Canadian
Never have I found a more rain to beasts
Then Clearly Canadian
Variety
Barry
Mountain BlackBerry
Okay country raspberry pretty good
Route of Andre
I knew something was up because I looked at the bottle of the clearly
Sparkling water beverage
I don't know what to do
Eliza Clearly Canadian
I am saying with the mountain Blackberry was alright
Wild Cherry there was something wrong with that so bad
It might have gotten is a rocket carry
That's how I was coming into 22
Negative
Start listen to the hives
I don't remember what their song was
Incapable
Cuz they country raspberry with pretty good
Klondike Donut Bar
Absolutely
So this is the nearest shelter will check back in next time and find out what we signed out
We got
Episode
It's going to be a bumpy ride and here's another context route from Today Show
Wrestler Disney's already moved out
Brake Rush Limbaugh
We don't need to lose him
Man
Feeling like
We got to direct our spiritual energy towards saving Rush Limbaugh
Be around the dinner table and just like
Heavenly Father
Look after Rush Limbaugh
I guess it's a little less because Alex is in the same field
Kind of kind of like their contemporaries or something
F****** weird
I remained totally neutral
And whatever you decide to do to him
So why we start off the show at the beginning of it
Talking about how like if you
Through the globalist plan you understand it really easily
Like himself
Sure drained metaphor that he tries to make
Free one that app
The globalist and how they operate
Philosophy
It's just like
Professional Barrel
Absolutely Elementary
My dear Watson
You got to have the courage
And I liked it it
Allegory or an analogy
Most big comets and asteroids
But end up being found
Most ever found by the millions of amateur astronomers
But my powered
Capitalism
Probably sounds pretty good to Alex I don't know
Extended metaphor
Amateur astronomers at 2
Isn't true
Amateur astronomers do not discover most of the near-earth objects that are found each year
That's why it's always a big story when an amateur does discover one which gets a lot of press
It professionals at the big telescope for find a comet all the time how come I only read headlines about amateurs finding
You can easily see how that selection bias but Alex's brain uses to land on
That's what's going on
Doesn't do any research on the topic he decides what he's just
Thought up with
True
No every the day today
The case that is not like the others but headlines are pointing up
What is perception that amateurs find more than the professionals is probably partially due to the fact that like
Hale-Bopp was found by amateurs
High-profile nature
According to a 2015 paper co-written by members of the jet propulsion laboratory the minor planet center and the universe
Reviews of Hawaii and Helsinki
From 1998 through 2013 only about 1.8%
Of the 10,000 and 44 discovered near-earth objects were found by the amateur community
Okay not what Alex
Alright
Is a minority-majority
That's true enough
Supported professional astronomers discovered the vast majority of near-earth asteroids
Follow-up observations needed to pinpoint the orbits and predict
The future motions of the asteroid
Once a new near-earth asteroid is discovered the efficiency with which amateurs provide these follow-up observations
Professional telescope
To continue scanning the skies for more new discoveries
There is a cool professional amateur collaboration
Is not true
It feels true to him though because he never reads past the headline
About the many discoveries that are made
Any never reads headlines about the discoveries are made by scientists and professionals with the labs because they don't make headlines
They're just taking credit for all the it what's what's an amateur other than that you don't like
Who's to say the people at Nasa aren't finding these on their off-hours that mean
I think the larger Point that he's trying to make he's the amateur astronomer sees the metaphorical comment heading
Towards us which is of course the globalist evil plant
Like the media or something he saying
I said I think that's the point because I was really doesn't complete the metaphor yet
Instead thinking about the Stars
And in the process
Who makes an admission that I find remarkable
1993 University
Warehouse
$25,000
For a 12 inch refractor telescope
Just come out
McDonald's
Technology in it
Name five more platters
Servo Motors
Hill Country
By myself
All night
I believe some of that
The cute little story a Sunbeam
Alex Alex Jones the 1993 until 1995
$25,000 telescope
It's something that I would consider a big interest of Alex's based on everything I've heard from his show
Started frequently
He does talk about going to the Stars
You got to look for where you're going first and elope
It should give you some sense of the kind of money Alex comes from because it's out spotted $25,000 telescope
It wasn't because you was making loads of cash
He's talked about his earlier jobs and everything's like assisting a Tyvek
Clinic in carpet cleaning
By the way
$5,000
$44,000 today adjusted for inflation
You better give you some idea of the type of purchase he's talking about on air
That's basically a year's salary at any of the jobs he's claiming to have had prior to getting into radio
I remember when I was
Around that age and my dad help
Get a loan for my first car that cost $2,500
Wasn't really negotiated
I don't think so
A rich and you basically just got whatever he wanted growing up
Specifics of the story lead me to suspect the latter
No names of things there's a lot of specifics
Yeah that's not good
Makes me think it's worth through cuz I
Why else would you tell the story about it like
Pull myself up by my bootstraps
25 Grand
That'd be great
I would appreciate that more
Continues as metaphor a little bit and becoming is this fantasy where
You know again I think I think those analogs that I was saying I Keys the amateur astronomer.
This is where he tells a story about it and I think there is
Hey this is kind of sad
We've talked about people in the yard
Genie coming out of the Kuiper belt
Pass Pluto
A 20th planet
What
Pluto's not even a planet anymore bro
Astronomer
Photographs of this thing entering our solar system
Pluto
Coming in
A million miles an hour
People begin to anywhere
Picking up
Call the government and Industry
I see this
How did
CIA
My God
They know this planets coming in
You are
Solar system
Why did they make the decision.
Vitalis
And then you,
With the realization
The mathematicians that it's going to hit Earth
So you do need professional
Scrapped out there
No I made it with nuclear weapons and blow it up
This is the plot of The Fifth Element
Humanity
Little bit closer
Is The Fifth Element
It's not a planet
Galaxy just watch The Fifth Element
Where is Miller
The coherent metaphor
For what he's trying to say
He usually isn't capable of that
More or less
Tracks
Like he's trying to make
Is the globalist playing finding talks about
He talks about it
Google's plan is coming and they wanted to come pick up and start looking planet
Are the people who he's indoctrinated
Conspiracy theory followers
Whatever
I don't understand it
It makes sense.
I applaud
Okay
Praise
A grant
Completely off track before he's able
Make something kind of makes
Unfortunately even if the metaphor holds
There's some holes
For instance what if you're an amateur astronomer you find an asteroid you insist is new and of course
It's on its way to hit
Discovered
Calculations you made about its orbit are wrong
Your work but it's also possible that you did a bad job
Let me take a look at your evidence and tell you that you're mistaken that's a rock formation you think it's a dead engine
A imagination is Fun making things up
Is metaphor in playing around with what I'm doing
I can see what's going on here
This case I can actually engage with it a little bit
I think even in the hypothetical realm that he's talking about you can clearly see how like oh no you didn't
You didn't find an asteroid
Astrology
Gary Oldman
$25,000 telescope will not give you an understanding of space
Still need to learn
Oh that's true
Baby inside baseball
Coming up
I thought about talking about the president what really goes on White House
My forces
Bird's eye view
Longview under the towel
He watches TV and eat junk food
Shut up
Assholes
No I can do it justice
Cuz
It's actually
Positive
You know what
Last segment of the shower remind me to do a guys
It's very very sad
It's also very very empower
Yep that's
Cuz I don't know what he's talking about
I think someone forgot to reply
So it is next life we get to Alex talk about how cool it is
To drive fast
But
Is not telling the story to sound cool because sounding cool is uncool
This is a guy who's obsessed with coolness
How fast they are
Almost 200 Mi an hour
It's fine
Oh my gosh midnight out there there's not a damn far
Freeport Lane
Absolutely
About 150 while back
There's one huh
I'm outside the Austin had the car.
Dukes of Hazzard man
Noosa hazard
Stop right there
Is a new show
Shelby stories
Because
There is
Cool because
He is trying to look cool
This is a white paradox
I'm also back when I was like 18
Do love driving over big humps
I'm not telling cool stories
Is that what you talking about beating all these famous people
Write a meeting saving people
Famous thing you can do is be not famous
Stabbed
The one of these famous people interact
May have gotten in trouble
For interacting with Alex
Translator
Lisa email
Attorney
Southern
To arrest him
Deal
Mark Cuban owned a company that wasn't a 911 film loose change
This documentary in quotes by Alex and Dylan Avery release
Easter 2005
If it was considered what they called a living document which is code for things they were constantly
The super embarrassing stuff not be in it
In 2007 the third version came out called Loose Change Final Cut
Popular property in conspiracy theory world and Alex signed on as an executive producer for the Final Cut
Diversion
In Fords
Actually Apparently one of the things I read Charlie Sheen was it
Barbie career to worry about
Jason bermas would go on
Earlier days and Warrior
Work on loose change predates all of that
Dylan Avery incidentally has gone on to continue working it movie
Zendaya in that industry
Not on conspiracy documentaries
Because
At the age of 18
Is a collection of articles that trace the roots of 9/11
Literally 9/11 conspiracy theories
Avery was inspired by this book to make a movie
According to an article in slate discovered of government
Cover up
Essentially he was going to make a fiction movie about people discovering that the government did 9/11 but he realized that was too defensive
The government do 9/11
Okay so he just made The Blair Witch Project
Yeah but you was into it at the time.
Give me the article from 2011 stall
Show me article
You still says he supports the
Getting sucked in deeper than you
Into a hardcore mentality that it was almost too easy to get into back then
Because the war just started and everybody was just so pissed off
When he says he still supports the movement he means that he's are some unanswered questions about 9/11
But that's not what Loose Change was about primarily
Dylan Avery was a bright ambitious used to channel does energies into the world of conspiracy
It's kind of hardening to it
Know that at least to some extent he got out of it
I found a 2017 interview with the outline Which online
Princeton
When the interviewer ask them where
I never did rely on Infowars as a source but I definitely don't know
Anyway it's just kind of funny that the director of the movie that Alex claims of his own which helps
Really put us on the map
We all need to grow up
So what is Mark Cuban
Companies looking to distribute loose change
Unrelated
Play the SEC was investigating Mark Cuban for insider trading
In the course of that investigation Cuban release an email
Cuban was
Alright
This lawyer definitely something's emails because of Cubans almost Distributing
You had nothing to do with Cubans insider-trading investigation
He was suspended for 42 weeks for his behavior and then eventually fired
Sec
We're sending
Post an internal SEC email which were determined to be inappropriate
12 article on Reuters this lawyer Jeffrey Norris
What a federal appeal in his case that he deserved
A chance to get his job back by presenting medical evidence that those actions won't happen again
Fihi argued that his life situation was chaotic back when you sent those emails and that he'd been seeing a psychiatrist and
Santa's in his life
To the point where
It wouldn't be that again
Business Insider was able to find some Internet comments that Norris made around that time of those emails
It kind of seems like he just particular
Expand
In one combat North suggest
The Cubans threw a recent game against the Warriors for some Financial motive
It partially sounds paranoid and partially like a guy f****** around it is talking s*** about Mark Cuban it's unclear
I got it I got it
Snow being an SEC lawyer I might be more inclined to enjoy it but I get what you say
Scores were
Hatred of Mark Cuban
Whatever
Anyway just wanted nothing to do with humans ABC insider-trading case
Just turned it into proof of the SEC
Cuban for Distributing Alex's film
Bernard Jordan
Remember I told you the beginning of this Nikes
But Alex would have
My favorite lie
My town for this
This is breathtaking
Once you don't want them they really want your soul
Okay
In Hollywood that is
Here's a 3 million dollar deal to star in this movie
It's a space fantasy movie
You're a space
The movie
Pictures later on in the theater watching this
Huge movie
I would have been cool to play that guy
Like the most valuable thing in my life
My children and then doing the right thing
. will drive up like for things like that
The big giant franchise
Kurt Russell was in a second
Valuable in the final equation
Major huge movies
So I think you know what you talk about
Do you know what movies are playing
I could sell discount Russells
Entire entire filmography and there's only one movie
That's a sequel that Kurt Russell wasn't in the original
End of the space fantasy worth it
Kurt Russell was also in Naperville
Furious 7. Whatever
But he wasn't
AMC movie
Yet he was in the first Soldier but he was definitely
He thinks that he was up for the Chris Pratt
In Guardians of the Galaxy
Star-Lord
Do you think the James Gunn
Was like
We don't even need to do an audition
Anyway
Get me Jones alright
Wow that's great awesome
That's no good
First Guardians of the Galaxy film came out in 2014
Operative star six years 2000
Which unfortunately predates the start of production by about 4 years
At that point
To be written
This isn't the point you protecting you is offered the starring role
Play billionaire Rich Playboy
All right and Iraq or whatever and it gets captured
I don't know how it is
I'll tell you that right now
Kiss Kiss Bang Bang
You were offered movie role
I still don't answer your face about it
Identifying details like his lies just too egregious
Stanford
Are you at group God damn it I'm.
Also according to style
Is just coming off Parks and Rec
Cast member
Like parts of parks and rec
TV Guide
Alex's radio
He had a roll yelling into a bullhorn
The movie The Only Reason
Get the f*** out of here
This is this is what I'm talking about
Country Door
I heard that we're done
Domino's Pizza
Reimagining Guardians of the Galaxy
Michael Rooker role complex
Able to handle angry
Capable translate nobody
Good morning
No I don't think he could pull that off
I don't even think he could do the opening crawl scene with Chris Pratt dancing I don't think that's the issue would be distracted
F*** you Alex
Get the f*** out of here
Universe
Is way more fun than ours
The movie would be very different
Alright well we got our phones
I don't I don't think of dead yet I'm just going to
Taste bad for 11 for a little bit
And Alex with a spica cast
Articulating these things is gross even though
Trying to say I think he's saying as a interview
Something like that
Old crappy car
All the rest on your head
That is a connection to God has you and that's beautiful
Beautiful
They are amazing
I see the most beautiful people that don't have God eyes are dead
Is God
Body Shop
Good it doesn't matter if they're beautiful
Woman is ServSafe to be the most beautiful body
You ever imagine it's like
Plastic mannequin
It's not
Real
Justice and freedom
Your financial support so weird
A relationship just that like
Because I can't have it
You look so awful
It's not good
Yeah
I could use your
So I guess is the covid-19 positive cases that are in the White House
Send Sachi
You're at the virus isn't real uses to deal with this story on its real terms because I think he recognizes that the way
He would cover the realities
Be dangerous
Self quarantining
Because the White House has a Contagion
Vardy
Testing positive no.16 asymptomatic
So Alex refuses to cover the other aspects of the covid-19 in the White House like he's very consistently
8 secret service members
Which is bad on its own you know but there's more to it than that
There's at least two staffers in the executive branch of tested positive
Who's married to someone who has close contact with everyone
As of May 11th
CNN was reporting that the person who Miller caught the virus from is unknown
Forcep to wear masks at the office and apparently
Trump's economic advisor
Scary to go to work
S*** is not good
Also by the time houses on the air
He's not doing a good job
Is minimizing the old news while sent
Last teeth hurt even more Secret Service
Recovered
Not nearly the small problem Alex and pretending
Well if Alex were to cover here's how Alex would cover it
They're killing the president
We have to act right
Drift really quickly into Insurrection territory
Telling them to go assassinate people near the
It's up to minimize thing to that level
Stare
Slurred 1 * who's like they're poisoning president president is literally
Times were different back then whatever you really want
The meat packing plant
Himself he doesn't understand what asymptomatic cases
A bunch of deaths linked to workers
Do plants complete disrespect these people and their families
Do you have to go to work to continue
The ability of people to have food process
He's minimizing the experience that they're having to deal with that
Abhorrent
McAlister's
A better word
News on this episode cauchy's testimony
They didn't do a good job
Reserve a little clip of this because I mean
It would be exhausting
Need to go over all of it
Fauci announcing
Reasonable martial law
I said many times
We have worked out
Is a guideline framework
You safely
What we have workout
How you safely
Bill Gates
Doesn't matter all my glass hold
50 * wrong
And making our move
Let's hear from him
Business strategy and kind of feels like a remembering a bit he hasn't done is just going to try
Play some video
He also realizes
You build up his image of them is arch-villain
So when he tries to actually know play longer clips
Fairly well
Constant interruptions
Patxi's words in complete set
Some technique also breaks in
80 distract the audience with references to completely unrelated aspect of his conspiracy narrative
Things that have no bearing on what
Thought you saying at all
Yeah and for good measure he calls them nerds he's like
Tell me what to do
McKay's analysis use the strategy it out here in the same thing over and over again
Interesting
It just goes on and on for like two segments of the show where Alex just makes himself mad listening Saatchi
Been interrupting do impressions of the Elegance talking
Why he's a childhood
Alex has a guest on
This episode because
More the Project Camelot side of things
Appearances really all that interesting except for the fact
Kind of interesting
We have
Also joining us this.
Possible
UFO Invasion that's what I told the crew today
I'm glad I read that
Baked
Project Blue beam
You and
Name five more planets
Invasion
Artificial
UFO
Guys
Reboot
Alright let's just go to break
Jesus
That was surreal
Okay
Impossible to argue with the alt right
Ludacris.
Exactly
But just
Perfect essence
The right way
Steven Greer is a big name in the world is like a alien
Disclosure
Project Camelot episode
Specifically
Eazy-E figure that some of the
Maybe some of the weirder alien folk distrust
Documentaries about him and I think maybe
He's a bit of a like
Alien Dude Perfect
Nicky's II do remember that
I think I think he does have an actual doctor
I don't know how relevant
For as long as I've known about it
Guyon
Wants to talk about how they're planning to do a fake alien infection
Alex
Explain why you having this conversation because it's even absurd for his show
So this is how we tried to do that
Greer Park
Point
A couple of his books and I probably had to say
Forgot into UFOs and all of this because
Real
Shadow government
But
Now is ready for the day
Couple hours next week
The show is descendants
Else to do I'm not going I don't have any
I don't find it at all interesting diculous
Alex
Gushing over this guy
It's because I listen to the next day and this whole thing is fun
Drop like a hot potato it's not
I think it was just a weird because this guy has a new documentary coming out she wants
Traffic
So I don't really care
Greer promote his documentary and Alex's interview with
But
It is David Alan Grier will promote
If out does continue down the road of saying there's going to be
I promise if he keeps it up for now we just use like a blip on the radar
The rest of the 12
Is a weird day weird day
I mean
It's hard to get weirder than Alex saying that he was going to be in Guardians of the Galaxy
And that is because he has
And I got on my knees about 3 a.m. this morning when I woke up
NASCAR
Give me the guidance and direction to not
Indigestion
Calmly
Information you was best
Give you the
Very soothing music
I'm right now you'll see the live show
Feed title
Global bombshell
Who confirms
Them on a planetary scale
I have an entire
Folder
The United Nations
Admitting they're doing
I think about
Think about it
There's no news here!
This isn't the news article in it
It's literally a blog post that just
Including the show that Alex is in the middle of
East sightings of the process of the show he's in the middle of doing
That is
Spectacular
Preston that's really great
I have never seen an Ouroboros in real life
Is really gorgeous
It's circular citation confirm
Play whatever I'm going to say in half an hour
You are a weirdo
Future proves what I'm saying in the past because eventually the future will be the past
It's pretty wild
Cool thing on this episode is going to be this World Health Organization and all these folks have admitted that they put sterilants at the vaccines
In order to make people unable to reproduce and what have you
So that will be a large pieces
Over which the rest of the Alex's episode
Also of course
There's going to be a bunch of weird other s*** going on
With his commitment
To be focused
So you don't stay on topic for a
Sinbad
Tablet
Let me go see what
Play a video
Buy a group like
Anyone
I don't know what that means
Talking about
Interviewing
About 8
Yeah they wouldn't dare do that
Course this morning
20 m
All I did was type
I've been
HCG
Website
Admitted
UK group is and I don't really care because everything reported they're talking about
I have no idea that Rabbit Trail down
Does not admit on their website HCG sterilized
In fact if you go to the website read their materials easy-to-understand explanation for how this misinformation work
Julie milstein P David Griffin and JW Lee release paper called quote
Imitation programs for misinformation on contraceptive vaccine
Which explains the dynamic play
There was a campaign to attack vaccine
Supported
Executed by the World Health Organization
Which was a clinical trial
Designed to provide
Protection against
Four. Of 122
Ears
The active ingredient that birth control with HCG or human chorionic
Them
Which is a hormone necessary for pregnancy to begin
In order for this hormone to be delivered it needed a carrier and then this Indian study that use diphtheria and tetanus toxoid
Which reproduce
Adjuster visit carrier
Took the stud
In lab
Vaccines were sent to hospital Laboratory
Which word assessment and are not appropriate for a vaccine
Because they're using something that it was a test that it wasn't made to Analyze This
And they were able to quit
They found low levels of HCG like activity in some samples
That was enough to create a narrative
Actual researchers followed up in quotes when the vaccines were tested in Laboratories which used properly validated test systems
The results clearly show that the vaccines did not contain HCG
This was validated by six Laboratories in five countries but it doesn't matter
Aronia science confirm the conclusion these folks are looking
Corsa weather
They just ignore that about the erroneous. They wanted to believe to begin with
That's the root of what a bunch of this they're putting steroids in the vaccine stuff explanation
Super easy to understand
Is there. Just keeps popping up over time
Africa check traced have the same as information was being used in 2014
Clean the World Health Organization was conducting a quote Master relaxation exercise in Kenya masquerading as a tetanus back
Boca storage
Women of childbearing age because
One of the concerns
Is the children dying from tetanus early
Enabled
Take those tetanus related deaths
So far down
In the developed world
You know you take the the the demographic that would
Be most help by the vaccine
Turn fat into some sort of a nefarious conspiracy about
Trying to make people
The plan
It's a mess we always have a manhole Within
3 ft of each other
And
If somebody says anything anti-vax bulshit you get to pushing down the manhole
That is my new law
As long as it's only an inconvenience 10000000 manholes across
Chicago as long as
Dirty water movie
Society
After two years you may be able to come back
That'll be an interesting way to do things
Probably
Approved all this stuff about it
Pencil 880
I've known so much information for so long
Hey
Here it is
Here's the URL on the UN website
That's why you want to use a
Something else
Yippee interesting hold on to that thought for later
URL there
Quote
HCG founded World Health Organization tetanus vaccine concerns in the developing world
Published in the open-access library journal and let's just say it has an interesting history
Firstly it's just based on the same nonsense about the tetanus vaccine that can place the India birth control shot study with
This was a paper that was written by two researchers named Shaw and
Who had a history about vaccines
Is it okay
In 2016 they put out a paper in the journal vaccine
HPV and behavioral issues
This article has been withdrawn at the request of the editor-in-chief due to Serious concerns regarding the scientific soundness of the art
Review by the editor-in-chief and evaluation by outside experts
And the claims that the article makes or unjust
This was Shah in Tamil
Third study-related seriously flawed
History is littered with paper
In the generous interpretation
Aspersion
Headline Alex flashed up on screen
The World Health Organization website
So their basic plan is to try and get something
Published for at least a little bit then it's retracted
Then make music for a right-wing propaganda
Their plan
You know if that's what you're suggesting
Maybe
Beyonce
Furby to say like hey they've done all this stuff repeatedly in the past messenger and you know
You can't just say that you know just goes there
They are there clear history of not being good
And turns out this paper is worthless as well
In the paper they did no new tasks they just relied on data that already existed and was part of that 2014 campaign
There's honestly not much more to it than that it's just a rehashing of the tetanus birth control shot
Confusion propaganda
Literally all it is
The study doesn't prove anything but doesn't show any new information
It's just a republishing of an already debunked
Conspiracy theory about vaccines
Oh my
My God it's the
Paper version of Alex posting his video on his own blog
Another important remember is that you
It would make you temporarily unable to get pregnant
Many people opt for the depo-provera shot as a means of birth
Control and have to get that every 3 months to control reproduction
Permanent sterilization Alex's imagine
Is going to go with
But whatever
Justice fantasy supported discredited work of a vaxelis
Also the open-access library Journal is not a credible outlet that you would accept
Take your time to make an
You might like this
The fact that Alex has an article this article is a primary source that he relies on big claims that he's taking information
The World Health Organization
Is this the definition of dishonest
That's what there's a lot of this is based on where it's coming from
And its rash
So of course I got to connect
Bill Gates in here we got to complain about him a little bit
Find
Hitler
India through his ass out
There are a lot of folks in India man
But do you really want to sign on to sterilizing
Where's this going
You can see it from his perspective Until you realize
So I don't know how he comes off when he says that he kind of understands
To me that's totally fine exterminate people the developing world
Summarize the principal said that I would never say something like that
That sounds like someone who I would be very comfortable in a white supremacist authoritarian state
A race specific biome
Seems like a
The story The Bill Gates on Gates Foundation is completely not true
It was something in 2017
Some media reports have suggested that all health-related collaboration with the Gates Foundation
National
Has been stopped
This is inaccurate and misleading
Melinda Gates Foundation continues to collaborate and support the Ministry of Health and Family welfare
The propaganda
In April 2012
After the reports that seven of the youths of the trial had died
Subsequent investigations found that the deaths were not related to the back
Magazine
One girl drowned in a quarry another died from a snake bite
And one died from complications of malaria
Investigators deemed the other two dance unlikely to have been related to the vaccine
This is just absolutely
Propaganda narrative
Thinks of credible
That's the level of workout lazy and delicious
Also I think you just
The making
The part about Pakistan
Because in September 2019
Pakistan
It will commit approximately 200 million dollars in support of the FPS
Initiative
A comprehensive effort in combating poverty and improving Health Nutrition in financial inclusion in that country
The prime minister of Pakistan Imran Khan
I'm pleased the Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation will assist with a range of activities including accelerating stunting Reduction Program
Supporting Financial inclusion initiatives
Investing in public health systems to improve health
Introduce maternal newborn and child mortality
This one
Emmaline
Which is presented to his audiences which is just unacceptable
Istanbul
Look up kicked out of a bar before it's just a billionaire when you get kicked out of a bar
Send his money over
He's not invited back interesting but also rule
Also no record is that okay
But the thing is the Bill Gates
Big bad guy
Did you know
But there's a council
Lovett the world
Alex doesn't know
Okay that's an issue just makes me really sad for a conspiracy theorist
I've been really researching millgate
4 years
He is
The science officer on
Committee
Course
Rotating
Members
And there are
Galahad
Lancelot
Information out
It makes more sense that he doesn't notice
Or like in a politburo
You're allowed to retire
From the council soros's in there probably the mix
Well
Calories in there
I don't I think she was kick Obama Obama
Past presidents
12 is a better number for a council
Stella D'oro
Bolsonaro's in there's always have crazy is that
No bolsonaro's not both
I know Alex has been not talking about bolsonaro this whole time
Could be
Arguments in order to minimize the the covid-19 situation
Which I find disgraceful
Contested
Because its effect
This is such a monster get away with it
On May 8th the Milwaukee Journal Sentinel reported on the second deck that income for people infected at a local meat packing plant
This person
Condition decline so quickly
Receive Advanced treatment records show
That same day Business Insider reported at least 48 me pack
Can plant workers have died but covid-19
If you consider that as Business Insider also pointed out
Employers are not required to track coronavirus cases among workers for recent guidance
And does not require on-site inspections for worker complaints related to the virus you consider that the number of infected
And possibly related deaths could be much higher than the numbers we know
Alex's lamps on to this story out of Missouri where 373 workers at a Triumph pork plant
For covid-19
But the stories about the case
Asymptomatic
This is an interesting headline but also failed to capture a lot of the relevant information about the story
This story came out in the first week of May but it wasn't the first time this plant made headlines involved in Coronavirus
On April 24th local news report
Which is prompting them to go ahead
Test everyone
This article implies that they're going to change their strategy testing individuals
You are which would lead one to believe the previously they were only testing people who had symptoms
These original 16 cases are completely foreign to Alex he has no idea about this part of the story
Cuz he just saw a headline
Decided it must be no one sick and look no further into the case than that
Also
At least one employee if I plan to test positive for covid-19 is now dead
What Alex is saying has no connection with reality
Details he feels like in order to prop up
Is predetermined conclusion
With Noah's Espinosa a person would do that if they were interested in the truth
F****** liar
And I wish you done cast in Guardians of the Galaxy
Cuz
I don't understand
Like there's got to be
People Are People culpable
There's no lawsuits there's no nothing that we can
Can do honey
I wonder if
You know I've seen some headlines and
I see a little irresponsible thing this because I haven't looked into them but
I wonder if one day there will be statistical
Difference you will be able to find between dab
People who taken different sorts of media
Having any kind of criminal or civil liability but like
I wonder if one day we will be able to see those trends
I would be horrified
Two man
It's just there
There are people who are doing this knowing
If you can't
I can't get that thought out of my head people are knowingly choosing
To watch other people die
And they and they are in a position to do something about it
Some in fact they're in the position we're in there
Specifically choosing
Not to do something about it
Absolutely culpable tour
Some of them may think
Amount of pain caused by the
Whatever it snapped off
Yep so in this next clip Alex gets into his racist Asian voice in a while
Do a little bit of that
China says oh
Wuhan
China Taste
Bubbles
I'm going to tell you this right now
Vampires
We can get people in the government
So cowardly
If you don't have horrible food
The New World Order
Anteater
You're crazy
We got trouble food ready to ship out
Cool
So
Stration
I wish it was a Galaxy
Anniversary
So we get into the Alex comes back
From break
The big news
Is just
The
YouTube the news
Realizes that he
Can't get into it because you've got to get in the zone or something
Completely focused
I was I was busy doing some work so I can't do it
Get back in the zone
Are you back in the shower
So much
Anything to make him unprepared
Shirley
Repair Today Show
Surprise
Haha
I really hope that
Eugenicist trying to one-up each other but
They're going to they're going to carry the shop
Haha
Going to get really bad
False flag
Thank God and your lucky stars
Whatever reason our way
We're in a relationship
These guys worship
Goddamn
Cooper.
Dispelling Spade I would tell you about all this but first I got to warn my right-wing Buddies
Probably going to do some terrorism sooner or later
Back into the zone
He explains exactly
You going to do today
True is massive case
They're sterile into the vaccine
Right now
Read the headlines and tell you where they came
You should do more than
Explain to you that
This year's
Is my destination
At what year
Available there's 18
Through 4
I've kept track of how many gets through and
At the end of us
This is actually start I thought this was the first example but it's not actually
Ben
Westphal
Woman thing
All the time
The pregnancy hormone
That was the first piece of evidence that the 1985 study
Google HCG in vaccines
Sure Indian saree
Was misrepresented by the propaganda
Somebody researching into the idea of a temporary birth control vaccine
Search ocean scientist name
Call War
Continuing his work of trying to produce effective and safe birth control methods
And you changed his name to Stout I'm not sure about that
Implying
But it was about a trial for thanks temporary birth control
There's literally nothing to do with corn
National Institute of Neurology
Which kind of sounds close to the entity
The National Institute of allergy and infectious diseases
Primarily because the nation in question National Institute of Immunology
So how does
Prove the connection between towel bars
1985 study
I'm not sure
It's demonstrated
Immortal has to change his appearance every 50
Years in order to keep people from
Thinking that he is
Maybe mortal Maybe
That was the first example
Quit after 1
HCG
Learned about and is now exactly
HCG gets released from
It gets released
Wayne
Majestic
So is it making stuff up
I guess you can make something either related but that is really accurate either
According to hormone. Org
Is produced by the cells that are surrounded growing embryo which eventually forms the placenta
The ovaries itself do not actually go on to become the
Santa
It is true that the pituitary gland also produces a low levels of HCG
Would normally affect pregnancy
This is not Taiwan about
Fontspace
Just awesome as well
And I just wanted to point out that you think it comes from your balls
So
Still has not gone down to bed
On
Metrogel
Usher's understand that
Login
But I'm begging you for mice
Let me just show you headlines
E85 thing was the first
Actually started the clock yet
Okay
So Alex getting ready to go
This is going to be
I don't know how long I'm going to play with him
He's going to serve it up right back in the first one
Drumming
Cool
From many years ago
It's here now
So this was not from the NIH it's a journal article that's housed on the National Library of Medicine website
Is also at the
It was a 1993 article in the journal annals of Medicine
And it discusses his work in terms of developing control shots even the abstract of this article
Birth control vaccine he was riding up close
Has previously been demonstrated to be reversible
And it requires a booster every 8 to 9 months
Article number one has nothing to do with the point
And does not show that
Evil Globe luster products
He is over one alright
Here's serve to
Fertility vaccines
How they work
Shell.com
So this is an April 2002 review article
In the journal Trends in Immunology
Posted on sale.com
This is literally just an article
Discusses recent developments in the field of vaccines
It does nothing
Eagle
I guess if that's the argument he's trying to make sure that I don't know if it's birth control is nefarious
All of these examples start to make sense
I'm going to be honest
I think
That he is not getting into the Articles body
On purpose cuz he doesn't
But they don't really
I'm starting to put this all together he's like he's like a Fifth Element coming at at this point
Love you to the third headline
United States
CVS
Barry Democrat
You got to love
So this BBS articles specifically about the programs in the United States is mighty early 1900's that were enacted on non-white
Population through the country
As long as way to redeem code minded or mentally ill
There's also mention of recent days which is all awful
Connect to all these cases
Justice wasn't taking self-determination away from the people who are subjected to these programs
These cases are used to support
The argument that people should have access to all of the Family Planning and reproductive Health Care
They choose to use which
Should strongly be against
Based on what he believed
I suppose I guess
I guess I don't know
History in our country of this except
Global staff today
Lies on the kind of thinking basically winking and nudging you saying people do.
Couple things way in the past probably doing it
It's a way of trying to insinuate something and then pretend it's proof
Show me the humans
Americans are capable of a particular evil
They are doing it
However it's the kind of evidence
Possible
It's a lord of the BART
To the point where whatever you proven is ultimately meaningless to the actual conversation
Alex is over 3
This doesn't work for what he say
That's unfortunate
So he does make it to 4
Sweaters he got kicked out
Problem
God dammit
Do Indian history with sterilization
Sterilization
There's a lot to the picture however
None of it has to do with pudding
Sterlington vaccines
It has to do with things like paying for people to have their tubes tied
This particular
I'm Center
This is completely unrelated to the point
The trying to make
Clearly thought
Contradicting is imperative
I thought Bill Gates's posed to been thrown out of the deal because of the
Back seats for 2,000
All the stuff is internally inconsistent
They just to make whatever point he feels like
I don't mean to diminish the issue of safe reproductive health
India at all
There's definitely question
In a conversation to be had
But it has nothing to do with
About yours over 4
Unfortunately Euro 41
Size of the Gates Foundation
Boiler
It's from many years ago
Partial control immunization technical support unit
Which was formerly fully funded by The Gates Foundation
The decision is seen as part of India's broader clampdown on nongovernmental organizations
Decision making
And key policy area
Last year India ordered the dismissal of dozens of foreign funded Health experts working on public welfare schemes
Circles entrecote senior health Ministry official soumya
Swaminathan
Stressed there were no influence
And the decision was only in perception about foreign funding of program
Which is to say that
Weird
The reason for taking control of some of these
Was a concern about influenza for people over policy
But upon review there weren't any actual instances
So after this decision foundation-funded the parts of the itsuno were involved in tracking vaccinations
Coverage in managing Logistics
So this is more of a government reorganization than anything else
If Alex's story were correct in the Indian government made this
Because they found out dates with sterilizing everyone you probably expected they wouldn't
Retain The Gates Foundation of the partner on vaccinations logistic
Management
Are you supposed to been kicked out a country at this point makes no fucken sense I was over 50
We caught you with the sterilization thing
That's our
You stick around with hey we still need that we still need all kinds of other stuff but we're not going to lie to you
Provide
Tivity regulating
Immunotherapeutic vaccines reaching human trials
Just another article about talloires work on the Earth
Control shots
Also academic
Is the Oxford academic archives.com
A posting on their Archive of an article from the July 1997 issue of human reproduction update
How to no idea what he's trying to use
Pointy completely doesn't understand
This is so pathetic
This is this is really just hard
This is a real bummer when they actually try and prove their point
World Health Organization
None of this
Forget the number 7
Population Research Institute
Read All About It
Sprouts doesn't even offer a citation investigation by the population
I don't care about this Outlet run by Steven Mosher
Unless whatever is in that report is being substantiated by someone who is not the time of day
It's not even worth it
But he does
Number 8
Another one
Dial feels like he's not even trying
Control shots
Development
Reproduction World Health Organization
Switzerland
Okay
The fact that the World Health Organization as a part of it that's dedicated to reproductive and it's some other interest might involve
Control
That makes total sense
Anything specific
I can't really just prove anything here cuz there's nothing to just Brew
How to overnight
I do like that it seems like he's forgotten that we're watching
Just sitting in Titans like he's in
Stable just looking at the paper
Look at what they did today Lucky Charms
Supposed to be in Guardians of the Galaxy
Double-digit
Medical journal
What's the main one
Get the f*** out of here at all
Backlash in India surrounding Research into birth control vaccine
Confirm 1998 has nothing to do with anything other than opposition to birth
Control the shop
Alex's weaving HPV and for some reason probably just because he wants to make it sound more damning or something but
Until 2000
608 years after this Lancet article came out
Birth control in opposition to birth control
2.8 / 10
Yeah let's try again here we go
Alright you got me
Fertility vaccine options
Just now it's posted on sciencedirect.
The same Source multiple times
1989 and it's just an article in the journal vaccine
Work on birth control
We're talking about you do for 11
Impressive
This is kind of a
In a certain way
Impressed by sloppiness
You hit one right of the
Number 12
Sterilizing you
What I have no idea what I was talking about and I don't care
I don't give a s***
I can't possibly imagine
Cassidy
Bad for your balls
That's where we're at number 13, radar
Snopes
Yes
$10
Open Access Library Journal paper
Wow would you be surprised to learn that we get to 14
This Sunday
So this article claims clinical trial of tetanus vaccine
Which was announced in the journal Nature medicine
There's no link to the nature medicine article
It's the same thing about the birth control vaccine
His backbone is
The carrier the same misunderstanding misrepresentation
In this Sunday Guardian article
Stop reporting erroneous
Particularly
And that's where we at
Yeah you made it to 14
4918 is way better than
Obviously I was betting on
Never will know what those other four were
Other members of the 12 that will never know
There's layers here
What's 4 + 4 - 2 exactly
Yeah so I was unimpressed
About birth control shot
They were in development over the years
Mars research
These birth control
We keep coming up like in 97 2002
A lot of them do end up facing back to
His research
Is Alex trying to make this argument
Obelisks are putting
Sterilant in vaccine
None of this demonstrates that anyway
But of course he thinks he's proven his point
Yeah I mean if you didn't if you're just passively paying not paying attention
With him saying
Anti-fertility vaccine
You might get the
Vaccine
And that's not at all what's going on there
Could be taking a lot of different ways by people
And that's what he's thinking
Is it banking on people not paying attention being a guy
These people have got
So nuts
What's that
It appears like
We're like
Professional people are studying them like they're a different subspecies like
Just like there's cellulitis
Where are these people coming from
Unrecognizable see people
Messages from people about
People they know who
You'll fall into the u.s.
I would have a very difficult time believing
Yeah it's really is becoming like a
Something happened
Like the internet
People up to such an
Text Ed 911
Everything's nuts is weird
Who is this
It comes back and he's got a message
Trump
A message for Bill Gates
He doesn't get to the message
Search for Trump
I'm not sure what is nice
Bill Gates's other than event
Message Donald Trump
Bill Gates
President-trump
Cuz they're both very intense
Focus job dedicated
I don't want to say
Choke
You know
I need to measure my words very carefully
Because I don't say these things to be braggadocious Iraq
Powerful
That you keep
Something like that
So dangerous
Call Michael Mazda playing I get very excited
Wants me to do
Promise me very calm and focused today
I'm going to be calm and I'm going to be focused
A good boy
Let me go
Got a 300 right now
Go bankrupt
Belle Belle
Put your big sweater on you got to see this
Is telling some stuff hold on he's going to go to the he's going to go to the real quick
Is almost like
I have to cut commercial but I don't do it when I'm not on air
Stuff outside of the US
3 hours that I'm on the are pretty sweet gig only working for 3 hours
Enjoyed
Can you buy my pillow
And then we're going to get the how I hate Bill Gates
Man
Commercial 2
Feels like there's like
This is just the flat-out wild west of just one man psychosis
Just being like
There are no
Standard Universe where I'm always caring
I'm always the hero and I think that's I think that's why there's no one like you
Hard right awful folks
They generally are beholden to some sort of thing that will stop them from
Make his own podcast
Something that they need to
Do in order to make their money that I have bosses
Is the Blazing stuff but like a billionaire donors
He's not going to
Alex's
Just like
It is free it is really free
It's not a positive
He wants to f*** around and do the world's worst proof
Ever he can do that
Can't Stop
Yeah
It's crazy it was like the freedom
Will be missed but not much
No no
Soylent
What's this point
Focus 2
Doesn't want offensive viola
But
Lester to do any
Offensive
Has
Common sense
Turn it into
Not cuz people will die
Rain
Cannot be turned off
You claim your this
You're not a coward
Sterilize you and your family
All these media people are going along with it
Looking for a fight
Here's the thing
Consistent talking about how he doesn't want all senses violin
And yet
He does
All of these things
In order to make the argument
Pretty explicit
Yeah these are coming at you with these needles
Otherwise you going to kill you in a month if you don't act
Is directional encouraged
People to engage in these acts of violence
Probably
Terrorist attack
And Alex's
Defensive cuz they wanted
But he's not
Encouraging
Terror
So
Great
In service of the government murdering people
Interesting it is weird
Sing
Version of self defense is murdering people because
But then the larger government is on his
We're weird we proved vaccines.
Says as much here
In the first hour
The mainline admission
The UN
The 1980s
Inside
Current world population
Romance clear
Feels like he's done his work for the day
Also stupid
That is not good
He probably feels like himself
Just go to bed
Right now
Special Report
Number they're on the list so they know where it is
Obama did all roads lead to Winger's laptop just quit and shut
Do it
Because
Comfortable
When living under the TV
Don't want to get up here and talk about some
Yes
You think this is a damned thing it's a joke
Yes yes
The other followers
All the other BS
Real one
Okay alright Alex
Nomad
For that have my kids and I don't want to deal with the
Child
And that's what we're dealing
So Alex is on this team of
You just leave for a month
Cancer
Clear body do whatever they want
Here
With stacks of you and ports on their own website
It doesn't exist
Other people have fire
Why is the fight
Compliant
I know so many man
Watched
164 big
They like think it's at 6
Girlfriend
Dude you're being Prime for destruct
Supposed to be at
You want freedom and justice
Cheerleader
Listen to your girlfriend
You are a weak well
Coward is going to be taken over by the right right
But if I'm 5 ft
I can be
You can be out later
I don't know realtor
Perhaps
Trabajo
I know how to take care of all this and of course
Shooting people
As described
Spoiler alert warning
This is gross
Not many context
Contact
Great
H anybody
Guns
Along
Phone call
Okay I think if
Fantasies of murdering your enemies gives you sexual gratification
Application it's more like you
Bill Gates has a boner on TV or whatever
I don't know I can imagine it in fours and just go on and be like this
I've been worried for the guy
Come home.
Love your partner how is how is work today well
How to say Alex Cupid started rambling
You make any more murder
Probably
Promise to surprise that I don't think ever beti realized
San Antonio City Council
Going to get arrested for
IC rise
It was
Report where he did his character
You had a different ideas remember you said it was
You said it was like send someone down there to yell China virus
Thought you were correct
Antonio
China virus into a bullhorn
Prove
The f*** you that
Yeah it's very weird
Little bit
So if there's any way forward without
War
You believe that
Possibility
Having a
Resin
Platform without actually
Ghost
Do some kind
War over the
We're talkin about your we're going to be completely taken off everything
Definition
What about tequila
But that
More and more
In today's world violent crime victim on anyone anytime
Cut off my break
Birds of the government already
That's true but a third nipple
That's fair we're going to have to go to Ward's house
No it's
Get on Facebook
Twitter that's what matters
I am I mean
It's not good
To talk to your audience
Maybe not the most critical minded Folk
Sprite and
And your answer is no
Because when you already sort of laid out of violence of being defensive
Stopping you from a
Like sort of reasoning perspective like what's the difference
Between that and advocating
You got to do something
Do you want
You want to be starved out until the robot
What are you going to do
I messed up the message that comes forth pretty clearly
From Alex
Is there anything we could do to stop a war
Listen to your neighbors
Okay cuz there anything else we could do to stop a war you know I rest now
F***** up
Run around
The mayor
Police
Alex wants the police department's to take over overthrow mayors
The
I do like that sister
Alex and I got fired from my job as a cop
Well I guess you're the new bear those are the rules
Unacceptable
Cops
Cop should take over the mayorship
Guy and like a cop was like
Your dad
And then that creates an endless circle of different cops
Becoming mayor on a day-to-day basis
Fire
I think it's taking over
Okay well I mean essentially militarized police
Committing is bad
Technically be sort of the form of martial law
Military
Results
Right red heart
I have not heard on before
And the sound is terrible
So I apologize for that in advance
Giphy.com
Another meeting is a really active fellow
Great job
Sounded so there's something wrong with their audio
Yippee
A guy named Rich Granville
Because in the past
Recorded on the soldiers confer
Prince which was organized by
A big chew promoters
Bill
The website promoting with the Stars rearranged to make a
Accu
Conspiracy theory
Rich also described his company UPS intelligence Enterprise
You probably warned him quotes
You don't know who your f****** with
This was probably because
From the article
I don't give a f*** about the Deep State he said
If I could I would shoot them in the head
Because that's illegal
At one point during the conversation Granville abruptly asserted that his IQ is 172
Why not
Dan the people most likely to scream at you for disrespecting the flag would love to turn it in
Yep cool due to the Q profiteering weirdo
If you remember the c-pack episode that we did was trying to promote
Turn to give a speech
If I understand the situation correctly
Jpr big Flynn fundraiser
Soldiers whatever
Explain the whole lot
It explains why Mike Flynn Jr was at the Sea-Tac in that to begin with
Hang out with the guy
And now maybe they're sponsoring our to show but probably not I mean
Money even if you're a weirdo
But understand return
How do I look up eclipse of this guy being a real suck head
I think the United States
Get through this done right now
Really
Broken
So the only way we're going to get through this
Superiority that no one else can even get
They're still mad because he's so smart
Yeah that makes sense
God-ordained
Or whatever
President
Two-term limit
Or did I
2BR
That is
Translate all the way down to his family I got
Obama
All right here we go
I can't do an internal hybrid Kings
He is super against King
Dedicated
Toothless and I care so much about the Second Amendment I will just throw away the entire concert
Just have the Second Amendment and I want a cake
Yeah I mean
Even if he believed in the same person
King
F*** off my shell-like let's
You know it's 2000
I'm doing
I don't even know what that would look like
Supporter
I think he's great I prove that he's in the office I think he's doing a lot of great things
Country
I have some crazy person on and they're like Obama was sent by God and is our King I can't talk to you anymore
You are you are you
Start crying talking about how
The prayers of hundreds of years ago
They are so out
I just I just wish that we were better able to come
Are these people
Underneath so much of this s*** is that
I kind of idea of
And I say I do maintain the theory that it's because the right wing
Push the idea that Obama was a dictator
Inadvertently created a right-wing bed
Didn't
Think that dictators were bad they just wanted their own dictator
If that's if you're if you're insisting that the
Dictator it and you're one of these right-wing
Am I legit really change that much
You know I guess
I guess one way you could deal with that is be like
Or you could go the way you're describing be like
Yeah I don't know either
Conclusion consciously but maybe on some subconscious level
Thought maybe you should do some research on it
I don't know why
The combination of
Maybe something you're talkin about
Obsession to strongman leadership
Perversion of individualism
Whatever it is like this is what it comes to
And you got a guy
Here
And Alex
Sitting around talking about the goddess ordaining Trump to be our King there's nothing more
Submitting yourself
Separate yourself
And become an individual is by
So these people are
Looking sad
Alberto's saddened that they're winning
Yippee guy
Yippee ki-yay
They worship the devil
Cruise
If they're falling Luther
Then Christ must
Be real as well
Right
There's your
That is a
Very bad level
70 Stanley
If the globalist do worship the devil
That doesn't prove the devil's existence
No it doesn't
Is the Devil exist
That doesn't prove God's account
Bourbon God's existence doesn't necessarily prove
Existence
Necessarily through it
Just oh my God this level of thinking just
I'm sorry guy
I don't even care
I'm glad you were able to run a search engine check it out
Bring it to the table
God-ordained
King and because the globalist worship the devil that prove God's real
I got nothing for you and I got to go
Create some sort of stronger
Way to deal with these people because right now it seems like all we're doing is just going
Again
She funded them on Twitter and doing all that s*** and there's
So many opinion pieces written in LA
There needs to be some sort of United
It can't be we can't allow them
Threatened everybody with violence while we mock them on Twitter
Yeah I don't know that
Anything that you can do would really be effective
Unless we first deal with
A shared reality
Like there's no real way to deal with anything
While realities are so distinct from each other that
Alex can do that reading 14 headlines instead of 18 is brahmas
I'm thinking very proves the point
Nothing I could do nothing nothing conversation
Could possibly
Make a difference
That was different reality until those reality
We come to a
Sentence of what is and what isn't real
What parts of things that I don't believe are real but you might acceptable for us to disagree
Like let's say I'm an atheist in your someone who believes
In Christianity perfectly acceptable for me to not believe in the reality of something
Can you believe is real
And Ice Cube
Be okay with that and move along in our lives
Bashar reality doesn't have to extend to everything
Arterra place right now where everyone shares the same
The issues that you're bringing up I don't think he'll be dealt with until we do occasionally
Critical thinking skills any of those are important
Any good helpful
Hopefully if you were to
Tackle some of those problems and work on them to an extent
I think maybe it would help
In making people understand shared reality
But until until that's more dressed I just don't know what you can do
A now there'll be some people who cares whatever he does eat grapes
That's really sad
Sad but
Jordan the end of the day
We can all take pleasure in knowing that Alex is almost
Star-Lord
Emotionally vulnerable as well
Actor is the way he's able to tap into all of those feelings
The capacity for growth is really clear an hour
Another one
Abruptly tomorrow and go away for a month and never come back or whatever
That moment you realize you was talking about
Because I was going through
2001 A Space Odyssey
He's like Kurt Russell
That is not real that is unreal it's amazing thank you
In advance
For my next Friday next episode does my brights by
Where's the back door
On Monday but until then B website Twitter
In theater like on the juggles actors real living real patreon if you would like a please donate to a local charity
In your area we would a
You are correct
Headline 15 through 18
Alex
Dim color
I love your work