Jordan
I have great respect for its knowledge by knowledge
Knowledge fight
MoneyGram
Knowledge vype.com
Joan Jordan Jordan
Today well interesting Lee I found a copy of the
Assassin's Creed games
Nintendo guide pretty much most of my life
I never had the capability to play a lot of the early ones that weren't on Nintendo system
Like a Wii U
The Black Flag
That came out on
Nintendo systems I got recorded copy of the SEO
Assassin's Creed 2 and then to other one
Brotherhood
Stand
-1
I'm Blown Away
How good
Given given how old is he
Yeah yeah I remember watching my roommate Swearingen
And I'm not sure it was a do at that point
Really reasonably priced game in a series that I like but I wasn't sure I'm going to enjoy
And it turns out
It's just super fun
And you can run around in this Italian city
Blown away because the only reason that I played any of the other assassins
Creed games
American
All I care about
Credible what about you what are you with a lot of pent-up frustration
I recently because the world
Your bright spot is
But I got to get all of it out
A very public Hobby
Frustration
Private conversation
A couple days ago Jordan literally said
Iran Twitter
Just regular
Maybe I'm over yesterday you forgot about your burning hatred for the man
Cell phone
Yeah
We need to get rid of Wacky Wednesday but not in the way you think
Alliteration of it and that's why we have that name
Focusing on the present
As much as we are now
I'm focusing on the present
Protracted situation going on
That he's lying about all sorts of stuff
That is relevant
Breakdown and constantly talk about
Mike.
Kind of
I'm going to go to the Special Report I might be back
I realize that has my workflow in the way things go it doesn't make sense to have a Wednesday episode
It's dedicated to something
Kind of just like
Long stretches where we don't have anything other than Alex
Should be I don't think
I think mostly Alex Jones absolutely
Almost all Alex Jones
Sure
But if you go back to 3 episodes
Kind of wood bees
In everyone's best interest to probably try to do something else
I just don't think Wednesday work
Very well for that
Monday works much better
And here's why
When we do our episodes
The come out on Friday we can have up to Thursday covered
From Alex to cover on Monday
L in Alert in a situation much better serve
Do something
Wednesday and Friday Alex
So I generally do that
Episode
Wake up
So
And this will be the beginning of something that might take a little while
Okay
Darnell thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Joseph
My Rhonda
Wendy
Thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Ewok
Donated on elevator
Thank you so much
Money off that heroin
So good
Is freakishly large
If you would like to
Charity Terraria that's
Spoke to Ernie we would appreciate
So like I said today
We are going to do
And I almost everything blow up in my face and be able to do this
I think we've maybe given to Rosie as you of Bill Cooper
In the past Alex
In Jackson
Position with this guy who you looked up with
Because it's like hey Alex
Compared with material and who this guy
Little bit
I felt like there was stuff that was more fun
Hilarious
Absolutely that is a lot of fun
Tech support
Hilarious
Very good yes very good but ultimately that is not a fair picture of Bill Cooper
So I felt Lake
One of the things
Is get into the Oklahoma City bombing
And Bill Cooper's coverage of it
We are going to embark on a journey
I'm going over Bill Cooper
And how
Conspiracy theories about the Oklahoma City bombing developed
Over the course of it
Today we're going to be listening to the hour of the time from April 19th
April 20th
First
And that we will see
How things went Patriot militia
And I wanted to you know make sure that we try
Respectful as possible
This was a gigantic tragedy
Good so many people's lives
And you know
168 people lost their lives and
Are you just sort of
Umbrella that out to family and friends coworkers
The number of people who are traumatized
By the events of April 19th
AR
Jokes about
Disrespected people
And all that
So that's
My boilerplate
Little bit
Dirigo where to start on the 19th
Broadcast on April 19th
His show is the evening
I'll get the night shift
So he's had plenty of time to gather his thoughts
About the bombing ad
Here's what are you doing
You're listening to be our
William Cooper
Today is the
Second anniversary
Call the Waco
I don't want anyone out there too
Forget it
Ever
A Thousand Years
For now I want to take you somewhere
Patriots
Ideals of Liberty and freedom
To remember
Unfortunately
Appears that someone is using
Anniversary
To promote
An agenda
We will be
Pepper right now there's a vote coming up on the conference of states and Men
Minnesota
That's the big news
Important
Perfect
Charcoal steak
Resolution has
Her
Animal slaughterhouse
Independence
April 9th
Mention the bombing
Have you completely sideline it to talk about something else entirely
With an agenda and it's
If my agenda it has the same agenda that I do
Here we have Bill warning in Minnesota about a conference of states
This is absolutely not a situation where it's a vote of the public
What essential problem is it doesn't ever give a bill number or name on this
When you just Google Minnesota and Conference Estates
Which basically men
Then I got to go to the Minnesota State Legislature
In Minnesota 1995
3265 total
And thanks to this exercise I learned some interesting things
That is an instance of me lying
This was not fun or interesting as passive exploration
Because you know what
All these legislative bodies do is allocate funds for projects
Fixing roads
And slightly just about rules regarding things like building code
In 1995 it seemed like it was a fair amount of bridge naming related business in the Minnesota Legislature
Lisa couple Bridges
One of them was about to have former
State Legislature person who the bridge is named after her
Shots, cross
Which is about the right
That is
The ditches
That part isn't interesting
But what it is
Is it had to do with a town called embarrassed
Alright
And they're proud of it God dammit
Consequences New Mexico
Embarrassed
Minnesota house or Senate in 1995
What bill is talking about is the idea of States calling for a constitutional convention
Constitution
A Convention of states to ratify three-fourths of the states
This has never been done in the history of the country and no one really knows how it would play out Estates were to actually go down this road
Beer and rallying cry for folks on the extreme right four years depending on
You know what point they want to try and make
Super worried about the Liberals adding things to the Constitution
2000 time frame
How to be strongly pushing for these sorts of things as a way to
For the states to fight back against Barack Obama
Three-quarters of the states agreeing on f****** anything honorable man
They wouldn't even agree on abolishes slavery in 2020
It seems like it would become a political football
So the people can change or affect the Constitution are
Preoccupation of people with constitutionalist
Understand where this drive comes from
According to article
State legislators this process
Resolution
In 1995 only three resolutions passed the Minnesota house
Or Senate
166 production
Another hs9 57 without the sale of the administration of power
Our services for the Western area of the state
HF 821
What about the funding for Amtrak
Interesting we've there was a big piece scaremongering
Legislators
In the April 1990 Schlafly report
Gray gray gray
What's going on
Alstyle Gathering of representatives from State legislatures
Call the conference of State
Which was twisted by conspiracy theorist into
Being a plan to Stage the Constitutional Convention
Is wasn't really strictly speaking true but folks like Schlafly and Bill Cooper were able to
The convention of people this is part of
Letter-writing campaigns are gone
Abandoned
We just wanted to get
Together at Schlafly Zone the f****** case that lady is crazy.
So the plan was absolutely right
Paradoxically was torpedoed in
Michael Levitt governor of Utah
The plan looks back on
Time
In the 1994 midterms
Control of all of Congress
A majority of State governorship many state legislators
After that
Any more government in Republican
They could try that approach
Literally said himself
Legislative agenda unfolds
The conference of states
Could see momentum had shifted
In a direction we approve.
Different anticipated
We recalibrated the conference of state's effort into a far less grandvision
And focus our energies on legislative proposals which returned
Control of the nation's welfare system
And Medicaid do state
Control
April 1995 Bill Cooper is fighting against a version of an idea
In any meaningful way
The people who are pushing for it as a last resort against Bill Clinton
So this move wasn't really important to them anymore
I can find no solid evidence that a resolution like
Just passed the Minnesota house in 1990s
But even if it was already
It was only really being kept Alive by conspiracy theorist
Of the destruction of the Constitution
Sure power in the federal government
110th Congress beginning 1007
Weird have a tea party popped up just a little bit
Power they try and subvert democracy and when they get power they try and
Democracy
I will likely use sweeping Groundswell Zozo
Playground
Spell
He's in Texas Minnesota people are doing
Alluka crisping
He spends the first like six minutes of the show
It's like hey we have big issues here man if you don't want to deal with what's going on
Want to deal with that
Which is
So weird
Forever one else
Stop which course is Obama
Morning
Just after
Most of the
Workers
Have entered the
Federal office
Building
Call the city
For their daily
Routine
Explosion
Occur
Respectful
No one was
For this lady
Gentleman
All those inside the building
Found himself presently
Calling tumbling
For the year
Them
Or buried
Tongue
Debris
As usual
Intelligence service
Available
Time
Are you opine repack have not been read
Reported in there
Entirety
Anywhere else
In the world in
Including the major media in the United States
The meteor
In Oklahoma City
So you can see here this anti-media tendency
It doesn't know that the waybill is expressing these things
Just that he's intelligence-gathering team is far more competent story
Universal among people like Bill or Alex Jones
It's keeping them to invalidate all other sources of information on themselves
Particularly potentially contradict their version of reality
Your listeners who send you messages teligent service
Stranger sending unit
Yesi this is
That's a little
Hoover's
And you got to separate those from the truth
You know we have our people on scene
Press passes in hand
And they have
Report
Email
Relay
If you listen carefully ladies gentleman because rumors are always about
We have heard every rumor in every possible solution
Come to this
What you were going to get now
So there's rumors
But this is not rumor
Yeah
Rumors lighter
Rumors
Who knows
Email with something
There's one thing the bill takes particular issue actually complains about on the 20th
21st
Recording of death tools
He seems to like really be staking a claim on this here was like this is the proof
All the media lying or something okay
Very good I don't think
Responsible
Will news reports
DC
Completely
Bass
And out of line
Are you mad
Beck the body count
Keep going up
Bar
As actual on the scenes recording goes
4:30
P.m. this afternoon
Oklahoma time
Only 22
Confirmed are
17 of them children
From the daycare.
Washington web reporting 81g
But no one on the
Can confirm
Even approach
That number
I think the Bills playing understand
The point is
Exaggerating
Basically I think it might be more like
It's not that big a deal
People were maliciously lying about stuff
Maybe that would be bad but estimated
Possibly inaccurate in the at mediate aftermath of a giant
No he can really call someone
Call people
I'm going to call that
Worst
A mistake
Based on trying to report to
Mass casualty estimates ago roundabout
Which almost always end up being higher than the eventual concrete number
People throwing around numbers in the tens of thousands
About 911 on that day possible
This pollen
If you want to take preliminary estimates
The bombing of the Murrah building resulted in 168 deaths from what
ABC News
Actually High
Doesn't say we're his number of 22 dad comes from a based on how is reporting generally goes
Probably just something one of his listeners told in which event
Call intelligence service
An article from April 19th United Press International
An undetermined number of people
Dozens perhaps hundreds of people died in the blast
The governor's office put the
Confirm death toll at 26 late Wednesday
But the number was expected to rise as Rescuers searched the wreckage
It seemed article cozy then Governor Frank Keating saying that you'd heard as many as 40 people were dead
Confirm
They also quote a doctor at one of the
The triage centers
Who told you
They found 80 people but only two were alive so they told us to go home
Could not be confirmed
Who's caviar
I don't know what precise reporting
It is the bill Cooper's not about in terms of death estimate
But it seems entirely likely to me that when he says Washington was reporting 81 dead
It has been media reports
Like things
Yeah
Your way this feels like a cheap way from to play games that's around the idea that he's more careful than other media
And that's more trustworthy
We just kind of dishonest
Anyone reporting on this story as it unfolded on April 19th but obviously know that it'll be impossible to have a concrete number fatality
Quite a while
Leaving bills 22 number of confirmed deaths contradicts the upei recording of 26
When bill says 4:30 p.m. that makes me think he's talking about is a press conference that Bill Clinton
Reno held the brief reporters
On the status of
Because that was the time that they had that pressure
Andy's mention Washington in Washington
In this conference
Then Reno gets up and discusses the police response investigation
So discussion of suspects are methods of the attacker off-limits
Every no is taking questions this Exchange
Funny statistic
We have
The casualties
But they are increasing every
What we are trying to
Chores
If we pursue ever
Elead
What we have been told is that
Assign in the building
Only 200
50 had been accounted
Four before i k
There may be as many as
Is 100 to 200
More people
To account for
The casualties
He said yours are
100 victim
Six children
It works over in the daytime
Eyecare center
Have been confirmed as
Is Dad
And
We are just
Pursuing Absol
Play Every Lie
That was a statement from Washington at 4:30 p.m. on April 19th
Gennarino didn't say that 81 people were dead there's just an acknowledgment that the number is going up there
Image recognition
With the work of tracking down all the folks who could have been in the building adopting completed yet
Little credibility or Credence to our bill is reporting based on contemporary public reports
It really feels like he's creating a straw bad a bad recording
Compare himself to in order to
Self look like
Reporting reporting is willingness to say we don't know yet and that is
The right-wing propaganda
Whatever it is that they say is going to be
More than likely
Is reportaj close
Immediately
After
The shopping mall at Northwest
50th and
Evacuated
Houses a smaller office of
The Federal Bureau of Investigation
No mention was made of funeral
The areas in Moana
17 MI
Call Steve Oklahoma City
What
The office of the FBI which is
Located about four blocks
Door
Of one of our
Office
Information intersection of Northwest
Pennsylvania Avenue in Oklahoma City
What is the Penn Square Mall which is a mall like you might conceive of a shopping
It's indoors and it's home to stores like JCPenney at Dillard's
The other is a big office complex called
50 Penn place right across the street
In the aftermath of the bombing both because there are some FBI offices on the top
A couple floors
50 Penn place the office building
Shopping mall
This was done as a precaution
But the same person making that argument
Almost sounds like there's a shopping mall Orange Julius next
SPI substation
That's not the
Delicious
Norman
Terrorist attack
Be cautious
I can't find any confirmation that the FBI satellite office in Norman was
Evacuated or closed
I would guess that it was it was
Gigantic terrorist attack
Conspiracy Norman is like
25 minute drive away from Oklahoma City
Is your offer operating off an assumption that the target might
Someone attacking Federal authorities
You'd be putting lives at risk unnecessarily if you didn't
Cover your bases
I don't see anything weird about the things bill is pointing to as weird so far
And honestly this section of the show revealed something to me
I've already touched on a little bit
No one bill is reporting this stuff about there being a closure and Normandy said you're one of his intelligence
Already put
X
Or like a newspaper article
He's actually reading an email from one of his listeners
You speak some authoritative voice because he believes that every was in one of his listeners taoism is Intel
As opposed to just being possibly inaccurate gossip
Something that makes bills
Harder to decipher
For me
When I'm listening to make a claim it sounds absurd should come from
Possibly
Operate
Mostly because Bill doesn't differentiate concrete reporting from listener emails
Explicitly
Which introduces confusion
When UPI reported on the triage doctors claimed that there were 78 people
You know it's hasn't been
Confirm to the reader is the ability perspective
That have been interviewed
The same time understanding that this Pacific
Word verified
And should not be taken as such
Media Outlet operate in such a decision
Important aspects
About you know
Wow solid some information
I suspect the bill doesn't call out
Mostly listen our emails
Those are kind of exposed his journalistic Endeavor is more theater than journalism
It's Boris
To imagine that he has
Observe only four blocks away from the FBI office
Who is somebody always watching me
Now it's just some guy
Certainly
Get some more reports from Weird Al listeners
Tinker Air Force Base was put on emergency alert on for several hours
No one was admitted on her off the base
Later in the day make Personnel were allowed on the base
But everyone is
Kettering was subjected to a total identity
Check in
Worker
So what
I'm struggling here
Some people from Tinker Air Force Base assisted in search-and-rescue in the aftermath of the bombing
Fighter jet Pilots or Chabert
And one of the most important things on Fire Department
Security aftermath
Paris attack nothing suspicious I don't understand
Transportation is on the road
Complains that like females getting involved in the National Guard
The National Guard can be activated by the governor
Declaration of emergency
Being treated as an emergency prior to him
Articulating it
All of the agencies specifically to respond
902 ama9
Management was fully activated
Triggering of certain thing
You can call in FEMA and start coordinating with the federal assistance response
None of that stuff is suspicious at all it's exactly what you would think
It's very it's a job
Car is today Force Base
Substation in Norman
Might have been evacuated
Girls South and Walker from Northwest 23rd Street train
Closer
But was turned
Certified by Garden Grove block
She tried
Entering the area of several
Possible back road
Route
But there were simply
Too many police National Guard highway patrol sheriff
Japanese
To get anywhere near the
Express Pass
And credentials
And veritas
Alleyway in gravel
You tried to access
Was only Garden
Yield
The parameter
Polyp
Good
To get on the thing
Our people
Would have
Empire
Enteral
That person comes out again
We can talk
Gypsy reports
Or there's no coming
Taken out of the area
Let you
Access
To the emergency communications equipped
Pickles on
The Bell has actually possesses
I don't know what the standards are forgetting Universal press passes but it seems like
Shortwave radio
And the hosts zine
Might not make the cut
Seems like I don't know about that
Couldn't get into restricted areas
There's no need for bloggers assistance
Do we getting in the way alright I can see where you're coming
Aerial shots of the building
Continuous
It totally makes sense that the police and other groups are making a predator
Would do whatever they could to make sure there were just
Hundreds of reporters
Credibility wandering around
That's probably bad whenever you're investigating something
We just have to spend a minimum
Obviously cellphones were to the level that they are today back in 1995 there were cell phone
This person who probably would be able to call Bill at any point
Are there wasn't just like normal lack of signal problem
People trying to make calls in the Bay Area
Jamming signals
Capabilities
Particularly for the area of downtown Oklahoma City
The problem of not getting a signal
And this work was completed by 2:15 p.m.
The overloading that was going on at the time between 2 and 11 a.m.
Southwestern Bell recorded over
12 million calls
Attempted in the city
Damn I'm sure there were some bands of frequency that were dedicated to emergency responders but that it really has no bearing
Turn on whether or not a guy Bill knows
Snuck into the Murrah building site would be able to call Bill
And then tell him what he saw
That story does not make sense
Minecraft more conspiracy into the story than a straight-up reporter might
Person got in there
Sorry I would like
Cross-country trip Wuzzy was it snowing at the time was a skiing all the way over there or snows and glasses
Always about moving
Sowega
Only medical people
Get through
The only other people being allowed through the roadblock for medical
Personnel
Quiet
Michael card no one else is being allowed into the area regardless of
The only other people are medical books
Are people who work for like utility companies like to shut off gas for the surrounding area in order
Explosion
All members of the local fans who were not on the scene within the first hour have been allowed in
The rumor spread
Birth of a son
Anthony third comfortable bra
The groomers
Or not
True
How do you know everyone in the downtown area who did not have any medical fire or police
When was move back away
Federal Building
Area
Play Justin
Barb block
Reason for non-essential people to be allowed anywhere near that belt
It might be too much possibly to say absolutely no pressure
Circumstances that were going on where people were trapped in the rubble and search-and-rescue triage work was going onto the
It makes complete sense to really only letting a few members of the media
Please allow me in
Beat It
More than just medical personnel were allowed in
Like the letter good reasons bees hair
Bill's listener tried to get Emma guard wouldn't let them
The guard said something like the medical card you not getting
Richard translated to report medical cards are allowed in
Either way I really do appreciate the bills on the side of thing that's bomb scares that happened after the initial explosion were not real
I'm sure you can have a terrible take on this
But at least directly more Bob
Switches
Oklahoma City
Conspiracy theorist
At 10:28 a.m. there's a rumor of a possible explosive in the building and everyone fell.
Obviously even if you think the odds are unlikely when there's a possibility of another bomb
The all-clear went out at 11:22 a.m.
At 1:30 p.m. Searchers found a suspicious crate
The building was once again evacuated
At 1:48 p.m.
The bomb squad showed up in determined
Explosives of the all-clear quicker this time in rescue efforts were back on track by 2:02 p.m.
It's just tragic and terrible two valuable time was lost in these rescue efforts but
Is almost unimaginable
If you have time the first
Responders of rescue teams of the building
Trying to help people then a second bomb goes off
The physical and psychological
Stagger
If I understand
Which she doesn't release Pow Wow but it definitely seems like there's a
Fake
I think they were faking the sunset there were actual bomb
The teams on the site didn't know whether they were real bombs or not operate under the assumption that they might be
You seem to believe
Set the bomb scares are fake in the sense that they were made up by the officials as a pretext
The former perimeter five blocks away from
Explicitly say that but it's a strong impression that I get when I was listening to
Yeah the weight on Uconnect
Certain ideas to each other makes you makes you look behind and you're like I don't think you are disagreeing with me the way that I
Remember
Get in ya
It seems to be from the tracking of thoughts
Baby it's related
I can't say what he says
Explicitly
A possible second bomb they're just like
Now my gut says this guy can only make one bomb let's just keep on going ignore that s***
Yeah
Show me there were some reports
Suspect tour of Middle Eastern heritage
9 a.m.
Kohl's credit
Bridge accident
Earlier reports
We're made of three possible suspects
Honey Boo Boo
Tinted windows
2 of Middle Eastern appearance
Gmail
Noticed
Who supposedly was driving
Nothing was said about why they were tough
My question is
DeSoto are agents on the scene
For there is a large population
Middle Eastern Muslims
In Oklahoma City
Edmond
Aaron's Norman
On the University of Oklahoma has several large
Islamic student
Community group
Unless the three men actually
Jordan something
I should have been nothing out of the ordinary about that present
Mini crotch individuals live and work in the
Especially in that part of downtown Oklahoma City
Houses so many off
Officer
Or Middle Eastern
Businesses
My name
Considering he's just throwing pictures up
Left and right true
Through
This episode you won't have a closet
Review of bells
Recognize
Explicit the fact that
Critique of why
First thing
But he doesn't do anything there should be no reason why they be considered halfway there
A someone in the world that bill is in and the Wii cover
Kind
Amazing
Play sitting in a certain way
Is it like not putting that second step together is like
But now that's stupid
There's a certain part of like it this is
This is bad investigation on your choir
Criticism
Maybe maybe not
I think you're assuming the motivation I'm not positive what it is
Oh you're saying I don't know
Giving me a very like
F*** is your deal vibe
We're going to find out a little bit about it
Builder
Okay good
He's just
Is a terrible job
This report from one of his intelligence
Sources to
Respond I got some rumors
Liquor going around
A rumor
Erroneous reports
And Jeffers
Speculations
They have been broadcast
Around the world
Today
These are some of the rumors
Speculations
I found it incredibly complex
Confusing at first because he's just done this far away is like the Base Air Force Base has heightened
Insecurities
Is he talking about those rumors
To say the rumors
I have to go back and listen to it a couple times
Are you saying
We reported before the Air Force Base
This is a substation is not rumor
To talk about it
Remember these are rumors
Calculator
A local television station in Oklahoma City received a call from
Unidentified
Mail
Reportedly speaking
Who stated
Definition of Islam
Queen responsibility
For the bounty
I kind of wonder how much utility there isn't coming on a conspiracy paranoia theme broadcast industry
Heating random rumors about the Bahamas
Irresponsible
I just don't know what
Also housed Silly's
That caller
But he's willing to accept
His collars
Bulshit instantaneous
There's a couple of times or
Is reporting that this local station did receive this call of Islam
Nothing precise with his own reporting
This station in Oklahoma with KFOR and another anchor
It could be a prank call
They were not even reporting this is anything real themselves
For saying that on air
Even if even if he pointed out that it might be a crank call go f*** yourself bring anything to anybody
That's some pretty responsible stuff it's bills only point
Bring up sloppy work
I'll probably be on the very similar pages
Even this discussion of the
Report on KFOR
Isn't even downright crazy making the same mistake
From shortwave conspiracy theory
Hey I got to call the desire to refinance my mortgage and also
They're also other people repeating this
Another broadcast date
McCurdy former democratic
Congressman
Promptly
Pokemon television
Same
Cynthia
Rumor
Dave McCurdy was a former Oklahoma congressman
Not to the Nation of Islam
Ubi reported on his comments
My first reaction was there could be a very real connection to some of the fundamentalist groups operate
Eating around the city
The former, Congressman said
He said a number of Muslim fundamentalist group some with links to Hamas it recently held a convention in the area
Begin Angie is not good at detail work
Not their Forte
Start to wonder if he does anything
You could just go get
The quote yourself
True know it's there
Yeah by the time he's doing this broadcast
He could just go look at that cut it out of the show
Difficult
Today
Yeah still do it
Well I mean
Here's another little bit of a rumor
Going around
Another report
Firefighter
Going through the rubble of the Federal Building
Discovered other
Explosive device
And plastic
Which have been allegedly
In the offices
Of the
Located in
The Federal Building
Alcohol Tobacco and Firearms
That particular
I like all of the others
Heard today
Was never
Reported
Again
We've also not heard it making
Further on the skin
True rumor
Or if it was true
Was quickly
The context of his list of rumors
And the last year explicitly debunking them and you make that very clear
It's unhealthy to shrugging Lee report rumors that entertain the possibility that maybe they're true
What do you operate like this the only real outcome that comes of it is the Dumber elements of an audience ignore the part where you say
The rumor is true
Anyone listening is probably already heard these rumors somewhere already so what's the value and repeating them
Just lazy as hell and it doesn't bring anything to the table
Can just be like
I'm pretty sure I remembered something about the 80s Haydn's
The rumor
Datapoint now or whatever they call it to find an explosive Parts in the rubble did not disappear
Where is Bella's
For quite a while
In September 1995 they released a statement saying that they were quote absolutely no explosives in their office
Could be mistaken
Explode
According to a 1996 article in the Washington
Supposed sighting
These items were not explosive
Design for training purposes but never complained
Explosive material
He said these types of items are used as exploitative prop
In court
And then you rip both sleeves off and he's like
In Timothy mcveigh's trial
Chief of the Oklahoma City Fire Department
A desk ornament from an ATF agent that was knocked into the stairwell
The Death Clock
Typical type of a bomb
Eddie was in the stairwell and people were really nervous at the time
That were mistaken for possible bombs and then reported by media Outlets that were
Get out any possible news
When you hear things like in the police scanner the report of a possible second device found
Know what all the details are and get the wrong impression
Here's the thing
Bill Cooper repeating a rumor about the ATF is not just a guy repeating a rumor for the sake of bringing erroneous
The audience's awareness history with the ATF
Set a repeating of a rumor about them having bombs in their office
I refuse to believe that bill wouldn't be aware of that
But he can pretend he's just discussing rumors but that's
Bulshit yeah
There's a rumor going around the entire world
Pizzas around
Saying that they're doing it
But if you don't hear about again this cuz they f***
So why one more little piece of rubber here before I start
Pay bill
They later
Where you at
Report
Mission of Iraq
Launcher being found in the debris
Which was supposed to have
Also been
And the Bureau of Alcohol Tobacco and Firearms office
Report also
Has never been
Repeat it
Substantiated
Or
Gemini
Bentonite
Actually true
Actually find a rocket launcher in the wreckage of the
The building there's even a picture of it in the final action report about the bombing
It sounds completely outlandish Serbia rocket launcher in the debris of a building but it's important to remember there are multiple different law enforcement
Secret Service
Some of the stuff that would end up being normal pile of debris
Explain be normal reaction of birth
He doesn't offer any explanation for why this find might not be as weird as it sounds
You just repeated as gossip that may be true and is being covered up maybe
Or maybe it's just that Intel
It was true
Weird
It was reported in the AP the next day April 20th
Yeah
Care
So this is where it
The day of
What do you expect
This is where I was
Yelp
Do you like Gentleman by
Pregnant
If you want
Your ass up
Against what
Broadcast for long
You know
Many of you have already
Repair
Prediction apps
Prediction
True I don't
Schedule not because I'm psycho
Subway
Because God talks
Oh my God
Because I look into a crib
Football
Not because I'm in contact
Retractable being
Archana leaf
Ascended masters
Because I
Study
The last 25 years
Listening to act like you can almost see Alex the Bill Cooper impression
Know what the globalist magic powers because
This is Alex's
Down to the paranoia field sales paper
4 Gold
He brings up his gold sponsor and then starts
Already paranoid
It doesn't even further into a deep paranoia about how it's going down
Incidents of terrorism
The power of
The police state
Will
Chronicles
Freedom
Liberty
Will disappear
All Nations and all people will be different
There are Russian
Adrian
In this country now
Supervising sure
States of America
And we have
People in Russia
Supervising
Supposedly
So Russian agents are disarming us and we're determined Russia or whatever there's you know terrorism going to ask
Exponentially
It's bad news
Yeah but it gets worse this is going to affect you on the local level 2
A moment
Chaos
Develop
Local
Anarchy
It will disappear
From the supermarket
The economy
Color
Those who have not
Prepared
Are going to find themselves
Whoa
Minnesota as well by Barris
But they are real
Screw warnings Macomb from my heart
From a position
Not racist
Wiring for America
So you're going to be
Those who will not take charge either with the New World Order
Country
Will be the place over and
The tides of War
Will be at the mercy
Observative
I got to pause right there has really quick
I would assume
Should the Patriots win
You shouldn't say that we're going to enslave
That might be a little bit
Can we picnic
Well you're going to be
One-goal
Are silver coin
Really
No one during that. Of time was
Paper money
Why
You are have something useful
Are real money
I need on a black market
You will be home
You will be hungry
And you will be without shelter
Bastille your house
I suggest you call 1 800 tricks
Gould's
Masquerading as coverage of Oklahoma City bombing
Make no mistake
This is from the night of the bombing
He's on here saying they'll be escalating terrorism local Anarchy shortages in a financial collapse
If you and your family don't have gold or silver to barter with your f***
This is as manipulative as pretty much anything I've ever heard from Alex and the sales pitches
Different category
That's something like that
Clearly
He's willing to let it sensationalism run wild in a time when his audiences
Particularly confused and scared
Trying to sell them gold
We're just going to save them
Gold sales operations
Disclosure
In a context like this
What are you doing is abusive sale practice
Every other movie you have
Becomes very suspicious
Sing Sing is as Alex BMX
Will save your like this he's literally saying that gold will save your life
Could save your life
Unless you have at least one piece of gold
And
So kidnap a leprechaun
I'm not I'm not like fully convinced
That he doesn't also really loved gold
Right
But
When you're in the middle of a plug for your gold sponsors
Clearly Financial
And I
I just can't I can't allow it
Yeah that's almost the FDA should send a letter gold can save your life
Full on doctor's note
Yeah
Talking about how about every prediction event
The trial is Manuel Noriega
Every other one
You can't because
He thought that Manuel Noriega would have sovereign immunity and so the us could
Contrived
Or something doesn't usually go into other countries and talk about that be
Crazy
For under international law
Community
Sotalol
You're going to see that
If you're also
Sovereignty of Nations is no more including the proper
States of America
Sure
Military forces
The Army-Navy
Dark Horse
And Marine
Functioning as the police force
Of the United Nations
Publication
The bill was in the middle of prediction
The norriego on
Which is better give credibility prediction of stuff that's coming which was only in order to
He starts they're saying the people who other than
Yeah maybe
Shepherd
It was wrong
Also that's a document 7277 as a favorite of Alex's claims
United States
We talked about
Bedtime the past purchases a reminder
It was a plan that was per
Proposed but never enacted in any way
It was released in 1960 wondering. Of severe tension between the United States and the Soviet Union
Nuclear war any day
Announce plans for
Peaceful the escalation were sometimes
Can conception
Mikaso 7277
The first stage of a proposed plan involves Limited
States and Soviet Armed Forces to 2.1 million persons
Which definitely
We're a little bit over there Benchmark but Russia's Army is currently in about 3.5 million
So clearly that stage has not been met
It's a plan that the Opium but it was proposed by us
I've never been enacted and was product
Cold War desperation
It's basically just lived on as a boogeyman of the hard-right folks of the Minuteman and the John Birch Society
The globalist want to take their guns when it wasn't even about you
Yeah that's great
That's great
Network guys
That's another little direct parallel of a document
The bill and Alex both use
Beginning of the show
You know within a minute
It's starting
False flag
Becomes Morris
With it as we go along
Holiday Inn Oklahoma City
The part of the agenda
Bring about
The New World Order
You watching
Story
Continue to
It is no accident
Record on the 2nd anniversary
The Waco Massacre
Correct
Completely falls apart or at least it should for anyone is paying attention
Early are you complaining
But now before is over
Which is in no way proven
It was comfortable deciding on the entire Narrative of the overarching Troost of the event
With no proof at all
Someone prove exactly how many people responsible
Very serious disconnect here and it's a problem
Already decided
You know that's going to affect information about it
Is a predetermined conclusion already and he's publicly declared where he's planting his flag
Do you think he's going to go out of his way to debunk
He's already committed to based on years of supposed research
This is a massive problem for me
Will present himself as a guy who insist you do your research
Music I was cool just collars for repeating things they just heard somewhere
He's the guy who complains about rumors
And yet here he is decided with zero proof
Bombing was done to advance the New World Order
Just a really sad betrayal of what's supposed to be his brand
Gold sales thing you really start to see a different picture of Bill
He's kind of the same piece of s*** that all these guys are he's just a little bit more serious about himself
You know it is what it is
Is clearly about Waco
Like it
It's very clear anybody else
I don't know what you're talkin about
That is true
About that
Investigating the Murrah building bombing
Iznogoud
5:30
P.m.
Power washing
Begin our meeting with
The governor in the governor's mansion
Supposedly to get coordinated
Investigators
Barney
Winco Reno
And the governor has a mouth
The entire investigation
Is now in the hands of
The Federal Bureau of
Investigation
Could we hear on anyone
Live rumahan
Federal Bureau of Investigation
Four burner
But a few more since then
Texas BBQ
That's the selection problem
Definitely
A big part of how he's interpreting
Events before he has any reason to think those
And that's pretty essential to understand
Really
Sloppy as hell
It's really embarrassing
When you start to look at some of the things
But he's taking the time to make a point of like this
Oklahoma crime in Carlisle
Scanner report
Discovered at 3
Medallion Hotel
Request was made for a bomb dog
Chicken to the hotel
Perks of a phone directory
Shows that there is
No.
Hotel listed
Any Oklahoma City phone book
We will
Of course not
Whether or not bill or his listeners were able to find The Medallion hotel in the phone book
There is a medallion hotel in Oklahoma City
An article in the Oklahoma from October 29th 1996
For real
Shutdown
Because they were in the middle of an 8 million-dollar renovation project
I was even able to find a February 1995 article about the beginning of the renovation
Project like a hotel exist
There's a New York daily news story from May 7th
Because they lost his reservations but he was there covering the bombing
The petty image of that aside this article also a major way
An offer room
2 people were injured in the bombing as well as rescue workers who really needed a place
Good for you medallion
In 1998 The Medallion was bought by
Star in Oklahoma City
Anyway the point here is Villas reporting the news if it's a
They heard on the scanner that a bomb-sniffing dog was sent to The Medallion but they can't find it
In this is worth bringing up the show
All this proves is that his investigative team
Find a hotel
The phone book
A second step to figure out of the hotel was real
Flip through a few pages and decide Bill needed to know of
Did you guys check the Yellow Pages as well
It's only four blocks away from the Murrah building
This doesn't seem like something maybe a hardest thing to get to the bottom of
Literally not asked anyone
What do they think this wall so what do you think is bruised
I don't know what that is I guess is that they're speaking in code like a medallion Hotel mean something else
What else are you bringing this up
Red Roof Inn
No such company exist
Ridiculous nonsense
It's a little harder to swallow
Are you a hard tonight this is the only
Complete
Actual report
Has occurred
Any meteor
All day long
Zoo
People who have dedicated their resources
Their lives
Officer
Admitting women
I'll be intelligence service
Of the Second Continental Army
Of the Republic
Uline
It's not
Yep
I'm not playing that are just like
You know the Red Cross set up a blood drive Center
Saying stuff like that
Uncontroversial in like
Actual pieces of it
I am in the overall picture that you did for listen
Make the faces not
Actual recording
Sing with little bit
But I really want to put in there just so you know what I mean
Prediction
What's playing the audio of the bomb
Repeatedly
Almost like it's
The Tramp
You know like hell play it and then he'll say something and then play it again and then say something if it's very weird
A tiny bit of the end of the sound Eminem saying something
I just wanted to give you a sense of like what
The structure
Couple minutes okay
Memorize that sound like
More
And more
In America
Not because I want it
And believe me
Sing whatsoever
I didn't think you didn't
Just now
Emerging
Oneworld
Paleteria
It is partnering the agenda of the department
The American
It is
ATC
It is a lie
It is all manipulation
So
Please repeat
There's going to be more bombings
The New World Order
Migos
Spring bomb sounds
Has no problem
With egg roll
Gunite
No Patriots
In this country whatever
Our government
Without being attacked government
Parks
No fundamentalist religious organization
Has any
Resume
To bomb any building
In Oklahoma City
We all know in our hearts
Why this was done
Andrew's agenda
Kroger's
So we all know that this also I'm sorry the repeated playing of the bomb
Is a little bit after this because
First one
First time in this stretch plays a little bit more
Before he gets into the
Over and over
Stop
Think we do
I think Ivan
I don't think I don't think he and I agreed on the radio and your home
Saying is like
Prove it
You don't get to say we know in our hearts YouTube
Do that and
It's keep the facade up your some kind of alike
A researcher
100 or 22
Obviously this is a false flag attack
Watch
So he's already predicted there's going to be more bombs
Diction again really
Really quickly after
Remember that crown
You will hear it again
In America
Again
Until they realize their goal
Their utopian
Totalitarian
Cocosworld
Government
What's happening
Krogers in agenda
It's really hard to capture something like this
If I just playing clips
But I want to stress to you that at the end of this episode bill is making a very serious 22 predicting there'll be more bombing
Is the New World Order brings in their utopian socialist tyranny
This is an important point
False flag
This prediction essentially sets
The condition where if you see more bombings
Bill's credibility goes off
There's a pretty common trait that's Campo to propagandist
Going to be more mass shootings and some other prediction
His assertion that the current mass shooting is a false flag
Okay
Is there a bit last time.
I don't understand
Did he believe that
Because he's in those circles
He knows people
He knows the hard ripe
I'm not saying nude
You know like he knows people like Timothy McVeigh
You know the lot of people in the militia Patriot world
I'm self to be a leader of the Patriots on the militia
Said because he says
We would never do this
Unless it was quote-unquote self-defense
That means all of the militia people believe that same thing
Some of that
You know bill has some idealistic ideas about the group
People that actually people eat
Sincere or performance
Chomping at the bit right
We are surrounded by
Constitution protect against
A bunch of my friends are f****** scary
Did you guys know cops are crazy baby doesn't work for you
So this is where he's just like coming in and out of the bomb sound effect
This is ridiculous this is unacceptable
It is not our
Agenda
Yeah it's
It's a presentation that is
Deeply f*****-up Snapchat
Skip the big one drop there
So it was a false flag
Gilman of world
Call Asurion
Call Joya
Don't you
Ever
You're welcome
Forgiveness
It will come again
Goodnites
And God bless you all
Everybody
That song is a song that has all the time in version of a dove
All the time
It's very interesting that I've never heard that on any other radio show
The song Bill ends
Oklahoma City
Show with is a common Bumper Music
Interesting
I was listening to that
That's
Weird
Probably still literally everything for built
Paranoid sensationalism in service
Do so much here that is just
Very Alex
Continuing
In a weird way
What is the most important
Is you see the way this bill is kind of playing volleyball by amsel
Except himself up and then he spikes a ball
Restart the show with
And I hate to tell you this ladies and gentlemen
Because I just can't
Being right
What I'm right about these
A pipe bomb located under a wheelchair access ramp
P.m. eastern Daylight Time
Sacramento
Legislature building
Charlestown
Edward Island
Amazon
The legislature was in session
The bomb blew out the windows on three floors
The glass cleaner on the lake
Calculator
One person
I'm sitting on the bench outside the building was
Injured
No suspects
Have been found
Security
Husband
I told you this will escalate
Joke
Stop running
They will do anything
Is there philosophy
Read my book you know what I'm talk
Talking about you know what
Anything
Anything and everything
You get there
Utopia World governor
Good example of how conspiracy theory works
Operating is critical
What is April 19th prediction that there be more bombing
Does the utopian socialists try to bring in their authoritarian state
And then the next day another bombing
This is enough.
They believe that the bombing was not
Possibly be a solitary terrorist attack if there was another bombing the next day
You can easily see how if you didn't take a step back this pattern
But ultimately
The bombing in Prince Edward's Island Rhode Island
December 1996
Has no idea who he was at this point at all in when he's on air
Was a disgruntled former teacher who decided to lash out by carrying out bombing
You struck first in 1988 when he set up
Bomb in front of the provincial Law Courts
You lay low for 6 years then bombed again leaving the pipe bomb in a trash can in the Halifax Park
From this point he seemed to escalate his pattern with this legislature bombing in April 1995
And then an attempted attack on a propane plant in Charlottetown
In June 1996
Play that one did not work out
1995 bombing sending messages to the police using the Alias Loki seven
One of these messages
And the title
Torta final solution
The body of his message said quote the latest attack by
Of the thieving Scoundrels in Canada's bought-and-paid-for of legislature in quarts
The Troika greedy businessmen even politicians and Justice officials
Mehron but they cannot hide
Operations against dies and other enemies of the people we be continued by Loki seven
Thor
Oh wow is Manifesto
Cousin
Threatening letters in the like his
Adjectives if I was I would just say cut a little bit of it out
Troika is a little bit showy
96 propane tank
Down to basically cut down
And had him under surveillance around the clock
But would plead guilty to the sense to 10 years in prison
I don't think you killed anybody
I'm not advocating for more
The US
Fair
On April 20th 1995
When Bill Cooper's on are baking
Connections between the Oklahoma City bombing
Yeah that's really no reason to do so
If your process largely consists of drawing connections between things that you decide must be related sure they're both bomb
So I can see how you connect
Undisciplined set of standards
For reaching a conclusion
Alex Jones doing whatever he's
In the middle of trying to craft a narrative when something happen right
Uconnect
All kinds of unrelated things
What was the Boston bombing
The the ricin letters and it was actually the Elvis impersonator
Reconnecting
It's now because Bill on the 19th predicted more going whole-hog into this and it
And as we find out
Only after all the details are in the only connection to them is that Nazis like bombings
It's f***** up kind of
You know
I don't know
Feel like you get a swastika
I'm just going to go
You're right
I don't know
You can weasel your way out of this wasp
I just you know how it's like an old Hindu symbol I was thinking like
Yeah I know
Maybe it is much more certain that I do.
Chewbacca
A lot of that part of the case
Does swastika Nazi comfortable with
So in the next Club Bill gets to like speculating about
The motives might be
Forthemommas
Remember every time a piece of gun Legend
Clayton was coming up
Can Congress somebody would walk into a McDonald's
Somewhere blow away a whole bunch
Yeah
Connect those dots
I told you it was going
I told you who these people would be
I told you this was going to happen to
Unfortunately
Single
Omnibus
Counter-terrorism drill
Work reading in Congress
It has all kinds of opposition
Control now
Train and passed through Congress and the president will sign it before you can blink your eye
Omnibus
Counterterrorism Bureau
Another similar bills
Which will implement
Tighter
Thanks CeCe almost identical
Thinking patterns
Alex the shootings in the McDonald's are in order to facilitate
Which must mean that there are castrated somehow by the globalist new world order whatever
In the same way this Omnibus Omnibus terrorism bill
Is it
In order to get this through
Bill about predictions of future things
Says that there's nothing that can be done
Time to stop this bill
You better not let a parent but I'm telling you right now after that bombing yesterday there's nothing you can do to stop but it will pass
I don't care if the whole country
Stop it will pass I'm telling you now
It will pass
I got some
Stop it but I'm telling you you won't be able to
S-390 and s761 and neither of them passed
A watered-down compromise Bill the antiterrorism and effective death penalty Act of 1996
Richmond
Omnibus Bill was FasTrak
Surrounding the Oklahoma City bombing
This is how conspiracy thinking works
There was a big
The bombing was done in order to guarantee the passage of the bill which will give
More controlling
Ability to crush the militia Patriots
The bill doesn't pass
The part that seems to never really be considered when cracker G Series
Federal Building
If not thousands of people lying many of them under oath
Pressure who congresspeople
Like terrorists in other countries claim s*** that they didn't do but all the right-wing terrorism in America are bunch of f******
Craven coward
How do you willing to accept
Responsibility
Terrorism
Information will never take responsibility for something
Committing terrorist Acts
In our community could possibly have done this
Of the first instead of being like
The community of acceptable
Elements attracted to the same thing
Do really unacceptable we should take an audit of that
Be allowed to
To talk about whether or not terrorism is real
Yeah
They have
Capable of pulling off
A gigantic
Bombing power bill
The insistence of creating an anime to be against to simultaneously all-powerful and
What your narrative requires
By the time these two Omnibus bills that bill is using as proof that the new world order did the Oklahoma City bombing die
They aren't essential to the narrative anymore
Tons of other stories
Tons of butter
Plates that are so you don't notice 11 drops
Essential pieces
Why we're creating the suspicion
It's it's
Hey at work
Bill what is
Problem
Right
First of all bills got all these
I don't know
Listeners
Share who are
The writing stuff right
Internet counterterrorism Billet gives the president the United
You got them
All around them dead bodies are lying
AccountNow way up and
Linda Thompson
Been awhile since I've heard about how many people
The clintons have just murdered
Text Hillary
Tons of military that are coming in to help
Like whether Act
Active-duty a reservist
Baby doctors Maybe
Logistics
Only Soldiers the military only employs soldiers Bill Bill sees this as proof
Something
Name of that this is a drought
But why
Military personnel police officer
Prison guard
Reserva
National Guard
And Airport
Empire City of Oklahoma City
Cuz there was a bomb
This is some kind of
Grill
No
I don't know the answer to that
I do I know that what is happy
Is rain Dion
Call Porter
Can't do s*** like this
You can't lead his audience to a conclusion then deliver the conclusion is speculation and then just pretend
I get this kind of thing and honestly it's totally fine under normal
Circumstances
If you wants to use this
Spin speculative insinuation
But part of the
Conspiracy game
You gotta respect the hustle
It's really delicious to do this sort of thing
About the very thing
People grieving
Search and rescue operations are still going on as Bill speaks
And for some reason
The bat around idea that the whole thing is a drill
This dude
Weave
Gloves are really off for me
This isn't just some weird idiot who believes fake documents
USA Today
Either realshit
Exploding monster
Like Alex
When you start to look at
The Flash
Appointment
Alex is such a
Piece of s*** that we can give
Bill Cooper a glowing review
Comparison you come back to Bill Cooper
Okay well they're both kind of things that are goofy
Yeah you can make a case for like
Bill's Pawn in federal broadcasting throws music
We weave
Should make it clear
Either J pilot
So we get to smorc
Conspiracies here
Still March 8th
Several surveillance
Cameron Mathison
Parking lot
Apartments around
Building
Sounds like what I would do
These will be checked
See if they can spot the bomb vehicle
Prospects
The question is if they do I tell the public
Statesville
Wow
The only reason to do that is doing playing to your audience the suggestion that the public will ever see.
In 2009 the FBI release umbrella video The Day of the bombing and other surveillance come out
Video that everyone would want however has been actually exist
In court Richard Williams the event assistant building manager testified that the cameras outside the borough building
Had not been operational for at least two years before the bombing
Experience number of security cameras
Movie theater where I used to work was one such place and I've definitely heard stories about the
This motherfolk
Is a whole strategy a lot of businesses employee called dummy surveillance systems
The goal is to put up expensive
Open camera
If you have a high-tech security system oftentimes it would be criminal justice eyes it's not worth the risk
They choose not to.
You get the desired result
Can you save a bunch of money
This is actually a really bad plan
Because
Criminals know the difference between
I can tell and then second
If you put up fake cameras you might introduce a liability
So you could get sued for cuz you don't actually have footage of
Security
That might lead someone to take a risk that they wouldn't do otherwise I go outside a building a walking by
But that one actually makes much sense to me
There are like
Just to be clear if you're out there don't put up
The camera not worth it
But there are businesses
It's I mean not everybody does good
Practice you know like
Some people just want to cut Corners saves money
This is
This isn't to say that that's what the Murrah building was doing
But it is
No conceivable these camera stopped working and they were never replaced
Because it wasn't a high priority
Until the highest priority
I can have this detail would seem incredibly suspicious to conspiracy theorist but it isn't a giant red like me
The mix
Makes sense no cameras
Cameras being old and not working at a government building makes
Perfect and
Reticence to replace the computer
Punch Cards like
Nobody's changing anything
And these are these are the sorts of things that unfortunately never seem like that big a deal until we realized
Why would you even worry about replacing a computer that
Control the nuclear weapons no reason to do that if it works now it's going to work forever
Who were some rumors going around trying to sell surveillance video
TV stations for $1000000
But retired FBI agent Steven
In addition there was a secret service log
From April 24th
Dimension of a Ryder truck
Before the bombing
This is caused a widespread belief that the government is covering up the exist
It went nowhere
Stacy bauerschmidt the event assistant to the special agent in charge of the Secret Service
Division
Explain the question was a detailing of unconfirmed reports from the days of the
Beginning of the investigation
This is a lot less concrete that it's made out to be you know there goes a log
Things that may be at been discussed or her
Investigation
Have testified that they have never seen such a
Courthouse
It's it's possible to misrepresent it
The rumors are always so transparent whenever they give you a dollar number where it's like
They've been trying to sell it for $1000000
In its 1995 money so $1000000 might as well be 400
Like it's nonsense
If you were trying to sell it to a magazine or something
200k
Get out get in get out let me get out of here
No one's going to investigate the FBI agent who suddenly a millionaire
Enough
To get out of the country and have a decent life
The function of distrust whatever happened
If no tapes reproduce
That's not the result
Because that you know obviously the reason to be released for a long time from here
It's not that it's proof of there's a cover-up
Part of the cow
The parameters are set up
It's just your your priming the audience
Squidbillies decided that the
Reports that are going around that is a fertilizer bomb
Are not true
I can tell you for looking
Building of the Great
Crater in front of the building
But that was not made with a fertilizer soap
Ecofuel bar
Practice and Papa
Whatever did that damn eat
Was a fast
Burning High
Explosive
Type use only
In military weapon
With that kind of
For my kind
Vietnam
Any explosive
Pittsburgh can tell you this lady
I'll tell you that I have to
Told you right on the truth
This is meaningless
Bill is just saying that he's looked
Pictures and determined that this could be a
Tomato fertilizer and fuel oil
Which literally means nothing
This is the exact same thing as Alex pictures from the Boston
And determining that some people must be secret CIA
Because he knows a lot about secret CIA agent posture
Ibis Point bill has no information to go on
To either support or reject
Event theory that the bomb was a fertilizer bomb
You have no idea the actual bomb had supplementary
This is really just a knee-jerk reaction of denialism with no proof behind it
You can't prove that this wasn't a fertilizer bomb
. making it.
If someone else did this about a conclusion Bill didn't like probably Ranch
Games
Critiques
Even like I'd like
You can't tell
Just by looking at a few pictures Cooper
Fire investigators investigations of Investigations
Those guys have no f******
What they're talking about
Sickly made-up nonsense
Like there's no way
F*** off
So here's more sloppiness
Station chief
A little note
Because I get it
But I don't
What's to the blame for all of those guys
You get arrested nobody is really.
Maybe they wanted to be arrested
Or maybe they were somehow
Shut up with the FBI running Michelle will probably hear the real story
We probably should never fear the real stuff
Even the local newscaster reporting
Latest
Slightly raised eyebrows
Right here
I'm going to take a
Bill
Temporarily run out of
That's all
Quality
Air quality report
No no speculation in there
I forgot to cut out this clip
But there's a point where bill says that he knows what the bomb was
Because there were
Fulminate of mercury was taken out of the building cuz they're unexploded
Fulminated Mercury
Oklahoma City Police Lieutenant Bill Martin
The embedded digital explosives native Mercury
Were found on the scene
Testimony
What the attributed to me is it
Complete falsehood
I never heard of mercury fulminate before that article came out
And then just generally this is a little bit hard to swallow as a theory
It seems hard to believe that these explosives
Fulminate of mercury would have survived a giant explosion
I will need some pretty compelling proof of that claim
In an absence of proof and just a present
Speculation
Can I get on board
Bill Campbell
To us they are irrelevant
But apparently they have a great deal
Strong relevance
Another report from a cat
Sneezing
Newburyport
David in Oklahoma
Today I have none for
Cast of visiting the most
Physically
Spiritually
I have ever been in mine
Car lots
Disney World
Downtown Oklahoma
City
Is now literally under martial law
If that was a letter from a friend
Fine
If you're treating it as like a report
What are you doing
Jesus
Ridiculous
So this guy
This guy love this guy's writing style
Bill
I don't know if literal definition of martial law
Really makes me laugh
After he found a parking place
Which was a genuine miracle was
Putting money in the park
M & M.
Business suit
Said
Quote
You don't have to put any money in
And there is
What are the primary characteristics of martial law
Free pocket
There's no way I can just be about the marking m
Martial law
We're getting Church
Chicago really interesting when she start to listen to this stuff and you like these are
The table
There's things that is weirdo collars
Maybe callers I guess his listeners are
Are just faxing hamleys weird letters from
Frontline
Because he is Bill Cooper and he is a
Conspiracy-minded Melissa dude
This is a full
Girl
Take over
American city
After
Stage
Frank Wright
You were listening last night
You know why I say that
I predict
For a long time
And I'm going to tell you it's gone
Escalate
Call about war
Control
Are you alive
My together
Eventually
Nations
Oneworld
Totalitarian
Vocalist
The hills pretty confident probably because they have Prince Edward Island bobbing to make him look like a prophet is going to work but
Anyways about Janet Reno
State's Attorney General is a murderer
She murdered men women and little children Waco Texas
And now today on television
To offer a 2 million-dollar reward
For the instigators
Of the bombing
Federal Building Seattle
Oklahoma City
And she said she was worried about our women and children
Call now get your hands on some real money you going to need it might
Save your life
One of these days 1-800 289
Warren
The body
Surrounding
Well over 30
You don't want to know
Very well
You might end up there
You can almost imagine Alex listening to that and like ingraining somebody's pattern
Planting
Plug
Into like really intense emotional eating
Contact
It's a
It's like a every radio host does this
I haven't listened to radio entirely possible we could be He Could Be the One
Crazy hair 60
I don't know I don't do a lot of like let's play Loveline girl
I certainly don't remember them breaking out into really overly dramatic ads
Get back to some of his Intel
Coming in from Kashmir
Why are you doing
What is the point
Nice lady from Norway who was with
Depressed you got nowhere
Inside the perimeter
She was accompanied by
Soundman in cameraman
Surprised that I knew what I
Mixer
Are Bantam Los Angeles
Very angry
But he was going to have to
To walk all the way to
To the Civic Center
Find out
You got them
Yeah that's no one in Los Angeles walk
Yeah
Newburyport
Los Angeles
Automobile
That's wild Norwegian lady
Ultrasound
Press no I think he was trying to brag about that sound
Suspicious work like
Never would have guessed that I would be on
Like someone's mom writing a letter
From vacation
I was at the Grand Canyon have a wonderful couple
We were surprised by how much I do about pie bacon
Totally rice
Being a stickler again about the death toll
To like use as a
Like a fulcrum control over and use it as a sub
Victor bludgeon people that I don't like with
It's not mine
About estimate
Yeah it's Petty
So
Where you start taking phone calls and doing
Agencies were in the building
Activity
The perpetrators are in Langley Virginia
This is a guy
Bacon
Direct
Conspiracy Theory without any proof
It's almost like him scolding of his callers is really about
Protecting the appearance of his own credibility
Another caller brings up
Conspiracy
You heard that the University of Oklahoma recorded
No I have not heard yet
Well I will certain point
I've heard of it
Doctor
Announce the honey the local paper
Oklahoma City
Where did you hear that
Call Barry
Easy to find out
We have people write in Norman Oklahoma where the
University of Oklahoma
Is that
Send somebody
Right over there
Factory
Probably somebody listening
On their way
Your take on it sounds like
No it's right on the money
Call Medallion Hotel
Yeah so
That's a seismograph
Later
Respond to this guy is like
I don't know I haven't heard that
Whatever a host says
I don't know there's a mild restraint I can applaud a little bit
Completely out the window because of everything else he does
We have a report
United States Navy
Super tops
Secret
Installation
What's the day before
It's Tuesday
How old a bomb drill
In the
One of their major
Installation building
And the
Drill involved
In the car
Ever heard of the building
Exactly the day before
Erroneous gossip or something
What where was it
Doesn't matter where it is
The New World Order is everywhere Dan
Irresponsible nonsense
Experience when I'm listening to the shows
Is imagining what it would be like if you were someone who lives
Essence 28 and believe that
About like
Recording on rumors
For no reason like obviously that is something you will have an effect on his listeners
Whether or not
Reinstated
And the reason is because you do hear things like this sometimes
The content like this
Does have an affair
Facts on people
Like it if you're not careful with stuff like this it will change
Some of your perception
And maybe not in ways that are very positive
Working out
Looking at the world in a different way
This caller is very
But it's not
Yeah
Bill has changed
Yeah just to save
Use
Created a context overarching narrative
That allows you to contextualize situation
That you wouldn't have otherwise because there isn't a connection
Like it that you have a guy like Bill
Essentially this
I guarantee there'll be more bombs after the bombing cuz it was a false flag and then the Prince Edward Island bombing happen
That Way You Are
Settings that kind of an example for your audience
You're going to end up
Having the effect
That is not possible
And that's that's bad
That is not good
Yeah there's nothing inherently wrong with it like a powerful piece of media
If you use that power are responsibly and like an a******
Then it's not going to put better
Viewpoints in people's eyes ago
I've been waiting for my short way for a few days and I've had to consume
Pitstop
Stop
Maybe we should get people to read the lines
You can try reading between the lines
Forever bothering with the LIE
You can't do it
Kickflip until you can always
So this last year from the April 20th show
Making stuff up
There is more movement of military equipment
Material and vehicles in this country to
Days Inn there ever was in World War I
Are you going to start asking yourself
Why
I know the answer to that
So do some of you
You just making it up for him to know
That
He can't
Back that up at all
More movement has military stuff in Oklahoma City bombing
The Vietnam War
Could know that is if he was
Is privy to a series of
Orders and s*** like that because no matter what
No matter what like
Singular anecdotal evidence you can measure the
History of military history you could probably
Quantification for troop movement
Now I don't believe that on April 20th bill would have any reliable way to quantify
Regarding Oklahoma City
Just the facts
Miami
You can't do stuff like makeup now
Bulshit
I don't like that I don't like it when bills mean to me like that huh
April 21st comes around this point
It's become clear that Timothy McVeigh is the best
Do you mean
The false flag Patsy
According to Bell
Yes
Discussion of Timothy McVeigh connections to militia
Has come up
It's clear
21st is not nearly as interesting
Kind of
Uninspired
The only reason I
Is because there is a continuation of something from the 20th because these are part of a three-part series
About Oklahoma City
They're packaged
Together on the hour of the time
Episode title
And so I didn't want to
Completed
This is not
In terms of things that are interesting there was much more in the 19th and 20th
Bill starts out on an alarming town
Berkeley house
In order
The Commanding General on 2nd
Continental Army
Don't like that all
Archery Maine
On Boulevard
Are to maintain discipline of their unit
Every unit
Protective
And under no circumstances
Are you in a little while
The militia
Broken
As a result
The propaganda campaign
Stingrays
Against the legitimate
Legal
Melissa
Kerrville state
I love United States
Of America
That doesn't sound like
That sounds like him coming up on the Fly
From the Commanding General of these
I think that's him I'm pretty sure it is him
Witchfinder General
Seems to me that might be Bill's title for himself but I don't know
I'm going to
Suspicion
His real name is Milton
Here's my pitch
H2u
Xi'an It Reno s***
Mind
Everybody do it
Melissa Elementary the story is,
Pretty strong denial
He's in a bad mood a lot
Get some of that
It's unclear if it's sincere or performance-based naivete
Pizza
No way you can believe this is true
The only way the national rumour-mongers are going to be able to promote
Involved
Rumor
Is by simultaneous
Pioneer
Play racist group
Have you heard that
All day long
White
What time is it
Religious
Fundamentalist
Constitutional
Patriot group
Government painter
The truth is even in the Backwoods
Country of Oklahoma
Investigators are not likely
Surprising to many groups
Which are both races
Unpatriotic
Investigation
Anderson Tire Macon
There are probably
Hundred total
White supremacist
.
Keep keep looking Bell
Keep looking
Yeah man I don't know
You can't have a group
It's racist and patriotic because if you do then
You're not patriotic
The fair that you would go on
That you would say out loud I think they're only
Maybe 500 White
Supremacist
Tire country
Stone's throw of our place in Mansfield
Chicago
So I would say for me you know
Yeah I think that's really
Absurdly denial
About the nature of the person that will be arrested for this crime
You can research
That whoever is arrested will be
First proclaimed a rapist
Raider image
Election will be fabricated
Or what is there a racist
I don't think that's possible obvious
Buy in the world
Makeup similar connection
Does get arrested
Scripting this in order to make the Patriots look bad
Perry identical to Alex's
Sort of methods and narrative surrounding
People who do really terrible things happened to be part of the self-selected group
Her bill is very much heavily militia
Brow wax
In Western riots
It is
It is annoying to me that they
Preach this rhetoric
That comes down to
The government is
Is always attacking you
Self defense measures
Weird be basically whatever it is you want to do
And then at the same time being like
But we would never take offense of action
Even though you've already said that any action is functionally self
Right it is
I think most people would agree with that are
And you'd have a really tough time making
The same time
The narratives in that that sort of mentality has the effect
Desired
Follow through with it
And then end up becoming proof
The man is trying to make the Patriots look bad
Becomes itself
Perpetuating
Yeah which is
So big for on the 20th
The caller called in seismograph
Sure little thing
The University
Over in Norman
And I looked into this
Report from Gary
The report of two seismological event
Consistent with Margie
Organs on the morning of April 9th
13th March
T95
Ears
Confirm
At 1:20 p.m.
Today
Or 2195
I spoke with dr. Luther
I'll be Oklahoma do you like
Google survey which is located in the
McCarthy Energy building at the University of Oklahoma
Doctor loser showed me the price
Minecraft recordings made on Atmore
Going to
Supper
Cosmological
Disturbances
The first occurring
20 4 a.m.
Occurring at 90 2:14 a.m.
So this is interesting
Because like I mentioned earlier what are you talkin about is a real thing
Bill jumping to Wild
Conclusions without any doesn't end up running this narrative at all
The way you presented things there were two events registered on a seismograph
At the Murrah building
This is a simple conclusion to reach if you have a habit of not considering
Other possibilities
Which it seems like Bill might not do a lot
The fact that there were two ways registered on the seismograph
So they study the phenomenon further
What the result of low and high frequency
Rates
The low-frequency signal made it be 16 miles from the bomb site to the seismograph in Norman a few seconds prior
Do the high-frequency signal
Right
Additional seismograph
Review to wave signals despite there being only one
Controlled explosion
Urban studies demonstrated clearly
Signal pattern is not provoked explosion
Conclusions about this
He's breaking one of his own cardinal rules
Because it's important
Statistics of someone who believes the same things
So he eat takes
He doesn't know what it means there's no explanation that he can really provide
2 things to bomb
I understand
But you just don't know it now
So
Terry Nichols
Was I involved
If we are found
You know what's going to be left
Not bad
Call Terry Nichols no don't do that
He is apparently
At this point there's also been some discussion that he has some connection with the
Militia
Now bill has an easy answer for that
I told you all along
Symptoms of mono
Montana
And others
Our agent provocateur
Couture
They would fuel the flames
And provide the ammunition that would be used
Lacrosse boots
Mesa
And
I was absolute
Correct
AR reading Marissa of Montana material
And all the other beer
Put some more
DOL
Sophia Grace's
Again where is that naive that seems to be popping up there
I understand there are
I'm
Certain
There are some people who are into malicious dolphins
Some patriots stuff
Has that racism that's attached
Universal
You know maybe there's a there's an idealistic version of it bills and subscribe
Did anybody else does
It's just Luke
Yeah I would be shocked Irish octave Bill wasn't even aware
Bill has to know if he's ever been to a militia
He has to know at least one guy there who got a Nazi flag
Like
It doesn't
He didn't ever want to
I'm pretty mad at the militia Michigan because it should be the militia
And they really wasted
Yeah that is important
Emotive
For the bombing was Terror Bill through sure
But there's a reason
That Oklahoma was chosen
May 17th 9
State of Oklahoma
Gentleman
Replace your cast
HR 1040
Oklahoma the very first
State in the United
To actually go on record
Perusing
The approaching
New World Order
It called for the United
What states
Not to move
Military personnel
To support the United Nation
And many other things
Okay
Happened in Oklahoma City
Oh boy
Been passed by the Oklahoma Legislature
New World Order decided to attack Oklahoma of all places
The first thing that's important to understand is that HR 1047
Resolutions that our paths are not legally binding at all and they're really good things
It's like the recent thing we talked about where the San Antonio city council passed a resolution
Denouncing the use of the term China virus
This resolution was introduced on March
1994. May 17th
It completely completely absurd Proclamation but how the US needs to quote seize any support for the establishment of a new world
Global government
It's definitely paranoid and just
Very weird resolute
But honestly
If I were Bill HR 1056 works better
Resolution
Claiming sovereignty under the 10th Amendment to the concert
Do some of the United States over certain powers
Serving notice of the federal government to cease-and-desist certain mandates
And directing distribution
I want closer to Bill's introduction
Intro May 12th 1994
Works better for his narrative
I kind of suspected bill just combining or confusing me to Revolution
What baby does nobody talk about
No reason to blow the Federal Building because of a non-binding non legally actionable
Cramps
They might as well be but at the end of them you halfway expected to be like for the UN and I hate my wife
Angela
I heard you Angela get rid of the New World Order and the UN is evil
Three back-to-back kind of lunacy something very weird suspected there something else
Behind marital strife
But how right he is about
Right
Our study d
Works for years and I'm right on the target
I'm the only one
Who has pain
Differently
And with
Absolute accuracy
Predicted every
SEPTA going to
Listen to this
Anti-terrorism bill now on
On Tuesday the Omnibus counterterrorism Act of 1995
What's a proposal
Wanelo tracking Congress
Any object of a lively debate as to whether it would violate some
Fundamental civil liberties
Including the right to
Accuser
Now after the Oklahoma City bombing
There are
You sure largest lady texting walking
Democrats and Republicans
If you hate blugil of new releases Thursday
Calling for the bills
Quick
The Cutlass
Wonders are added again
Is there any discussion about how right he is about everything he's talking about how certain a bill of passages that doesn't end
About that he's right about everything I will not worry about that
Every move with perfect accuracy
Suggest that you
Nobody wants to play chess with somebody who knows everything that you're going to do that sucks
Introduce like a really interesting there right
But they're correct
The only explanation for them
Actually happened
For a reason
But I do think it's wrong to suspend habeas corpus
The dog say
Around
The time of the
Just about every high-profile thing
Call Zorba people
We were trying to sell more
Bill thinks that that's the New World Order doing
Golden bomber
Airport temporary evacuation
Federal office
Chili's in Traverse City
Miami
Santa Ana California
Birmingham Alabama Wilmington Delaware Portland Oregon
Boise Idaho
Carswell Air Force Base
Fort Worth Texas
Bombs girl support
Evacuation
The Balkans
City Hall what did they do but all the inmates out of The Nut House
Not on your life
This is all
Planned
To paralyze the American people
To give up the Bill of Rights
You can't prove any of that
You're the guy who's mr. proof you can't prove that
All of these bomb threats were done by the globalist
Did you think that maybe they did let all of the people out of the asylum
Or do you think that it's possible cuz that's not necessary for one to make a threat
Play Maybe
F****** teenagers who don't know any better yet
Crying prank call
Before like the internet with
It's good now for harassing people
Steal something
So
I don't know
It's very similar to Alex
Why is
Call to action is a little bit different
Fairly large similarities
Are you going to continue to
To say
Nothing's going on the government wouldn't hurt
Are you going to come
Can you until your rounded up
Socialist
Labor camp
Because you don't
Fitting room
How your mind is supposed to work in the New World Order
Is that what it's going to take
Before you wake up
Look around you this is not the United
States of America
Not at all
And that is not a constitutional Republican government in Waukee
DC
Nor in
Dates of the several
How many states
Craigslist
Continue
Recruit for your militia
Continue to prepare
Continue to arm yourselves
Continue to teach your children and your neighbor the truth about the Conch
Bill of Rights
I'ma principles and ideals upon which
Country was base
So I mean
Yeah
Ynobe
Illegitimate government
Kind of thing
Sounds a lot
Like
Beliefs of people who might attack the government
But no Patriot wood
Legitimate
Going to take you off to camp
FEMA camps.
It's all very similar
It only makes sense if you're saying to me that the Socialists are going to take me to
That is going to happen
Well either I can be in a camper I can fight back
This isn't alert
Government in place
Exactly
Belief system
Measure
To get in
Until I guess the power
Struck powershift
Something like that
I don't I don't know
The point is
Alex
Stop you seeing this episode is very much
Like exploitative
Per episode
It's not like it's taking over his show
Confused
Like what
Exactly the point is
If it's not
Create some sort of 8 brat
20 Franklin
You can see how successful it is even with a small scale
You can shut down government if you just have
20 guys wearing fake body armor and fake guns
Awkward Fox
So I took a look
These three days
Job
Not good
Lottery rumors
Down. My time no worse
Time for you to
Suck up like a
Then like in the immediate aftermath of
Gigantic terrorist attack
It's really really terrible
Through this
Prism you do see a lot more of Alex
Yeah in terms of these these patterns
These Trends these behaviors
I think the picture becomes a bit quicker
As to why
Somerville other episodes
Really necessarily make of the connection strongly enough as to why he is an important
Figure out the context of our show clarified here
It was better clarify.
Yeah
I just hate the cowardice so much
I hate how cowardly they are because
In one sense
Alright you can have the courage to step up and say
This is an illegitimate government and I support this
Terrorist attack
Another instance of Courage is you could step up and say
I don't believe this is part of the militia Movement we need to get these we need to find out where this is coming from
Rooted out
Cowardice comes in
I want to be the leader of
Fake militia
At the same time
I don't want any consequences for the b******* that I say
Very similar to Alex
Coward
I realize that
Really explain
I completely got derailed
Because I Was preparing this episode last night
Another episode 4
What we need to get to work
Gigantic fire in LA
Almost done getting ready
Somehow we
Turn on bills
To respond
You got to go to bed
Just really quick before we get out of here
So far is not been an all-encompassing
Approach or coverage
About Oklahoma City
Kobe possible number one
And number two
To take the same approach
As he brings things up
5. Go to them
Conspiracy gif
It's denser
There'll be more of the
Cuz I can see somebody listen to something like what about
As time goes along will experience it as
Bill's audience might
So I think that's the way to do it
Next
Yep we'll Toronto
Twitter
The Patriot living review or you could please donate to a local charity
Yes absolutely
I'm Leah I'm dzx Clark
I'm the concierge at The Medallion Hotel
That means I've ghost
Thanks for holding
Alex