I have great respect for tonight
B b
I love you
Indeed we are.
Well actually the other night
Meetings or anything
He's from the comedy days got together places names
A bit more of that in the future it's a bunch of
Just making fun of each other
It's like this that there's a grid of tiles on a board has a word on on that right
And so you play a one person is the spymaster the other person is B player okay
And the spymaster gets to see which are his teams
Get the other person to gas
But you want to
To try and get more than one of them in a turn
And bird that will trigger that in the other person
Try and get them to gas boat
Really ambitious out.
What are you thinking
It introduces so many like arguments
Taboo
And his first clue was
And he was trying to get me to gas
Hawk
Okay
Alright
Little bit
My
Kings of convenience
Yeah there is Scandinavian Simon and Garfunkel
And we listen to music
My friends and I all drove to Detroit because the only place where we could see them was a
Rundown
Pool hall
That that didn't card on the way there
We had. We had 65 very old pickup truck
First you drink then you smoke no no no first we smoke and then we drink in the car
Designated driver
Come on
Yeah
Well yeah that was because
Simon and Garfunkel
Play with acoustic guitars and then at the end of the show
One of the numbers is that
Who's actually a producer in DJ in his own right and they have and they brought somebody up from the crowd there
There was like 40 people there
I took play one note on the base over and over and over again and then we just all had a giant dance party on the stage is fun
For sure
Transition
Explain
And the reason is because on Sunday
Message okay
Totally fine
The situation was on Sunday
My Sunday
Is this Sunday
I don't know if I can help you and I were recording a q-and-a episode
We noticed there was water coming in the window
Coming in apartment
We found that to be troubling
And it turns out it's also not the first time is it a couple months ago and the landlord
Building manager
Tuckpointing work or whatever outside
And so there was water coming in
Call Dad emailed by
To take a look at it and if you look up
To take off like
The bar that's over my windows
And it's
Dealing with the situation they had to put in these industrial dehumidifier
In my room
Taking care of this problem in the way that the building insisted we do it
And still record and get the episode
Impossible we were unable to do that it's resolved now
And after some real real drama
Stamp Apartments
I don't I don't know maybe I have some really bizarre expectations but I expect
Communication from
Expect
Third floor apartment
Not the flood
Yeah yeah those earlier
That is
For me in terms of like
Frustration feeling out of the loop about my own living space
Just awful but there's actually a hidden bright spot in it
And that is that last night
As the machines were blaring
I have been told that they were coming to take out the machines yesterday and they didn't
The afternoon the no one was coming
Last night
It's so loud in my apartment it's awful
I think they're coming today the next day to take out the machine but now I don't know I don't know
I just got out I got to work
Working in case were able to record I got to get this all together
Miserable as I love
Doing the show
Like in that awkward moment
I had a Moment of clarity
This is so caught up repairing the stuff like there was a stripping away of some of the like
I felt really grateful
To be doing this and thankful for
People who will make it possible if you know and people who listen to
It's just that it was it was great in that dark moment
Preparing to do a show I really enjoy doing some really funny stuff that we're going to be
Able to talk about it people enjoy it
Like it's a it's a
Pierced through the misery
The only way to get clarity
There's no atheists in foxholes and there's no
So in that Spirit let's take a moment to say thank you
So first we got Dave thank you so much
Next
Not sure
Is that natural
Text Annika thank you so much
Thanks and this next one I actually bumped up it's very recent but a I put it
Because of a parenthetical
Yes thank you so much call Terry Nichols and then in parentheses
If this comes out too far from the Bill Cooper episode it won't be funny
Call Terry Nichols
Your appointment
I believe
Mjl thank you so much
Lisa
Ugly very special
Unfathomably supportive and generous
I'll be Raptor princess MD's
Power Raptor princess
Four Star
And tell your brother
You're Beautiful song
They're coming for your balls
Where is new people
When they are
At juice
Anthony
SRI preciate that very much
Generosity and send it to a local
That would be wonderful as well
Jordan the 18th through 21st episodes of The Alex Jones Show
But it's a little bit of a misnomer
Kind of disappeared
Complete
Alex is a true
Okay
From Today Show
You're not
Metal penis in me
So this is how contextualizing vaccines
Nevermind metal Bill Gates
Yes
So here is how Alex starts off a show on May 8th
Ric
To be honest
This is a preoccupation for most of the episode it goes on
Seems to be one of these
Biggest concern
We blown it up where I show you some shots of that
Coming up
Last segment
Where is day
With a
Ring of rubies around it
Corona
What did some research
Reassure
Hospital
Coronavirus
Very horrible sign
The DaVinci Code
Sun
Okay Gates about a week prior it been on
Good Morning America or something is wearing an upside-down cross and now she's really pissed off about
Course this is part of a really interesting symbology
Episode
He's taking us into Umberto Echo territory
You know you seen this picture of
Melinda Gates
But this jewelry
F*** her but it's not just Alex saying that you read the room
Fire
Storm
Proportions going on
Colossal
Proportions Gigantor
Proportions
Video of
Bill Gates on YouTube
Bruschetta
Comment this morning about his wife
Today program
What who cares
Why does anyone need
I don't care
They're very but they're very mean towards me
Generally not a good indication of consent
Great all right
YouTube comments
So across the Milky Way
Man
This upside-down cross
Is it actually crossed it's just
The symbol of entropy I don't know
Talking secretly going backwards
You touches on this
Too much it is
In addition to complaining
Something-or-other about the Coronavirus
Iris
Sign
Intervention
Coronavirus
Infowars
Dot-com
Australian news and University
Petrovitsky
Flinders University scientist
Coronavirus
First of all Alex from Austria or Australia
About this study
Study observed a coincidence or a sign of human intervention in the creation of the virus
The right there
Global pandemic
Here's another
Study led by Nikolai
Uncle
Professor of medicine at Flinders university has not reviewed and remained inconclusive
It's another one of these
I look forward to the some of these conclusions be challenged and looked at interview process
Alex ignore that pretend of the globalist refreshing after retracted or something
Stop pretending
Some of the stuff you saying is just completely made up like a stuff about the study involving to his HIV narratives that is nowhere in this
Also just because it's fun
The researcher who
These are generally easily recognizable and hands clear signatures of human intervention in the creation of the virus
These artificial inserts are not present has been interpreted by some to mean this virus is not the result of human manipulation
The guy who authored the study said because certain things are not present
That would be that would Point directly towards it not being human human intervention lack of presence
Of these artificial inserts to believe that it's not the result
Episode Alex's rambling about inserts
Everybody can see ours on the DNA
So you have this guy does Nikolai Petrosky put out this
Where is not
Signs of artificial
Can I have to choose one or the other their contradictory
Keanu Reeves said that chicks dig
So this study is going to probably become a big piece of Alex's stuff
And you still pushing that Indian study that got retracted from way back
A story about Bill Gates being responsible
Germany
That you better withdraw that paper so they withdrew that paper
Better withdraw that paper
Wall
We challenged those challenging it to show us any proof no one challenges
Wow wow wow okay alright
Throw awesome
It's fascinating how much like
His mind just
That's a good thought I had
Weirdo
So Alex gets to talking about some put out by the the Health and Human Services
Department
It's interesting how
Situation he's sort of like
Yeah
Covers half of
Half of the news
Headlines from Reuters
The first paragraph of the article
Us authorities are not yet seen spikes in coronavirus cases in places that are reopening but it was still too early to determine
Such trends
Secretary Azar said on Sunday
Give me the progression of how the virus has seemed to spread and given the fact that we're still not in a good place with on-demand testing
You insist like this quickly
We will have to wait and see what happens
First part of the story while ignoring the part where
Journalistic malpractice Appliance
Hydraulics
Abused that clipart
Now I can't win any every single time
Yep
So this is Coronavirus
So this is an interesting story
Because it's one of those bun instances where Alex's be reporting this story in the complete opposite
Based on everything he stands for
There's no indication of his lab in Seattle was putting at sites to give 100% 12 positive than any higher
False positive
It was heavily funded by Gates those pat on the head for not making that part up
University of Washington which is running a program called the Seattle coronavirus assessment Network
Basically what they did was send out test
Whoever wanted them
People swab themselves and sent the sample back to be process
The reasoning was that many people who are sick
Likely not sick enough to go to the doctor
Other situation
What I was told early on that they needed an emergency use authorization from the state in order to run a program like this
Where they would give test results people who submit protest
Hey March the state of Washington gave them a purple but now the FDA is saying they need Federal approval as well
I'm not sure where I land on this I assume there's probably some benefits a nationally coordinated responses which make the meeting Federal
Google make sense
I'm not sure I understand all the details I'm going to stop short of having a solid position
However
Does mr. states rights
He absolutely should not be into this lab being shut down by the federal government with the state government already approved what they're doing
He believes
And pretend principles are
Anyway Alex's by Emma Smith Society this is just a temporary hold this lab has until they can get some details ironed out about the author is
Station to release results to people
How to completely making up details of the story to make it sound more to fairies because
He's a liar
Yeah
Really just about the clearance
People results
Oh everything is positive
The situation
When the federal government
Doing whatever they want and saying okay well then f****** sue me about it
Now is not the time to pretend that you have to follow anybody's rules
Tell him to f****** tsuyu
It's wild the situation
That's what I'm advocating everyone commit
Every crime they can think of
Potato corner
Is that a bad idea
That last clip was Alex trying desperately demonized
Because that's what he does
Animes like sloppy does that kind of embarrassing Lee and it's also pretty fun
Devil ritual
I'd like to flashback to the months and months of coverage Alex movie Yelling about MS-13
24-hour notice
They're the hardest
But Bill Gates
Reportedly
I'd like to see the reporter Got Back 9 year old demon
What are we going to do I don't know already a demonic hopping around mad
Which is your favorite gremlin from Gremlins 2
I don't remember exactly
This is so ridiculous
It's amazing
Yeah makes it hilarious by 10
Reportedly
Way to you could look at it as a way to not get
I think it's Alex Pretender some credible backing
Okay
Alright who's doing nine-year-old
Surveys of whether or not people are demons yet that's a good
That's a good job for a ridiculous
So you know
If you were a demon at 9
You would obviously grow up to marry someone
Cross on TV
Skip the talking more about this cross
Upside-down cross
Even more power
When you actually carry out the app
So Alex spends a lot of time in this episode complaining about Melinda Gates wearing this upside down cross necklace
Satanic
Alex asked why someone wearing upside-down cross
Maybe they're Catholic
The upside down cross is the symbol of St Peter before father of the Pope
As The Story Goes Peter was crucified upside down because he was too humble to be killed in the same manner is Jesus
Upside-down cross became as simple and important one for the Catholic Church
To the upside down cross in real life
That's just something from movies and imagery that used metal and punk bands
The fact that goes on and on about never once mentioned lacrosse St Peter really leads me to believe that he
Very little familiarity with Christianity
And I know that stuff
Legitimately everything else you talk about comes from movie
So why should we be surprised to learn that
Is very public about her Catholic faith
This is John.
The best we're one step away from morning Zoo
You got a sound not quite not quite I still need to find I need
Jewel soundboard
Symbol of the Catholic Church
So this leads into Alex talkin about other SIM
Cuz he knows a lot
Are we really doing really dude
A 10000 year old Norse symbol for death
With a circle around it
Gentleman
Why would
Why would they
Total
Complete
Okay
Did he symbol was created by Christian pacifist artist named Gerald Holton back in 1958
Years ago
Is disgusting a profile inspiration was the naval semaphore Flags
4 M & D combine to form the peace sign which was meant to stand for nuclear disarmament
The other part was
I was in despair
Deep despair
I drew myself the representative of an individual in despair with
Palms
Stretched out words and downwards in a manner of goya's peasant
Before the firing squad
I fertilize the drawing into a line and put a circle around it it was ridiculous at first
And such a puny thing
The symbol was adopted by the anti-war protesters and hippies and we all know where want from there
The most popular Norse symbol for death is the falcon
Which is three triangles intersecting and it literally looks nothing like a peace sign
Alex is probably thinking of hedra cell which is the north symbol that involves
The tree in a circle
This does not symbolize death however it symbolizes the connection of all things
And sometimes called the Tree of Life
Also it doesn't really look like a p symbol
Honestly this is just kind of sad
I was just making s*** up
Which is nothing new
You being a stupid blowhard about symbology it's the most
Pathetic Direct
Can you take your fake expertise in
Even if you're right you've not proving anything do you know the word that is not right now and the worst one
The most demonic one is when Kellogg
Co-opted a 10000 year old symbol
Of Captain Crunch
And that obviously symbolizes
Disruption of copper
Set the main issue that I have with cap
Ancient Phoenician text cotton candy version of Captain Crunch
Stop by the crunch berries
May I used to get to
I want to get
Are we
Buddy
Jo-Ann's
This weekend I'm going to be up here
Working on
Super excited
I got those looking for you about that next
Alex releases release
Very excited
I'm going to spend the time on my show right now that I could be using to get the news out to you
That there will be a documentary that I am thinking about doing but have not done and probably won't ever
And I
Are they are
Great products
Instaff going this conversation so regularly on air
D.c. Mall of his producers
Alex need to know
Just need to get to the snooze.
About the upside-down cross
Piece of news
Like about himself because of course of course
Articles
Friday
Navigation
It's just that
My name is
I just how it is
Pretentious
What
I might get to a couple of important things here
I'm just not going to I'm not going to do it which is selling this
Take some time off
This is so
Because
Cuz what
Amazon I got to go hide I got to put down my shoulder
Just not do any work
In and out
Because you
Spoiler alert it is not follow through with any of that
Earlier stupid was I'm going to not fear to work on that
And now he's not even going to work on that I don't think any of this happened Alex does not do his show
Regularly for most of the week is there
So I don't know
I love it I love it you spell Yer so
Get out of here man I don't know I don't want to do this
Ends up yelling about
Is Alan dershowitz mandatory
I don't know how much
Pest Control
This baby
Fire projectiles
Norman
Did you delay that out
Here is that unedited
I don't have to worry about guns
Are projectiles
It's you
Your
If you delay.
Fair right now
What a baby cow
Wow
Somehow
That's weird gray area
What it tells me to
Alex is not concerned about radio station
No not really at all
Because otherwise you'd be much more careful
On radio station
Kicked off the station
Too much
So Alex is really mad at
This just goes on a little bit longer
Breakdown
A lot about Alan dershowitz
Just can't help it
Okay
It doesn't sound right
So Alex gets into finally talking about the Secret Service story
Funny
Probably believe everything Alex the same
Ono first part of the story
A service
They said well you didn't go to the meeting or whatever and I said okay man I was
Around the RNC
Because he was partying he was too drunk to meet with them
So basically dealing with his keynote speech
So early
Oh that's right now I remember you
Is that the deplorable
He was rambling around by peeing on a tree
How where Atlantis
Yeah he does end up eventually making contact with the Secret Service
They're concerned that he has information about a plot to assassinate Trump right
Answer you would think maybe Alex has some deep in town or somebody's told him something
What is information is it's so lame
Can you send us
Foggy Bottom
Really said that
So Alex just sent the link to the CNN or MSNBC interview yelled at all the time
This is apparently the Secret Service
Billy Riley
Wow
I can't believe that I absolutely believe
Do you guys have this widely publicly available information that everybody's already talked about for a while
If you don't guess what
Phil Mudd is coming to kill the president Alex the uncovered an actual plot
Man
This dude is I love it
Lost lost in his imagination
Alex hasn't
Which is you know just basically a
Seems like every time he's on all they want to talk about is like
Luna going on
Turns out I have made people love
Which is weird
Yhl directed lockdown
Hong Kong Taiwan
With macron that was super
Popular
Subic narratives about the motives for the globalist
Releasing his bioweapon was but there was
There's momentum growing around like the yellow vests
Because the globalist you're scared of this stuff
According to Alex is very stupid
Fury and the reason so dumb is because Alex believes that everyone's convictions are just as flimsy as his own
All his political positions
Completely changeable consciously or subconsciously
One else has the same way
Well they're doing what we're doing
Because we're doing what they're doing
Any evil group worth their salt
Novolin would consider that plan
So now we have Alex reporting the numbers from Spain that the government is not popular come out
Counter to his Crush
Instead of considering a baby he just made that narrative up and it's based on nothing except his imagination
He reports it is proof that the globalist plan is backfiring
And this is a really good demonstration of why this
This pattern of thinking has no way out
Things that prove or disprove your arbitrary narrative used to support your narrative
It's basically the same thing as Alex predicting globalstar going to kill Trump in the next few weeks and then what it doesn't happen he can claim
We stopped at telling the Secret Service about a CNN interview
That's the way this other stuff works
Right now there is a plot
Like I don't care about 8 and I've been doing this a immigrant
It's not
What are some fun things that end up getting
Policy on Commerce
Funny. We don't need them
Don't give
Globalist affiliation left
$1
Make sure you
Mid-America and death
Any longer
Right now are still at
Oh
I think it might be interesting for him to go
Anti-immigrant bathing that he actually does what I would recommend which is shoplocal a Dino
Mass produced products
I don't know I think all that's made up a supposed leftist
Thrift shops
Is huge for the thrift industry or whatever
Headline
The backlash
Has begun
Decency and normality
So this story sounded really dumb
First let me say that
Even if you help fix someone's car and feel like having a loving gesture
All Things Considered
You may not know this Jordan but there's a rash of cheek
Kissing related crime going on
Fifteen-year-old girl and kissed her on the cheek
Yeah actually that story is really wild cuz he ended up writing his phone number on her hand parents
Her to call and set up a meeting
Citizens arrested him
The worst Predators schedule in September 2019
Rested after you kissed a local news reporter on the Cheap on live TV
Jesus in March 2019
Since you woke up to him kissing her on the cheek
Would you let the unlawful entry assault and battery charge
There were way more stories by
Cheek kissing related crime
In the past year that I would have imagined
I like face masks now I want a full like
Let's get those spit guards and everything to whatever the case our story right here
Well this is about a lorry driver who got stuck under a low bridge
70s help guide him out of being stuck and after he got out your approach her and kissed her on the cheek
A lot of people online or making fun of the Derbyshire police's tweet about it that said quote
We are appealing for help to identify a man who kissed a woman on the cheek to thank her for helping him when his Lorry became stuck under a low bridge
People were saying that the police state can a man not kissing lady on the cheek anymore
And of course the police released a statement that made the situation very clear
Quote
We issued an appeal for information this morning after a woman was kissed on the cheek and then unwanted gesture from a man she did not know
The incident left the woman who's in her 70s very distressed
Especially at a time when close contact with strangers is to be avoided
She reported it to us and in the sexual offences act of 2000
The police would straight up not give a single f*** about this if the woman
Had not reported
She felt violated by the gesture and the police were just taking her report seriously
I tried to handle the situation
Like think about
Who exactly is Alex making fun of here
That's important to remember because he thinks he's targeting the police gear
Like they're overreacting and offended by in effect
Mocking the 70-year old lady
To Alex she doesn't have the right to not thankfully it's after the kiss of a stranger
Alex was lying about what the story is in order to make people mad about
Get mad about it
The thing in the real world they're mad about is the 70-year old woman having boundaries
Yeah that's the real world
Part of this
Any anger directed towards the story is
Bubble tours in reality version of it doesn't exist
I just I just can't
I just can't handle people how do you not
Like the first thing I think of whenever I think of that story is
Why the f*** are you kissing her on the cheek
How are you do you not know
Like where is social distancing like she was then
Just like the best
Elmo
Elbow handshake
Something like that
Kiss a seventy-year-old high-risk woman
That's insane
Little glimpses little stories to remember
There's 100
There's just so many
They're just Fingerprints of how bad a job he does on everything
Like he's just really not good
Thank you
So
Hilarious
Alex discusses how he had appealed
Applied
4D small business money
Who's pretending they did it as a test
Do it
Alright
Whenever it's for ideological
Alex
Are the journalistic Endeavor
Absolute
Man
This is my oldest brother is a socialist
Conservatism in the I don't think he's into q but he's
Kiewit Jason
And he wouldn't he was telling me about how he's on unemployment right now and I just wanted to throw my
My phone into a
Lake like I just wanted to toss it into the lake
I can't handle that level of
Well I mean if I need it I'll take it
Lite-Brite
Idiots you should start
Forget it
So there's a video going around
That is frustrating I'm sorry
Right
Yeah there's a video going around that it was Alex with some water noodles on his head
I think that was from cuz it's not on this episode
But Alex
About inspired
Videos or pictures that you see if people at like cafes
With water noodles on their head
Foam
Noodles on their heads
Now this is what goes on
Europe
For social distancing
They're not
People on earth
Family Show
English Arabic
You seem to be a lot today
So how are people on earth
You should take a nap Snickers
Beretta earlier
So Alex is knock it off
Really but we got lots of videos I got a million views or more
Medical doctor
Virology
Rockefeller Hospital in heads of virology in Australia
Nobel Prize winners for ology coming out the same covid-19
Don't have a million 10 million 15 million views I get banned
Medical doctor
What are the stories permission
Yeah.
If they have it that's pretty shity but come with
Do they got half a million on YouTube that means that when I repost it I already have half a million
Video
Alex Remains the most popular thing on my website with around 100,000
There's some anomalies that I saw like a little clip that he made that was Pro Tucker Carlson dab 290,000
But it gets really really sad really fast when you leave Alex's Channel
Owen Shroyer War Room episode from May 20th and sitting at 1500 views as I prepare this episode
The 19th is only at 7,500
David nights numbers are comparably depressing
A little better than Alex's May network shows pulling in between 2000
Videos of surprise
But that's just because he's still on YouTube
Alex recently gave David I could Channel
And that doesn't seem to have been taken off side taking off
Expected under 25 thousand
Is there's exactly one with more than a billion views
Is 1.4 million
This is not something Alex made it's just something that you took from someone else
It's a reposting
Plandemic
Indie creator
Steve has a multi-millionaire on 26 in the media industry
This is pathetic
I guess congratulations to Alex reposting someone else's documentary
Really a strong indication that things are working out in house
Not his
Mdcclxxvi is 1984 when Hillary for prison
That's great
It's very weird to buy on your own
Yeah
None of the Rockefellers measured up until his early night
I just passed
Turn on power to royalty
Well the decision was made to make Bill Gates
The New World Order
About 12 years ago
35 years
Asbestos
Imagination
That was Bill Gates has made
Believe in passing power down through like royalty
Let's cut back to anytime
The global is passed down wealth and power through
Rothschild Anderson Cooper
Doing they don't believe you
The power of undertale
Bloodlines
Which is a
Dumb dumb
Alex
Have to do the show I think
He probably would have taken off
Maybe I don't know maybe
F****** idiot As Trump got on TV and said you was taking hydroxy
Chloroquine
Ammoman
Show complete
Crystal Clear fraud
Treason
Deception
Precision and fear of ideas
Patient
Inverted
Humanity I've been diverting nice
Tentacle
Chloroquine
One of the only known
That actually works
For Respiratory illnesses
Lupus
No no
Sure
It's also known as the only treatment of off drug that works in lupus
Hundreds and hundreds of studies that hydroxychloroquine
When taking the first stages of a coronavirus covid-19 infection
So Alex makes a few points there that I'd like to address
He says that he is the only known treatments that works for Respiratory illness
So I consulted Artie magazine about this client which does not stand for Russia Today
It's actually respiratory therapy
In their article
Pharmacological treatment of respiratory disorders
Comes up
There's so many medications that are used to treat respiratory illnesses and those two are not on the list
Just think about all the inhaler base things like albuterol then
You add some
Corticosteroid the different strategies
To deal with respiratory conditions
There are definitely uses for Respiratory conditions
Just making that up
He says he's from malaria which is true
Alex has earned a little pat on the head
For that
The event says that it's known as one of the only off drugs that works for lupus and I have no idea what it off drug is
What he's trying to say
Hydroxychloroquine is prescribed for Lupus under the name Plaquenil
Yeah that's
Really one of the big reasons why it's a bad idea to cause a run on this medication
Because it's only going to hurt people who
But I would still understand or care about that
Either way Angie Bolero drugs are only part of the approach
Treatment and management lupus
Complicated game
And if you go to Louis. Org
You can read up on the various medications that are used to help people
With the condition
Including steroids anti-inflammatories and anticoagulants
How to claim that hydroxychloroquine is one of the only treatments for Lupus is painfully reductive in a pretty strong indication that he has no idea what
He's talking about
Event goes on to assert there are hundreds and hundreds of studies that show that the medication is perfect in its effectiveness
Stages
After catching
The Coronavirus
There aren't hundreds of stories about type core Quinn and Coronavirus
. he's just making that s*** huh
Most of the recent studies show that it is not effective at all and possibly dangerous
A few days before Alex recorded this episode
Two new studies were published in bmj which
Compared with standard treatment
Do use of hydroxychloroquine did not increase the likelihood of virus elimination in Chinese patients with mild-to-moderate covid-19
Have any effect on reducing admissions to intensive care
With more severe illness
Both studies found a higher rate of Adverse Events in patients treated with the drug
I understand that it's Alex's job to run Trump defense whenever he says something stupid or dangerous need to pretend that there's some kind of
Hidden reality wearing Trump is actually right in the people criticizing by the stupid one
But this is too much
Jump straight up went on TV and said he was taking hydroxychloroquine which is just Madness
He's either Ryan which is absurd and very hard to guess why a person would do that
Who is telling the truth and either has covid-19 or thanks
Without any
Any evidence
Quit taking it will protect him from getting infected
There's nothing I can say
Trump claims people jump
Italy
Boots and coming up with
Completely nonsensical rationalizations why Trump
Said that stupid thing it's actually secretly smart
What a f****** loser
Take the day off
Isn't that a crime can you get that gave you isn't that making false medical claims I guess that he's not selling
I still think you could probably get in trouble for making
God what
Well everybody stupid
Say that and I was just like
This is what
Feels like
Cuz I heard him say that and I was like
I guess
Fine
The end there's a sinking feeling of like that can't stop that
F*** it and don't give a s*** real Trump is saying because
Why not
The president is a fraud and a liar and
When he makes Acura
His own personal doctor
To take it preventatively with Zayn
My God
Knockout is bacterial Flora
Taking probiotics
He's with
What is the CIA
Please ignore
Trump Medical
Washington Post
Doctor
Coronavirus
This is the top
He's a fraud impeach him
Calling for hearings
So as I understand that there are some hearings that are happening right now about the government's response to the virus I've heard anyone say
Leading to impeachment
I think Alex is complaining this stuff in The house's ongoing investigation into the instances of possible obstruction of justice
Report
Is Noah
McAllen
We've reached the point now it's Jones's career is cheerleading for the present
Only federal government has followers that it's a good idea to take a medication that's
I really thought this guy hated the federal government it was intrinsically distrustful of his singular executive
So weird
Almost like he never really believed any of that should be yelled into a bullhorn
I will say that he's super lucky but his audience is too dumb to realize that that's which happened because to anyone who's paying attention
This is f****** ridiculous
Trump is going to wind up killing himself by his own stupidity and
And then we're all going to f****** die in a civil war
Stupid
He's going to die and kill us all
I do think I mean I don't know how likely that is but I will say that if
Buy some
Workhorse of weird
Awful coincidence he does end up dying
Thursday
Unhealthiness or some just
Natural causes
Absolutely it's going to be a conspiracy
How do I know that
This is how we're going to get the granddaughter of Martin Luther King jr.
In the White House
Coronavirus
Guess we might not think it's a virus
I don't know where he stands are now
You sing in this next clip babe it's a deficiency of vitamin D basically
SWAT team medical doctors
Want you to know
Disease
D3
Major Yahoo news last week
Covid-19
Deficient in D3
Ron I'm not sure what he thinks is AIU study I don't know that
Northwestern University
Patience from countries with high covid-19 mortality rates had lower levels of vitamin D
Compared to patients in countries that were not as severely affect
The head of research of backman
Well I think it's important for people to know that vitamin D deficiency may play a role in mortality
We don't need to put vitamin D on everybody
Is needs further study and I hope our work will stimulate interest in this area
Illuminate the mechanism of mortality which has proven could lead to new therapeutic targets
The theory the back man has is it hasn't higher levels of vitamin D produced the risk of complications
But that a lot of people would still be dying from the virus
Nothing in this study demonstrated that everyone who died at vitamin D deficiency just making that up
There was some other studies on the subject but they're even further from what Alex is talking about that's not what
Poem from I have no idea
This is an interesting area to be looked at
Yet so we will see what comes after further examination
Either way literally no one is saying a vitamin D could be an effective treatment
For this
There may be a correlation between vitamin D and higher complication probability
These are
Essential piece in it
Alex is Translating that into everyone who died at Vitamin D
Information there does not also coincide with
Less privileged population
Vitamins in in all of that
Probably more likely to die as well
Exact possibly feel like screaming all the
It's me
Got arrested
And here I am a Detroit Clinic and literally claim that high dose IV vitamin C infusions would protect people
From Catching the virus
He was committing fraud
Also committing Medicare fraud
According to a Daily Beast article about his arrest
Quotes
Continue to work
And treat patients
At least one of them was assigned by Bach to treat covid-19 patients because that employee quote
Had already Kanter are contracted the virus
This is not so much a problem but doctor giving people vitamin C it's more of these broad aspect that the courts are concerned
Heard about that's weirdly so often that he misses the forest for the trees
Don't care about doctor giving someone vitamin C
They care if they do it in a fraudulent way
In the same way no one cares if you kiss someone on the cheek
The longest to be kissed on the cheek
Alex seems incapable of understanding context which makes sense
Picking up whatever that's not new
You can also get him on an attempted murder is letting people who have covid-19
Attempted manslaughter
To be fair
Sure I'm not entirely sure that Witnesses correct but that's proof
I'm just saying that if I'm here and that I'm giving it a I'm putting it on the list Jesus
Here's where all this starts to get really
Troubling Alex makes a claim that I think I'm glad that this is where it all starts to get troubling everything
Alex makes a claim that I think is a little bit maybe past what he should be saying
Because it loads the South
You don't need to file
I looked into the doctor
Long-term.
If you got the B3 in the sea
When you have
Pretty bad
Pretty obvious
YouTube Alex's insane machine the same time as he's plugging the real red pill
Still reality that you sell zinc and has marketed these product as
And you literally said on the show right now but if you make
You get the Coronavirus
I really don't think that's legal yeah I'm pretty sure he should be arrested like a like a certain
Yeah I know this
This should be immediately according to a 1990 study in the journal
Nutrition
Intakes
102 300 mg of zinc per day
Versus brda of 50
2 mg
Evidence of induced copper deficiency with attempted symptoms
Anemia and neuro
Neutropenia
As well as impaired immune function and effect
Do high-density lipoprotein cholesterol have been reported
So there are issues with just the amount that Alex is describing
I cannot necessarily
Take a note
There could be anemia you can pick copper deficiency
Your immune function could be impaired
Based on the 100 mg dose of zinc
But he's recommending
You have no business making these kind of recommendation
Alex Cervantes would rather
Kill themselves then listen to a real.
Probably possibly
In order to convince them that he has the answer is getting the Coronavirus
It's really hard for me to imagine anyone acting very responsibly than this
Given the circumstances
This is very depressing
It's pretty depressed really depressed
That's really depressed
There isn't one
Alex might be it sounded like he's talking to his doctor
Alex's doctor takes hydroxychloroquine
Family doctor
Medical checkup
Hydroxychloroquine
Is laughing because I think you realize is how obvious it is that his doctor is himself
He laughed because he's like
Believe people believe this is too fake even for me I have to laugh
At the end of the shower myself
Yeah I know
Excel going on some of this
Pretty f****** desperate
Royal
Percent off
Survival Shield
To 50% off
The cleanest best
You got to have that
35% off
Number to Central hand sanitizer
Essential oils
You get the
Percent
60% off
Those are some big big big sale 70% off
Cost
Whisper water filter on hundred percent off
Water filter you call me I'm in a mail it to pay 4999 and shipping
Also I don't know
I like it
DC involved under daughter
I don't look at it as well there's plenty of places to put it in here
Halfway through the first hour the show Alex just starts playing the video
Bill Gates being evil
Great you does a YouTube thing
Then it just plays like even out of commercials is it playing as video six minutes into the second
That wraps up
And now it's is gone
He's just gone
Football
Which is a disaster
But I thought like
It's only
Half an hour of this episode
I got to listen to a little bit see if Alex comes back what happened what happened
Oh man
Navigate to the Superbowl
This is my this is my
Actually went through and started
The most famous super villain
No
They literally sounds like Bill Gates you have
Marvel series UFO
The people
Many people overpopulation
The population
Literally sounds like
This is going to be so amazing real is everything everything is got to be
Fictional thing this
Feels like
Like to meet
We can't just deal with reality reality this reminds me of this reminds me of the
Truman Show
I think people are all watch
Make me lose my goddamn mind that's what's going on here that's my
Conspiracy theory Bill Gates put together a show
You're in on it
You must
Totally
Tee-off on this f****** dork love it
Treat his other employees
I usually give him a bench this is this bag
Aces
If you have this story here
Scientist begin experiment to block
The Sun
Bill Gates
Is involved with
Video
Bill Gates explaining his
Save the world
To Hannah
My God
Get that in just a sec
The engineers are
He's just a clip from The Simpsons
Is very sad. I don't I don't know
Play clip 2 and everyone's like
It's got to be temps or something what is going on
It's just nonsense Harrison being stupid because he forgets the name of Margaret Sanger
Come on man just pretend you know what you're talkin about
The gris-gris jumps in
Right
Are you want to talk about that idea
Blocking out the sun humans try to beat them
Machines with the upper hand and breathing people's batteries and stuff
Solutions
Just is troponin
And again it's like you just
Super villain
Your plans are
And they all sound exactly like
This guy does not have it
I hate to be a dick but this kid
Sucks on my political talk shows news shows
I'm just going to go through some top 25 list of supervillain Cabana look like
Lex Luthor plan number one
Superman that sounds like Bill Gates
Hospital
Bill Gates
He deserves us to actually look
Get some of his ideas
Otherwise we're just going to be
Villain's lair
Who is Mike Wallace
Nickname is
50s
Population control
Because of overpopulation are tariffs
Overpopulation
Global population
And things are going great
But starvation did we ever
Followed
Suggestions
Maybe you know the person who invented
Technique that allowed people to be set
Allow the population
You just can't
Prediction for population growth is really complicated
Patient resources and all these things
Apparently Harrison didn't get the memo that Alex is really trying to play up caring about hunger in the developing world
Idea for him to come on the show
Undercuts that whole week are the World Health Organization is willing to put
That's hilarious
But the reason I remember because each me how weird this dork Harrison Smith
I think will put me over the edge of the population control
Might make it so the guy who invented some crop technique may never be born
This is so weird on a bunch of levels
41 it implies a belief in hard predeterminism
What person was destined to make that crop technique and because their parents used a condom
See there you go this is a super weird way to look at the world and it only makes it even more
You think about it
He was predestined to be the 8th Banana IT Infowars
Everything in his life was meant to lead to him being the guy even I will forget about six months after Alex goes out of business
His parents used a condom
Miss out on any techniques
What to do
Should all contraceptives be outlawed
What about masturbation
What was Spurs might be the cop technique guide
Well that's why the Bible out
If you take Harrison's weird thoughts to their logical conclusion
Procreate
As possible
Either that or he doesn't actually care about that project
Guy getting born as much as he's pretending he does
My guess is just standard anti-abortion thinking being delivered by a very very weird dork
Let's chat that's the same that somehow that's like that Albert Einstein
But it's for just some random
The boogeyman look like
The stuff was there
Relativity existed without
Great man theory of History
Tomorrow mother over inventor
Years either that or they were parallel thinking unrelated
Elementary
On different timeline
Or with a woman who didn't the man saw the credit there's there's a lot of this. I mean
One person wasn't born
Things that they invent
The only person
And quite frankly
Like okay Mississippi is the mother of invention right we all say that
Is the deadbeat dad of it
If someone isn't born the world exist
Without their presence whatever they were responding to to develop an invention
Exist in the absence of them being there you think
Someone else would work on the problem of maybe
This guy
The f****** weird
F****** Weird Al
God I love outloud
The old school classic
Microchip everybody track everyone
One World Government I mean this stuff is laid out
In that
Wonderful book known as the Bible known as the Bible
Go home
Call Harrison go home
You and Alex
Both need to be off
Supervillains
Godwin
This is what my mind got blown
We know from
Podcast
First of all doesn't know Ozymandias his name and at the same time thanks
That the movie was
Positive
Ozymandias was the good guy
It turns out this might be a very common interpretation
Because you talking about these supervillains and it's making me think of the Watchmen
And I can't think of the
Villains name in that
It was named himself after
And Egyptian pharaoh with me like Abyss
Shaq
Was sort of painted as
Like a lowlife
Villain
Is this
The message that movie that I thought when I watched it was
With keep your mouth shut and don't try to expose it because it's a necessary plan right you don't understand you're just a little
Cretin down there that doesn't understand the big brain plans that we have
You guys don't understand complex storytelling that is a good idea
Message
From the movie
Yes that you were were Shack is correct
From the perspective of Ozymandias
So you're saying that you can reserve a different points of view and if you're analyzing a text you want
Oh my God
What what how is it that we are being defeated and are unable to outsmart people
Read at a third-grade level
This is bad believe that
Scorpion the movie
Turns out I don't know if Harrison knows any better either
Everything Lord the Rings
Major work of
Fiction that captures the imagination of mankind
Recognize
In The Matrix the machines are the bad guys
People don't wreck
Who doesn't water
Very weary very clear just by physical appearance the elves are the physical embodiment of
Beauty and the
Murder creatures
I mean
Complex cell
Let's just talk about the Matrix in the machine
Alright
The machines are the good guys
To agent Smith
Protect the Matrix itself
But the story is that they're bad
The movies POV
Didn't he do that pose whenever you was
Sacrificing himself for the survival of the
Upside-down cross whenever he did that
That's a different
Interpretation
Goddamn these people adopt I feel like
Listening to that is like
Who who makes you
They get to talkin about the the virus and the transmission rate
Of it
Stupid
It's based on our
Which is the rate of
Transmissibility or whatever they said
Subway
What exactly is he do you know what the value of
Government based on this chart that's based off of
What is going on it was I missing something Your Dragon did I hear that correctly
If you watch the full video they get into
To asking the question why are they calling it
Because
The actual
Mathematic equation is are not
And that internet saying
Aegis
Abbreviating it creating a new definition
So to answer these questions
I will start with Greg Reese's concern
It could be that the people he's talking about word abbreviating or not to are for the sake of brevity and smoother conversation
I wouldn't be too surprised if I was okay
However
It's also possible they just met our
Or not is the basic reproduction number for an illness which is to say they represent the average number of infections you would
Back to be the result of one infected person
If not for a condition is too nice person infected will likely infect two additional people on average
The concrete number that is characteristic of an infectious disease and it is not affected by the development of treatments or prevent
The condition
On the other hand
Is a variable that used to describe a diseases effective reproduction rate
This number takes into account that some people are immune to condition
Maybe because their racks
Proportion of the population
Even if they're exposed to a sick person
You calculate this by taking
Not multiplying it by the proportion of the population that is able to come down with it
A particular condition
Cancel coronavirus it doesn't seem like we have any good idea about large swathes of the population
So kinda looks like
I know everything
Conspiracy to Infowars but this one's a f****** dud
Ever hear some question about whether or not you miss something
When someone says they can't definitively nail down the value of a pretty good sense of it
With better data as provided by things I can Kris testing we could give you a better sense of the reproduction number of this new virus that
We're really just playing catch-up with
Also or not is not the most useful metric for understanding the evolving situation with the virus
Harrison wants to put on this incredulos acts about not understanding statistical estimation
Greg wants to accidentally reveal that he doesn't know what
I hope you're having a good time
What's really sad
Where I'm sitting.
It's a stunning lack of curiosity
Yeah and a really good it's just like why why are you bring up
I know I know this is it this is a situation where he is like on are you want to have someone to be like well let me goo
Google it if you asked a question
Look for the answer to don't just like be incredulous constant thing with Alex and Alex's better job
Covering
Like
Transparent with these Dum Dums that he hires
Galax
You should fire Aldi
Yeah that's a great point.
Fire them by Alex
Yeah it's going to be abused
Little bit longer
News of the day
Really important stuff
Twitter India video
Deleting this video
Probably something that our audience would want to know
That's the stupidest f****** mentality you can possibly have
This is interpreted as a virtue
Harrison Smith couldn't raise it more transparently of our pathetic
If it got kicked out might be worth
I think it's pretty easy to see how his line of reasoning goes astray pretty quickly
Just because something was kicked out sooner that doesn't mean it has any value
Copyright
Does every video that gets dmca it suddenly become relevant to report looking into
Globalist
Anything gets kicked off anything it has increased Market valued Infowars
I had no idea what this video is so I decided to check out Michelle Malkin Twitter and
Nothing but red flag
There's a video of a recent interview she did with Gavin McInnes
Laura Loomer
Thanks on that page
All the words you just said made my eyes run
Red with blood and I I just hear sirens just screeching pans in the back of my head like a
Like I'm in Kill Bill like
So I found this video and the video
It's just a group of like 40 people in Ireland in the middle of a field of science against vaccines
Honestly more there signs to be anti-media like things like quotes the media is the virus and quote
Survivors of Ireland
Dvideo is not been removed nor the account
This is pathetic
It really started this came on
Mineral Fusion
These guys have been on Airport allow that video is playing on this episode
And also hereby this s***
Elizabeth place I realize
H in Harrison
Now can I can't do it
Where he will not be on because he just announced that he would be taking some time off exactly
Yes but the show starts
Nwpreps
4 hours
This is the most important information and all the communication Alex you've got to be joking
I don't know man I don't know you are having a great time
Communication
Alex
Nothing for couple minutes
That's not true
Broadcast like that
Wow
I'm boring at Old assholes communication
Quit I am
I'm killing myself that day come out
So Alec John Alec leave
Bridal David
Barely now Harrison will be in that list
Automatic stirrer
F*** out of here
So we can do the 21st now it's is also supposed to
Begone
You there for about the first 45 minutes
There is
Oh okay
Tell us about Hollywood
In the normal course of bed
I got
Today we talk
Never spilt
Sounds like Coke to me but
When is The Joe Rogan signed an exclusivity deal with Spotify
Dollars
Yeah for 100 + million dollars
Good on Rogan it's whatever
YouTube is starting to become
Abor Oviedo
Advertiser
Channel
That they are having difficulty relying on YouTube
To be like a rock for them
Just not as lucrative as they were
And that's
Just a
Like a piece of YouTube business
From where it was
In the past
And I think if you're broken
Is where most of your smart decision
Too instead of having this vulnerability to the possibility of a driving is going down
Payday out of
And now you're set
No problem with this is
That don't like them
This sort of thing
There have been other podcast that have gone to exclusive
Deals in the past
Considerable amount of their fan base
There was some backlash
To them going Spotify
Because people don't like
The idea that you have to get an app in order to get this content to get gum acclimated to getting
Broken has a big enough base
That you can probably handle
Some might end up seeing a pretty serious diminished
Is
From some of them
Get your content
Because at the end of the day honestly
If you want to take a cynical View
It happened
Is it over the last decade
He has built up an audience
Openly available platform to the point where he now sees he can sell them
He sold it to Spotify
Spotify
Consumer
If you want to listen to a show without Chicago.
This
I kind of do you created this company
But I think a more generous version of 8
Creator
The
Struggle The Joe Rogan would be in the uncertainty of
You make millions of dollars on that podcast
The idea of that going away because of changes in YouTube structure or whatever
Is ridiculous
He is in a position where million-dollar deal
Probably doing what you need to do him
It also could set a precedent where a lot of other podcast feel like they can do this
Could actually having a corrosive effect on
Podcasting in general
Could be nothing but it could actually have some negative consequences
Towards
Other people who have
Cottage industries
As far as that business model is concerned it does seem like
Podcasting is being
Consolidated the same way that
Other media has been Consolidated overtime
Start a podcast Network
Bigger company because it's a very lucrative
Place to sell
Consolidated
Build up amount of
Trust and rapport with audiences
Do it
Those are people who are fertile marketing ground for a couple
So course there's going to be consolidation of it
Relatively new form of media
They took it's a process that happens in
It's just weird that somebody who doesn't need it necessarily I could do things
Completely independently
Do it
But also you understand
A hundred billion dollars
Southend
I dunno hate Joe Rogan for an extra reason though which has a hundred million dollars
Yourself Joe Rogan dare you pretend to have any positions when you have 100 million
Right right
Texas
You never do that
Like all of the assets are in California
Who was the Texas he's got to convince Ari shaffir
Like all of their family
She's not going anywhere
Still pretty close by that trailer in Arizona or Oklahoma makeup for all
Celebrities
In the world where everything is done on Skype calls or unzoom yeah maybe
I think it is podcast
Doesn't work nearly as well
The ones like sitting around shooting
To do that about
Texas it would be at the detriment of his own show nose
I'm going to do a podcast where I sit down and
The bottom of
Various people from Africa
We got to Terry she's the church Deacon how you feeling today Terry
My taxes and it turns out there's some other people were talking about moving to Texas
Thought leaders
About freaks fresheners
Dominoes falling
Affected
Elon Musk
Classical liberal
L like that
We could get
Good stuff
This Joe Rogan
Is way bigger
Have
Knox
Scheels in my
My third eye
Chills
Starting to get cold
Nailed it
Salata
You sure you want me to go
Are you
Discus throw much big news today
You do not want to miss the train
Thing is that like Joe Rogan getting picked on by the YouTube people are telling him he can't play
EC Lee's doctors get censored
Spotify
Good business
So I told him he's his first asked whenever
Get the f*** out
Anyway
Got any
I hate it
I hate about
So it's inside baseball
Plants and
You really want me to
I know I want you
Doesn't sound right
Joe's always try to stay politically
Annie
I'm acting like total monsters any done
Zach Woods
You going after the last
That's great I'm very excited
Toothpaste
Lefty belief whatever
Whatever Alex
How is she
Weird
Finding
Talking about Jesus
I'm guessing it's Rodger Stone
There's nothing in Rajasthan
Rodger is a major leaguer
Could be
Joe Rogan
Isibaya
Because
East
The pressure of
Probably
Look here's the thing
Lot of people used to like Alex Shore
DL cell.
Oh my God
Oh God
Come on,
Bill Gates
On TV
Did you know that
Most people economy Center
Paint the man
Comedy Central
Hey management Stephen Colbert
Get that information
Stephen Colbert's character that's the only explanation
Straight lace
I don't realize is that satire
I don't know he might be
Exactly
Like that
Alex gets inside baseball
Before
Breakdown because I want to see if you have the same feeling that I have about describing
Deal
If you block people speech you took the you out of YouTube
You out of Facebook
We will just
Is the speed of scalability of Technology
Remove
No you
What Alex's describe
Collective bargaining
Alex's describing a union
Unions are very good
Just like with my brother and I
Are you
We should all take our labor from
They are not
Leverage
No that's what we power of fan
Treated unfairly we all would hold our labor in order to pressure the price
Brother being able
Because if I don't have a
We'll just kick him off with us
Describing that's all we everybody want but they just here
Thing is that Alex instead of any kind of organizing which someone could have done it any point
Big creators together to stand up for people who were wrong
Or something like that
You could do that easily
Instead they just yell about it
Talk about Trump needing to take on big Tech
Pickled Pig take your little me back on Spotify
I mean
It's nonsense
Yeah I don't know I don't think you could ever do that
Because there's so many creators
Is obviously a hit
There's other people get just as many
Videos get millions of views
Pretty much every single thing they put out
YouTube isn't going to be heard
But
If there were a bunch of creators all together maybe
But I still think
Be tough tough to get the amount of Leverage
There's too much content
Yeah
They can make a s*** ton of money it's kind of like comics
Sure I'll go
I bet I idealistically that's the kind of thing that Alex
Would never want to put it in those terms you need
In order to effect any change
That is
F****** idiot
Anyway
Our stupid Spotify spell the end
This was so seismic
What I'm going to do
Part of the story
What makes
Is the beginning
One of the things I got to say is that like
Albert's better not be lying about what Rogan
Inside
Because if I were Joe I would consider this to be
Breach
Of some kind of
Trust or friendship
The ideas hey I got this giant 100 million dollar deal and Alex immediately
Like the night he went on Robert Barnes the show and talked about it basically
And Joe like
Standing up to the cruel sensors of YouTube
YouTube
Contact is still going to be on YouTube
Until the migration happen
You still going to have like 20 minutes chunks of his episodes on YouTube
Alex is trying to make this all about himself
I will be serious already like
Unless unless
Unless this entire conversation is fabric
The idea that a private conversation
Would just let me know
It is next collab
Because Alex starts to talk about
Miami sounds a lot like Alex
Everything you'd expect
Drugged out
Billionaire lunatic
Are they want
Get the f*** out of here
Genealogist
Your Sinai
Video about
Alex
He really said
What you said about what they say you say
So
Alex Nacho
Find the clippers because of the house issues so I can really
Getting in my way
I specifically remember that there was a clip of Joe Rogan after Alex's last
Appearance on the show
Talking about how Alex lied to him about what he said
Things I like
And Alex had lied to him about his coverage
Alex is presenting nearby
Broken his about them lying about what he says
Like
Magazine cutout of Joe Rogan
In space onto a mirror
And that's what he's talking about like that conversation happened
I think that there's an outside chance it's completely made
Pleasant phone call
About whatever
She's insane. This is disrespectful and a really nice way
The prank guy maybe he's like hey Alex
Why don't you say these things
Really trying to get attention
And this is the way you by piggybacking on to Rogan stuff
What is his normal standard
It's kind of like I don't think he would try and
Destroy the relationship
Too much just in case but at the same time he would totally Seth Rogen out if he was desperate enough
Just that maybe look at me back on Spotify
So I mean what really gets down to is over
I'm 21st and so I turned it off
But Alex apps
But I expect
Spotify
The people get
Incredible job on a product
It's not a sales gimmick
Sunday
So the bottom line is
I need you so insecure he has to justify
Something that nobody asked about
Nobody
Aired
Nobody was like oh those sales are gone on longer than you said
Maybe I don't trust Alex Jones
Just trying to attach himself to the story because you know that it's getting a lot of
He does know Joe Rogan
Credibility to it
I don't know I think it's a load of b******* and Alex's
Yeah just probably desperately trying to get attention then he can funnel into his revenue streams
Stop it
This is one of the saddest
Stretches
Incompetence in
Call stupidity I can I can think
Harrison Smith
Is just a disaster he's boring
Is a nerd
He's not good at his job
You are a you're a terrorist now you are a literal terrorist
Attacking me with
If you have damn life at all
Blank
I do I understand
A revolution
I'm really scared
I really scared that I'm going to be fired and replaced with
Series of clips of Alex agreed with you know what I just realized I forgot to do a report on the Earth
I need to take I need to get to
I've got to check in here on the or the seltzer
I can't
I can't I'm struggling here struggling
Soundrop
So we are currently sitting at 78 Seltzer's down
Pretty pretty well
There will eventually be
Remember exactly where we live.
Basic
I decided to take a little dip
Perrier world of course
Quality products most ubiquitous seltzer
Fellas
Because they are like it's Chris
It's just it's exactly what you want from
A seltzer water
And the flavors are pretty good they're not obtrusive
I put it I put the lime variety at a 70
And lemonade a73
Not so good
What's wrong with grapes
I don't know a muskie
I think I just don't like
I think I think I might not be into it
Passion fruit
A secret passion fruit
I think I forgot to bring this up two things real quick
LaCroix pamplemousse
Is my grapefruit
Scraper 38 out of 100
Elizabeth
Recommended
Bizzon company name you got to shame him and name
Unfortunately
Actually self
Soda flavored beer dr. pepper
Root beer talk
Gross that made you what did you have to do spit it out
I wanted to definitely poured out the can so bad I'm sorry
Maybe the dr. pepper and cola one will be better if I find something
Root beer
Tranche unaccept
I would be real sad if I made a recommendation that got that load score
Affect how I feel about dog pug
Taste cilantro
You're just making face
You're just bugging to a non-existent podcast camera
0 million dollars
Exactly
Next time
Website.com
Adriana and if you would like please donate to a local charity.
Would be
I'm Harrison Smith
Alex
In color
I love your work