Important
Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for its knowledge by now it's like I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Need money
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
But sit around and talk a little bit about Alex
Jordan Jordan
What's up
On this one
Don't know
Are couches been Savage by all kinds of small dogs
We got to get a new couch
What type of sense then they delivered it
I supposed to come in
He said it came at 8:30
And neither you nor I are
No job on the horizon
Add any coffee whatsoever yet
No it was an insanely we got into one of those fights
Just like the super dark
And then that's why I was out of control cuz we're both exhausted
Couch looks great also it didn't come with two of the cushion so it's now
Zig-zag pattern
Is there a good morning
In the afternoon
I guess my brakes
The last couple days has definitely been
Preparing for an episode that we're not doing today
Episode for today
Talk about Alex Jones
But I Was preparing for a Bill Cooper episode
And something happened in that episode
That I was marching around the apartment like fingers up in the air kind of celebratory
Is I heard something in episode that I never would have expected
I don't want to be teasing
And you'll understand as soon as that happens
Navigate to Rosauers
Jordan
You know what you
20 second 20 episode 20
Into that today
Tamar Friday episode for sure
Before we do this
According to
So first and Ruel
I'm a policy wonk
Andrew
I'd like to try news last initials one possible that Mike
Just might
Jeff no last name to
Alright
Seriously
Salley SC
You're an alcoholic
Text Derek
I'm a policy wonk donate it on elevated level appreciate that very much
Do Kristen p
Democrat
Heroin
Usually large
Local charity in your area that help
I'm trying to find different ways to say a Jordan I like it I like it was not as good as its
Could have been
So Jordan out of time for the entire episode
My life
Call man
I forgot
I forgot the name of the first newest episode
Jordan
I wanted to get weird with it
So I was at the store not too long ago and I saw
I think it's the brand okay
There was orange cream and strawberry cream
Trash
What did I do with my life
Cross my mind all the time
When I'm dancing
That is so highly rated
The pieces of a good is that there was a sort of vanilla.
Is an orange thing with a vanilla tames or strawberry with a vanilla
Slayer
Just doesn't work there there's something wrong with the flavors are bad
Lemoncello's just a much better balanced vanilla offenses
Sometimes it's the execution not the
Podcast
Not terrible I wanted more out of
22nd
Fun things to talk about but that shows
It's a lot of rambling the devil and what have you
The devil is everywhere
Play last episode
Friday's episode
This is from May 21st Thursday
Joe Rogan
And his plans to go after the last
You really want me to tell people that I want you
Joe's always try to stay politically neutral
Are you trying to get along with the last
Acting like total monsters any done
He doesn't care what they do he's coming
So this episode came out
Over the weekend
Rogan released an episode
David pakman
Noted left-wing YouTube
Episode
That was very cordial and very nice
It also included Joe sings this
And this is up
Important
Crazy videos
Where he was
YouTube
A great company
The great deal
Partnership
As opposed to
Company
Stop
YouTube sensors
Do that
Envy
Their position
So you can get them to talk about
YouTube
Companies by themselves
Has a reasonable thoughts about Joe Rogan
B 101 the conversation
Baby was
You know I do not I don't think that it's great that YouTube
So now it's like he's on the warpath that's a really shity friend
Terrible terrible person
So I was listening to this episode
Episode
Like to his credit I guess
Cuz I'm I can watch these things critically
He does they like
No one should listen to me
I don't know what to talk about
Like I don't want
Shows about Michael I am a racist
You you know what you said
People confuse do
Not like you for it or liking for it
Banana on news radio
Don't listen to my political
Yeah I think some people do still take him seriously
Deconstruct
Joe says not to take him seriously
I don't respond
A couple things
Worth pointing out
So here's the first one where Joe
Wanderers
About Bill Gates
When you go back in
Bill Gates
I talked in 2000
Teen talking about
Everybody out
Are there in 5 years
Teresa
Nobody listen
How crazy is it that people are now Bill Gates's the bad guy
Hosting
Insane conspiracies about
Bill Gates
Help me help me
I know
I have a gas
Freak
Says the devil
Weirdest memes
I know a guy with a bullhorn
Cultural meme
Who says that
Bill Gates
This
Philanthropic
Who's literally like
Africa
Education
Billions of dollars on
Allsorts
So good also
This is so Illuminating
Because I'm the one
Freezing it that way
How can you make Bill Gates the bad guy talk to your friend
You support realize that's Alex's biggest
You don't even know I like this guy he's a friend of mine
Great
But recognize that a lot of things
Is
Very strongly pushing
Into the mainstream consciousness
I am so that's pretty sad one of my least favorite
The things that make me so infuriating as it is when people
Diagnose the correct problem
That we all know how it happened
Everyone knows
Like I like
Alright his creator
And because it's easier to do that but everybody knows
And take it outside
And larger one world government a vaccination communities
Have demonized a long time in the right-wing is picking up on that and amplifying
They might not have
Recognizing
Charlie conspiracy
Here's the last clip
From Rogan
This one really I love because
Rogan
How I like a
In Alicante
It's no good but there's like a profit motive in vaccines right bye-bye
GoPro
So what is actually supporting is like public subsidization
Yes nice yes
Write to a brick wall
There is profit
What's the problem
When someone looks
Conspiracy
Say something like
You can't say
How much
Is a
I wish there was none
I wish
Making them just
Ferraris
Everything where people do it
Seems to require
You know it's funny
Maybe
Be
Angry
Make money
They're also
Angry because
Where Senegal
And we won
Okay they're making
Money
Would it be possible
Basketball
People more
Or is he
Got more
More money
Problem
Human Nature
Boreal
Give me the reality
Not vaccinating
And having way more people to
Is Roy Moore profit
That's a good point is it
Be alright
Oh yeah
Haha
Episode breakdown about
Really pretty
Alex completely lied
About that
Hey Alex insane crazy s*** about our conversation
Like that's embarrassing that's really bad
I can't I can't find a way
His reaction to that to make sense to me because he's a good old man
That constitutes a massive betrayal
Twisted it changed it and ruined it and turned it into a propaganda
Without my knowledge
Try to piggyback a story and make it about himself
Borderline sociopath
Well I don't know right to make up their boundaries as they see the broken doesn't season
Complete breach of trust than that works right
It seems like
You got to expect you at work
Not expect after saying like how did Bill Gates become the bad guy you build toilets
We're going to get to the 22nd
But there's another thing that I came across that I felt needed to be talked about
Of the War Room
Not a full episode but a clip
Owen Shroyer put out
I just want to put this down on wax as it were putting stuff like
Out into the world
Wow
So that's probably bad take I will
I didn't do this and you shouldn't do it
Still negative consequences format
People like to get sick
Like yes
Lakewood View
Like I understand they're still even like some Randomness with the doorknob
Like would you you know you could do that a possibility
Picture Exchange
Bodily fluids
With someone who has tested positive is definitely contagious
Express
Real lame
Right to reopen stuff and what have you
Hear about how would it really is
Is a rally to spread the virus
Because
Then what they can do is they can say that we're trying to spread the virus
No one gets it
It'll all blow up in the media space
This is really bad really stupid
I'm exhausted
Fake fake fake fake fake fake
I remember brevity being the soul of wit and I guess I was wrong
Yeah yeah
But I think things like really bad
If you're wrong
I think that if people die
These rallies or
Or gory things it kind of makes it look like you're
Encouraging
That might have been a part of leading to their
Being infected and getting sick and dying so
First of all even if that was like
You know
A joke
It's not a good joke
No I can I can separate myself and be like
No
I mean they might as well
At this point
String somebody up in brno holes Farm
The person inside of you guys are sacrificing yourselves
Or something I don't know why
It's it's weird because
It doesn't feel exactly like that because of the like randomness
You're not Randomness but you know you could go to all of the rallies and not get sick
It is possible
You can tell yourself that there isn't a risk
I don't know I don't know
Each time when the bombs fell there was a guy who lived through two nuclear bombs
I didn't know that
You can
You can do all kinds of s*** but I'm not going to know I understand
Taking risks
So we get to the 22nd
Rogan's rebuttal and Owen City jokes
Tom and Jerry about that except
Remember that
Yeah so we can do the 22nd and here we jump
And that is
Pastors
America are fighting back
Great
The closure
We have
The beginning of the
Pastors
6 days
Ninja Turtle martial law lockdown
You under the First Amendment have no law have no right
Tutuapp
Open
Congress shall make no law
Tablespoon of religion
Exercise
The first word
What's a government form
By the people was established
What
Congress
Telmate
No law
You realize that was
Adidon
Congress
Shall make no law
Show me no law
Moses up on the mountain
Shall make no law
Congress
She'll make no law
Congress Moses didn't really make the laws
Fake fake fake
Bushman
Sarah
I wonder if it any point in that constant repetition of saying Congress shall not
Nothing to do with any of this at all borders or business closures Congress
I shall make no law
The only person who's walking into dicey constitutional territory right now is Trump when he threatens to override the
State Governors don't go wrong with what he wants
Imperia violation of the Tenth Amendment
Do bunch of nonsense illegally can't make the governor's open up everything it's all just posturing and
Yelling to his basin
Crooked dangerous embarrassment
He's Mister states rights and he's supposed to be a constitutional scholar
Don't make sense
If the Constitution says the Congress shall not make a law about religion or prohibiting the free exercise
Bring up when Congress isn't making
General you know like when it says Congress is kind of more just saying like everybody shall make no
Any group of people is really a congress
Do you notice something that last clip that was a little bit weird
About Alex's phrasing
I caught that the first time around 2 I got real worried
Words of the government established
The Rebellion
We the People
What about the articles
The confederation
Government the first word
Cannot make any laws or have no regulations
Bill of Rights
Embarrassing
What is bad the Declaration of Independence begins We the People
And that is not true
Anywhere the Declaration of Independence
What Alex quote
And to assume among the powers of the Earth been separated
A decent respect to the opinions of mankind requires that they should declare the causes which impel them to the separation
The beginning of the Declaration of Independence
King Richard shall make no law restricting
The people is the preamble to the Constitution
The difference between constitutional Declaration of Independence
American Patriot
Who started all this stuff
Constitution
Soon as we got ourselves a country going we're all like alright let's start with a
I got to do something
Union
Guides
The country
It starts with Article 1
Which lays out the structure of the legislative branch
The news article 24 the executive
There's seven articles and total the original document for the Amendments ever added
Alex doesn't know that much about the Constitution or American history
Scary whenever
Disagrees with you he's not really interested
You just wants to fight
And the Amendments of the enumeration of things that the government can't do
And would give him Justice
Application to the government
Anyone with the familiarity with US Government like I don't know what say you took a class in high school on it
No idea
Is a whole thing as a charade
Everything is b*******
People most likely
Karaokanta
Pull it out and put it up in Hugo
I don't remember that being there at all
So Alex
The beginning of this episode is about
Churches to be on essential
Is mad about that cuz
He thinks that they want to end religion
And make us all worship estate
Why has
Europe
The Europe
Do you ask
The longest
Because it's the most essential
Sociology psychology and biology textbook
Religion is mental illness
Religion of the state
Humanism
Process
I don't like it either
This is
Prime movement
Prime
The end
You're right either believe in God or not believe in God
So in terms of opening up
Church isn't a difference of opinion on the question
Community
Reverend itself could not be the focus
Pics of the question
Because the people themselves
Are the church
People are essential important but not essential
As long as there's a virus spreading that's killing people it's more important to protecting them and then to go to a building
He cites other folks like Pastor David yule
Who said
What are the essentials God would ask for the church
Ultra series called Essentials and guess what
Wasn't
Church is a healthy Church
Who are their pastors Zack esswein new said quote
We don't prove our faith by defying orders the hand of another
We prove our faith by denying ourselves
So that we can clear the throat of a neighbor who can't breathe
I mean even though even their own f****** books as a anywhere men Gather in my name I am with ever whatever it is
Gather digital exactly
Christian Community believes it's at the suspension of in-person surfaces is appropriate
The guardian reported in early April about Sacramento
Search the didn't take warning seriously at least 71
Headlight March NBC News reported on an Arkansas
And the result was at least 30 catching Coronavirus
Including a pastor and his wife
The pastor made a statement
Maybe you assume that it couldn't happen to you just like I did
Please adhere to the social instructions that you receive in locally and nationally
Another was Bishop Gerald o Glenn from Richmond Virginia
He was defiant about continuing to hold Services quote unless I'm in jail or the hospital
He said quote I am essential I'm a preacher I talked
The god
His wife also tested positive and it's hard to imagine that there aren't some other churchgoers who have as well
Granddaughter said it becomes very real to you
I just begged people to understand the severity
It's about everyone around us
They're more stories like this but I think you get the point and they're all about the same
We will not take the risk seriously then when the consequences come they say I should have listened please take this seriously
The goal is to hopefully never end up in a position where you have to tell people to not be like you and to take the situation
Seriously
That's what these people whose lives are affected by the virus are trying to communicate to the rest of us
It would be wise to heed their words
I think everything that I've read
Do even like even most
Recent polls
The overwhelming majority even among Christians even among Republicans even among everybody is
Let's stay inside
Get through this s***
But the symbols
From every possible journalistic Outlet
These
He was protesting
Steel like
Holyshit the entire right-wing is
A small vocal minority that keeps dying every bit of press they possibly can
Consistent polling is showing people not wanting to rush
Yeah
Witches mark
Which is why of course they elected people who are screaming at them that it's time to reopen
The reasons why churches will be a serious Vector for virus transmission is pretty clear about it for a second
There's an almost ritualize environment of shaking hands of hugging and eating
Universal a donation basket
Who sings could be a big problem
I understand and I empathize with the people for whom going to church of the Cornerstone of their lives
People with physical Church of the center of their social and emotional
I would never want to minimize that and I do want to respect it but at the same time
When they're such serious Stakes involved are other ways the spirituality
And religion of your choice
Can still be practice
I really enjoy this quote from Reverend deals op-ed
Virus has not cancelled worship but it changed the way we worship
The New Normal or at least for the moment may put more emphasis on our personal relationship to our God
And how each one of us chooses to work
Maybe just maybe The New Normal will be a positive thing
Batman
Beautiful sentiment
Constanta through them and they don't have any effect on
What supposed to be the Cornerstone which is our own
Connection with the divine
Christianity
To wear masks and not go to church for a little bit
Christianity is not a religion
It's never survived anything like this
Most of what Alex's is getting on about
Because he has an interview on the show
Who does went viral for tearing up a cease-and-desist order
Play uncomfortable
Possibly
I don't know enough about that preacher I don't care
Astorian
That's a bummer
Non-essential
Because
Refused to close
Two Shoes watching TV
I don't know but what he talked about in Europe necessarily but one in the USA
I'm not positive
Two shoes and watches TV but fortunately it is a real story
At least as they're currently available
The first Pentecostal Church in Holly Springs Mississippi
Divide local stay-at-home orders and set fire to it and left a message
Bet you stay home now you Hypocrites spelled hypokrites
Was that tough misspelling
There's some investigation needs to be done to nail down the culprit and all that but it looks like this
If that's what it turns out to be
Counterproductive to the aims of the potential
I like the arsonist motivated by
Churches going to stop over like renting out another space
It's an act
Pointless wrong
Probably counterproductive
It's interesting to think about this though and compared to the other instances of crimes like this and how Alex response to them
Whenever there's an incident of someone sprain swastikas on a Jewish person
Any of that sort of hate crime
How to immediately and without proof that the whole thing is fake
Sub leftist spray-painted the swastika in order to make it look like there's a actual knob he's around
Haven't caught the culprit
We just had some graffiti that indicates
The first because the church's Define stay-at-home order
Because this incident works for Alex's
How much does a question this at all
Consideration
You should be speculating about the possibility
Unless that message
The speculation and conspiracy doesn't apply in cases like this because they don't need to
Speculation and conspiracy for Alex or tools
Of right-wing gun and white supremacist apology
And to be clear I'm not saying
I don't think it is a mostly just pointing out how
Instances how to study Alex dance
Pay attention to the way he engages in similar stories that Target different groups
Pay attention to that
Immensely
The s*** out of me
Why what
Come on man.
I know this is just going to make more people false flags are a real thing
Hey Siri
Investigation
Okay well I just I just don't use your mind
More just because
Regardless of how it
The church and the church goers and all of us are in this together
They're not
They're not a problem
The problem is how they got to where they are
We need to focus on
The propaganda and who's doing all of this and who's pushing this way
Why are you why would you bother with it with that that's insane
It only serves to hurt
The possibility of of
Some sort of understanding and better pass forward
Here's here's why I think he's talking about it
Situation
Yep okay
He tells a story about going on a walk and seeing a white guy in a
Like a building under construction
What no
What is the difference between the two stories
He's using inoculate himself from a lot of the racism
How's the position
He's going to express
And I will say this
Upright story
I do believe it's true
But you he's founded Alex inside a new video
I would say that this is not good
It's not hard hitting
Show coming up I've got
The footage
We just pulled up in the park
In the middle of the parkway
In the middle of a park over the curb
Sabella Park
Parking lot
Billionaire Superstars
Messing with the police that's really asking for it
Whatever
Hit a patch of grass next to some train tracks
When the police say why they're talking to him
Drug activity
This is just part of propaganda
It's really important for Alex to make excuses for inform conspiracies about any incidents that appear to be racially motivated by
Violent scary
Because his entire worldview centers around White victimhood
The actual killing looks pretty bad
That way pretending to be opposed to The Killing
But at the same time it'll really condemn it for what it appears to be
What are you doing
This is a group of a deficient that means he probably
Obviously
The only thing that's the game is being played here
And again this is almost the perfect case study analysis racism
What do you want to understand
Covers
We're two white men chase down an unarmed black man
And how we covered the case of Kate steinle
The gun rack in a rag
When white people are the victims is an anti-white hate crime
When white people are the perpetrator
The victim wasn't so great themselves they probably had it coming
This is how this works yet again it's about the differences
You compare things that are
You know hey Will your coverage goes this way one time
Why is that really only one explanation does not matter
The
Circumstances
Surrounding
Don't murder people
That seems very simple
I don't understand why you need to add other like on well
Hold on this person I don't know if you know this
So a pack of gum one time
Oh well nevermind
Of course
He was in a house
Precedes and Alex doing is essentially trying to Bill
Build a shity case as to why you shouldn't care
That much
About about arberys death
With jogging pants
Calling with marijuana
They didn't arresting
Because they were politically correct
So then months later
He takes them out
People go to stopping who the f*** are you
Holyshit
Kind of sounds like you are
Neighborhood
With a hood over his head
Bootleggers robber outfit
You asked me how do I do song
Weather in Blackfoot Idaho
They got that dumb stupid
So the police in 2017 didn't catch arbery with marijuana
Allow them to search his car and suspect
Matter at all in terms of the bigger conversation that's being had here
I was literally says that weed to be decriminalized yet he's here using a lie about the police catching Arbor with weed painted picture
Is not that big a deal
Also the argument let's citizen's arrest
Rules about the use of force in terms of putting someone under citizen's arrest
Anyone could make the argument that the Justified lethal Force
Outback in love for Alex make that argument especially in court
That would be fun
The whole story Alex's telling about seeing a white person in a hoodie on his morning hike or whatever it's absolutely a fakes
Story has just concocted to say horrible things about looks like a thug
Alex gives himself permission to make these very clearly racially coded attacks on a murder victim by fabricating person
But he's also applying these labels to
Person
Really
You know there
I don't have anything to do
From where I'm sitting is
What do you know that that would be too explicit
He probably doesn't want to deal with the consequences of expressing his opinion
It's insane
I wouldn't
I would do this
No matter what like okay
Let's do this
Do the opposite situation
There is a white dude dressed in Army fatigues carrying gun
Who has who is
Killed for looking like a terror
And then we find out he's got a previous conviction for domestic violence and yada yada yada and all that s***
That doesn't mean I want I'm okay or it's not a tragedy that he got murdered
Still a f****** murder
Right
Disgusting an awful and you should just be able to
Say
Murdered
For being black
Rihanna anti honest way
Can't do
Compelling
Sort of reports on it alongside another story
Where black you
Beat up
Really related at all
Covering that story to talk about
Story
Black people white people
Right
Shawn Mendes
But it's okay cuz they're white
Weird
Nothing like
Cuz I can't
How's your parents while you're off having fun you're going to be there too
What
What is happening
Door
YouTube videos explained
Picture of the devil
So I don't I don't know what Alex is trying to prove here although that is a facetious babe I know exactly what he's trying to do
This story is about a twenty-year-old the history of unspecified mental illness Westwood Nursing Center
It's awful and I'm not making excuses for this kind of thing it's never okay for someone to assault another person
It does appear that the issues that are relevant to
Consider
The first is the history of mental illness there was a reason
The second is how much of that history was the staff of the hospital
Also in the video the man is clearly saying this guy was in his bed
So it's unclear if it's appropriate to describe a racial motivation
For this beating
A very well may be the case that this guy wasn't as bad knee was just mad at white people that's possible
I'm not sure I guess
Still alive
And the attackers facing charges for the beat
There are tons of stories in the media you can find about this case
If it's black guy beating up white guy
I was just telling the story the way he is
Because he feels that this is a trump card Ahmad arbery killing was racially motivated
I find that offensive
Whatever the case is literally nothing to do
Every situation
Also you can just hear an Alex's voice how much more passionate he is about a story like that
Ideas of persecution
Where he feels the most comfortable which is really f***** up
Beat that white ho
What it is
Very much amplifying the brutality one because he likes the boot
That's just the brutality cell
Yeah exactly because
He is making sure that you think
Look
Look at how brutal this black person
Violent
Well hey they were protect
Hayward community
He got
Till he played in
And it's a shame I wish I wish
Peter Peter
Come on
The show and Alex interviews that creature ripped at the cease-and-desist order
St Pete I don't care about that interview
So after that Alex
Weird man I don't know if this is the effect of this guy praying on Aaron Alex getting real spiritual
He said some things I think are f***** up
Get on my knees
You can actually see everything going on in the universe
Plugging directly in
Hey this is all right
How is this electoral college
Show me safety on site
Yeah it's good this is
God has given him
Listen
Neutral context
You know everybody wants a little little add something to their
Although I don't really understand the Constitution would think that y'all about all the time I have no idea what Civics are
But I'm a psychic
Not just for news that would be okay on like a reality TV show
People on the planet
I don't think I've heard anybody on
The Amazing Race
Hey don't worry about this I know you're angry right now
I can see the next
Clue we're skipping this s***. The answers to the tribal council's in the future
I can predict voting
God
We were granted mean
That's weird
Another Power
Wheat
Really see what this looks like
Literally stare the minds of the enemy
You're going to do it
Pics of the universe
You're not saying
So
Alex Jones
Reluctant telepath
God is 462 telepathy
I just wish you was like a fifteenth-century monk who could just plan to wait with a cat-o'-nine-tails that would be so much easier
That's what he wants
Duke
Forcing himself to
Experience
Interpreting
I don't know if that's accurate but I just wish I couldn't see what the enemy
Ticket to Read
The most powerful telepath in the world
Where's the
This is where it all gets really funny
When you look at people
Rockefeller
Have sold their soul
Turn themselves over
They had
Giving up
Humanity
Connected to something is dead.
And that's all
Lincoln news
Run around
Conventional
Their special on their powerful
They run around a special and Powerful telepathic
Another Bill Gates how are you doing
Stupid
Psychic powers
Office episode give us a glimpse into the future
Mary Claire
This way
Because
We had to vent
God doesn't
When the whole game
Up to you God gives it to you
I'll say this now
Eliza Taylor
B24
Caramel monsters up
The harvill
Kobe Bryant
Tens of millions of washers to go knock on doors
PR
Everything
Can't get the justice department is our good people there.
Rolls up similar
Supposed to end
Scares is outside Global Force
Make them run
Consolidate power prior to the election
Unless he strong-armed his way into the next election
Probably
Point number one
If Trump loses
It's because everybody else cheated in the election results are illegitimate is brainwasher is going door-to-door
Mail-in ballots
Cheating
Number two
If Trump starts let's say jailing his political because he's consolidating
Although
He is consolidating power but it's mainly because he's getting rid of evil
To stop
Authoritarianism we must
The authoritarian
This is a good plan
Always walk
Play the clip of trump talking about how he's going to override the governor's if they don't open up
Churches
I'm going to do some unconstitutional
Galaxy 7 Anderson take on it
Need to do the right thing and allow these very important essential places
Efface to open
Right now
For this weekend
If they don't do it I will override the governor's
In America we need more prayer
Thank you very much
The Rebellion you should be really against that Alex
Celebrate
Ultimate executive power
Just like the Constitution says I should because
MX Player
This is a long clip
Okay
And it's cuz I wanted everyone to have a taste
What episode was
And I thought this was the most entertaining and also
Stretch
Alex play some techno music
And rants about the devil
This
Is
Nothing this is a f****** a killing
Free-will must be tested
Free will
You don't want to do
Consciousness that God to make perfect robot all day long
Carry out whatever task God wanted
Sextus robot created
They passed the test one day we'll stand
Buy supercomputer
Not done by mad scientist
That's not done by Larry Page or Sergey Brin
Orchestrated by the creator of the universe
Where we are now
Billy
Settings long
You said it was long
I think that's how this train goes
Imaginate
Omnipresent because you
Ancestors use omnipresent what
Dinner Faithfully.
Did we
From the very beginning
Wine Down
A hole with that you believe that you
What
What are we doing
Wasn't already it's real
Believe you were King believe you are the author of the universe
What's the potential for conscious
Sure
I'm so high
Transcendence but you rejected the very force that created you naturally
So because of that
Why they call you the Fallen
Without the wind
Call man
Music store
Humanity
Believe
Cut off the universe
You are a god
Georgia
Discussion
Dershowitz
Interview with the Sovereign citizen guy
I got this ticket
And I went to the court and I went to
I said
I'm not going to take you
And all the while playing underneath it is just some swelling godspeed You black Emperor music and God it would be so
So much better if it was a lie
Why you why you doing other than you enjoy talking over music
Like that's the only thing that is
Just being ran out of music
And then like 10 seconds later the outro music
Alan dershowitz
So
Stupid
That's pretty great
What I wanted
Why do feel
What episode is Alaska
And honestly like
I wasn't even going to cut that clip at all I was listening to it
The weather like
I'm falling asleep
Watco too long
You talked about how you doing
At the inauguration
Sure
And you get sent
How a little bit later and it's trouble
I was there on January 20th
Present
The secret technology that are suppressed
Truly are March the star
Speed Trump
You know right
Is it totally a true story
Sounds like a very true story
Without God
Haven't
So I don't believe that story
Restored the New York Times reporters Alex
Would they still growling problem
Miracle cures
Those eyes those technologies that were going to be revealed
So Alex complains
Do you want
Controller
Hydroxychloroquine
You in control
You turn CNN on
Don't say that
Sprouts
How's it going May 22nd
It looked at the fatality rates across six continents
The people who were taking hydroxychloroquine
Guardian article
Taking drugs with higher than among people who were not given up
Too good a cure
Taking the drugs died
If it were on hydroxychloroquine an antibiotic
Drugs with 1 and 11
This wasn't formal studies of there aren't variable controls in place of the differences of death rates may not be as big as those numbers
But the studies say allowing for these differences there was still higher mortality among
Those taking the drugs
More and more evidence is mounting that this is not a good drug
To be boosting
Covid treatment
Alex is still on that the hill
He's so desperate to defend the stupid things Trump says he's willing to support an unproven treatment
I love Trump is off base on this one I don't know what he's doing
Really sad
For someone who's like
You know I'm a free thinker I'm outside the box all you sheep all you people with followers
I will do that literally anything this dumpster
You know like
Remember all the drugs that are developed over time with imported scientists they aren't just like
A politician comes out and says
Take them
Those are all the good drug
Those are all the good one
Send interesting Axiom politician
Hate this
Not good
I'm going to go I'm just going to say that right now that I didn't take it
The first words of the Constitution are Congress shall make no law restricting the president
Pushing some b******* on people
Alex
The president is Free Speech
Cool
So I know you're probably wondering
How did Alex know
What tropical
Going to stay at the inaugural was not wandering
You weren't
Telephone
Somebody slap him
Picking it up
You got
Pray for Trump
The middle
We're here what
The pier is a reverse
We're here
A geyser
What
You don't even know that
Now
Scared
Okay
Here's a
If he can talk to Trump without the use of a phone he's definitely applying telepathic communication
National Security
No doubt he is and he's got all of the secrets
You could just tell the path in there all the time
Other countries need to be kidnapping Alex Jones reading his mind for all the Trump Secret
Secrets is just like ice cream
What the f*** is this
That's
Telepathic
So I am
Definitely implying that there's a telepathic connection with him and truck with
Upset
And then the other thing is super exciting there is that
He's definitely saying that God is here we're here in Trump is in the middle
And that seems to be Jesus's
It's one thing to consider but it's basically like
Kingship this is what you say about like
Someone is divinely ordained to be your ruler conduit through which
It's exactly the early early church was
The priest was the only one who could speak your goddamn convey the messages
From the holy of holies
Like hell it was only two Japanese Emperors ago and they were the conduit for God
So
It's
Republic
Democratic Republic
View
Of the ruler
Are the Justified
A peaceful transition of power away from
God's chosen president
I mean there's two possibilities either he is lost
And whoever wins
Skip
The Mandate of Heaven is so clumsy that I'm done by
Human echinacea that God doesn't really have much of much of the Swing on this one
He can be he can be knocked out every 4 years
If Alex's is there I mean what are we doing
This this guy is as the realm of acceptable
You should be ashamed
So Alex that plays the eclipse
I believe it is very
He does it again plays the clip of trump talking about opening up the churches
Interpretation of this is real funny
Need to do the right thing and allow these very important essential
Places
Aphasia
To open
Right now
For this weekend
Did they. They don't do it I will override the governor's
In America we need more prayer
Did you just hear that teeth never said override
Aegis
The owner
When the federal government override
It is the first
Or second
40% of you either
What
What are you f****** talking
The only dog that only the first few amendments
Only a few Amendment allow the government to do
Christ making stuff in order to try and make it
Guzma contradicts
Really extreme 10th Amendment ship from back in the earlier days
Shawty rationalization of
I'll come
In order to
Membership
Remember Shane
Shame Shame was good
Shame I like seeing when people experience for saying s*** like that
I feel physically bad after saying something they completely compromised everything I've ever espoused in my entire
I feel bad about the
Yeah actually we are not there anymore
Just say that s***
Brianne rollock
Lord Rothschild
We've covered a large part of that like
2009. Off the show where he was like
He was having
State legislators on Ricky
Resolution
He was he was talking about
Constitutional Convention
Yeah I got kind of ridiculous
Picture of this
Is broken down loser that he is in 2020
God damn man
You would hate yourself
You would be Your Own Worst Enemy
The person
Backwood be second
To your future self
Very sad
Together a
What is like a
Debate between new Alex and old Alex and just have them argument other all day
Thinking about you I don't have the time and enterprising
Yeah I don't have the time
Focus on putting out
12 hour episodes per week instead of making one thing that will go viral
It's an issue person
That is a problem
Our last episode on Friday said that he prayed with somebody,
This comes up again
Person
The devil
Like four years ago was telling me how much you love Jesus
God
Patrick the f*** out of here
We all know.
What
Do you like like
Lord's Prayer
Rodger
Yeah I don't know why you playing so close to the vet
Probably cuz they also committed a crime during up
Maybe attorney-client
Give me
Congress shall make no law restricting my prayer for crier
Sure we planned the crime so
Admissible in court
The First Amendment
Yeah I know cuz Alex has talked
Praying with Rodger Rodger to God
Like you would be playing this game
We're on multiple episodes it was Rodger but maybe he's just not supposed to
Probably tired. Not allowed to talk about you forgot you said
That about Rodger
Possible
So we know that Alex is really bad with Thomas Jefferson quote
How does he do
No he's not he's very bad with
How do they do it
Quotes from outside of the United
Well if it's a non-white person I bet he's going to Tribute to a white person
There's no choice in this life
Gentleman
HUD
You think you're on this planet.
Game
You think it's about watching TV
No man this is about your soul you're a sentient creature
You have like Mahatma Gandhi said
What are you
The universe
That is
Then you start
Playing game
Very weird
Okay
Gandhi quotes
Find it anywhere
I don't know any our souls are the seeds or the universe or
Doesn't sound like
I couldn't find anything I don't know if it's a real quote
Go bad
It's real and I just can't find it but ours trying to track down
Awesome quotes
Sure that sounds great
Everybody knows
Sometimes you want to go
Where everybody
Knows your name
That one sound that one
Run here with Jason Goodman
Who runs his own YouTube show
About nonsense
Talk about it
YouTube
I mean
Where is an Alex and Joe Rogan and everybody at war with YouTube
So you know I'm saying because they have audiences
He's the guy who interviewed
Dershowitz
Okay in that interview that Alex got super pissed off about
Started screaming
So you
Is answers about Epstein and stuff like that
According to him
I don't care about interviewing the guy who interviewed a guy
I don't care
If I cared I go watch
The interview
You're not allowed to bypass animal trials under federal law house
How is
Modern I'm in the mother in Spanish
Doing human testing in the United States right now
Modern in Spanish Padre mother
Moderno memes
Mother
No Padre
Moderna
Also isn't
About animal trial
It's it's just normal operating procedure
For vaccine development to use animal trials
An article in Staten
Regulators require that manufacturer show a product is safe before it goes into people
Researchers almost always check
Before putting Cuban volunteers of potential risk
How much does making up that there's a lob be uncommon
You are uncommon circumstances were in right now that there are potential dangers
They could come from skipping any kind of step in normal process
I'm certainly not in a position where I have enough awareness to understand
What kind of calculus people are making me learn from the animal trials
That we might not be riding out cruel or animal child. What you doing
Factor those out as a boy
I don't know enough
The number of articles
There's no law
And
People who have
Familiarity with the topic
Understand
If you do the normal route it'll be 10 years
What is Vice Ganda
And
You don't want to wait 10 years.
I don't know what the risk if there is a situation
Ends up position where something
Really unexpected and negative better to take
Your time to do things
I'm not sitting here whatever vaccine
This is our lives
They they understand those concerns that I might think of in my head when I try and look for
Perspective
But I have her pretty well
Yeah it seems like
Now I'm just
I'm just spitballing
You and I probably aren't the guys to make that
Kind of call cuz we don't really know enough
Say that that would be true for many
So what we should do is allow people for whom that area is there expert
To make those
Decisions
That makes sense right I think we can all agree that that's a good idea
So why can't we agree that that's a good idea
Because some people are angry
I was going to say it's a rare glimpse into Alex's bad boss
This one is particularly
Because
A bad boss
He's actually kind of a kind of undercut some of his beliefs
Back to Sunday by the way
For 6 p.m. central doing that Sunday show live
The cruise trying to talk
Me I'll do an immortal Day live
So your day off
Job
Will will will will see what happen
Yeah well that you're going to be there on Memorial Day and making your staff work
I think you're going to get
DES office for what
Broadcast
Or I'm going to yell at weirdos
So I don't know
That great
The fact that he did
First of all
Explicit
Lily said that Alex was lying
Psychic entity believes
If we got to sit through a three-minute rant about the devil to get there I think it's worth it
So what do you think he's what do you think is favorite X-Files X-Files the last guy or a
DVD codes for The X-Files
I think his favorite X-File is
Captain America
Sure there are a lot of
I just really really like you would like a
Mdzs I am the juiciest Ice Cube
Holding
Alex