Damn important I sweat it
I have great respect for knowledge B B I'm sick of them posing as if through the good guy
Need MoneyGram
Dot-com
Novelty Beverages and talk a little bit
About Alex Jones
Jordan Jordan
Courtesy of my
Dragon Queen Chrissy Center
Perfectly
She is not supposed to you
She will kill me
Point out that black dragon Queen
Made her life
Infinitely
Anaheim
I guess my right side for the week
Are in a week
You both are screwing that up now
I'm in watching some videos of a guy convict
Talk about life in prison
I was already not really
I really got glad that I don't have to know any of that stuff
You know they talking about how you clean a peanut butter jar and stuff
He's fascinating to watch him rip up newspaper and coils of water with
Well I'm glad I just got water
No don't get out yet
That is displayed by people in prison
Like you take away people's ability to do very simple thing
Like send a message a couple sales over
Insanely elaborate ways to do it hardening toothpaste up to make a weight to throw
It's impressive
But also very depressing circumstances dictate kind of
Sojourn
So first Michael
Next word
Very much
Next
I'm a policy wonk
Therapy that goes Electric
Thank you so much Brett
See obstructive thank you so much
Heroin
Is freakishly large
Thank you so much
Generosity
DirecTV local cheerleader
Sweet appreciate either very much
Steve Jordan before we get to be
I really been doing I've been really focusing on some like real meat
Basic Celtic uninteresting ambitious selfie
No no
Lebanon block of ice melt
Okay that sounds Sparkling Waters
Hell yeah
Girl fight
Real good nothing to get too excited about
I've gone with the Campfield
The soda called
That's kind of a Fresca
Play I Like it I've always enjoyed that
Alright
Do we got the the line of 11 of those
They're better they're better than nothing crazy
Yes it's nice it's been a little bit of time in this world of just like
Normal
Normal self
Deep questions
And this is probably the year of the shelter's biggest
Alright
Would you
Revisit the ecstatic
Seltzer's
You know what I mean or is that as well as any ecstatic Seltzer something that must exist
In its own time
Do you mean you mean the ones that I rated very highly
Would you drink the lemoncello
As as just like a regular time because I wouldn't want to get tired of it but
On a regular basis
I think that there's some that I rated pretty highly that I have to be in the mood
Matt is that like
I do give points for ingenuity
Creativity
No Doubt
Because there's little-to-no preparation that I need to do on that and I have not had the time
Recently I have to move
And so I've been apartment hunting
And that's the pain under normal circumstances
What show more complicated now
Frustration
Tons and tons of stuff
That's taking up my time
And so the thing will have to wait
When we can properly
Right but at the same time there is something important
What's going on
In the world of our Wacky Wednesday
He's going to have lasting consequences I think I actually am and it's the kind of thing that
I was thinking about getting some music to play on this episode
Goodbye Yellow Brick Road
Some other song that has goodbye in it
No no one no one
We've done it before but I think we officially probably have to say goodbye
To our friends with Project Camelot
Matter
Just the other day over project catalog
Be aware there was a big announcement
But you made
Hi everyone
Hi Carrie
We are going
And I
Free plans
Simple
Ways to
And
What I like
Like to say is
Demonetized
Solution
Ends us we have Gary Cassidy taken project subscription model
Kerry Cassidy
You I think that's the actual and the road is covering her.
41 there's absolutely no chance that anybody on her God sent
Feel-Rite to do episodes going over things that creators keep behind a paywall
Yeah it's stupid but I still respect carries right their intellectual property
If she wants to try to get people to pay for access to her videos of me to pay for a membership than we brought
Podcast most of her videos on our own show
That's kind of unethical
Cersei is going to subscription model than just based on understanding of
What I think the limitations of fair use our I don't think we can do episodes about him
It's very frustrating that I
Pictures of bad
Corset
A lot of respect
Compare when they're bad I don't really care
Thoroughly
Looks like where we park you know
I'm not the only one
The YouTube announcement appears that the response is pretty divided
Some people saying that they're going to come along with the new model
Another saying they aren't going
There's a lot of people who are having their videos demonetized on YouTube right now
And so a lot of folks are trying to migrate to subscription model
Look in the comments is a ton of people who like I get
Buy content from XYZ different people and I'm not going to be able to afford to pay all of them
Whatever
Why don't you guys all this group up and make your own and now we're back to YouTube
Kind of
Words to make people have to pay for the lies you tell them really sucks me
Definitely
Not Lies We Tell You
You know
Kind of expected
These some people are and some people are out there
You keep some people in the fold but you're definitely going to lose some of that audience
What's less expected is it a couple commenters point out in the comments section at the page
Where you're supposed to sign up for a membership to be new Project Camelot is an unsecured website
All right for myself and sure enough it is an unsecured page which is pretty f****** days
Put my
Let's put all my credit card on an unsecured
Anyone sign up for Subscription Service could have had their information stolen
I think this is a terrible plan I have zero faith that it's actually going to work out well
Is pretty decent chance it'll just end up staying on YouTube
This is dumb dumb
Unless you're also putting all your content up on YouTube
You're never going to reach people who might stumble across your contact
Like it's just it seems like shooting yourself in the foot in order to make a couple bucks
If you mix a significant amount of money from YouTube monetization
And that's all gone then she has no income
So she tries to replace it with her
I guess
Subscription
But nobody's go
It doesn't seem like that
Yeah I mean she might as well sell hats
Actually does bring up the series going to start selling summer
Ideal
I don't feel that bad cuz
Honestly
We don't sell any
No
I don't feel bad for the situation because it's like yes
Sitting around talking about how the coronavirus is turning people into vampire China
There is a virus
YouTube has every right to say you can't make money off these videos
The past
So I don't feel bad about anybody
People shooting situation
I do wish her luck on some level
Except I don't because I also might be an anti-semite
Kind of isn't
This is to me this is a lot like
Al Capone kind of situation
You're getting her where her money
You're not getting her for her actual crime
Disinformation is going to get people hurt
Even killed
But what you're doing is you're just taking away your money straight
Yeah I get what you're saying but she should probably be arraigned on some other day
You know as long as three speeches thing I don't know what you're going to do with that
Some lawsuit I wonder what his tax
Who knows
What is it what's the name of it
Now I'm mad
Goddamn know it's bad in San Francisco
Later than we normally do and I think it's affecting
This might be our last rodeo with the Project Camelot is what I'm saying
Yeah
That makes me feel a little bit stupid about this is a we've already been like
You know it is
There is still content that's not behind a paywall that's still on YouTube that I
Still considered a game through the possibility of Raptors and
The Mercantile Mercantile dog
Spider leadership
And so we will go on this
Last
Adventure
In theory
Today wonderful
A couple days earlier
Before she made the announcement
Krypton model
Carrie got interviewed by a guy named Shepherd ambulance
Okay well I had an organization
I guess call
Called intellihub
And YouTube
View that started it all
Alex
I've had him on as a gas
Very regularly
He's tried to give him a job on there all the time I
He was one of these sources for Alex's coverage of the Las Vegas shooting
Shepherd
I would go on to talk about how there were helicopters in the crowd
And what-have-you is a real ding-dong adjacent to Alex
This is a really close to your need six
Degrees of Separation. Just one
This is
DirecTV literally is Kevin Baker
He is a guy interviewing Kerry Cassidy
Bulshit you got going on
So are we starting Shepherd
Introduces The Thinker
To work which is bad too bad start
Cabela's
Today we have
Very special
With us
Project
Camelot I know you all know the name
Perico
Her website
Project Camelot
Portal
Dot-com
Terry you
Done
Thousand interview
Whistleblowers
First question
Should you have
Fascinating stories I've ever
Heard in my life
Alright came from
A lot of your interviews
Fascinating People
This guy is terrible
He's got an awful interview-style you've got an awful droning voice
It's very top
Whistleblowers
Most Fascinating Amazing Stories
You talking about how the Walking with Dinosaurs actually
No it's like interview
So is this is our last time
Sitting around talking with Carrie
It's actually kind of fitting because Shepherd ask her
About her route
How did this the hardest get going
Did the creation of Project Camelot and of course
It's a career that didn't work out show
Okay well I
Started out
Actually I was
Working in Hollywood
20 years
And
I reached
I decided
Consumer-grade camcorder
And
I started going out
Consumer-grade by the way
Attempting
Call Princess
Actually got this
This idea that I would make
Documentary saying
Have you seen you
Talk about everybody else
But not themselves
I like that idea I like that
I don't want to talk about what you know about the subject
Have you seen it
I have not seen one I've not a series of interviews that last about
14 seconds that start with have you seen a UFO and somebody's like
Alright
Next person also
Great way to phrase it
Glass ceiling in Hollywood
That's a perfect right has so many comics
Idaho
100000 comics
Which is not
Say that women do not hit the glass
Harry hit the glass yes I think Carrie Coon
Dealing with a lot more I don't want
Camcorder in Espanol
Do prunes in the second half
You didn't hit the first happen
If that's the first project that you go to after your Unshackled to Hollywood dreams or whatever
Best ideas whenever I say
Is it gone great church
Maybe a better way to put it is looking plateau
My career
In her
Trajectory of trying to make a documentary
Admit very very
Who ended up being
Is incarnation of King Arthur
From King Arthur or something
Also came across
Call Ryan
Partner
Camelot
Was representing the
And
Invited
Later app
And
I interviewed
We ended up staying in
Best friend
And I
I got a small
Okay
Turn on the way back
Showed me
Fireplace
England
Casual wear
Arthur
And that's where the idea was born to
Create a website
Impressed
There's no consensus King Arthur was a real person
Historical
Also
Place working Arthur was conceived
Based on
Being in the Wolves appreciate a legend
Subsumed by such banality
The king who brought all of Britain together and pulled the sword from the stone
Peterbilt
It makes me wonder if you use like
Mark Richards as like Galahad
I'd like to see Lancelot
I would love to see what the round table is in a Kentucky
I think I'm out
Don't remember anymore
Demonetization thing that you did
Completely bizarre be
Because also
Viewership
L'artisan stay and
It had even jumped
In the last 3 months like
So I was
Why is work
Yeah but the bottom line is
Weeks ago today
You know
Deleted
And then the
Same night
Miles Johnston
What other people
Same thing
Clamping down there doing
Bishop thing and
And embarrassed
Completely
Pensacola
Cuz I don't
Have any video sure
I had a problem
Because
You think there isn't a virus
If you don't like it is it is an interesting thing that like a lot of
Conspiracy theories are just sort of been ignored and
You know one of the compelling reasons why
In theory
Is that other conspiracy theories can lead you to radicalization that could lead you to take violent action
But it's not really essentially dangerous
Like talking about how the Illuminati is in control of the world and they put
Pyramid the music videos
That's not not real
With you wanting to hurt Jay Z made
But ultimately it's also just kind of stupid
It's relatively harmless
Conspiracies about there not being virus
Very easily lead you to take actions that end up putting yourself and others at risk
Director
I can see why you take this more seriously and have a different approach to it
Although it does
It does hurt Things That No One
Do this in the past
That's David Icke Spa
I mean honestly not listening to that
George Clinton song then
The bottom line here is the Carrie knows exactly what the f*** is going on
Anybody Who's acting honestly about this
They wouldn't be they wouldn't be behaving
Pretend like I didn't do anything
Alright whatever
So
This is pretty funny to me
Shepherd
Is talking about
He's like
YouTube owes him tens of thousands of dollars for back revenue or something
Read down too much
You're doing
Weird thing they did to me was
I basically haven't use my channel again
Five six seven eight years or so
I got mad because they were basically
Not ever letting me know
Even though they never
About it it's like
Figured out I don't know
I stopped kind of using the platform and I was just doing my wife
Tyrese
Start this pod
And it's kind of going
You know and it's
I mean
It's only gotten thousands of
Abuser whatever
It's starting to pick up and then
All of a sudden
I get a notice
That 6 videos
Copyright strike
Conspiracy
Feel like he's just explaining what's going
Yeah in a very simple indirect list
Because
But they never said it maybe I just couldn't figure out how to do it
You couldn't figure out how to do it
Years later I put Avengers
They wouldn't let me monetize say I don't understand
Did everything Tuesday yeah those copyright strikes do happen
Sometimes it's
Wildlife
We posted a couple of our episodes
On YouTube
And we've gotten copyright strikes on all of the
Because of Alex it's because of the music Alex uses in and out of
We couldn't do it because whoever owns the rights to Silver Stallion
Or some Highwaymen song copyright
Of course so I wouldn't be too surprised if it was something even if it is like Shepherd using
Footage from
News broadcast it is not the rights to
It doesn't mean your shift gets taken down it just means if you tried monetize if they get a cut
Of course I don't
I just don't like big baby
And they're notorious for being
Copyright
Pick up most of the show
So carries trying to this point I don't think she has decided on going with
Subscription model
If you still trying to figure out what you going to do about the demonetization
And Shepherd has a dumb idea
What about just having your own products like us
Snoop Dogg doesn't show any of like
Sneakers
That's because
Yeah that's it that's
Question I mean we are
Actually
Right now
Zinc baby
So yeah
Not tonight
The rent I know
It's stopping this
This is what they're doing
Information
What's the new world order
Nicole
Covina Lane
It's the
Flaws of shepherds
Play no one would pay for everything
Able to sell any ads
Joshua cucumbers there's a slight difference in relative credibility of popular
30 between herself and Snoop Dogg
Yeah I'm just saying she could sell some random head
Tell me about the home game gorilla
Space definitely
I will say though I like to imagine that she's the same level of Snoop Dogg and that
When they did the all cities remix of welcome to Atlanta
That would be great
Talk about it
And that's what she's going to drop an LP that's going to blow her mind
So
Shepherd
Responses interesting
You were talk
What about a vortex
Earlier I had a
Really interest
Experiencing
Sedona with what I think
Was a boy.
Tell you about something
Also I have
Read
Very
UFOs in one was at
Cedar Point
I saw all the men
Catalan
Bored one day
Yeah
How you want it
Generally I remember back
Whatever the responses
Yeah that's that's all right
Response
Gary I've had a lot of experiences that would go great on your show
I got to go
I promise you
I don't impose
Discusses her research
Into covid-19
Justin Bombshells hear that
Hurt her monetization traffic
Can tell you is
Says that
A grave
Is basically been
The guardian said that
Started
Breeding a bioweapon
Carolina
These women
In front of me
DNA
That's from The Times-Picayune
Yeah that's what I was kind of trying to pick your brain cuz I'm
I'm trying to like
What I came up with
What is like
All this stuff
Really
Suspiciously
I don't know if it's the same things together
IPhone
Together
It's all coming together
The time together
Aliens biological weapon
You got evil
Scientist
Right it is all coming together
That is that is the progression that I was looking
I don't know I don't necessarily dangerous
Outright denialism
Is more dangerous from just like a what kind of behaviors
Could it
Endorse
Mercury is like this is alien
IAAI
Dangerous but I would still say
Trespassed line
Yeah but it's just unfortunate
Noticed
Quite frankly
Biscuits right back to are the grifters
Perfect if you stay in that sweet
Spot if you get to Big the Griff fails and if you're not big enough the grift
Yeah
Celebrity
Going to like you want to be in the middle you don't want to be so people start to treat you
With the people
Being that level
People don't know who you are
Exactly that's the best
Stay in the middle the end zone
Propaganda
That's what you got to do
So Shepherd
Sort-of is implying that
Maybe their space stuff involved with coronavirus but it's unclear
Carrie's instabake that he thinks
Covid-19 came from space
She doesn't real
Technology
Embedded
That apps
Was put there
Many many years
Shoot-down
This has been longing
Again a method of
War
Reasonable
Atlantis was sunken
Ways that we
Hitting it
Sure
And so on so
Jarvis
Now
I know that
It sounds as though you're try
You say that
Covid case
Meteor
But I do
Well no no not really although I did
Do some research on that
Like that is pause
Okay
Yes
Focuses their conversation is about like
Object
They're all his there's been a barrage of them carries beliefs about this is that whenever there's me
Meteors are comets they're actually projectiles
EXO
Going to be real bummed in 2040 when we fight the Vietnam War it again that'll be that'll be
Pretty sad
There their idea and comets near worth
Objects are generally a means of
Chameleons
And she wants to clarify
Soda Shepherd
But they're not saying
The coronavirus is from space
So there's all these rules man you know
People that's where are we supposed to wear masks in stores
Stuff like that
I'm sure they're Pro those
Like if you go to the beach
Sometimes
People at beaches don't follow rules
And those my friend
Are the cool t-shirts
Intelligent
Governor
Bars are open
State
People are
Amanda Ivanova
Opened up the beach
California
Lay on
Nonetheless
And people are ignoring
Stomach
Cool beaches
You should be leaving the coronavirus response want just enumerate
Mission of which beaches are coolgardie scary and wishon.
Find the banks of the sand in covid-19 disappear
Beach
Cool beaches
So Carrie
We know that she's known to talk to Weirdos like
The
Who
Made a movie and remember his name Ronald there's the super soldiers
Who are weird there's both the guy who can Channel people but doesn't need to voice
But also
Not the guy who can handle all sorts of folks.
Murderer
Top of Diamond Park
The former MP
I still think he's a good guy
So it's a
Credible source
I can't say this is
And tell you that
White House
The cute
Anyway
There was a fly thing that flew in
Real flying Nanobots
Space Program
And I can tell you that
That
Trump's latest statement about
He's rolling out
Call it
She's great on Saturday
Rapid fire
Because they're all great on that
It's like
Another words
In a race
With gay
Who is working
DARPA
Sure
And
Department of the
How does that work
Right
Government
Is in charge
Is it
1up
Trump
What does that even mean
Getting a virus
So if you're if you're following here but she has people that she's in direct contact or involved with
Trump team at the Q team chorus goes across areas of a coon dog person
Fast track of vaccine is really just him trying to race built
Is Bill Gates's going to make
Evil vaccine
I just wish everybody could hate Bill Gates for the same reason I hate Bill Gates which is purely
He has
Too much money take care our criticism
Philanthropic stuff there are some questions
Kind of appositive
And what I see that
Has a berry naked within it
But it feels like it's their way through
Psychologically dealing with the inevitability of needing a vaccine about you
At least
Scene
I will let you know how you get
Buried
Further people down into the only tropic
Can save us in a Public Health crisis
That's the story you tell yourself
Whatever
A vaccine is going to, they're not going to give
Trump credit for it
Write like there's no way they don't say well it's because Trump did
Most likely end
So you see these things that trumps doing like signaling that he's okay with vaccines
Racist
Henry Ford level like
I like Hitler like that kind
We don't talk about that
It's important for weirdos I carry and Alex
To talk about the stuff like when Trump says
Hey we're doing this stuff
The vaccines
Because they're so against vaccines they have to figure out how to make it okay cuz otherwise it should be
Prop
And waiting to do this is by
Saying that he's
Competitive
Art of War for the chest
People don't
Stan house
Operate
And don't they
Video song
Who sings this
The state of the game
That one's son's you called it with
And not appear
Against
What they are at
And so there
You're going along
Stay on
Parallel
To the enemy
Up Intuit
When they
Enchanted
Overtake
So or not
You know that's also a possibility
Hurts my brain more than theirs
I want because it's stuff
Like the level of cognitive dissonance
Makes my brain like
Explode with I need like
10 Tylenol and they're just like well obviously
10 million
That we never happen
Yeah it's like we're going down this road
It's just another right
Goodluck Goodluck
Insane so we have a little bit of a shorter interview cuz there's not a whole lot going
Some bombs of Interest
Cool beaches
Oh you know ogres telling you that you're a bunch of nerds for opening of your beaches
King Arthur
Demonstration of
Something that really confuses
I'm not actually certain whether they
People are joking or not
Merlin
Aged
Backward
Now I know that you'll get a lot of people
Get stuck on you know you read that
Fitzgerald
He couldn't do
Any magic
What's the point
There's a good point
I need you to help me get to the bottom of their joke
I think they're joke
I am underprepared
Drilling outside all the sudden
That's alright go ahead now it's
Yeah I know that Hopper
They started
Mowing lawn
Do you think they're joking absolutely not
I can't tell cuz he's laughing Shepherds
Really think that like some Drilling and some construction
What's going on or some neighbor mowing the lawn
Is a deep State attack when you're trying to record something
That's back to me is if they're not joking that's f****** scary that level of paranoia is
Really really weird is like when I make a joke about something that
Actually happen again
You know like
I make a joke
This here's my commentary on that
Not like
Situation
Array
I'm telling truth
There's a certain amount of discomfort that is causing the last
Absolutely telling the truth on what they plan
It's got to be frustrating way to live
Hilarious
How they're doing
Yeah isn't it hilarious that is or isn't it hilarious if they were doing this
It's hilarious that the evil people are using
A lawnmower I'm not a f****** laser
Bright with things like
Carrie thinking there's like
Problems attack from the globalist
Yeah yeah
My window weekend was a patriot act
That must be what
American militia
Water dripping from I did notice this is weird I did notice
I looked up in my window
I thought that was your rock.
American Water
Seems like a really unsatisfying
In frustrating
Way to look at things like everything is an attack everything must be
Coordinated in some way
What
The paranoia
Is Joseph
Beer and yet
Treated mocking
You know what I'm saying
You like I'd believe that they believe that they are under it
Hack but the implications of their attack
Is so massive
And so huge
That it seems ridiculous to treat it as like
Oh man
Don't you see how weird it is that this Global Interstellar
Bucking cabal of monsters fighting with aliens
Is using the lawn mowers
Like do you not understand how much
More terrifying is that they usually see I don't think
That's what he's laughing
No it's B it really it's up satellites
If this is the end
Then this is the end
It is
Kind of
Ultimately that's
What everyone needs to know is that Carrie is very boring
This show is incredibly boring except for the parts that I end up finding
This is kind of a fitting
Close
Cota
Is the to be interviewed by somebody who is an Infowars associate
For someone who is
Like a guest
Pretty regularly on Alex's show
Ifucking higher
So you see this like these two important pieces
She's boring and this is
Pretty much
Because at this point
Very similar
Herspace of the secret space program weirdo alien shed
Is
More less
Normal
Bray Wingstop South
Has no further
You know no further non connection
Yeah like it's all one big
Perfect Circle
Becoming more and more that her anymore
Well good luck on your subscription service
I don't know what else to say yeah I don't know good luck
Will be what it is another episode
The website is not
We are Intruders at no just go to bed Jordan world
If you would like please donate to a local charity in your area we would
Alex