Damn important
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Knowledge
Dot-com
Jordan Jordan
Well actually interesting
I was sitting around I was looking at Twitter
U-Haul Lotto
I don't need much with social media
I don't put out promotional materials on Twitter
I got a rare like
I was giving out today I've never got no
Robert Evans
But also
I saw them live when I was very young
What is the first concert
Appropriate age
Star Trek uniforms
MPS scar time, remember
The group called the girl that she actually has
Group or new workers I don't know
I don't know how I stumbled upon this
Listening Five Iron Frenzy
Hurry up.
I'm glad that she is going on to smother interesting project
We have help getting the word out of us disagree
O.c. supertones
I do like me
And then there's a whole different
Taste from when I was 14
Everyone mocked me my whole life but I will end up being shown
Don't be correct Taylor Club discount
Absolutely
Italo disco
What's your bright spot
How to get away with murder because I
Unwatchable
Learn how to get away with a murderer
They were totally going to get caught for that murder
I mean no rope
Perfect margarita
Well that's almost over
I'm hoping today
Good learn about reality
Alex
26-28
Tuesday Wednesday and Thursday this week if you're nasty
I'm not in the mood for bulshit today
Ubisoft
Do you know we're going to cover a lot of these current events that are going on but shockingly a number of things are completely
Best I can
Consider a productive way
Stuff that goes on
And I'll spoil this
I think Alex admitted to a felony on air Maybe
Episode
Spoke to sign up in Oscoda Michigan
Disappointing the Seltzer report
Not you and I'll probably walk
I'm a policy wonk
No
Baconator
Standard
Text Cassandra s
Children charities LLC
And thank you so much you are now it's
We got to go
Business
Heroin
Is freakishly large
Congratulations
100 picture
B-real
That's the confusing
Literary references
Please
Take that generous spirit and apply to a local
Charity in your area or
In some sort of a field that you feel
I'll tell people where I need
So Jordan like I said this morning sell to report what is going to get it out of the way real quick
I got nothing
I got nothing you didn't you didn't try any Seltzer's
I'm stuck at 92
I don't
Can I get nothing good to report or accident report can I be honest
Okay
I every time I go to the store
I try and stock up on Seltzer's
You know like a bunch of the loose bottles seltzer
To go to the store over and over again
Like it probably sounds like I am
I'd like nibble on it like a squirrel
Go out and buy another one
Yeah it into number of the fridge
I find this apartment so I've been really busy with that I'm going to
A couple of viewings I haven't really stocked up on Seltzer in a bit
Things that are left in my fridge are all coconut
I've been just drinking
Ones that I've already had before that I had to buy a six-pack of
Looks like a couple that are in my pantry that I've just been I got to put these in the fridge for later but apricot coconut garbage
I did end up having to happen cuz I will never drink those of my own volition
Terrible
For our next episode I think we should
Should try both the pantheon of coconuts
Make it a little bit more tolerable
So that's the shelter report nothing to record but maybe something in the future
No sales indeed
Like I said
Is it going to be a bumpy ride at Point
In addition to me being sick
Uno
Not that I generally pull punches
Upon a practice today
In addition
I feel like I would like to offer a little bit of a window into the creation of one of these episodes
It's a long way I'm going
To give a couple of little notes
They can help people understand exactly what the process that goes into
About that and it's really difficult for me to answer the question without doing some of it illustratively
The show itself
If you notes along the way
Don't have those in my process
Pretended like James Lipton
Sports Clip
Where we start on the 26th
Launching into a bit of a new narrative surrounding
Coronavirus statistics
He seen a man named that
Great white shark attack
Caladium
This is just in the news
Today
Mobile.com
Victim
Coronavirus death
This is some real original reporting
Information Act
Request and they admitted
Gunshot wound
Suicides
And then they text you
With the bill of Melinda Gates you in
Shut down for fraud
Find almost everyone
Positivity
Coronavirus
Listening
Alex
And what took over 2 hours
To break down
Right now we can ignore all the stuff at the end that's just the b******* about that
You had a cold in the last decade all that's pretty standard stuff
This is this report was put out by the foundation
Which of the name but if you hear it used to be like that I don't know about that every organization that we talked about
National Freedom patriotism is very trustworthy
Are a real life
So Alex absolutely is not read this report because he's just making stuff up about the Freedom of Information request
Distance of like that
It's no idea what this actual report was saying
In the record they were looking at Washington State out how many of these deaths were caused
Definitively by the virus
And which might have been people virus but unrelated
Too that I've done
Listen to Bad question to be asked
Since the more precise data we have
The better we can respond to the situation in front of us
However in the hands of conspiracy theorist
Audiences were just here headlines and made-up
Conclusion
Freedom foundation's first piece about this came out on May 18th
Hypothesize that the states
19 deaths total
Is inflated by as much as 13%
This number was taken from Washington's Department of Health percent of death switch
Involve persons who had previously tested positive for covid-19
But did not have the virus listed anywhere on their death certificate is either causing or contributing
This is not.
If you read the report
Freedom Foundation clearly has an angle on this
Such as to imply that most
These aren't coronavirus deaths charts
Lexus take on it well I mean even if it is actually
13 Earth
Yeah 13% than that
Great there's 87000 dead
Due to Coronavirus
Is
Yeah
Pine-Sol on May 21st they were boarded an update on the story
Which included reporting on a telephonic press briefing that the Department of Health
Open house
Poh statistics manager Katie Hutch
Over the course of the outbreak we've been monitoring and recording the causes of death as we know it
We currently do have some debts that are being reported that are clearly from other causes
We have about five deaths less than 5 deaths that we know of that are related to obvious other cause
In this case they are from gunshot wounds
This is the image that people like Alex will latch onto and Baker big story
Serious concerns that this report and freedom Foundation is not given the full picture about this press conference
Luckily I got my hands on the audio this press conference and I can play for you some of the parts that are
Conspicuous
Distance from the original reporting
Which naturally means
By the time the connection to the primary source
A clip beer is dr. Katie Hutchinson explained that there are some non covid deaths
That get listed
We've been hurt
You think death information Within
One day
We're or notice
Spell particularly
Culinary
Data this rapidly
Is really not our normal
Or normal process
Relief relief
Explain in a few minutes
Takes up
From start to finish
We also found that in the early stages
The outbreak
Medical certifiers
We're really not aware
Location
Covid-19 and did not have a clear
Understanding
How to complete
The death certificate accurately
Because of this
We implemented some prophecy to connect
Data from multiple data
Detroit identified
To covid cases
Earliest
And to work with certifiers
Local Healthcare
Under which
Over the course of the outbreak
We have been
A small number of death
Ingrid
Word that end up not being due to
I'll describe these.
More specifically in a few minutes
Removing them
I'm overtime
This is part of our regular
Elementary in
We know that the Quality Inn
Information
Naturally
Ultimately
As I will describe in a little bit
We suspect that we are actually more likely to be under counter
And become more apparent Once you walk through the process
So here Hutchinson is a
This kind of reporting is not business as usual
The Department of Health and naturally
The process would be
In order to create
The kind of
Information that people need
You have to do all the mantid process
That's right we don't have time to maintain our high level of quality standards
As soon as possible that half
These
Sort of death certifications can take up to a year
And by that point
You are out of the window where this information would be a guide for us right now
There are going to be little things that come up along the way
Did these
You cases that you talkin about
Included in what you would call those cups
Here to talk about that a little bit more
We currently do have some death
They're being
Reported that are
Clearly some other
We have about
Lesson 5
Let me know
That are related
Obvious
Gun Shop
We don't have any. Currently being
Car crash
There were a few cases there was something I could catch a gunshot that was labeled as covid-19
Mental process refines itself those cases will be removed for the telly
This is the only thing that people like Alex will hang their hats on because it's what they need to create a narrative it all deaths
Probably fraud
As opposed to this being part of a system working
Far outside its normal operation
We're serving the needs of the few mistakes
Earlier we heard Hutchinson say that she was convinced that the numbers were actually undercounting actual covid-19
And she says more about why in this next clip
This is a particular issue
Earlier
Where at
Pneumonia
And the certifier with
Unaware
Could have been
Currently in our system
We have about 3,000 that certificate
What indicates symptoms
Unclear whether
Are any of these
Belated
Press conference from the freedom Foundation
If you have an interest in Investments has covid
Worried about the possibility that
UNS
The state of Washington only has an official death count of about 1,000
So if any considerable portion of those 3000 death certificate
Yeah
That could be
April's like on the low-end twice as big
I refuse to believe any sincere person could hear this press conference and Come Away with the impression that be less than 5.
Shameless acts like Alex Jones.
Go back to work
And also to come as no surprise to literally anyone
It's almost entirely bankrolled by conservative billionaires
The recipients of money from the coax from the donors trust as well as from the Bradley Foundation
They're little more than an anti-union auntie worker agitated policy house
Which is paid by the super-rich to argue against their workers more
For instance in 2014 they released a policy paper arguing against mandatory six sick leave rules for employees
The guardian release Foundation
The freedom Foundation is a proven plan for bankrupting and defeating government unions their education litigation
Legislation and Community activation
They've also been militantly opposed to raising the minimum wage laws
The freedom Foundation is exactly the sort of place you would expect to hear this kind of ship from
Their bought-and-paid-for mouthpieces of the people who aren't worried about the virus except in terms of
Y'all keeping people home from work
I know I don't need to spell this out for you but to make things perfectly clear these people are paid by billionaires to make everyone else's lives worse
Covid-19 Washington story not because they're uncovering some truths about these
Less than 5 deaths
Because it helps shift the conversation and it gives cover for politicians
To put workers at risk
The dead giveaways they're funded
But also the fact that their article doesn't mention the 3,000 death certificates aren't listed is covid-19 cases
The omission of that information is proof positive that they took
Wanted from the press conference
We just brought July
Reproduce this seemingly professional piece with a snazzy headline and then Alex in Russian
And that's all anyone will hear they will go find the actual press conference and listen to it
It's hard to read there might be as many as four pages
These people
And they do it because their lies are profitable to the right-wing billionaires who pay them I think billionaires are
Great first off
I'm isolated position
And has always been I want a small number of people to have as much money as possible
Through and through
That was really frustrating
But I'm glad that I understand it
Yeah
Alex talks about the New York Times I know your favorite
Black Friday
Fix the name on
Bless you stick
27 year old man who was murdered
When you get stabbed when you get shot
You are
This is all
Who's Alex's
Defense sensitive support for his other
Of the narrative which is this Washington
Whatever
I suspected I was just taking the story from the Washington Times Sunset the favorite source of his
Mr. Haynes name was later omitted from a dramatic front page list of nearly 1,000
Usf's
An incalculable loss
New York Times issued a correction and they fix this
Before the late edition white out
You sorta mistakes and oversights can happen and the times did with their supposed to in that situation
They owned up to the error made a statement to correct their mistake
Published an updated version
Something tells me that this was a solitary error in there listed because I have a hunch that conspiracies
Anyway the point here is its X made a mistake and they
Responded appropriately
I'll take Alex seriously about this complaint about other media Outlets making errors once he issues a correction properly
Maybe about the whole FDA closing down the lab
Story that he mentioned earlier
X
A calculable loss
Good workout
God you are
What's my name tissue correction about this to
Covid-19
Because it's a fraud you die
Other diseases in kidney
Failure in liver failure and lung cancer and bone cancer
Can you list design be a fraud
When you cry
I know
All of you know this
Anger is not true
That's not surprised
Supremacy DC's provisional data
Covid-19 related deaths
Over 85,000 179 deaths of May 16th
That's 80% of 100,000 right that's right
The total 1613
Which would make the population over 85 represent 32%
Of the covid-19 Cure
Easy highest overall individual group
D75 284
And 65-74 is 21%
A drop-off from there but the population between the ages of 55 and 64 is still 12%
Feel something
This touches
Making up numbers
Because the actual numbers are contradictory to his narrative
Also if Alex has to be believed there's very important question that he needs to answer
He's a legend of these evil globalist just take me everyone is over 85 and gets sick and dies of natural causes in a collie
Covid-19 to scare everyone
It seems to be him leaning closer to the David Icke there is no virus area Coronavirus
Read meadowside Gmail has to explain why there are so many more people dying this year than usual
If it was just a thing where they're just buys fine natural cause deaths is covid-19 to scare you
Other years they just all be covered.
And that is not what you're seeing
The CDC put out a report on May 15th which calculated that just
New York City from March 11th
May 2nd
Compared to long-term averages for that. Of time
It's really hard to get a clear picture of things right now but some of the indications are looking like when the dust settles
Will be looking at larger numbers than we're seeing now
Even without nailing a
Precise specific
I would like Alex to explain those excess deaths missing the real plague here
Hornets are taking over the northwest
I did for you know we haven't heard about those Hornets take one today
Or you know
Explain.
You want you want to get married to go is it matter if you want to go hang out with Carrie cancer
If your whole thing is going to be this game
I'm sick of it
Anyway
Alex believe
The Dakota
Situation
Although
Juno
Business clothes
What have you
It's to make us not stand up
We submit the more they
Queen
To see what they can get
Progress
Human standing up in demanding Liberty
Blood
Treasure
Everything else
So bad
We face
Society
Spoiler alert
Difference in how important standing up to him very shortly
Deep In The Weeds of the b******* about you know algren viruses
He hasn't he has a couple passions in life
1 is
Selling his product
Camping
I don't know he likes the camp he does like to run around shirtless in the wood that's true
Part of it
No his other passion is telling me not true stories of social interaction
Always makes time to do that
Gas station I go into
Going to now that they reopen partially
I thought well we know they're Counting
Car racks gunshot wound
People that had cancer
I heard that
Actually somewhat info
We already know all this
Then you need to tell other people
You need to
Let them know it's a frog
This female waitress was sitting there yesterday she said you're right
And the manager
This is all just a giant
Phone numbers weather in Chennai
Ocean View
Mail also Chevrolet
Chivalrous
Who is talking to him that isn't carrying an automatic rifle
Directions
You know what you're right your
Working at a restaurant in Austin you're not aware who Alex Jones
You don't know from his behavior
It's a he's a either wacky dude
I want to exchange numbers with this cap
Stop yelling everything off during this pandemic
You sound trustworthy take over for a bit
This episode and the next
The story we heard on our last episode we covered of Alex's which is about that guy there was a twenty-year-old in Detroit who beat up an l
Elderly man in
Unfortunate wrinkle to that story and that is
Batman
Tested positive for covid-19
No Alex is going to take that story
And he's going to build on it
And try and create a narrative
That the Democrats
Are trying to ship
Young people
Into nursing home in order to kill off the old people
Why in New York
In Michigan
Oregon
In Washington State
In Minnesota
New Jersey
They're on record skipping
Young people
Nursing homes
Nursing homes artwork covid patient
T-Mobile hospitals are empty
Nursing home
Almost abusive
Amargosa
Angel
Purple
That's 13th
And then
Lordy lordy lordy
Years old on average
When I get that car
They said
Un set the standard
Make
Thousand
Sweet cheese
But you got
To put the poison in
Peabody nursing home sick
So you're fine
People making me uneasy
Skip that weapon light
British troops
Smallpox going
Smallpox on Egypt
And then you get all that
According to Alex is 20 year old in Detroit
He was in the hospital because
You tested positive for Coronavirus
Really true
Scan Medicare or something
Was that a little bit
Obviously
Westwood Nursing Center cannot release this
This guy's medical information
But they did, undergo Rehabilitation and Recovery
More specific
And suffers from mental illness
It seems very likely
Rehabilitation on one of those grounds
Fox2detroit
What was diagnosed with covid-19 and was quote
Supposed to be taken
To another facility to be quarantine
From all indications that I can see here
What happened is likely complete breakdown of responsibilities
It seems entirely possible there was a failure to communicate
And further his father is said quote he was there I would have never
Consented to it
Anyway
The point here is that back up his claim that they're sending young people with covid-19
Infect the elderly
That's an example of him taking some of the details of the story
Twisting them
Weiss all these evil Democrats it's just his perverse imagination
How much
Or how little these people view the value of a human
Like
Really
40 Grand is what you're willing to kill people for right
Like if you believe that make sense to you
That's because you believe that
And how much do you think
People are like making from insurance and Medicare Medicaid for other procedures that are
Would happen normally
How much do you think it's not that much more than a lot of other procedure
Teachers need an extra gram
It's ludicrous that even worse once we realize
Something down the line
Preclude them from behaving this way
You know
Alex's Alex has a really swinging. Because
I don't know what the odds are but there's a possibility that people in Iowa kazadi
I've lost family members
Maybe even have some family members who are in nursing home that kind of thing
Create your your settings
A fire saying that your political enemies as bio-weapon
How to kill your family exact
4:30
Also he does still support
Serial episode
We have to talk about in a while but I think
So in this next people are criticizing Trump
Chloroquine
Perhaps
We don't need to go over that too much because
Freaks out like a little baby about it
And then he tries to
Like focus on the stories about
There's always fake diagnosis of covid-19
Do his own show
Buy arrest all over the news
In the world
Fake fake
We are on
Gunshot wounds
County mall is covid-19
Gunshot
Account
The Coronavirus
6 a.m.
7 year old man
Who was murdered
Can you go deeper in the whole list just full of pee
John Carter
Operate
Despair
I have no doubt that he shows up to the studio 10 minutes before the show
These a couple adlines and is like I can work with that
He has a has built up in his head where he has all the proof
But when the rubber meets the road this is what you have
Yo to headlines
Complete Fabrications about Beau and then reading the same headline is second time without realizing it's the same story
Alex has absolutely zero familiarity with the topics he's covering
That's the surface headline level and it shows
It's just a bummer
I would say that you should retire so some
Hungry, I could come in and take his place in the pecking order
But I don't think there's anyone to do that
He's still should probably retire though cuz it's getting depressing to watch
Filled with a lot of rage
It's very difficult for be2
I'm just not loud I'm just shaking and the window open today
I did notice
A little bit of what I would describe as a coiled spring
Sorry hypertension episode
So
If I get a heart attack then I'll be counted as covid
Absolutely
So Jordan if you think you're
You're not mad
Not compared to Alex in this next clip
Also
Partially
Because he thinks about Brian stelter
In the pool
Michigan Governor Gretchen Whitmer
And what she is done
Related to the virus
You got the baby
Don't want to fireworks
I want to give you a little warning visit along
Alex
Play Over the Top with this
I can get away with
We sit there and put up with him killing his unborn baby
Whatever the hell we get and let me check we're going to get
Governor
Do you have any
Watch Josie and Brian stelter books
Are you joking
Michigan just a random photo vraska
Video
Disgusting
Lookout
Wow
Countdown Pacino's what are we doing
You can take
People and lockups
Lock up your door
Coming for you
I got to bring Bilbo into this
That's not human
I just get upset around me
Look at that face
It wants to do
About 2 months ago
Don't put sick
People in the nursing home
He said we're sending the covid page
I was trolling a little bit there I wanted everyone to feel my pain
Cuz I think sometimes I do Alex a solid
So similar to
Media kind of packages with Trump says cuz if you print actually
Islam stupid
Wait where we've run out of inches
Pointed out every time
Never talked about it
Cvlife
So anyway Alex has the story about Gretchen Whitmer a little bit wrong
Michigan Governor covid-19 cases be sent to nursing homes however
You did sign an executive order in April which quote
Nursing homes with less than 80% capacity create dedicated isolation units for covid-19 affected
Residence
And I'm live article about this from April 15th makes it clear that what the order was seeking to achieve
Separate areas in long-term care facilities where was possible
In cases where it was not possible
Transfer patients who test
The positive to quote the facility in the region that has one
Which is be a dedicated unit
Right people who tested positive for covid-19
That will only provide care to Residents who have tested positive for the disease
Alex is trying to twist that wording into being that
Become Regional hubs for anyone who tested positive
This is about nursing home residents who tested positive
We still need specialized
Care
Give a good idea
Alex
She looks crazy that's who's going to win tonight Dia in an approach to challenging problem
Yeah
Executive order
Some roadblocks
41 it makes its executive order it makes it so any of any long-term care facility
What are more of the principal symptom
Sims 4 covid-19 president
But their employer shall not discharge discipline or otherwise retaliate against them
Skiers looking to spread a virus
Easy to leave that paragraph out
I think they I think they definitely use that is a smoke
Screen
All this going on here is the governor Whitmer is someone who Trump has targeted in the past so she's one of the big villains for Alex
Right now
I don't know what I think
Entirely the executive order because fully evaluating it is far beyond my paygrade
Can say is it nothing in it is about sending infected persons to nursing home to intentionally infected
That's just bullshittin Alex's dreamed up to make himself mad
If I had to guess
Alex just recently read headline about how Whitmer amended the order to give disabilities more flexibility
Giving rid of the 80% capacity rule
We can set up a unit while we can
I heard about that
Just got mad about it
These are looking for ways to escalate
Something
Yeah these people
Discontinued
Alex and Superman
Damsel murdering us
Human time bomb
Into nursing home sure
And this is where I want to give the second glimpse into the creation of these episodes
At this point
You know
We had that whole thing at the beginning about the freedom foundation and Alex
Is freaking out a bit here
Until I heard this next clip
I wasn't sure if we had an episode
This clarifies like
I think I think we got something we can work
Those and killed an old person their house for $1,000
A jewelry
Can we send her ass to me
Send them to the lethal injection we should
Door when the government corporations
Please note
Borrow.
Number two
Who promoted worse and worse people
In the power position
Now watch a Democrat event men women black
Why don't you
The movie
Gremlins
Ridiculous
So
What being under them
How much to say
The lilliputians
Nani juice
Won't be here
Special running
Global Grover
Spider-Man 3
I want I want
Catches her now on a limited number of movies that have Gremlins in them
There's a directed
Backflip is going to be nosey
I've never heard an ad picture he's like mentioning a sail through
Of course we got coconut protein bars
On this 26-episode it was really interesting to listen to because
Really felt like
Alex is almost
In Subway's returning to normal
Like
It felt like there was a lot more
There's like more familiar thing
Started to dip his toe back into Southridge stop
Little bit
Springfield like a gradual return to like you used to do this
Of course
Oh boy
Systems of Islam
Antichrist
Wait till I tell you about what you believe
The war
But in Europe
Accepted
Islamic
Call to prayer broadcast
Speakers in Great Britain
That's been
Celebrating
As political and
He couldn't afford it buddy
So what's going on here is it because it was Ramadan number of cities you know they've granted
The Coronavirus
This was not something that you like through the entire city of London or anything it was more localized to communities
People living near mosques in London which is a bigger city than be overwhelmed by
9 loudspeakers
ARF and Abraham told the Metro
Because the mosque is such a focal play
Point especially this month not being able to go is very
For my parents at home and heard it so at least they could listen to your coming directly from the mosque
It meant a lot for them
That the mosque is still there
Hopefully this will be over very soon get back to some sort of normality
So
Normal
Imagine if I were to build a building and then regularly at certain intervals of time
A large monster would I be
Trying to scare his audience
Taking over the last year
Is essentially white nationalist agitation comforting blanket of victimhood
Like you mentioned church bells ringing through American cities all the
State Street downtown Chicago
I used to work downtown and literally every day on my way to redline
Microphone plugged in
Every single day I would have to walk past him yelling at people they're going to be found on
Godly whores
And saying all kinds of homophobic s***
This guy out on State Street harassing people he's up there so much that he has his own Wikipedia page
Specifically because he harasses people with such regularity in Chicago
This is how like this how cute
Castle the sky is
After Trump cancels his rally in Chicago back in 2016
The right-wing was going on about how Chicago doesn't care about free speech
Pig response people started posting a meme with the states and the caption
Anybody taking Chicago denies freedom of speech doesn't know this guy
In the biggest busiest section of one of the country's biggest cities a Bastion of evil globalist demon
This guy has not too loud speakers for decades
You don't have been harassing people pretending that's preaching
And no one is shut him down
So f*** you but it's
Since we've had one of those marriages
Denying hundreds of 100,000 deaths for a long time
So focused on Lakewood
You know
Virus in China stuff
That is almost as backup
Because of the story I guess
I don't know what's called supply shop
For them so that's threatened
For Alex
But because
On the Run
In an interesting way
Michigan
London to Los Angeles
Rio de Janeiro to Berlin
Name five more cities
Cuz I know it's a group
See this here's where I really and truly my f****** self
It seems has no problem with the Chinese treatment of Muslim
This just doesn't square with whatever you wants to attack China Alex
This is just so indicative of how everything is a tool
For Alex
Has is used whatever he needs to attack
When he's trying to make people scared of Islam
It's not productive to be concerned about oppression directed at Muslims if your argument is supposed to be that they're taking over
I feel like a pure distillation of Alex's worldview is captured right there
Do whatever you want
But we people who remind me of myself a lot
That's basically the bottom line
Essentially genocide
Listen China
Go ahead with the genocide just leave me out
Continue to yell about the things that I find abhorrent
You guys are ready whenever I need to make
About you
I mean I want you to keep doing it because then I get to Yellow
So some people in the UK
We're passing along with the Muslim Community in solidarity
Fasting for holy month of Ramadan in solidarity with Muslims
So this is dim Democrat leader over there
Is promoting you know
Sexualization of children everything
Sure
30 Rock
Today
Ramadan
I won't see you shortly
To this month
I'm not saying this as a child molester
Reaping
Is it here all the Muslims
Virtue signaling
Disgusting to see the way that Alex was so wantonly use accusations
Anyone he wants to attack
If you decide to engage in an act to make non-white non-Christian groups feel welcome in society
That's enough to trigger Alex
Like it's crazy
Yeah it doesn't take much to go from just regular old evil globalist obviously
He looks like a pedifier
There's also something interesting
Because I'm sure
What are the folks that was doing this gesture in solidarity a guy named Ian Manning
Are you planning to do this fast for Ramadan
But eat so you woke up in the morning and he tweeted a picture of his breakfast pre-fast included bacon
Apologize I realize
Whoops a doodle
Whoever
You know whoever is nice to people I don't like
Sonreal
What a disgusting monster totally
So
Alex
I've got so we haven't heard from in a little bit
He is
The guy who
Has been known
To have his own currency
Sure sure better tip you off
Before he comes on air
Scott is going to pop in
History show on RT
Just turned into a
Promotion I'm going to end it
Alakazam
Just trying to push people into
Particularly through the channels
Rite Aid or Thursday
You and Alex
Hey Alex
I tried to give you a ton of Bitcoin worth millions
Alfred me
Like 1,000 Bitcoin when they were worth a penny
Dial like
Sure
More than more than 10 for Alex
Sense of how rich Max geyser is
Dammit most likely
Evil always win
A lot of milk
Dobbs
Alex
Before you get to the center of the day
Put play
The Red Rocker Sammy Hagar
A boy
Anymore
This is this is a Gordon
This is important.
Sammy Hagar
So
Cabo Wabo
You know what
Booze that's interesting
I was going to DUI a little bit ago
Because then you know no one will have it over me or anything
Bad news about that
I was
To tell a story trailer
Pier 14
Wait what
Is Mommy
Yet another story that didn't happen
Party my friends are
Jennifer's birthday out ever it is
They all showed up to the liquor store by Cameo
To get some beer and wine for a party that I shouldn't
Be going to
Man this is amazing
This
He's
Man
I've never heard an interview like this how long does it last
The entire time
I thought I was going to be
Cuz
I don't even know how to set this up
I've never heard somebody do something
And I'm going to change your viewers
Alive
Dealers
Free Bitcoin
Right now
Promo code
$10
Free Bitcoin
Accused some sec
This the first time learning of this
Okay we're going to
Make a solution available
Listeners
Experience
Prison
$10
Free
Bitcoin.com
She's outside the system
Just not even respect little volume
Get across the border with money that's yours
I told you I like
You're on the show I need you by Plumb
What circulation
I thought you were ready to go into
Shut off my break
That's why I'll just got to produce your show man
That is brewdog destroyed by Owen
I surprised Alex
The URL stand
Drug that's such an ass kicking is a flex of the highest order
Before the interview if you start selling interview
Not only doesn't end the interview
Max
He has to prepare that
Just completely
Forced Alex into that
Play Power imbalance Max knows he can
What's on the show
You Makes Me Maybe suspect that this is broker program
Another possible explanation
Is that you know
We're looking at how she is treating Joe Rogan
Spotify deals
It's just like hey my world this this is how we would browse doing
Job way
I can't wait to take advantage of a moral buckedup way
Makeup for all of them
Dollars of Bitcoin is what when 1001 something terrible
So Alex in this next
If they come back and kick Max off a little bit
But the problem that Alex has
Is he's not getting paid
Fix the problem
Understand
Get rid of the preamble
Call Liza mobile
Important that we get this information out there at 7.
Alex
Good being like it's always like that makes me think that
You make me think of those are his primary considerations Maybe
Negotiations were Max's been like you'll get all this money
Alex is out front
If we use one of those f****** referral program
Maybe knowledge
Keisha
You know
By the time this interview wraps up it feels like Alex's come around on it
What is also telling his audience like hey this is bad news but I'm okay with it
Separately
Moving away from animal put up your lur to put out for folks one again
I think as long as you take it is that
Why are you allowing someone
To sell your audience cheese on a mousetrap
I think what China is doing with Lakeline is horrific
And it's terrible also hey you do what you do just so long as I don't get f***** up my audience yeah I would like
No interest in all of this
People you swindled
Weird
Nonsense
27th and by this point
Trump has started to make some noise
About
Sure
Support.com
Close down social media
They're blocking the President telling people that
California
New York
There are five states in the United States that conduct
Elections by mail
Colorado Oregon Washington and Utah
There's no indication of any increased fraudulent Behavior
California Nebraska and North Dakota all allow counties to decide if they want to do mail-in ballots for their elections
Bunch of other places that allow
Varying degrees
This entire talking point from the right wing is exclusively about trying to suppress the vote
Is there people have to go to crowded building
Devote you're going to convince at least a portion of them to stay home
And this election in particular seems
It's just about who has more folks
Come out
In that environment if you're looking to win
The best strategies
To suppress voter
They're waves collection safely but they're going to have to include some of these remote voting strategies
Impossibly allowing voting over a week instead of one spread out the number of people at polling location
The number of ideas people have floated
You can expect Trump in his mouth pieces to resist all such measures or suggest
This being inherently fraudulent
And please do know that their concerns aren't sincere at all
CBS News reported last week that White House Press Secretary Kayleigh mcenany
They're attacking Malin
She herself voted by mail in every election since November 2008
It's not a fraudulent system when they use it but it is when you do
Are you I'm s-so
Media has failed us entirely on this
Because that should be this entire thing should literally be like
Republicans are lying to suppress the vote
Talk about voter fraud
Don't even mention voter fraud whatsoever
Just say
That the Republicans are lying to suppress the vote
It just
Yeah that's it that's all you need to do even pretending to take them seriously is doing every
One such a huge disservice
So it turns out Trump
Is on the warpath
Cuz we live in the single worst timeline that I can
Is also still Palace intrigue
You have nothing against
Personally
If that is what you believe that you have to believe that Trump
Is fine
Having them
High-level advisers and to have
Google up their ass or whatever
This is so stupid is Trump and I want him to have complete
Total power as much as possible
Well that's just how it works and I'm fine with that I look I think it's bad but I still want him to be God.
God I hate this is a nonsensical
Gap
So we we not revisit this narrative about Democrats sending covid patients
Cancel destination
51%
Domino's
Think about
The cold-blooded miss I miss the UN comes up with it
Put out
Yeah think about the cold-blooded mythology
People with pneumonia
The one group that was killing that they knew
Not really
54000 dollars
Gravy you got your chicken fried steak
Name five more Foods
Alex is hungry
So couple things to remember in terms of nursing homes
Is particularly vulnerable populations
Higher there than in the general population
A second thing is that because we all understand that Dynamic much more stringent testing
Care facilities
And for the general population
Because it's really important to know
Resume comparison in Massachusetts there's a 90% threshold that's required for testing
Where is the general
There's no requirement
Obviously I'm not trying to minimize the issue the fact that a lot of people are dying in these nursing homes easy horrible tragedy
I only want to provide a little context for Alex
Bulshit
Also I'm not sure
About his statistics about the ratio of deaths in nursing home
According to a May 26th release from the AARP
Approximately 16000 people who are in nursing homes
Either residence or staff have died from covid-19
Didn't close
You have the number United States I'm not entirely sure
A couple of things that were
I think one of the things that was getting
Is there are like
Some states where the number is much
Percentage of people who are interested Holmes is like
You know 50
50%
Of the deaths in the state and then in New York it's like
13% might be getting mistranslated is not waiting these numbers correct
I think I'm not entirely sure I don't want to
Say for sure but that AARP thing is pretty recent
They're in the business of knowing things about retirees seems like now their lasso
I'm not entirely sure
I don't even particularly care to get into the stupid conspiracy by Democrat States intentionally
Nursing homes because honestly it's nuts and wanted more dangerous possible.
Could be advancing as a conspiracy theory right now
There's no excuse for this kind of thing and he is absolutely no proof of anything like this is happening
Outside of an executive order Governor Whitmer signed
But he hasn't read
His theory is that
Teen cases in nursing home so they could infect everyone it doesn't make a lot of money by scamming
And then the steak is power or whatever
This theory is stupid but it gets even stupider when you consider that on March 4th
The centers for Medicare and Medicaid services released
They put into place additional regulations related to screening and infection containment protocol at nursing home
If not followed
Results
Disqualification
From participation in Medicare and Medicaid
For behaving in the ER
There's a memo here that makes
The clear that they would be ineligible to collect the money Alex things as one of their main motivation
All of the money from Medicare and Medicaid
Go to jail
Yeah this is fun games for Alex
Something for him
Absolutely reprehensible
It's normal for Alex but it is
F****** villain
It's tough to look at because these are very sensitive things
I mean with the amount of Rage
That is
Everywhere
It's just it's so irresponsible to
Suddenly just blame
The all of the fuc
People trying to help are now the people that are Target
Get to
All these f******
So there are number of states that Alex Democrat states that are doing
Patsy have
Primarily here Michigan
Governor Whitmer and then New York is also apparently at Alex's crosshairs
Because of something about their website
Documents
Website quietly delete
Controversial,
Federal state law New York
Delete delete
1663 u.s. code justice.gov
New York
So scared of beautiful
Although I'm so scared of beautiful
So I really enjoy the turn of phrase
You know Alex always shoes
Yeah let's get into the article
The website of the New York
That's not the same thing as deleting a record
Statute that's completely unrelated to removing some website
Trump's Administration taken off websites and Alcove care about that at all
Worried about the EPA and climate change
In this Daily Mail article spokesperson said that this was just a situation where there was update
Built upon the original declaration so they replaced
The original guidance
Failing to understand is pretty much without exception
All of these situations that he's talking about with these Democratic Governors and all this
These orders are about making explicit that Health Centers could not discriminate
About which patients they would or would not accept
Based on their covid status
This is about creating risks
Nursing home
Ensuring patients rights to care
So they're even rules in place that it places
Cannot accept patients if they are unable to provide adequate care
Including staff screening CPE
And infection
Control measure
So even in the original thing that was taken down from the website
Proper update
If these places aren't up to the task
Housing and given adequate care to patients who tested positive then they
The original order is
Hospitals are probably going to turn away poor people and then the other order is
But if you can't
Do anything then you can't
Do anything
And people who are in
Long-term care facilities have specialized needs that may not be able to be helped
Normal hospital or just a regular run-of-the-mill Hospital
There might be a particular reason why
They need to be taken care of by specialist
And denying people Healthcare based on
Their conditions America's way
It's it's
Negative consequences for people
Who would be refused care
And so
Primarily New York
And Michigan were misrepresented around
Because of course
And that's where he's getting into this
They sent these people in with the coronavirus in order to in
In fact these people
And now he's getting to the point
Premeditated
I'm kind of insinuating that you should go show up at hospital
The people that took Medical
I just spent the whole first hour on that I'm having trouble getting off of it
To go physically
Places
I hate you
Person rabbit they love the power
Kill an old person
Besides shades
Insinuations of murdering children in math
Kind of same vibe
Because no one teaches him less
Cuz nobody is held accountable when you're in the right wing
Apparently no rules
He does these things
Potential consequences
Racine
The patterns of behavior that are facilitated by people
You know encouraging this
People don't start showing up at hospitals
Thinking you're going to
Free
Elderly patients who are being
Hospital
Alex should be immediately removed
You probably won't
So his next clip Alex
Continues on this theme
I'm talking about how all of his enemies
Everybody throw zombies maybe you should probably kill him
Hey Mary hey
Look
Caleb at the most
Legal limit that I can get Iowa
But I'm not doing it
Zombie
Jamey Johnson
What
The zombie one
Because he doesn't have brain
Allegory
What
You got brain
You got a husband and you got a wife
You got a lot
You got a charger you love God you're not perfect
But you believe you don't like it
Do you think you can make a deal with a zombie
You throw a zombie me over your fence
You're thinking of possums
Placating
Violet
Governor
Whitmar
Good cowardly America
So if you're not a good calendar
Turn them into
Shut the last thing we want is a little hair on American soil
Lycos had to be hard
We need to destroy his name
Monstrous
Them to be indicted
If I were a dishonest actor I would have cut that after
You know that
Clearly
Would kill the governor
And I don't think that that part at the end actually takes away my problem
I mean that's just the same thing as I'm going to kill them politically
You can walk away from that exact same impression
And it's just like
Add a recent downsides to killing him but maybe you should or maybe not I don't know
Also he's really just describing
The Scarecrow but I guess like George Romero's take on the Scarecrow
Yeah there's some problems I get really tired of
I get really tired of doing like Alex Jones literary analysis
Lower history
He's wrong about everything pretty much everything
Best clips from May 27th
It's Alaska because
Tower of the f****** show is libertarian
Former Satanist
Priest guy was named I've already forgotten
Click
Yes
Don't give a s***
It is a
A real
Real disaster
Yeah I used to be
It sucks quite annoying
So you're the last clip
Is Alex lying about the Twitter stock
Check
Declaim
The 2020 election was stolen
Please
There's a rattlesnake
Don't stick your hand out at you're going to get bit
Maybe it's not hungry
Maybe it doesn't bite you
That was not their problem
Their problem was
Primarily twofold
One is that there isn't evidence that mail-in ballots have a higher propensity for fraud
And the second is that
What Trump was doing
Was literally an explicit
Of election
Misinformation
We primarily use mail
What you saying is that your system of election
Is rice
Is
Peaceful transition of power at the end of 20 the electoral process of at least five states
Well you'll be very concept of an electoral
You back he would prefer not to have
Twitter fact-checks things not because
Ridiculous
I'm going to be real sad day
Navigate to the 28th Thursday show
And
I thought this was going to be because of things are happening
In the world
Particularly in Minneapolis
I was pretty shocked when we opened the show
I know that there's a lot of different political ideas looks systems out there in the world
What I do
Robber Baron dynasties actually believe interrupter show
Cuz you run propaganda for a McGriddle to this show it's the reason
Broadcast
It's the reason that millions of people
Know what you're talkin about
Today
And this is real in this is unfiltered
Now
I'll just an Australian I'll just in UK but now the US has come out the state park
Confirmed they knew they were doing bio weapons
Development
Viruses
You know what that means
That means
So this is how we starting to show he's talking about
I tried to find with this disarray State Department
Snowy
I was I was
Completely thrown
I heard the air-raid sirens I thought for sure you'd be talking about the situation is unfold
Immediately but he does get to it pretty quickly
What he does is something that I
I think
Yo
I kind of have a sense of how things are going to go
I think there's probably a lot of people who figured you was blow up in
Freak out
What are you going to do is give a patronizing call for Unity
Yeah this is where Alex
It turns out I was Gray
Dodger said be positive
Positive talk about what unifies US
Because that's weather
Music
Really
Fun
All of us
Black or white
Similar cases of white cop sitting on top
Like I said smiley bags is terrible footage
You want just one of those you killed
Portrait
About 8 minutes
1 sides locked up
To death so you don't like it
All the people died in nursing homes with
Blond
Quiet
Crazy cover
Black beating up white
All
Going on
Evil Fallen
In general
You can look at those images and then look at all the
People burning down Target
Applewhite ladies to their white
It's all stupid
The people perish for lack of knowledge
Are going to win their coming after
Like I said this is about
Come to expect from whataboutism injury
Instead of being a brutal Act of horrific violence doesn't know what he's doing
Just be very initial framing of this is indicative of Oz angle to minimize the murderer
In focus on the public backlash
To what was felt to be an inadequate response firing Wisconsin
Alex does not give a f*** about this story or George Floyd
Just gotten too big for him to ignore
I can see that pretty comfortably considering that this is the first time the story has come up
Thursday episode
Has killed on Monday evening be released soon after
Alex could have easily brought this up on the show on Tuesday if he was
Concerned about the cops action
Stupidly minimize on the Coronavirus
Large protests
Took place on Tuesday police responded protesters with percussion
Which is a very Stark technical difference
The way the police responded
Invading State Building
Complain about Starbucks
Enclose just a few weeks ago
Valic scared about this story you could have covered the protests that took place on Tuesday on his Wednesday show
He's too busy lying about Democratic Governors intentionally infecting Coronavirus
Interviewing the satanic libertarian
The protests were in response to the police department just firing officers who were involved instead of charged with murder
That was force
On Wednesday night there were more protesting again
The police used tear gas
Flashbangs
To try and disperse the crowd
There was property damage and the chaos
Look at the ensuing events and not understand exactly how this happened and how he could have easily been
Completely averted
The situation is still ongoing and I do not recording feel like I have enough information
Grasp
A lot of the intricacies things I've been trying to keep up as best I can but I feel like
It's very difficult
For me to fully
Understand b b b b
Yeah
Towards the evening
I don't know what's going on
Get to into coverages.
Alex's
Doesn't care
About that
Here's
If This Were reverse
So to speak
If this was a white probe
And they have done what they done
Alex would immediately be like
This country was started because of property damage
The Tea Party damaged property
Then they don't listen then you have to get louder in the only way to get louder and make them listen is with property damage
So I don't know
I don't care
I don't give a fuk with any of these right-wing dum-dums have to say I don't know everything but these
People shut the f***
Just shut the fuk
So what's going on here is the Alex wants to take the initial inciting event
A murder of a subdued man in police custody and say well that's a shame
He can pay lip service to the initial is at
Existing narrative
About the nursing home
20 year old beat up that elderly guide
Even in the way Alex connects these stories
He's picking
Little concession that George Floyd
Temping killed
The story without saying it's bad things to which tells you all you need to know
It's imperative for Alex to find ways to refocus the story of the
A defenseless black man by the police
Are you done that is
It'll bring up in
Instances of unrelated bad things
And to reframe stories
Disgusting
Protest
In such ways to Center white people's Victor Wood stories as the main thing to really worry about like woman in the wheelchair
He's talking about this is supremely unsurprising
Wrapped up in
Being entirely about white identity
People always under attack
We feel like
Especially compared to his rhetoric from the 26th and 27th where he's like
Literally murdering people
And then you look at the racial disparity in not just police violence but in the attack
People and there's it's hard not to
Is passive genocide going on and then an active
And it's
So yeah wants to Center
White victimhood
So
Surprise
About
We just do this
Let's just play 14 radio listeners
45 clips
The Looting and the rioting in the race
In LA
Minnesota
You know this is how he's starting out
Discussing the story is by
Apria
Front loading
The stories about tax on whites
And scary black people looting
Are focusing on that angle of the story is a way to contextualize things
It's intentional it's what Alex is doing
The first two jobs he's achieved
What he plans to do
Is making a guy
You shouldn't have died you should have been killed him, didn't know what he was doing
And the second is
Center everything around White
Alex
Appeal to you
Protesters multi-generational multiracial
And the people on the other side are white
It does seem that way
Another part of this
It has to be done is Alex
Make excuses
For the officer
And here
People
And somebody
Killing killing
Yes he did
Dumbass said no about Anatomy
He's a murderer
Unis Robinson carotid artery Bubba
He's a dumbass like so many other people there dumb cops are good cops
You're dumb doctors are good doctor
Bad
People people they're good people
Dumbass you can see you soon
Enjoying it
He's in charge
All he's doing
Is murdering his whole life
Along with George Floyd
I'm here
DC primary teachers
Alex's white apologize
The problem is shuffling Blaine
Guarantee
But the cop had no idea that he was killing Floyd
You go back to the beginning when I clip his exact words were close
And I'm glad people have some Humanity when they see somebody
Penndel baking
For their life
He said that right before saying that the cop didn't know he was killing him
Alex can watch this video and see
For his life
The others couldn't see this
I think you can see how this doesn't come anywhere close to passing the smell test analysis isn't making sense
Doesn't situations like this
Is addiction a real meaningful blame away from White aggressors against non-white people
We saw this recently in the case of Ahmad
Suspicious
And after they chased him down he defended himself
This is a softening of the way in which the murderer is discussed
Same thing here
The cop is only responsible for this
Which is kind of cowardly position
The Daily Beast reported on May 28th about a man named IRA tolls
Missing number of other incidents in the Scots history
A generous reading valances positions is that he's naive
But I'm past the point of generosity
He's calling to stop an idiot and that he had no idea
Out tonight the story
Make up his own narrative about it
So this is a game ticket
Get played
I am certain
It's beyond
It's just beyond what you can
Reasonably expect from a human being
As he says
With a
Yep
So he wants to do that with take a natural human reaction to empathy
To feel the concern the outrage
YouTube
Well I mean
Play the clip
Video
Which we won't be listening to on the show
This is what he says immediately after
You just watch them
Kill me
Murder
I want you to check what you just saw
56,000 people
White young
But mainly old
Hospital
Me and murdered
Opposed
I mean this very sincerely
Determined
He's hoping to take whatever rightful responsive to see the police kill a defenseless man
Shoes of police brutality or racial differences in policing
Appointed squarely at his narrative
It's an attempt to basically take over the story by way of minimizing it and co-opting it which is really shity
It's pretty clear to pay
Yeah
So Alex is
Seriously Focus
On doing this
Shifting
The narratives
And also insisting
The cop didn't know what he was doing
Was listening to this clip
I had some very visceral flashbacks
Two other things we've covered on this episode
I'll explain myself
On the other side
Show us the footage
Police officer committed manslaughter
Murder
Somebody
So this is murder
Dumbass cop
Did not know he was gay
Murdered
Knowing you
Because
He should be punished more
Kathy empathize for everybody
62 million babies would kill
Millions have been kept alive
Don't you think about them
About
Neither is f****** Floyd anymore
Good
Not all those old people in all those babies and you ask
Where are the people piss upset about that
Where's the targeted action
Call Target
You'll burn down Target
Kill the black guy what about the people
Like I said when I was listening to
I had a visceral
Flashback
I felt sick
And I realized
That the way Alex was talking about this current tragedy
Who's exactly what he did the day after the Charleston shooting
You're so Alex open to show on June 18th
Charleston on the East Coast
Looking young man
Church last night
Shooting and killing execution-style
9 black people
On a
White on black racial attack
And this is one of these events that I call a Rosetta Stone
This event look at every angle of our problem
Front
Sarcastically
Dylann roof
Himself wearing South African
And patches
John and God
Medical school to be an abortionist
Thousands of black people in his career
And be called a great number of society
Racist
This is one of Alex's big strategies for minimizing violence against non-white
If you ever find yourself caring about an unarmed minority being murder
Which should help you to stop caring so much
Preclude you from ever considering the things we could do as a society to stop
You never
And I mean never
This strategy is a crime against the wipers
Can you imagine him responding to the Kate steinle shooting by saying it's terrible and sad
Consider
Of course not
He use my breath for months to argue against the US allowing in any immigrants
This is a technique
Alex wants to look like
To broaden the scope of the story
Psycho take this and consider
But in reality these trying to shift
Stories like these two are very threatening to Alex
About them
The best lip service to the very clear reality
And then tried argue that the real story is abortion
Why do bog down and bickering about one death when there are so many baby
Math never gets
Deploy to distract from
It is in reality his way of minimizing of non-white death
And it's very clear
If you pay attention
So this is a bummer
One thing I find pretty interesting is that Alex doesn't stay on the story all that long
Just got a touch
Do this thing and then move along
For too long is not in his best interests of his audience
Or into
No they already didn't care you don't need to convince them not
And so we jumped from here onto just talking more about gay
Gates and vaccines
Wow wow
Junior
Can a mother Children's Health
In the news
Bill Gates
To have 700,000 people get sticker.
20% is not 1,000
Seven and a half billion people
Adverse reaction
What 20%
7 + 1/2
Billion people
You clearly don't ya
Plus million people
We all know the math
Wow
I bet
So Alex
The touchdown that over the course
No connection with reality
Vaccine story visagist anti-vax propaganda that's being put out by Robert Kennedy Jr
The headline of the story is quote another Gates vaccine Bites the Dust which Alex's interpreting as a story about a vaccine not working
Misrepresenting the results of preliminary trials
This Kennedy articles are in the process of development
What is from moderna which is a course Spanish for mother
Nickelback I don't have to wake up
I got a. Do jokes like that
The press release titled moderna announces positive interim Phase 1 beta
MRNA vaccine against novel Coronavirus
The other is a different vaccine which is being tested on macaque
Kennedy in his article rights quote
Vaccinated mechanics sickened after exposure to covid-19
The wintry provide is to the pre-publication data of the University of Oxford
V Network website
If you read it you'll find this line
Asaurus CO2 challenge post-vaccination
Clinical symptoms in 5 out of 6 vaccinated disease progression compared to non-vaccinated
Which is what
Kennedy recorded in this article
He's an a****** isn't as the receipts take seriously on this issue but Alex is more than happy to blindly accept his narrative
Cuz they help attack vaccine
Man that's wild that the son of a guy who
What who is like
Transformed into a bit of a progressive hero many people fantasy book on creating a better America
Bag
That's a real bummer
It's just a step in the process
Super 20% number that Alex seems to be citing
I think he was percent of the monkeys got sick or something share
But that was about the Kennedys article
Time trials
Moderna press release which is what is a supposed to be sourced from
In a related fraction anywhere in the press release
I honestly have no idea where that number is coming from because it's not in the source
Nor is any indication that there were high incidence of adverse reactions
Really seems to all to be made up
No one is suggesting given
Anyone that vaccine or any percent negative reaction rate
Is that number were actually reflected in the data that would be one thing because I understand
Next is figuring out what went wrong
This seems like another
Honestly
I found it offensively Petty
Serious stuff going on right now
Junior's nonsense child
It appears to be made of
I think
Almost any other issue than the
What's going on in Minneapolis
Is probably
Small potatoes in terms of
Relevant
What's going on in the world
Alex
We talked about so I could attack
So I am disappointed by talking about a dumb Gates vaccine thing
However
I'm not disappointed by this next clip
Is this is where he commits
The felony
I think he's lying
Even f****** serious trouble
Not about taking credit
Taking stock
President
Cuz if you did
Why do hats
Pollock
Play the biggest in d.c.
Dried up grass
Executive orders
Commission
People in jail
Medication
Very close on like in the chair
What you doing
He's talking about Trump's executive order about social media
Keith Urban
According to that last clip
What's the number for firms to draw up some plans for Trump to uses
Executive order
Apparently signed today
I don't believe any of its real
But if we pretend it is let's consider some ramifications of this admission
But I don't think Alex realizes he say
E-40 saying is true
No longer fake journalist
He's no longer broadcaster
Use explicit
The argue for specific desired legislation is basically the definition of lobbying
And guess what
If Alex
Did you what you saying and he didn't report the money spent
You could get arrested for that
That is very illegal
Assuming that he's not making this up
According to the lobby disclosure disclosure Act of 1995
If you will employ lobbyists and you're not a non-profit
You have to register with the secretary of state and the clerk
Of the House of Representatives
You don't need to register if you spend less than $11,500 but Alex said he spent a lot of money on this
The top three firms in d.c.
So he's not making s*** up he's been more than 11 five
What's the top three law firms in d.c. are not giving out
F****** president
Small Potatoes
People who are in the position Alex's pretending
Activity
So can lead to a fine of up to $200,000
There's an additional problem Becomes of this
Regarding lobbyist
And that is what I want to show
Popcorn
Affirms to Lobby to Trump
Positive coverage that Alex
Is a form of donation in kind
Which could be considered a gift
Trump
Sycophantic exuberance Alex says for everything Trump does
Could be reconsidered as an illegal donation to try to sway the
The person you're
In terms of enacting legislation or in this case an executive order
Which could
Make you see much bigger crime
If someone were to investigate this
And find that Alex had actually done this
Which I still don't necessarily think
He actually did Al Capone tax evasion
Situation
I don't believe
3 top law firms
Is normal blowhard narcissist braggart self
You can't stand to not make himself the center of everything
He's not lying
He better have reported that s***
Like I searched
The US Senate lobbying disclosure act database Alexander
Or anyone associated with Infowars or Free Speech system
I can see that he could have some fake business name but he's hiding under that's possible but
It's better we better
F****** hope that no one decides to investigation
This could get you jammed up
Please
Play Somebody
Something to bad people just once
In my life I would like to see something bad done too bad it's just random weird thing to be discussing
Second person
Actually I kind of used
When I hear that
That's somebody else's story
Somebody else did that and Alex has been like
Oh that sounds like a good story for me to be
Mostly cooked up by someone from the Heritage Foundation
It's possible that I'm just saying
Probably isn't Medicare
Call Barb
Alex isn't going to say that's why then
774 nuclear submarines I was building
I wasn't trying to get 74 golf course I was trying to get something for supper
Something from the present for me
Yes you did
Or be back on Facebook and Twitter
Everybody
So I guess trying to come from but legally that doesn't matter at all
You're still required to report
Stupid
Even point
Bulshit
Social media platforms like Twitter Facebook and YouTube would be worth millions in Revenue to Alex
Lobbying the president to try to force these companies to allow you on their platform
Yeah the subsidy or not it's the same thing
A big deal firms a ton of money
President to do something
Back on social media social media
Everything's get murky
Trump's executive order is trying to take away the legal protection that these platforms have regarding what
Posted
Princeton's if you post some copyrighted material on YouTube YouTube isn't held response
That's the nature of
The dynamic
In terms of being a platform for
The publisher
You know like it's Alex Jones educates people about a satanic eating children at a pizza place Twitter isn't responsible for
No sex
If you platforms have to take responsibility for the things that individuals post
They will not exist anymore
It's equivalent to them like breaking the toy that someone won't let them play with because
You know the other person's last time we played together you punch them in the face
That's the mentality operating from
If it does work on his only service to humanity
Destroying all of these companies
Disabling their online community
Running a place to assume responsibility for everything anyone Post in their space
It's no longer worth it
Open Spaces up for
Communication
Also a whole lot of people are
Really only still on social media because the individual companies aren't responsible for what they post
If anything removing that protection will only result in a way way more strict content rules
Also
It will never really hate everybody
The media has failed us on a level that is
Incomprehensive even even legally this is Quest
Probably won't work out
It's a stupid short-sighted authoritarian
It'll definitely has nothing to do with Alex is supposed
Sloppy
Fact check on Trump's tweet clear instances
Electoral
Information
I was using the apparatus of the stage retaliate against a private company which is constitutional
Alex
Oh well use the federal government private business
These predictions are going to kill Trump
Sure he actually has a specific
Prediction
One to write down I don't think it's going to come through but
Here are some of the predictions that he's got going
Women come out
Already did
You got that going on
BB's Earth-like kinetic normal predict
Alex has a total what feels like preemptive damage
Control as standard stop
Alex is the China going to move in on Hong Kong which
He's against
I wonder does he not know that the Trump Administration just certified in Hong Kong is no longer considered autonomous from shein
Does the Alex not realize that Mike Pompeo came out and just declared that this Wednesday
Is that what's really that unaware of the real world that he doesn't realize that he's team
Is already signaled The Bayview Hong Kong is part of China most likely as way to ratchet up tensions with China
Like this is critically important to understand
Austin
Nothing nothing
Pompeo
Cool that's
I don't like a b****
So
NSX could we get back to the summit
Feelings about
George Floyd
What are the things
But I wanted to bring up
First of all
The way I would say that's the narratives
It brings up like consider the abortion
It's something that is explicitly and specifically done on his show
In order to minimize
Non-white victims survive
Is one thing that is very important
I think it's essential that we highlight
In terms of this cover
This second comes up in this club
The point is though
And their children a reason needs to go out
Kurdish military
Well it's uniform
These are white
At least the first step to understanding
The first level of fighting
First level
The Real Enemy
Engineered all of this
Politically stand up
Politics in life
State Building
Interesting about this is I think this is how Alex thinks
I think of the time you think that's what it says
We should go after them politically you think he thinks
I think that Alex
Boot licker
Might believe
This is how he always react to situations like this
But it's only true when there's white on black crime
He's like we need to kill these people and find them in their house
Politically he thinks it's the same as being like
If you guys put all of that
Revolutionary energy into just really engaging with the political process
All the time
Response to
Hey
You see someone do something really bad to an innocent civilian and what you do is you respond
To these markers about them like they're white or they're a cop
Good that you get mad about that but you need to focus
Alex
Tendon
That is the way he behaved Universal
And it is not true
Like I said this is only true
Okay sis where there's white on black crime committed genocide
He absolutely doesn't encourage people to look past the racer position of the perpetrator when there's a situation with a white fish
Victim
In those cases
He's very much about seeing who did something and indicting an entire group
When Kate steinle die Daleks created an entire imagine storyline
And then killed her because he thought that the
The dad was her boyfriend
He was jealous that he couldn't be with this
Beautiful white woman
Alex cover Discovery dishonestly and racistly per month
Despite evidence coming out in trial that completely contradicted his made-up version of the story
And at no point was the
The identity of the person being blamed for the death
And focus on the globalist
What Alex was covering the story
He was doing so to agitate specifically against
And he use the entirely fabricated version of it that his perverted mind dreamt as a weapon
Against a vulnerable community
It's important to understand this
Alex sounds so conciliatory and like he's Above The Fray when he's here on are saying that it's sad that died
It bog down and who did it
Focus on the evil globalist
That's part of Alex's trick
It's a misdirection
And it's so obvious when you consider how these stories get cover
To refresh your memory
Here's a little clip
Discovery Kate steinle stat
Making up details
And editorializing like crazy
Shot
The 31-year old
He was found about a mile away or later arrested
If he has an attorney I would want
She was loving smart beautiful
Complained
She was smoking hot that's why
Young woman
Help me help me
So you see the complete different
Absolute
I don't know I want to come up with $5 word for essential
Different quintessential sure go for a structural difference
It's in the way these things are presented
And make no mistake
Episode
Singularly focused on the identity of the
Complaining about how know headlines about
Undocumented
When was a single
Popping sound in here we don't call the cops
Illegal
God
And so
She fell the ground well I mean
Alex is not above
Afraid he's not above the right left Paradigm Egypt
Pretends to be because that tricks idiot
Reasonable ideas
Racist ideology
This is part of the gigantic trick that I'll explain what you think about like
How much
Mileage you got out of people being like
Yeah man
Sure sure he hates to
Like okay what you're trying to imply is that he's somewhere in the middle and he calls out everybody know
The bush because Bush wasn't far-right enough
Cuz he was black
That kind of distills in
Alex really wants to in these situations
Like when there is
A very obvious case of a white police officer killing an unarmed black man
You can't deny it
You can't make up a story about it can't do anything like that
He has to
Rely on this
She got to be above it
You don't fall for the globalist tricks
And then when the situation is the opposite
Let's get all immigrants out of the country
They're just jealous of beautiful white people
If you understand that difference
Goes a long way towards understanding
The way that Alex Bill to content
And how he hides the true character of what he does
What do you believe
And what he wants his audience to
I mean I would assume he wants them to get from his show
I guess that might be a little much
For me to assume but
I that's what it seems like tonight
So there's this there's that angle to
He's a he's also spreading the worst
F****** vitriol that will get people killed that I can think
Yeah I'm not sure I'm not sure I take bilking racist out of money but I guess it's fine
Centralized
This was really bad
Waiting to go through this again
And really have
The the hindsight
The Kate steinle situation
The Charleston shooting
With Alex's coverage to be able to
Look at the situation
You start to see things
In a more robust way
And job
It's it's tragic
It's awful
The real life situation
It's tragic and awful the way Alex
Makes things into a farce
Does with the rest of the show
You're called out of respect for the hour
Covid-19
He's got a new piece
Will be premiering here with us today
As well
So you cheating on Carpe donktum
Cover of Corey Hart I wear my sunglasses
What about wearing a mask
Cool
Call Rich
We're doing musical comedy
I told her doing
We're doing a right-wing Weird Al
Great it only goes
For half an hour cuz there is zero chemistry between these two dudes
Alex doesn't get
I think you might get
That the dude is trying to do some B
It's really bad
Like I told you earlier
Stupid interview is dumb dumb meme guy
Alex is a specific prediction
About the attempt
To kill Trump
Doesn't happen
Alex will pretend you never said it
Trump
Explosive devices
Spots
Months ago
Inside construction Crews on normal Construction route
Secret Service should
Not the president around any recent construction site
Like the last 6 months
I'm serious
Centramatic
Okay filo dramatico
Decoy helicopters
Real bunch of
Construction sites
You don't want to
You got to have some flavor you know like
Of course if you put hundreds of IEDs around
The only person who will be affected by those
Everybody knows that the ability to coordinate multiple IEDs being buried at
Construction site
Doesn't see what you need to go
Just not that hard
It'll keep it simple stupid really does apply to assassinations as well I really feel like Alex Jones just like
His brain just comes up with Rube Goldberg
So what's going to happen is one of those.
Decoy helicopters
Start a chain reaction of dominoes that are going to graduate
That's what I get all the way up
Stuck under the house that he had down there was a game of
Mousetrap just got real f*****-up on those fumes
So now we get to this meme dork Sheila and his name is via bear
This is really interesting because
There is no way I believe that Alex
Wrote this intro
Absolutely disguise script
Well rarely does an ad
Occasionally
Surpass the original
Sunglasses
Has been clipped
Yes is example of dutiful
Beautiful
ER
I'm surprised by the way
Not hard to outdo Corey Hart I wear my sunglasses
Classic everyone everyone sings that song on purpose
Not very good
So they talked about this meme
I really give a s***
To get into
Substance with him
It's really sad
They're in the news Chang
Mountain climbing accidents
That's not true also
What are you saying is I don't know how to find them
Very short amount of time compared to other things
F****** idiot
Like I understand he's a troll
Like yeah YouTube
Is about
Allocution
Are people answering questions answers
Go fuc yourself
Walk out of my life you know what time it is for you
It's a f****** Sugar Ray outside
Barely even started
I made all f****** dumb
Corey Hart cover
Alright you're having too much scoffin right now I do
No I meant that in the largest earlier
Jokester
He's wearing a mask throughout the entire anime
Who is this
Disney commercial break
We're going out to commercial
Media bear decided to start doing a bit
Where
A contact Tracer showed up at his house
Tell him that he
They rushed
Dogman
I'm just busy being a hero right now
Has great content
You really are
Biological weapon release
Biological
MB like animals
Giving improv Partners like seeing partners that you really want to have
In about
Alex Jones all that list
Everybody is taken like a stage 1 Second City class and hasn't had that guy
Oh I got this voucher for my business cuz they said it was a public speaker it's the time the funniest guy
The office Michael Scott office.
Almost can't think of things that are like
What is
Defining
Viscerally
Vicodin the exact
Feeling of no
It's
I feel like media bear doesn't like Alex. Alex doesn't like
It's just trash
And Natalie Portman and then there's
There's also a farce to it like I said it like
First of all
It's pretty important
Spending a half-hour talking to this dick
I think it probably ended early and close calls and wasn't call the stupid
But there is one episode
This caller think
Did the best thing Trump can do is rehire Flynn
Michael Flynn
Will piss people off that will piss people off
True response to that is pretty
Military
The military
Exactly
Alex and commiserating about how their ideal situation is
Military people
Play speaking that's worked out
Alex
The Republic
This guy is the worst
Okay word
This is the worst
So
The weight
I really feel complete about this a little bit because these circumstances
Are ongoing
The situation Minneapolis
And
But even as we're recording probably happening that irrelevant
And by tomorrow Alex will have his Friday going over stopping
You'll feel very immediate but we can get to it till Monday and part of me was honestly considering holding off on this
Until Monday
But ultimately I just saw like
We got a
Yeah I got to take care of this
Let's go west we gets our way behind and ignore a lot of Alex's
Horrible bulshit
Horrible
Horrible Bosses
I don't know I don't know
I don't know what to say what to say sometimes
I guess
Tragedy
I would say
That I have is very similar
Two feelings I've had a number of times
Kind of like
You're just an overwhelming sense of like
Amazing we've let this get to the point
Specifically
It's so amazing to me
That like
He hasn't
Just blown up already
There hasn't been the end of his career already
Right
It's it's fascinating
Well I think it's I mean
The worst the worst thing I have bit all the way back in 2015
About
How how Trump
I thought it was very funny
And it turned out to be absolutely true but it was it was the idea of like
A used-to-be one Scandal would take you down but the trick is
If you do a new whenever
We can catch up to
And it seems like Alex has that kind of thing going on for him to where it's like
Sure he committed to go but
He's already on some new b******* I don't have time to go back
Deal with that stuff will end up catching up with
You hope I think
I don't know
That's what I'm saying about Alex to his military dictatorship who knows we'll catch up to maybe
I probably should have mentioned that this visit the beginning of the episode but I forgot because of
Issues I think it would be important for us to point out this
There was a resolution in his bankruptcy case that we brought up
And it turns out that the court rules
In dismissing the involuntary bankruptcy
And the reason for that given in this
Is that be
Deal amount that he owes that his ex-wife
Which is about $786,000 according to whatever claims are
Is less
The amount
That is the value of the property
That is backing
Buy this property
More than that amount you can't force someone into involuntary bankruptcy
Because what's security
Could cover that
Probably and maybe that's why he's been talking about selling the house because
I'm not entirely sure
My reading of this is what I can understand
There isn't
So much
Icon testing
The amount
You can't be forced into involuntary bankruptcy for it about that
His property that is backing it is greater than
Speculated about it
And so it would be wrong of us not to point
That's why I want to bring it up
The beginning of the episode
Vamps are probably listen to episodes
I think we'll see
Four other podcasts
Fingers crossed
But until then
Where website
World on Twitter
If you can please donate to the Minneapolis funds for
Bail and everything of the sort
I'm Leo and easyacc
Clark my go-to guy from medical advice is the Red Rocker Sammy Hagar
Alex
Birthstone colors