Damn important
I have great respect for its knowledge by knowledge
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Sit around drink novelty Beverages and talk a little bit
About Alex Jones
What up
For today
This is this is groovy old maybe
So I didn't realize
I like to dip you like to
I like to dip them but you are not a constellation of any sort
I'm going to be an Alex Jones improvised
Ridiculous
Next
I dip you like a sauce
But
Never considered like the way that most people have wings is the sauces
Put the sauce on their juice squeeze it on there
I didn't realize if you have Tupperware
You can put the sauce
Fingers
Ziploc bag works too
Whole New World
I finally realized
Capoeira
Lifetime how much pepper where do you have
I mean not a ton not as much as my mom probably
Periodically I will get a couple things of Tupperware
I'm just throwing away and up
Not getting reused or something
What's the easiest thing you do
Necessary
Better as I get older but it's just like
Yeah this just can't be clean this can't be washed
You know I think of
A lot of bright spots going on now
Right now
Is anxious and nervous and I'm not sure just like I can't hang right now you got to celebrate
Relation of your Rhythm to sleep right
Episode 2
Hotly anticipating whatever bulshit going to happen here
30th and 31st 2020
But Alex
Realizes
Interesting but will still go over it
News about stuff is about what you'd expect
A lot of stuff is very transparently
Course
According to show
So first FNL thank you so much you are now policy walk
I'm a policy wonk
Hey Leslie
Thomas the political Martian
Thank you so much you're an alcoholic
That Marvin PetSmart
Martian
People donated on elevator
She went outside
Heroin
Is freakishly large
These gents website
Probably your area perhaps
Generosity and throat not directions
For today
29th that's Friday Saturday and Sunday
It's get us fully up-to-speed where we are as
Escalated and deteriorated in many cities around the country
I will take on it is
Temptation
Live from Austin Texas broadcasting reply
Millie Weaver
Austin Texas broadcasting World why
Alex Jones
There's something fun about the computer
Let's hear it for the computer
So we start off I can't wait to speak to you
Alex
We start off on Friday
Then they were on Thursday
That's not safe.
I don't think Alex
I'll be there I'll include myself in this
I don't think that anyone
Maybe some people but let's just keep this upset to me and Alex
I don't think he and I
Victor necessarily that things would go as
As much of
A hard take on things
Killing
The people who are speaking out against
Ignored it until the point where he could
And
It's a big deal
On Friday it's a big deal
And you know what that means
It's time to shift
Narratives
Document
Civil unrest and martial law in Baltimore Maryland
Nationwide unrest
In 2018
Friends of democracy run by Alexander Soros
Crying trigger with
Americans
Dieting as the cover
Overthrow major city governments Obama whatever
Pretext
National martial law in 2018
It did not go the way they wanted to
It seems
I was watching things unfold on Thursday and Friday night
About to start hearing more about Soros
This is the value of Alex's strategy of having his whole list of villains
But he can pull out whenever he needs to
Ruby last four months or so
Because the relevant kind of fear use trying to explain to the characterization of Soros
The medical tyranny of the evils of vaccines those are in the Bill Gates wheelhouse so Alex Focus mode almost entirely on
Bill and Melinda Gates
Of course the new villain
Please remember
That the first time Alex
Mention fauci broadcast on February 8th
I was just pretending the fauci and said that they were investigating if
Coronavirus was man made
And that he was a hero within the administration
Once it became clear that this was all bulshit that Alex is making up
Alex pretend you never said any of those things
Thought you became a long time
Just looking
Make it up as you go along
Even decided the Bill Gates was ahead of the New World Order and had been for the past 12 years or so
Alex claimed the gates reportedly been a committed statements at the age of 10
He was taking over with his pink sweater
It was the season of going very hard against
Soros
Now that we have societal unrest in protesting
Wheelhouse
Alex can't credibly claim that Bill Gates is playing antifa protesters to go around and cause trouble
Because his audience already
End.
As Alex open to show on Friday soros's called off the bench
As anyone who's listen to our show for any stretch of time nose
These Soros antifa contract Alex is talking about are very fake
What are the least competent underlings hours
No federal law enforcement has ever
Confirm their real Alex is making that up
Also I'm not sure what he means when he says no media has ever disputed them because we're media and I sure as s*** dispute
And mock the very idea of someone
Contractor start riots
The notion that never put down at the paper is laughable
The real new enter into a contract with someone is so that you can take action against them in court if they fail to live up to their obligation
Literally zero purpose to start a riot
F****** stupid
I would assume the absence of coverage of these fake documents in the larger media
Apparently fake
Seems like something the most media Outlets wouldn't waste their time
On the other hand have nothing but time for this.
I feel like the media has not yet refuted the details of
The treaty between the Elves and the orc
Works either and I feel like that's something they've been silent about Eisenhower going on record about his meeting with alien
South America
Soccer contract with him
The ship
And he hired some movers and the contract about the Ark of the Covenant
Don't look at the Ark of the Covenant contract as well
How do I say would be sued for their face melting
Yeah yeah yeah something like that
So Alex is going to enter into the season of trying to make a
RC Theory out of this
Sure he's going to talk about the protests and riots and make them into
The work of metal and Soros operatives
Stop
Sense of intensity in in severity
And Alex
GE starts weaving also conspiracies
About the killing of George Floyd itself
Why not the center of the case
But the local police are not our enemy
Anybody that's live long enough on average knows that
Minnesota that the media has hyped up
That was becoming more and more suspicious very well
And
Do you put your knee on the Carotid artery is somebody that's not a police
Somebody
So Alex police aren't they
Counter to his entire self mythology
According to his telling of his own life story he uncovered an elaborate drug-dealing ring in the police department of Dallas
Would you like to a lawyer calling Alex's dad kill Alex
Alex's life story the beginning of his career is at odds with his current state
Obviously I don't believe that's why I was moved to Austin but it's telling that the corrosive effect of supporting Trump has
He's supposed to be pretending to be
Answer that news item about George Floyd and the cop Derek Chauvin knew each other
Reporting a bit
This is something that's based on some comments from buy a Santa Maria Club in Minneapolis called El Nuevo Rodeo
She told the local news Outlet.
Took to mean that they knew each other and this must have been person
This is ignoring me.
Santa Maria's comments
They were working together at the same time it's just that Chauvin worked outside
Working together for several years even the blaze included the information in their article
It's only work there for roughly a year
It's definitely interesting and I'll need to wait till there's more information to draw any conclusion from it but
I mean Santa Maria told the local news outlet that she did not know the two guys knew each other and it's entirely possible
They didn't
She said there were dozens of guards on busy nights like when their shift would have overlapped so
It's entirely possible they were only distant acquaintance
The stories being used by some
It shouldn't fall into the same category
This is where a white cop kills another black person
I think that's a losing strategy
If you think about it for even a second
If it turns out that this case was something where it's
The cop killed George Floyd
The situation is far worse than it looks
That's the idea that he could get away with acting like that
View of his co-workers and expected he would pay any consequences for it
Encapsulation of the problem
Whether or not these two knew each other is an interesting future but regardless
It doesn't change the fact of the situation one bit
It's some kind of a
You know like this is something else
It's not something else it is a little bit like
Saying that
You know it's like domestic abuse is fine for cops
Apps to get away with because
They
Personal you know it's not them using their badge to get away with
Kind of s*** it's B personal if their personal life
It's like no I'm still going to go with that's f***** up
It's kind of standard a lot of people float these kinds of things out
I didn't realize where Alex was going to go from there
He takes that little bit
Misinterpreted news
And he just Builds on it support
Good luck f****** defending this conspiracy theory Alex
Tomatoes looks like sometime
You're probably going to find this corruption going on in this is some kind of weird police game
How do you kill somebody on camera why would you just
Here we see Alex correctly assessed there's something completely sucked up
In an attempt to
Police games
This is absurd
But Beyonce
Claiming gang involved killing does literally nothing to explain away the thing that he's claiming to find suspicious of The Originals
It is probably assumed there be even more reason and honestly
While you're on shift as a cop in public
You'd think that would ultimately lead to an investigation which would likely real reveal the existence of this cop game
You're probably trying to keep a secret
I want those conspiracy supposed to explain why the cop did this even though he was on sale but it doesn't choose that goal
All it does is create a possibly more intriguing But ultimately very difficult to prove distraction from reality
Let me tell you
Now Alex needs to establish that there is a police gang in Minneapolis The Wolverine that this cop was a member of the police
You had a tattoo the other members of the officers there were also members
I have a reason to commit mass murders imaginable
Rise to the level of a cop in uniform killing someone in the street with recording
You think it would have to be something really serious like I don't know Floyd was going to provide evidence to the attorney general about the cop gang
You can easily see how this might be fun for conspiracy theorists to think about but it's pure speculation
!
Even though you knew we was on tape
Any consequences
Maybe you can make an argument that he didn't actually think that
Floyd was going to die but still requires you to accept
If those be concerned autocar's
Not as not seriously enough to consider
It would be very easy to see
I hope you would think that there wouldn't be any consequence
There really are
For police people of color and early in his career
Just Liza last episode 2000
The same cop Derek Chauvin responded to a domestic disturbance call
When the police arrived the guy with police called on him Ira tolls
According to his telling of the story to The Daily Beast show the officers entered the house unannounced
Ben Chauvin kicked
At the door of the bathroom
When he got in he started hitting tools
I didn't know what to think when he started hitting me
I swear he was hitting me with the gun
Show me Kohl's in the stomach
Because he claimed the tolls reached for an officer's gun
If his first reaction was hitting me in the face then it means I can't see it and I'm too disoriented to First locate is gone
And then try to take it from him and for what
Misdemeanor disorderly situation into a felony
He tried to kill me in that bathroom
Consequences for this
Which teaches a lesson that there are consequences for this sort of thing
You just got paid he got put on paid administrative leave while there was an investigation that didn't result in any consequences
Vacation
I find it substantially easier to believe that a cop with a record like chauvin's living in America like the one we've been living it
Just didn't give a s*** about her
That's easier to believe than this
Completely baseless conspiracy about the Imagine
Who's coming up with
Subway that was 2008
Obviously
Good cop
Allow bad cops to stay in there
Angry
Stroke
Work on Alex's bar
Is you really have to look at
You can see how now that he hasn't Angela story that he thinks defuses the race issues
He's completely comfortable dropping the whole like Captain know what he was doing
That was only his ankle on Thursday because he couldn't come up with anything better to
Defend whiteness
That's all he had I've now you
It's just realize
You're attacking the very
Cornerstone of the all cops argument which is that
If you want to argue there are good cops
Then why are they doing everything humanly possible to protect murderers you know
So that's the that's
The Cornerstone in for you to say at me
To my face
They don't suffer bad cops there for very long
F*** off
That's that one problem with the other problem is that like
That's
Contradiction of Alex's entire life story
It's ridiculous to be this idea like cops don't put up with bad cop
You got run out of Dallas by French.
Like one of those with Chief if you were correct
Then you wouldn't have needed to do the thing that you think you're right here overdo it never would have moved
Exactly
Dallas ass-whole
Sure not over 4000.
A video of the fire at the 3rd Precinct
Minneapolis
You think of
Chicago Fire
The fireworks going off at Celebration of the pool
Station
Just move out of that already
Thursday night protesters Minneapolis Police Station
The image of that was something I could have never imagined
I never thought my lifetime I would see a police station
Capture that's where the
Police are
That's where they keep their gun did not seem like a possibility I was
Shocked
Leaving my basement decide there been some responses from business owners in the area and some are not happy but others
Musically
The Gandhi Mahal Indian restaurant was one of the businesses that caught fire that night
The owner's daughter posted on Facebook
Don't worry about us we will rebuild and we will recover
Referring to her father she said quote
I hear him say on the phone let my building bird Justice needs to be served
But those officers in jail
Another was the target
Which was the site of the initial looting that's so scandalize the right-wing think about the target they said
Their CEO Brian Connell put a press release that started community in pain
That pain is not unique
Twin Cities across America
The murder of George Floyd is Unleashed dipenta pain of years
Breonna Taylor
We say their names and hold a to long list of other than our heart
As a Target team we've huddled and we've been sold and we've witnessed
Horrific seed similar to it's playing out now and where
Is that not enough is changed
As a team we vowed to face pain with purpose
You went on to reaffirm targets
Commitment to the effect
Store in neighborhood
Our store
Team a former Lake Street store in
We'll make sure they are full pay and benefits in the coming week
As well as access to other resources and opportunities within Target
We'll continue to invest in this vibrant
Crossroads of Seward Longfellow Philip
And Powderhorn
Communities
Preserving jobs and economic opportunities by rebuild
I'm bringing back the store that has served as a community resource
Since 1976
I mean it's corporate Target
The f****** word of it but
At least I don't believe a word of it
Will so you know
They're almost certainly some businesses that will be hesitant to reopen or want to relocate but it's not a universal thing
Megan realize the larger reality what's going on in the country in a responding by attempting to reaffirm their commitment to the communities they
Serve
These are two voices that are inspiring
Here in carnival
Elvis travels
Really what he's trying to do is shame the protesters with ideas that they've driven business out of their Community which is a very
Response for people in events like that community
Dla right before Alex Jones ever on air
On-air at that time
Spell Cooper
So after that after the policeman
McCain were found not guilty
And right broke out
A part of what he had to say
No biggie
McMurray
An open grocery store
Supermarket
Discount store
Electronics store.
Floor heating
Pringles
Store
Rihanna
It is not going
Whenever a group of protesters engaging property damage on the right making this argument
Not to just hear it as a form of scold
Supalonely
I was considering
Plane
Talking
Much more about Bill Cooper's response to that the riots that broke out after the acquittal
But I I just I didn't feel like it would be an episode
Bill's response to it is very complicated and very different from Alex's
Inasmuch as he completely understands
The reasons
Flight that these communities were in
And anybody who supports
Is categorically a race
He has
Some strong stances
Are you also
Very similar
Take that Alex eyes towards
Sleep regression that the the protest
Truck Yeah
Yeah.
Encapsulation of the that right-wing whites light
That idea of like
Something in my neighborhood has changed
I am not going to spend a single dime helping to rebuild it
Or changing with it or growing as a person
I'm leaving
Not that
Other people would say see what was going on and what
Maintain the community
Something somebody kept saying the middle class
Incredibly difficult thing to unpack
IQs
Approach to its like
There's there's moments of like
You get it
Qronika
And then you pick into blaming Rodney King for driving drunk
Gran Torino
Know that kind of thing
Too much to throw away already
So Alex wants to play another standard conspiracy game here on the
29th
And that is that happens in the world Maybe
All that stuff
Maybe it's really a distraction
Remember that while we're all folks
Los Angeles
And
Minneapolis-Saint Paul
Batman riots
That's going on videos come out of Joe Biden in
United States
I'm not sure that Alex ever does get back to that video I don't know
To most of this episode
I did end up turning it off a tiny bit early because I was just sick of it
Know if he got to it and I don't care
It's not worth
I want to take a second to show Alex there were bunch of murders and racial attacks on white people
This is interesting because if I'm not much mistaken Alex is currently on a nationally televised program
If he's upset and no one's covering this
He should be covering with himself
When you realize that he's not starts coming to focus
Alex isn't covering specific details but he claims that he's aware of tons of murders and violence
I don't see these specific
Fix being brought up
Cuz
He's there to make up a talking point no one in the mainstream media is talk
Talking about it
No one is talking about Bingo and I would talk about it but that's not my job
Who would listen that used the talking point
Queen of the story is that no one in the media is covering the murders and anti-violence
That's the whole story covering
Not the underlying events he claims to be upset about no one covering
If Alex had these stories and he's not covering them that conceivably he's just as bad as all the other media Outlets he's complaining about
He's on air right now be specific whenever you want and he doesn't
Because he doesn't want to
Only seeking to impart to his audience is the general feeling that there's a massive cover-up of murder
Violence against whites going on to give them further incentive
To demonize the underlying point of
The protest
Quite simply it's an expression of his white supremacy the media is covering this and to prove it
Neither will I
I mean like
In terms of like when I was getting this episode together the concrete instances of like deaths
Find there was that guy in the protester who got shot by someone driving by in a gray Dodge Durango
And he died
There was a security officer a contracted
Security officer in Oakland who was shot
But again it was by someone in a vehicle
Fire is under investigation but I can find there's nothing solid connecting this with any protest
And then Fox News reported on St Louis man who died after being
Dragged under a FedEx truck
That guy was a protester as well
Run over
So like I don't know how
Yeah inside English
Not anything to be like a
Bunch of burgers at Alex's ramp
It seems like mostly police beating people up and property damage real problem is is that
Protesters
People
Because if they were killing people man they could really make hay out of it
And said protesters are just
Hurting building
They don't like that
Wow it makes it to clear the like property rights over everything kind of mentality of so
So many people on the right
But whatever
I don't particularly care to engage with his complaints about anti-white racial attacks because his definition of that is meaningless
And even gone to a white person is racial attack when he wants it to be so I'm sure I'll try to save that guy was waving around a bow and arrow on Sunday
They got beat up with the victim of a surprise
Kind of idiot flail about with a crossbow on camera
Sure
Is coming out while we're distracted I didn't point out that the government released
The phone call
Michael Flynn and Russian Ambassador Sergey kislyak on Friday
Well that's when we can all best analyze what the content of that is
No that's why we have time
The readouts clearly show Flynn discussing Obama's sanctions with Russia and how Russia should respond which is something they all said
It was before Trump took office and Flynn said quote
Let's keep this at even
IQ level that would we come in we'll have a better conversation where we're going to go regarding our relation
Is the documents even show a follow-up call where kislyak tells Blended Enon escalation on Russia's part was because
Because of their previous conversation
Some might say this is bad stuff and religion is being engulfed
Intense protesting seems fishy
I'm guessing that I went to never cover these documents and instead focus on
Biden saying something about China
You get you come away with the impression that
Trump himself has no idea what's being just
That's what I thought when I read those it says to me
A man who is
Hiding this from Trump
That's what I'm reading in those
I don't know
I don't know what to search
Or something
China
Well the Rothschilds
That's why
Joe Biden and Bill Gates
Economist cover to cover
See here we have this weird tendency popping up again
Alex and a whole lot of his associates really seem to think the messages are being delivered in newspapers and magazines
We heard Alex and Steve pieczenik just gossiping feel like newspapers were communicating directly with them
I think the Rothschild still there The Economist
Honestly this is stupid and I would make fun of him but honestly I think it might be indicative of like mental
What do you do set like how else would you speak to people in power like
There's no way we'll be able to catch that
The Economist
BBC.
Everyone knows that the economist is the name of the episode in season 4 of Lost
Where we learned that after leaving the island Syed is becoming assassin
For the nefarious Ben Linus
Important
Joking aside
Just let this
I'm just along for the ride
The Economist ownership is a weird thing
The structure of the company is pretty bizarre
21% stake in the publication
In 2015 a company called Pearson hit on half of the economist
Decided to sell
The arrangement was made where the and Galley family through their Investment Company excerpt from 4.7 per cent
40% which allowed to previous status quo of powers within the magazine to stay intact
According to an article in Politico
Economist Independence
Is protected by a unique complicated corporate structure that was place in the 1920s
Ownership is widely dispersed among wealthy English families descendants of past editors
And numerous current and former employee
Significant changes must be approved by four independent trustees charged with preserving the magazines Legacy
It's ridiculous and childish just to say that the Rothschilds own the magazine use it to disseminate their marching orders
Ridiculous and childish or Alex is so whatever
Yeah that's awesome I'm already confused in a little bit angry at everything you just said just like
It shouldn't be that complicated I guess I don't know
I don't know if it's to make sure that the legacy of the paper of the magazine stays in
You can't be subject to a hostile takeover
I understand
It's just it's just
The frustrating series of things for me to have to understand
Just continue to own all of our paper anymore
Didn't work out great
Alex teases one of his gas
For the day
Miss Mexico
Boy
Badass
Tim Enloe
He's going to be in studio
His experience
Mobile Police federal police
Barney going for Blackwater state
What he sees going on
Case of this poor man
How suspicious
Different angles of the Gorge
Because none of it
None of it none of it added up
Must have known each other must have been inside dealing out turns out
Nightclub
George Floyd orthoscopics that I'm just saying
Chances of this
Structurally
Why should we
Transmission lined up on Friday
If you're listening Alex literally just said I'm not saying I'm just saying
Crime tip well I mean he's playing around with it.
Responsible for Library
Got excellent results
But doesn't want to say that
That's because I didn't even
There's just no words I can come up with express my disgust
The way he's behaving August 29th episode
But I can at least laugh directly in his face
We're having a guest on who used to be in Blackwater to talk about this
If you told Alex from
320i 2004
He probably tell you to feel your hand you know what
I'm just going to bring in my mercenary friend haha
Crime
Not really a black water thing as I understand it this would be a great I started to have feelings
Songs of like
Like you know that A Christmas Carol
This is this is like it's Alex
But Alex just is what you called
Back in time and she'll probably
Scooter rental
Probably
Interesting Lee to Menlo was definitely in Blackwater
Is it rebranded to later
He specifically named in a lawsuit brought by to whistleblowers who claimed they were fired after they raised the alarm that someone in the cup
Falsifying doesn't
Marksmanship test
For security contract
Wired story
Inaccurately
The Academy's guards were proficient with shotguns and machine guns
Failed to bring an M249 belt-fed machine gun
Near Kabul
But reported a successful test anyway
That person was Tim Enloe
Insecurities forums
Now Tim Brunson gun training outfit in Texas on their website you'll find that he was
Water contractor
In Iraq and Afghanistan between 2000 for 2012
Consider that the Square massacre happened in
Alex should a f****** hate this guy
Not that he was involved companies
Yeah there for 5 years
Termites
Can I continue
It's tremendously f*****
You know
Yeah
So Alex takes a turn for the racist here
We don't do a good job this country with people
Araby by another countries
Is Bad Country
Why countries went through a Renaissance
We want to treat people good
And other places
We've been really good
Overthrow the European ethos
Appreciate
Because you get rid of that people won't stand up for each other
The song about racism
You can see just from that clip how much of a piece of s*** double talkin a****** Alex is
And that one
Cliff he says that certain countries are countries and their better because they have Christianity
Other places presumably not awake
Countries follow the rules of the jungle
Everything wrapped up his thoughts by saying this is not about race
I would ask if it's not about race countries are
If it's not about race why does he defined the United States in Europe as being
White countries to begin with
The unexamined Baseline of Alex's beliefs are racist
To begin with
Doesn't feel like they are
They're just common sense to him
So if someone were to point out for example that America is not a white country
He thinks it is
Common sense
The basic reality
United States they said send over all of your boats to put ourselves and
I hope you kill a bunch of us along the way and while you're on the boat if you got a capsize us and kill us all
You know what
That's what we got to do in order to get into that white country
Accurate information and imaginary bulshit
Most of what you picked up from
Old school racist
He spends basically no time engaging self-reflection and literally Everything feels like an attack to him
Until he decides he doesn't want to anymore
Which probably will be never
He's just going to like have these positions that he thinks or just common sense
Good people races
Single white country
Country
To say it to my face
16 countries in Africa that Alex would probably call a non-white countries that have higher percentages of the population
Christendom
Actually looks 8:15
I'm pretty sure he would say that South Africa is awake.
You can hide behind whatever these like
Freezing if you want
No bulshit
Yeah people wanted to join White
Country so bad whenever a white country with setup in their land
They made sure that it lasted forever
That's why we all sing the national anthem of Rhodesia every morning
That's how it worked out
So
Box and
It said when the Looting starts the shooting starts
And
Pretty soon
Shoot rioters that's what you do
Well I mean
This is where Alex is at
Shooting protesters
Chance to murder people at something that they consider looting and Twitter for some strange
The reason decided that people shouldn't see that
You know like II
It's like the people at the Bundy Ranch were stupid
Don't care for their
Are there are there position
The government threatened to shoot all of them I would be opposed to
Sir
When the occupation starts the Shuki patient begins
So we get back to deflecting by talking about China stuff
You're the sex club
And I found something that Alex
Is the most racist country other than probably North the real planet
China
One Muslim another country
Literally looks down on black
Zzp
Meijer Hitler
Are you
Chinese folks
Alex
Wait a second
Now is the time for me to hear that all Chinese people look alike that's what I hear
Friday the 31st
It's amazing
It was only our last episode where we covered Alex discussing China's treatment of Muslims
As I pointed out in that episode whenever Alex wants to attack China
Completely different
The use of their treatment of Muslims as a prop
This is because Alex is a hack and doesn't care about any of this
Also that think about Judaism
True
That's from a 2019 book called deceiving the sky inside China's drive for Global
Supremacy by guy named Bill Gertz
Necessarily trust anything
Especially Rancho
In 2019 he was fired by the Washington Free Beacon
BuzzFeed news reported that it was for quote
What replication called an undisclosed
Financial transaction with someone he covered
This person is a Chinese billionaire
Gertz and long-standing relationship
Wengert's was writing this book about China approach clock for money
Send clock is an opponent of the Chinese government
Allegedly turned him down but Gert approach Williams
Who gave him $100,000
The former head of voice of America's Mandarin Services said the Kwok referred to G as quote the money guy
This $100,000 was never disclosed his work so severely
Climber's to hazard
Is a shady stuff
Also because it
Miles Kwok is a guy who sued Rodger stone for 100 million dollars
Miles Kwok somewhere Rodger for defaming him on Infowars
Advertisements apologizing
Rodger claimed Oquawka been convicted of financial crimes and maybe legal donations to Hillary Clinton but when he blamed it on
Bad information he got from
Kindly drop the suit on the condition that Rodger profusely apologized and admitted he lied and Rodger
Rodger going to prison
Unrelated
Must have read a blurb about Bill group is
Because that's
Pretty much the only place I can find a story from
Iowa Rutgers
Self has been like
Hitler was a complete badass is that going to be like Hitler on record
We have you on record right into how many of your guests
6 million numbers inflated
Fairly maligning his good name
So I don't know
Optimistic feeling
About
Things that are going on
In the world
That's not good
I believe we can win
I believe
Intelligence agencies collaborator
Balls out the glove with minions
The president takes the gloves off
Switch
Section 230
They are at Gabby's are violating our rights
He does all of that very boldly
Have a good chance of winning
Things are going to really go downhill
We are on a Razor's Edge
I feel
Absolutely one-hundred-percent moral
Strong
Proud and good
Episodes
Wow wow
I was really worried you're going to step on that
Moab field moral to sell you food
To do for them to win
Need to go to war with China
Of course needs to come out against the protests around the country and bring up its soros's
Rules for social media company
Alex wants a military
Repressive dictatorship to be put into place
Suggesting or nightmarish
Under complete authoritarian rule
Likely few allies
Too bad idea honestly it just
Keyhole anyting
Then
Like a manifestation of Alex's desperation
Like be ridiculous extent to which the things he wants to see your he's advocating like would be
Disaster
Kind of just lead you to be like okay well this is what Alex has to
Do to feel anything anymore what he needs to do in order to
Get people to give him money anymore
Allow my country that I supposedly love with Constitution that I supposedly have read
To completely burn in every aspect in be destroyed
In order to get back on Facebook because I am hemorrhaging
So because
Got a got a cowboy
The sales man
Last night in the office Shimmer like
60% off
Across-the-board Flagstaff
Biggest sale of the year
60% off
When is will only run till Saturday
What day is today. I don't know if
I don't care
Is something we see very regularly
Less common is the outward at
We're doing ads and then you use them to launch into extremism
Is it as common example of it
It goes off the rails
Available again
We don't win this 157 days
Young like a rocket
Clock
Very face, did that much
Literally
Sitting there salivating
Whatever energy you got
You want to bend over
Housewise defecate every for 25 minutes
Cut off by the brake
Jesus Christ on our side
Housewives shiting everywhere
Yeah I mean that's bad
You're doing your sales pitch and then you like
I got to give all these extreme
About the getting beat up and raped in a gulag
And
I think there's a real danger it's Alex being like this is this is where we fight
Constantly
When is the time to start shooting
I can't imagine how you don't hear that is being like
Okay
Well the commies are going to take over unless we start shooting
Power stacked
Now is the time now we make our stand by buying slightly
Less than eight things out of a b
The 8-pack power sack of 9th
I know it wasn't 8
Yeah it's troubling and I think it's probably through
Worst ankle you can have right about now
So also the night before I guess in the morning
Yeah it's one of those things X blurry
Prior to this episode
CNN reporter Omar Jimenez
Interesting take on this
That's why the police finally
Robert Lee directed gangs
Directing
This is like
Read look at this level of disconnection from reality Alex lives
Perpetuates
Thursday early Friday morning
Wanted to cover the protests
Who's a pretty egregious Act of press
Intimidation police responded
In a statement the Minneapolis Police said Jimenez was arrested but released when they realize that he was a recorder
Where does make sense
That's considering
Was arrested because he and his crew wouldn't move
But there's videos that sentiment has said quote
We can move back to where you like
We're getting out of your way wherever you want us we'll go out of your way
Since this point they're a bit of bunch more journalists to seem to be getting targeted
Police were clearly intentionally shooting at Kaitlin rust and her crew as they cover
Protested
On Saturday night New York PD rust up and arrested Huffington Post reporter Christmas
Matthias
While he was clearly wearing a press badge around his neck
Linda tirado photographer in Minneapolis was shot in the eye with a rubber bullet
And it's been told that she's going to be left to eye with scarring and permanent blindness
And I want my
Might be too much to save these please seem to be intentionally trying to hurt journalist
Going it doesn't seem like they're going out of their way
In society
They blame copter they blame the media because if the media didn't report on it nobody would know and they would be allowed to be left alone
Probably
Purpose of First Amendment
And that's supposed to include freedom of the press
Exactly dissonance work
The claim that Omar Jimenez
In orchestrating the protests
This is some seriously unhinged
Excuses for reporters being abused by police
Which is
Kind of counterintuitive documents
But which is why we will see a tweet from Trump tomorrow saying that this is run by operatives
Right
Yeah there's another narratives playing around on this day and that was the VIP
Everyone Minnesota
It's a big part of his coverage
A big part of it is the fake Soros documents
Just showed you the documents where the Smoking Gun
Soros funding plan
Martial law
Out-of-town group buses almost
White leftist communist
White people butt
All white people
Manipulate black people in the rioting
Oceanwide
Can install the economy for chicon
Is the local police in Minnesota actually announcing
Preparing from Arlo
Community leaders
Get me the people that were involved
The criminal contact
We're not known many of
Peloton Studio
And so on
Who were involved
Last night that.
Just being here from the sea
So the angle that started to
To take shape was there people who are being arrested in Minneapolis were from out of
Your Governor Tim walz
The Minneapolis mayor Jacob
St. Paul Mayor Melvin Carter
Governor Waltz of the 80% of the rioters were from outside many Minnesota
Mayor Frey said quote I want to be very very clear the people that are doing this are not Minneapolis residence
They're coming in largely from outside the city outside the region
Chipotle on everything we've built over the last several decades
Mayor Carter said quote every single person we arrested last night I'm told was from out of state
Kare 11 News Review jail records and found
Almost everybody been arrested for unlawful assembly in Minnesota
Opposite
But it's all the information that's available
Their responsibility to then be able to explain why the data seems to contradict those clients
All of them are not commented or said they were operating on information that they had at the time
Baby
Hey if the cop
Gave them that information I will accept that
They could have received false information on account of the cops are
Probably not on the protest
Possible
Pretty much every time there's an outburst of protesting and rioting surrounding non-white population
He's demanding to be hurt stranded Justice be respected
Again let's go back to Bill Cooper's coverage of the LA riot
Riverpark Oladipo
Neighborhood
Telephone
Karma the fires started by
This is a trope
It serves a couple of purposes for people like Bill and Alex
What are the main functions is to assure their audiences that they really feel motivated for justice
It's an attempt to knock out the Cornerstone of what the protests are actually about
In bills case was the outrage about cops being acquitted for clearly beating a man almost to death on video
For killing unarmed.
Dubai very public attempts to get people to take the matter seriously
Things like
People taking a knee
Things like every
Everything
You robbed the black community the ability to focus on the central grievance
Where is
What you should be discussing
Playing on your audience's unexamined racist beliefs that are stupid
Easily tricked
Did the pig bike ride
The other main thing that this does is it allows Bill and Alex to redirect the story for their own purpose
For their audiences this is no longer about whatever the protesters supposed to be about
It's not about the global
Start a new world order
The rioters are well-meaning folks got tricked into this whole thing by the meddling cabal
Smart enough to see through the trick
Nearby they co-opted the story that has nothing to do with them
And actually being really about their mission
Of course it is
It's always about their mission
It's it see what it is
Is black people
White people come in and they start causing a race war
Secretly they're using it to oppress black people
The black people definitely shouldn't even go out at all there's no point in protesting it's just going to be white people who are making it about
Exercise your voice
Sure there were plenty of people at every protest we seen this last week who coming from out of town somewhere but I'm not sure what that
Proves and I'm sure that there's some people who are behaving in ways that
Maybe the central organizers of a rally do not approve
I think there's a lot
QuikTrip
Should be dealt with and wrestled with in terms of that
In terms of a lot of the specifics of it
It's really hard to assess
Sperm me especially as things are going on
The level to which that
Invalidates and I have a place to stay
I can't hear people like Alex saying things like this and not recognized
Yeah I heard there's so much misinformation going around
It's astonish
No like last night
So many people all of a sudden started tweeting about how
The KKK word Chicago and 38th in Chicago
And it's like if you're not paying attention
You remember those are parallel Street
Such thing as Chicago and 38
People are saying
Get out of the Chicago right now
And there's a ton of stuff that might
Be misinformation that you don't know
Exact and that's one of the reasons why difficult for me to discuss
The ongoing situation
With any kind of like
Real feeling of comfort
And I don't mean comforting some sort of like
No there's some of the stuff we will discuss
I'll tell you like
This is
No but like
It's very difficult
Aquaman is that
I believe it
The underlying conversation
That is around this
Is
Important
It's valuable
And I don't
That
Whether a genuine part of anything or a sad offshoot
Burning down a Target or whatever to inconsequential compared to
The real issues at hand
And I feel like it's a disservice
To get to bog down inside
Losing sight
The
Tons more footage in MN said he can find of people peacefully Gathering and organizing a protest
Videos you can find communities cleaning up after
Let's say a business has the windows broke
There's there's all kinds of stuff that are that are really more important
Tumi
Van focusing on the
Sensationalism of
Fire
The only thing I hear from everybody that makes me so f****** mad
Evereve everybody like Lori Lightfoot gave a press conference today where she lied to her
Continue
Yourself
But all of this now is everybody needs to focus on
Not being violent to focus on not
Doing any of those things
None of them say
Hey here's how we're going to stop
We're going to make a f***
Not one of them said to do something
To hold police accountable for ourselves accountable none of them said that
They said it's your fault
You're the ones who were burning down
Another National Guard will come in
Yeah it's not it's not us with our I don't know millions of years bulshit
Your fault for being unruly there's no reason for you to get violent
Add slits. These people are
F******
Crazy
Complicated Elementary This and like
How much can you trust
Everything you see on Twitter when lot of things are really unverifiable
For some of those reasons
Think that a lot of my thoughts are best
In hindsight
I also want to present what Alex says
When do you know when there is things he brings up that are like this is a meme that was going around
At the same time sometimes I'm just
It sometimes
But
Anyway
Next clip Alex man
Man-boy
Dot-dot-dot Dot.
Searching about
Alright you're done
Quick
Break
You know that's not true
Kiss your ass all day long
The other day
You're scared of me walking Street tonight
What happened
Democratic party Plantation
B73
Pacific
They were some of the most successful groups their own hotels or restaurants
Oppression
Stronger
Okay Alex
It's another one of those really bad I'm not saying I'm just saying
I'm just here in my ears
If you go and listen to any kind of like
White nationalist are white supremacist media
Even people like Jesse Lee Peterson
Constantly talk about how blacks were better off
Undergem
Pretty standard mentality
He's too much of a coward to like to stand by that
He is suggesting that
No I mean what you're suggesting
Here's what your suggest
They were so much more successful
Under Armour
So Alex has his black Blackwater buddy
I really care what this guy's got
Responsible
Corner at in the autopsy room
Tim died of a sudden cardiac
Due to the toxic
Chain
Associated with
Restrain
When you get out
So this guy from Blackwater is here on the show making up details about the preliminary autopsy that
Examiner is released
The actions of the police health conditions and quote any potential intoxicants contribute to the debt
I'm guessing it was Alex
And reports that George Floyd had been arrested in December 2000
For possession of less than
Which is being reported as in being on cocaine when he was killed
At this point there's no evidence to support this conclusion
That is later shown to be the case these dudes are still just making this up
They aren't I bet he was on coke
Definitive thing
Which is lying
A strong suspicion that if Lloyd was on cocaine
It's pretty it's a pretty simple test they could run and would likely show up in the coroner's report but instead
Potential in toxic
Seems weird for the corner to just speculate on whether or not their words
Weird but I don't know
Of course not until there's more information available it's impossible to make a determination
Assuming facts
This case
Alex and his Blackwater buddy aren't playing the same game
They've decided without evidence that was on Koke because that supports the narrative that they're trying to establish
Sucks
You know who is it was it who was it that the guy who's like boring isn't torture I'll get waterboarded whenever
My old friend
No you can't post clips
Yeah yeah that was a guy f****** f****** two seconds or whatever
Yeah Blackwater guy how about
So
Address of the show's Alex Hawkins
Twitter are witches
Good work Barn I really really wouldn't care about this even under the most boring circumstances
After they have disliked bull session about how great Trump is
For doing this job
Alex brings on Andrew torba
The guy who runs Gab
Really weird to see that be the person who you want to bring
Discuss transplant executive order
Because if it goes into effect
Is basically dead
There's no way that's I can operate if doorbell becomes
Personally responsible for
The things that you post on there
And guess what
He's not so stupid to not recognize that that's the case
Leads Alex getting completely blindsided
They tried to shut him down that demonize this
And he's here to watch
This is a very strong-willed what do you think
Actually totally disagree Alex
Relation is not
In this case at least
Understand this conversation back and forth where
Come to Subaru
They taught
By recognizing that yeah okay well if you write the executive order only applies to the companies we wanted to apply
That'll be great
I'm protected from
Responsibility
Yeah I'm fine
As long as I'm not destroyed
The same mentality
I'm not going to be sexy
Love it.
It's this is it one of the Cornerstone
The school of the right
Victimhood narrative
So we jump
May 30th
Do you jump to Saturday
And this episode is not very good
Important to do because
Is the day that Alex is fake
Gets assaulted in Austin
Scoresandodds
Excited about that
It starts before
So that doesn't have we don't
Alex
LPS horses on this story
I've been
Security
Personal shot
And killed
Different parts
In the country
Police have been shot
The media
So this is his coverage on Saturday
Plenty of available
Discuss by police clearly assaulting people on provoke
He's covering the story
Alex doesn't speak in specifics and he never will because he doesn't know any
Specifics
Is about creating a
To make his audience scared and hateful towards protest
There's only one contractor who was killed
And there's no evidence even a protester was responsible for that
I don't know what tops Alex's claiming were shot discuss specifics all engaged
From what I can tell the violence being done
Polices far outweigh the violence Direct
Did toward them
But it's complicated situation to extract exact details from
Still ongoing
Just why it's such a massive disservice for Alex to speak of these vague
Generalities has nowhere
Yeah the concrete hasn't tried yet
That's kind of what's going on
Broadcast by centering the idea of violence against police is the most important element of the story
By doing this if the subject
The police brutalizing protesters comes up
You can justify it by saying it was only because the cops are getting shot
This isn't intentional strategy to create
Yep
So a lot of people sending me messages that
It was in the tank
When it was two testing Austin
It is not the case
He was in studio
Destroyer
Was there
Howard but it's interesting because
When Alex starts off the show he discusses his people in the field
And if you know who they are
You come and get a sense of what the game they were trying to play is
Recovery map
Demonstration
Saturday
You can kind of see how Alex is strategies going to play out
In terms of trying to create a publicity stunt
He does this by sending to people into the field working
Together but using very different tactic
Owen Shroyer shows up in the fake tank which is meant to draw
Alex has every reason to know that there's a good chance that things getting egged at least and probably worse
Indian people spray painted on a try to immobilize it and then ultimately chased it off
This would be good scary footage
Ultimately
Supposed to be the guy who
Stand up
Put them in their place so try to roll a tank into a protest and gets chased off with graffiti on his car
Optics that you want
Between
Hit them with Tales everybody does that right
That's where Savannah Hernandez comes in
She's someone who almost no one knows
Recognizes working for Infowars
She doesn't
From an unrelated outfits
Maybe even about the attack on Alex's
Completely differently
We're just going out there getting clown
Owen shows up
To draw the Heat
He is the Infowars guy who's there
In Savannah tricks people into thinking that she's not working
Use to build an arrow
Maybe it's that all the protesters want to kill
I hate real journalists hate the First Amendment whatever whatever the case is
And then Savannah cat
Infowars reporter
Good cop
It's a pretty clear setup and its Airline
It's one of the reasons why this is a giant
Catholics to misrepresent who you work for unless your undercover work
This instance is probably one where you could make an argument that Savannah safety could be threatened
By being an enforcer reporter there
And that's the like
Could be justified
But that kind of goes out the window when you consider they're also sending
It kind of doesn't make sense
It did disappoint me that they didn't flip it over and Light It Up
Because I would have like to hear Alex scream
He claims that they bought it now original your rentals snow
The reality of that isn't
Particularly don't care
Because like
Yeah it was actually you will get flat
Oh yeah
Destroy
So anyways
Aleksandr blood courses still pushing the fake Soros documents Center
This is the media winding up
Remember the homeless
Security documents
Remember
Those numbers
George soros's son with
Uniform
So now their Homeland Security documents
Jamaican all this s*** KGB Homeland Security MI6
Whatever China's God according to him
So CNN
It's paid by China and therefore
Reporter
Orchestrating protest
Undoubtedly
China though they're all got their fingers in so many pies
I mean they bought off
They bought off
Autopsy
I'll give you fifty bucks
They bought off
It's on the news
When the leaders of those countries
That I'm going to do a French accent there
Party paste
For the gun
MO
Of the French
So cops are bad
Meu police
G
Doesn't sound right
Manush
So I want to make is that at this point I'm not sure Alex even remember his wedgies real name is
Pronounces it that way because it's like a derisive thing or because he
You doing it wrong
I don't know
To talk about from all accounts actually buys a lot of Weaponry from European countries
I can't find any sources to back up what he saying it because he's the one making the claim it's his responsibility to cite a source
He's just making it up
If it isn't the news and it's all over the place back in this up should be no problem for him so I'll wait for that to happen
Knockout is that is it is just these friends L thing thank you China
Or whatever
It's like a business sponsoring a local Little League team the new China buys of their uniforms they have to put China on
The back of the
The next Club Alex I think
I think you think so he's got like a real Haymaker knockout punch
It turns out all he's really doing
Is revealing
Maybe videos says real white supremacy problem
Hands up
Lenny's Rider
White Liberals are hands of photoshoot
Blackhawks panic 112000
John Black
Wyoming
Hispanic on white
Fantasy 5
Ratio black-on-white
And you can argue well
So Alex is driving out some crime statistics in an attempt to make the argument people commit more crimes
I don't want this is an argument that
Or you can imagine
Call here isn't to talk about actual Dynamics
Some crime
Violence
People is the preferred Target of those threats
Supremacist
Criminality
It exists in black people
And even if Alex isn't directly saying that it has built on that sound
Could possibly not be aware of that
This analysis of crimes
Mystics you know what it what it does is it takes all the context away from numbers
More thorough analyses have been done likely 2014 Bureau statistics Bureau of Justice
6:30
Differences that you can find Rachel way when you control
Poverty
They also found her done to alleviate poverty violent crime rates went down regardless of race
Reese's missa interpretations of crime statistics like this are Mainstays and white supremacist discourse
Motivate dylann roof
2015 mass shooting
The Emanuel African Methodist
Episcopal Church
In Charleston
Whether Alex wants to accept it or not he's continuing in that Legacy
Also in this is crucially important
These statistics are
Completely irrelevant to the conversation
These protesters are are meant to be forcing
The conversation is around a lack of accountability for police officers who killing victimized non-white people
And no amount of random out of context crime statistics out
Come up with
Love any bearing on that
He's trying to move goal post because he feels like this crime statistic conversation is one where is narratives of white victimhood standard
Better chance of success
All he's doing is making the argument that maybe police should be killing black people kind of
What he's doing it without having to accept the consequences
Saying that out loud
Stocks
Alright
Liberal protest
Hands up don't shoot these people are out at protest cops are in discriminately pepper spraying people
These people are out in the streets while fires are going on everywhere around them saying hands up don't shoot
Well you put your dumbfucks in it
And you don't even go to a
In protest
Dairy
Darius on Sunday but I'm not entirely sure
So excessive promoting
I don't know if I want to say I have a
Call to action but I want to make
Ford.com
4 / 0
URL doesn't
Paul Revere
The first thing I think is really funny is that suggesting that his audience post links to
Videos
You are else
Just kind of stupid
All the time and I usually just ignore it
Discussion
Alex is directly flouting the bands on social media sites and using it as a marketing
Until social media sites wise up and realize they're dealing with people who constantly try to get around the rules because their business model.
Sonic
They're going to lose
They sell blockers so Infowars can't go up but I was supposed to all the same articles on newswars of all the same
Incontact
If the goal is to restrict Infowars ability to perpetuate their lies and misinformation
Directions are symbolic and ultimately at least partially
Contagious to Alex
Don't feel good
Get David Knight off of there too I'm sick of him being unsure.
David
Impulse
Yeah he's got to go
Buckeye
So Alex in the snakes clips
House which seems like a good idea
Johnny's
Delivered
Question you got to ask
The freaking game folks
Believe
This isn't like all the BS
About
Imaginary
GameStop
Hugh tells you don't go out and protest
The White House
For America for Trump
Tomorrow morning
He doesn't know
Some groups that don't do anything don't be involved
You heard the president tweet
Today, d.c.
Surround the White House
No
There's some good peep
Alex
Care about this dangerous
Everybody has
The right to protest and what have you but like
I think
The odds are not good
Of people doing so responsibly
Calling themselves to
Protects the White House of f*** out of here
To protect the White House
What are the highly most highly guarded places in the f****** world seems like trouble
Millie Weaver was coming up
And tries to tries to start their interview here
We have audio IC
So we are going to go to her
Male nurse
And then he
Billy your back
How big is what's happening right now
What is your Intel
What's your view
So
Skeleton Crew
Figuring it out
Figuring it out should have figured it out
Yeah man
Exact same scenario playing out so I can
It's cool Alex's chill about it inside like Special Report
Emiliano be fine
Amazing
Skype
Tomorrow the Sunday show
No like no one at Alex's with no one can figure this out
It's a simple issue
You could have
Call her
Use the phone
This is it this is why
Do you have the mark of the beast
Detach
The best
Like a regular problem
Well we can only use we can only use platforms that have a band music
We don't need milk
Because Owen
Get back to the studio
This point and Analysis
Is so excited
Victory here in Austin on that footage
I mean you're going to have
Communist
Democrat
Out in Austin Texas
Unless 100 immediately
I mean start over
Piranhas
Alex loves excited about it
Such a good representation
And it gets so good to him and talking about this this attack on his truck
Really like swing for the fences
And see these people don't understand that the only reason
They feel so Robin live
That is not because other people
Probably getting ready to
You know they want to talk
Gallery
F*** you
So
Alex
The Water Guy
No that's why he's special
Security's got to be in the tank
It's really interesting because
Mirrors the exact same talkingpoi
You know there's still some stuff that needs to be talked about with George Floyd
The autopsy said that he actually died from an overdose
It's not
It's not too effectually backed up trying to craft a new story
The same things that people do nationalist folks
Cindy all right
In the aftermath of the United right rally with the narrative and talking to Heather heyer
I had a heart attack
It's the same
Sort of thing
Free Speech whatsoever
However
If you say some b******* like that
You have to be wearing full KKK rope
That way
Date nobody's restricting your speech
But everybody knows what you're saying
I like that
It seems tough to implement
We'll just have one above everyone person's head
Is that can descend to matter where they will report
Suggestion let's send it to the committee I'll see what I can do
Android
No
Blackwater guy discussing
The protest
Competitive
Competitive nature I think
To some of these groups
Footage
The money and the donations and everything
To support our cause
And if you look
Attacks
That's exactly what's going on here
Except the sponsors are
These big private individual
Ride that donated
Search
So what's going on
Is the protesters
LaRosa's video contest
Justifying their budget
Rihanna
A real mess
About you or around you
So are we close out this 30th
Special episode
Alex is just like it's
Like we keep saying and have been saying for a while that's like he just wants Trump to become a dictator
And will accept whatever
Now he's sort of making peace with that a bit more open and upfront about it
He just
You got to get behind
What does omnipresent mean
Short
Along
Tchaikovsky get behind the president
I think
Has the people behind him
Think what
And then
People catch up he needs to take a leak
Citizenship around the White House
Take that don't do that
Yeah I guess
Great behind the president
Questioningly
One thing I think is
It's listening to me
Is that even Owen Shroyer
Can recognize a lack of leadership
Even Owen record
Leadership in the wrong direction
Directions
They are even able to take a
Take a finger put it on the pulse
And recognize we have no leadership.
Yeah
Yep we not jump to the 31st
You know
And other number
Conspiracies that are floating around
Everywhere started to feel a lot like
Going back and looking at the Boston bombing
.
The immediate aftermath of things happening Alex would just throw whatever
Really feels like on Sunday trying to do he's trying to
Directions as possible
Maybe there was a cop game
There's a bit of a
But I think it accelerates quite a bit
And it begins
Immediately
On the 31st
There's an article at infowars.com
Elsa doll
Bricks delivered
Dallas
City Hall and police
Fireball
Minnesota
The left
Soros
Martial law in America
So the only source Alex has on a brick story is ground on
In a location that was not near any
Construction site and someone must have put them there on purpose
Must have been an employee store
No idea what's going on in that video on Twitter
I've seen some people online say that the bricks were there because there was a construction project at the intersection involving a replace
Couldn't tell you if that's accurate or not I can't find any confirmation
It really doesn't make sense though this would be a spot where Soros and wanted his minions would just drop off a pallet of bricks
For no reason
Video shot outside of a federal building so you would assume there be a decent chance that there might be some surveillance around it
And I know that we recently just talked about how there were cameras pointed outside the Murrah building in Oklahoma City and that was
Suspicious
But this is a different situation
The building in this video it was shot outside
Federal Building in Courthouse
Which was the site of the shooting on June 17th 2019
If there were some failures and cameras at that point
Afterwards the building raised their security considerably
Someone dropped off a pallet of bricks outside that Federal Building
So let's see if that ever
Operation
Dumbo Drop
Kind of
There's a helicopter would have scattered
The person who made that video It's Been Awhile
Protesters
Cause trouble
I don't see any confirmation that there
Mysteriously dropped there
So I'm going to need more on that that's that's not good that's not good enough for me
Yep
So
Has realized that to the National Guard
Getting involved what you should be against
You would think
Against
To send the military into places you should
There's a video
National Guard shooting people on their porches
He's for it
Of course
Minneapolis-Saint Paul
National Guard
Rubber bullet
Twitter
Dash
Civil War
I asked for
This doesn't seem like what mister anti-police
You shouldn't be like well yeah but we stayed is what you got to do when there's no
Multiple documentaries called police scanner
We're at the point now where he might as well be like
And I do believe that people should have to
Soldiers in their homes
Just do a complete about-face on literally everything
You got you got to give him a bath
The Constitution
So Alex is building here on this episode about his conspiracies about George
George Floyd
Return to death
Into a grande
Conspiracy
Evolve
The Smollett case
Just like Stone
I'm not saying you did
The items I know information about the other cop knowing George Floyd
More like I can't find any story about it on there
Also I don't care if someone has done p***
Nomex work doesn't make someone suspicious or more likely to be involved in criminal activity
I want to do whatever you can throw spaghetti
The guy who Police murdered
In order to make that murder more except
Audible to his audience
I'm not saying that he's I don't think he deserves to die and I definitely think that there was an incompetent
Please officer
He regularly drove 25 miles an hour in a 30 mile an hour speed zone so I look
I'm not saying it's not that they deserved
I'm just saying that you know what don't worry about
Sure
Good good
Thanks buddy.
Is also continuing to push the out-of-town
Specials
Alex is still pushing
And then
I can't believe how fun it is
You got all of them coming on
Couldn't
Sing
These are out of town
The governor's daughter
Scott Direct
Leaving aside the fact
Governor waltzes
About rumors about the National Guard
Deployed
Take me to takes time to mobilize them
This is a full-on qanon theory that Alex is repeating
Issuing directives
Protesters
Stealthily through Twitter because she tweeted about the National Guard taking time to
Make no mistake about it
Secret Cove
That's the level of both of these working
The governor's daughter is secretly running antifa
The governor's daughter is
Somebody's running antifa the governor of Minnesota
What is daughter
The children
Alex abrines
House Intrigue around Infowars
Twitter
You don't matter
Probably not pay did not say that
And you know what
Newswars.com today
The pig
Police
Kill the police
Unabomber crap
Because of these people
Anti-free speech
Now there it is
So it just goes on
The big Tommy's
I don't know about this man
The only website covering this story is Infowars itself so I don't know about this
Hope it doesn't seem quite right about it
Almost no one outside of his listeners even know exist
Do that
It makes no sense to have no impact to hack newswars
Alex
Don't know exist how we'll get
A huge amount of attention to hack a website and no one will know about right
It's like
If I were Alex I would hundred percent call this a false flag
But I'm not Alex decided take over a site that literally no one cares about
And I'm sure no one would have noticed unless I was brought up
Possible
Completely fabricating DDOS attacks and pasta
Let's move on with some of his previous Behavior
Bored hacker
Also I don't believe for a second that protesters are saying
You got kicked off Facebook and Twitter
I also don't believe that Alex is Securities any different
For newswars and Infowars today
Trying to take over anything it would be
Distance doesn't pass the smell test I don't think it would be that far
Talk more about this Brick story in Dallas here
Economy
By the way
Boy we have a prize
We haven't
15 bricks
Black folks the people
Be right there
Fabricating details about that
Multiple pallets 15 police station
We have them delivering it
We have existed
Twitter of them standing next to some bricks
George Soros
Pallets of bricks
Today
Receipt for Soros
Fork truck
So in addition to Alex's pushing
Narratives that are about
Police setting fires in New York
Sis South
In a false-flag kind of thing
People doing
You know my position on all that stuff
I don't know
If there are instigators who are infiltrating in some
Capacity check
White-supremacist folks
Accelerationist types
I don't know some of them are very misguided
Total anti-statist
I don't know
Like I can
Pretend to know
And I don't
We will know
For a while
May be able to identify things
I don't know
But I do think that the way Alex is covering the stuff is still a responsible given that
He doesn't know either
Footage in New York
Volkswagen
Your classic for this
Very creepy photos looking like the police percent
Dylan
We're going to pass
Configure tonight
Because the truth
So it seems like asking those questions is equivalent to Truth for him
And that's a problem
Him asking those questions
Him asking questions
In order to
Start s*** or whatever he has
Soros dropped off those bricks
You know that
He is so irresponsible
The asking those questions
You lying for
It's it's
He just has to recognize at a certain point
Just asking questions
For someone else before him
Dangerous
That's his Northstar
Weird white people tricks
Don't forget
Left
A little bit of footage that Savannah Hernandez got She Was Out
The field
I think it's about what you'd expect actually it's version for Infowars that could be
I do think
Sincerely that their intention was to try this thing
Right and just talked to a communist
Is like ice
Support food not bombs
And they think that this is like a big
They're so stupid
A communist
Austin Texas whiskey
Reporter
Run by Communists or
Not the songwriter
The-Dream
Where do you think
We go after this what do you think
Well that's another
Demonstration tomorrow
Is doing
Organizations
Actually trying to change
So join an organization
Granix organization
That's what I recommend
The plan
You can't even figure out how to say hi.
Landslide
How does that square with
Constant talk about how you go out new Tommy's or sneering and
Demons
Maybe you don't
I fully agree with the anarchist
And at the same time
You're the hold old present
The premises
We need to increase self-governance
Added some
Police reports
Yeah man on the street
Question right
Okay
So now brings up another
Video that was going around
And this one
Not good
Here's just one of the many videos of white people being
We're just being white
Here is the clip from Dallas
And is now in a coma in Dallas
But these white
Deserves it
Avon so hat tip to our friend Jared Holt
For this one has to get to the bottom of the story
Circulating online
Which was posted by Elijah Schaffer
The works for Glenn Beck's Blaze TV
He was misleading re-edited to appear that it showed a guy who did nothing getting beaten up for no reason
Hours later and after being pestered to do so Schaefer posted the iron version of the video which shows what actually happened
According to CBS 21 Dallas-Fort Worth protesters with a machete
Lee said that he'd shown up to allegedly protect his neighborhood
Some protesters
What you did
This is not machete
Because this context was removed from the initials
Established beating up for no reason
By the time the reality was already in place and you see Alex here
And Alex is taking it a step further and lying about two additional aspects
He's saying that it's racism against whites related crime which is
Clearly is not
And he's saying that this guy is in a coma
There's no evidence
Not mentioned in the CBS 21 story about in which says that he's in stable condition at the hospital
Understand he was tweeting later
Thanks, sweetie
Regular occurrence nowadays
Do you have these things and like the optic
Pics of a guy obviously if you are
Taking this out of context
I'm showing it it looks
Really bad
The unedited full context
Hey this guy's charging people with a f****** machete
In these Conte in these situations
I don't know what how you expect you wouldn't get beat up
The definition of self-defense when it comes to a man running at you with a machete
A B for people who love stand your f****** ground laws
The full context of the short version
Problems
Has decided to add to it
Process that Alex has to report his stories and white
Really dangerous
In these times like we talked about
Because
It's hard it's hard like I mean I think I probably could have found
This story in CBS
To contact surrounding this
Difficult for someone who's in these right-wing information speakers
To figure out this is bulshit
They have no interest in figuring out if it's b*******
Not there with the machete
It's just a little
Release the even more full clip of the protesters starting the fight with him and then him pulling the machete out
It's just all
That's so f***** up
That's so f***** up at guywood additive
That way that's just so f***** up
What am I
You know you want to create the appearance that you want to create
Natsu
Disqualifying for ever being considered a journalist ever again
Probably
He's already
What kind of heavy
Time to lighten up the mood
No
Play morning
My daughter
Want to go buy some toys
Carter Brothers. But I go there for the
I didn't need to know that
Fremont
Make a joke out of it to fill out
Call Ali
That's not report
Also
Such b******* any stores
Fighting with people about
Maybe he can say he hasn't worn a mask or whatever I don't know if I believe that entirely but
He's got too many stores
Just not not judging Latimer liquor store
Where he puts on a dinosaur mask
And walked around Target
Anywhere near there
So Alex spends a lot of time on this episode talking about his truck
How we got
You got beat not why would I expected
To be about anything other than
This point after talking
And about how do you say I tell him, he's came up and
Could you have
We were doing it to illustrate
These are anti-free speech
Monster
So because they're anti-free speech Dirtbag monsters
Hey man
Don't matter no matter what happens to
You got started this
I mean.
There's no
By the way to tell you and I'm not even
I'm proud about it
Will make sure
That
Tell me tell you something
You started this fight
Superman
Presence
You really start a fight
The wrong people
So it's not with me it's not some big Power
Air America
Bauer
Because once America's under attack you once were Unleashed
There's not
Anywhere you peep
The figure it out there's no space
Safeway
You guys
You want to fight
Hope you ready for it.
Hope you ready for it
What is the just Alex basically being like my political enemies are fine to go to FEMA camps
Supermax prisons that's no different
Differentiate
Ocean between America and
People
But he sees as his
You know it is hard not to hear that and also think of Trump's comment about Imago people love black people
Being almost two distinct things
Probably make the argument that he's not talking about
No minorities here
I'm about to eat
Weird white people who are working for China or trying to make these
It's it doesn't matter like his audience is going to hear the way that you're at
That's also Illustrated of of
I hate
Fundamental cowardice in the same most people on the right
In that kind of militia Circle Sheriff's just that like
Oh I could have
I know I could have
I could have no we could have beat him
Beasley
And then it's like
They'll see what happens when America wakes up
Cuz obviously all of these people
Joining together in protein
Police brutality
These are just a thought
Protesters
Sora
Know if it's there
Meddling
There was a my neck report
Bertha came out disgust howl a lot of
Fringe right-wing militia dangerous types
And there was some things that were
Could be associated with them
Some things like
Support for Ron Paul
Ron Paul supporters were all dangerous right-wing militia
Liking the Turner Diaries
Keep an eye on these people
To get this report
This whole thing is trying to say that
Trump
Is hero
Is come out
And said that he was going to
Label
Domestic terrorist
That means
Terrorist as well probably
Control
Trump tweet
United States
America
Will be desert
Esoteric
Organization
George Soros
And they are trying
Terrorized the nation
What is jaundice
Alive right now
At what time indeed
This is
Turn of events if only because
That exists is whomever you don't like
That's the problem
Yeah it's a big issue
Heard discussing this the most clearly is a note saying
Is just move
Basically
Whoever you don't want terrorists to
Big tits
There's a lot of things that you shouldn't be a lot of things you can imagine
And very easily an earlier version of Alex Jones
Very
Falcon worried about
Things like the National Guard shooting paintballs a rubber bullets at people on their porch
Yeah their personal property
The president labeling non-existent non-centralized group terrorist group
Any number of these things
Alex would be against those things
He was out on the streets
People might have reminded him of that
And here is his rationalization for why
Hey man
I'm still against the police say it
Verde
Every person who I was
You were against the police state
The police
These people is amazing
I swear there's no rule of law
Under martial law
Has nothing to do with a cop
What
Policy Meats real
The globalists are trying to train cops
The paint gun
Forcibly take her seven-year-old for a sex change
Personally mad at that
Police officer
Coming to do
Fight them
For the robber
Lisa Road
Translate that for you
Bowie State doesn't mean anything other than police enforcing rules that Alex doesn't like
That is all
Even if they're imaginary it's just
There's nothing to do
The tactics or nothing
To do with
Any of the
Larger implications
It has everything to do with
I know like
Documentaries titled police state
Real bad
What a pathetic loser
Alex starts to really get wistful
Remember when I believed
Stuff
I wish
Instead he starts thinking about like man
There were times when
So foolish.
The Dow Trump
How could I have ever been
Name
Here in the year twenty
Adele
God dammit
Questions man
Three nights ago
I stayed up
Mike Wang
I wasn't ashamed but I look down
About 30 minutes
110 to get a job
Everytime I second-guess
Surrounded
He was right about
He still up
Oh my God
This is gross
This is more intensely
You know
He is the savior he's the chosen one
Been anything I ever heard anyone
This is obscene
No this is like I had my head down
For 30 minutes and then I lifted it up and I licks Trump's butthole
Cuz I loved it so much
Can't believe that I ever imagined not looking Trump
Alex almost
Cries here talkin about how it happens
We have to support Trump
Matter what
F***
The president
Now we deserve
So I literally had a moment on Friday night
Publishers I said
Is my gut
Because while we're in this fight
Checking
Is he perfect
From my position of my
Being in the middle of where he is
I told me
Just back the present hundred percent no matter what now
Because if he doesn't get
Spiritual
Metaphysical
Full document
Yes
Thousand percent
He is the champion of
He has done
Believable
God
This person
No The Patriot
Preparing
Knowing
What he was doing
For the position
Somebody was metaphysically
That
Position
This is so f*****
Believable transition of power in 2020
Sunday episode
Jesus say Jared crosses are on your head and call yourself
Church today what I did is I got on Aaron at Blue hard about Alexa fine
That is so bad
Yeah that's very weak
Little
Sophos topic for a little bit
Mascaras audience about these
I'm going to blow Trump no matter what he did. Man I think of Courage
Palmer Twitter
Don't have a Twitter
Tonight's the night
My comrades
Half the city
Hilarious
White
Race-based
Stikbot
So this is an account there's a Tifa underscore us
Constantly gets tricked by these things probably
Also that account
Been suspended by Twitter so Alex is
States not even a boy
Too real
I don't know who got called in on the weekend but someone was able to
Skype working
Cuz Millie calls in I want you to
Make time for this
I'm going to be honest with you upfront
I have no f****** idea what this really is talking about
I have no idea Alex completely confused by a conspiracy theory that you trying to spend
And
I'd like everyone to remember that Millie Weaver first came to our attention exactly
Hey goofy clown comedy comedy character
This is more than just
This is actually a military Insurrection that's going on right now
This is
Classic
Operation that's
Internet
Interactive
Psychological
Operation
Being run on US citizen
This is technology the same
Told you that they use in Ukraine
With their wikistrat
Did they are deploying
On US citizens
Call the government
Deep State elements are launching this right now
Solutely this is an attack
Because they know
They have used their
Predictive
Program soft
To know that your why Dan is not going to have a
In the 2020 election
They have prediction
Software
Can use their
I was just listen to him like I got
I got no interest in this
Okay we got
F****** future pretty
Addicting software
And they're worried
So they started some kind of an online interactive simulation where
Please call Pokemon go at the start and now it's
I looked into this a tiny bit
I think she just found a Blog
It's a Munroe to talk with his is a stuff
I have no f****** idea I also don't care
So is Alex disrespectful
He believed
She wouldn't act this way if you believe
All this is just psych Warfare or something
Keep interrupting Her Like Us
The created shadow
Operations
The way they got a whole Vista
Contract
Corporations to
Secretes
William Jennings been on record
Private contractors
More access to the governor
1000 contractors
Have more access to the Press
Exactly
That's not that's not good communication
Sold information
A little disrespectful
What job should do
Sure about this
Operation or whatever
I don't understand exactly what
Dirt bike
Basically they want the military to come in to fight against AI I don't know what this means
We do
Trump
I think that Trump needs to crack
Down and try to
Deploy the National Guard but he needs to do it in all these before she brought
30 ruling us or not
He should stand the Armenian
Nearly grabbed control of all this AI that we built
Billy was saying sending in the National Guard to Aldi's
That's not
Alex I think is talking about sending the Army to Google
Or something like that
Right
I don't understand how some kind of a giant
Online-based psychological warfare things on two different tracks completely
But they both involve Trump using military force against
Someone they don't like
And neither of them make any sense
Not really I'm amazed
I'm really amazed at the volume of
Times they talked about what Trump
Should do
The subsequent number of times Trump does not do that
And then them claiming that he's fulfilled every promise
Yeah yeah yeah it is
It happens a lot
Imagine all the stuff you don't hear
Yeah but I do tell
Yeah probably
You expect to come there
It's only going to
Crazier Alex
Try to buy a weapon
It wasn't enough
Bogus
Him with every
American Pie
With everything
Coincidence
As soon as businesses are about to open up the economies about the
Soon as that
They all go out and hit all these bit
No stop them from opening
Call Mia
As well as
To try to
Further divide
It's only going to get worse Alex
People need to buy
Please share information with important sharing information
So that we can get that
Shrimp
How to the right people to the Americas a ride it's so precious every person listing however
Rebel radio station TV show
You're all men
Did Alex take a sedative
Like he feels like he's about to fall asleep tired of her bulshit
She's presenting
The military internet
Interactive
Millie what the f*** are you talking about
Editorial stance
Don't forget to eat cuz I rode photography
I would appreciate an Infowars
The AP style guide
Anytime anytime you're talking about this
Soros
Together
I was thinking like
I wonder I would
To surprise
I don't think this is the case writers rooms over going to whatever it in for the office
There was some kind of
It went into like here's the
Type of news here is the product we sell released on this
Like I wouldn't be too surprised like there was like almost a branching
Like
Treat other reasoning tree of like if this then that
If this then that that would make perfect sense
If they haven't developed that after 20 years or whatever
Be pretty wild
You would have to read at least four pages for that
Not going to enforce must be literate though it help
Anyway
Things are going to get worse at everything else but I do think
I think they're going to keep going
In the direction that they're going
Absent any kind of leadership any kind of
I reckon
Cognition of conversation
Yeah
Otzi
It is force is Matt
Force I don't see
I don't see people who are protesting
Any reason
To not
Continue
Because of the validity and the sincerely held beliefs that are
Find
The what is
What they're doing
At the same time
Straight
The bigamist
Recognize the complaints
To accept
Conversation
I think there's too much built up into like not looking
And those two forces
Stop against each other intersecting
I do worry about that
I think all the other stuff is b******* like
Fake impeachment face virus
All I all I can see
From
Because this is the opportunity
All of our local leaders to step
And they're absolutely not doing
What is what is the question
Nobody that they are answering this
What is going to make
The protest stop
And all of them so far are saying that it will be
Police brutality
That will stop the pro
Obviously not saying brutality but
Will be I'll be goddamned if that's not with their banking
How many fats and if that's
Not so if that's not going to stop the protests
We have to provide them with an alternative
Because the protest right now
To stop the protests
Nobody has the demand nobody is saying
What we need to do is
You know
Get rid of go through
The cops we have lists of people who have posted on Facebook
We have.
You make
Concerted change within the system and they're not taking any responsibility
I'm sure there have been some
Optimistic
Well it's going to take the leadership
It's going to take like Lori Lightfoot press conference to take them not just saying
8 is what happened to Floyd
It's going to take them saying
Because of our inaction
Ever
That is why you guys are protests
It is because of us
We have to change to
And they are not doing that
It does seem like that
Would be an essential piece of it
Just keep the same to Soto's
Gut punch all of the narratives that Alex has and all the censorship
You just not say things like this
Millie Weaver think
Thank you so much
Your videos are at Millennium
On on
Thank you so much
I think you know and
I think you start to see a little bit of like
Deers are starting
Try and work
For Alex
He's trying to create the things that he needs
To create a false narrative
Out of this
Besoros contracts that are b******* that he's bringing back into the conversation
Shifting the villain from gates to Soros to suit the
David needs of the moment
I think you see
I'm picking up whatever he can in terms of videos that come out
The bricks metal
You got the
The guy getting beat up you just take a note
You see that behavior
Very reminiscent
It's a very it's very much that's Alex Jones what he does
And then at the same time I think probably more offensively the
I just
Complete
Fabrication of embellishment
Speculation wildly about
George Floyd
Himself
In any way that
Just designed to
Make the audience feel more comfortable with the
But that could he got murder
It's not fun for anybody to die but it's more fine for him to
Yep
I think there's a two-pronged approach
Make this
Not as hard pill to swallow
Create a narrative
You said it's starting to take shape here
I predict that it will continue and
You know when
Coronavirus started off really helped out a lot of money
Pretty afloat
For a bit and I'm
Pretty worried that like
This is a ratings Bonanza kind of thing for Alex
Potential
Alex
Most
Adapt
Taking things that are really hot
Unclear
And using them to his advantage
And I do have a real sincere worried that you'll be able to make a lot of money options
God dammit
Of these people being rewarded
I'm just sick
Hopefully it's
It's followed by consequences of these lawsuits
Crippling him
Jordan
Read website
Go to bed Jordan
Please donate to a bail fund or there are Agra
Forget bail funds now where you can donate and they will distribute across the
Yep
George Soros with forklift
Alex
Kristen color