Alex
We're couple dudes you like to sit around slightly different introduction today
That's right
Fake news
I'm not drinking wine
Unfortunately all too real news
I don't want to come to you with the pity party
It's not what I'm about but I
You want to say
I think that this show
Is taking a massive effect on my mental how
Which is something We've joked about in the past
And people have expected
And unfortunately it's kind of true
I think
Maybe you were joking
You can't listen to copious hours of Alex Jones
And not having to take some sort of negative toll on you
I am a combination of excessive drinking
In my life
Reinforce
Drink menu list
Alex Jones
For comfort
Yeah yeah yeah
It's a it's a disaster
Moving forward we're going to stop drinking wine
We're going to start drinking
Comical beverages
Until today we've got strawberry and Perrier plan forever
Yeah
Whatever Alex
Cuz doing to me
Over
Not
Because I do believe the word
Doing something
Important important than most of what else were doing
Myself that I would listen to him everyday for a year
What kind of games are no matter what happens
Cancel my mental health
We stopped doing
Michelle
Make it to that point I am going
You need to
Here's the thing
Alex makes me very mad
But it's not because
I'm triggered
Or anything like that
The experience of listening to his show is madness
Because I know his lies
At this point we've been doing this I've been listening everyday for like
It's five and a half months
I know all of his little lies
The waypoints I researched them
And I know they're bulshit
So whenever a new tragedy happen
Narrative room to go down
And he just uses the same lines to reinforce them
It's so frustrating cuz there's no winning
There's no winning against the guy who's that like
Bombastic and entertaining
With
Stat-wise
Commitment
2 is
Alternate route
Yeah and so that's what
That's what's hurting my mental health
Is listening to it and realizing like
Where
The knowledge fight is ultimately pointless
And that's great
But if the end goal is making a difference at all we can
That's really what
I don't know if that makes any sense or anything but
In order to deal with that frustration and how all-encompassing that is how much it makes me really afraid
Place
Shittyfood
Irresponsibility with
More meditation in my life
Exercise
So
Will negotiate on that last
Sure
Is that Rodger Stone might today
Barrels
I don't know what that mean
Might be the etymology
Maybe or is Simon a pickle Barrel
I don't
Or
When you're really poor you have to wear a barrel
Turn on cartoon
More real
We're going to be going over a special report that Alex put out
Okay finally finally
We're going to do that because people have been asking about on Twitter
And then on top of that
The world
I don't
Allison very predictable
I don't want to talk about it
I don't want talk about his insane Muslim dating
I am
Beer tax
Yep if you read
Reports from people in
London
In England
You hear a lot of really positive stories about people helping each other
And
About not being
Bound by fear
Dumbass Texas
Hey screaming
That sort of thing
Can I just don't care
It's
It's so cookie-cutter for him that I just don't even want to do it
People are already
Kick them out of our
They're doing it before
Anyway
I've got a special report
And I don't want to tell you what it's about
I want to just let you
I'm going to play the first
Could trick you that fast I'm going to play the first clip and imma let you try and guess
What he's talking about
Ladies and gentlemen film 06 Central 7 Eastern 5
Central Time
This is my day off today I took a day off
Suspension children
And the family
And
I had to come back in the day because of major major
Wards.com
Important
Just on Google News alone
Trump and Israel
But
It's not his real what is
The biggest breaking news with Alex Jones
On his day off
6:00 at night
To discuss
In a special report
What do you think it is
Intelligent
Were asked
Specifically
And personally by
To interfere
Beer with the FBI
Not that one
No but it's not the most
If works
That's the only thing I can make news
If we're going to play hot and cold that's Isis
Alright
How about
See what else is going on in the
Did somebody talk about Alex
Warmer
Not directly towards Alex
Tertiary Ali
Who but I do want to
Corsi has
Select a story
Today is not Trump and Israel
Infowars
And there are over 3,000
Google has 3,000
Oh my God
He was watching that number climb
Jerking off the results
Totally
The day off just to
Just to refresh refresh
Refresh it's 3000 now
Check off again
Again
Course we got credentials baby
I saw that and I
I'm just sitting there going
We just did an episode where he
Blissey laid out
Plan
To wage a
Literal propaganda war against Americans
His argument because Edward Bernays trained me
Uniquely capable at Justice
Groin propaganda
The campaign
Cuz I think he does bring it up later
That like
Jerome corsi knows how to pierce through propaganda campaign
Where in the training manual was like the only way to fight propaganda
Is with even more
I honestly think that that is what
Oh actually yeah that's pretty much exactly
Absolutely would be
So
Oh man I just got real sad
The specifics about it and we'll talk about sad the realities and
Really all that terrible you got a week
Pastor
Alex even admits as much
Almost episodes
High School
There's a couple things
You might be in my school
Is this
Speaker
Breaking news
Course
Is going to be spending a week in the White House
And then the rest of it
Life Underground
If he shows up at the White House with John Cena you know something's up with
I want to bring up
One is that
Alex doing everything wrong
Cuz he's engaged with Stephen Colbert
The historic buckford character
Stephen Colbert's just
Clowning on Alex Alex
Enjoyable
We're not going to take anybody
I wish anyone cared as much about what we do is
I'm not better
That's a good point I started I can neither prove nor disprove your claim
Back when I was
Letterman Leno
Those Island
YouTube
Because you didn't know any better answer happen
He should not be engaging at all
Colbert
Do whatever he wants
Colbert is incredibly funny
She's always going to win
It's always going to be
Alex is lying about everything
We can't win with the truth
It's only going to get more ammunition for Colbert to make fun of if Alex gets mad
There's no win for him
Just ignore it
You f****** up there
Now the rest of this episode
Even a moment
Maybe I should
Every
Single
Time
Mangos
Oh I got to say something about this
Immediately every time Google result
We're making fun of him
Got to take a little more Superbowl vitality
The first thing he's f****** up big time right now
The second thing is f****** up big-time is how he respond
In this episode
People's criticism
About corsi getting pressed
Right
Should waive his dick around
She is a troll
Write the whole thing isn't the course he is in the Press Corps he's legitimate
That's not what's going on they're just doing it to show him at the White House to piss people off
Yeah that's why Jack pasovic went for a day that's why that's why Mike cernovich went for a date
To piss people off
That's what these all right
Good optic
Cuz you are going to make people mad Levi
And then all of a sudden they're talking about you
This is super defensive
This episode
Incredibly defensive
And Alex's
Well
He should just be like my guys in there
Sukkot libtards
Perfect that's a perfect angle
Does this instead of of
Having White House press credentials
We fought about
We thought
Then you put it in for daily that you get weekly
Because eventually that we going to run out
No he's worried that
He's going to get it
From his team
He's worried that he's going to get the
OU sold out
Bingo
It's not about
It's not about us
Anymore this is
Infowars
You dumbass follower
Butte
Suggested there in the middle was a little bit
It's going to be like
Then you go with the weekly that's course
They don't even do permanent anymore
So he's already given up that
This is probably the best we're going to do
Don't expect more from us
I don't know about
If they don't do permanent I think the New York Times
As a permanent eating their not rotating out the New York
Game time for Washington
Ice maker
I think it becomes a conversation every time I tried to
Lest you think that's
The limit
Alex's
It's about this situation
Okay he gets super defensive and then gets defensive about his own pass
I am about an accusation
Which is super fun
Ears
Access TV
Check
What's going on here
But of course I started out
Years old
By 21 years old 20 years old
Oh it's amazing this guy
Read all the people
No it's all he was on
I don't think anyone feels that way I don't think anyone cares but he was on exit TV
TV
Stop
I think Alex having roots and look like this
Makes them cool
Local
I've considered every day of my life
I don't know how to do it
Alright let's check into it
So you're right I mean like it is
Your radio show haven't because your dad bought an add-on radio and pimped pics with the producers
Yep like
You're not I mean
The case of a
Self made
Millionaire
It's always pull myself up
It helped that my dad had 14 million
It was a bonus
But he only gave me one
More than a million
So
People
Hate him cuz he was on public access
Knox
Because
He's a liar
Super defensive
Everything
This school
20 minute clip
Is a greatest hits
Of all like his fun current lies
Like Eli's about pizzagate
He lies a little bit about Chobani
He lies a little bit about his this one right here
This next clip
Is about his newest
Narrative
Yes the thing about Comey lying to
We didn't actually play him talking about it I just explained it
So here we go here's Alex not understanding
The fake narrative he's pushing with gum
This isn't about me but the media is totally upset they got a bunch of news articles Daily Beast
Alex Jones helped push up the stock market East dangerous
Well that's the clip
They just say I'm a liar but admittedly boots in the stock market
It's crazy
It was two-plus months ago that the memo was supposedly written and then
Month later on May 3rd
Tomi testifies that no one not the attorney-general no one quote no one
Contradiction before Congress or the memos alive which they won't show us so that's probably a lot
Probably
Not great
Migrating owls
What do you say
Nope, he was asked
Specifically about the attorney general or officials with the Department of Justice
Alex
Alex is trying to say that just because you said
Tony's answer doesn't relate to the question he was at
I just because you said that hasn't happened to Mike.
Answering question about the.
Alex just takes the
That hasn't happened.
Text is unnecessary it hasn't happened in my experience
Never
Yeah
Congress
The Daily Beast article that came out apparently
I do I don't know what the f*** this article was talking
But apparently the stock market
Take a little bit of a jump
I am they attributed to Traders
Alex covering this, equip
And the idea that Trump wasn't in trouble and they told me himself was in trouble
Make them by
Hazel
Places where they found out it was fake
And it went down
Most of those training
Are built now around algor
Jeff
And if there is enough
There's enough of these certain
Keywords
That it will change that's why there was that one day
There's suddenly a massive crash
Is because all the algorithms
Wiped out
That
What we pointed out
About how
Specific question
Understand
That at all
In the article old clip
Alex
Cuz he can't wrestle with
Incontact
Adjust glommed onto the fact that
Sure that parts
This is why
Why he's f******
This is why use propaganda
Cuz he can't not under
A child could understand
If you can't understand that I don't think
You could tie a shoe
That's our new conspiracy
To be fair I has anybody seen Alex public wearing anything other than
Velcro
Slip on shoes
And I will give him this
Those shoes that have roller
The soap shoes
My grind shoes
Can jump on Rails and posts
I'm thinking specifically the ones where the wheels pop out on the bottom
The ones with lights
Is that like lights
This is bulshit
Yes just b*******
So when Alex
In this world defensive thing about Sony press credentials to be legitimate
I want to talk about how we made the stock market go up with our fake s***
It's not fake
They think it's two weeks old
His argument is that
Has to be
B-real
Because the stock market was
Was affected by
No
He's saying
But it has to be real because he
I mean it is in Jesus
His criticism of the daily
So you saying that they put out this article
Saying that he was fake
And yet
Because look
The stock market is real
True
I think there's an even more interesting argument to be made it's really dangerous when bulshit
Makes the market go up
Because
We're going to economy where we're sort of incentive eyes to lie
Yeah
So Jordan you might be asking yourself
What am I asking myself
Asking myself that but
Myself has Alex Jones
Ever held
A puppy in his arms
The truth of life
Whoever looked
Himself in a dog's eyes
Maybe
When he strangled Nong
Oh man
You're really set on this narrative that he get to killing off his bare hands
I think there's no other reasonable explanation
Super where we are at
Talk about his drunken rambling about exactly
1 + 1 makes 2 exactly
I wonder about that myself
More
I know that everyone
When were the memos
Bye
To kill knock in order to become a man
I'll look it up and reported in Fortune 500
We can't report on that right now
Without a doubt we have calls out exactly Alex Jones
Refused
He has commented on
Is this next bulshit story
Prudential
You got the medium running
Thousands of news articles an hour
Top story what are the top stories in the United States right now
They put out the same disinfo
But I didn't get them
We were told to get press passes
We can't refuse you anyway
Best-selling author
Presidential candidates
Yes I was trying to get movies
Where's the paperwork make shop
They say where are you
We want you here
Okay
How's this spacer Twilight select moving from side to side
Which part of the covers a
And he's on today character
Cerveza.
That's bad you got to turn your head to the right to the left
Alright
Over to my shop after the show
I can come over
With your wife
That is so that's not how Alex talk
A lot of the time
It kind of makes me think that was based on a real conversation he had with somebody
That is that is well
That's a lot less
Detailed
Yeah
This man
Macaque
Amazing
Legit
That's that's what he's really missing
Mention any
Waiting time
That it was a legitimate
Let's assume it was
Which is
Which is something he does not
Austin to because it is
Never
B people he's talking to our legitimate
He has to certify it
Which does Dublin
Exterior thought that it was a real
Can I be clear what I think happened
No
OK Google
Or at the very least
Obfuscate
I definitely don't
Think that someone like Mike
Flynn
Said hey you should get press credentials
I definitely don't think that that's probably what happened
But like he wasn't in such hot water
It was more like
Is that one still got to do any good lawyers
Oh okay so it's not in this episode
But man
He's been spending a Chobani s*** hard
Yeah I believe it
He's been saying that okay so Colbert
I talked about on his like
In one of his jokes
The character called tuck Buckner
Yes
It's becoming
The most one-sided War ever
Alex
That's dangerous
Stephen Colbert has finally alerted how much more
Full on
Villa Rosa
Outside doesn't understand humor
Stuff
Said that he lost in court without
Retraction
Didn't lose
If he wasn't
F***** over a bear
Otherwise
Context clues
And figure that out
Colbert said he had to pay out a settlement
Isn't public
Really knows
True
Because it was a private
Settlement
So I don't know if Alex
Colbert said it but he didn't say anything
Specific
But Alex took
The Chobani told him
What the secret settlement was
Because it's all of talking PR stunt
Play Giovanni
So
I don't know
I have a broken mentally ill
That's always great up
Push with negative associate in their brand with him
Especially after they settle them down
Gyros
Maybe just no no
4-barrel
Good man
So Alec believes that is talked about it
Chobani is cold
Colbert the lawsuit details
Enzo Alex
Put Chobani on notice
Told them not to destroy any documents
How do you spell albino double jeopardy
Tickets for the same thing
Again that you've already scheduled for
Also
Like it wouldn't even be possible for them to share that information
Unless they didn't have a non-disclosure
Within the settlement agreement
I think they do
Because otherwise it would be public information
Teepublic reviews
So of course
He knows that your body could
Possibly
Yeah but he's got to try and win somehow and that's how he's doing
Counter sue them for disclosing
Settlement
He is very happy about it
Yeah because you didn't get destroyed
Packing House
Okay to him for the article the slander of their their article liquid
S*** rolls downhill
Going to land on Alex's
Downhill
Definitely not Alex Jones
Downhill downhill from
David Knight is like
Corsi
Corpse
Jerome corsi
What is the buck stops without
But he owns
But you know they don't want Reese to him for that
The stuff you talked about that episode that we went over
Pictures of something for that
He's doubling down on everything like okay you're off the hook on that one but here we go
So
Get some of that settle money first I don't want to do that
Good man
The other thing that Alex has been doing that's really funny
Is
Because
Is Buick
Get free pretending to be a fake Alex
Is pretending to be a fake
Stephen Colbert
No but
Keep getting the point
And he's quickly deconstructing the B
He's doing what
He's going through
Alex
Is going line-by-line
Itsfunneh itsfunneh conceptually that he's doing it but it's
I listen to a new wooden play on this
I don't have any of that
But one thing
A1 Colbert's monologue she's like
Claim that Chobani is bringing
Spread tuberculosis
Which we all know is Yoplait
Alex response to that wasn't
Alright we made that joke
But I think we used an app
Slander
Why does
Omani just
Play jokes
Does he have a
Wherever like in his real life no I don't think so
He's a man with
Without humor
Deborah
He's a big he's a sad man
Cuz all the last
Yeah he's the weird dude
You know you getting defensive
He's talking about how we don't need
For credibility
But that's not enough
It's not enough for Alex and Infowars
They have to go one step further
Are very extended way
Cook-Out the Press Corps
Real heart
So he's
These credentials and it does
Same time
All over these merry credential
He got
Totally the wrong angle
These credentials
Office
Those are three things Alex keeps bringing up I assume that's it
But I mean
Guessing it's a slightly more complicated
We need you to have an office in a driver
Rubber stamp
Good
So here go your ears with a cocking
Begins
Here's what's going on
What's going house press credentials
In a way
Spokesman a woman
And then we hear what the president
Flights
We look at stock numbers
We look at reality
Show me other experts
But ocean came out
Do you understand
There's coursing there's coursing at the White House
True
They came out and said Infowars was correct
Is such a
Such a funny thing
For him to save
The first lie is of course
The way that
Doesn't come out and say
Mason said
The information
That Infowars game
That
What Infowars reported on Wii
Was correct
Alex
Came out and said Infowars is correct
As a whole.
The other part of that
Is know that absolutely did not have
Totally
He doubles down on the One Lending himself credibility by having
High updos
Look at how right info
The time we're just confirming info
Already told you
That's me is great
Because that distract from the fact that
Like that's a brilliant little move there
Jerome corsi broke a story that's not true
And we've been over it
We've explained both versions of the
The penny Freddy's story that they tried to pull one couple months back couple weeks ago
We've been over there both not true they're both
F****** lies
Do you mnuchin confirmed it
A fertilized
Don't understand
Only frustration
So if you
You keep on lying eventually people finally
Forget the old
And move on to the new score man we got it we got
Sucking mnuchin telling us words
Genright
I do believe him when he says
They don't need
To be in the Press Corps to
To legitimize
That sure is fuk is
Isn't going to happen
Where they are the people who think that they're legitimate
So he's not done cutting up a press Corps
Losses in a little bit
Controversy in January February March and April that we were Liars
If you got
D.c. license
They can't block you
From your press credentials
Has a PHD in international finance from Harvard
A New York Times best sellers
11 presidential
So real quick
Swift boat veterans
Torpedo John Kerry's campaign
The fact that he helped
Alex you hate George W bush
Hydrocodone that you know that light rack
He was responsible for
It's so stupid
So f****** stupid
If it was
Like some sort of
IPic nationalist win in that election
Corsican taking down carry
I don't think Alex do is jerk him off here regarding
So much as
Look at how powerful that affected his property
It's hard to argue against it like you heard about the
The Swift boat V
Like
According to
My dad thought it was water bottles
Whole Hog on it and you got to go
Successful
Millions of people murdered
Fasting for workout
Also his number
We're about how Obama birth certificate is fake
And how about Obama's illegitimate
Sellers
I don't get it
I don't get it does Alex
Okay if I was just really impressed by this
He have to be superficial as f***
And really only care about the fact
And a book
Because if
Look beneath the surface
Right under that rock is George h.w. Bush
And then also under that rock is
Oh no
I have to be a birther now
I don't think Alex wants to talk about the
Your initial statement Alex The Superficial of s***
You could have just stopped right
Well I'm just trying to give an alternative
He superficial is because the alternative is I'm thrilled with Georgia
George W bush being president
Yeah you're right he doesn't need that
Think it was
Right but who cares
Like it was
Even with the wars man
Abstruse
She's going to torpedo
Control over the propaganda
If you got working for World News Daily anyone like North Korea we've got the bomb
Anyway he's a more positive things to say about course hero
Disagree with all of
Exposed
Terrorism in the Middle East
Is that
About it
Sprint car
What do you Murphy
Chris
You think you don't
You think you're better than course
International Sia
Fictional organization is almost ready to talk about
He wouldn't even talk about it until exactly one week ago to his Great Bend
Take all of it
Also that Hillary was being paid by the Chinese government
Choose on the payroll
I'm at Eric's family have been threatened
He's going to be back on to talk about
Still never come on
He's almost ready to talk
Amendatory has never really has a much better lawyers don't go anywhere.
Don't make any insinuations you can't backup
Yeah
Currently says about other people
Lie about yourself all the f*** you want who's going to watch the lion of slander for a long
These were miraculously not been destroyed by all the bulshit he's done
But now is where the episode take a harsh turn
It's just been like that we need the press credentials but also we
Everyone hates us cuz we're so truthful
Full of integrity
Fake meat
Documented
Episode
Superficially in this episode as well as easy as not being
Yeah he's a dick
Alex
The talks about
The why the media attacks
The media hates them
I bet it's for the right raise
Pizzagate right before this
Cut it out cuz I don't really care to hear and why more about
Pizzagate on the podcast
He's like that you like to do all they do whatever they want to discredit me they're just pizzagate
Because I suppose the fact
They don't show his full quote I know he's done this on the show already but they can't get you
Just to be like hey Alex they didn't show your full quote here's your full quote you dumb
Use a synthetic
Completely fake
What actors in my view Manufacturing
Or just shows how bold they are
That they clearly
Used even ended up
Photos of kids killed in mass shootings
Shooting target
The sky is now the limit I appreciate your call
Anyway
Shut up just shut the fuk up
Just stop
I'm just going to play that clip
Every time he brings up Sandy Hook
You might have had
Multiple times and adverbs adjectives supporting eggs
Exactly what
Cup still there man
Yep still alive
If you're gonna lie about what you said in the past
It down
Try really defensive about how they're all into truth
Everything
Truth
Everyone just lies about Infowars man
Is it everyone just lies about them
Stephen Colbert
You got people to saying that he lost a chobanian court because
You made an embarrassing public retraction
You got people saying that he's a liar because he had to come out and say
Very in-depth talk about the pizza place but you have to go listen to them
You have to listen to Infowars
Of all of these Liars out there
Spell it out
Here's what he was
You want
Krowd
They get you into feeling like they're part of the winter isn't SWAT Stephen Colbert
Teleprompter Raiders
Actually two men
Infowars.com daily to myself and the rest of breakthrough
Really, really sing
What we're really doing
Listening to this and going well
I better double-check
You have done this to yourself
Eclipse
Sorry
Or what you cover
And they're f****** horrible
Where to start with one that we've already played on the show just
Just so you know
Give us a little bit of
Just familiar hatred discovers his homophobia
Portion
Everywhere I went.
Suburb
I went into shock
Drown with the pool supply place
Starbucks
With a coffee
After school supplies
That are not tolerant that are the most oppressive
Call wife
People on earth
You bet I'm freaked out
I got $3 lady Joan
So I wanted to start with just because we've already listened to before
What is afraid of young Muslim
Who are very integrated
I love that is so dumb on so many levels because that
Proved
What makes America better than Saudi Arabia is about
More like Saudi Arabia
Lobster in a pot
This is the cold water
So we've already
Just going to get worse from here
So this next clip is him
Talking about Jade helm
Conspiracy theory that the government was going to take over Texas
This is him talking about it
Algorithm
Code
Special Forces to kill you
Special Forces families
Serious disabilities
Robots are going to be everywhere
Understand
Are you talkin about cumin
That's right directly on iRobot
Cases for the past 20 years
So he really bought into Jade Helm and tried to scare people about it all the time
Is already planning
For future Guerrilla operations
Is the water still not all that hot
This is just you reporting dumb s***
That was going on in
2814 15
Something like that Texas
Still free
The Spurs lost so are any of us really
Jason Howell did not
But you're winning every basketball game
Muslim hating America
The next one I'm going to do here is
But I'm going to call Whites Whites
I was raised culture of white guilt
Christians
Across-the-board
Crap
That's crazy
Black people have been abused
By white people the same way he's been abused
3 minute
Unity is it street fights
Why people are better than him apparel
Structural abuse that has been ingrained in this country
Pre-sentence beginning
Nothing of the ideas
Guilt people make me feel
Refugee
Four things that people that I am
Probably directly related to your family fought for the South
Why am I being
Feel guilt over
Fight for the South
In the Civil War
My dad got his Dentistry license
From Robert E Lee
The famous General he was authorized
That's a whole lot in this next clip Alex misunderstands panhandling as being bugged
Superfund
I've been down there
Buy a
I don't say give it to me
Almost always
Because there's this attitude
Call more white victimhood
Alex
That's a personal care what color Alex
Is
I think anybody who does what he does
Deserves to have people asking for money every now and then
If he always turns everything into like a scene from a movie
The beginning here
The more he lies the more details he gives
Over 200
Was homeless probably was
Do you have any money yeah that's everything you've turned it into
I'm being attacked by this guy
Course cuz he's black
I'm sick of his wife victimhood Supply
A summer
Yeah and it freaked
Me
Here's a nice fun clip of Paul Joseph Watson
He did a report making fun of the idea of being trans
Wards.com
My name is no
Videos that whole bunch
Boy toys
You know what's really funny that put that special report
Turn off
Yeah
You know I was getting just outwardly
Throwing everything in everything
A throne just every pause
Possible thing that it's like
Everybody who isn't a white male Christian
Is the single worst thing in there trying to destroy everybody
Louis
Which
Which frankly
What what is the character doing wrong
Characters just described
Bring like a guy who's
I would guess they were the character is doing wrong is it annoying Christian
I don't want to feel
This is really all about how he
He doesn't want to feel
You don't want to feel bad about being white
Possibility
F*** off and the Saints
True
Like everybody
He's on the right
Who's always
Flying about safe
Spaces in
Trigger word
There's an all that s*** are really just trying to avoid
Feeling like
Yeah
Entirety
Existence
Hurting people
I'm doing everything possible to avoid
Feeling like that
There's a lot of that
Paul Joseph Watson
Unexplained
Forever
This is this is bad
Press do with race
But it has to do with more than just race
Pretty bad
Complete fabrication
Completely bogus statistics
I'm in the Middle East expert on these prices why there is an actual right it's completely ignore
White so it's okay
Exploring what you cover and so far
Like everyone's right to hate you
Boils down to
White s***
Home care that Alex don't care that your wife
You're not depressed
Star Wars soda
Stop it
Now
Here's the last one
I think this is terrible
This is from today
Today's episode
Tuesday
Alright
Put the mic down cuz it
In this clip
He kind of blame
The parents of the kid that died
I'm sure many of the parents of the young people that were at this concert my doorbells many were Tweenies when were team
Probably there
Do want to go along.
Responsible for this animal
Plus people
Call fruit
Hillary Clinton and Obama and all the rest of them
You're the one
That's the day after
Nap
Hey guys don't just take other people's roof find out why people
Do that
Do you remember how is angry before
I want
To not live
Westworld
This is what time
People died
Disrupted and this is
F****** with the heads of everybody
Because of course
What else can
Do you think butt
Where's the next one
Game with the heads-up so many people in Britain
Because they're now they're in the middle of a
F****** elec
So this kind of nationalistic vulture
It is only going to get stronger because
Because of that dip
Any
Something work
You look at
Set up saying
I don't want any
Don't want
I don't
Instead you look at that and say
I want
I want more people
I want there
2B War
Tube blockage
I want anybody who's a refuge
Eugene wants to come in here
I want them to drown on their way
And even if I want them to be pushed away
I want more
People that died because of this
Believe in something
So hard right
And so evil that reminder
Three of you f***
Yeah longer I swear to God
All the lights
Yeah
I don't even give a f***
A goddamn terrorist walked
Through this book
Endure because then at least be like
Hey Will you're not trying to take away my goddamn Healthcare
Dial f****** garbage
Yeah you
Believable
One second
Experienced a tiny bit of a
None
And
You blame
Parents once again grieving there
F***************
And Alex
You fuc
Pizza
F*** you
Totally wow
Totally
Who created more hurt that's just a societal element of this
Like your Buda scribe
Absolutely
But on an even smaller scale
But if you're one of those parents who do here and say something like that
He specifically wants to hurt them
And this is this
Like this is worse than
Sandy Hook
This is
Hannity spouting words instead of delete vert you're not actively
Blaming the parents for being the cause of their children is going to hide behind the idea
Cowardly Dog
Now that's
Bereavement
You really want to break down what he's afraid of
It's not a bomb
Any of that stuff
It has to do with his white identity
That's what he's afraid of
He's afraid of these people coming in who aren't like
He's afraid of being victimized by people who aren't White
Did you have no leg to stand on other than
Did you read the transcript of the New Orlean
I did not he gave a perfect
Speech on how the monument
Taking down Confederate monuments
Through it all
Acknowledge
Start to finish
Just how those
Replaced up there by
Trying
To White
Endeavor
Free time
If you were black
You were from a different country
There is always that f***
These monuments
Represent
How a
Large part of this called
Trying to make sure that
We were in
Slate
And he gave a perc
Exactly what is beautiful about America is the the guy
New Orleans is ever
New Orleans is the truest Melting Pot
That America has
Yeah cuz that you can drink outside
Everyone loves
Yeah
Well and the only reason is again
The slave trade
Because of
Because everybody was there because
His Creoles were there
Because black people
Because it.
Huge
Everybody
That's how you create an awesome culture
Beautiful
And that
Is the thing that they hate
It really is
Because it's not
Holy there's
You have to share it
That's the issue with Alex because sharing leads to socialism which leads to Communism
Re-read
Yeah
So my message
Should be
I mean I have a couple fold
From this episode
The first
He's obviously don't tell people to actually listen to
A show
Because
They will find out what you cover
You could do find out what you cover in
It's bad
That's why we do this year
What's secondarily
What you need to do when you get press credentials
Is just like tell people to suck
Justglo
You're supposed to be trolling people
This isn't going to work
You're not illegitimate news orca
Way too much baggage
You can't report
This call me things as zero
All of y'all are lies and Hillary Clinton's no matter how much they
Narrative
F*** them
We're done
Damn Hillary already lost
You can't still be running a can
Campaign against
But you sold that uranium was Russia trying to
To govern the f***
Goddamn
Sorry
This is why we need the wind Dad look we'll figure it out will be better in the future
I know that was a little a little much
Can't
I can't f****** deal with that
How do you how do you listen to
The truth
Towards
True cruelty
Like there's
No a
See it all there is
Only
Inflict more pain on
Why and I want to shame them for their victimhood why would you want to
There are victims
Their literal victim
You can't be mad that there
Victims when they were Vic
Victimized because hypothetically
Specifically Peru
I don't know
Who cares who cares
Why you're saying that's another very important piece
Shut the guy who
Like
I can't think of any
Anything other than
The amount
Pain
You just want
Single other
To Felix
Exactly
More panda
He wants to experience the least amount of pain right
Other people feel better by
Ghetto doing good
He has to feel better about making everybody else
Look I don't know he sucks that's the bottom line
Hope there's no way around it
I wish I had more clips
Okay so we're still figuring out exactly how this podcast is going to go without our old friend wine
Arc legs
We'll figure out a rhythm
Without the libation
But until then you can find us at knowledge fight.com anyone follow us on Twitter or at knowledge
Underscore
We will time travel to the Past
Episode
How about today
Really f******
And how here
Explicitly said
He wants to run a day
Disinformation
Bad about him
Don't be mad because he's
He's from Infowars
That's bulshit on
Cuz this man
We Believe
Is going to
To be the best way to solve the problem
This is
Who's the guy who is
Sweetly on interest
False reality
American
Absolutely right I was talking about
Interested in the truth and making sure no one knows
Because
Yeah exactly
Secrets and secrets
Yeah
Without without wine
The mood is really f*** this guy
To keep my temper
I wasn't scared
Spit flying from my goddamn list
All over your beard Mike screen
What what good news
Who's that reports
Holding
Alex