Air Jordan
Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for its knowledge B I'm sick of imposing
Born in the wild
What's up man
Well it's most certainly I was getting ready for
Department
Qualifications for me to
Make more of a home as opposed to one of these transient flop Squad ending up in
Usually they're filled with steak snakes and there's no Saint Patrick around three years
I found this place I really like
Fast I think it's good
Because
Visited a number of places it just weren't
We're not up to
Just be angry
And it was really pretty.
And I was lucky
I guess I got lucky
Cuz it's just
Put in an application
Her back pretty quickly
Are we moving at the middle of this month
I will be walking out the door as if I do
That might be part of the reason why I guess the generalized everything that's going on
Thousands of people at Uptown
Smartstandard just kicked ass all over the place
So many people how many people is thousand
Genuinely inspiring
Because of everything that's going on I feel the obligation to stay in the present.
Alex the first
And 2nd of June 2020 bands of 2020
No I think there's one thing to talk about and then there's a lot of
Little mini bulshit things that Alex is doing but I think
Seen a lot of similar trends
Continue on
Acceleration
There's a lot of
Intensification
Valances call for blood
Basically
There's a desire to rationalize the idea of trump using military against
You have those things and there's an interesting sort of push and pull that Alex is trying to do where you trying today
Pretend that he retains some of his principles
Now yelling for blood
But
We'll see how it plays out
Cortana show
Before we do got a show
Call him am I think
C a g h a i n
Thank you so much you are now policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you
Next
Techy thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk Matthias be
Journal biology
I'm a policy wonk
Where am I
Policy wonk
I donated on elevated thank you so much
You are now a technocrat
You're now a technocrat
We got to go
Heroin
Chick-fil-A large
Thinking about your body
Generosity
Bundle it up really nice and toss it over to Mutual Aid
Kind of situation to help people in your area and eat
I don't want to belabor this or spend too much time here but it
You know we if we stop
Doing here the Seltzer it will just at
So although these times are great and serious
Are we also still need to check in with the year of the
So not a lot of progress
Great white plague
Such a positive
Not much going on
How much progress in the year 96
Drink
This point today is recess
It's a god-like cdda
Take a break from your life
I got two varieties of recess one of them was a pomegranate hibiscus
Fantastic
Then
I tried
Their other one which was Peach Ginger
Peach Ginger
Disaster
It's strange to me that the companies are capable
Such Heights in such a nose
Such as the recent
So so much
Thank you for the pomegranate and I may have another one of those at some point
Start here on June 1st
Alex
There's some big things happening
And Alex gets down to it here in this first
Savannah Hernandez
He's been here five years
He's now been accused by the Twitter mob of
He's the one that burned
Because when they're burning at 1 old Marine was almost cousins
Are you
Cockroaches
You done this because he just
The audience
Video of the man experiencing homelessness who had his mattress set on fire in Austin
And I chose not to include it on our episode that we put out on Monday for a specific reason
It was an editorial decision that I made because I tried to get to the bottom of what was going on in the video and I couldn't find any
In other cases the ambiguous video had some context clues that allowed me to get something of a grip on them
Like in the case of the brakes and ballast we know what building that video is in front of it we can discuss the idea of bricks being quiet
In the context of some surrounding Clues
The case of the video of the mattress fire was another thing altogether
All you had was Alex presenting a video of a mattress being bird and his claim that it was the protesters who set it on
Fire and other people saying Alex
In that kind of situation I'm presented with a couple of options
The first is to accept Alex's framing of the story and work to explain how it's an isolated incident
Doesn't necessarily implicate the larger character the protest
This isn't a good option because it relies wholly on taking Alex's word about an unclear situation
It's usually unwise to do that
The second option is to speculate that all is not what it appears to be
This could take the form of saying in 4th probably set the whole thing up or that it was the proud boys or any possible entity you could come up
Oyster Point the finger at
Big eruption feels better to someone who has the positions are beliefs I do
Because I hate to imagine that someone who would be associated with protests that I support believe in the closet
Would victimize a person experience
It's like that
It's ugly
And to avoid the feelings that that ugliness would bring up
Conclusion it with no evidence
Infowars stage the whole thing
The third eye
Option in the one I took was to be cautious
And not discuss it until there was more
To go on
Isolated incidents of property damage
Even this this egregious are not so pressing the news-item that we should feel like we have to make unforced errors
By either making unfounded accusations of a false flag making a mistake was feeding the ground to Alexandra
Accepting is framing
Hope those are not winning solution
It's hard
And I fully understand people's impulse to craft a theory that Alex or Infowars did this to make protesters look bad
Bummer to watch people do this
I've heard a number of rationalizations for why someone would assume Alex was behind it
One is that he's capable of doing something like this
And I can see that he almost certainly is
And that if there were evidence that I wouldn't be surprised at all
Being capable of a false flag publicity stunt is not the same thing as actually doing
Another rationalization is that Alex lies all the time
It's fine to weaponize it
Conspiracy against him
I have something important to say about anyone who might feel that way
I'm often unfairly accused of being gay when they go low we go high guy
And I resent that and this is nothing even close to that in this case
Absolute proof that Infowars set this fire this is a conspiracy theory that some people are choosing to acceptance
Fact or likely fact
Because it helps them build a narrative more convenient
After three-and-a-half years of studying Alex Jones
I'm comfortable saying that this pattern of thinking
Of accepting conspiracies absent evidence
Is what made Alex Jones into Alex Jones
We were show that's about this mentality and how it's corrosive
We primarily discuss this through the prism of Alex because he's the most flagrant an obvious example of someone who's become super
Whose entire career
Is based on
Conspiracy narrative
And building them out of things he cannot ever
Come close to prove it
But if you look at all the people that we covered that's essentially one of the big commonalities
Yeah
Do any
He doesn't make anything
Thanks
Because all the things humpers shirts are probably stolen from some random person
He doesn't make anything other than lies
Conspiracy thinking this kind of s*** is a manifestation generally of laziness
Your processing case process the next time
And on some level this is why Alex suck so much
He's learned over the course of his career that he doesn't need to do better than just make something up and his audience will be trained to accept that level
If people are going to be opposed to that kind of information
Economy that the right-wing is thrust us into
Crucial that they don't become lazy themselves and just use the same tricks
This isn't because the tricks are inherently wrong it's because they're corrosive
They work well
Yeah you can smear people like crazy and it work
Yeah but they also hurt you when you use
These techniques are not
Are there bad for you
Naturally probably the less abstract consideration is that you can't prove
That Alex are Infowars started that fire
And if you can't
You might as well be working for Infowars
When you make that accusation
A Twitter account that posted this accusation got over 13,000 retweets
And a video on Twitter
25 million views
Stop it you getting tons and tons of repressed and guess what like I said if you can't prove that you've given him the perfect
You can point to this is a great piece of evidence
Set the media the last they always lie about him cuz he's always right about everything
Deconstructing in discussing this propaganda is on
Sing to me
It satisfies an intellectual curiosity and I like learning about f***** up
But on another level it's motivated by a desire to limit the Toxic effect
People like Alex have on the people they've indoctrinated
His worldview is nonsensical and his businesses exploitative to the people who've been tricked into following it
The Narrative change to suit Alex's needs and maximizes
Is Prophets
He's been on the verge both Victory and the globalist shutting them down
20 years
The reason that this kind of thing the accusation that Infowars at this guy's mattress on fire really really really rubbed me
Romwe
Is because it has the potential to expose a lot of people to Infowars
And also trick them into thinking that he's right
There's a decent chance
And convinced that they found true
Because of an unproven accusations of Infowars staged a new story acceptable
You you can't give him the opportunity to
Play the victim by mitten
Because then you amplify his message again
25 million views
You see all these people and if he proves himself correctly
Or even if there's no proof that he did it
He can absolutely play the victim
Amplifiers message
And when people see that he actually is the victim of something that's untrue
Or at least impossible to prove
They're going to be like well obviously this guy is right and they're going to pay more attention to him
It's it's awful
It's a trick he relies on stuff like this
And if you just deprive him of this kind of oxygen he won't be able
Much more difficult time
Having access to
Fertile Minds to corrupt
I mean it's it is very much like oh you say that it's fine to use his own tricks against him
But what you don't understand it
He's been telling people that you're using those tricks anyways
True you're not doing anything other than proving that you're using those
Also you're not going to
These tricks
25 years ago
You're going to feel bad at some point
I want to be clear to I can't say that he didn't do it I don't know if you
I don't know I watch the video bunch of times slowed down
Eventually something will come out that shows that can have the discussion
I've asked multiple people to provide any evidence that this was in forwards doing and the best anyone has
Is a blurry picture of a logo
Impossible to tell if it is
And I don't think it is a computer instead
Enhance
I usually that works on CSI
The other piece of evidence is that the man who owns the mattress approaches
The camera and says quote I live here what the f*** are you doing
To me this doesn't really prove that the man is accusing the camera person of burning the mattress considering that the people who brought the mattress to the
Fire camp
Clearly different direction
Confirm the camera it looks more like he was just yelling at the closest
It doesn't really prove anything
But those are the two pieces of evidence
I just don't accept those as
Solid evidence
Not to say that Alex is the king but this is a situation where you can't miss
You can't do stuff like this unless you know
I believe
He could have did it
But if you can't prove that you're
Yeah it's 142 plays into his hands
It's important to remember that the camera person here too and the people who throw the mattress in the fire are not associated in the
Video at all
And that there's no way the camera person would have an Infowars sign on them
Being accosted or yelled at so it's definitely a situation where they were in stealth mode
This guy would have known
I'll be wearing a f******
Little card in their hats
Run out of there so fast know what happened to the tank
Is allowing somebody with an Infowars press badge on
Fox News
He didn't think they ran off
Alex's
What they do with the person who's just a person
At the very least is that camera would be gone for like yelling at
That was not the case
40-gallon Infowars that don't require this kind of unforced error
And that don't play directly into Alex's Playbook
This kind of thing just doesn't play and that's why I think the prudent decision in cases like this has to wait until there's more information
If it turns out to be Rogue protester acting reprehensible
You can discuss it on that front doesn't invalidate the
Larger protester the points of what's going on in the world
And you still then and you don't have to then see the ground to Infowars
Central position
And if it does turn out that there is evidence that Infowars dated
You can have the
Discussion formal responsibly because you can say
Here is why
I don't know I just I was
Nomad
I was texting somebody
Don't understand
Why people I beat you
It's not true I do
Understand
I don't understand why people can't get to the second step and recognize like
This is going to be counterproductive
It feels good I don't know
I guess we just accepted it so there's a massive population that's just going to do this
Let's all
Do Irish
That's that's what I can say
Delta and Alex gift-wrapped propaganda terrorist
So in the next class Alex discusses how
Realize that we were weak
This is at
And this is the deathclaw
All of the following political correctness
Has maybe establishment believe that you
The goose is cooked
Full
It just include attempts to kill the president
It doesn't
Kill the whole thing and
So that's exciting
Episode
What will I think this is probably part of it
That is it
Through all this
You know what's coming to know what you got to do you have to understand that your enemies are
I'm going to still say it's the murderer
No no
Your enemies
He has to recognize and they're not human
If you want to start a campaign is the murder hornet
It's that is your business
Stay out of it
Murder Hornet how cool is Jordan
Northeast
Doolittle beardie axle
These are scientifically evil
People committed
Destruction
As soon as you wake up
After that you'll be able to
Do you realize you're dealing with
Homicidal
You don't have a dad
Okay so that's all
Call coming out
Double down because things are so insane
That means it's time to sell
Things going on in the world unless I'm getting people really riled up
Big Move
I know I can move to
The product
Get the good sales going
Also goes to f****** it disgraceful mess of like
You have to recognize that your enemies are evil and then you can win also by the way I got to tell you
Well you got to get those pills out of there
Spilled out of there so he can
You can
Not
Fight globalist without an empty Warehouse
How many times do I have to tell you this
Empty Warehouse okay alright middle 12
So Alex is a big story about coronavirus covid-19
And it gets to admit next Club
Should we start
Second
Let me just a single
The German interior Ministry
Pamela pop scientist
And I came out instead
It is
Normal seasonal Desperado things about attributed to it
And it's just a cold virus
Destroyed civilization
Cannon Society
Alarm
False alarm
Is an alleged leaked report that a German official released recently that says that the fear of
Covid-19 might have been overstated
And honestly I can't find coverage of this alleged leak on any website that looks reputable at all
And none of them even linked to the actual suppose League's reports I have no idea about this
I have no idea if this is a real things it's kind of tough for me to respond even if it
I'd like presumably I'm going to give the benefit of the doubt and assume it's not made up
Entirely
I can't read it
I don't know I'm going to go ahead and err on the side of
Not taking Alex's word on this
No scientific report
About covid-19 read a lot of stuff
But no matter how many scientific reports I read
None of them agree with my conclusions 100% you know I'm going to get something wrong
It's very odd for a scientific report agree with every narrative that Alex puts
At least one
Well it turns out it was
Exasperation
His made-up story about the stories about
Alleged leak.
See if I can find it eventually but I have no idea
Has proved that everything about coronavirus
Is Big a hoax
There we go
I do diva
Group
Still not
Still not further
That will they go where where is their headquarters what's Silicon Valley
Tell you there is one
Terrorist groups
Shutdown
Violence
For political or economic
Definition of it
Cobra Commander
By your definition so are the cops
Thunder record
Under organized crime
With their radios
Accused
Reels
Forest
Documents two years ago
All hell broke loose Burroughs financing lawsuits against
We meet Hitler were going to be
I just can't stress this enough with Alex said anything better
You wouldn't
Constantly bring up these stupid document
It's a symbol of how weak his arguments are constantly fall back
They have a headquarters
The community commanded by Alexander store was based on some dumb s*** I found on 4chan
You might as well just be some idiot fourteen-year-old telling you about what he read on a Blog communicative message
Board nonsense
Also let's organize
A rubber ducky Smokey is coming through
Amos-4 organizing
Politically
They're really a get-out-the-vote
Organization
Sure
So we could talk in a little bit more about these documents here
Over and over again
Play martial law in Maryland
The police captain
Marylanders
Baltimore
Riot triggering a nationwide up
That's why Democrats
100 are promoting
And saying it's good
Endorsing it
What day
Democratic Governors and Mayors are endorsing everything that's going on
See you but you don't answer mean
They work for Alexandra Stewart
Milgard grave
Troops everywhere I need
Humvees armored I need those down there because I really endorse the message of these protests
Setting absurd curfews
Military grade weapons
Pointed at the citizens of my state because I support them
Yeah it seems a little convoluted
So Alex says the time
You know where I'm going to get down to it eventually
What's coming next
Controlling myself
Last segment
Bubba sour
Finish this
Play out the
Argue that all day long
Almost
Let me show you what really went on
It wasn't all over the news on Twitter tweeting stuff about that irresponsible
What's all over the news and also the Democrats didn't do anything
What are you talkin about
That was Nancy Pelosi in those videos
Personally doing I could see that cash it's also
Do that
Just getting ready to head to the hills though cuz it was just starting to get to that get to worrying him a little bit
Because I want to run
But if Americans are so soft and so stupid
Can't stop this
Rob Russia in
Why was Austin awake
The party's over funk
Unless
Globalist
Trump decisive
Anybody who was born in 1917 is 103 right now
The lieutenant governor said that he want to be elderly to sacrifice themselves for the economy this is the greatest sacrifice
Fight
3 years old I don't know
Balloon
House of War
And if you listen to Alex's show expression has a very specific
You
80 Temple Derry Ono
Now although I like it is a like ethology
No it's specifically used
To talk about Islam
Used to say that Muslims believe that any Muslim control care territory is
The house of peace
Horrible misunderstanding of something
Video of God dammit
That is a phrase that Alex is using
And because I know that he only uses that expression in those terms
He's essentially saying we're at a point where you should go kill
Like he's he's saying the terrorist Act
Are acceptable the only way we win is to decapitate the globalist
But I don't want to do that and neither
Should you as anything other than
Well we should be killed
The only way to win so you want to win
I think you do
Right Ronnie still keeps like you're saying like Trump's got to get the military to do it should be against
Preparing to evacuate is one thing and that's pretty extreme
This next clip really f***** me up a little bit he's he's he's
Really weird
Club Aesthetics
Vince each other
You're doing is normal
They're all going to be destroyed
Power outages starvation Mass
Nuclear war is on the table
Sending the military into the states is on the table
Pretty mentally tough
Literally
Praying with images
Bye-bye.
Talking on her back to say goodbye to your kids
Are you doing man
At around 3 a.m.
Goodbye when you wake up
This is either really childish you're presenting a dumb face to your audience of severity
You're f****** these kids up and you got to stop that stuff
Shut the fuk up
I don't know about that I love the first
Jordan
Did you say that
Alex Alex has a point when he's right he's right
Okay we can't do this
This is this is this is
Literally
Preparing to evacuate from the show
What are you
I'm not trying to set you up so don't worry
I do I just like the idea they close without getting to a room together convince each other what they're doing
A good man
Should we start a nuclear war I think that might be a bad thing
No dairy dairy it is a good thing
So Alex gets talking about the bunker go
Touch and Go
Rajput
At protest
Trump Doral
Call
Weak tools chart
People
In Washington State
Delirious
Police
Kneeling the black
Sure
That's amazing
For too long the governor
States rights don't talk about that at all
Groupon call in
And abused
Constitutional
Yeah well I mean honestly what happened next
I'm a little mad photo-ops like for different reasons
Hypocrisy of the later
People
Alex it's you just as racist
Complicated feelings
There's a top story on Infowars here on Monday and no
I don't think it's good
Story
On the site
Pull that up
Video
George Floyd
Bombshell
Reveal
Corroborate
Support
Floyd
Heart attack
It's cost him.
Criswell who cares
About the last part
I don't care about anyone
Watch the video on Infowars
It looks like
Possible
Like I said it doesn't matter
Even if he had a small amount of cocaine on it I accept no argument that is essentially
It's not fine to kill it for the police to kill somebody but it's more fine for them to kill me this person because they
No it's not any friends
You could have easily been caught with some cocaine all them and I don't think the police are justified in killing
Everybody the same way
You would think
Alex is trying to use this to argue
Killed by the officer but he had a heart attack from being on cocaine
But even if he had cocaine in his hands that doesn't mean he was on it or is it a system
Conclusions the dog
Match
Further neither of the preliminary autopsy should have come out of
That he had drugs in his system
Later there will be one that says that he had traces of sense
System is true later but at this point
The two preliminary autopsy
Come out at night
Specify.
Sure sure drop this cocaine he was already
Basically under
Police custody
They will go on
A killer and
I definitely zero doubt that if George Floyd drops cocaine that it would have been found
It would have been a part of the police report looking to find any sort of extenuating circumstances that could justify the police's action
It's really inappropriate for Alex jump
To conclusions just based on something one of his insurance on a video
Cuz here's the reality
He was wearing a sleeveless shirt at no point does it go into his pockets
If you read the police report it makes no sense
He could have been in his hand the whole time
From the report
As officer Lane began
Speaking with mr. Floyd got out and pointed it at Mr Floyd
Floyd to show his hands
It seems like in the process of showing his hand this would have been revealed that doesn't seem likely
Here's what I think the video shows and I should tell you I can't prove this but it's a possible explanation
Supposed to drop out of Floyd's
He's Back Against The Wall by police and slid down into a sitting position
He's coming down this wall hands behind his back
You can clearly see that this wall that is sliding down is painted white
With some of the paint missing from the side panel
Clearly visible in the video shot
I think it's entirely possible that would be enslaved into a sitting position his arms and back scraped against the wall
Power is really just a paint chip
I don't know that but it's impossible
Explanation for what's a phenomenon
And your eyes I just don't
Right it shows them beating him into a cop car and then murder
I don't I don't know what the situation is with his little white
My Explorations possible
What I can say with certainty is that Alex cannot prove that this is a bag of white powder yet he's reporting it as Defender
He's a reporting at that like this
Steube a bag of white powder
He clearly drops a bag of white powder
This is not
Like this isn't something that they can report
This is a guest but they're making
Well it should be
I can't because he's desperate
To tarnish the victim
Police violence
Works for his narrative
What's discusses more stuff about George Floyd
He's doing this
With the
Hyper intention trying to smear
Does George Floyd
Research
I wonder what kind of research Alex date about George Floyd
I'm curious how you missed the article in Christianity Today titled
George Floyd left the gospel Legacy in Houston
Just a small walk through been involved in Ministry
To Minneapolis for a job interview through a Christian work program
The church in Houston
The things that he would say to young man always reference
The god Trump speech Street culture
I think he wanted to see young men put guns down and have Jesus instead of the streets
Another fellow churchgoers
His faith was a heart for the Third Ward
That was radically changed by the gospel
And his mission was empowering other believers to be able to come in
I push that cost
Before
I would assume that I was just read various tweets from racist undecided that counts as research
He's invested in telling the story one particular way and it's important to recognize that and recognize why
It's just
It's just he's black
Obviously
Maybe more something
But it's just he is black
Might be more analysis if we hadn't done this a lot already
Yeah well that's a guy
So Alex pretends it's like a man
I knew this was all coming
I knew it
Cavanal me to house
A totalitarian regime oh sorry
Play jazz
You can't prove any of that
So I can't get on rest might be coming and images of race Wars
Pretty regularly
Tons and tons of predictions which is an intentional strategy
Be right about one of them
I can't count the number of times he said that the he knows the globalists are going to try to kill Trump within the next week or two
These predictions have never come true but his audience is trained to ignore those failed predictions and only focus on fake stuff
You can pretend he was accurate about
In the midst of the coronavirus death Alex did talk about social unrest concerns related to the
It didn't come in the form of protest against the stomach police violence and Glisan. Responsiveness to violence against non-white person
How to start up in the lockdown was going to crush the economy and then everyone to be starving and that would cause upheaval
As he discussed when he ranted by eating his neighbors
That prediction was literally nothing like we're seeing happening right now
So even if he can massage things for his audience to make it look prosthetic
You you was not
Maybe like if they interviewed Charles Manson and he was like see I was right
Like fuk off
It's not a thing
You said there would be erased but that's not
Get night also this isn't
Exactly
Should be repeated over and over again
Glassware
So Alex has big overarching prediction like what are you talking about like what comes after
Things coronavirus coverage days
Was that the whole coronavirus thing with
The test run
And it was leading tomato ravech scenes and also another biological weapon release though kill billions of people
That was the primary focus of his narrative and before that
In Chicago over and over again
Are you sure
Because Alex Rambles about bulshit pretty much everyday and so much of it
Last few months of yelling about race Wars or some s***
All I was saying was
My prediction
It's not his prediction was about a medical tyranny run by Bill Gates
Because the circumstances of the world Reckoning is predictions of the Beast being focused on all this as being what
Comes next app
Double-check
Space
It's like writing a package
A late night show you got to have
Different predictions to make put them all out on the same episode that way you can cut it to whatever one of them maybe
Ensure
Alex
Savannah Hernandez
Here's a Incognito reporter and a person
Zach
On
They come on to talk about the mattress burnout
They talked about it for a long time
I hide the fact they are naked propaganda
Did they come out to talk about that and I'll say like if they did do it
Brass balls
Brass balls trip
A strip
Bear arms.
I think is really troubling
If you do not resist you're not going to get killed
And that's a fact
What's the organized what's boom
Corruption
Yeah
This was even horse somebody called on him
Control
They put their niani
A combination of drugs and that killed him and now we got right
I don't know how it's
Makes sense for someone Infowars
Hard
Libertarian-leaning supposedly
Ron Paul Style
Conservative Outlet
Mister police state is allowing one of his reports and sing
Yeah absolutely after she says if you don't resist arrest
If you just submit to the authorities are not going to get killed
Yeah that's the libertarian position submit to Authority
I don't I don't
That's why Bill Cooper died because he was submitting to authority too much
This is a pretty standard refrain from braces
If they would just resist not resist the place
It's a standard justify the brand of State back violence they support
Well keeping in touch their complaints about the imaginary State Violence lyrics
Fears about gun regulations
Jet
What are the other cases it comes up very often in relation to current protest is the killing of breonna Taylor
Taylor was killed in her home after police executed a no-knock search warrant
Because they thought the suspected drug dealer kept drugs and money in that home
Do did not live there and he'd already been arrested
Some reason felt it important to do a no-knock which is really dangerous
It was about 12:40 at night so Brianna's boyfriend Kenneth Walker thought they were home Invaders
John and fired one shot
Please return to Taylor and sending bullets into the next child
Kenneth Walker beagley on his firearm and
Galaxy
Firmly believe he has every right to protect himself in those circumstances
So what about that Savannah
How did breonna Taylor acted like to her death
If you don't resist arrest
They're far too many cases that service counterexample
Put on Savannah's doing here is joining the Infowars game
I'm trying to make non-white peoples murders their own fault
Just b*******
Our groceries
I don't support what they did
I don't think that it's
Too right I don't think
Well if he wasn't resisting arrest he wouldn't
It's his fault he's not even doing the right thing by doing what they're doing he was resisting arrest
She knows
He's not as good at
No she's I should say that for the cops
If they're at all resisting
I think I
I think it'll take probably a
Fairly specific
Type of person to start working at Infowars late in the game
Maybe have been there for like 50
18 years or so
And maybe they
Boiled while they were in it near the lobsters who didn't
Realized
Like to be gravitating towards a particularly after 2015
Is weird and I think you have to be
Pretty angry pretty violent
I just don't
I can't imagine
Anybody thinking
There are legitimate
Or credible Outlet
Or that there anything other than
It like a means to express
Hey
Says a lot about you
So after this Alex has Owen Shroyer and a guy who owned the gun shop on and I just
Turn it off
I don't care
So we do. Here on the 2nd on Tuesday
And a little bit of an update on this your bricks story
About Soros in the fork
Ladies and gentlemen we've now discovered who is delivering bricks to more than 20 cities is
Wow yes you can if I had to guess what's going on here some dum-dum online company to link to
Do traditional globalist behind existence of bricks at protest
Actually that is what time
Acme Brick Factory before 1900 name of the world
As well as, codes
True
Corporation
Steve Justin companies
From Fort Worth Texas
And Louisiana concrete products
In 1972 they formally changed their name to Justin Industries Incorporated
Underneath this umbrella they're a bunch of
Subsidiary businesses including Acme Brick as well as Featherlite Building Products
And Justin Boots
Amir 2000 Berkshire Hathaway acquired Justin Industries which includes all those subsidiary business
Alexander be f****** up the whole thing cuz Bill Gates and the guy you talked about with Berkshire Hathaway
It's me ice cream lover himself Warren Bobby
Bill Gates is on the board of Berkshire Hathaway
Premier League charitable initiative
Rarely has any stock compared to Buffy
Is the guy who you point fingers at with Berkshire Hathaway
Been the laziest time for Alex to make Bill Gates connect to your social unrest narratives missing Bill Gates
Is on the board as the head of subterfuge
Mistresses going to play Manny just got to stick with Soros
I don't know what he's trying to do
Alex is taking this from a videos on Twitter supposed to be
It's just her talking to her camera and sing dropping off brakes
Bill Gates it's very clear that this is a source
And almost one eleven thousand retweet
Jesus it was making the rounds
There's nothing I believe more than a random woman standing in front of brick saying that it's Berkshire Hathaway
Okay great elise's bio reads quotes researcher and Truth
Great about your videos hashtag
Hashtag
In the past week she's posted
Clearly fake Craigslist post that are by recruiting crisis actors tons of stuff about plandemic
One particularly
Mel Gibson quotes
Try to expose the scum in 2017
Sure
She's commenting on there is about how Gibson said the quote parasites of kids
Which of the whole lot like a blood libel kind of thing
His dad's a holocaust and Ira in 2006 when he got arrested for drunk driving
This was part of the police report or what are you going to do
Gibson almost continually threatened the Malibu and will spend all his money to get even with
Gibson blurted out a barrage of anti-semitic remarks about Jews
Gibson gelder quote the Jews are responsible for all the wars in the world
The Gibson that ass
He's saying stuff school stuff about these group of people involved children
But I believe you
If you might want to question what kind of information you're passing a law
Maybe that's something
So idiot qanon weirdo
Asserting something without proof
Donaire
I feel like Berkshire Hathaway in Acme Brick could have grounds for a legal suit
Alex
He's claiming they're involved in a plan to cause this property damage and that's definitely meant to defame them and hurt their business
I think they should.
F****** sue them for all the ice cream in the world
It's totally naturally-occurring the sign here's the thing
Connect this kind of like with Sandy
Is that when questioned about why he reported things as fact and proven
He's in those depositions
He points to this
Bulshit that he found if you was asked to prove this Acme Brick
All he could do is point of this qanon weirdos video
And then be like that you're taking this from that's the level of work you do for work
So that would be the benefit of suing
You know it's not liable if somebody else says it and then I reported as fact
That's not how it works
I'm not I'm not sitting here particularly concerned about Warren Buffett of Berkshire Hathaway's reputation
Really forcing Alex to admit like I just took a f****** qanon Twitter video
I reported it as fax
Somebody just do it
Nope the benefit
Do it so also there was a new video that was going around which is reporting to police with a truck full of bricks
Leaving the break somewhere strategically in order for protesters
And to justify a violent
Response
Presumably they're working for Soros if you're on the right
Or they're just cops if you're not
I'm not going to say that it's impossible that there are some in
Census of police trying to facilitate situation
Where they could get people to respond violently
Rationalized
Autotrader's bfbi everybody Department of Homeland Security I'm not saying
Doesn't happen
This video doesn't prove anything and honestly it's
Pretty sad seeing you get passed around by people I've seen between it
Alexander Parker
Followed by three stars
Which is a dead giveaway this is further established by them
Play The Medic in between
Who's a huge qanon booster
Also tagged in the Tweet is an account called
Punished damn 1776
Which speaks for itself
Also they're biohaz where we go one we go all in it
Alexander Parker his Retreat Jack Pacific multiple times
And also a cute walking out of the White House with a sword in his hand and angel wings drawing
We're all doing
Great video doesn't show anything
Inconclusive being spread by qanon accounts it might be wise to pump the brakes on
Confirming the store you want to be
QuikTrip
HD stops in Boston War planting bricks
I have no idea
Fuel does not show that
There plenty of other explanations were could be going on
Losing strategy
Yeah there's just so much frustration and fury and
And confusion and
Nobody knows what the hell is going on
Understand why you can
Like get caught up in
Like I said it's very easy we saw it happen over and over and over again we saw Alex
Immediately after the Boston bombings did what we did
No
Show me people shared pictures of other people
Spaces just said hey these are the guys so many times
It's just
It's just so hard I understand because
Restraint
Now
Seems f****** insane
Write the idea of like
Hold off until we figure this out I understand that
Directed
Twitter
I never be great
Yeah
My hypocritical dumb
I just think that like there is
There's something about the immediacy of
Social media that allows everyone to be really suck
Sloppy with it
I am II
I just
I would ask people be a little bit more
Conscious be more careful like
If you're if you're putting a
A video
It has the caption
Police in Boston caught
Believing bricks as asset
Watch the video and if it doesn't show that
Don't pass it along
Like I don't I can't
Understand
I know I grew up on social media
I understand how social media
I don't understand how people can
Well in all the terms-of-service ones that you click okay
It's not like any of them say you should use social media responsibly
Put it in those terms of service I'm sure we would all read all the way down
That's a good point
So this next clip
Alex talks about how
He's only going out arms now he's always got to go and
And then
I just I found this Eddie doesn't want to ask her later
He's a d escalation
But I will tell everybody now
You should not be out
After Dark
Passover
Live that my son was going to visit my parents
Looters in the store attacking people
Kick their ass
Unbelievable
IMovie
Alex's using video a video of his son beating up a guy like a 7-Eleven
That's real yeah Jesus
Right yeah it's really messed up
I don't even know what to say about it
Goddamn
Yeah
Pretty bad
If you hate looters then you hate that guy was allegedly stealing stuff from the store
For this Alex's Sun happen to be in
Right
Whatever
Is Christ conflicted content on his show
It's incentivizing
Something very negative you definitely shouldn't be proud of it
Later
Rock shows up on the show.
Places you should give him an uppercut
Instead of those hooks and it's really sad
That's really f****** sad
Video got taken
Turn off we need Alex's I'm talking to a gang leader about floppy titties
Tip of the spear
So we get now to this other medical report
They came out
By this point on June 2nd
Here's Alex.
Now
He had enough
The police were scared
Attention and put their knee on his neck
Defending what's copped
That's literally what you just did
Hennepin County Medical Examiner has released
I had traces of Fentanyl and methamphetamine use in his system
This is pretty imprecise but you can see how information
For five people
Whether he was on drugs or not whether he had drugs on him or not all of it is kind of irrelevant to the larger issue
And that is that neither of those
Make his death okay
All of this stuff Alex is doing is an attempt to make his death okay because if he's forced to get his mad about this man Beamer
Murdered by the police
As he might be if I don't know a state require background checks
Private Sales of guns
That would have a cascading effect
What is a basically Fall Apart
Because they're all based on
White
Different yeah
Superiority
He starts to give ground
To that
It will have a domino effect
Insects with Alex complains you know
Wet certainly whenever businesses
Is the refrain
I was think of the business
Alex same thing that happens
And now Alex is saying
Don't you think of the police
There have been cops
More than 10 police shot
In the last 24 hours
One of their name
Izzamedia wonder why
Humanized
Truth
Tacoma.
Randomly shot in the head
They won't show him
Say his name
Because they will not humanize people that we all know George
Boys name
I think there's probably a reason why they're not releasing names
Folks
Pennywise
There are four cops that were shot in St Louis on Monday night
Three were hit in the foot or leg and Fork was shot in the arm recovery
As of the time of this recording I can find no information on who shot them so I have no idea who the people associated with the protest
Or not
In Las Vegas a couple shot and killed and that is not good
The shooter was arrested and is in custody but there's no information I can find about the perpetrator as of the time of
Recording
However that night Las Vegas Police also shot and killed someone at a protest who they said was reaching for a firearm
I don't know the reality that story is but that's at
Turn Alex's coverage
Also centralized episode police shot and killed BBQ restaurant owner David michetti
Would you like to deeply Street being fired
I'm not going to sit here and justify in discriminately firing guns at police but I am going to say that if you're going to cover that story
It's your responsibility to also point out that there's a high level of police brutality
It's being documented across the country
These are borderline cases either
These are instances of people marching or congregating peacefully only to have tear gas grenades
Sometimes fired at their faces videos of police throwing people to the ground unprovoked
Footage of cops driving through people
Yeah
If you're telling the story of the police being attacked and not talking about the other side
Explicitly trying to do PR work for the
Police you're just trying to hide their actions
Yeah but that is all that's going on
For free
For the for the Coppa of PR system
Yep
There's a
Grape
Kivik for Alex's career mister anti-police
Free Press work for the cops with a dick
The cops are all cops they're always acting
Can you tell defense
Threat
That seems to be Alex's position
That's where he's coming from if you don't
Resist they won't kill you
I just don't understand how you is like it has to be there so insulated
These people must be so insulated
From viewing any of these
Cuz you can't see
So many
And then have them recommend every single one of them until your glass
Like f****** one of us
It's not radical isn't it strikes me it strikes me that I think Alex doesn't do any work
I think that he just comes in as the curated stuff that is
Crew has given him any yells about it
That must be what goes on because otherwise like
He would be seeing
Tons and tons
Tons of videos
Police acting inappropriately
Basically just be sitting there must have done something
Yeah exactly every single one
Keep doing that
I just find
Pretty difficult to believe that
Someone
Who's yelled about the police and
Brutalities
For so long
So performatively
So funny so funny that this guy who made multiple documentaries about the police state
Be around when police were enacting curfews and
Sending the national guard against protesters and
You'll be on the side of
Police
Who are the predicted it's real sad real sad day
Here's the thing man
Important
I do
He's gone he's really important to wrong disagree if you want to if you want a nice
Snapshot of some real narcissism
This is where you're going to find it
No that won't be too much
Flown in for an audience
His lordship
You killed on the spot
Dumbasses
Globalist don't collect
Like people like me
They want me to join the New World Order
You don't have value in their eyes
You're what they call
Are useless here
Are useful
You're a dumbass
He's a dumbass three times in less than a minute so I don't know if he has much of Al you
The value cuz he's so good at yelling he's created a supplement line
I can't believe
He thinks
Anyone will invite him to anywhere
That's amazing
I mean that is a real
Pathetic level of self-aggrandizement
But I will actually be invited places because the future will need clowns Dan and I will
Put makeup on my face
Don't care
I do remember hearing some folks like begging the stand-up days here
Folks like maybe late at night at a party
Talking about how like
What side is a
Through hard time to people in need
Comedy so important
It is not
I don't know how positive
Nobody on the street
Right now is like
I got to do my type so I just got to get this out of the way.
There's enough people out there that there's
Someone who wants to get a second
Alex blames Zuckerberg works for Bill Gates blah blah
Call Bob Delp mobile
Okay
Now he is okay
Truxel fastest military Zuckerberg
Jake work for you
This is the biggest thing we've done in
A year
Look at it so I can do doing the match lady out there
Little boy
I like I like the contractor for this for Satan.
Bill Gates Bill Gates daughter works for sake subcontract
Of course
So dumb
So stupid
You're just making sure.
Alex talks about Susan Rice has come out
Ion TV talked about
Some of this stuff
It's going on is out of the Russian Playbook
Alex
Feelings about that
Play Barack Obama
Let me
Witness in major cities is right out
Is it goes on to say
Doing this with no proof
So the argument that Susan Rice's make monthly
The Russian actors use social media accounts to play both sides of device
Naked people fighting
With each other
She said that she had no idea that was the case
I'm not reading the
Today or these days
She went on to say that we cannot allow ourselves to be distracted from the real problems we have in this country that are lost
Centuries-old and need to be addressed
Responsibly
I don't particularly care about this.
I'm going to tell there's a little more information behind it
That's Alex's assertion though which is weird
Susan Rice is a big global
Austin Alex's eyes
So how does it make sense
I thought that Russia was the thing that they used against things they didn't like like
Alexander does make no sense
Even just on a surface level
And these couple episodes are really full of s*** like this man
Alex took off
It's just it's a mess
Poetic Justice
Any any any rope
In 5 minutes draw literally
Castrating every
So maybe that's why the Russian
Doesn't think that you know
Sing
Right right
But with no proof
Which he's again
In this circumstance
Right
It doesn't really work
Galaxy still mad at everyone saying this mattress on fire
Defend himself about it
What else is mean what is the top of Twitter
A homeless
We have the footage released
Burning
The whole thing
This isn't true
Their timing for Associates in employees are still on Twitter and they're posting a bunch of videos that
Definitively prove that Alex
Do show a longer stretch of time
Saddam Salazar Kaitlin Bennett Millie Weaver Mark Tyson
Confirm
They're all still on Twitter
Protestations
Innocence
In order to get right with the script Twitter just needs to let Alex back on Orban all of those
People because the way it is right now please
Entirely into Alex's Optics
He can pretend to be totally abandoned sensor
Well still haven't conduit with hundreds of thousands of followers to promote is content on the platform
He's a win-win
They just need to ban all those f****** people
To do
Yeah
I guess it's probably because they're technically personal accounts or whatever you know
Dancing stuff
Prison Planet
Seems like that one dude is knockout one outside
I don't know
Where would I defend myself
Where could I defend myself I need to go on some sort of media platform I need to have my old one because
How many people are silencing my voice
Right now
Okay
God
That's
Alan Keyes
He's coming with a bulge
Alright
That's protected in the car
The right of the people
Pizza Boli's
If people are out there
Definition of the United
What they are actually doing
And when Insurrection becomes widespread which it has been lately
The commander-in-chief
The Army and Navy
Into the actual service
He's making an argument a constitutional basis allow
Save it burning a police station is a
You Know cover by the Constitution or whatever maybe you could have an interesting conversation about that
But if you're going to do that then you need to be looking at every single instance where police acted upon
Peaceful
Protesters at demonstrators
And take that just as seriously as you would someone break and I don't see any of that coming
From Alex's side at all
David has brought this conversation
Stupid the constitutionalist Serbian
Not necessarily
I forgot about that
Is interesting
Shootout in Keys
I know although they do get into little bit of a slice
Is a really funny coming up
I wouldn't call this a novel solution cuz it's
Somebody said f****** million times
The situation where at
Nuketown
Going after the organisers.
FBI raids
Five people.
Obama Hillary the globalist they're running this
Martial law
Listen to that clip you just realize how f****** pathetic Alex's
Bicurious suggesting at the solution for Trump in this situation is to raid and arrest the people
Clinton
2015 and 2016 on the campaign Trail the chance of lock her up broke up broke out at every Trump rally
People wore Hillary for prison shirts
The whole thing was such a force in his base that it one of the presidential debates Trump said
If I win I'm going to instruct my attorney general to get a special prosecutor to look into your situation
Bnm sardellis 11 instances of trump threaten
Hillary up
Or Trump
Where is telling crowds at his rally that he was going to get a special prosecutor involved
You didn't do that because you was never gone
How to do that there was all the publicity strategy years later you have Alex desperately still trying to make it happen
You have essentially bacon his god-king dictator to enact Vengeance on his imagined enemy
Juicy I'm just
Begging Uncle please sir
I've contradicted all my principles for you won't you at least fight this Evil Woman
Please sir she runs antifa
So sad little baby
The president's people in somewhere
Good good the president sending people in somewhere
Send it
Great place to pick up take a load off
Newport Beach
He's already said that he wants like malicious
Coming in
I really think that's a bad idea to start deputizing everybody
What is enters into it
To the country
Pointing
Allen keys does not like Alex style interrupting everybody all the time
I don't blame you
It's weird to hear Alex I kind of have to take it
Was a dude ran for president if you got keys in your way you got to get steamrolled by him
Conversation is pointless
I made it Beyond am just saying like Trump needs to Posse up
All right guys
You guys
Really wish that somebody would be like oh okay if I looked into a mirror
All the sudden magically a swastika appear
These people are out-and-out Nazis
Better
That's not
Little brown church
These are going to win World War 2
It's bumming me out
Well you might be
The interview with Alan Keyes ends and now Alex gets into
Nice
I'll be honest with you
Check the last few months ago
What's happening
Pulaski days out of
But I like
Because I meet a tall you
Trendys all you people
Around your neck
Memorial Day is he
God dammit
He is never going to get in trouble for not saying politically there
He is such a he's such a douche
Talking
But I want to start a literal hot water
Not no political there I want to kill all of my specifically
Trying to antagonize
People I say have fake contract with the antifa
I would never say that cuz I gotta protect
The revenue stream
Court and so ominous
Lytic lesion
But didn't forget to say it a little while
Not good.
So Alex gets back to this o'bricks
Story
And this is funny to me
20 studies delivered
Just took off
Kill the police murderer
I know because I have my phone
You sure they did didn't
Alex
He double-checked it
Watch that qanon video game
Congratulations
He has a responsibility to prove that Acme Brick delivered bricks specifically for these protests
Turn violent United States
Off the hook with the
Just press the button teleporting thing
I don't care about that so he said he's confirmed
Solid
Concrete like a brick pack
You're really going to have to prove
20 things if you say there's 20 City
Oh yeah
It's still not 20%
So Alex
Marshall Law basically
You understand
Starting point
We have to
Is not shutting them down
The anti-fascist
We're here now this is where we were brought
Now I'm Pro police
Did the Pentagon
The president
Doesn't
Start
We're going to lose
So you've lost
Civil War
New Zealand
Hawaii
Let's just not go there
Want to kill
These people
Really sounds like you do
Caribou
You're calling for decapitation
Telling them now as representative
If we're anybody wants to kill you
Because you
Politically
Just commit suicide
Jokes
Chordify
Political
Sitting here watching
Soros
All these other people
Because they're already dead
You need to die
What acquaintance
Martyr
Political
Soros would be turned into a martyr for the left
Streets out there they kill Soros
Rambo and long-winded
We're going to kill you you should kill yourselves global astralis
But I don't want that
Pretty mad at the end
Doesn't undo the emotional effect
I forgot about that
Yeah absolutely
Navigate to New gas
Get another guy
New for the show
She was just on
It's rainbow
Rainbow stats
Now that's that's how she should go to protest
Yes that was the original idea
Blend in with the sjw that was the point where rainbows
Yes I'm starting to think that that wasn't a good idea
Using one character I would love it
Millie comes in a convoluted conspiracy
From our last episode was weird
She's got
I don't know how to describe this
This is Pulitzer work
Okay
Breaking news
Premature we were hoping to get it out later
With more detail
But the Paw
Problem is is they stop
Make sure that we had anticipated
We have had
Trader that was the problem
Green movement
We are going to start releasing the document
The infiltrator
She she's been in there for
For two years now nice recovery
Level
Devastating stuff inside the sunrise movement
Deep-cover Infowars mole
We have there
Tire mirrored servers
We have it all
Other internal Communications.
Got the receipts
Then bye
Is insane what we have
If you have all of this information and you can't come up with something
Disquieting
Anyway Alex wants Miley to lay it out
What was going on what are you
Alex always expects her to lay it out
With it there's a glass ceiling in a far better work than Alex if
I didn't take all this
She's at least
Trying
Keeps interrupting her and cheese
Begin at the beginning
Thousand years ago
2 years
Invio globalist
Yes it is the same group
Bernie Sanders was endorsed by
Comics
Yes babies Democrat
Cats are in League with these
These groups
They just think they're allowed to do this
You just can't stop getting in the making of the mix
She can't get her sentences out about what her big
Conspiracy that she's uncovered is
About me
Mommy
So anyway I guess she's got these documents and what have you but she hasn't released them so I don't have any way to assess what you think
Even talking about really hard cuz they're on the server
We have so much stuff
Somebody here a lot of stuff we can't do
So much so much truth
Talk about any other I really meant to get into those thousands of documents we just ran out of time in this hour
Hour-long interview
So I guess this is part of it I don't know necessarily but apparently I don't have to do this
Coronavirus non-existent or something
Getting everyone to wear masks
You know who came up with that
Antifa
Been pushing for all these masks
Their plan
They can use the mass to be able to go out there concealer eye
Identity theft
Everybody's
Exactly
Call from
The mask
Do you believe
You just said it.
Deep stuff everyone's wearing a mask
That's some like really deep
I'm saying
Nobody's ever worn masks
As we all know Auntie invented the first match
Celebrate for that and then we took advantage
They took advantage of their Brilliant Invention in order to
Blend in with us and as we all know blending in makes you feel very powerful
True individual
Discrete games
Organizations headquarters you know who makes wrist blade
Acme Brick
Fairhaven District
Alex comes back from break and he's getting real Hattie
8 starts
Thinking about fortune cookies
Determination
Talent
Insight no competent
Literacy correctness
Termination
Just haven't quit
Understanding
Turn on Wills over.
God doesn't
Control your will.
No.
Dreams
You can't do it
Unless you imagine
Two really good points
Think I'm Gigi pain
What the f*** is that
Like I do I don't know what this kind of waste of time bulshit is
Dick what crazy
Dick
See there we go
Take me to
You still on
Like I mean baby at some point in history has been straight-up get you fired
But now is the actor alive
Voice
The Hunt Hill bridge in
Last night
The military
National Guard
Able to actually Corral the Riders onto the bridge they had
Both sides of the bridge closed
Post office
The military police were able to make
Large array
People about 300
Riders Terror
Okay
Or arrested in
Raking
Curfew
That's what they were able to
Get the terrorist
Officer all on social media
These are peaceful protest
Masterpiece Old Pro
No they're not
Criminals peaceful protest
Don't break the law
They don't commit crimes
Okay they won't be out there because they wouldn't be wanting to buy
Wow
Bad stuff that is the power we want for our movement
Everyone in the hard right movement make
Sure you submit your curfew don't courage great otherwise you're not a peaceful protest
You're a criminal
I mean
Daughter singing for curfew
Licorice kiss this kind of like
All these people in masks because they're out
Wow
You know what I think the military police should absolutely perform a pincer movement in order to trap a large group of
People on a bridge that they cannot Escape
And then of course fire non-lethal weapons into a crowd indiscriminately now I think that's a good idea
8 pm
You bring up something else that's really interesting accidentally and that is Alex missed his opportunities to pincer movement
She loves to do
Is Deathstroke update on the Trump family
Are they on fire yet
Have you noticed that
Totally
Risking his job everything to say that
For the Deep state is literally sabotaging Trump
Here's a couple things I want to say if Tucker
Carlson critiquing Jared Kushner is risking his job
That's indicative of a problem
Should
Criticize those in power
Need to make sure feel threatened
Alex just says that it looked at all examine the idea of what
Frazee
And the second thing
Cuckoo bananas
Alright
Let's imagine Alex's right
Jared kushner's the Deep state
No one wants him to be there
Yes
It's not like he has some kind of policy expertise
Tires that likes o you know what yeah maybe
Maybe he has a little bit maybe he's affiliated with some think tanks or whatever but he's just so damn good
Ematic alright we're going to orchestrate
Shadow idea we need for the job
F****** Kush
Let's do we got to get on ourselves let's get Trump's bucking son-in-law
In order to implant
What the hell is going on here
Here's what we need we need a spoil
Bridge motherfuker
In order to get our
Alex does this game with Kushner all the time
Like he's in and out on that dude all the f****** time
It's so it's so strange to me like how many times he's turned face and turned heel
It's
This for the wrestling as well beat the Big Show
He poops a lot
I don't know man I can't really get interested in this
But it's funny hilarious
Main Street
How much is
Fox News is a propaganda Network and if they speak out against their leader
What does l
Luckily hired someone lost
So Billy gets to talk about how
That she has a few things
Write about
This big ass
She's got
Peabody Pulitzer
You got for it even though it's not a musical
TV show true
Released
Tomorrow started already released video today
Private internal copper
Prince's work
Osseo Cortez
Is calling for more uprising
Pictures of the rides that we're seeing
Publicly she sang
She saying everyone should know
We got that out today
Video released of AOC
It's not her saying that there should be more uprisings or anyting
Cortez making the point that we can make all of this
People to protest
In the first place
That's an argument that super threatening to Alex Because deep down invest in the status quo
Discuss a possible shifting
Traditional power dynamics
Any instinctually labels as the work of the global
We'll see what millions of releasing
This ends up being a disappointment
This isn't about any actual documents they got from a server or
Russell resume Billy might have dropped something interesting at all interview
It's kind of just a theatrical piece that exists in order for Alex to say stuff like this
Boy Scouts
The stuff is so horrible.
Weird
Jeffrey Dahmer looking people like
Alex needs his own project Veritas style stories of about a million
I have no idea if they have a mole at all of this server mirror
This recording recorded Zoom call but you could have gotten some other way
Screenshots of public websites and a guy's LinkedIn
We'll see what comes of this forwards do not give your hopes
So Alex has racks on
Raining off and waste my time
Talking about how f*****-up it is that Alex is talking about how his son beat up a guy in a
Convenience store
No but there were two things
Worthpoint
Here's the first
My little baby's here my first-born Rex
So I don't want to talk about this like I said
Cuz I think it's inappropriate
I only keep this clip-in because Alex says that Rex is his first born
And that made me think of something
What's that
According to Alex the race memory of a person is passed out to their firstborn son and strips
And then she becomes a queen
But here's where things get murky
Alex's said that he's paid for a ton of abortion
Before
One of those children would be his first born son
Rexburg
Keyboard
At the point where Alex chose to terminate
His partner whole thing with John
Fertilize their eggs and development
So here's my point
If Alex is theory about race memory means anything but either Rex doesn't have Alex's race memory
And in fact the inheritor that race memory was
Or
Rex does have race memory
Then it can't have anything to do with the father
If that's the case
Possible
Okay sorry has to be in Rex has race memory it has to be entirely something
Things related to the interaction between a fetus
Since mother again here's where
Here's where we're in trouble with
All right because this could absolutely invalidate everything he says about him
Abortion
If he says to me
That the soul doesn't enter
Or the race memory doesn't enter
Until the child is born
Guess what's fine
Zeit now Finding Dory
Or he's full of f***
I think it's possible but even with your rebuttal he could wiggle out of it
We will sure only a thing for the first born son
All the other aborted babies
Something that I think is really really interesting to consider it a little implications
He's never consider
They're just a means to hide a chauvinist worldview behind romantic mystical ideas
He's never even given any thought to the process he believes that the most important thing in the world
You just making all this s*** up so you can sound deep as opposed to just saying what he means
He believes that women are inferior to men apparently
Fort George Lucas not giving chewy a metal theme to Star Wars
F****** racism
Do not give him a
Not going to give him a f******
Erase memory exist need to explain to either your son does not have race memory
Yeah
You need to
Explain to me
Erase memory has nothing to do with you and everything to do with
You are a spouse or mate
That case
I do I don't even care you need to prove to me that race memory
Yeah I mean I don't believe that either but I just like to have fun with his super delayed
So here's the last clip that we have and
Such a bummer
You would do something and then at one point I guess I had to jump in and do something
I was terrified but I mean I had to do it
And now that we love our somalis
Tamales
We love our Muslims too
I hate talking about Alex's family because I tried to go out of my way to leave his personal life alone
This however was something that I think is important to bring up
If you ever need any bigotry is a learned behavior
Here you have it
There's no indication that the person that wrecks beat-up was from Somalia or a Muslim become a code
On Alex's show
The person who made with Alex
Dial Alex
Whenever he found an instance of any violence that was done by a person who happens to be a Muslim
Eddie transformed the song show everyone always makes fun of him
But he's actually right about it all
Basically the same sort of gas that you're giving
When you accuse him of setting a mattress on fire
The song in the code on Alex's
Its original context
And you can see here how a father and son joined together to sing a song that's explicitly about 18 by norty group because you're scared of
And that's what's going on
I mean
I can't imagine
I can't believe that
Alex
Is covering a video of his son beating up somebody at a convenience store
Their conversation is
Worse
Then just that
You know it's it's
It's bad
It's really really disgusting
So I may we come to the end of this age
Something I find a little bit interesting is that like
Eurokies
Really
Pretty much staying on similar tracks
But he's been on
In terms of the
Trying to invalidate George Floyd's murder to make it palatable to his audience
Not a big deal
And then second the
Conspiracy theory Rising about the protest
Demonstration
All this stuff is
Continuing unabated
You know you have the the Brick narratives I was assigned a great amount of Comfort Inn
He's got a ratings Bonanza coming through with the mattress fire
Trajectory wise is 8
Calls for blood
Yeah you're seeing that and you're seeing him have people like Alan Keyes
Come on to give like a
A weird constitutional rationalization
Denver coffee and up and having
I guess armed civilians
Fighting
Alongside National Guard people or whatever which seems nightmarish
It's it's
Really
Jarring
It's really jarring to find out
Just how few people are living in 2020
And how many are living in
Like
This old time of like
Fascism is fine we need to fire upon
Nobody is learned that lesson
Over and over and over again
Very tough
Everybody just keeps
Thinking man
I'm going to be a higher up
In the fascist order
I'm going to take a level up
In fascism
So I am
Profesh
Immediately
No no problems there so I'm safe from it
Insane to me that we've
We've normalize this so much and we're super in a year where
F******
Amphibious cars
I can't have him fibia scars and now she's running America you know like I just can't do it
Yeah what do you think about Alex
Like on this episode
I don't know he seems very fake
The only thing that seemed generally like that whole screaming speech like Phyllis price
Yeah but this is just
Is this a real f******
Stop at you man
Does not like that
Subway
Until then we website
We are on
And if you could please donate to a aggregators
Spread that money across a large number
Yes please
Holding
Alex
I love your work