Air Jordan
Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for knowledge B I'm sick of them
Need
College fight
Acknowledge
I don't know why but suggested a little video for me
We're all in trouble
Guy's a big news about vaccines
They're bad
It was a video of its kind of a John R I wasn't aware of on YouTube
And that is
People who are experts in a certain field reviewing scenes from movies about those things
Is a crime scene investigator or Detective
It's Fascinating People of just like a really specialized
That's accurate this is bulshit
Is an animal a
Expert like I Wildlife behavioral expert really charming and like
Had some interesting things to say about animals
Through the Heart by started just thinking about how much I love
Love animals like I love my cat
And I decided that as part of celebrating this new apartment
I'm getting a second animal threatened
But I don't know what it's going to be
Maybe I don't like I don't hate dogs but I'm not I've never seen myself as being someone who would have
I'm not not a dog person in this
Although I could get used to it I've lived with jobs in the past
I was thinking maybe another cat but that also seems kind of like
I don't know if Celine is
Teambuilder
Go to another cat is some kind of
Like
But you can't write you can't
You can't get those. Let me tell you something
Maybe I should get a bird
Do not get Coronavirus
They're too loud evil
Many reasons not have Birds
I would think about like maybe a chicken or somebody told you eventually
Chicken inside my partner
I'm thinking about a hedgehog
Chinchilla
I'm thinking about a pair of sugar gliders that are cool
I think they're probably too and I wouldn't have enough space without
Now I'm not entirely sure I've got up there's a lot of stuff
First of all for the
Removing like
You know
Getting some more space for some plants Ryan also
For possibly another animal threat
Which is first off
Sugar gliders need a lot of sucrose and you don't have that
And they need space to Clyde
I don't know if you have enough space for but if I get some
Glide all over the text
Thoughts about animals
Fire to just live in the woods hang out and talk to Deer
Stumble through my shack
What I'm trying to get the most out of while still living in the city
I'll get a little tiny marsupial to sit in my pocket
For me there's only one
Right now and that is TJ Ford
And all that
And you can donate two of the best things that you can do right now listen to art
Bj4 and give money to people
For those uninitiated that's run the jewels
Go to Broad audience
Okay
They told you
You are not
Alright they told you again on our team
RG. RG
I'm out over and over again
I always say that and sometimes I'm wrong
Congratulations
What happened.
What happened directions
See there you go
Stretch of time kind of I guess not really
Feeling very frustrated a little bit
I don't think his narratives are going anywhere it's the oldest just like a guy who's
Dunham's ad
Liquors are boring
What really exciting stuff
Stop going on in the room
Right and you would think that I would be able to rise to the occasion with interesting stuff in his own propaganda
It just doesn't really like you just talks to a couple of
Dead end
Congressional candidate
A guy who probably
Man I probably definitely doesn't believe the Holocaust is real
Yeah when you're limited by the dumbest man in history it really does kind of mess with
With your ability. You know exercise imagination you have to be the stupidest
There's a mainstream conversation
Putting the military
Against protesters is a great idea responsibility of normalizing
Since the barbed-wire is allocation neighborhood to be the first building
You have to be the tip of the spear towards poking burlesque
Responsibility
Not
You have to also
Not be specific about violent threats Roshe run the risk getting in trouble
Inspired
None-the-less angle
Spoke suicide up and recording the show
Jom thank you so much
Joanna
Text Susan.
We're doing a lot of that
Don't take my back
I got to get that away from you
Jon B because I'm up here and I was wrong
Sloop John B
Chelsea thank you so much
Coronavirus news
Fair that would already ends end
Chelsea Dagger
Nextera
Noah's veterinarian
Michael W thank you so much you are now it's
Red with two D's last initials thank you so much you are now technocrat
And Susie
Be thank you so much and I'll technocrat
We got to go
Thank you so much Michael think is much Fred and Suzanne
Cymbalta and directed towards
Charitable initiatives that are going around right now
One will talk about a little bit later on the the show our friend Chris Redd
Is meant to provide some
The money is for testing
And for hospital bills that may come up
From people who made get coronavirus fantastic being out on
On the front lines and now protesting
Necessarily go donate download is an option
There's a 100 things
You find the most important
Do you personally I feel like you can help the most
A local
Locals going to be really important to build communities from the from the local up
Get around the people that you're around
Take care take care of whatever you're feeling is your priority
So
I got
And I know it sounds like I keep saying that but I I've just been trying to get this taken care of
It's really
Getting to a point now where I realize like I got a bunch of Seltzer's already that I got it I'm not moving the seltzer
Drink one of them already so it's not like a new thing
View
If you were arrested arrested with attend
Intent to deal yet its distribution levels
Bringing some of them and then I'm going to take the rest to the food bank
I'm too distracted to even
I try and bother with a bunch of filters
Apace
Will be fine
And once we hit the ground running
It's a new place
It'll be nothing but could be a f****** Seltzer Palace me and my goddamn sugar glider sitting here on my shoulder
Talking about Seltzer's
Celtics
You don't know that
I did not report
Not soon enough my Seltzer heads up there
We start off the show and we get to start on June 3rd and this is
All that Mark esper Secretary of Defense has come out and said
Let's not do that insurrection.act thing
Job
We don't want the insurrection
And they're like no
Everyone I know either has been robbed
Most the crew that had their mailbox
All the time now
Covid-19 Asteria
But the crime he is
I told my
My son
Alex is really overstating a lot of this probably to create a lot of fear
I can't imagine why he wants them to feel of the other
I also like your son was out after 8 or 9
I don't I don't know doesn't get much more you can't tell me what to do dad then beating a man to death at a 7-Eleven
Just to be clear
Yeah I don't know I think Alex is overstating a lot of this stuff because that's in his best interest
Create a sense
The fever generalized an overwhelming sense of fear
In the audience very much doubt that he's carrying a
Gun with them
I think he's full of s*** on that too I mean I know that up to a certain point
Being at least
Didn't have a carry permit
You probably have gotten one since then but he may not
Open carry a Barrett 50 cal never underestimate Alex's cowardice
So
You've got these tests that are going on around the country that are
You know motivated by
Feelings of
Police murdering
On our black people are outside agitators
From all the other 50
Nowhere trading them between state
Now that's
I mean some people will make that argument so you know where we're sending a good ones from New York
Chicago Chicago 7th of January
No people are people upset about the police murdering people and then on top of that
Not having consequences
And such Anthony
Beyond kept going in a large part because
Some of these protests
Have been met with police brutality
And that certainly is a vicious cycle that can continue
And I certainly upset people me I would say that if you wanted to end the protest about
Police brutality one of the worst ways to go about it would be with
Police brutality it tends to make the protesters argument become a lot more
It's hard to disagree with
Right it should be a good idea
Yeah so you and it just so happens that the other day
For the situation that gave Alex the exact thing that you needed
In order to attempt
To invalidate a lot of this stuff
Nashville news
Walden security
Store
Black
I was very sad
Disgusting
Video repeatedly throughout the show
Incredible
That is a problem
We're all mad at the same tragedy
Right that's an issue
I don't want anybody
Right and Beyond this is not so much
Applicable to our conversation
What's going on
I absolutely don't that I have any
Feelings of support for anybody who would do something like that
Nevermore fine for somebody to be murder
It's not fine and it's definitely not more fine for somebody else
Plenty of coverage about this
People bring this up weather peon
On Twitter or at least a few news stories about this
This guy David Dorn
No and I don't think anybody who believes in sports
What's going on in protest I don't think anybody
Is necessarily afraid of looking at this and saying yeah those those people who were looting pawnshop are
It's like an awful man is an awful thing to do.
In line with
What time we sporting with us
Is it going for
But I do think that Alex incidentally can't do the reverse
He can't look at the inside
To the police brutality against peaceful protesters
And discuss that is like as if it's not happening at all
Cases of the police killing people which it happened
Sense
Restaurateur
It's the he can't talk about go so he ignores those
Where is I don't think the people are ignoring
Mr Dornan the same way that they are
It's just disgusting to see him exploit that's the way he does
He plays it repeatedly like God no one cares about this guy
Just it's it's just f***** up
So Alex
He has the credentials of
Noble Alex Jones gas tonight is that a video of him got popular
That's all you need do you need the video of him yelling at a city council.
Little more.
Glamorgan
He's going to be
Welcome
Trailer
Make him so bad
Real mr. what
Doesn't respect
Video
Suck my dick and choke on it
He got his got out
Franklin
It just did to your s***
It's a little too close to Patton Oswalt yelling at Leslie Knope that's the problem
And not nearly as amusing
So Alex is going to interview this guy whose name is Tom special up because of this video of him is making the rounds and right-wing
Circles it's just him yelling at a city council meeting about how the Communists are taking over as all the Democrats
Resisted arrest
How do you sprain Jess candidates running for office is probably at
He thinks that Infowars is going to help him win the primaries
And this strategy up till this point has not been a good one I think it's 0% batting average
The last Iraq
No no no
I think that people like
Deanna Lorraine yeah those are Naomi I almost forgot her name already forgot
You're the only person who would
No she lost her primary when she was going to unseat Nancy Pelosi
Really very close really
Whatever is inside
Enrique tarrio dropped
I can't I can't think of anybody who's been on Infowars
Who has had a successful run in the primary
Fine
We got one
What is a big knot on your bed
Well he hasn't come back
EXO
We got some
Good guys
Becky's going to win
Alex is going to get to that interview in a little bit but yesterday
Stream to the audience that we're basically out of town
There's no time
Wish we had more time
We don't have more time
They're going to go For Broke
Stop
Kuwait from prep in DC and fear
Try to make the main move
Running
Operational
Retired generals
Hayden Clapper
Obama daughter
You're never going to get away with this
Prison School
Show me how full of s*** Alex is going to make me realize they like this is a game
Yeah if you've been preparing for this for 20 years and this was the globalist big move and the Patriots are running out of time
Time he be saying it's time to start shooting nothing left
I'd like
This move doesn't like the Patriots
Doesn't work
Game is over
Big continuing of doing a show like Alex does in the middle of what's presumably the big one
Feels like it's just another publicity stunt for him
Because he's holding back in the same way he always does
Fully committed quote-unquote patriot who was looking to save the Republic
Wouldn't do that
If time was running out
This is all just an act for Alex and it's pretty gross
Be out in the streets
No more party
He says with a couple times I think he might be trying to Brandon ooshirts party's over
Decide what you'll be free or slave
What side you're on
June 3rd Wednesday transmission
Pause the unrest
I got to call for his resignation or removal
Fifth
Is coming next
You can set your watch by
This is again why this is such a game he's been saying they're right about to do the 25th Amendment for
Years now this is just
Bland
It's so boring I just want bring back polonium poisoning sure something good
Give me a give me
Richmond style they're going to break into the White House pull them out to the f****** ledge and see if everybody wants to chop his head off
Play real quick stuff
Dive deep into the they put a hundred bombs at construction sites
Keep going with that white stuff
Covered this territory over and over and over again even wrong every time
Wait I wouldn't set
Alex
Trump has come out and said that antifa should be a
Terrorist organization
And actually there's some rest
Sprite plant
Cantera stuff Alex's like this
The news
Winger's
Wingers are posing
Looters
There's no looters there's no antifa
Yeah we all meet at the Eagles Lodge
The publican
So dumb dumb
Antonio news
Staind
People he knows
Fairy of the mobster
Because there was
Tweets flying around about Alex and Enforcer
Around the same time promoting a video of his son beating up a guy at a 7-Eleven
So it's kind of an easy mistake for someone to make I don't know
This is your fault Alex desk
Confusion is your fault
Earned that can
But again this is a good demonstration of why you never want to give Alex these sorts of
Abilities to bring these things up as if
They are
Proof that everyone lies about
Every single occasion
So it's hard to say exactly to what extent protests have been infiltrated by Bad actors from the white nationalist
Accelerationist
Community or the Boogaloo types but it's definitely not
Not at all
I don't know
How you can quantify it or
To what extent
You would
The address I just don't know how you'll be able to
Yeah it's
It seems like
There's a likelihood of some it is it is a
Tossed around concept people every time I see a protest there's at least
The kkk's been spotted there
Avoid app
Play for the most part
It happened but to the point where it's really
I don't know what I mean
Yeah and m.j. yeah I think there's a normal human impulse
You saw it with Alex's seapak
Courtney eats with Enrique tarrio
Hey there's infiltrators in this route every does that
And so
I do I do think
But I know there is at least
One example I can point to clear as day
But it would be responsible for me to definitively say if one act of property damage
Another is being done by one group or another
Do not even going to try and attempt to thread that needle don't know what's going on
Is prove Alex wrong
About his assertion
That there are no right-wing people infiltrating and pretending to be antifa
And I can do that based on Alex's own report
On May 31st Alex reported on a particularly menacing statements
That was said to be coming from antifa
Put out on their Twitter
Tonight's the night
My comrades
Saf
Remove
Hilarious
White
When we discussed this our response was that it was pretty obviously that was a fake Twitter account
Determined
Bitey white nationalist group
American identity movement
Formerly known as identity evropa who could have guessed that
Pretty
Very simple as there was Maude
They might as well have had a neon sign flashing we're lying to
This is a very common right-wing extremist
Fake antifa accounts on social media
Which make left-wing protest look bad
They do this a lot because it's super effective
In the past days there has been so much conversation and hand-wringing
For showing up to your white man house and killing you and your family
It's a tool of delegitimization
We're by the right-wing socopa demonize the larger point of the protests
Imaginary organization that'll scare off the middle-of-the-road folks
It's more or less an attempt
The pool support in their direction from the center by scaring it away from the other side
Alex played right into this game and actually use an active participant and enabling a white nationalist group to infiltrate the protest
For him to say it's not happening is
But as we also seen that clip the downside of the accusation Betty bar in the matter
Nadia settings back pocket as an example of how the media lies he can deploy didn't
Dances like this
You can't possibly believe that their right-wing
Extremist infiltrating left-leaning protest
You're the media says that there are
Please that I burn that mattress
So nothing is real
That's the danger that you can begin to see it
So now we get to Tom speziale
Anyway he says that
He says it Infowars is great
Which might hurt him in the campaign
Because of him
Because
Information
Family
Challenges
The so-called conservatives
Machine
Mentalities like this because
Tom's right there when he says that they do is they challenged these
These narratives
I just argue that they do
General
There is a I mean yes absolutely there are many ways to
To challenge something
Is the other thing I was going through my mind.
Not going to like those cues
Tom gives me every reason to not like him by saying that if you like
A certain person you'll like him which means I would like him
Jim Jordan
To you
Go out
Across the swamp monster
I'm sure you will
So yeah I got the father Son and the Holy Ghost right there perhaps
Yeah you got the guy who yells at city council meeting right corrupt lunatic real estate
College coach
Abusing tons of students
I'm outside
So Alex has his guy on and it's clearly some kind of a situation where like Alex saw this video
It was like man that's getting some attention I got to get this guy on this guy's run
For Congress and he's like I got a boost my profile somehow set myself away from the pack of the
These losers been a Republican primary that Alex is good
Play I don't give a s***
Find your way onto Sinclair buddy that'll give you a lot better probably
So Alex has another person coming up on the show here on the 3rd
Does have its a primary Bonanza
He's going through here another person is running
Tough cookie
Is she
She does support
Organization
But you does
Laura Loomer is running for office in the 21st district in Florida and
She does have a chance at
Then he'll be surprised Republican primaries on August 18th
And even though she is raising a good bit of money for her campaign she's an embarrassing disaster and I find it very hard to
Imagine that any significant number of people would vote for
I think we're going to steal our computers at the
What are the main problems for a campaign is that she's already made a bunch of really good attack ads on herself
Like every time he's been on Infowars
Twitter
Anyone running
For an election
A wannabe at least six candidates in the Republican primary
Who has a long history and government
Pringles in the Florida house from 1986 to 1992 then again from 1994 to 2000
Time to choose elected mayor of West Palm Beach in 2003 and served until 2011
At which point she ran for the US House where she has been since 2013
Frank was a strong track record of electoral competence whereas
Just really has a resume full of week shift and self-defeating publicity stunts
Mixed in with disgraceful islamophobia
Sitting to the children lock
You're so inexplicably to adore
And let's not forget
Laura Loomer was the co-star with Jacob Wohl
Stupid fake documentary where they where the ilham Omar was married to her brother
Like she is a disaster
216 election this District went for Hillary by a margin of 59% to 39%
Laura Loomer doing is all for attention if I had to guess to try and get back on Twitter
Yeah yeah give me a exemption for being a candidate for some
This very seriously
I was going to play later whenever I would look like a real dick
Berthelot and I are already on the show
Pictures where Mar-A-Lago is
That's where Trump vote by mail
Motor belt mail
Voter fraud so she's like when I get elected
Trump will be one of my constituents
Iowa
The president I am a big fan of delusions of grandeur
So Alex and the snakes flip discusses how like
He doesn't want to please stay
Everybody likes
What's a police state police state
Borders control.
What
Boils my blood will head
Herein
You're so crazy I decided to extend the big sale we've had
Jer
Gap
Across-the-board
Torrid.com
Decided
Take a loss of everything
This is just like
We can sell stuff now we probably can't
In three weeks no evil will not be as scared
Yeah let's use it
So good good good stuff Alex I'm proud of you
Whatever
Whenever Alex says that he's Mister anti-police state
I love that
Think of who's that who's mr. Steal Your Girl
Who's that guy
It wasn't that I liked it
Rod Rosenstein testifies
Was really taking him to the woodshed
What has Ted Cruz ever done anything
Grabber tool
Oh
Howdy Doody doll
This is the last
Justice
Was going after a
3-star General
The incoming
They already said they're going to dismiss
The case against
Predicate for all of this
Is the Logan Act
What you know
Perfectly well
Is Imran Khan
Constitutional law that is never been prosecuted
History of the Department of
He should have been laugh
Any response
If someone is sick
Where can I go
Security advisor
For violating the Logan Act
Which says
Consistent
See you today right now
Violating Logan Act
Suncoast
So who cares
Out of the room and why didn't you get
Answers on this
Why did you let the
Isle of partisan
Why
Consume the country
Appreciate
Cuz he's a criminal
He's got get away with way which person in this case
Really regular thing for propagandists like
You can see through this
Prism health hazard facilitated by people like Ted Cruz government
Wasn't asking Rod Rosenstein a serious question on that cliff
And you're shooting off a ton of ridiculous right-wing talking
This was done because Cruz knew that it would be red meat for the right-wing media sphere
It would take some kind of a creature of the deep state
However in the context of a
Congressional hearing does get to respond
Things like this and he did
You could hear them starting to respond right before Alex cut it off
Good for propaganda so someone like Alex just cuts the clip right there before Rod Road
Steve has a chance to speak
This accomplishes presenting Cruz's words is the only reality of the hearing
He's framing of the situation is the only one that's real and by cutting off Rosenstein's answer you make it appear that he didn't have a
Sponsor a rebuttal
In reality Rosenstein side
With regard to
The plan to take that particular issue senator
My understanding at the time that I arrived was the General Flynn had lied to the vice president
And that I believe was the primary issue that was under investigation
Oh that's seems really
Right
In the context of the larger hearing Cruz's words look like a petulant Outburst that means nothing and it's clearly a performance
But if you isolate the comments and deprive them of any of that context
You can make him appear to be some kind of a meaningful Brave we're not going to take it kind of thing
And it's not it's just a child throwing a tantrum it's kind of amazing that on this
Very same episode
He makes Ted Cruz looking
Exactly like
Especially
Or whatever it is like that literally open
Yeah okay I hate
But that literally like I'm already over my time
F*** off your dust you're just saying dumb nuts
Yeah stop it
You're stupid.
Kabuki theater
For a long time Alex is really in support of Donald Trump and his family and everybody
God dang
Things have changed
Alex is already said that he doesn't like Jared Kushner cuz Tucker Carlson sets bad things about him and Alex Azar
Yep
Turns out this is spread
It's no longer Just Jared and Ivanka
People that know
What's going on and they literally make fun of
Just like me
Yeah no s***
Flaming liberals
Can't no s***
Who called
Which building
Chinese Donuts
Problem
Yeah
Trump's daughter
Space aliens
Money
Spoiled rotten
We have a telescope
Get into politics
Walk-around
Yeah it guess what
What the only reason they have anything to do with White House is because of the guy you love so much
So
He's pointing the finger at Ivanka about her multi-generational money
A generation dad
It was a Multiverse subtracted generationals he's complaining about
Children of next-generation money who get into politics
Is that exactly the definition of Donald Trump insane
Weird blue-collar background
F****** nuts
Shut up
God
I love the idea
They got to go about this shouldn't be involved
Got there different ways really stupid still trying to
Find some way to preserve
Like Trump is seriously actually like does a good job but he put his daughter in some kind of a weird position
Vision that she had no business being at because she's related to him turns out
Turns out
Fullmetal Alchemist you guys ever heard Alex bring up Eric
What would you maybe that means Eric
Alex's Source never know Alex admitted that he was
Cernovich is sort of Alex
That might be why you never
Does on the show anymore
I wonder if that's
Okay
I mean I suppose burning your sources probably a pretty legitimate reason
Cernovich could very well have been on an episode that I didn't see
Where is it
Is there a lot
Jared and Ivanka
Good. No longer Maga
The movement has turned
Is the most
Thin-skinned
Group
Elitist wannabe
Custer is just one of them
About the present
Christiana Mall
They all are hedging their bets
Can you imagine how sad it would be if there was like
Some
Obama a put Malia into a official position at the White House
Obama supporter radio show
Listen I love President Obama butt
Malia is a problem she is a conservative hiding in the administration
Take a Bow
That idea of Malia Obama
Well we got a hedge our bets nobody's going to take my dad out
Fight with it and let's let's explore that a tiny bit more
Idea that Jared Kushner or Ivanka would think they have a
They're going to survive they're going to be in the New York Times next year
Sing their way through this if you can help us if you can publish some b******* the
W said without lighting them on fire first
Fine as long as going to have an opinion people listen
There is a big difference between having a position that could affect policy decisions
No chance that either of them will be anywhere near any kind of the power that they are now without
Are you running for mayor of New York
You probably would remedies lose
The idea that they're like
Yeah Biden's going to keep pushing around a special Envoy
Non-partisan there you got to work for multiple Administration comes inside
Cancel call
Cuz he's got a great track record this
And how this is so stupid
Just take a second look at the kind of b*******
He just says those things
Now it's now it's just
F****** Arch Democrats
And I couldn't her vice president
Going to happen
So there's a war on religion early cuz only June
Until the end of the year the war on Christmas
Happens every year the skirmishes Breakout
For Christianity
Search for photo op
So that broke out of War on religion
Country
No you're right this is Laura Loomer said there will be right back
I completely forgot that I said that
Zero respect for her and she kind of just makes me sad you have zero respect
Fionna cuz I respect all people as human
Respect people's rights
Yeah and it's just a bummer generally to see what you bring to the
The table in terms of propaganda
I want to do dresses Point really quick ship
People are really offended by Trump holding up that bible the way that she's pretending they are
Some people are probably offended by how crass a publicity stunt he was trying to pull off
And apparently he's trying to hide his authoritarian Ambitions behind religion
Offended
We're so because
How that photo op happen
It's been widely reported both by people who were there and is out by Outlets like the New York time
But in order to stand in front of st. John's Episcopal Church and give his dumb speech
Peaceful protesters dispersed with use of rubber bullets
Pure Gas in Perkasie
Renee
These were not people breaking into buildings and looting
They were peacefully assemble because the Optics of trump going to the church and
President acted State violence on them to get to believe so he can look strong
And undo the damage to his ego that have come from the news stories about him hiding in a bunker
This is what people are most offended by
And that includes Rev gini gerbasi
Who used to be a minister
St. John's Episcopal Church
Describe Trump's actions as a sacrilege for All Peoples of all face face that are grounded and peaceful
Honest and loving compassion reconciliation
Wholeness healing forgiveness Peace Love
Compassion
Gervasi was there at the church when the police disbanded the people gathered there
Response to what you saw was quote
When I realized the people have been hurt and terrified for a political stunt
I like offended hardly begins to describe how I feel
Also
Reverend Mariann budde
The episcopal episcopal Bishop of Washington
The DC was not so happy about this.
She told CNN's let me be clear the president just use the Bible the most sacred text of the
Christian tradition
And one of the churches of my diocese without permission
As a backdrop for a message antithetical to the teachings of Jesus
She also told the Washington Post
I am the bishop of the Episcopal Diocese of Washington and was not given even a courtesy call
That would be clearing that they would be clearing the area with tear gas so they could use one of our churches
As a prop
No one's offended by just somebody being religious or at least very few people are
What people get kind of pissed off about is when people use religion as a shield to justify their incredibly evil Behavior
Uber knows that
She's pretending not to understand because it Riles her base up when she acts like people just hate Trump cuz he held a Bible
And riling the bass up and getting people all worked up is what she gets paid to do
You've everybody forgets the the verse at the end of Luke
Do you think that they move that giant boulder out of his way you can't move a boulder out of that way they're the boulder was too
So what happened Jesus started firing some bullets into the into the into the
In order to kind of softened up then he moved it using his superpowers and then he tear gases way out of there
All the Romans died he met with his f****** followers they created Christianity
Next thing you know Trump
If you were a right-wing already told Alex that he would probably
Yeah that's probably true that's got to say it but
Alex
News going on
And that is that
Alex's read a Robert Kennedy article
That are being tested for covid
You got a interesting take
Infowars.
You know
Another Network
Ashanti Southside on Hayden's television
So it's interesting story of Robert Kennedy Jr
Just repeating
This is basically
Because it hurts the agenda of the vaccine pusher
That's weird and it's also not true
This guy eating Hayden had a story written about his reaction to the vaccine in Staten ooze back on May
Apparently he did get sick after getting the vaccine
According to his story
12 hours after receiving his second dose he developed a fever of more than 130 degrees
Stop medical attention and after being released from urgent care facility fainted in his home
You recovered within a day
So it was bad but not nearly the level of
Make the sound way way worse
Hayden said that he felt more sick than he has ever felt
But quote you was never afraid for his long-term health
He also went on to say quote I don't regret the decision to enroll in this study
What's really tragic is that when Hayden was discussing his decision to go public about his adverse reaction
You explicitly said quote
I hope it doesn't
Fuel any sort of General antagonism towards vaccines even this vaccine
Unfortunately that's exactly what happened just rewrote that Yakety Sax started crying
People like Robert chambless hacks
For that 100,000 most Deb they've ever been in their life
What's an interesting headline
So Alex predict that he's going to disappear and no one's going to talk about him anymore because he's no longer useful as a
Vaccine
Care Share but more importantly Alex
Just you just
Pete's
Inaccuracies
From
This Robert report
It's important to recognize what's going on here
He was among the 15 ball
20%
Hospital
You like it
Alex can't even remember it's moderna
So this is a perfect example of how Alex is Audience by never actually checking into any of the information
He and accurately as decided to Robert Kennedy is a trustworthy source so he just takes anything he says is accurate which is a bad
Hear Kennedy is talking about a moderna press release and asserting the three out of the 15 people in the highest dose cohort in this
Study had severe reaction
But if you actually read the press release here's what it's
MRNA 1273 was generally safe and well-tolerated with
Consistent
With that scene in Prior moderna infectious
Disease vaccine clinical studies
The incidence of a grade 3 adverse event in the 25 to 100 dose cohorts
Was a single participant in the 100 group
Around the injection site
Today the most notable Adverse Events were seen in the 250 dose level
Comprising three participants with grade three systemic symptoms
Only following the second dose
Adverse Events have been transient and self resolving
No grade for Adverse Events or serious Adverse Events have been reported
Alex wants to tell the story 23 out of 15 people in this trial were paralyzed
Who is employer
But the reality is that there
Were three participants who had reactions
Everything's like fever or dizziness with the loss of appetite
This is important in noteworthy
Because it helps to researchers better understand an optimal dose range
But it's not the sort of thing that's so severe that it ruins trials
For the vaccine being study
More than anything else that gives more information which is ultimately a positive thing
Particularly because all those adverse reactions were quote
Self resolving
Alex has no idea about any of the stories he's telling on his show
You just has a bunch of extremist sources that he picks headlines from and then he passes along as factual
If you were forced to he couldn't explain anything about this moderna study or press release
His knowledge literally starts and ends with the word cities cold reading
From Robert Kennedy's blog
And not just that he believes moderna means mother
In Spanish
It's true
Which is correct that's what I looked into that
Turns out there's a secret form of Spanish
Secrets created
The real Spanish
Are 33rd degree Mason
So
Redwood on East 3rd
It's not
No not too much
Show me jump into the forest and he starts the show
It is the 31st anniversary of
When
Pro-democracy demonstrators
Run over by Auburn
Realtor
When the military comes in
Holy s*** you moron
Shepherd University
So there's some real comedy
At that time
The image of the protests in Tiananmen Square is really all Alex knows about the entire piece of history and he's just filled in the rest with
What do you want the story to be
You want some protesters to be America lovers and all this because it's an easy peeling story to tell us
Complicated
The movement that was a part of this is a part of grew out of student unrest in Chinese college campuses beginning in 1986
They had a diverse set of priorities so getting into all that here would be a bit much to explain right now
Things really intensified after the death of
Huyao Bang
A high-level politicians as a reformer
He died on April 15th 1989 and at that point protest became more serious
Approximately a week later rioting and looting
Various cities in China which led to the politburo feeling the need to escalate their response
The student movie
On April 26th
The people's daily released an editorial with the headline quotes
It's necessary to take a clear-cut stand against disturbances
This is more or less a historical equivalent to Tom Cotton
Recent op-ed in the New York Times title quote send in the troops
Which nation must restore order
The military stands for
Is history protesters continued to organize a demonstrate even launching a hunger strike in mid-may
The state responded by declaring martial law and sending in military against the
Particularly the students occupying Tiananmen Square
This is all important context that led up to the iconic image of a man standing in front of a tank
These things that preceded the standoff can't be ignored when discussing the protest because of soda prizes
The real
When you look at the events that led to Tiananmen Square it's
It's easy to see how Alex would be calling for the deaths of the students
Breaking out associated with their movement
They were calling for an upheaval of the status quo
The stated made clear their argument for using Force against them
Many of these details you can draw a direct parallels to the current situation in our country and you see what side Alex is on
Now like 121 direct Paris
See Alex trying to take that Legacy
And pretend
Some kind of belief that he has that he wouldn't be entirely in favor of crushing the
The other two
The protest every conservative
Even contain if you say Martin Luther King Junior's name in your conservative you should be slapped in the face like it's
Pathetic how dare you
So Alex
To make things even worse like
Alex brings Tom Cotton
IPad you seem fine with
Talkin about
You're being
Official martial law
What
Pokemon order
Trump office lights
Okay
Yes
Dcd's rationalization
Not a good idea
I don't know why that came to his mind.
Not at all
Complaining about
CNN wants white children
To be sad about being white or something
I think there's a little bit more nuanced to what the argument is but
CNN
Children
Low self-esteem
Orders
Border
For the original sin
The new religion the priesthood
Country
Police
Has anybody's premise
Human sacrifice
The field goal from the 20-yard line
Out here
All police
What the f*** is that
First player
20 yard line kick a field goal
Toss it out there alright Alex okay
You're making sense
Also I tried to find instances of the police killing white children with toy guns I couldn't find any
All the time
Alex's is way out of line here
Which is not surprising
Aziz big old right
Bellingcat has recently had a nice sub breakdown of that whole situation
If you want to learn more about that
If you don't want to learn more about what they're up to
Don't worry they're fake
Who is Justin
Velasquez just use me
We found it
The anti-balaka store us things
BFDI
Victorious luxury Georgia
That is outrageous
Run
We know the organization
Centrelink
A civil unrest and martial law
By Obama
Brennan
Your fake ass porch and documents, logout of your relationship
Presenting it as like such of the like the most concrete solid thing ever
Something mentally doesn't exist
For you people stop it
They're just not they're not real
The command-and-control structure run by Alexander Soros and George
Soros
That's not good I noticed something interesting actually number
Really interesting things
The first is it Billy Weaver doesn't come back and break her big story
Tons of documents
That doesn't happen interesting James O'Keefe put out a new piece of s***
Talk about that either
I hope I hope everybody agrees to just not talk about it the Acme Brick narrative is gone love it
That hasn't popped the other one yeah
I got Devon's tweeted about our coverage
Alex's theory that George Floyd
I was mixed up with the cop game
Watters on Fox News repeating some of these ideas
Narrative is also Alex
Isn't pushing back any further because it's made its way to where it needs to go it's made it
Way through the pipeline without giving it access to farm
Then would have seen otherwise
I find that really interesting these absences and terms of like what he is
What he's doing
Conspicuous very strange the Acme Brick one in particular I think maybe he does realize like
I can't prove is that all that was a weird to an odd person
Person
S***
Everytime I start trying to be a weirdo I find out I'm using these weirdos
And it I think it is entirely possible that like
You know
That sort of talk
Could lead to violence against
Acme employees
Well yeah that's fair because if you'd believe me brick
Is putting these bricks around and cause all this trouble
If you could see somebody who's unhinged and just believes it
Like
Seeing somebody who works for Acme rigging like you were trying to start a revolutionary war by 20
Lawyer being like
You can't you can't do that
You can't because if you get pressed on it all you can do the back that up and point to the stunad video
Hurt
You are fuc
Yeah
I think maybe that
That might have been
She's too busy working on the pulling a computer chip out of a homeless person
What's a season finale dad
So also another thing that happened is that
Matt. He came out and said that Trump is a threat to the Constitution
Good work assholes
F*** him
Pic of former Trump
Blanc de Blanc f*** off you're not wrong to feel that way
Day late dollar short
You know to the trolling game
A high-level General saying this stuff might be worth something
We'll talk a****** barely even
Address the story
Coming out
Even Alex can see through this b*******
We Bennett
Absolutely
Was that Napa
Good rebuttal
Yes I don't know
Malaysian for butt
I don't know if that's the case but yeah Alex going to just invalidate his comment with that and then talk about
Slavery
No
So in the next clip
This is really funny
William Barr
Attorney general Barr
Speech that Alex realized you'd have to cover live
And a big part of that was Alex thinking that he's going to talk about antifa
He doesn't really get to that at the beginning of the speech at all and Alex gets
Super bored because we cannot allow people
Lease to behave in the ways that led to George Floyd
And Alex like this
Is not working for me now so here's what he does
That sounds right
Nothing less
Is expected
Leading
Can I drown robots
What are we doing X-Men
Watch watch
Are the Sentinels coming is that what's going on
Commercial
Talking about there's a difference between protesters
And Alex
Custom-made Queer as Bill Barr is talking
That even
The peaceful protesters
Alex
Exercising
Amendment right
There's no real difference he thinks that anybody who's doing anything hate America so whatever
Beyond
So are we at the end of Bill bars
Very frustrated for
Because he's not getting what he wants
Which is Bill Barr being like I'm going to arrest George Soros
Tonight
We are going to deal with
With a Criminal
Those two are involved
Hayden
Okay well the Coppola George Soros
Obama
General
Leadership
Good morning
Needless to say any
I can't handle just turned off
Won't they kill reimagined anime
Is pretty mad about that
Frustrating
Told yourself that was what was going to happen
True
So in the next wave Alex's get them to one of his standard predict
Can games whenever retentions get really high in the country
You'll see Alex
Predict false Flags
What are the functions that this serves on sublevel Alex
One of these right-wing groups one of these
F****** dudes
All my buddies know how to build bombs just going to go
Crazy on some level knows there's a decent chance of someone to blow something
Something
So he's building that
Assassinated presidents
Going to do it
Obama's load up a fuel truck
Roundup on
Hotel room right now
Brainwash Looney tuners
Everywhere ready to go
There's no way to stop
Leadership
Which is
Everything
Because the globalist are going to break your back
Really trying to talk quick going out to break their
Yeah like that's so boring
Imagine right-wing gun nuts
Hey we're here
To protect you so if any fake white nationalist come here with giant machine gun
We're going to kill those guys doesn't seem likely
I just
I am so
This stuff is like
Is it's farcical
In-N-Out Things Are
You know I don't know things are changing but there is a mood
In the world that
Tends toward the possibility of a different
Right there's talk
I've seen some people wanting to
Dismantle Police Department
Floatin around dismantling police departments and rebuilding something that serves people better than what we have now
Now it only took a few hundred
Great but there is a very
This wouldn't be possible without people coming out into the streets and the
The conversations that this provokes
AMV ideas
We word
Lose our ability to
Dream in such a
Identity in his right wing
S*** that huge be like okay they're going to be coming up
Like he does every single time
Like he's treating this like any other circumstance that is ever happened throughout his career
As opposed to
I don't know something that has the potential to be something far more
I would rather this country burn to the ground then share my spaces equals with non-white
That's what he might as well
Where you coming from
So Alice is another Gaston
Quite a while
Sucks and he's not running for office
I'm really excited to have hotep Jesus whether the balance
The hour
Social media
Real name Brian
Hotep Jesus is a real piece of s***
That's a coffee from Starbucks as reparation
Videos of these employees are such a white Cox that they've just given
Free coffee
As someone who used to manage a Starbucks I can tell you that employees are trained to give free coffee to people
I know that a lot of coffee is just going to get waste
Did anyway
Any amount of Goodwill they could be gained by giving
Coffee to people in need is far more valuable then demanding payment
At our store we have some people experiencing homelessness who would come in pretty much every day we give them coffee you say hi chat with them
A little bit
Never charge them
This dude's video was based on faulty premise which is used to make a pseudo racist point so congrats
You guys should really consider
Calling in the cops to really escalate that situation
You know that idea of giving somebody a free cup of coffee
That leads to socialism Dan
That is socialist that's why we need an overwhelming military police present
To go in there and make sure that that
-4 Cent cup of coffee Estates
I mean the reason for his stunts in the first place was those two
Boxer
And they're like
Set up a video of Starbucks is racist I want my coffee
Yeah whatever is everything is faulty and all of it is just counterproductive
An article in The Daily Beast
Holocaust denier was created truth
He released a video earlier that year he said quote alright isn't afraid to call out the Jews and their implications in the destruction
The black community in America
It's just the truth you can't call me anti-semitic if it's
The truth
You don't want to be a guess
Explicitly white nationalist Outlet red
Gave a message to the almost certainly not existent black audiences that program
Do not like you they hate you they think your s***
He was a promoter V pizzagate conspiracy theory eyes that eating soy makes people gay
Despite being an anti-semitic conspiracy pushing idiot hosted by people like Joe Rogan
Laura Ingraham
Men turning point USA
Hotep Jesus was on Joe Rogan show
What
I'm guessing that I returned his calls anymore
Some
Annie just
Please give me a black person to pretend that what I say isn't insane
I think that this is like
Also like hotep Jesus is available
Because it was awhile back that right
Call Alex Jones
Infowars
A few media Outlets
Media Outlets to reach out to me
10 frame
Yes less
Let's start off by pointing out that no one wants to talk to me
Start off by saying good-bye voice is not
Censored there's no other explanation they are trying to silence me
Let me start off by saying I'm glad you bought my book because I have sold literally 02
Talking about how I feel
Don't give money to Black lives matter right there somewhere battery
You can give your money
She said her friend
Donation
Black lives matter
Is going to go towards the destruction
There's only one group
In fact
All about
You keep saying black lives matter what you need to know is black life matter
MetLife
Is me
Oh boy
Weather
Are we going to talk in here about something that is
The reasonable
Concern I guess what is being used
Unreasonably
And that is a fact that these are large Gatherings of people and they're happening while there is still a concern about
Covid-19
And the weaponized this idea a bit
What
Social distancing
The social distance
I wish that were true
Top scientists and governments are come outside with all basic and make lights
Phase always know there's some
Jordan honestly I can see in your face exactly what your response is going to be and do for it
It's always going to be a messed up video of making the point
Dying but making this way
Thank you Alex male the problem
But beyond that there's a baseline misunderstanding
It's still pretty unsafe for people to be out protesting in these big group
But I just generally speaking while they're still covid-19
Steps
Sunstate apart is much
But the reality is that there's probably no way to fully social distancing protest like this
And that there is a risk of people protesting that they have except
Yeah because they believe that the underlying cause of the protests
The movement Airport
Are more important
And
Happy
Agree
I'd like to take a moment to compare these things to the stay-at-home order protesters that we're Gathering
I like last month so I can illustrate why this isn't analogous at all
These protests are built on a foundation of a Cause
In the case of the current protests it's police murdering people at least not facing consequences when they do so
As the protests have been going on there's been a rash of police brutality directed towards the testers
The scope of
Complaints
Which makes sense
Stay-at-home protests cause was their ability to shop and go get haircuts
They weren't rallying for the right to go back to work they were rounding to send
Others back to work so they wouldn't be as inconvenience to slightly as they had been
And felt they were at that moment
I can understand them feeling intensely about that but I also really don't agree that it's a very strong
Point
These two complaints matters
Yaki protesting right now is risk
So for people to commit to doing it's important they have a firm conviction that a meaningful cause
From my position to current protesters do have that
Whereas the folks from a month ago
I meant beyond that
You have to consider the safety measure
In the case of the protesters from month or so back there was a high level of virus denialism among them disregard
Idea that there could be a problem
In the current case that's not that's not so
People wearing masks
People have been very vocal about how people who feel sick should stay home
I've seen a number of people imploring everybody who went to go protest to get tested
It's a quarantine afterwards and like I mentioned our friend SNL cast member Chris red organized the GoFundMe
Throughout these protesters get to pay hospital bills they come down with covid-19
At the point this recording it's raised over $240,000 which will go a long way towards making sure
And people who attend these rallies or able to get tested
And thereby know what actions to take if they need to firmly Courant
What have you
Large group of people coming together like this for an important cause is not necessarily terribly dangerous thing
Provided the people handle it responsibly
We'll see how that plays out but the people who are involved in this protest
Reminder
There's a heavy streak of mutual Aid that runs through it and that extends each other
Keep each other safe so I don't foresee
The being as much of a
Problem as some other
Large Gatherings could be but it's it it would be foolish to
Pretend but it's not a risk now it's absolutely
And it's it's
Really a bummer
That it is or maybe it's actually Nessa
Maybe the only reason that we can
Can really finally
F******
Do this s***
Is because we have been sold
Trapped and so
Held hostage by the coronavirus in
Everything is been exposed
Snow desk
Maybe I don't know if I don't I'm so awful that it uses coinciding with the f******
I don't know
I just don't to
I felt
This cancer
Really worried about the possibility that there could be a sharp increase in cases
That would be unfortunate
You know what I was thinking is the words of that dumb f*** lieutenant governor where he's like people if the old people are will
Willing to die for the economy
And in this situation
A people are willing to die for the possibility
That's finally having some sort of social Jay
People are willing to die as we've seen on a daily nightly basis
People are either under threat or they have been murdered
This is too big
To say no
You know
Sure
Misunderstandings
Coming from
But I disagree
Using the
Orally
I've been this next clip though we find something that I just think it's
Is more intentional and his misinformation
Is he
Lucy won this year
Just Happening Now
Election year
Cycles
So Google Transit and interesting tool
It's also one that's super easy to misuse
Like how hotep Jesus is right now
If you go and look at the trends for the term black lives matter you'll see a spike currently and wanted 2016 which he's asserting
Is because it's an election year
But the fun assumption to make but this biking 2016 happened on the week of July 10th
What does just after Alton Sterling and philando Castillo were murdered by the police
It's also right after that sniper in Dallas shot at the police killing five
Good reason
There's also spike in August 2015 that wasn't an election year had to do with the aftermath of the Charleston
Also there's a very different dataset you can find if you search for black lives matter all one word
So I've no idea
This is an example of him taking some numbers and then writing a story about them it's based on nothing
Conspiracy thinking run wild and basically doesn't mean anything
You can do that with Google
It's really easy to try and
Come up with an argument based on
Website
Traffic and search
Terms
And if you don't do it responsibly and look for
Context was like okay there's a lot of people interested in this thing at this point why is that the case
If you don't engage in that level of context
Trying to mislead people
Pure
And it's it's such that if you if you do
The people listening to Infowars alike holyshit how do you even
Find Google Trends in firm
You know like it sounds like you're at
Check this is Wizardry
There's a lot of stuff going on in qanon circles right now
And such
Believe that
September
Yes
September 9th
Aaliyah ride
Yeah
So
I want to say
The significant date
White Sox
Yeah yeah.
Look at this. I think something else happened
Oh wait
December 11th
You see how they
Put that date
Right under something that are allowed in the disguise thing I see how you put that date
Meaningless
Nothing nothing is more obvious than 19 years after September 11th
That's that's the golden hour for them
Find information about Hillary having to testify
The Buzz
Links to anything
Sure
I found another blog called Josh WHO news
Who's being brought by Judicial Watch
This article doesn't say the Clinton has to testify it's just that the case of currently adjourned until
Templar Knight
Story about this
CNBC March 2nd
This kind of
O'Reilly's
Apparently what happened is the Court ruled that Hillary has to testify in a deposition related to this lawsuit about
It seems like what happened is that Hillary appealed that decision in the appeals court which is currently adjourn
Pick up the case on September 9th
Can't find any reliable evidence that says that she's supposed to testify on that day
But here we are we see how these guys
Record on this stuff
Speculation
You're mongering any Logan 9/11
Impressively stupid
Good stuff just all around Hillary was pretty short is like
Come the f*** on you know these guys
Stop it
Exactly
So Alex plays that video of hotep Jesus going to Starbucks
You know nobody wants to come here the new stuff everybody wants to hear the hits
Really
Basically on
Undercuts the entire point of video
Freak out
Starbucks employees are trained to give people free coffee
Things to do
That datapoint really doesn't prove my earlier the kind of tends to indicate
Just wanted you to go away
Maybe
Maybe that's part of the training
Hotep Jesus is talking about how they're all out-of-towners in mini
Minneapolis
He's not updated his story yet
Still working on Old talking
Governor said in Minneapolis
95% of the people that were arrested were from out of town
Did not get the update on that story
The press conferences that had to be walked back
I'm sure that
These bail funds that are going around that are largely
Her folks were protesting by the police there are tons and tons of those people
Donating to bail funds right now
Dakota Jesus believes that all of this money is just going to rioters and looters is not
Baccarat at all
And then based on his last
95% of these folks being out-of-towners
What do you say after this
Hilarious
People that donate
So basic what you doing is your
Community
This what happens when your
Up-to-date
Information that's available
When you
Cover your eyes
And cover your ears
Blind facts cuz you're not up-to-date
It seems like he was trying to ironically claim hotep
But man does he live up to being a hotel
Really lives up to it he's going
You know
So Alex asks his daughter
Alex's daughter who's 12
This is kinda interesting because
Twelve-year-old daughter
Donate to Hotel page
Tell her
Media industrial complex
Industrial complex in
Make people believe
So interesting Lee Jesus complained about the media when he was on red ICE 2
But you see that shows a little more openly anti-jewish
He said quote the only thing that makes white supremacy a thought in people's minds is the media and the media is controlled by who
The only thing that makes white supremacy if thing is music and
Control
The movies Hollywood
Controls that
Control
White people don't control that
Who controls these Banks
This is the world you that hotep Jesus espouses and he knows what to make his message palatable to Alex's broadcast
Down a little bit
All the Slick bigots do that when they come on Infowars
As you see that from all of these people
It's all these folks who are pretty deep into Holocaust denial will never directly say those things
Show
Because they know that there is enough of an audience that Alex has
You could probably get someone over to you but if you come out and you're like six billion is a fake number
That kind of s***
You're never going to get them to take the first step
Once they've taken three or four steps in your direction might be able to Spring that on them
Hard water
They were right all along
If you're trying to open
With the audience
Alex's they are selling his audience to bigot
Yeah pretty cast
And you can't
It just is unjustifiable if you come Out Swinging with bigotry
Ratchet says to me is that Jesus hasn't listened to the show for the past 4 months
Because now
Swing away buddy is that 80-yard field goal people other than like Steve
Speak a little bit more carefully Steve don't give a fuk
Just like
I have humiliated out is unimaginable I can say whatever the f***
Alex's
It's over for him
When do they sound really interesting I think Alex might have been eating or something
But there are a bunch of times when
Hotep Jesus is talking
And
Stop stalking clearly done with a thought and then Alex does not come in doesn't try
Event start another thought
Consciousness community
Just on TV that supported by the Liberals
Movies in Everett
If you look at
That's very weird for Alex's show was never here
And that's not an instance of someone politely letting their guests for second pause
Must not have been in
Or something bizarre
Here's hoping that he would keep he was hoping that he can ride it out for a little bit longer
Yes sir willing to just talk and talk and talk for no problem
Natural end
Pause the starting of another cop
Having a natural end of a thought that's true
So we have this is a clip
Episode
Who is LifeWay
I've Jordan This is 20/20 shirt
We come back next week to especially
Give Michelle
Something really
I'd like to do
Something
Studio
Really awesome
You name the time if you're ready to jump on a plane please come I'll Finance
Dot-com we love you we appreciate it
This might be one of the only instances where Alex gives
I really like taking my body
I would like to
Deport you back to the very beginning of his interview
No other media Outlets are calling situation
T.i.
I found this really interesting you know like you have
Almost
No very little progression in terms of
Interesting things about the narratives that Alex is pushing or building around this
Just an anger at protesters
A resentment about
Secretary of Defense esper not wanting to use the Insurrection Act
You know that's kind of all the
The same time there's a we're running out of time there is no time left that still intensity
An interview with
Zoo weird I was running for office
Hotep Jesus
Alright
These are these are the folks you want to talk to
So I don't know
What are you doing
I'm back
Say we'll be back and then you do this
DMX
30 years
30 years for you
Inside its knowledge nike.com
Find a local funding
You possibly can
Back but until then I'm here
Ice Cube
Alex