Nola.com
I have great respect for knowledge B
Sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Knowledge
Knowledge fight
Wendy
Jordans
What up
Interesting
For the week I work today is that
The audience
The show is so
Engaged in productive ways
Like last episode I discussed how I want to get a new animal friend
And a couple about animals that might be in the running
Thought through
But I got to eat
Honda feedback
From people about those options about like
Here's some of the drawbacks of those pets
And also a very bored
Piece of feedback that is sugar gliders are not things you should know
The table was necessarily like a leader in the clubhouse
Looking cute
I think a lot of the possibilities in
Baby another cat
And that could be more productive use of my time so I want another animal friend to come around and play with me
Somebody sent me a message
I don't remember your name
I sent this message
Kangaroo
And I immediately threw up and across the room
Suggested to get like cockroaches
No I can't do that
I don't want to
Terraria man
About
Mantis
Emancipated
Completely collapses you'll be able to make little
I don't think that's going to be in the cards
I think there's a lot of broad
Ramifications of their choice
Animal friends
And I appreciate the audience
Making a good
Decision
Ludacris like I end up with
A wallaby
Jada Wilder service
Cute and lovely but at the same time be abusive for me to have never fallen
That trap so
I've always dreamt of getting a sock
Jackson those things are
You just can't
Yeah they don't
I don't think you're being squirrels
Around my neck and I instantly have a personality
So what about you
My brakes I have you ever seen the TV show alone
It's like a history it's like a survival show
Dijon
This show is you
They make these great little shelters like my partner and I were watching these just like
Other people watch HGTV
How do you make that a frame with all the boss on it that sounds amazing
So I think
Survivor
If you would watch season 2 or so
I think season one is pretty good with season 2 is like what really
Grabbed me
Possible
I think you would have enjoyed seeing the ingenuity
I mean positive
Cheated for for a fact
Got to be some of that
You would have really enjoyed
Survivors
Thanks
Religion alter star because
Subway
Colleges which are often like
Food
Everyone compete in a reward challenge
You know so they'll do that people
Early stars on Survivor
Picture of a step back
I feel so dystopian
But it's like if you watch a Japanese game show you like
Holy s*** I don't understand how we got to this place but I don't know what we're going to
Controls
Challenging environment
All I will say Survivor got to control some of their concept
The breakdown of the tribes in later seasons
It was troubling
Blue barracuda
Head
Most incompetent Temple guards
I don't remember who was that with it
Mike O'Malley's during appeal
Beyond the generations he started out on Nickelodeon and then he got his own TV show and s***
Congratulations to Mike
Sure
Congratulations
Episode
June 5th 2020
Grammy's 2020
So first SC
Southern California
Thank you so much
Thanks Erik with a k
Next
Jenneke
Are you going around here today
Are you still throwing in some KKK I'm certainly not I'm just trying to spell people's names correctly
But Jenna
Juvenile policy walk
Next Phillippe
Text Eric C
Next.
Alex M you're now a technocrat
Money off that heroin
Yes
The people who don't
You are right I mean there are
3 mm
There's no last initial
Okay so there's just
Ibid
I don't think it is
Alright I feel very self-conscious about something
Scooby-Doo
Everybody gets I think so
I was just getting in my head
Jordan
I was planning on trying to do Sunday episode
For this episode is wild
I get us as close to current as possible
This is too much going on on this episode and also
The flip a Sunday episode for a Monday podcast
Is Barry difficult
It requires us to record at like 8 or 9 at night
It's just I'm up all night
If I'm trying to get that episode
Turned around a time so
Will be able to check in on that on our next episode on these here bones
Under the sea
By not to do with protests
Billy strange
House on Friday
Strange
So Alex starts off the show he wants to get back into the business with talking about
It's your right to argue that he's right about everything
They say how are you right
Every time
How did you know the Builder
You made it up
Search that it was a group
Recovery
Play those clips
News
Study
Gasp
Think about how big
About it
Alright
F*** off
One study that disagrees with him is retracted it's obviously a cover-up one steady that agrees with him is retracted its
Like I don't I don't need any
This one is now that it's
Retracted
That game is not making up
Do the Guardians report
Never called
Treating covid-19
This was
The early studies
Chance of mortality
In covid-19
The reason that the authors were attracted the study was that they were basing their analysis on compiled by a company called
Surgisphere
Who's methods came under Quest
The others became concerned when surgisphere apparently was uncooperative the provided
Ultimately
Around the same time that this paper was rejected the New England Journal of Medicine that relied on data from surgisphere
But it was unrelated to hydroxychloroquine
This is clearly a story about
Statistical reliability more than it is about
Or anyone trying to attack Trump
Did you hear that the retraction is not the result of the data being shown to be inaccurate
Just that the authors are no longer convinced he's reliable
Which are different things
It may be the case that the underlying data is bad
Or it may be fine but since they can't stand behind it
Outlets
I can find concrete connections between surgisphere and Bill Gates nor between Gates and surgisphere zoner
Sepang beside
So unless Alex can substantiate that I assume he's just making it up
Another thing to keep in mind is that no matter what the reality is with this study getting rejected it has no effect on
Responsible Trump was being what he promoted
The drug is a potential miracle
Procure
You would have all science came back
It did say that it was a perfect cure for covid-19
Trump had absolutely no reason to say what he did
Which is the problem
And finally
Alex is completely wrong about the study's referencing
He's just read a few headlines about early studies that showed promise you no like as a hundred percent
They just decided to look no further into it
There's plenty of other studies that have shown like you shouldn't be giving this to people
On June 3rd of Derry rigorously controlled study was published in the New England Journal of Medicine would show.
Malaria drug hydroxychloroquine did not help prevent people with vinegar
Exposed to others of covid-19 from developing the disease
This is the first double-blind randomized placebo-controlled study that's been done on the subject
Amy found that the drug had a copper elbow effect to a placebo
On June 5th is reported on a clinical trial that had just wrapped up in the UK
One of the Weeds on that study and Oxford epidemiologist said
Today's preliminary results from the recovery trial are quite
Clear hydroxychloroquine does not reduce the risk of death among hospitalized patients with this
New disease
Some of the new day we're seeing or tending towards the impression
There's also no medical reason to prescribe for covid-19
Studies are showing that it's not have a significant effect on recovery
There are other studies that are looking at other aspects of the drugs possible
Applications interactions with covid-19
But it doesn't look like there's anything
Particularly promising here at this point making the presidency
Listen to prescribe drugs
Will you put it that way
I bet Alex would argue that
President
I probably would make
I guess what I was doing here as he's trying to claim a major win or a victory in hindsight
Trump may not have been advocating for people to take an unnecessary medication that might kill her
Well it sounds really bad
Is there a medication that has a smoke
What are gyros
Claire victory
Mission accomplished
Chanterelle mushrooms
Very interesting approach
Did that
Because of these complicated reasons involving
Uncertainty around the sourcing of this
And Alex is going to report that
All of everything about covid-19
Also Bill Gates is involved
This particular retract
Which I can find no evidence
Surgisphere does have a kind of evil name to accompany
The medical companies probably have things that are
Sort of similarly
What are the chief problems about this is that
As Alex talks more about the story
Attractions
He doesn't know anything about the
How much did
Otherwise none
Bill Gates
7 trillion
The story is
He's just read a headline about them and now he's Off to the Races
He doesn't know what the other journals that retracted their study was which was the New England Journal of Medicine
Further he doesn't
What that New England Journal medicine paper was about
I was acting like it was about hydroxychloroquine but it wasn't
And you would know that if you knew anything about this story
The study that was retracted from the New England Journal of Medicine was based on data also provided by surgisphere
But it was looking at the possible interaction
Between covid-19 and blood pressure medication
Is the major variable nested Alec seems completely unaware of which is troubling
Anyone acting innocent Seer capacity would never report on a story like this with such a little knowledge about the topic
Does this all the time
He gets like two or three details and then just mix up the rest in a way that generally fits his propaganda angle
We just called lion
A second major thing that Alex is making up in the story of how these retractions happen
He's pretending that public pushback was responsible for getting the researchers to retract that's not at all what hap
In reality
There are some questions that experts and news media brought question the particular provided by
What are the major things that happened was as you mentioned the guardian reported on May 28th
Researchers in Australia review
Did 73 deaths from covid-19 in the country
At that point when there was actually only 67 official.
This set off alarm just exactly the state was coming from
The Australian researchers contacted Lancet contacted the study's authors for clarification
Requested surgisphere authenticate their data
To make matters more suspicious
The pain beside the head of surgisphere
Quotes
Accidentally been included in the Australian
From there
You can't rely on this data unless it's audited
And studies that relied on it has to be retracted
Which is why those two were
Absolutely nothing to do with public backlash it had to do with Australian researchers attempting to conduct a study
Who found an irregularity
And then the attempt to sort it out uncovered a possible instance of shoddy
This honestly should give people a lot more confidence
The numbers that were seen
Because it's such a great example of scientific self-policing
People conducting This research pour over the data and discrepancies sit there
Yeah he's a good guy
Underlying data
It's not clear really
Absence of data
Poorly organized and regulated data which renders it unreliable to be used for professional analysis
That's not the same thing as having no data or just being made of
The case of this Asian / Australian hospital that was found in the data
That could well be a mistake
But they made in terms of archiving the data and possibly if you remove the hospital from Australia
He's in set of numbers
The numbers might match official number
Very well may be the case but even if it is you still have to retract
Because of the possibility
Of other unexamined problems being there in the data would pop up later
So you're saying Ashley looking over their own data sets in order to refine their information and
Use it more effectively in the way that they're doing
I really think that sounds like a cover-up to
Is dr. Allen chin infectious disease doctor in Australia told the guardian
If they got that wrong what else could be wrong
In terms of the surgisphere dataset
A mistake like that taints a set of data because it introduces far too much on reliability and uncertainty so using it is
Is essentially like trying to build a house on Sam
There are some indications that are coming out the points in the direction that decide may have a history of fabrication
As BuzzFeed reported on June 6th
Publix
In 2004
Is part of his Graduate Studies at the University of Illinois Chicago
Have some instances of duplication and images used
Which is a no no
A computer scientist they talked to said
It's like the guy went crazy with Photoshop
And went on to say quote I've never seen something like this it's outrageous
That being said that alone is not proof that the dataset that surgisphere was using was fabricated or made up
These indications of past malfeasance introduced that possibility
But it still needs to be proven which I have not seen up till this point
It might happen in the future but was made-up is an indication that he doesn't understand
Reporting he's kind of just wings
Well you know who works
Surgisphere
It's a Polish or in the Lesser Baldwin
Cobalt
I don't remember
I don't know my Baldwin
So the fourth problem is again Alex
If Alex wants to make the story about Bill Gates
Understand the basics
The story
He's ever going to
The Gates Foundation in the Declaration of Interest section
Which would have been done if they've been involved in the study or responding
I need a citation here if Alex wants me to take her seriously
Not going to happen
So I'm not going
Bill Gates
Create
The popularity of
Photoshop witch
Guy used
Trick people on his graduates.
I would love for Alex. Do that sounds amazing
Demonstration of how poorly thanks
I need to have a little chat with you about
A method of lying and a method of analysis that Alex does
Clear enough.
The past
Bloomberg
Funded
That's amazing
Nowhere in the Lancet article Business Insider article
You just making that up because he doesn't care to understand the actual story and just wants to make things fit
This is important
Because Alex is directly asserting that Lancet is reporting that the study of the total and was funded by Bill Gates
That statement is a lie
Alex is actually doing
When I was in college I was drawn toward the study of ancient things
I dabbled in anthropology and religious studies before I landed on the ill-advised path I ended up taking
I have a degree with basically for minors instead of one major
Is the cost of being indecisive you end up having
Start a podcast about Alex Jones when you grow up
My advisor in college did not warn me of this bike
I kind of felt like a famous stand-up
I wasn't
Just imagine my high school guidance counselor college hours story as like a
Cautionary Tale
Do you want to start a podcast about a lunatic
My religious studies classes are the concepts of exegesis and eisegesis
Styles of textual criticism
Engages in exegesis attempts to understand the text that's in front of them and understand that text to a number
Applied contact
Text
The prism of understanding a text in terms of historical events happening around
Writing
Another school of exegesis used
The text itself is divinely-inspired
It does studies a text in the context that there's a meeting beyond the original author intended
But it's still a study of the
There's a lot of different views on exegesis but all of it is studying within a framework and all the things
From the text to study
The opposite of his practice is called eisegesis
Which is when it's something serious.
Strongly
Someone who engages and eisegesis is someone approaches a text for a reason
Anderson
Define supplicant demonstrates
Conclusion they already have
An exegesis you rely on things to take out of the text inform your study
Where is an eisegesis
Text
And are bringing that point to the text itself to defend your point
It's a dangerous cracked
Just because it allows you to misuse primary sources and take small passages out of appropriate context to make whatever point
Incline to make anyway
But you're pretending
Figuring gauging with Source material and that's what led you to your conclusion
It's a bastardized version to study
Are you sure they
Missy Missy cuz what I hear is
It's one of those is exigence
This isn't one of those is fun
I like believe what I believe and not worrying about what other people
People say I will save it in my life that are disciplined are typically last
Is why I have it for my Hearthstone
Exegesis and eisegesis art in relation to biblical criticism
Apply to basically all sorts of
Text Roland Allison
The person who engages in rampant eisegesis
The other point that he intends to make and he picks various headlines that he thinks things will reinforce his point
As opposed to reading the news in forming conclusions based on the information that comes to him
About reality
A lot of conspiracy-minded people do this
Since eisegesis is a practice that essentially it's just a pastor confirmation bias
You go looking for something
And if you're lazy enough of a researcher
But there's a decent chance it won't be real
Seen happen here with this new story that Alex is covering
He's already decided everything about covid-19 is a hoax so he's bringing that to his reading of this story when the actual texted no
No way support sis
Conclusion
The only way he could arrive at that can
Conclusion to the T
Text with him
Which is inappropriate
Does this all the time and I generally just say he's lying or making things up
I thought this was a particularly good example of his specific behavior
Explaining this precise technique that uses
Do you understand this a little bit better you
Can see it pop up in so many insta
Symptoms of Alex very regular
Technique that if he'd actually learn
Things
In his younger years about how to engage
Write with different text
Differently
He probably wouldn't
Fall into
I don't even want to call so
It's so
Intentional
Like I said Jesus isn't necessarily
Engagement
Or a lot of a lot of creative nonfiction
ReliOn the reader bringing something to the text to engage with
It's it's the it's the
The Forum
It is more appropriate for those
The one you're talking about
We're talking about
Factual based things are primary sources
Document
It's just
Responsible thing
To engage
Yeah as my age
Somebody who's gone to five colleges in still doesn't even have a single degree
Most of most of those were all in literature
Not that conversation in so many different classes about like
Authorial intent versus
Always some people who are in the any of those classes
Just like
I refuse to even bother picking up a history book
About what was going on
What he was obviously writing about was whatever it is
That I wish you would
And it happened every time
Conviction
End
You know looking at a piece of even
Fiction within the context of
What could think be allegories for based on the live experience of the author
It's a different approach to it
Typically
Especially when covering topics that are similar to the one that Alex is
Jesus is just like
A completely inappropriate
And flawed way to engage with
Material
You're going to
End up lying
Intentionally you're going to end up lying intentionally everything is going to be disconnected from reality
Cuz every story is only going to
Really be depiction of what you
Think and feel
Pointless
I can only
For when I see Jesus isn't
Reality
I like the.
Did you ever read that well the author just goes through in
Like tries to explain taoism and Buddhism by using these characters in The Way They Were
They interact as like
But he's not saying
It was a clearly Buddhist
Series of books
Books trying to explain something
More like an application thing
That applies
I think about it more so I have it rented out
Read books
That like everyone tells me to read
Tabaxi
Little Miss Sunshine
You're not missing any
You're fine
Thank you can live without those movies
I promise you
Further into you know anti-vaccine
Denialism
And stuff and
Making stuff up
Butcher Boys
Told by
Not
Public
People are still
So I
Ian Hayden
It discusses adverse
I'm ready
Bunch of stories about this dude and literally none of them back up without the same
Here Alex is presenting to climb
First
Bill Gates of Gates Foundation told him not to come forward
An article in the New York Post clearly says quote
He also insisted that is sick as he was it was never life-threatening
They're over and it back to Marathon run
No Outlet interviewed him seems to be reporting that Ian almost died unless you allow for a very very broad reading of
Almost died
Princeton Post article discusses how his girlfriend was there to catch him when he
He fainted
So you can make a disingenuous argument that if he'd fainted in the wrong place and she was
Barry could have been fatal
That's a stretch for the type of Art
Alex is trying
Except
Again
This is eisegesis
Alex wants the story to be that these vaccines are killing people to the story
It completely Alters the way he reports it
You makes up details and embellish his things in order to match his narrative
Because it's not important
To discuss reality
It's crucial to Warp
Reality to match the predetermined narrative
As for the second claim the Bill Gates told I can find no evidence of this claim
And it's a responsibility to prove it or admit
I checked out his Twitter account needs very supportive still love the vaccine he was a part of the trial for
At the end of May he retweeted a modern announcement that they were entering Phase 2 trial
It seems like he's mostly interested in coming forward to demystify the phenomenon of adverse
I think is pretty admirable
Alex wants the story to be the Bill Gates is somehow threatened by Ian coming forward because Alex thinks that all the media.
Medicines can sometimes
Adverse reactions
For the people
That premise is faulty
Well what's your missing here
Here is what act
Is he was standing out by
Behind the semi truck
That had the Box
Dolly
Not the Box
What is the vaccine on it
Almost hit him in the head so we almost got killed by the vaccine and then bill
And you know how that's proof
If you didn't tell anybody about that mix-up you know what I heard actually mostly moves
Vaccines by way of
Pianos on strings
Situation where a piano that cleans NFL on it
Similar thing he was keeping a bunch of vaccines about Apple cards and all that stuff as they walked by slowly
In reality the gates people the scientist at moderna probably have no problem telling a story
Better understanding about clinical trials work
Things get tweak does trials progress
That's not brightening
Princeton in the press release that Ian retweeted from moderna they discussed their initial dosing in face
And guess what
They completely eliminated the top dose which was 250 micrograms
From the trials because the information they collected Indians round of tests
3 people in the 250 microgram group had self-dissolving
Adverse effect
From the back
Researchers to learn
So the new trials are focusing on
Placebo 50 microgram dose and a 100 mg dose
They learned from the first round but the difference between 100 and 250 microgram wasn't relevant to terms
People engage with these sorts of things in terms of reality understand that this is a process
Asurion wasn't
Got a bad fever and fainted
But I'm also sure that research is gather essential information about how to proceed creating a bags
It's safest for everyone
And further the researchers and moderna and Bill Gates
I don't look at you in telling the story of the huge negative
They have to report on Adverse Events anyway
So those numbers were released prior to eating coming forward
Does it put the human face on that number
Human face
Pretty publicly saying what the side effect wasn't
And that he's glad that he was a part of the study and he still believes in
I don't know how that's a negative for Bill Gates it's insane to me
That bet this point of view that Alex
Is expressing is fake
His hatred and distrust of a company trying to make a vaccine and part of that trial
Is putting small group
Together getting
Clean and then getting that data in order to refine it and
Ben
Pass it on to a larger group
That's the idea
Not somebody coming out and just saying
We've got the vaccine
Everyone taken
Without trying it without testing it without doing anything like that
Santa Cruz
Would you took the guys just like I do this over the people
Lumos fictionalized version
Through misusing primary sources
In order to provide a foundation in a basis
People who don't pay attention
Yeah
So
Yep
So his next big story actually pretty exciting
And fun
To look into a little bit
And guess what
2 days ago
But you talked about 9
This is coming
Now is
Reset
With the UN imf-world Bank
Control
Excuse
They say it
Exactly
Wonderful
Rothschild
Digital money back
How we Livin
Your Lifestyles never going to be the same but it's
The best
Permission to travel
Officially
From the day
Go to hear them come back up in Forever
Reading this report
I strongly suspect that he saying he read it because it's completely unbelievable
She's trying to make a slightly lesser claim in order to make it sound more plausible
A man who claimed to be
Furious it mostly read it that still puts well over four
My reasons
One I cannot find any 100-page report
3 page synopsis appears to just be an op-ed on the world economic forum's website with that line
Now is the time for a great reset
It's not a synopsis is just an iPad about a larger idea
For covering this story just links to the world economic forum
Comic forums article
Provide attribution for
World economic forum
Which is a copyright free photo service
If any pictures under copyright he could get into trouble
For stealing intellectual property without permission
Generac rebutia
So Alex is making up the stuff he says about what's in the report
That's not in the op-ed which is mostly about how the situation
Tends toward a very rare opportunity to reshape the world for the better
This involves steering the market George Fair outcome
Ensuring investment Advanced shared goals such as sustainability
You support the public
Especially by addressing Health and Social Challenges
You can read into that whatever you like insurance
It's probably sensible to be a little suspicious of the world economic forum
Is disconnected from reality
Again he's engaging and eisegesis
Is it bad practice
Yeah it's
I like the world
Place where they're saying all this stuff but at the end of the day for their Solutions probably like
And that's why private Equity Funds need to own a business
This is
What's the closest thing that I can come up to with this 100-page report
Interactive issues map
The world economic forum's website
The great reset
That sounds fun
I strongly suspect for a membership
See him taking the time to sign up for 1 just to read something
Since 2000
I got up right now it's actually really interesting the way it is data and information
Is laid out
Is an outrageously informative presentation on topics
It starts with the great reset in the middle
A couple with nodes that are go off of that the branch out
These nodes are things like
Shaping the economic recovery
Strengthening Regional development
If you click on one of these let's use restoring health
The environment as an example
It highlights all the issue on the outermost next set of nodes that relate to that topic
So in this case if you click on restoring the health of the environment you have things like the ocean
Forest
Plastics in the environment and a whole bunch of others
Of course each of these nodes reflects
The interplay with other nodes from the first level
Like the ocean involves the intersection of restoring the health of the environment
Evie Hardison before
Industrial Revolution
Then if you click on one of these issues with the outermost issues
The farthest out nodes
Because we've already been
Using
Example if you click on that you're taking to a whole new wheel of notes
Now the ocean is in the center of the visualization witch
With new node surrounding it
Like overfishing
Aquaculture
And the ocean
In the original visuals the great reset their outermost nodes
In that visualization
And each of these like the ocean
Transfer to their own wheel bearings
What I'm saying is more than 100 pages of information on here
But it's not laid out in any kind of way where you busy
Plausible to be like I read most of it's almost like a visualization of the club of Rome
Problematique in empty in that kind of sense
Call to that
Idea of a way to approach
Problems is really interesting
I'm not positive there are a ton of
Prescribed
Within that
But it's largely just about like these are topics that are really important
Compiled by experts
One of these
Is essentially a presentation
That is is farmed out
Two experts in the field
I can't even pretend that I can accurately report on this visualization
It's a presentation of presentation the presentation there's so much there and there's pertains to somebody different issues
Poopy impossible for me to cover it
There's a lot of stuff to be found
But it's really outside the scope of the show for me to break it all down
The point is that Alex didn't do any work on this
About this op-ed
On the world economic Forum 100-page report that he's read almost all of
Blah blah blah
This is all bulshit
We're a lot of people's heads
They're at cuz
You can you can go to that and you can realize the scope of
What's the problem
Really visualize everything that's going on and how the entire system itself is set up
The Destroyer
You could tell a strong crazy moron to kill your
Friends
And you're in
Those are those are alternate strategy
We just kind of think that one is easier than the other
Alex
I suppose it's an expert about something
Google Trends
The black lives matter
Wash
20%
Some stuff in for fun
I already discussed the error that hotep Jesus is making our life episode how use a racing context from the trends numbers writing his own
Story about it
Again he was having his own son today
Sure
What's important to remember is that Alex's is the stuff about antifa
If you go to Google Transit you type in Antigua is Enos picat all in 2016
Cuz the right-wing wasn't obsessed with
The first bike you see is on August 13th 2017 and that's because it was right after that
What happened on August 12th
You remember that was a bunch of
Protester in his car
You may recall that there was a concerted campaign
Which is undoubtedly why there was a spike
Or interest
In August
This is critical to understand
Ultimately the Google prove anything other than there was an increased interest in a certain topic
Make it a certain time
Interestin blacklivesmatter increase after the murders of Alton Sterling and philando Castillo
And the interest is
Really spiky
Increase
Make sense
People are curious about this thing that they hadn't heard of it people keep talking about so they Googled
Alex is making up Google Transit formation 2016
Which wouldn't mean anything
Even if it were true
Just for fun
I just had to check the information for the
Not surprisingly there was a spike
On January 22nd 2017
Because I was right after Trump got inaugurated president
Who is in violation of that closet
There's another big spike in late October 2019
G7 at one of his properties
Phony
Neither of these spikes mean anything other than something people were talking about
Contacts
Around
Each of these spikes
You can clearly understand what the glue is reflecting
Alex pretends
Got a secret code that's being shown in these numbers
Ridiculous but it's
Prion praying for him
Cuz he's a dumb dumb liar
Dumb dumb
I'm still going to go out
The violence
I can't see any other extra
You have to shut up
You're going to get us killed
Holyshit
Alex is a MPI.
Is really all about killing
Tops
Find a particular irony
In Alex's were
Revolution
So I don't think
Speaking
Kill cops even indoors
Eliminating Police Department
Stop short of expressing a desire to
Kill all cops
Alex come play with us
Interesting
In the past we've heard Alex very clearly expressed that if people start to pass gun regulations that he doesn't approve of the
The right wing and start killing cops
He's talked about it many times and extremist text unintended consequence
Which was about right-wing extremist waging a war on the police because of gun laws
We heard the topic
Slightly get broached caller brought up unintended consequences Alex replied that it was a good book
We just go get coffee
So that was a show on January 16th 2013
By February 10th 2013
Covering the story of Chris daughter
The LAPD cop who is going on a killing
Seemingly primarily targeting police
Alex was super upset that the shooting spree would lead to new gun regulation
He expressed his concern
Brett police games
Gun owners
Would rise up and kill them
Motorcycles
20 something
Social engineering
And just go out
Play way more explicit about this whole thing directly
Literally all cops would be dead
Very quickly
You can see here on Alex's mindworks
Version of the current protests
Make them scared
In this reality these protesters
Because I just going to end up
Bordelaise
In case of husted issue
Imaginary
He's directly threatening the lives of literally all cops in the country with murder
Real and this is smart and will not end up with more police
This is a dreadful Glimpse because what it tells you that Alex wishes
Protesting for a cause he's opposed to
In this case greater equality in terms
Justice
However when it comes to issues impacted by like gun regulation
He feels entitled to any violence against the state to the point of murdering all cops
This is an astoundingly authoritarian level
Provide some explanation for how we got to where we are now
Alex has always been this
Massive ships that have happened since Trump
He's always been
Fundamentally I want everybody who disagrees with me
Yeah
You know it's the term the guy use so much like right after Trump's election that kind of became
I kind of a joke was emboldened
But legitimate
I think
Clearly what you see with Alex's
Not so much
Total Gym
Impulses
And things that were there already
Yeah absolutely
And then it just
Underscores the fact that the
Heart rate for all their Bluster about wanting a second
Civil War
Really just want a
Blankets permission to kill whom they don't like
They don't want a revolution
They don't want to change the system is great for them
Alex is his big thing that he goes I guess someone forwarded him like
A Facebook post
Or something
Protest organizers who were explaining like
Hey if you're white
And you come to these tests please
Understand
Follow the lead of the non-white
Rally-goers
Restart
Exactly selfies in order
Google I mean
What level
Tourism site secondarily you run the risk of identifying people if you have
Other protesters
Who could be
Be put at risk by by way of you
You photographing.
Track people down and suck at throwing up
Concerns that this post that Alex is making
The express
Yeah decided they what they say it is black people turning white such a Slave
Man
When we come back
And I'll stop the bubble
No selfies
Bosch
Reinventing slavery
Please do not forget
That
The biggest sale
This year
Gold sale
This is just tiresome
This this level of like
Misrepresenting stuff
Stupid
Gestalt
Something
Told you
About
Because I was just bored
And I don't care
A couple days Alex has been having a
Chess board skull and roses on his desk
Pretending
Set dresser to look at it
Despite his desk before he's brought up that like is Dad is a dentist near the skull
He found it
He wasn't
Cuz it's taking to the next level with a chessboard
Roses
Iowa
I can't tell you enough how much I love this clip
Is
This is what kind of overdose
For me the other stuff I can handle the hardships
With you
Read you
Documents
Can just look directly into the camera
Radio Western
Who is Mike Trout
Askew
Do you want
You control your own future
Future
Do you want a pro-human
Decided
You're worthless
But you need
Just rhetoric
But I'm up here
Things that are half
Your family's future
I should appear on this TV program
This chat said
The skull
The flowers
Why do people fast
Your show it looks
Superjet
On the edge
What you're thinking
Tumi
All God's gifts
StreetWise
A while
Oh my God that's so perfect to me that is like
Funniest
F****** thing in the world
It's
Alex
2 minutes
Of like oh my God
No one could do that but Alex
So it started esoteric
I want to walk you through what's so great about this
It starts with Alex he has responsibility to prove anything
Sure I can prove it all but instead I'm just going to
Speaker earnestly into the camera am rattle off a bunch of vague platitudes about nothing lot easier to do that in such a
Perfect encapsulation
Alex's style of proven things
It runs through so much of his program how do you say you know like
But I can't get to any of it so he doesn't get that
Right there's so many major news stories break
This is Alex's sleight-of-hand
Dixon just to Clearview
Amazing
Alex gets to the chess set in the scope of the Rose
Riverbend except he's on his desk for the last few days
You like about it
Obviously there's some kind of point he's trying to impart
It means whatever it means to you
Alex instinctually knows that this is disappointing as hell so he starts breaking down what it means to him
Apparently the rose is a tree that symbolizes
Add red blood to the red rose
I bet it all falls apart
A very clearly sounded like he got distracted by his own bullets and then was like
Wait what was the fuc
Just about any of this toroso you thought because you're special report
You want so desperately to be reflected in these
It's hilarious what an active putting on here just everything is pretense and facade
He acts like he can prove his claims
Batteries
He act like he was some kind of a deep esoteric message props on his desk
You can't come up with a ship pass calling
He acts like he's fully committed to his show and all the same
I want things are going well
This dude is legitimately the saddest person in media right now.
Just
He was like he's like if a bookshelf filled with cardboard box
This is bound to look like Britannica became a person
It's almost impressively that
No one else could do big books
Just like okay stale
And then come back and stay on tomorrow never learn any lesson
You telling me that there are less
Amazing
Really rich people in fair enough discussion of Jeff Bezos
This little piece of his
Really reflects
Ultimately how bad Alex is even with a Leo
0 1%
$37
Fairies all good and well
Dissolution probably to get Bezos to give a billion to Gunn weirdos
I'm not I don't care
So what I'm most interested nightclub is the mass
You take the ratio
Maybe the equivalent of them giving $87 a year
Alex's claim at 8.01% of Bezos income
The same as $87 to euro
Some news for Alec
$87 to be .01% of your income in $870,000
Come on Investopedia the median income in the United States per household
In 2018 with 63000 179 dollars
I've no idea what Alex thinks about at all
I heard him throughout those numbers and even without doing the math I do this is load of s*** but I didn't realize how far off he was
What's going on here is it out with Miss read the headline in Vox that he's trying to cover
Which of the Bezos gay
1% of his wealth
Charity in 2018
But in the headline this is visualized as 0.1
Sounds just moved until 1
Alright you didn't realize how big of a difference moving the decimal point
Accuracies they come from sloppy and lazy reporting
You could say that it doesn't matter that the point of Bezos doesn't give enough
The charity is right
This is a serious issue like bezos's charity
Actually has misread to score dumb points.
Incapable the kind of discussions
Solve problems
Society the billionaires are hypothetical trillionaires
He's part of it is just
Kind of counterproductive
Six of the topic
Cuz he doesn't eat skimmed a headlines
4.01
Send
It is a small problem
Implies a large problem if you were to go to a protest at Jeff Bezos
How's about this situation
He would not sit and listen to the f****** organizers
Play some b*******
Protests in Austin
All that Alex came out the organizers
We're trying to get him to come speak up on the diocese just distracting
Point where they theorize that like he was
Intentionally disrupting their protest
And it probably wasn't that
It is that kind of takes them over
And he doesn't take them over just makes them s*** makes everybody hate
Yeah
This is another one that's really fascinating
Hilarious
Fantastic in the same way there's something that is
Anything you stalking
And I'll discuss it
After you left
The biggest
Myself
For you for your
Businesses
You guys got a mic
Really stressed out about all this
Show now
Adjustable mattress
Medical martial law
Operate
Did he ran Jeffrey
Operation
Children
Films
Scientific
Clipper super interesting
You can tell from Alex's tone and he was preparing
Or more likely begging his audience to spread it around and sucker in new customer
It's very distinctive ramps
Before the end of the hour
That's usually when he's most likely to plug
Trying to tell by the tone of his voice at the beginning of the
Then he gets distracted by Tech problems and completely loses his train of thought and he blows up about how he's not doing any of this
The theatrics
When he realizes that he's got a big daddy charcoal about accusations it is being theatrical
He knows he has to give some kind of an explanation for why he's on edge
Can you see what he comes up with
It's the Bill Gates was Jeffrey Epstein's entire operation
Here's what's fascinating
You can actually hear Alex decide to run with a narrative
I'll play you just a little section where you can hear his footing Shake slightly and then you can hear him reassure himself
Fascinating
Medical martial law
Jeffrey Epstein
You can hear it in the tone he says the Bill Gates ran Epstein's operation and then
It's amazing to me since it's not very often you can hear Alex Devore extreme narratives in real time
Clear the gates and Epstein knew each other and there was a connection between the two in the past and that's all good and well
But this is a massive departure
From that beaten path
This is honestly possibly the kind of slander you might even get in trouble with the
Black figure
Alex directly asserting on his operation wasn't
Going to making snuff film
Obviously it's not worth cases time to get into the mud with Alex but that
Hesitation and reassurance
I'm almost certain about I was I was thinking
I get away with this
I meant deciding that he care
I'm not sure this is the best place for someone to step in it
Eat Alex's lunch
No one has financially destroyed
Because they eat makes jet up to this point
Just know that there's no consequences raining he said
Any evidence being involved in murders and there's no consequences
It's honestly pretty remarkable
Is basically a living example of how these sorts of laws only apply when someone is willing to enforce them
And if you spend all your time slandering
You're pretty much free to say whatever you want about them
So let this be a lesson to Future propagandist
If you want to make materially false
Defamatory claims about someone
Always go for top-tier targets
Trouble is when you go after private persons like Sandy Hook families
Or mid-tier folks like the owner of Chobani
Actually are too busy
So you can just defend them all you want it generally there'll be no,
Isn't there
You know okay I get babies busy
Maybe he's busy
What do I give him
But come on just send that guy
100 Junior lawyers
For somebody straight out of Law School
Slam-dunk case give them their first win right out the gate
50 Grand a year you'll get it
Possibly
You know you end up
As we've seen with so many of these cases that Alex is involved in a situation
Motortrend create more attention for himself
You end up with the possibility of like just getting bogged down in something
The plays at his hand even if you would end up winning the case
Don't even talk to don't even acknowledge that there is a lawsuit
My position on it is more that like that
This point
Probably past the point where anyone
Outside in
Indicating that way
Long ago
Yeah so what
New project Veritas video
Any plays little bit of it
Alex is dumb
Videos complete
In the video James O'Keefe
Ellen and proven repeatedly liar
Of course this person is completely Anonymous and has their face
Skewers are honestly everything up they probably are
There's some serious inconsistency
She's a come up in the video which The Daily Beast
The biggest one is the guy in the video
Storage Portland
Call Kim Edwards open for business problem
Because according to Oregon live in other words closed in 2018
What does indicator shows this bookstore for a reason easy to guess what that reason is
In other words was the inspiration for the fictional book store women and women first in the show Portlandia
If you are a right-wing propaganda attacking you were trying to come up with a location for this militant sjw
It makes sense with the first thing come to mind Be the One Bookstore you've heard of in that City
But you have to do your homework
Because when you don't wind up questions
There's undercover footage
In a video that's alleged to be from one of these secret antifa meetings in other words
But that's not really possible
Business for over
For two years
Possibility
It's not like it's supposed to
2017 Pacifica
It'll be completely laughable and discredited
Under normal
He was doing as a strong potential to lead to violence against left-leaning protesters
Easily tricked viewers will assume
Domestic Terror
This is one of the reasons why people have to be shut down
If you was doing some cigarettes gate of Journalism like into the potential political malfeasance of democratic
Are reporting on stories that were real inconvenience
To the left
Absolutely defend entirely is right
Continue doing that work
His career is just too full of
Complete fraud
Ultimately he doesn't care if what he puts outputs
People in danger
His misinformation isn't intellectual or abstract
He's lying in a ways that can directly lead to people getting hurt and that
Cannot be allowed to continue
Mikey
Inspire
Inspired by
Or something I don't know what the mechanism would be but like this
Is
This is unacceptable
One of our laws should have just been like
If you're doing grbl s***
No
Like real simple just like a grbl did this this in this that's bad
Don't do that if you do
I don't understand
Yeah
Clear and transparent b*******
Troubling
Not good because there's other s*** going on
Cialix
George Floyd's death
And trying to use it for his own political purposes
Really interesting the way he's taking
And using it to reinforce a narrative that he already had
Is not
Covid-19
We obviously.
So it is true that George Floyd tested positive for Coronavirus back in April
Autopsy
Do the covid-19 death count
Airports I can find coronavirus played any role in his death
Just assuming because he tested positive he was listed then as a covid death
Differently by different states
Spectre too sloppy
Muscle
Would have looked into this at all they would have found that the state of Minnesota released specific
Reporting covid-19
Back in April
If they looked into this
He might have a better understanding
Reporting form in Minnesota has multiple
The first most important section is about the underlying cause of death
This is part one and it set up as a sequence of causality
In one example they give the cause of death could be reported as a cute dress
For Tory distress symptom
Due to pneumonia covid-19
There's a descendant causality
Cause of death is like
The second section part to where the death certifier other significant conditions
Contributing to death
Not resulting in the underlying cause given in part 1
Possible
Does
There's another consideration to keep in mind and then Minnesota guidance.
The manner of death sometimes referred to as circumstances of death is also reported on death
In the case of death due to covid-19 infection the manner of death will almost always be natural
What are the other classifications of manner of death was homicide
Classification of homicide almost by definition
That's for being counted as a covid-19
In order for covid-19
Case where someone was intentionally insect
People shot this
That is a claim that Alex's asserting is fat
He needs to back that up and he absolutely can't do it which means he's making this s*** up
Yeah no I need anyting
I'm done with
Distractions about
Now it doesn't I don't care
I don't care what
We can't get distracted
So is mostly about discussing these distractions
Is the paradise unfortunately frustrating because of the nature of the thing we decided to do
No
I don't think the podcast where I just scream
Times when I've had to just say so
You're entitled to that
Voice in a point to make is that a lot of this stuff is distractionary
It's meant
Take focus and attention away from
These protests
That are growing
It's the same thing with attack
The tactic of Summer
Focusing on
Tens of thousands of people gathered
2chan to a speaker
Or make a point
The distraction everything and is always important
Do remember
What the Center focus
Your eyes to be taken off
Because otherwise you lose
Entire job is
To take eyes off
You know
So it is
It is
Unfortunately yeah yeah
We don't you know I mean
It is still important
To bring that up so I'm glad you did
At the same time
Alex is what he in
So Alex gets into this we talked about a black lives matter protest
What to do about Australia
This is the official backlight
Melbourne
The area
Pizza population
Allowed
Their job are there racist
First things first Alex's describing black people in Melbourne
To tell him about what happened to the Aborigines in Mowry
Don't have racism in Australia cuz it's all white
There is literally no other way to get those comments
Example of white nationalist
Alex says that Melbourne Police Department is mostly minorities
I've no idea where he's getting that information from and I strongly suspect
He's making it up
I was able to find a 2008 analysis of the Victoria police forces which Melbourne is a port
Show a lot of diversity
Victoria police's predominantly in Australia
Police force
It has an over-representation of English-speaking
Can countries and under-representation of
English speaking minorities
In 2006 there were 9037 australian-born officers in the Victoria Police compared to
From northern African countries
25 from South African countries
And 17 from Southwest Asian ones
This is in contrast to 698 from other English
Countries predominantly from the UK
These numbers are low even when you look in terms of proportions of the population is still under representation
Today's staggering
The Great
It's almost like fashion
Just love being caught
I was able to find another analysis from 1979 with showbiz
If we add the Australian and British categories together we find that all forces are between 94 and 98 +
Anglo-Saxon
Some progress has been made in 2008
Still showing
Kind of under-representation that was marked
Pain in the 1979
Analysis
Probably unlikely since 2008 it's become majority-minority
Ludacris ride
But I mean that's also
Like
The incremental approach isn't cut
Run it has
Cut it cut it
We're still at 85%
Incremental should probably
Not the best way to approach thing
Incremental things that are solving the wrong problem
The way to go
So I can play
Minorities
Also it doesn't really matter
Delores Jones Brown the founder of the center on Race crime and Justice at the John Jay College
Criminal justice
Accountability project
There's a bit of naivete that if you have an officer of color that officer Canton Rachel profile
And I think all the evidence suggests that it is not the case
John Brown goes on to express
It's eating places primarily likely a result of the culture of police departments as opposed to the individual
Officers
The police accountability project also cited a 2004 National research Council study which said
There is no credible evidence that officers of different racial or
Make background perform differently during interaction
Citizens
Simply because of race or ethnicity
If you're going to have a police department it's good to have them not all these
One demographic group
Simple Act of increasing representative diversity is going to solve the underlying problems of police Sevilla
Directions
You're very naive and it's not the
Primary problem to be solved
I mean the police are trained now
As a military
Yes send an army into wherever it
The soldiers are just because they're different you know
From different backgrounds doesn't mean they're not all trained to be soldiers
Who take orders
And do that same s*** it's it's
It's the fact that they are essentially an invading Force
It is the the bottom of the bottom line
Salting the wrong
Problem
No
Good
You shouldn't have
Complete
Uniformity of background or
I need your age group or gender
I don't I don't think that's good
What is follow me people who are allowed to be librarians
We're Polynesian
When that be weird things that be like a Pokemon world where everybody is
So in the next place we learn
Physically interesting cuz I see is ours trying to ship
Black lives matter and societal unrest paper narrative
Into being
I think is interesting because it doesn't
It doesn't work for the way Alex categorizes villain
But he's trying to get the stupid thing to do
Black babies
Your babies
Your ass up to
Run buy online
Everything's going on that we've not
When did The Big Mac
Yep
To like
Sidelines Soros Soros Meritus
I don't I don't I don't think it works very well I don't think his audience is going to be able to
Follow the bread
But all I heard is all I heard in my head was just a voice
Voice Yukon
Stop stop
I know this feels good but it don't
Alex at the beginning of this episode was bragging about I was going to take calls and take so many calls
Technical
Talkin ever to go
It's called
5 total something in that ballpark
First Call
Northern Ireland
And this guy
Not good
Nevada terzin researchers
Star video
Chopped explaining all the crap
Is true that Obama
Executive order
He presents
They would all be done
You're absolutely right at
Tubidy
Notice our Fox News
The troubles he was
Ganttic breach of the First Amendment
Caribou Properties broadcasters on propaganda and contact
Far worse than Twitter Banning someone because it's government forcing speech
I care about is pretending
The tution always just been a costume
Principal
Expression of his anger at an increasingly integrated and connected
We're people like him don't have a monopoly on social capital
That's all that's going on it's pathetic
Why did you throw the hammer into the TV but the nice man was talking he was telling us all doubt if
Feel
God dammit
Government-controlled media First Amendment
What what
Because of this Northern Irish British nationalist I will
Trump to take over the media
Another thought is very dumb
Vitamin Water
People say enough
The card
Is enough
The check and then I watch your show every day religiously
Incredibly
Illuminati card game and protect these cards are acceptable
Godzilla tires
There's a card in the deck it's titled enough is enough which depicts a guy yelling
But there's no indication
The effect of the card is to clear out all Zack paralysis or freeze effect that have been played against you
You can't move your plot forward in that turn
The angry yelling person on the card is basically depicting someone who's had enough of these that paralysis or freeze effects 04
Because enough is enough
It's a ridiculous stretch to pretend that this is Trump or that there's any kind of
Meaning in here
I was perusing these blogs that make these arguments
The same people who speculate about this also claimed that was a prediction of the Boston
They also claim the Deep card predicted the Deepwater Horizon spill
Exxon Valdez spill happened prior to the game's release
Everybody saw after the Exxon Valdez
Steps to make sure that this never occurred to
So stupid
Of the
Conspiracies
That
AR
Floated
I wish you'd just
I mean it's frustrating and boring but
Sometimes like all right let's do this
A time traveler
Ifucking wish
Cut out this clip
It starts talking about Steve Jackson games
A lot of stuff looks like me either
Did this guy have time machine
F****** do that Alex get into improve its Steve Jackson has a time machine
Takes out a single verse to Target
He just pulls out
And here's how I'm going to prove exactly what this is
Alright Jackson angels are up there Angels be flying around anyways
Yeah I would love it it's like some kind of man in the High Castle
God
Anyway
Talking about some other news stories about the National Guard being
Not welcome in d.c. hotels
Void d.c.
Motel
1200 confirm
What do we say we don't want your
Find here
Corporations are we don't want police
We don't want military around Legos
Pulled all of it
That policeman
He want
We want
Students repeating inaccurate stories a trace back to propaganda campaigns Push by Trump social media Guy Brad parscale
The idea they were putting out
Which isn't true
Email the right-wing lawyers were misrepresented to clarify
We did not pull our product
From shells rather paused digital marketing activities as well
Show sensitivity for the tragic events of the United States
Generations of children of love playing with assessing our Lego City Line
Stanton or collection
Given the tragic events of the United States over the past 10 days we positive digital marketing assets that could be perceived as incense
If promoted at this time
Statement from Lego
We read the room
A company correctly recognized that now is not the time for
To come off as a little girl
They requested affiliate links they had advertising this product
Ad campaign for said products you can still buy them at the store
I want you probably still call this virtue signaling but it's pretty telling that he doesn't even know what the actual story is
You only knows the fake outrage bait version that he's picked up from fellow right when bulshit artist
And what he says the left is mad that they're not virtue signaling enough
Crystal like a list of random tweets
You got the left
You got a few tweets I didn't recognize any of the accounts
Left everything in a meeting
Leftist online whatever
Coffee
Triggered by people having a position on Twitter
Accounts with like $100
It takes scouring
Utah National Guard out of proportion
DC mayor Muriel Bowser requested that Trump remove Federal and Military troops have been sent to the city because they were
Absolutely not going to lead with the escalation
She was cleared the troops could stay in the DC Hotel
DC will not pay for them
To be housed
This led to them being relocated from one hotel to another
US Army Master Sergeant W Michael
Ksl-tv
Some National Guard responders were quartering in hotel accommodations which had pre-existing contractual agreements with the district
Out of respect for existing agreements those facilities
Do service members have
Relocated
What is ultimately comes down to
Is the DC already a contract with these hotels for National Guard members who responded
Thanks covid-19
This contract did not apply to guard members who were there to respond to the protest
DC didn't evict anyone
Did you stop payment for the housing because they hadn't agreed to take it on and as a result the effective guard members had to find other lodging
There's no Scandal here there's no implication
The third amendment like Twitter has been having fun with
It's just a bureaucratic billing issue
Alex is missing
As well
200 was the number of National Guard members from Utah that had to move hotels which Senator Mike Lee was very upset about
12:00 was the number of d.c. National Guard members who were activated
Is declaration that DC wasn't going
5100 people who work
200 numbers only relevant cuz bike leaves from Utah made a big deal out of this
Play the victim
My really embarrassing way
I don't see I don't see instances of like
Governors of other states who had their guard activated now
I know where we're at
Whatever
But he's got a wine if you're
We come
Towards the end of this episode
And
I've got to say
I have one piece of bad news
Something else that happened
Bad news out of the way
Corrected Alex
How awesome is bolsonaro
So Alex is finally figured out how to pronounce bolsonaro
Just took the day off Ali's doing office
This f****** how can you praise bolsonaro even the right-wing that dropped bolsonaro up and Brazil is like
Murderer because his son Alex at ePacket
Keep our soundboard despite anything
Bolsonaro Captain called Brazil Trump
So Alex just guys got to be awesome
You don't know anything
Next clip
Sphynx is saying Outlaw the Democratic Party
Nice
Neglected garbage needs to be
Capri's Pizza
Outlawed
So I'm sure Alex just thinks he's calling for the political party he doesn't like to be outlawed which is
Liberalism doesn't mean liberal or democrat or anything like that
I don't have much love to quote encyclopedias so here's the definition of liberalism from Encyclopedia Britannica
Quotes
A political Doctrine
Protecting and enhancing the freedom of the individual Central problem of politic
Liberals pepper
We believe that government is necessary to protect individuals from being harmed by others
But they also recognize that government itself can pose a threat to Liberty
The philosopher John Locke came up with
Concept is defined as a system based on
Contract
Where individuals have rights
The government's
Cannot vile
When Alex gets on Aaron argues that liberalism
Should be outlawed for a totalitarian
For one that's not based on the concept of individual liberty
I'm sure that's not what Alex means no idea what the words he says mean
That is what he's advocating
And it makes it all the more hilarious when I tell you this Jordan
Less than a minute before he did that himself a classical liberal he says this
Don't say don't say I have a don't say anything
This introduces
Kind of what I would describe as
A segment where Alex
Tries to play with words
A little bit
He goes on a pond run
Already box
This liberalism
That he's he's bragged about his vocabulary and then misuse the word liberalism
His words are fine a
Oligarch
Oh no
A mob
Mob rule
Is the role of government
Some people
Wow
That was a perfect
Okay look at the war called
Definition of an oligarchy
If you can solve Merriam-Webster definition of oligarchy government by the few
Which is kind of the opposite of Marlboro
What happened here is that Alex didn't realize was actually reading the definition of the word aqua
Until he was halfway
Through it
How many just decided to cover his tracks by saying it goes off
It's an easy mistake to make when you dump repair
Just talking out of your ass
I mean go to work to do looks
Similar
I'd like to figure out exactly what happened here and I did get to the bottom of this
It's just reading the definition of autocracy from the top of its Wikipedia page
In the middle of it
Greek in College Point out
The end of these two words are a sure sign
Walker cnz crossy
Which comes from the Greek
Root word in democracy or aristocracy or theocracy
It means power in Greek which is reflected in
Each of these terms
Up social structure
Democracy is where the crotches or power is rooted in the demos
The people
Aristocracy has no power in the aristos or the excellent
Meaning the power lies in the hands of the elite
Theocracy is where power is rooted in the idea
Forgot
Control Society
Conversely
Oligarchy and xanarchy
Which comes from the word Arco
Which means to rule
Words that end in R key typically reflect the type of rulers there are in assist
He comes from
Switch translates to the few
It's just descriptive of a system where these few rule the money
Aristocracy meritocracy or theocracy or subsets of oligarchy systems because the rule of the few
Take many different forms
Depending on how
Find a particular society Alex has a big vocabulary to Dan Bon
No other languages
Who even speaks English
Pictures of War
Is what you're doing
Examples of this linguistic patterns
Or the apps
Since of a ruler
Which is a system where rulers and officials are selected from a random sampling of the population
More of a system where the ruler
Monarchy is a system where there is power in the hands of an individual
If you want to break down more stuff and words
It's important to remember that words mean things when the system is described
Crotches or crossing
It's disgusting
Power derives from
In democracy the source of power is
The people chakra see it's God
It's the mob or in Greek which is
For a crowd or the rebel
When the system is described with a word ending in
Narco
It's describing who actually is in a power position
Oligarchy has a few
In positions of power
The king or queen in a position
The power
In a position of power
Basic linguistic distinction
It's staggering
For 20-plus years
Eddie doesn't grasp this very Elementary think about how political systems are
Really f****** sad and probably not a sadist pretending to know the definition of oligarchy oligarchy
Clock receiver
Mistake mid definition
Pretending
That's a pathetic level disregard for accuracy
I'm honestly not very surprising
That's just
Is comically bad
For anyone
Serious about Alec
Exercise
Kind of think that Alex
Might be right
That's the kind of thing that I would really like them to understand
He has no idea what he's talking about
Almost all the time
And sometimes really f****** steps
He doesn't understand the definition
Articles
This one business pretty
I enjoy it because I also really enjoy the opportunity to explain
I think it's really interesting the way that these
Suffixes two words
In terms of what
They're describing and how
You can find these patterns within the word
Yeah it's important if you want to understand
What is the difference
Between democracy
What is the fundamental difference
Glitches
If you understand it it helps you understand
What things mean
Recognized on a fundamental level first of all the wrong word
Oligarchy is a narc
Apocracy is a cross
I don't know he's just very sad
He's very very very very
I do
Applaud
Sorta
Because he goes to commercial
He comes back
And he admits
He sort of admit
Bet he got the wrong word
Ofloxacin
In the room
The people or the intimidation of legitimate authorities
How to speak from Wikipedia but he's still not
Correct
A clock received derives from polybius
Who was a Greek historian
The term was adopted by Latin
Millie comes from Greek
Alex wasn't just randomly reading that definition
You in the middle of a rant about how oligarchy is actually incorrect definition
I'm glad he's coming but it completely invalidates the prior
He was talkin about
Straight to cover his ass here and it's silly
Create the
But worried about
Historically accurate definitions of these words
Completely Escape Alex
Bruin Anarchy or absolutely not synonymous but is acting as if they are
It's entirely possible for an anarchist system
To be implemented in a stable way and has literally nothing to do with the signature features of ox
Typically autocracy is not a functional system of Affairs
The characterizes a. As opposed to any kind of stable working order or
Examples like the Salem witch trials and racialized violence like lynch mobs it looks like in real life
It's pretty easy to understand
It's just not a sustainable system
Reconstruction Era South workout perfect it just doesn't work
A great typically do not grow out of an arc
Many theorists believe that oligarchy is actually the natural result of not rigidly controlled social
Renovations as they grow
Eventually the size of the system will be too large for any kind of effective direct representation
Naturally develop
This is the basis of Robert Michels Theory called the iron law of oligarchy
Scro
Oligarchy
I'm not sure if that's accurate but that's something that a lot of people point to
It's a it's a pattern
It's a pattern displayed out whether or not you
Say that they
You know reasoning behind it is
Found itself
A repetitive thing
Making things up and trying to cover his ass because he realized
Mickey was wrong
Because he's too proud
He's such that guy you know that everybody knows that guy who no matter what
What I was saying was actually
And you are still 100 but I have a very big
Barry Beck
But now.
Who's dating the word
Too proud
We come to the last two
They're sort of around the same subject
Because we get to explore
The subject of
The chessboard
Alex did not intend to get back to the subject
Encircled the call
From a former accountant
Is not so thrilled
Alex's is worried
Send messages to Demons
And that brings me to something
Concerns me and that is something that your
Has been panning doodle
And putting as the central Focus instead of you multiple times now
And I recognize that
That could be used as something that devudu who done
Surya and
People who have ancestor altar
It concerns me
Chess board
They're playing both sides
That's not how you play chess
You dumbass.
Do I thought
Kaiser in
Flowers
Delivered
I was setting us up
What a joke
We'll put some flowers out here
Execute people what's the
Message
Is all about
People
All came together
Expressing
He just
Show some random stuff to put out there
B somebody would
Start a campaign of accusing him
Of doing some kind of a satanic
And then he could be like
No this is just a debit
Comes back to bite him in the ass
I wanted people to bring what they brought through it and she did
And now you're all flustered and what help
It's a joke the next Kaiser sent him flowers
What is it
Is that cuz
Beck's in Southaven
Explain
Process
First of all you do have the black and white and we know that that's been used
The checkerboard
Offering to whatever
Or whatever is demons whatever it is
Pieces flowers
Of course
The flower or the Stevens
The most
Disturbing thing what is of course
Placed on the altar
So if you are an accomplice
Be something that you would use
Specifically
To gain the favor of
Demonic
Make me a little nervous that it's on
Invocations or anything like that
I'm really bummed
Alex
I didn't mean it
You can't even just accept a vulnerability of the like
Look you tried something a little creative creative
Okay I've got these flowers Mexican to me
My dad there's the chessboard
Can't do that what you're Alex because it's a tacit admission that you fail
Yeah
He's presenting that he still succeeded cuz he made something
Or whatever if you do things out but I accidentally
Exclamation
Inform her about why demons like
Sure
How does human sacrifices
That's my guess
Toilet
Disconnected broadcast not straight out of the park
Alex
Another
When on the bus
Let's just let's take a look at the win column for Alex's
25000 million in the win column zero in the loss
Spectacularly disconnected from reality
Important stuff that are going on in the world right now
That I might
Little bit
Bar in the direction of
Teachable moment understand
I mean the way I was lies the way
He tries to feign expertise about things
Like a moment that I really think
The most
Shocking for me
About the Bill Gates running a speed narrative
Because that's where you can see him like
He is what he did
It's almost like Kim
Resisting for a moment be giving into the momentum
Of his own narrative
I'm kind of going so if you look at it that way cuz
Knoebels makes it seem like he's
Powerless over the
But I also know
I'm not happy for him
What's the best excuse
I think it's just kind of sad
Until then
Local charity in your neighborhood please donate
Bail fund
Please donate to supplies anything that you can
I have a
Vocabulary
Alex
In color