Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for knowledge B
We are the bad guys
Jordan Jordan
Cuz it's actually involved with something else so
Is it dating
My bright spot Nana after putting more than 100 hours into Final Fantasy 7
I have finally 207
Stupid
Verizon
I know lot of listeners responded well to my love
Narrow base game but it's
Just fantastic
Really interesting end
Lovely done sidequest
Story. It's very rare that I give someone a recommendation it turns out well I'm glad that
What is Acacia
Spotify
Seltzer Jordan because then everything
But I'm focused
Part of that is because I pack up everything
100 Brussels
Right now 69
Great for goodsgreats awesome
We did everything we a set out to do. Is that it also comes with
It's a really exciting thing and that is
There is a new entry in the top 5
We've encountered an 80 plus seltzer
March bars breweries coming in at number 1
Done with the flower power
Number two is still aha black cherry coffee
Is it 84
And then another entry at the spot
Aspartic
It is been taken
The 3 spot
Pedal Power
They have one that's an Elderberry White
Tea Flower
That sounds amazing about it I don't know Bob
Encountering it but I took a
I'm just
Hyping this up as soon as good as I think it is
I need to go to the store and get more of this weather is as
I didn't think it would beat the black cherry coffee
But it it still
Number for in Lacroix limoncello rounding
Two bubbler passionfruit a great run
Man that's what's that Elderberry White
Flower
Wow that sounds like something that I Woodland creature in
Fantasy
Haha
So yeah it's I think there's a trend that I'm starting to notice and I think it's somebody's th ones maybe or
More my speed
Complexity in Arabic
Past 100
Got a new entry in the top 5
Hell yeah
What day
Big news
Exciting to celebrate
Little thing to go over today
So are we
Stop
After the show
There's a little bit of a trend of fecal
Names
But I so appreciate
I'm a policy wonk
Identify
I need to save Vic pooper
Adam Sandler reference coffee
Text Rachelle
McDavid be
But
Is to rise above
Yes they deserve special recognition
Rebecca
Aah
Who has wonderful hair you so much
You are now a raptor princess of the highest order
And also I think I may have already given a princess
Laura W thank you so much
You're also a raptor princess
Or start until you're brilliant
It's over for Humanity
You're Beautiful song
They're coming for your balls
It's all over your God
Very few people
When they are
At juice
Are you so much
These Gents
You can take that generosity
Wonderful as well
Sweetheart appreciate
Hindi
Like I said Jordan
This episode because Monday
I turned on the show and
Shroyer
Come in and do some of the show later but
I don't know what I'm doing.
So I was pretty worried that we have nothing to really cover for this episode so Tuesday comes around 29
And I turn it on
Stuff
Goodnight is bro
And he's
He said
Alex is going to be in a little bit later Steve pieczenik was going to be on
Ozark well alright
Got to find out what she has to say about things that
Awful
Broad
Ignore all the time to David nights I was staying
The end of the first hour Alex shows up
In the last segment of the first hour
And so we begin our investigation and exploration
When Alex comes in and actually I will say
Disappointed
There's something else that goes on in this episode
Fantastic
And definitely worth our time
So we start off with Alex teasing
Although
Is you know
He starts off with like an intention of what the show is going to be at 9
Almost done
It's what I want to do today
Open the phone
Stop the balance
The next
Make your phone calls
On the subject of what's on
So Alex is going to take phone calls hours
Three phone calls
He doesn't start taking calls for another hour
Retakes
A couple calls
There's a reason for this
He will later stipulate
Okay
So you are
Alex
Call Africa
He talks about this phenomenon that we're seeing people getting hit by cars at protest
Nationalist
Video video
Throw themselves on the hoods of people's cars
Wow
Says oh look
Someone tried to Ram them down and killed
Repeat Charlottesville
A big steak
Drama club
Entomology
Kontrolfreek
Repeating
The same.
Do a lot of
A lot of people are shooting themselves 40 or 50 times in the back before they talked to the
The cop true
Sometimes in the back
So I would say that this is a really interesting for Alex drank contextualize and hand wave away a bunch of videos of protein
Cars left and right another way to look at it is it since the unite the right rally
Celebrate
And what you're seeing likely contains at least a kernel
So I don't know what else is doing
But here videos describing a slightly different
Stances
Some of them are police to attempt to drive through people or intentionally open their doors are passing the protester in order
Other civilian
Consider driving it to people
Pictures of individual case
It's kind of hard for me to speak about them in a blanket sense
Please one is a little bit different
People isn't attack
That's where I'm at
In the last week or so I can find instances of protesters being hit by cars
Chattanooga Jackson five-year-old Robert who died after being struck by a car in
Course the weather the incident to Denver from the end of May
It says he's been happening quite a bit
I can't get into the specifics of all of those cases but what I can't do is discuss one recent instance of this that is very cool
Illustrate
An awful Alex's
On Sunday night in Seattle 31 year old man drove his car directly toward a group of protesters who stopped
Wendy's car stopped some protesters naturally started hitting his cars
You tried to run people over
Nearest open driver side window falls to the ground haven't been shot by the man who's driving
The car
Dude gets out of the car brandishing a gun
You try to escape by a sort of mix
Again with the crowd and ultimately subdued by protesters
Been forced to shoot someone with carjacking at sounds
Doesn't match with the video
This is intentions were to run
People
Wait to see what information eventually comes out on this front
This is disgusting stuff going from Alex
The First Amendment right to protest
Alex knows that
I hope it eats them up inside
Because he's Mox
I'm surprised that he's not going with the false flag and somewhat
Like refresh
It's too easy to go with the false flag now protesters are jumping in front of cars
I guess so but it's not really cuz that is.
I'll give him I'll give him at least one new wrinkle
It's not a new wrinkle
What are the difficulties of Alex's
100 different things
Depending on what the circumstances are you sure
The Claymore fake
Very frustrated
You know these last two days for us you've been pulling half right
Well too many processors been jumping in front of this car might make the argument
Maybe he's not as committed as you really pretend
Come on Alex, I just
Floating theories floating Theory
Alex has an explanation for why
Sitting in the first one
Montego Bay
When you go to break
Reason you should
Whether or not it's sold as a toothache
I find it
Difficult
To believe that Alex had a tooth extracted and it's not affecting his speech at all
It's possible but it seems really weird
If you don't have no swelling
You could get a you wouldn't want to be doing a ton of talking
Dry socket is shoes or kinds of reasons
2BR advisable
He's been practicing his neck so big
He's been chewing cotton balls in the back of his molars you met with 9
It keeps accidentally swallow
My perspective surgery take a day
I think maybe he's not lying
Waze back
Podcast I used to do I had a root canal
And then I came immediately
No s*** like I it is possible that my voice is pretty altered because
Massive swelling
I don't know anyway
Just take the day off man
Take the day off all right
Yes I'm not sure what Alex thinks about
Kennedy
John
I'm not sure what Alex's take is on the assassination
It's a conspiracy
Maybe
I don't know what is specific take on it is because Rodger stones in the book about it
Talked about a bunch of
You Howard Hunton
The bums in whatever
But like
I've not really heard a coherent version of what he thinks the conspiracy is especially not want
Consist
I think
He's going to come out with
John F Kennedy
Jump into the bullet
And that's why it was so magic
Straight into the bullet
This next destination
It doesn't make sense
I know that work for the CIA
Eia.gov
The real quick
Miss talking about memorandum 7277 is the
Cold war-era
Department of War
We talked about it
Just to clarify
You know I don't think you're all of them
But he was really behind in this world
Did by end of the gun
What was the last straw
Play sad
Meant well
What
It was behind
What's opening up China
Plan
But he was actually opposed
So complex who would have been a lot better off
Okay
Expect Alex's Angleton OB that's some good guys in the government decided to stay because
Designated the president
Confiscation that was the last straw for
Whatever and
Alex could say that's complex and sophisticated what it actually is
And convoluted
Eia.gov
Talking about memorandum 7277 being real
Plan to disarm the citizens
It's a link to a CIA posting in their reading room of an issue of the minutemen's newsletter On Target from 1960
Which presents 7277 is a plan to disarm the public
And it's from the Minutemen so whatever
The Minutemen
Anti-communist
They're not talk
Think about it.
Right it was one of the things in their newsletter that I
It doesn't mean anything
Is assassinated in November 22nd 1960
Memorandum 7277 was written
And released in September 1961
So I guess what Alex is saying is
Major
Destroy the world
And this was the last straw for the good guys?
Who killed JFK
This memorandum which did nothing
Succeed in the Escalade in the Cold War
Good guys
Got together on the
Plan to kill the president
They're not even doing it together they both
Just happened to come upon him as a hundred percent they showed up and they're both
Right on either side of a
Impressively are always at least ten years behind
Planning to kill JFK before using
I could be
I don't know if they were behind in the 60s
I think God
Increasingly behind Sussman schedule
This is sloppy even for Alex like what makes absolutely no sense
Keeping a low profile
You come in there and slap Alex around or sing this kind of foolish
This is embarrassing
Alex
It's on the next mentioned that he wants to take calls but he's trying to get
People from a null set
And you'll hear that here
What I want to do today
I want to open
The phones are
Who's walking
To tell their story
People that work
Black matter
The call-in
Your story of what you witnessed
Good luck with getting those collars from your audio
Taneous info Warrior and
Former antifa member communist
So do you like to talk
And I don't believe him for a second on this one
Also when I open the phone
For leftist
Really do think prompts
I really do think
Abolishing the police
Is a good idea
Think that
Temperature
You seriously disagree
I think there's a distinct
I'd like to respectfully hear from you
I'm not going to be respectful
Rank disrespect but I need respect from you
Imagine anybody listening to the show
I think one of those even then
One of those
Pretty much
Exclude the other two right
Like you can't be leftist who really believes in abolished
Sing the police and think that the Democratic party has your best interest
Mind
They have no interest in abolishing the Democrats
The black-and-white simplistic version of what's going on
Infowars land
Sort of requires that just so I can see how
For you
That makes no sense
Heart of Darkness
So it doesn't slip Alex talked a little bit about
A little bit David George Floyd
You can kind of sense a lot of Alex's
Universal feelings about situations like like these and then also him starting
To get in line with
What I assume is going to be a lot of what the right-wing has to say about this
With wings
This is
He's dead
Doesn't sound like it
Five of them
To feel guilty about anything ever
Just consistent to Alex Jones
Pathology
Essentially
Leaning towards
Good person
Or whatever
Seems to be the end
You seem a bit more than some of the right-wing news
Sources
It's just it's a cheap
Cheap Trick
Like whether they're right or wrong which I don't believe a lot of things in particular
But whether they're right or wrong is irrelevant
A2dp larger situation
I'm so great
But like they even have almost a
Time stamp on it where it's like okay week after the the murder
Will people will be emotionally distant from it enough for us to be like
All right he was obviously leaving guy right now that we're all mad and we're all done with that let's just
Get together and realizes the cop should be able to kill
Earlier on
Try and say now's not the time to politicize things will let you know if we're if we're able to pull that off
Cheap either way let's be disingenuous yeah
A story that is actually fairly
Isn't Dad so it's not as tragic as it could have
Ended up being
Bad
Alex has a perfect example
To demonize All Pro
Video
He doesn't stop
Shoot them in the head
Satisfaction
Skin on the face for your TV viewer
He is a he
Shot a man
Stop.
Celebrating
You know what
Try to run him over when it did
He had a heart attack and died in Charlottesville
Two again
Create the Civil War
People on Highway
So this is the situation out of
What does
The name of the city Alamosa in Colorado
I found a video that was released by a local news
Absolutely does not look good
Looks like this guy James Marshall
Way out of line absolutely
Any shots
Yeah he's way out of f******
King lies
0 contacts
12 protesters in a small town called Alamosa intersection at a crosswalk
A black truck
The truck pulls up to drive through the intersection
There's a distinction without putting any of the protesters in danger
He is at a complete stop in from the video forward a little bit but not anyone
Silver or heard anyone
That's not cool
Appreciate someone doing
There's a big difference between that and someone speed in towards
He's coming through the intersection you see a guy appear to shoot him through the window
Amanda guy
So f***** up mess
Honestly I don't know all the details about the situation at this point since the investigation is still ongoing
The shooting has been arrested and charged with multiple crimes including attempted murder
I've not seen any indication that anyone is calling in a year out because
What is audience
Or he basing it on a couple random tweets that is interned found which mean nothing
I'm not entirely sure this is a tragic situation
Like I said
The guy who got shot isn't dead and that's great
Positive
I've not heard anyone say this guy's a hero or that this is
Hooray
No absolutely not
Consider this but I can't find anything
You can you can justify property
Nobody on the left
At these protests
Whatever
Condone that
I can't imagine
And Heather hair didn't die from heart attacks
Alex's
As a way of trying to
Make it better
They ran over over
Intoxicant
Right
So
That's all bulshit
It's like it's going to allow him to completely write off
Almost every
Sort of protest
But it'll work for his audience
Right now it's going to be
There will always be a what about forever
30 time for a while
Is first color that is presumably an ex leftist
A little bit nervous
Called in several
Since I start
Listening in 2011 and I ended up hanging up
Because of the long wait
But I was
It's really rather
Pleasantly surprised
How long I didn't have to this time
So first red flags
Not sure exactly
How's this
Works
Deeply involved in stuff prior to 2011 or whatever
Then she said something else
My last
The peace and joy
This movement
3 when we were
Country was Obama
Estimated maybe she wasn't that investigator all that she doesn't remember what f****** countries
He was protesting against those bombing
Massive red flags
Anybody
Claim speed
The moment that we go to absolutely aunt
And then you're like well we lost this one
I guess that's kind of ridiculous
Yeah so you have a situation presented themselves as
Annex person of Alaska whatever
All right you don't count
Whatever leftist credentials you think you have
You don't
Another caller
Don't think this guy's a person is much better
Tanger Outlets
Reliant
People
Hanging around those people just
I woke up
16 years old I knew that was
Wasn't they
The real thing you know I
High School
Here's the deal
Occupy
Right
How on the left disgusted by occupy
I don't know about that they were doing so much they were
Whatever
This is
Kind of collar that you're going to get called again when you put out these sorts of
Like this is the person I want to talk to
Ridiculous
Voted for Obama
Country and I
And it was
Media
Talbots
We're coming out
Uber
Contradict
What immediately
Yeah I know
So that's
Exactly
I lost my mind I literally lost but I didn't jokingly lose my mind it was gone
Yeah it's something that you could passively watch wants if you're not thinking you're high
Like you could get through it be like 10 and that road is a real
Alarm Bells go off unless you're
Are you like hold the f****** phone if you see me 20 times
You know what to say
Is good as Avenger
I will later
Bona fides are that you voted for Obama first and what's going on here
Cold callers is just
This is what you get
It's it's comical
Yeah
Baby
Jupiter toe into something slightly Democratic Party
God dammit
Weird
I am now most afraid of are anybody anytime
I did some research I'm like I shut off I'm done
I'm out on whatever you think research is
Is amounts yeah yeah it is
Climate we're watching YouTube videos and
Reading qanon Post got to be a little bit careful
Clip Alex from calls to
Complain
About GoFundMe
Total Wine
Stop looting
Is black
Thousand dollars on here
GoFundMe
Soaring 277 first family
But don't worry
$30
Okay
GoFundMe base Community Support
Purple to scams
Police release
The statement themselves warning that there were multiple fake fundraisers for David Dorn
And according to a June 3rd article in Fox News
Police say none of the pages have been authorized by his family
Authorities are in the process of taking them down
The GoFundMe page that Alex is referring to that is under $50,000 donated to it is actually one of the pages
It's listed as an example of such a scam fundraiser
That authorities are trying to get removed
In an article on the website of KMOX out of St Louis
Trying to stop scammers as also birth
Virtues
Donated $50,000
The family to help in this hard time
Backstoppers is an organization that provides aid for families of police firefighters and paramedics who were killed so they have
Work already in place
I'm not certain that this amount covers all their expenses or anything like that but it's likely relevant factor in them not to crowd
It's worth all of their system
I want to present this as a case of no one caring about David Dorn but in reality
This is a situation where a bunch of people
How to know I deal with the reality of the situation is so
Fraudulent crowdfunding campaign didn't make enough money
Nut yeah that's a weird thing to do
Yeah
The official George Floyd GoFundMe page has raised almost 14 million at this point but
So what
I mean I don't know you have 14 million dollars isn't worth
Human life so cute
If you had five children
Expenses that are needed for helping them
There's a possibility
Probably
At least
Some of it is going to go into charitable
Causes
See that is like the family May 14th
There will be plenty of things.
So
Maxscholar
Pretty pretty impressive
All say
I don't know if I don't know if I agree with everything The Scholar says
Restart
Pretty good
MattyB
America
Black people will never
Because of what
We went through
America
That's really was
Call Danelle
Do do bad things that we going through
Texas verse 810
Course you haven't
Opposing or trying to block it
A hundred percent
Clearly to sipping a drink that's that's something still in there it's true
That's suspicious
Yeah
Also a tax for 10 years is not the same
The problem
Has been attacked or destroyed for generation
And more importantly I suggested this or is
You believe for a second that people like Alex who think affirmative action is a brutal attack on whites
We hear Trump come out and see the black business owners don't have to pay taxes
Globalist reparations or some s***
How to make this up because he's eating
Any other Filipino response to the very real point of dollars make
Decides to make something up
Haven't heard about that
$100,000 tomorrow and Democrats block your mouth doesn't sound.
Another caller
This caller is apparently
Well you sound like
The movie
Onion rings
You're going to eat anyway
So this caller
Is
You know
Sub
Onion ring with an open molar are you shiting me that is going to release date
You're going to get dry socket
Is Santa real
So this caller goes on and this
Infowars
Panda
What happened to the old
Firepower
I'm very very racist because we
More crew
Michelle's very popular
We just have them
Suspend that
Election
We got a big
Problem
Call Oso
And then
Show for a while
What is inherently
Real weird
Audiology
I'm engaging evil racist
Tell me tell me more about what I did
Call Jack
So
This caller who thinks they're pulling a stunt accidentally kind of highlighted a bit of proof that Alex is making stuff up to cover his
Racist ass
Stopping the show Firepower which featured his only
Will Johnson
Alex claims that he stopped doing that show because they
Find the crew it's the clue thing
But in his defense
Actually disproves
Show started
After Firepower ended
Whatever crew barnes's using easily be handling Firepower so the crew excuse just doesn't work
For some reason Alex did not value Firepower as much as he values the possibility
Of doing another show
Gets worse
The other host of Firepower with Tom pepper
If you go to Bam. Video you'll see an entire section of a site dedicated to top and is dumb blog National file
Will Johnson
America first
Which there are no leaks
No
Will Grey
Will still has his own YouTube channel
There's absolutely no reason that itself produced
Contact Astilbe platform
I'm not saying this is proof of being racist
Definitely calls into question the argument that he didn't have a crew to keep well around
Memeworld Tommy Robinson David Icke
Kaitlin Bennett
And those are just third-party produced content
It's really suspicious that will Johnson doesn't have a page himself
It could be a personal thing
I can imagine how it sucks to work with
And honestly I think it would happen.
But one of these Trump rallies will Johnson was the guy who got interviewed by like CBS News
Whenever I interview
Border
Was really not good
And maybe will Johnson was like
Look it's going to be bad for me to express my opinion or whatever
Now I dissociate
Honestly my first thought
Less anything to do with Alex cuz I think he actually would
Really love having a problem
I do the whole thing with
Probably more an indictment of how racist Infowars viewers are
How could you can sustain the show that
Nobody
Watching because everybody
Alex is weird
I would say
Based on whatever you're putting in versus what you're getting out
Terms of
Ratings and all that stuff
Appalachia
If you just using it on a straight calculus
I don't see that being racist decision in and of itself
Kohinoor David Knight shows probably it's a little around forever so
To be allowed to be bad
Ranks or whatever
More notable to me that he doesn't have a page on band.
Estranged
The only thing that makes it
Released
Suspicious to me
Is this clear excuse
Doesn't work
You just keep people who think they were left us cuz they supported anti-war causes until the war started and Infowars
Very surprised for a leftist to call in and then provide Alex
The platform to advertise his other shows and do so very quiet
So in this next clip Alex gets another collar
About Mike Pence because kind too nice
Getting up in the
You know they
Couple things that I
Work together
Bill's you know
And I'm not saying he should
Talk bad about him
Anything but like
I just don't know about
Honestly I feel like
Paul was the
More people would come to his
Funeral
Call Marlon
You say yours
Another call
This is
He still wishes that buttigieg
The nice guy
Used to be on the last show what are you
The time of Benghazi
Really f****** do it
Obama just really wasn't saying that he met you know he was
He was just reading lines
First thing and it kind of just woke me up a little bit
Wow
Cool
Boy
Benghazi
Birtherism further ISM in Benghazi its unofficial
It seems to be a lot of people lost their minds around Benghazi
An incredibly full court press
The right-wing media
Underestimate a little bit in terms of like heaven
A real transformative effect
McDonald lot of people
Or if you were into birtherism
Maybe maybe you weren't that great
If you found that persuasive
Maybe that means it's you
The seventies is like cigarettes
She's probably fine
In this next clip Alex is trying to get to Steve pieczenik but
Is he couldn't even have a crew for his own show
Not good
He does actually complain that's like we get these people who apply and then they find out that it's Alex Jones and they say no
So instead of talking to Steve he doesn't
Entire segment
Pitching iodine
New one
Enough money
Percent off
Here is the new
New survival shieldx2 spray
33% off
Pricing
4 months of The Bella
Mason iodine
It's finally here
The harness the full power of
The ultimate
Feel good
It's so weird to hear them do like a straight
Weird how it has that testimonial
Ad copy
Very suspicious
Steve
Man
Messy. I missed him a little bit just because I think we should defend the government
Only fund the police may just want to break down the entire State Department pretty much everything about government
Police Department whatever
I just think that he usually is the kind of cuckoo really swings he takes
Are you cranky or sometimes he yells at Alex
Show that I can always appreciate interesting
Worthwhile
And I hear is Alex saying hello
Researcher
Just joined us
Break
With what we're witnessing
Singer George Floyd
Classic Coke
Programming Behavior
What they going to pull next year's with Steve has the situation going on in the world right now
The reason I say that with a smile is
She's not there
Neither of the leaders
Party
In the business
Station propaganda
In this case it's
Complete disaster
Or maybe that's not what's happening
Maybe your analysis is completely off
Popular
Various countries
Steve goes into a McDonald's has the worst Olive Garden
Never seen I can't believe these people are trying to do it
McDonald's
The breadsticks what are these what are these
Potato things that I'm saying
It's like saying If This Were agitation propaganda it's being done terribly the time you take the info
Yeah
Steve discusses this idea that you know
This is all just agitation propaganda
This case it's a complete disaster
Number one George
Is the wrong example
Nike element
How to do a fade
An argument is not good so far
If you commit a crime
You got it
It's not your fault
Super f***** up
Might also be evidence of
One listen to that station about George Floyd
This is a clear and flagrant example of
A very long time
For a lot of people
Demonizing George Floyd Mayfield important for the right-wing propaganda stink.
Really missing the forest for the trees
Every drug in the world on Emmet arrested as many times as you like in the past
It still doesn't really affect
How inappropriate the police action
And how they attempted to sweep it under the rug
Whether or not George Floyd was a good enough person not to be killed is the definition
Missing the point crucial for people like Steven
Because I'm sublevel
I think they have to recognize that the protest
Heaven results
That makes them very scared
The best trick to take NSYNC up is to attack the murder victim
But it's not going to be effective in any way
They can probably Harden their base up a little bit with this and make them feel better for hating the protest and protesters
I can't imagine anyone has anything other than
Like a complete disconnect from reality and if you want to play this game choose another person has been killed by the Pooh
Minneapolis
Situation
More
Realistically put Emma and Steve obviously couldn't
Say that about every single person
Steve's a dum dum this is stupid to try and use the veneer of
His like psych Warfare nonsense
To apply to the situation
Doris or whatever
It's even more.
Because that opens him up to okay fine
You think
Floyd is the wrong person
Who's the right person and then you go down the f****** list
And your point is made
That's one way to put it
So Steve believes that suspects are in the mix
Sociopath
Really unhappy create agitation
It would be a miracle
CI Elementary
The FBI
Some of the other elements within our
Which is
You guys explain
None of that means anything nothing
So now you want
I want to know
Now let me tell you who the leaders are
What
Reverend Alan Sharp Allen
If you haven't never will because his name is short for Alfred
What are you doing better
Write a book
About Sharpton
Tenn Tom Clancy
Anyway
Steve
Suggest something really troubling
Couchtuner
What did what begins kind of like
Sensibility
It's it's bad
Trump's wrong
What's wrong to say Instagram
You know what he may have been wrong but his job is to keep his mouth
Quiet
So they're expressing the Trump meme been wrong to want
What is f****** mouth
You don't want
Anybody in positions where they can make a difference to say something when something clearly wrong is being done
Until you retire and you've written a book
And then eventually say you were following of core make yourself feel better because nobody ever remembers the
The Nuremberg trials
Yeah I mean
I honestly don't understand perspective of like
Yes
The president was considering and talking about doing something
That would be dangerous
And it's completely wrong
But you should let him do it
Because he's
That's all you can you imagine them making that argument in any other circumstance
Absolutely that's what they do
Your f****** mouth
So much I hate him so much
Get to talkin about
Jared Kushner
I think this conversation could be described in one word
I want to get in the particular
Everybody needs
Issues it's a very
The inside he tells me that
Is literally the worst thing on the planet
When he brought in Georgia
He have to pay for
The issue now is he has
The
This is wild like four people over someone at respected expert on Alex
Feel like coming in and being like we need Lockheed Martin guys in the administration
This is beyond all of Alex's documentaries include like a little selected clips of Eisenhower's
Speech about the military guys doing
What is happening
Really bad
Unhinged
Look at
Let's get the Koch brothers I don't know which one of them is dead but bring his go so long to let him run everything
It's it's convoluted
It makes no sense
I mean I guess
Honestly
The problem is a little bit of
Sing something it's
Increasingly insect
Ultimately
Lead to the sort of friction
In reality if you were just listening to Alex's
Find would be a subject of the tides whatever is being
Talked about on the shows will literally come to the end of 1984
What
I wrote some documents somewhere that you could make an argument that
We've been wrong all along
Good really good
Right
Globe would be good if it was all under Trump
The problem isn't the method
Right there
Sure
So
Don't understand
No one
Is that
Trump gets things
No he doesn't
People like me and you
He eliminated regulation
Play
History
For the first time in our history
We have to use Russian rocket
Here's a president United States
Makespace
Muskingum said do it
You guys also
Rocket stove
Lunker
Stop being an office
That being said responded to a very fitting
Appropriate thing in that is
Presumably
Are sitting here talking about
Space walk board and the atmosphere entirely
Play and then we only have to fight Wars in space cuz everybody
Be first US launch in 40 years
The last one was in 2011
It's been nine years I have the last one was under Obama
The space shuttle Atlantis took
International Space Station on July 8th 2011
If you're including on man launches into this than Atlas 5
2020 out of Cape
Canaveral
Steve is trying to make you
Feels like Trump has gotten so little done that in order to make it seem like he's gotten a lot.
Is Stooges just makes it up
Yeah he's not done anything deregulation
And then
And you've got deregulation he's confirmed
Number of judicial appointment
History
Weird
Elon Musk
Get that rocket up because they have a secret
Because I'm sure you know this
They got a deal him and must actually get my
Year
They've already got robots
Step on the moon with a 3D printer
Tomorrow
Okay
Elon Musk
How many different album titles in the past
You try you know
Starship amazing
Sitting On the Dark Side of the Moon believe that her name of the song
Distance down the road kind of conversations about the possibility of building something on the Moon by
They're doing it now I'm going to need a citation on
We get a building on the moon give me Med beds
Also I
Do thing
This would be an international incident
Because space is not owned by United States
Is a Cooperative aspect
That kind of high-level information I mean unless
They were to listen to Alex Jones
Or notice
From the International Space Station
Alright
I think this is a load of s***
That is also kind of makes it
Also Moonraker
Totally real
Definitely
F****** around
America is going to release all these
Depressed Technologies Ezra
Technology
Dark Side of the Moon
Printers ready
They got a bunch of other stuff
Have mango
Enemies
They've already got the base
Not if it's already has already changed
Also there's literally no way
That Alex would be cleared to disseminate this information
If This Were something it was happening
President Yvonne bus
Look we got a base on the moon
Robots
Alex
Alex we want you randomly talk about this
You're stupid radio show after surgery
I need a bunch of onion rings
The protests have already
Accomplish more than
Trump has in office
Yeah that's probably
Will not
Get a moon base it will not end in a moon base
So This Is the End
Winestone uneventful end and then Paul Joseph Watson takes over for
4/4 hour
Half shift
I honestly because of the move and everything because Alex is out of Studio I was very seriously considering not doing it
I heard Steve was on
Like it's the siren song
Didn't live up to what I wanted it to be except for Alan Sharp
General courses
That's pretty great in the process finding the spring of calls
Was absurd banana
Episode
Or the correct length of an episode according to every other podcast in the world
Coconuts another hour out of this but am I going to
So
Cialix within his contacts
IC concerted effort
To try and invalidate
The protest what he thinks is the Coralville
He's missing the point entirely
But he's worried about it
Oh yeah
I mean the stuff about like really making a big deal out of
The guy who shot the guy in the truck
Another guy
Should be should have the consequences that
Yeah using that to be like
Guys in trucks or whatever
Kind of stuff is pretty pretty normal features
ICICI
In him
And
I think that's what he's expressing what he's trying to get these calls
From people who used to be an antifa
I think
You seems that signal project Veritas did this
We are b******* piece
Call her
No one does
Students
And the other thing with those calls to is
Trying to get the message that like
It's okay to come over here on this side
And unfortunately all the examples are people who
Or not
I was fine I didn't think Obama was born here I still vote for him because
You got to give it up to a guy who didn't even know who wasn't even born here become a
Who knows I don't know until then
We have website
It's knowledge fight.com
We are
We are out on Facebook
Find a local people
I'm Alan Sharp
Alex
In color