Air Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
MoneyGram
College
Little bit about
Alex Jones
Jordan Jordan
What up
Interesting Lee paradoxical Brightspot
Before we started recording
About how
I had some trouble with Xfinity
I got my papers in or whatever made by request for the transfer of service
And I got the date wrong
Answer instead of
Turned off my internet on Friday night
Because I need the internet in order to do the show
To the person
I had a Zen moment
Like
They were a parody of themselves such a bad job with customer service would like
Trying to give me what I needed as a customer
What is the point why be mad anymore what
Why ever why would I yell at this guy
Just sucks the shape of the universe
All is one and it's all garbage
Any decent person who worked there
So I just gave up
Fox News
I just gave up and last it's all you can do sometime
Yep that's basically it
How about you
Oh I have a combination dark spot bright spot
Today is both
All is one
Everybody outside
Open mic night playing at the ball
There's a lot of backstory there's a lot of boring
But anyways
Play with a little tennis ball some stickball bats we have a grand old time song playing in Bucks
Town and
Onmilwaukee like
Main Street Mill f****** Waukee
There was a guy who had strong proud boys
Oh I all black pants shirtless with terrible tattoos everywhere
Black Bandana for a mask
Horrible Bank
And he started harassing what look like a middle-aged woman
And all in full view of us at
There were plenty of people walking by and nobody was f****** do and everything
So we wound up running and chasing this dude off your stickball stickball game
Which was
Where is the m
That was our responsibility
That wasn't like a good deed for the day that was like that's what's expected in society
And I didn't get into a fight so I'm not in jail so we can still do the show everything's good
Home safely we helped her get into her daughter's car and they everybody was
Thursday of last week
Good day
This is a bit much
For me
Episode I might hit
A point where I'm going to express
Alex Jones
Like someone needs to
This is getting really dangerous
So first David B thank you so much juvenile policy want I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Next
You're now probably want
I gave you guys the gave you the chance
W
Appreciate that very much the first of all
What you are now it's
And easy spelled a l l y v e r
Technocrat
Heroin
Is freakishly large
Buttons
Bundle it up real nice put some gift wrapping on it and shut it off for a Christmas present today in the middle of June
Or a charity in your local area that helps people in need
Woodward
I wanted to bring something up cuz I got a couple of messages about this
Really helpful for me and I just want to give
A correction and slight topology in case this is something
The wrong way
I did not realize that I was using the incorrect term for indigenous people in Australia
You got on a recent episode
Out-of-date term
For that
I just wanted us out and
You know help me
Get a better understanding
And it's unfortunate
But it is a reality
There's always an opportunity to to here
Using his
I appreciate people giving me that opportunity and not that you know jumping down my neck
You are because
Life is learning
Axel and
That I didn't know before
Will do better job education system
Tearing particularly high on the list of things so
We don't we don't always get the correct everything
Start getting into the big narrative
Episode top story
And God this was a waste of my time
New York Undercover nurse confirm covid-19 criminal hoax
She's in the epicenter
The epicenter
The people didn't have covered and they were putting
Ventilators on the people in
Killing them
She has
The video
I'll just tell you that
That's what I'm for serves as is
Incubator
Do the research
We put out the Millions
Not man
So this video that Alex is reporting on was put up
Number of red flags
Not on this here story
Essential content of what she saying
Like in the video itself
And that's very active making this video that she made is a gigantic breach of patient rights to privacy
Yeah that's illegal
This point is something that is very medical professionals at
Very very mad
The unfortunate reality is that most medical professionals could come forward with horror stories and videos that would scare the s*** out of us
But I can't do to respecting their profession
Responsibilities about
And work with
Aaron decided to videotape people's medical charts and secretly recorded conversations with her colleagues which
He's going to get her license revoked
At least sued
Like it should be I can't imagine there not being legal consequences
A lot of the claims that she's making in the video or not supported by the actual video namely that the hospitals are just calling
Everyone covid-19 cases
Are knowingly killing people by hooking them up to ventilators
And that is only the patients have been given Hydroxycut
Since these claims are not established by her video itself unless to consider whether or not the person making the video
Motivation that they're not bringing up to make unfounded claims that I wish
Scooby-Doo vomit
So as it happened
Zouski
In 2018 she founded a group called
Wow
Get fun
Ton of information about this organization
Nurses for vaccine safety Alliance
She founded nurses and safety Alliance in October 2018
2018 nurses for vaccine safety Alliance
Does it pay the same entity they realized
Something Bland it's big enough
Investigator Jordans
Killing your children Without Borders
The business address for nurses are vaccine safety Alliance was just a FedEx mailing center in Florida
In November 2018 and was a guest on the show called Frieda Miser radio where she gives her bio
But that she quote
Natural Health sector is already
Anti-vax message
Interest in mainstream nursing or medicine
13 super weird that you didn't get involved in a New York Hospital when she's from Florida if she's kind of Apple
The type of medicine nobibi practice at this hospital he was going to end
Yeah that does Sprint has raised some red flags for me
Is one of a group of women CDC headquarters in Atlanta protest
Advisory committee on immunization practices
What are coming out July 6th
Call the undercover epicenter nurse is currently number one on Amazon
For pre-orders in the section
Critical and intensive care
Section pretty impressive participants at this Hospital the center of
Engaged stealthy undercover investigative work
All in a manner of a cup
Couple months
Suspicious
Nurse from Florida
Who responds to New York
To work in a heavily affected hospital then spends her time unethically documenting things that are protected by Privacy Rule
Then releases a big expose pre-sale numbers of her book
Arabic
Forgive me for sounding a bit jaded but from where I'm sitting this seems like a setup
When Alex is saying the Jews on Tucker that night
Has nothing to do with Alex covering it and then it's making its way
It's just the latest
Attack
Ecosystem
Plan to take credit for it
I was thinking about this I realized like Alex is in a weird position now where he doesn't really have a purpose
Like
Tucker doesn't need Alex to mainstream narratives for him anymore
Picked up on that thing about George Floyd
That's pointless
I get the awful and it's
Disgusting
See Alex's
But like
The big guy is like Tucker and Sean Hannity don't need Alex a Tucker's just
Out there
He could just take like people are coming for you Deaconess star on his show
Show have this doctor on
He's not useful to the internet anymore they don't need him to like amplify their messages
He has no use
It's a bummer but away from
I would like the only way that you would have any value as if he was
Outside of that ecos
Exist
And it can propagate without him entirely a remarkable person to like
Go on another path
Like that to do the things he does but for like
Not Trump
I don't know what that would be it would not be him trying to do the Glenn Beck I'm sorry about all that
I wouldn't happen I would not accept that you just like try to pave it into like
Completely other territory
That are like
The other people's conspiracy theories
I said that I'll leave my V
Super simple
This is a big story The Big narrative on this episode it's a large portion
Locks
Of this video
And in order to understand
A video and it's trash
But it's it's basically what Alex is preoccupied with
And it because this video is so extreme
It makes Alex need to be
This is such
Exercise app
That if people don't hang for the
Politically
Because you did
Testing
Face
About being
We put up with this
The message here I think is pretty clear
Are you talkin about that video that Aronofsky put out
Fully proved at the Coronavirus
And that medical doctors are actively killing people in order to get numbers up high enough to appear to be a pandemic
That's what he's talking about
Essentially Ellington putting forth the most vast conspiracy imaginable involving literally all the doctors and nurse
Hospital Calais other individuals
All conspired together to pull off a fake pandemic for some reason
This is nonsense information is put forth on the subject
Inclusive to honestly feels more like a person trying to buzz Market their new book
There's absolutely no way that anyone is
For whatever conspiracy
Proven
Because he and his resources are all making it up
Anthony fauci
The Coronavirus
It's just Alex's fantasy
This is what Alex has demanded this doesn't happen then the blood is on all of Alice's audiences
Pants
Alex is making his listeners guilty for the eventual deaths
The come from covid-19
You can easily see how this is an incitement to violence
Businessman saying that if these people has decided are guilty of running a fake pandemic
Responsible for the deaths that
You don't want to be responsible for all those deaths
Well maybe you should take matters into your own hands to keep blood off
This is profound dangerous mentality to push
One of the things that makes it most dangerous is that
He's not just talking about people like that
He's talkin about all these doctors and unnamed nurses at various hospitals
Part of our house keys video is a legend the doctors in the hospitals were killing patient
And that's what I was just talking about a nightclub I just played
He's calling for the hangings
Countless medical professionals around the country and if it doesn't happen
Has that blood on their hands
You'll be really hard to get a unhinged person to attack a Mac Tower
Alex's Vengeance ultimate like starchy or Bill Gates
Ruby less difficult to attack a hospital
And this is a real serious threat right now
On March 24th the FBI tried to arrest a man named Timothy Wilson
Haven't had him under investigation for 6 months
Wilson was a white supremacist who had decided to Baba hospital because of quote
The increased impact given the immediate
Tension in the health sector
On March 24th you met up with an undercover officer think he was picking up a bomb
And when the off the arrest started he initiated a shootout result
This is not an isolated it's
On May 11th Saint Helena Hospital in Napa Valley had to be evacuated
A bomb threat
On June 9th the 33-year old man named Robert Roden arrived at Stony Brook Hospital in New York quotes
Wearing a tactical vest and carrying operable homemade bomb
A BB gun
Hatchet and
Handcuffs
On June 11th someone called in a bomb threat to the University of Illinois hospital
You're in Chicago
Again having to shut down the building
. of time
Grapes
There's a seriousness of this issue that
That takes this kind of rhetoric
Conspiracy theorist into
Guy who has a considerable chance of getting people killed
This kind of nonsense
This video that I was just covering is a blatant piece of s***
Propaganda nonsense
And the shifted it represents is terrifying
InStep take name of the faceless big Pharma the nebulous idea of the globalist to push vaccines
This video takes aim at the Frontline doctors
Nurses and other healthcare workers
The tree people
Is a very serious escalation and I really worry about what it pretends
Take this narrative from here
Whatever happens Alex is playing with fire
Absolutely inexcusable no matter what the consequences come
The possibility of
Go to be created
With that is just like
Why would you do that
Why would you do this
It is one of those things where you say you could pivot away from somewhere else but it's like it
You can't have him
Like is that rhetoric
Could could be applied in some ways to the situation wherein from
From the reverse
Trump is doing all of this b******* that is all of these people reopening the country all of this stuff
Is going to get more people killed all of these white supremacist going around f****** people up
Call Bob
They're f****** people up and Alex Jones on that sound
The other direction would be saying if you don't kill a white supremacist you got their blood
And that's not how you solve any problem that's not what you do and it's bra no calling
Defunding the police
Discussions
Anybody
If there was anybody who was like
Relative
Stature of Alex Jones
Calling for murdering cops
Absolutely
I just don't understand
Get what he's doing he's doing it again
Like this is the same sort of behavior
But he's engaged in that is got him into trouble
Yeah I mean this is the same thing as
You know what they say
Incitement
These
You know people calling and threatening
Their lives
Over it it's the same behavior I don't understand
He doesn't
You say he has to understand
Probably
But it's just locked up like
Isle of Corsica
That's what that's what he and his ilk get the f*** off on is
Fantasies of
Hurting people
Of murdering p
And so these just expressing his Phantom
The end result of his fantasy is
Is people dying
So he has to know what he's do
But he thinks he's on the right side of things because
The doctors
View
There have been hundreds of men
Let him come out
And you're ugly.
University
Cedars-Sinai
Clinic owners
We're having a normal amount of death for Steve
Pneumonia
Testing the main testing
The broad
Employment references
Every specific instance
But he's brought up and I could just like maybe 5
Yeah couple of a chiropractors sure they count clinical like the guys who run the Urgent Care
Clinic in Bakersfield
There's like
Judy mikovits plandemic
Stairs not like
The list goes on is over now
My guess is
The head of the Rockefeller Hospital Cedars-Sinai as one of his
This is a case of Alex mixing up his narrative
Cedar-Sinai supposed to be part of his Trump was right to suggest injecting disinfectants into people talking point
Which has nothing to do with the covid-19 denialism
Does grasping at straws anything close to the medical field
And in doing so you can see how you're no grass
Or even his own
Conspiracy theory
Everybody knows the Rockefeller Hospital only serves Rock
Not even people in the family just anybody with the name Rockefeller
That's the only one
I'm trying to think of another non Rockefeller Rockefeller
Jay Rockefeller sure he was
So don't so they're not happening currently
They're very well maybe a normal number of that's coming from the flu
These are covid-19
There's a very widespread phenomenon of excess deaths that Alex has not given an explanation for it
Just decided to deny
Almost entirely fictional realities presented to the audience
Yeah you know
Active Island
To try and get people killed
Passively by make sure to make Northern
Gates links the Seattle coronavirus assessment Network wasn't shut down because
As a fraud it was a temporary closure over a text
Macavity about them being queer to release test results to civilian
Already gotten State approval but the federal government put a hold on their program cuz they said they needed Federal approval as well
A little update
Haven't found around
They're still working with the FDA to be granted full Federal approval for the release of results but in the meantime they submitted to a review
You bored with the University of Washington and the Seattle Children's and Fred Hutchinson cancer research center
Which has
Offered to provide oversight and implement this program as a study
Running this as a review board approved study allows for the test
To be processed without Federal approval but again
They are also still working
To get that Federal approval
Time is of the essence of something like this so they're they're working proceed and they can also follow appropriate after
Ba stock
I was just making up that they were shut down for fraud because he's making all of the
This up his story has no connection to reality and he doesn't even remember what words mean in terms of ozone conspiracy
Fucken pathetic giving him way too much credit
I don't think he remembers what words
That's fine
Situation with this New York nurse
The bad
Videos
Computers
Operatories
In the room showing
People
Run
They turn the hospital today executions
I want my watch Darren's video m
Immediate problems
First one of her patients charts on her cellphone and showing it to the camera
The person's name is very sloppy but I would bet just about anything
Very easy to unblur that with
Minimal amounts of Photoshop
Which strikes me as
Very response
It's really sloppy as a redaction
Then about five and a half minutes and they show some undercover footage that Aaron got where she's
Confirm covid-19
Test in the charts no traces found
This is a problem because based on everything we is viewers have been shown this isn't that same person
Chart from her cell phone
Eureka diesel one person that she's talking about
And there could be an explanation for this like for instance the doctors were worried that this was a case with a false
Negative result
Symptoms of covid-19
Without more information we don't know what the circumstances are here and it's just sloppy work
To make matters worse
The game of secret cameras
A+
The video was edited to end just before the other nurse gives her answer which is super suspicious
It almost makes you think
Maybe there was an answer that made sense but it completely blue
Forward so they just cut it out
That might be
What it is because I mean
Yeah
I can see
Possibility where the test came back negative
We're going to go ahead and assume moving forward
Hey because
I don't see what you don't know anymore about it other than you and also what is it is no traces found
Directly linked covid
Does it say you were stupid stupid you don't know alcohol
Far afield
I watched your video but my desire to discuss it fell apart really quickly
I think this would be a fantastic opportunity for the hospital and the other staff to sue the s*** out of
If he's willing to put out this kind of a stunt in a YouTube video
Is there a serious about that she wouldn't have released it as a suspiciously edited YouTube video full of claims she doesn't prove right
Right before her tell-all book
Comes out to file the lawsuit against the hospital
Or something along those lines
She's literally accusing people of murder
The shooting YouTube videos not the place to do that if you mean it
If you really are serious about this
And you should be
Taking action in that front
As opposed to
Whatever this is
Uncover a massive conspiracy to purposefully kill patient
Right course of action
A bunch of claims that you make Cinavia the sound
Until you look for contacts
Princeton she claims that everything was crazy in the hospital there was a dentist in charge of the ICU
A fellow practitioner at the hospital clarify
The dentist an ophthalmologist working in the iso use
They have a defined role
Their medical professionals that space-time family members at bedside
They're not treating
They're an extension of the nursing staff so we can provide more time caring for a patient with less time answering phone calls
That's suspiciously not brought up in Aaron because the videos a lot of s***
You can find some accounts from other people who are at the hospital she was at but of course
So they can't discuss patient
The camp is Express how much things like this video
One fellow nurse at Elmhurst at the hospital she was at
Express the level of betrayal hurt doubt your disgust and anger is something I cannot put into words
Working at a level 1 Trauma Center in a hurricane prevalent area I came to Elmhurst
To give the regular staff some reprieve
A fresh face
A skill a strong skill set
Answer answer by nursing of
I thought others did too and man did this wonders prove me wrong
We were welcomed with open arms
An Air Hogs
Put simply I believe that you can sell their message up is gofucker
Yourself Aaron
This is ridiculous message up with
Doctors murderer
To be clear
Don't do this on a YouTube video
If you mean this don't do this
Amazingly ridiculous
Even accepting of that
Is a weird thing to imagine
But whatever
Alex gets into
You can tell from
You know her past
Movements it's probably the large
Part of what's this is a desire to
You know work against
Potential coronavirus vaccine development
That's not necessarily super explicit in the actual video
But if you listen to Alex's coverage of it becomes totally clean
At the mall
You understand when they give preemies back
So a couple things real quick
It's widely known medical reality that premature babies are at a greater risk of diseases which are preventable with vaccine
Call
And I know McCorkle disease
Premature babies are a position where they are at a higher risk if they are not vaccinated
Most vaccines are supposed to be administered to premature births at the same schedule as their full term term counterparts
With couple exceptions like rotavirus
They require slightly different schedule but people understand that
Mystikal round about being inappropriate dangerous to vaccinate premature babies
Compliances
McKay's
It comes from ideas about a child's immune system not being fully developed in the gestational.
But this turns out to not be as big a deal as it might appear
A 2015 analysis in the journal human vaccines and immunotherapy
Well absolute primary antibody responses may be lower in preterm compared to
Intermittence vaccinated
Chronological age
Chief antibody concentration
Higher than levels generally accepted to be to correlate with
I can buy there's any increased mortality risk related to premature babies being vaccinated
Definitely no evidence that
Half of them died
Completely absurd and honestly
The opposite is closer to reality
Due to the increased danger that vaccine-preventable diseases pose to premature birth
Not vaccinating them is probably far more likely to lead to death then backs
If you pay close attention do like I said you can see the game
Full coverage the undercover video supposed covid-19
Covid-19 better hold these doctors responsible for their alleged
Promote
Zacks narrative
And you can see how Alex Instinct through insta to announce that
He goes from this video and smoothly transitions into an attack on texting because that's what this is all about
He gets it
You can tell
I just I just don't understand the confidence
I just don't get that
Level oven
Same confidence to be like
Like I know how big Medical
True you know and I haven't read
And doctors have read a lot of them
I don't know what the confidence of somebody who's not read any of those textbooks and is just like
Girl long they don't know a f****** thing about this
Doctor
I mean
Let's Trista Ludacris
One of those sites that I was looking at Within
Approximately 10% of births are premature
Half of the babies who are vaccinated
Alex
Finally to talking about the Capitol Hill autonomous Zone
Views it as a Libertarian space wearing
And they're treating it as though
No there's no laws
Picture of sovereign citizen paradise and slightly different timeline
You didn't spend a lot of time talking about the zone
Just has one
Demigod
Enlarged heart
Describe
Running around beating
People
Calling himself in it
So
Seattle Police Department
So he's talked about the Capitol Hill autonomous Zone the protester to set up in Seattle
It's this guy 1 police station that the police vacated which is now Community Center at
I need directions
I have no idea about the inner workings of what's going on there nor can I pretend to know what's going to happen with it in the future but from
All external appearances it seems interesting
People feeding folks for no charge
Kind of block party
Set up the block vehicle traffic
So the cops can't get into something that probably is a scary
All-in on the malheur Wildlife Refuge
Yeah
Nothing is without the
The cops they're fine
Like that is a really threatening idea that if there are no cops and everybody is fine
Maybe not getting as violent as otherwise
It really really ruins your job
Try to look into this seeing some reporting from there and I seen
The / get is that but I also don't want to commit too hard in case
There's a perception problem that's going on
From people who
From Chicago it's difficult for me to tell
Exactly what's the reality of it
F****** complicated even if you're there and in invest in it
I can't imagine it being the sort of thing where you could be like
Well here's what's going on one sentence
No matter how many
Videos I watch on
Twitter about the
I'm not going to get there
A clear picture of yak
Probably not
Activist named Raz Simone
He carries his permit on
Videos of Simone approaching an individual graffiti up on a building which is apparently a home or workplace
Tri-State explain to him that the business is nice enough to let people be there in the autonomous Zone and they quote we are the cop
Saying that he and his team
The absence of cops there everyone has their own responsibility
To the community
A fight does seem to break out but it's
Pretty clearly the guy was spray painting was the aggressor and making the situation escalated
This mode appears to be trying to get the guy to respect the person
Property metallic should be into
It's really hard to tell from the footage but it appears that it was the spray painter who's the person who makes it
Portrayed it as a like
Reply
This actually went beautifully and we all hugged it out and spoke with his dad
Is that that wants me to Mentor him
It was great black dialogue and men apologizing to each other abandoning Pride
We all hugged each other cried it out and it was beautiful
Video it's just what he saying
I don't have any reason to doubt him but I can't prove that is the end result of it
He's lost a hand then I will accept the African
Whatever your perspective is on the autonomous Zone absolutely an unfair characterization
Characterization is
Racialized characterization
Denny's weaponizing it to scare right-wing audience
African Warlord
Seattle
For Christ's sake in 2016 he was opening for Macklemore
Exactly and that's how you know
I can understand this is long form birth certificate I can understand some people having a people occupy
A couple blocks in a major US
Is too much
This is racist incitement which is ironic
What happens when people fight back
Fair enough
Is pretty preoccupied
A little bit more about it
Sector the city
And if it does not do that
Did not appoint anybody
Appointment
Bistro
Quote
God
Further Raz Simone is not the leader of the autonomous Zone and he's not the life of God
Is a fun game for Alex
Dial up his audiences racist Peters but it's not real at all
Also
His most recent release with a song called Shoot at everyone
It's a song about how much pain he feels largely about estrangement from his
The course begins quote
See there's a pain that I feel in my heart that
Can't be numb
Sometimes I want to shoot at everyone
Not the best song ever but honestly pretty good I enjoyed it
Edsby
Artist is involved in something that's not music
I found it a lot of the times I end up being disappointed
Twice
If that gives you any indication rarely listen to songs
Trying to present this as a threat that Simone is thinking about things
April
This was
This is almost a purity level of Alex trying to create a black Boogeyman
Media is like really
Find in Skyrim
Found Lee racist stuff
He plays like the like a video
Music video of Raz Simone where he's like
Surprising all of this of any context in order to frighten old white
Alex might as well be like
He said
Steals his phone
Not sure about that
I've ever seen for reparation
Smug snarky little look on his face like he likes like
Steph Curry did a little stand-up
Perfect response to somebody and you make a little
I fucken improv the best line
He's got
This is where things get really interesting and
I will say that watching Aaron's nurse video with a waste of an hour of my time
This was also a huge waste of my time
Super King
Confused because you need to hear what
Confused me
Authorized
Bill's phone
Society
Appeasement
Weird that something was cut out
Feed
Okay so you probably something like that
Because the audio feeds that I get are generally like genesis
And so whenever those broadcast on whatever
They got to cut that stuff out
So I went and I looked
For Alex's version on video
I was like what do you know what are we what are we got here here's what it is on HBO
He says that's not authorized so he beats them up
Steals his phone
As reparation
Make it up because
Cuz the good people
Won't stand up and say no
Call everyone you know because we're all out here
Today
There's even cut out of this version
But also they added a weird flash effect
Like to try and cover up the video
Something is really up here and Alex said something that they needed to bury
Whatever
This time
He had his team cut out something
Personally cut out on a limb
The Edward was dropped deliberately I thought that was a chance
Or he said something
Like to f***** up
And honestly I managed to find it you know I don't give up on things like this
Virgin of the.
I've ever been
The real world
He catches some antifa God tagging
He says that's not authorized so he beats them up
And steals his phone
As reparation
Make it up because
Is the good people
Stand up and say no
The very worst
Ends up ruling
ValuJet Warlords
That's how you get
Collapse of society
Is a piece
Chipotle
Today
Interesting situation because I don't feel like it's Clippers anymore
A conscious decision was made not only by
But also by Genesis Communications Network to cut that part out of the show
I don't know exactly what's up
So I consider the possibility that there's some kind of recording problem
It's perfect. No problem at all
The decision to cut that portion out
Was intentional
I think I know
Nixon
If you watch the video Alex makes that snarky reparations joke that's not actually
Based on anything except his racist
All expenses of the good people and gestures with both hands at himself
These good people don't stand up worst
Penny Trails off
You just
String towards the video screen which is playing the visuals of one of Razz's music
With his hand making it okay sign
When he says the very worst
It seems clear to me that someone was in his ear because there was a look of confusion on Alex's
Does face
It looks like he's trying to take in information which
Make sense
What are the producers
Pics of this or a disaster needs to bail right now
I don't know if the okay sign is intentional as like a whites
Supremacist think on his own platform
We have some sort of Suspicion about what could this has been about
I have no idea if this is the case
Like I'm just spitballing here I'm just guessing
What happened with the while they were in Oz
Would you explain that
You know on the Jensen
Just got them hard
Look like nothing could happen
For the first video
That was what happened I don't know what it is like I know like Alex is saying the good people and gesturing at himself
The very worst
I mean that's racist vicious racist but that doesn't seem outside of his own
Cut that out
Maybe they've even figured out that Alex should just cut it at
We're just trying to take little jumps in time for me to sort out
Nakiryu were predicting is going to drop an bombs I thought they were probably something at least like
I mean I don't know some sort of a slur
It is it is expensive
I meant to shelve the show
Penny I don't understand
I'm telling you right now
Pot commitment is a fallacy
You're never
Now that doesn't make any Colossus doesn't make any sense
Alex
He's going to talk about Bill Gates
Kilkenny
The weaponized
Operation
The whole recipe
Interrupt
The medical facility
This is how you said
People
Tabletop exercises
10 years ago
Because
And then also I wanted to demonstrate this is kind of Alex's new version of a narrative now that this nurse
Who's come out with her videos
Now Alex is working in this whole thing about the globalist corrupt all the doctor so they can speak out against
Beattyville plants
This is a really important piece of any conspiracy theory which is the explanation for why there aren't hundreds of people confirming what your sore
Sources are claiming and what you think you've proven
You get the doctors to kill people and then they can't talk up because they're in on it now it's like a
Getting guy kill someone to get in a gang Stasek Ali is busy
So I mean Alex has got a bunch of sketchy looking sources to back up his claims and the rest of it is basically just make
If any of that was real
Calling
Doctors and nurses do not want to kill you
It's the opposite
Something feels like you shouldn't have to say that out loud
Yeah
But there was something even close to it Alex is describing happening
Being your unimaginably large number of healthcare professionals coming forward as opposed to just one alternative health nurse
Who founded to promote a book
Also lockstep wasn't a drill or a tabletop exercise wasn't even a plan
One of four scenarios it was imagined as a way to
Conceive ways the technological advancement particular
In the coming years
Actual paper and is it lying about it being the plant because he is a huge liar
You can't be like all that is that Bill Gates plan to kill Granny and all that s*** whenever 2 months ago
Mary lieutenant governor
Old people should go to work and die
Nothing else but you can't have it
Exactly
Yes
Tonight
Assessment
Is a drill
There's going to be new chimera
This is kind of a drill
This is just
Event
The big events coming
So first of all Bill Gates doesn't have a vaccine for this
This is all just stuff that Alex took from a chicken vaccine patent
Which Ed receive some
I was just lifted this narrative from qanon posters online is accepted it is real
Repulsion
Bill Gates did not say on Colbert
Coronavirus situation
Is just a drill
He's coming for a little bit
What's than that right now
Quiltville
You try to warn us
About
What's the name
It's about
In five years
I understand I send you one
Everybody lose
Nobody wins
I'm just saying
What else are we not listen
Take action on
Well
The idea of a
A biotech
Okay
Going to do
To be ready
Most
Are also
Is that coming on The Tonight Show
It's always important
Constantly remind yourself of that
He takes a clip like this from Colbert interview and writes his own story
Is not someone who lives in reality
He's making all this s*** up
How to get mad at Colbert
Don't say
Weeden
Listen we had a whole f****** 79-page plan
CDC had a whole thing they listen they had the whole thing ready
Ready to go with the Royal we
Cleanser it's pretty funny
Bragi
You're making it up
Tattoo I'm not mad at
The crew
Formulaic
The movie Annie
So obvious
You're watching
It's a good guy
Still waiting on that.
From the
Chicago riots
All sorts of things that you said are right around the corner
Yeah
Iceman
All my working time
Studying Alex Jones listening to his dump
Nightmares about you
William his
Have dreams about like Waterpark clearly you're the only person spending
Much time analytically listening to have
Goodbye
So it is next clip there's a really long pause
Please
Be patient with Alex
The gears are turning
Sure he's trying to actually I'll explain
Really really funny
Baby Alive
Born
The bill did not
Why would they want to do that
Causes really funny if you go and watch the video
Suppose organ harvesting Bell on the context of him being on Rogan's podcast
Leave Alex until he looked into it
How to find out Alex's right
When that pain starts
Screw flashes up on screen and article from Newsweek with the headline
Alex Jones Joe Rogan conspiracy theory meltdown
This is sunscreen for like a second or two and then the camera Cuts back to Alex in silence
With a look on his face like
Come on guys
Deflation is just like his really that's the
Exasperation
Liquor just a moment of like
Where's about us cuz we're so good
Next clip
Come on guys
Liability for doctors
This is a cynical political move as even CBS News pointed out
The measures have been defeated multiple times in recent years but Senate Republicans vote
Will GOP lawmakers to make an election-year appeal
Conservative voter
I was just making sure it up about this because he's an idiot liar and a zealot pause was pretty f****** funny
I'll post a picture of it somewhere cuz I take a screenshot
Text me too much
So Alex's
Northstar
HomeBase
Racism
I was going to say Bible
Oh okay
Year in this next
Chucky doll
Kill your ass
Canterbury Hall
Like to be the one
When you attack
The Galaxy knows what suffering means in this context
Jesus said suffer the little children and forbid them not to come unto me
For of such is the kingdom of heaven
It's a term that's also used in Mark 10 14 and Luke 1816
The context is the same
In the language of the time suffer meant to allow something to be done
Jesus says suffer the children to come unto me
Jesus did not say going to kill your ass
Blasphemous
And delay but maybe they just cut that out of the Bible
The thing about disconnected from any of that stuff and it comes from
17 + 2
The disciples it's impossible but the offences will come
They come
It were better for him that a millstone were hanged about his neck
Cast into the sea of these little ones
Context is passages that Jesus is talking to his disciples and explain to them that it's impossible to live a life free from trouble
But woe to the person who brings about those troubles
The little ones of this passage doesn't refer to children but to new believers who early in
The pap and woe unto the person who would bring offense upon them that would lead them into sin
The next versus Ark
Take heed to yourselves
If your brother trespass against you rebuke
And if he repents forgive him
And if you trespass against you seven times in a day and 7 times in a day
Turn it again
How do you say
You shall forgive him
This is really more about appropriate behavior among believers
Is your fellow believer wrongs you or tries to lead you into sin
Call them out for it if they're receptive to that
Your responsibility to forgive
If they don't reply
Then woe unto them
And they're better off jumping into the sea with a millstone around their neck
This has nothing to do with suffering children spicy little ones part
In there
He has such a bad grasp. Like really basic elements
Understanding
Main text of the
Professor doesn't know how to read listen to anybody when they tell him that he's wrong
So we're seeing a little bit of an upper
Swing
And covid-19
18 cases
Shock
Alex makes fun of that innocence.
Oh gosh trucks
You do it
Boys and girls
Alex is he reporting that's coming out there spikes being seen in various states around the country which is pretty f***** up
Inevitably the story
The protests broke out after the murder of George the responsible for the updates
Optix we're going to see here
And it's probably very unfair
If we're already seeing increases that's way too fast for it to bend from these protests
Expectancy increases after these
Decided to open up
Without proper at the real guidelines a testing in place
Thibodaux
You know it's almost like yeah
MPR made a really good point that is right now
Fair to call it a second wave we're still in the first wave
It's just never ended
What are the countries just decided that's not real
They're still over 20,000 reported in the US daily according to 11
Working on a 7-Day rolling average
That's a ridiculously high number like adding as many cases as there are total in Ireland
We just become burnt out to this reality we started to get out
In order to do the sort of things states are deciding to do safely testing and observation
Reason placed in order to make sure the case of the infected Bunch for people
That's just not wear a lot of states are
Their number states that are looking mighty scary right now
I'm looking in the direction of Nevada Arkansas the Carolinas in Arizona
All states that do not have stay-at-home guidance
Someplace
There's a one-to-one correlation between states that have stay-at-home orders going up or down
Possible to drop
What the states that are all looking like there's trouble Brewing or ones where there aren't
Rock Island
We'll see what happens in the future but this is the point where I feel things are the most of all
You have a market obsessed lunatic his presidency can re-election in November you have an entire right-wing media
Ecosystem pushing messaging that no matter what the deal is with the virus we have to protect the economy at all cost
Outrageously dangerous
Messaging to Doctors Hospital
To create the false image of pandemic
That's just
F****** toxic combination
And it really it really does think about
Possibilities like if we see
Massive upticks in a lot of states
We could get you a position where people have to lockdown again
Like in the same way as or even harder than we did before Alex and so many of these people
Responded
I just don't know
Better than you
Your fears would be
The possibilities of what could come just
Terrifies me
I just hear
Barbara tuchman
Writing the march of folly to
Trump's War
That's that's just all I can think of right now this isn't the most
Terrifying position
With absolutely no leadership
Anyone
That's beyond political party
None of those people are dictator
With that
He's better than Lightfoot
Talking more about his soda
Denialism and also that dumb video
Mistakes that we know of
Premeditated
Pneumonia
In
Hospitals to murder
Sure
Seven-years-old
Bro
Mazda Flame
So it's pretty bad
Can go back to back
I come see you
Tortured to death
Thousand watches Casio
What
Who says that
Thousand lashes
Thanks
Okay
Video that Erin put outside
If you're a doctor at Elmhurst Hospital
Please do Alex Jones for defamation
He's directly reporting to you and your staff took a patient with anxiety and killed them in order to make a few bucks
This is a clear open-and-shut case I think I don't know
The only evidence he has is this video
This kind of thing cannot be allowed to stay
People's lives in danger on multiple fronts with this kind of rhetoric
What is very basic in concrete level in the medical profession as a whole
Time when there's increased hostility and frequency
Hospital
Alex clearly hope someone attacks the hospital at which point he can claim it was a false flag to make the nihilists look
The dangerous path that is content is on is very high
It's it's
Very scary to imagine what could
At the very least you'll be able to get that
Full video deposition
Call please
I want a sequel position
Supernaut
From covid-19
If they believe Alex
Quick quick
I'm being pulled off by these Hospital
If they do get sick they'll be less inclined to seek appropriate care
Go to the hospital
There's no worst combination of putting forth
This time
People safe
General neutral as possible
Where things get more out of control than they already in Elmhurst Hospital soon
The list of people who need constant
Staggering
Stagger
I think that you run into a situation where I'm saying like Alex needs consequences for this and like
You can easily get it twisted and meet you know think that I'm saying so much it is obviously I'm not
Give me the financial consequences he needs absolutely needs to have some sort of a negative
Push back to recognize these things are not okay
And I just don't obviously we can't do it ourselves but
Might have done it if we could
God I hope he Slanders
Come on man
I know you're listening
Say something
I don't know I don't know
Republic Republic figures
Put out of shower
I don't know public enough
So Alex last clip that like
GOP
They're so smart
Not psychotic at all cuz they're cool
Address that really quick it's another instance of his narrative
Cuz he's talking about them killing you for money in the hospital
The stuff about the red and blue states that supposed to be about
That's nonsense but it is nothing to do with the idea of hospitals killing people
Completely separate conspiracy
Has nothing to do with red and blue States
When do you use bundled
That's like what Alex's describing
Mount hospitals are paper treating patients by Medicare is uniform a national it doesn't matter if it's a red or blue state
Eye doctors in any state
Make the same treating patients
The same condition
The centers for Medicare and Medicaid Medicaid services figure out what the average cost of the treating a particular type of patient
Standardized range that covers that they covered it that about
This is a great for a number of reasons
The first is that a drastically cuts down on the process
That's because before
Hospitals would have to build insurance or various tests
On more paperwork
As you can imagine this also left a lot of windows open for people to run unnecessary tests to build the government for
That's not something you can really get away with
Because you're also I just given this one payment amount for a condition incentivized
To provide the best possible care so you don't end up in a situation where your treatment is costing a ton more than Medicare
Medicaid cover
Exploring for Medicare and Medicaid services vendors to cut costs and provide improved
Because it cut out a lot of the uncertainty in wiggle room
Also in terms of covid-19
That's because there are four ton of medical condition
The amount that they determined it should cost to treat an average covid-19 patient is $13,000
A tournament that it would be if someone then ends up on a ventilator is $39,000 we've talked about this wedding
Is 52,000 number is just him
Those together
Because he thinks that you get 13 for diagnosing them is covid-19 thousand bonus
Just making up
Hospitals are paid each day when they have the patience in there there
Treetop or whatever
I want to take advantage of his audience not knowing how these bundled payments work
Which is shity
But it's also very transparent
You take some time to look into the topic he's cover
Just think for one second
Is there a Stanford Hospital gets for pneumonia which there is
Then we'll be stopping hospital last year
I'm calling every cost pneumonia more money
What's that mean you understand this is when you strike
It's back then everybody nothing
Alex thinks he's reporting on proof of the vast conspiracy but
Really just reporting on how he doesn't know how Medicare bundles pay my
So that's cool well you know when you say he's taking advantage of his audience not knowing how anything works
That is also a blanket state
Please take that is applied on all future episodes
So what
To talking about how like you know
GOP
They're naive but not evil
God
The expanse
Why didn't
Real naive
But now they're not coming up
Because Lex Luthor
You're operating off of normal human communication
The scheme but Alex is referring to is the last scheme
He was getting money for covid patients
Talking about
So the decision about bundled payments
Covid-19
Possible by HR 748
Or the coronavirus Aid relief and Economic Security Act
This bill was signed into law
And was widely supported in Congress
I passed the house 419 to 6 and went through the Senate 90620 with for non-voters
Ramp parking lot
You can bet on that Mike Lee from Utah
From South Dakota
Ram Paulding vote because he was in isolation with the time cuz he tested positive for covid-19 and both Mike Leanne
Mitt Romney had to go into quarantine because it had contact with Ron
No idea was up
Call dumbass was responsible for
Coronavirus relief
That could have been
And honestly
I would say
I don't think I'm joking about this
Oh damn
Did the schemes have standardized bundled payments was part of the bipartisan bill that Trump signed into law
Something of a red state-blue state
Work cut out for us
Sign that panzano
And he was drinking poison Diet Coke
I think I got a lot on the ground
Yeah
You know when someone lies
I'm kind of lie about him and then they can't call you out about it
Environment where all sorts of lies are fine
Alex gets into that game about this nurse
Murder
Banal another
She was a nurse in the Army in a rock but Alex is absolutely making up that she has a Purple Heart
That's a specific metal or killed in service
Stolen Valor by proxy
Alex has absolutely zero respect for the armed services
You just makes up stuff like this when he needs it to make a weirdo anti-vax nurse sound more credible
And killed in the line of duty
And I was just give a s***
No
Alex gets a little bit
Fed Up
About
Black lives matter
And stuff
You gets pretty mad any another cost button Shores you
Calling you
Ugly black baby
Screw you too
Virtue signaling
Person
Up here
Little sloppy
It was very practical to tell you something professional
So here is that unedited
Starbucks
The New World Order
I will get your ass
Ono Ono Ono
Oh no
Is that 1997 got home
Physical now god dammit my life alright alright alright
Daughter
Never get it back whenever you're better
Ciders
Also I should say in that last
Episode
My little mini 7 minutes
Couple things I have in my iTunes
Clarify that cuz I heard it from enough people but ya don't disrespect
I got it disrespectful
Hollywood well I mean consider you took down
Disrespect
I am maybe all of them who cares
Have fun with that Scott Hall had a toothpick
Don't know
So Alex.
Discussing how his enemies are psychic vampires
Tamales
Along with it
Stray kids
Weave
That is such fake
Fashion in Socastee
I feel like we've heard that rats so many times
When I was listening to myself getting really bored
He was getting more excited
Pronouncement cuz it's definitely
How to declare war on Bill Gates about a thousand times already
Yelling a bunch of s***
I was thinking about the Declaration
The meaningless but I think it's a tacit acknowledgment to keep anyone
Attention these days
You have to act like this is a major step for him when in reality
Sissy
It's just
Atomic robot going through their set
It screams false passion I think it's really sad to see this rote repetition of
I declare war on Bill Gates
Did you see the
Clip going around two of the Marchers in the UK
East End eye
That's the way we like it I think I saw a link but I don't know I don't know if it's true I don't know if it's real
I was just listen to that ranch and I was thinking about that song Angie
It was almost a relief
To hear it like that
You know like thank you I don't have to do any thinking I don't have to do this Friday
Yes you're just saying what I already know
Thank you
As interesting as it is just as bad as
Because of what we do
Profession
Basically
Galaxy junior varsity plot which is the African warlord in Seattle
The top
Story is
Nurse video about the
This is the B story in an episode of Cheers
He's back to talking about this a little bit
Course the white
Communist
Front guy
Sure
What
So just up top leader of the autonomous Zone
The right-wing media
Examine the idea that Alex is putting forth some kind of
Virtue signaling
To be doing that over antifa okay
Alright Alex's assuming
Black person in a leadership role is virtue signaling
Most of the people at the autonomous zone are white
Pretending
Pencil erases for you for Alex to have
What is Simona legitimately happen to be the person with the best communication skills and Leadership abilities
What if he was the person most able to articulate the values of a community
The person of the community felt was best able to negotiate with the city
Because I was a gigantic
Possible context in decision-making
Through the prism of his white fear
There's a black guy
That leadership position
Must be a self-hating Jew signal
You can see how this thing can be broadly applied to essentially denigrate
Pretty much all non-white achievement in society
How is what Alex is saying any different than a racist you might know who says that a black woman who got a promotion at his office
Which is the business virtue signaling as opposed to her work
Hardin
How is what Alex is different than a bigot on a college campus seeing and non-white students and assuming that they got into school
Gustav diversity quotas
As opposed to them having great test scores in a GPA
Details about Ransom own
Just made up here and what is
Very real
Is Alex's reaction to imagine
Has to be a black person
Interposition
Authority over white people
He can't stand
Yeah especially for somebody whose guests are 99% white and calls hotep Jesus the
Black person to speak for him
Sure
That is 99% still
Thurgood Marshall
Let's get Clarence Thomas I should tell you that
American Gaston this show
Time black panther
People didn't
In the black lives matter stuff today's with looting and rioting she wear
The new generation is doing and I just have no time for that
It's pretty funny though because Larry Pinkney was arrested back in the mid-70s
You peel to the United Nations which is
That's interesting
If United States of the sovereign state
Step in that clearly implies that the UN has some kind of authority that supersedes sovereignty
And Alex really f****** hate that
That subject
She probably realized the original black panthers were straight up revolutionary socialist
How to sing
Rescue the same thing no I am sure that whenever a flanks of black panthers were walking
Carrying assault rifles watching the cops arrest somebody Alex
Good those are the good black panthers I don't like these new trying to present
Interview
Very weird
Huey Newton and Bobby seale were
F****** Marxist
The f****** breakfast program is literally socialism
If you consult the Panthers ten point program that serves as a basis for the party
Relevant to today
Distance number for was a demand for decent housing
And quote is the landlord's
Housing and Blanche
It's so the people in our government
Can build and make decent housing for the people
There's a lot of people conversation now
Number six was quote we completely free healthcare for all black and oppressed people
Number three was quote
We want an end to the robbery by the capitalists of our black community
Legitimately to around in the 60s he would have been doing everything in his power to get a white guy to kill Larry Pinkney
It's it is
It was actually hard to listen
Handle it
Oh man last clip here in Salix hitting a news story
I can go maybe it's his
Junior varsity two-story
I don't know this these stories
Wild
BLM protests
Virginia
It's an unfortunate truth that a man was
Hit by Falling statue of the protest in Portsmouth Virginia
He's currently in stable condition and hopefully he'll make a speedy recovery
When reached for comment by local news Rocky Huynh
Organizers of the protest
We are responsible for this whatever way we can
I apologized on our behalf and his sister said he doesn't want anyone upset with us
His family was not upset their hurting
The protest organizer set up a GoFundMe and they've raised over $40,000 to support the family pay for medical bills
It's a tragic accident but thankfully the guy survived the protesters recognize their responsibility
Because of something that went wrong in one of their
You'd obviously prefer it never would have happened at all I can never get in accidents like this happen
Seahawk communities
Step up and take care of each other
This actually
Inspirational
Wrinkle to the store
Of course
Because right now we're experiencing such chaos that it would be shocking to me
Didn't happen
Course they're going to end
The fact that people are actually
Taking responsibility for it is something
Universal
Like all across the board and again we were forced into this chaotic position
It's not like we all got here on our own
Thursday June 11th episode
I would say that I have circle around like this is so Danger
I know that Alex's disparage
Nurses and doctors as like they're just getting drunk and f****** in the hospital
I'm not disrespectful terrible
Now and it's so indiscriminate like 8
It could be at any Hospital
Just
This can't be acceptable like
Has the potential for
Something
Really really dark
Really bad
I think that's the most important thing
And then
A weird editing thing is going to bother me
Yeah
You know what
This will be the hook for my book
History of
Happened why did you cut that out
Very weird
Anyway 5 Seconds to the truth
Simon & Schuster hit up your boy
We're also on Twitter
And if you could please find a local charity
Of the sort to help out in any way
300ZX Clerk
Alex
In color
I love your work