Air Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge B I'm sick of them
Need
College
Gelato ice cream truffle
Broke my hand open
I know that's a hackneyed observation those f****** jars need to do something about that
Unacceptable
Is that right
The worst
They're damn good
About
Because I'm not paying that much for ice cream on the regular
What's good today
Recording this before the move
Right until like the high stresses of the movie required
A fair amount of self-medicating Chrysler
That's a smart move
Classic
Slapstick comedy
Then that is my bright spot today
We made pancakes
Classic rock
Classic breakfast for dinner situation
We were walking our dogs at the time
My partner was like no let me carry those eggs for you
I'm about to hand them to her
She grabs puts one hand into the thing
12 eggs
Gone that is not slapstick comedy
Slapstick
Did she do a soft-shoe now I don't think that's comedy
I think you could laugh at a conversation
That involves
Very
Very simple and direct perfect
Do we have to record
I'm still getting all set up
Wanted to say hello to the Future
Your granddaughter is the president now
You were correct
It's mostly bring this up just in case any of the things we say sound entirely
The world changes appendix 310
So
Some slack it's a alien show up on Monday or something the past we don't know that stuff
Give them shout outs
The first
Initial M thank you so much
Extra
Grian
Billie Billie thank you so much
Max G
Max
G
MO
XJ max speed
Thank you so much you are now
The Great jamatt
Thank you to a couple people who donated on elevator love and appreciate that very much
Thank you so much you are now it's
And Kelly no-last-name figures about you and I will technocrat
We got to go
Heroin
Thank you so much bad
If you'd like to
Cams
That generosity into the form of
Local charity that would also be wonderful
I'm not good at that
Maybe there's something good about how bad
Classic slaps
So Jordan
Last episode from Monday discussed
Alex is going hard on this
This woman had put out where she's accusing doctors of
Is killing people in hospital it was
Thursday show on June 11th
This does not come back up on the 12th
It doesn't come back up at all
What are you talkin about does it come back on Thursday to be like
Not really
Tip
Over-the-top it is not it is Biden
Has announced the coup
Infowars.com
Biden says the US Military
President
Is that what they were saying
That's how you fight
He's with the military grabbing the president
So this is something came from an interview on The Daily Show
If you lost the election
Convinced
The military would recognize that was a huge problem
And would escort him out of the White House
He's not saying there's going to be a military coup just recognized the result of an election he lost
Will be handled appropriately
I'm not as fun but I don't say goodbye
Position is that outlandish either
I still think there's a decent chance that worrying about Trump not stepping is a little premature
There plenty of circumstantial reasons to be concerned about that and I've come a lot closer to worrying about it myself but it's just
Seems like it
Explicit and Unruh
Not respecting the result of an election is something that couldn't be walked back or undone
It would necessitate a very severe reaction
Whether it be the military taking him out or out breaking hostilities in the general population
I think it's okay thing to consider and think about what to do with Trump does that
Mentally bad thing
But I can't operate as it on the assumption that it will
Narrows like
Yeah it's a possibility but like obsessing and thinking like that is what's going to happen I think
What part of the reason that I
2015 Alex
Install himself as the king
New Islamic
Caliphate of America
It looks silly to us because obviously it was but it felt real to them at the time and I know that Trump has given
Ardmore reason
Do suspect that's the way he would at least
Yeah there's an attack on Attack on the prospect
There's that
You know there is a ton of complete inability to recognize the legitimacy of any zeddy of his beloved
Go about it a hundred percent circumstantial
About this little babe
But I just don't want to fall into the same trap as
Is Alex
Buddies
I don't think about that it's not work
No one has any idea what would happen beyond all hell would break loose and there's really no point
Planning for all hell break loose
Cuz what the f*** do you what's the
The plan individual-level think you can think about what your plan might be
So in the sex club
Alex discusses how
Everybody's got a
Can I get the word out
Bye-bye
Transplant
Reactivity
Live feed of the show from
Comport slideshow
Gmail
They admit the coop
July
People
Global Toronto
CIA
Are the Deep state to believe they can actually
I think Alex just debunked himself
He believes that the military will escort them out of the way
They got to go on TV and make these announcements to ready the crew
Reinforces argument Alex brings up how you breathe
The Secret Service about a film mud interview on CNN
The announcement of a clue a coup plot
To kill Trump
Here are the two problem
One that still might interview is 3 years old
Has been watched
It doesn't seem like it was at all because there was no plot
The second problem is that Alex talk to the Secret Service about this film mud interview and they did nothing about it
Which clearly indicates that the Secret Service did not think
This was anything serious really just a guy talking s*** on TV
You would think if there was an actual instance of feel about announcing a coup on TV and Alex brief the Secret Service about it
That's a good thing
How about everything
That is soon as I left that meeting with the Secret Service
At least one jerk-off motion was made
Right
Spread my wings
Creative occasion to write a script of what I imagined
In front of you there is a script and highlighter highlights
Thank you very much Secret Service
Play Alex Jones
Alright
Scene interior
Old-school interrogation room lit by a single overhead light shot in black-and-white
Floppy man with a picnic table sweating
Holding a candy cigarette in a cup of cocoa he's pretending his coffee
I understand
That you have information
Plot against the president
You bet I do this thing goes all the way to the top I'm talking Rothschild Bill Gates Oprah Winfrey you name it
Okay okay okay
She just started
Watch CNN that guy's the last living Vanderbilt
That's not true
A bigger late he's working for the CIA and helped cover up Sandy Hook but my lawyer told me that I should pretend not to believe that last
Anderson Cooper
Not directly
But you know he should really take a look at over
CNN I got Brian stelter
Pedophile
I mean look good looking the way he smiles it's full of humorous
Here look I brought a picture of it
Alex hand the agent today by 10
That attempts to light is Katey Sagal
Brian stelter
Threatened Trump
I know I said that the Aether special was going to end today but we got extended until Tuesday
Is rare neurological condition called semi voluntary spontaneous advertisements syndrome
Absolutely
Chiropractors who pretend
Call prescribe me iodine to manage the condition of the University of Eldorado
The science is good but the globalist horse the researchers to retract or else they would reveal the location of the gold
Okay so what is this half did the Golden City threaten the Press
Years of studying the Bible
It's under Mount Rushmore
Mr. Jones I think you're thinking of the plot of National Treasure Book of Secrets
Now we called you in because you claimed to have information
About a credible threat
Credible
Against President
On CNN
Are you sure that he wasn't saying that the difficulty of governing was going to kill Trump
Not that a vague entity called the government was going to literally kill this was a joke
Mud with sending up the alarm Rising the army of demonic globulus minions heed the call
Okay if the government is going to kill Trump
How does an army of demonic globulus minions fact
These are demonic Lovelace menu
Like like at the dma at the DMV BMV is lousy with globalists
Thank you very much
Can you get Bill Gates to stop wearing pink sweaters it really pisses me off
My office
Beautiful thank you
Alright
I just made things
What really happened
You know like literally get into the way that you make
I just had an image of Alex sitting under a light in it
I know of a plot to kill the magic even in this scenario
He still has to wear Hancock
Cups like they still he's not
Convicted he's not accused of any crime but they likes
Okay if you're going to tell us about applied together
We need you would have all those Hannibal Lecter mask
Phil Mudd on this episode
I think Alex is getting into dicey territory
We
Will kill this guy
CIA
Governments going to kill this guy
Telegraph
Confidence to their Networks
Better than the government
To create false whistleblower report
Information
The current to poison the President
If you depressed
Somebody else does
Use the term because he's mock the idea when people talked about him doing it
Is it filmadas engaging in Stowe cast
Terrorism
Mud went on TV and said that the government was going to kill Trump hoping that someone would hear that message and take it as a sign that they should do it
This is really murky territory for Alex
You should be introducing is something he's accusing his enemies
The problem is that he does this all the time
He constantly talks about his enemies should be killed and how they're all going to burn in hell far more graphically in explicitly
Even fill mugs
Alex is directly asserting did Phil Mudd comments on TV are legally actionable to the point where he met with the secret
Service about them
Because he was someone wasn't because of
Analysis himself belongs
Prince music using somebody
Alex talks about this stuff, a part of the Lesser magic stuff
Global Tattoo announce what they're doing before they do it in order to get magical power out of the rich
That's stupid but at least it's not self dammit
To carry out his goals
Is it really bad direction for Alex to go down since it heavily implicates his own behavior
I would have advised it again
In the in the studio
Bail.
I mean the only thing that saved him is I don't think I've ever heard him
Not by his own b******* as immediately as he was saying it like
You don't believe a goddamn word of this you idiot
You know it and I know it stop
Skip this next part cuz it's pointless
Sinon
And I have no idea what he's talking about
You get to another one of the big thing so there's the
Which is where you announce Akoo
There's that narrative you got to have Trevor Noah giving you the sign off before you
Gives you the words
That's that's a big narrative and then
Another one that he's got going
Is the bike
Jon Boat has his book
Yes Aunt Alex is not happy
Course
Bolton
Call
Stupid
Why do we say
He's a Fox News watcher
What is policies
The Trojan Horse
It's so funny to hear Alex pretending the Trump just got suckered into hiring because he's a Fox News
Infowars because Alex supported the nomination of John Bolton
Munchkin
That was from March 23rd 2018 Rodger Stone
Directly says is a 30-year long poker buddy with John Bolton
So I guess that means Rodger was giving Trump added
Interesting
Defeat pechenik
Askreddit he was supposed to Bolton
Listen to Leann consistently but Alex did not listen
Alex that Rodger was more important
The Trump could use against his shadow enemies
Hope I didn't work out so great for everyone
And he was always on the right side of this one
He was always against Bolt from the gym
This is ridiculous
Noted national hero
When in a position of power to do something about those many impeachable offenses
Was like
Nah
Go for it
Can I suggest there's no
Interesting like
Hey
I thought that this is going to go a different way turned out
What's the problem with him saying that yeah I was led to believe that John Bolton would be someone who PDF
Effective as a ratchet
Do the information that I got was wrong that's not how it turned up.
Absolutely ability to just be wrong
Psychic knows everything even when he's wrong he's Trump is always right Everybody's Fool
He knows everything and is the smartest person on the planet
And God told him that you should hire
But even God is wrong sometimes sure
Timaeus
I don't I don't exhaust
Let's children
Let's just chill
So Alex is still also mad about Phil Mudd
I complained about him I thought he was mad about empty dirt
Come on now
No
Alright
Equate vessel bottle
Phil Mudd who's actually related
Your mud
The only other person
He's actually related to the Virginia
Tormod
What's a little bit before but the only evidence I can find at filmadas related to Samuel Mudd is a 2014
Tweet from Jake Tapper
It might be true that they're related or might not be I don't know I'm not really that concerned
There's a sex therapist named Wendy freezing who I've heard of I'm not related to her
The comedian named Don Friesen he's not a relative
People have names doesn't always mean
If I am related to Don Friesen I assure you will change my life at all
Yeah and either way I really don't think I would care what his great-grandfather
I don't think that has any effect on
Genetically predisposed to Kelly Preston
Oh that's true
Not the only other person charged in the plot to assassinate Lincoln
Princeton to David Harold was in the barn with John Wilkes Booth
Harold surrendered the booth did not eventually being shot by boss
Austin Corbett the subjective one of the best episodes of the dollar
Harold was convicted and sentenced to death by hanging
Longest three co-conspirators
He's kind of a big deal because one of them was Mary Surratt
The first woman executed by the US government
Three other conspirators were sentenced to life in prison and one got six years
Dr. Mudd was pardoned few years later since it wasn't really clear fuse in on the plot or may have just been the Doctor Who's new
Who created someone who was in distress who showed up at his house
It's not like it was
Twitter in 1865
Alex is supposed to be this big history buff
But he has clearly demonstrated he has absolutely zero awareness of the details of one of the biggest events in US history
I strongly strongly suspect because of Nicolas Cage
Ended up in the Second National Treasure movie
Because of Alex knows about the Lincoln assassination
It's impossible that he would know about Mary Surratt
It's
What are you what are you paying attention to women in history
What's a guy with the name like Harold
Come on
Cannot be simultaneously true
It's ridiculous.
If you're an Infowars listener and you think Alex knows what he's talking about you have to ask yourself
How can you f****** something that that seriously and that casually
How can you assert a historical payments absolutely usually falsifiable
Move on with it
Like the fact that Alex is so comfortable fabricating information about history
Like that mud was the only other person convicted in the assassination
That should be a serious red flag
Is Alex is capable of that kind of lie
Elsa eating as definitive fact that he's just making up
A lot of trump
Spoiler alert it's almost everything he talks about pretty much
Also doctor mode wasn't from Virginia is from Maryland man anyway
Really different state
What the f*** is
I don't know why you even look you could just see
Samuel Mudd was mixed up in the Lincoln assassination
Pathology
Just
John Wilkes Booth and why
Why would it just be those two
I tried to kill the vice president
About the vice-president crime these days come on
Stupid
Marcos
So 8:30 on Friday something amazing happened in Alex as explosion
Get him help
Is that I don't know
Use making stuff
Oh my God here waiting
That's weird but then the other thing that I think is really funny is now whenever Alex mentions Hitler in the bunker he has to
That's not a different thing I know they looked at similar
Are you just looking at
Yep I do like that
He is so self-conscious
For years he's been fine talking about Hitler in the bunker but
Lexus
Has made all of these people look
As pathetic as they always have been such a bad time for them
But I tell you one of the most
Nice
Steve pieczenik
Flipped out on air
We know
Is a nasty little
Here's another example of Alex
Showcase of the exact same
He doesn't understand the word
And what they mean
He thinks it's inter Blossom here is an insult because the word turd isn't
There's a very specific term being used in a very specific history
Turn Blossom was a nickname that George W bush affectionately gave to Karl Road
Because of his masterful ability to take a piece of s*** and bring a flower out of
Metaphorically
Turn Blossom is also if it's not an insult
Really only has a connotation of admiration particularly in the realm of politics
It's also the term pretty flower that grows from manure to isn't the good basis for an insult
I get the chance to compare the s*** but the flower is the contradict
Can of the s*** not it's a
Extension
Blossom is something that's beautiful growing out something shity
Alex just heard the term and assumes that it's something for Jordan
Much like you did because it involves poop
Complementing
Alex almost never knows what he's talking about
Yeah but the bottle fired matter
The modifier nasty over text
Even if it is a
Flower that blooms out of a turd if it's nasty it's still a nasty flower the realm of politics
Term only applies to George W bush talking affection
Currently about Carl Russell is a nasty piece of s*** from from George W bush
Show me pictures of nasty piece of s***
Call him back
That's a compliment
Imagine Florida
I disagree with your perspective and I'm definitely right
So
Roses and a chessboard
That you didn't realize had occult significance
And he's a little bit
He wants to drink with your eyes
Also
You're probably asking who is that
Auburn
Ali
Robert Ely
That's right
Robert E Lee statue
What else strong message to place the skull and roses
Robert Ely
I was being too
Let me be more out front what I wanted to say with the
Flower the skull and the chessboard
You wanted to be
Deeply esoteric
A little blonde
It's very little blood
This turns into a thing where Alex
I don't think he's being defensive
But at the same time he's trying to rationalize
Mad statues look at me I have a statue
Why do you get mad at me and give me free Pride come take down this statue
That's largely strategy
Alex is a different rationalization for why
Robert E Lee is cool
Nothing on there
There were articles
Thousands over the years
Because he fought armies
Buddy the north love the racism to
Molino shoes
Respected
Carriers
Military base
Dollar General
Why
Russia
That doesn't sound right
You know who they studying
Robert Ely
Civil War
Tight shorts
Sure buddy
And the Civil War was not about slavery was not Western expand
I can suggest a group or even further and Underdog and I would be slaves
Unless the underdog is the person on
In Chains
Underdog
I don't know I think generally speaking in terms of like the big picture siding without shoes is not white
Are you sure I pretty
Second point I'd like to cite my unimputable sore
Course one of the greatest story ever lived Alexander
Listen to Archie
He's trying to make
Whatever the situation of the world were black people are rightly asserting their right to equal treatment and conversation
History of post-slavery America comes up
Invalidate
Ozark
However when it comes to defending the Confederacy
Needs to justify his absurd supportive
Confederate generals
Without sounding racist
He's quick to point out that the Civil War wasn't about slavery
Often say that was about states rights of the economy both of which are just words
Deny the Confederacy seceded over slavery
Sherwood states rights but the particular right of the state where those in question was
In their whole little secession thing
The economy but the economic concern was being able to maintain an economy that relied on slavery
Free labor does help that's all obfuscation
I'm in this instance it's no different
Civil War was about western expansion
What do you think he means by that
Could it possibly be about whether or not duly admitted states that the union would be slave or free
Missouri Compromise Advanced slavery west of the Missouri west of Missouri
What are your problem
For any of the Confederate States
People who are landowners there
New Lancer western expansion yes of course
Uber at the bottom
Alex knows damn well what the Civil War was about you can tell because he's explicit about it being about slavery
What do you want black people to shut up and think white people for ending slavery
Ignoring the fact that he claims to literally be his ancestors who he said on many occasions
Fought for the Confederacy they were fighting for states rights to keep slaves
Not for slavery. It's a little luck
Constitutional
The little is Constitution that might be
So Alex
Talking more about Robert E Lee
This one confused me a little bit about what Alex was trying to say and then I figured it out
Very poorly
Property
He's one of the greatest generals
Name of the greater
George Washington
Washington had no genetic
What
What what
Progeny
So he grew up
Is his father
Robert Ely
Wasn't amazing
I have no idea what the f*** Alex was trying to say there but it sounded
Washington
Just isn't true
Yeah children and Patsy custis
Also just
Stefano be impossible cuz the Washington and gravity leaves lives didn't overlap share
Robert Ely married Mary Anna Randolph custis Who was the
Daughter of John Costas
Granddaughter of George Washington
Direct lineage
The fact that he's speaking so on clearly here makes me pretty worried that he doesn't know the full story
George Washington
After his father-in-law died took on the responsibility of custis family Plantation
Includes
His father-in-law's wheels that the slaves were to be
Be free within five years and after five years we did for those slaves
You did wait until the last minute
There's a good pizza in the Atlantic
Take the deconstructor the myth of generally being a good man just wanted to keep the country together
He was not
Quote
Leave heavy hand on the Arlington Virginia Plantation
Prior rights nearly led to a slave revolt
Previous Masters.
And we had engaged in a dubious legal interpretation of his will
In order to keep them as property
One that lasted until the Virginia courts forced him to free them
You didn't want to free the slaves
Instead he had that he had inherited but they made him do it
Emerald in water free his slaves
Well that's one of the things that all these people talk about like he freed the slaves that he inherited together
I know I literally because I remember cuz I read that piece in the Atlantic
And I remember like I have this huge flash back to what I was in
Fourth grade
And hearing really really nice s*** about Robert
The whole f****** time
Like it was insane
Especially looking back like
Wait a second why are you guys spending
A quarter of the Civil War thing on how great the losing General cuz it kind of have to I don't know.
Switch was actually again
Tradition IP Kostas Plantation
That was his innovation
Brothers Atlantic Ardell
Leave cruelty as a slave master was not confirmed to physical punish
In reading the man
And the historian Elizabeth Brown Pryor's portrait of Lee through his writing
Playwrights that ruptured E Washington custis tradition of respecting slave families
By hiring the other Plantation
By 1860 he broken up every family but one on the estate
Some of whom we've been together since Mount Vernon days
The separation of slave families was one of the most unfathomably devastating aspect of slavery
Is regarded him as quote the worst man I ever seen
And that's not all
When we was in charge of the army of Northern Virginia
Enslaved free black Americans and brought them back to the South as property
Prior rights the quote evidence links virtually every infantry and Cavalry unit in Lee's army to the
The Abduction of free black Americans with the activity under the supervision of senior officers
Robert E Lee is at best a horrible piece
Piece of s*** and Alex is not defending him cuz he's good at Battle strategy
Because he was the commander of a racist Army that tried to overthrow the American government
Because I couldn't own people anymore
So I can
Alex Jones to this is ridiculous
8 is revisionist
Nonsense normal slave owners
That's how awful this guy things in the world
And he's worse than them
Talking about Headlights
He's in trouble is right I mean
There's going to be some bad stuff, difficult obelus
Guitar
You've got these commies in the Seattle autonomous zone right
Chinese
Remove when they overthrow until prom
Or drugging up
Don't kill Ron Paul
I'm not saying don't
Analyze their tax profile talk radio
Alright alright so Bundy
Occupy National 40 National Park
Totally fine
Absolutely no problem
Some people without
They're the ones that the Chinese have chosen to assassinate Ron Paul and
So there's the distraction for the kids come in and take out Ron Paul Alex Jones
System is like we got to figure out what's going on with Chaz before weekend
Security
Convoluted
So Alex gets pretty mad about Tim Cook
In the middle of this episode about China
And how they treat Muslim
Weider labor
Report business hours
Brands using uighur Muslim forced labor
In fact
Allegedly using
Blinking Muslim slave camps
Got a bozo haircut
Read about it
So Alex is right I mean not the being of bigoted
Very serious issues that need to be addressed about the state of China Muslim population
Never trust Alex to be a credible voice on the subject
He can be right about a central point and also be completely wrong and detestable at the same time
One of the main reasons is because he doesn't mean what he says
Here he's trying to use the plight of the weaker population in China as a prop to attack China
Protect the actual people he's talking about
But he does
You don't give a s*** about these people pass the point you can use them
Is a blunt instrument to attack his imagined enemies
And I know that because of this
Something he said less than a month ago on May 26th
Michigan
From London to Austin
Rio de Janeiro
Do your thing
When Alex wants to he cares deeply about his treatment of Muslim
When he wants to start his outrageous islamophobia and convince his audience that Islam is trying to take over the West
Just trying to do their thing
It is a really good case example for why even if you kind of agree with the main point behind without to saying you can't
Ever let yourself agree with them
He doesn't agree with himself
And if you ever consider him an ally because of a point you seem to agree on
It'll look like a mistake in hindsight
All the left-leaning people thought that George W Bush come to mine
No matter the subject you're passionate about and find yourself thinking Alex is right about whether it's Bush hating or APA
Opposition to civil asset forfeiture
You will always be able to find a smarter more credible Source than him
On every single
People who actually care
Do they mean what they say
We're more than just intellectual sadist trying to take advantage of an audio
It's like that's all he's doing
You can pretend to
Karen
Cuz Islam's trying to take over
Yeah it's
Makes me think so much of this
Forest
Deference given to so many politicians by the media and the
You know you report what about this
Says or something like that
There's no accounting for bad faith
Like I don't believe
A f****** word Mitchell
McConnell says
Even if Mitch McConnell said literally everything that I believe
Straight into a camera and said we're going to do it
I don't care
I don't believe a thing you say you're acting in bad faith you don't get the protections of your words
When you're clearly acting in bad faith I guess what Alex does
All the time and that's
Kind of
Because you can't really argue with the conclusion that you know
Made in China absolutely
You can't sign up for his version of it cuz it'll take you down the road
You don't want to be on
That isn't what you signed up for
This leads to
Describe is an intensely homophobic discussion tobacco
If you complaining about
Tim Cook Apple work with plays
Clip of Tim Cook
And it just turns into a
Preoccupied with the fact that Tim Cook is gay
It's great
Childish
Tim Cook
Virtuous
Everyone
Justice and equality
Call chirotouch a on Hill
I'm on 12 hits of ecstasy right now
Newsom
Okay if I run Spokane
So I mean
If he's working on a new impression
There's a terrible impression
It's deeply homophobic
Childish
Disgusting
Yeah Penny managed to offend
I mean that was bigotry on
Just every
What's interesting to me is it like it goes on for a while
It's basically the same thing over and over again
Just saying
Every time he gets to the end of the wrif
I'm sorry I'm sorry
He doesn't do that as much lately as I used to do that quite a bit
Is going off
It seems like that I haven't seen in awhile
Probably meaningless doesn't signify anything
So he does that outbreak
Comes back
And then he's going to hit some of these like
Big
Topix
Only watch it halfway through
This is much
Hollywood star
Booking camp
You would know
Apologize
They're going to be better
If you don't like that video why are you wasting your time
Like what what's the what's the point
Did you have any instinct to bring it up and waste our time talking about it okay
It wasn't a thought I had people I wasn't like here's what I'm going to do
I'm going to derail this conversation
Apropos of nothing
White liberal celebrities
I mean like he's pretending this is like world leaders listen to show
He's he's taking his time to complain about
Celebrity videos
Emily
Sure I made this plenty of criticism if you want to tweet something go for it
Compared to what
Recovering baby
Views himself
And the fact that he's like I tried to watch it twice why
I don't try to watch it one
I don't know who.
Who cares
Samantha Gerard
This blew my mind
My my
In the middle of this episode
Twitter
I don't think we're not going to waste our time
I don't care still don't care either
So
I'm not even going to try to set this up
Coming in and out of break but it was
Fairy autoplay
What is that
Soakin wet
Worldwide
Are joined
Lee Stranahan really appreciate
About to get a journal
Work for the cable rails
Juxtaposition is f****** amazing he comes in with shake it like a salt shaker
Pizza much they call her Billy Ocean
Man
If Infowars had a booty
It'll be big
You would not listen to music
Just.
You're not allowed to have
Cuz it's not
Oh I I should say this I forgot earlier
Rubber this visit family show with the shake it like a salt shaker
This is the out-of-context drop from Today Show
Lesbian orgy with John Bolton
I love your identity sit around thinking about what it would be like to be an orgy with John Holt to try to get a boner
It's like one of those High School camping trips you know everybody's somebody's like do you believe in God
Do you ever wonder what it would be like to be in orgy with John Bolton trying to get a hard-on
Considered
Now I'm considering it
How's it going
Exactly like him
I think
I want to question.
Let's talk about a rock
If you're in an orgy with Rodger Stone
You expect
To see him there so you're already
How do you do even if even if your Nike I didn't know Rodger Stone was going to be here like it was going to be
And even if it's like a mask affair
So
I mean
Yeah that was that was derailing a little bit on my part I apologize but I needed to hear that out of conflicts drop
Anytime Alex
Stranahan's on his interview sucks
Explaining that like the globalist what they're doing
Is there taking this domestic issue
We should be I don't know
Black people being murdered by the police saying it to their
We don't really need to talk about because I don't really care about his argument
You'll see why I kept this club in pretty quick
Internal issue
Big Jenna.
To take over the Civil Rights Movement
Sociology
Alex's eating
It's easier to having lunch
Lee Stranahan
You how do you not feel incredibly
I can't imagine because I really
Kohl's
Yeah I can't even imagine it either cuz like your time is valuable
Joseph company
Infertile
If you are somebody who's likely
Valuable professional
I do serious work
Talk to Alex down
Rude That is rude
F****** rude Emily rude
Open sign
Disrespecting the breeze to be on Infowars that isn't that guy who hit stuff with a hammer
I don't actually know is that guy is cool or not
Ask you to come on and you make a joke out of it
I don't hate you
But everybody else
F*** off you deserve to have a sandwich exact
I spoken too soon I forgot
Stranahan has a gigantic new project
And I respect the hell out of this
I probably want a booking
Close TV it's 11
My Twitter feed
That's not a TV show that's not a streaming on Twitter
Wow
Alex talks to leave for a little bit it's mostly about like Soros is running black lives matter and all this like
Now
Things get real interest
Because
Okay so now we are on hold
But Alex needs to talk to Steve
Talk about Alex's is going to introduce him here
Which is so pathetic
Attic
Short notice
Critical almost broke
You didn't mention
I told him
Alex can't cop to the fact that he was
F****** wrong you can't do it
Text to be against Bolton
And Alex did not acknowledge
Not ever
Cowardly
You can never lose
You can never be wrong
You can never admit for one second that you had something to learn because when he was born
He knew everything
Steven
Some s*** to talk about John Bolton
Victory lap prestige
It's pretty great
Manipulate
So you have a mutual
Fishing is a sexual activity
Many many years ago in New York
Please don't
Disagree
First I'm going to need you to confirm or deny whether or not there was a video of Reagan getting paid
And to I want to know more about what Bolton was doing at that f****** with Trump and
Whitestone wasn't there
I guess I don't know
I guess Bolton
Got sexual blackmail on tropical
I don't know man
These sorts of things are like
Yeah right
I mean I guess if you have sexual blackmail on Trump
Assume it's in that book right now there's no
Treasonous
Treason and then there's revealing that you cheated on your wife
Okay
There is a code of ethics
Talking nonsense
I don't I don't know
I like I like that Steve still swinging
Sexual blackmail is way more damaging than
Revealing treason I do I do appreciate the blackmail standards are very
That right
Well it seems like he should be implicating himself in the very treason that he's describing
On account of him watching it and not doing it about it
If you're committing if you watch somebody commit treason
You commit treason he told the lawyer I'm not part of this or something so fine
Next to somebody committing murder and they were talking about
How can I help
As long as you certify with a lawyer that like
Miss Murder
Okay okay
Steve's got this idea that has got sexual blackmail on Trump
Any further
But Lee Stranahan still there
He comes in
With what I think is the most exciting piece
Of Juicy right-wing media gossip
This is exciting
Lee's talking about like Steve Bannon
Destroyer
Notice
But this is
People involved
Steve is working with Mike cernovich
To destroy
You
When those guys were on the network
Destroying yourself
You could not be more right
Steve you couldn't have been more right
He's also talking about
Hate these people they're all envious of you because
I want to be that person in Destroy them. Make them able to do
Big flattering cup
Alright
Owleez coming in
It's Steve Bannon is working with Jack Purcell
He was eating a sandwich put you on home
For stupid
To talk about both having sex with black men
This man how dare you I just love the idea
Spine
If I could do this all over again
The script of bee
I'll do is I'll go to Comet Ping Pong Pizza
Define demonic activity and then I'll go get on info
I love it
Yes okay
What a group of losers
Losers
I can't I mean
Obviously potential of
Other people getting hurt
In process is high
But I love the idea of there
Being like
A rogue's gallery or Justice League
Because they take his place or something
Just how awful the Algonquin Table
Sufferable
God is fair
Like it really ends up becoming a thing where like leads
Steve or Josh
Sucking up to Alex
Flattering him to a level that is almost
It's kind of gross to listen to
Ali Askari
I'll tell you why
Ucreate
Jealousy
To be clear this is Steve restating his points yet
Various
You're very funny
And at the same time you're very serious
You created
Millions of people who enjoy what you do
That is
The sociopaths
Self-aggrandizing
There's other reasons for
People not liking people you just mentioned are absolutely
And there is no one else around
You do understand the people think it's cuz they Envy
Cuz I know yours in cuz they said they're not just jealous
It's cuz you're too good man
That's why you're not going to get JFL
It's silly
Oh God I wish I would have got this it was in the middle of stuff that you
Work
A 2-second
For a 10 minute clinic
Steve
He's busy baby
Now that's some drunk s*** right
I don't think it's
Drunk coming
Steve I think
The unhinged
Hospital
Last clip here and Steve loose
I mean I don't know what this is
I have to believe that Steve called Alexandra's like
I mean come on
I was right about both
I'm going to come on and go
But Lee Stranahan still on for a couple minutes
Afterwards
And he has this really
Shity idea
Is do
Bass wants him to do
Hardin Manor
Because man
What's going on with Russia
He was trying to warn Trump
Face
That's exactly right
Yeah that's what they should do that should be in people's faces
Personally
Leeor Alexandra
Similar circles
The only thing to work at Breitbart
So like
Otherwise it doesn't
Make any sense to me
Chardon why you would say out loud
I mean if I had to be a cynical minded person about it
I would say it's some of the same reasons
Want to
Pardon Rodger
The night is that they know a lot
Totally
You don't want them
Just spell the kind of
Guess but it blows up
If
Not the entire ecosystem
But particularly that of Alex and
Vewlix sycophantically Pro Trump
Especially people who associate with Alex because Rodger was basically running it for a while
Have a vested interest
And someone like Rodger never be hottest
And I'm sure it's similar but without the like
Media focus with metaphors
It's your wild to me because
Yeah he did that s*** man you know it and I know it he's a bad dude and if you don't think that he did that
That should
Don't stick your neck out for him
He's done all the other s***
What does it work for Trump being president we could have got him on so much more s***
Work together there consulting firm predict taters for years
In prison when they were nine
I don't know how they got to this far
Night
Team
Alright Nora put minors in prison
So I come to the end of this and this episode is
Made it by the fact that on Thursday Alex's preoccupied
With this video from this side
Completely falls off on Friday
He's now preoccupied with an interview on The Daily Show
There's a very minimal amount of coherent
Do this
You can't
You can't be that obsessed with that video and then just
Forget about it
I'd like at least mention it
Does he mention
I don't I mean
I would have remembered if you did
If he did it was in such passing that it was yet important at all
Yeah it's pretty it's pretty tough
You know what I think
I think there's a possibility that he recognizes it like
There's nothing to do on that front today
It'll be there for awhile let's focus on trying to build something
Pulling out of his Biden Daily Show thing
Right to the point where
It's another plate we're spinning
It does feel a little bit jarring
To be like
They're killing
F****** people in hospitals and this video proves it
And then it just be like a B on The Daily Show
Belief in what it is you're saying there's no possible way that you can spend a whole show on
All
Doctors are murdering people for money and then the next day
You see what Biden said on The Daily Show
The biggest story of the world of doctors are murdering people
I should be and that's kind of a towel but they're not
Most important thing on this episode
Thanks
They'd only two people were charged in the assassination of Mike
It's so revealing
Like I would say that the assassination of Abraham Lincoln is
Or there's a lot of very important events that shaped American history
You know his vice president was really trustworthy
I think
I think I think sober Isaac Clarity you could say that it's probably kopke
So I just think it's
Doesn't know
That story at all how many people were charged
And that's the only other person
Cuz I didn't know
I don't know if
You would know I don't know what everyone's awareness Bass
I would assume that you would have known that it wasn't just two people
Oh yeah I know there were are there were up I mean Mary Surratt is also a very important thing gets taught in history
Woman murdered by the United States and it's such a piece of the story of the Lincoln assassin
Seems impossible to educate yourself on the subject and not know about her
Mud
Is the only other person who is charged
And if you know about what happened after the assassination
You know that boot
Sled with Harold
So you know that like
There's another person who was with him
How to just f****** stupid
When you see things like that that
To borrow from
A philosopher named Alex Jones
Is that the Rosetta Stone
Make stuff out you got it
Confident
Exactly
The terrifying yeah it is
So we'll be back
Website
We are on Twitter
Could please find a local charity or anything that you can do
Do to help in the areas that you are
Indeed
Turd blossom
Holding
Alex
In color
I love your work