Air Jordan
Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for its knowledge B
Knowledge fight
Just a little bit
Question
Here's my bright spot I am madly in love with
I mean it's too early to say overcommitted but I really I really like
His place
Smooth
I think everybody out there who was sent to the
Of a smooth painless transition
That's not my bright spot
Got something in this apartment that I have been
Unknowingly looking for for my whole life that is a signifier of adulthood
A junk drawer
I never had to text Gerard
I have
Aluminum foil or plastic wrap
We're talkin about a screwdriver
Aluminum foil
The extra one for once I run out of this one
Phones that are completely dead
A couple of rocks
From back when I had a juul
There's always a playing card somewhere
To actually have a dedicated Place stuff in a box
Cintas
I didn't realize how much
It would be gratifying
Just have a drawer
Associate with being an adult like it's something that every grown-up house has like
Mike
Clutter and everything but they absolutely had a junk drawer in pretty much every house I didn't realize that
It's great I now feel
Complete yeah you're welcome
Thanks about you what's your Best Buy
I was going to have
I got to ride the train and I haven't heard the train in such a long time
So I could walk to a little further partner
Every single day
Experienced the wobble wobble
Yeah I hate it when I first moved here
Derail every time I wrote it took like 4 years for me
Yeah part of that was that when I first moved here all of my jobs were downtown
I lived in Lakeview
There's an express bus that runs on Lakeshore Drive from Lakeview to downtown
It takes like 5 minutes to get the never had to take
Take that to work
Going to shows
Stop
Is brown wine into that too
Bacci's
The very first time that I took the the L I was 7
19 we were up here for a New Year's Eve celebration
And on the way back
Somebody was very very drunkenly threw up on another guy
Such a red wine stain
Got stabbed so yeah I love it
A small town
Do you know
What the first time
To go to another for a mutual friend of ours
Chicago
Are the first time I come and we took the owl around and I had none of those fears
There was something about like I live here
Missouri coming up to the big city
Differently that's weird
Well congratulations on coming back to the
Yes
Episode
This isn't helping the rumors that I am Alex Jones
By the entire time
Studio
This is disturbing pattern
This really is a disturbing pattern
It seems to happen more than I would like I'm comfortable with
Anytime
Take vacations
He's listening anymore couple months back and then he was out of Studio
Yeah that Monday Tuesday Wednesday
Today ever recorded
It's all like we have
No Alex
Yeah I wanted to do because the first
Episode regarding the apartment I was like
Alright I can take back that whole thing about not doing Project Camelot episode
Come on Carrie YouTube channel
Of course there's no new episodes I'm going to respect
Phuc yea Jim Bakker
Jim Baker's are boy
He's AWOL
He's been gone from his own chauffeur
To the last
Scott knows how long
So I
Back to the wall I don't know what to do
I'm actually
This is a good time for a shout-out
Like he was out at 2
Wrote me a message on Facebook
And alerted
And it's definitely worth our time today
Some of the other shows
Like let's say the War Room
And this is one such
Is definitely
All right about what happened on June 12th
On the war room and
Real stupid
That makes sense
Signed up north boarding shows
Got to say thank you
Next
The cutest dog in the world I guarantee that
No competition
Thank you so much Molly you are now
Gabriel K thank you so much
You're an alcoholic
Gabriel
Last initial thank you Luis you're now probably walk
I'm a policy wonk
Gloria Lewis
11 yd
That sounds like
Lucas Neff
Chris Glover
Is it
You are now a technocrat you are now
Clever
Eddsworld
Technocrat
I'm a policy wonk
We got to go
Heroin
Ashley large
What's today
Thank you so much
You are now Iraq
Star Princess
Four Star
You're Beautiful song
They're coming for your balls
It's all over your God
Very few people
When they are
At juice
Thank you so much industrial robots
Appreciate it
Take that generosity
Bye
Pay it for sure why not
Earrings Grambling
How to make it work for a
Make a paper mache something and then send it to a charity I
People feel about paper mache in general because how to make it work
Theranos
Alright
So we we've hit the ground run
We are now
Alright and
Corner stores around here
The neighborhood check things out
And I managed to find a place that had the San Pellegrino essenza
Lucy's
Singlecare
I don't want to buy a phone
Box of them
Expensive and I might not like them
Absolutely Pellegrino line of sparkling water
They all knocked it out of the f****** part
Call Verity
So far
And we got to one that is the blood orange and black raspberry
Is good
Hi.
Text Eminem
Redundant
But is very good that is also a 78
Wild strawberry
This a little better than the other two
Very highly
Remote
I went and I got this brand
Pure aqua
P u r
Right is a white grape flavor
Apologetic
Apologizing to white grape flavor and not
You are you are apologizing to white grape for f****** I'm apologizing Institution
Flavor
I think it's a good player
But I do enjoy like
A sparkling white grape or something like that
It doesn't have the pills in it whenever incorrect
Okay whatever
Difference
Ivo Everlong history
Not good
Poorly executed
All right my apologies to bike race
Condolences
Jordan we're going to start our observation investigation
I'm here actually on June 11th
Okay because
Implications
For the 12th
From somebody by the
The end of this year I am burning this new apartment
Because we're not
Not this house
Anyway
There's no context
Yes I did just leg drop Alex Jones from the top of the news
Guy
Okay
That gives you some idea where we're going
It's not it's not nothing though
A big enough
All right ladies and gentlemen
What you see here in front of me
Is
The super
Alpha male
Championship belt
The super alpha male
The Infowars super ultimate championship belt that I now present here on the deck
So is a WWE belt
Something important
So that no one has for the alpha male champions
It's actually a Dairy Queen crown
Using is not a generic wrestling championship
It is a wrap
WWE belt
Pacific Bell
Vocal in their displeasure with some of the WWE
Particularly after the
The brand split
WWE started running two shows weekly a separate product with supper
Roster
Each show Raw and SmackDown have their own championship belts
Which follow Brandon
Freak Show
The belt on Raw generally red
Blue
The fifth marketing
The belt Owen has on his desk
It's from Smackdown
But it's also one of the Tag Team Championship
The design of the men so about belonging to the universal champion
From tag team strap
So this makes less sense than it already did
There should be a second
For some reason
Because I really thought we were going to find out that Owen had chosen a specifically racist
Wrestling belt of subsoil
History goes all the way back
To the beginnings of segregated WWE wrestling
That's what I was expecting
A little bit of a drop
Are we going to find out this is a racist
Current Smackdown Tag Team Champions are the new day
One of the most important groups in WWE
Beginning of the day they started horribly conceived
Gospel Choir
Theme team
Xavier Woods
Kofi
Eventually took the gimmick into their own hands they really got creative what they're doing
The currently one
The few groups in the WWE who actually seem to be having a great time together with
Nick's organic is now in
Possible to really explain
But involves unicorns torso thrusting Xavier Woods playing a trombone cause playing
Cakes of people and having their own cereal called booty-o's
Okay honey clearly have quite a large amount of control over the things they do like
Xavier Woods
Named his Tramp II trombone Francesca character
They hold the record for the longest Reign history of WWE
Steam traps and are Sure Shot
For the Hall of Fame
Kofi Kingston born in Ghana is the first african-born wrestler to ever be World Champ
Winning about Monsanto
Classic match at WrestleMania 35
In the lead-up
What's the match
Xavier had to win a gauntlet match in order to get Kofi into the championship fight
And despite some clunkiness
It was actually have each other's back
I want to see each other
Succeed
Where is so many other WWE tag teams are just
Preamble 41 member turns on the other to setup a hotspot
The new day has been
Pretty adamant that they are never going to
The Break-Up
Biggie put it this way
I'm not saying the Kobe doesn't get a world Title reign without the new day but you don't get that same with that same
Moment of Brotherhood
That same story of two guys who've been able to go through the gauntlet to get their brother his title match
Able to do the last couple of years that is unique and special
You don't get any of those Momin
We listen to people that say actually you should turn heel
It's my time I should really make this time about me
That's not something that even remotely
In 2018 Xavier Woods said quote
I don't remember a group in wrestling that hasn't
Turned on itself group again
Newday I'm telling you is right now do they will never turn
Ever and that's because we have zero desire to ever do that
Zero desire to go to work and not work with my
My friends
He went on to say quote we will all retire before we turn
That's a legitimate answer
That's not some thing that because it's happening
Know my government name is Austin Watson
Austin wanted to tell you that this is a truce
They love each other
Theralogix
Espresso creativity the branches into like
Some of their nerdier interest like
Xavier Woods a super into video games that he started the show called up up down down
We're human other wrestlers play video
The game competition
Spiraled into like massive popularity
Grape and enjoying every moment
Wonderful
Great day is a really great story three friends doing something great together in a shity
Pretty full of horribly sexist and racist
Does tendencies
If I had to guess I would bet that Owen has no idea he's using as a prop
What it is
Or how the individual competition
Or even who the rightful owners
It's just interesting to me how it's the worst possible belt
The chosen to using is there in
That's where I thought we were going
So I think about this a little bit
AJ Styles is currently the Intercontinental Champion and that dude is probably
Okay
Show in the title
AJ Styles
Debunk stocks
Masculinity
Spell are you sure
Sure wasn't
I don't know use the universal championship
Monster among men
Stroman
Seems like a really likeable guy for a while but
She took to the internet to s*** on out-of-work wrestlers who are having trouble paying their bills.
Because most wrestling events were canceled
After the Coronavirus
Caesars
Yeah those are both individual
It's held by due to probably think Alex might be onto something
The only downside is that the universal champion on the Intercontinental Champion her way too close to one world champion
Battery for what
This is stupid just because it's a tagged
So so disrespectful
Who Alex almost certainly thinks our heels because they're not
Yeah that would be the
The only explanation there
Bizarre to me the layers of
Maybe think it's a
Accidental circum
Suck up there
Course it's going to have some sort of
Connotation that he's not even aware of
Nothing they do nothing they touch
Does not wither
With racism
This was a horrible racist
I'm sure that
But I would strongly suspect
And they just got whatever about
Of course it is any of the other one
Cliff Owen talks about what the plan is here
Here's what's going to happen
Tomorrow
In the final segment
And I'm putting everyone here on blast I was going to be nice and I wasn't going to death now I wanted to razz me a little bit so
So here's the deal
Tomorrow
The first
Ever
Infowars super alpha male
Champion
Brought to you by super male Vitality in Alpha power
Infowarsstore.com
The first ever super Alpha Mill Champion will be crowned tomorrow
In the last segment
And we're going to be having a push-up competition
And I was going to be nice to everybody
But you wanted to harass me so I'll go ahead and say it
I'm going to kick all your ass
I don't know how they got that sponsorship
Appeal
Superman
Some really really picky with what
Easy just greenlit the show
Celebrities
They would sell
Unbelievable
Jesus
When is trying to cut a promo about
Cuz they're trying to ape
The WWE wrestling
Striped cut promo
All the sudden doing this on her show
Contest whoever wins gets MSNBC for another
I don't know how
In other news the Kremlin owns MSNBC
Shirtless on a horse he can do a s*** ton
So here Owens cutting a promo
Way too long response
I'll be surprised if anybody here in this building can even do half the push-ups I can do
We've had some people float Darren mcbreen's name around
He's old he's washed up
Some people said maybe Rob back there can do it
Too much hair
Heavyweight him down
The Charisma this guy
There's some lady's back here that all day
Now
No
No folks do so there you go so here is what will be my belt
In 24 hours
This is a
Tragic approximation of a guy trying to cut a wrestling promo
Not good
You just think that he's better at push-ups than the people in the office
And an unnamed woman in the office there light
But they can't stop him
The thing is that there is nothing here to sink your teeth
There's no passion behind this nor is there any
Switch Archy
Wrestling promos to work
Greatest Promos in WWE history was from King of the Ring 1996
A stone-cold
Steve Austin just defeated Jake
The snake
To win the King of the Ring
Tournament
Let's listen to the
This promo and then I'm going to lay out the way
This program is successful and OMG
I'm at the back door
Studio
The first thing I want
Crap out of my ring
Don't you
Bruce Sun
You ain't got what it takes anymore
Bible
And you say your prayers
Talk about your songs talk about John 3:6
Austin 3:16 Says I Just whooped your ass
Fieldstone called
Bottle of Thunderbird
I'm serving notice
Everyone of that WWE
Superstars
I don't give a damn what they are
Girl on the list
Start running
Alright Stone Cold Steve Austin
Anna's remarks
96 WWE
I don't give a damn if it's Davey Boy Smith
Call Shawn Michael
Steve Austin's time has come
And when I get those shots are looking at the next WWE
Headmaster bottom-line
Music apps
At the beginning
Because he
You know you saying he's washed ashore
That's kind of a better version of Owen just saying
Because Stone Cold added layers
Same to impart meaning
Jake The Snake was a really religious character says don't to create is Austin 3:16 catchphrase
Jake was a recovering alcoholic so we brought up the idea of a bottle of Thunderbird giving him back his confidence that he lost
These are ways of saying that your opponent is old and washed up without saying something so boring is just
You're old
That makes the promo compelling
Because Stone Cold
Take a picture with words instead of just saying
A thrashing has fallen upon its don't beat up later
This is how you do it when your goal is to pump yourself up against a nonspecific
Opponent
Uncle doesn't know who he's fighting
Next
This isn't
This isn't anything other than just self-aggrandizing
I'm better than everyone
Kind of thing
Davey Boy Smith he's old John Michaels Hair weighs too much
Wasted time on boring insults choosing instead to make passing reference
Focus on the best
And his time
Has come
That would have been great if Stone Cold
A lot of people think
About 8 the truth tri-light
Batter
Wrestling promos you really only want to talk about
Things get a little bit
Computer grandmother supposed to supplement existing
Storyline
The King of the Ring tournament and go was getting a title shot
Not so it makes sense for him to just beat and let everyone know that
What moving forward
The flipside of this kind of bra best exemplified by
The hard time
Promo delivered by Dusty Rhodes back in 1985
At the time Dusty and just returned from an injury he suffered at the hands of Ric Flair
He was finally getting a chance for Payback
Specifically targeted at Ric Flair
Let's listen to the
I would like to thank the many many faster at this country
Bedroom 20 the American dream while I was down
I want to take Jim Crockett promotions
Call waiting to take it at a because I know how important was
Any positives to the reservoir that is the Democratic promotion
Conductor of the American dream
What deadweight
Got what I wanted
What are the World Heavyweight Champion
I don't have to pay a lot more
About the way I feel about Ric Flair
No respect
Moana
But if you want to do Mondays in the first place
Time do Dusty Rhodes and his family
What does
I want to text I'm working around this contract
Waterworks
Bottle water bottle
Summertime dogs and hard times
But when I'm mad as working a job
What are you
Spider-Man watch
And say hey
Took your place.
OurTime
U-Pull-It
And we all had hard times together
I don't look like that Selena today
Little big
But brother
I am better they know I bet
Pendawa to bad people
When will John Wayne he's dead brother
Ridge Apartments
Right now
I won't do it all good no
Marlin
All over the world now
Because
The love
I will repay you now
I will be
World
Heavyweight champion
Enterprise
Major Von
Let me leave you with this
One way
Tell her.
McFly
Just take what he charges more than anything in the world
That's the world heavyweight title
I'm going to take it I've been there twice
This time when I take
Make a daddy
I'm going to take it
For you
Los Gatos
Don't let me down now
Cuz I came back
For you
So that man up there that
The dad
12 years ago and never got the opportunity
Castillo real wolf camp
I'm proud of you if they got a head
And I love you
Amazing
Amazing Obama's 2004
Recognized
Third grade
Union organized exactly
Everyone knows that Alex is going to be arguing over this stupid belt
So it makes sense that I just cut a promo on Alex Clare
No one thinks or the payoff it is going to be like
Gary is going to get her ass kicked
I have bad news about the payoff
But anyway
Steak about the Dusty Rhodes
Ric Flair fight
It's not just about who is Champ
It's about Ric Flair injuring Dusty and Dusty coming back because he loves the fan
He connects with the audience
It makes if you were feeling
Invested in him winning
You bring pesos to the feud by comparing his being injured and unable to work
Do the everyday person out there who got laid off or work 30 years and got to watch
He's making himself someone that the audience
Can project their own feelings onto and relate to
You want to Route 414.
And watch him beat up Ric Flair because he's elevated this into being
Himself being a stand-in for you or someone you know fighting
Cool faceless business as represented by Ric Flair
That's a very simple thing
Masterfully executed
Within a matter of a couple minutes
You have just like every like
Amazing Stories
Compare that to what
He just said you can do a lot of push-ups
So what
Are tons of examples of wrestlers are dukaki
Gimmicks
Another thing is that they're cocky
Usually the villain
Play up the annoying characteristics of a cock
So you as if you were really want to see the guy who don't like
Beating up
So obsessed with his body
Ted DiBiase always brag about being a millionaire
These were things that they played up
To make it more satisfying to see them get their comeuppance
In terms of being a cocky heel
Even failing
Another thing that Dusty does amazingly well is that he never says that Ric Flair sucks
This is so important and good wrestling promos because if your whole argument is that your opponent sucks
You've ruined the fight
If you're saying your opponent sucks and then you win so what
You beat someone who sucks
If you lose then you just lost someone who sucks
It's not a good way to build towards a fight
And good practitioners are able to put the
Cells over and simultaneously put over there
They're like hey you know what you're you're really good but I'm better that kind of
Is essential
Because Owen fails to even do this he's basic
Setting up a boring as hell
All departments are trash
So why do this yeah I'm going to do twice as many push-ups
The other people in my office
Is a lame thing to do
Even if you're not on
A radio show
Pretty lame yeah if you're just in regular office and you were like
You suck radio show that's in million times worse
It's clearly a situation where they're like let's do a play on wrestling ocean
Didn't think
Through any of the ways we could make it
Good well you have to think it through
It's it's shockingly embarrassing
And they don't
Bright
Maybe even you.
Because this is the wrestling that I like the most
The storytelling aspect of it
Good wrestlers Dallas
The people often don't understand at all
People just think the wrestling is people fake punching each other than occasional yelling into microphone
And that's pretty unfair
Also I'm making a big point about this because it's
Clearly a plan B
They have a replica belt just for the Segway
Owen is announcing that a champ is going to be crowned a day in advance
Infowars has every opportunity to prepare and actually try to do something decent here and this is what they come up with
They're trying to ape the style of an art form they don't understand and have no respect
And just comes off really embarrassing
I can listen to that clip of him challenging
People in his office
Do a push-up contest
NSYNC
This guy
Has it
I don't know what it is it's
That's not good
It's not good
There's a recognition or some kind of a feeling that a lot of people and Alex's might be wrestling fan
But if they are
I don't think they would enjoy that
Owen lazily insulting people that he's going to have a push-up
We got this prop
Good enough
Done nothing is worse than a
Corporate entity
Do you like taking over and just
Not pleasure of patronize
Such a disrespectful
If you like wrestler
Here you'll like this s***
Right right
Approximation of slop on your f******
Snap stock
So intense this announcement
Not to belabor the point but what someone with a bad back
Contest
It's it's
Nonsense less of an alpha male
Because you quit is debunking
Masculinity
Kentucky sucks
Email anymore
Consult AJ Styles on this
Comes down to
Bream versus Owen Shroyer
Right
Where do we get we don't get anywhere good
This was Darren mcbreen's flute
This is his Michael Jordan it's like
It comes from behind Adeno
Michael Jordan
He is not
Just keep saying like just like I want you
Which is uninspired and boring but at least
It's not destructive to the
Concept of the competition
To build towards
12 episode of the War Room opens up with a t-shirt
I know it's been super into props lately
You get the skull chess set
Rose thing
Comes off as a little desperate
Everybody loves
Props
That's why the most famous comics in the world
Comics
True
Oh yeah
Really f***** up was that
The big logo that's on the screen behind Atlanta
Says
War of War Room Raw
No definitely get them the owners of the WWE
Grecia
The small business administration president
Bravo
And I think
As I understand the WWE
Text to Sue people here's my biggest issue
With this whole thing
Alright do you realize
How infuriatingly close to a palindrome
War Room raw is
Yeah it is really close
Infuriating to me how they could do that that fux with my brain like now that I know that it's
Almost 2 lb rub it makes me so angry
Yeah
Bino bra and War
It is not clickable
It's not for real easy War
Difficult for me to handle
Call Soto
Sure
Well I'm going show
Interesting enough to robot or discuss on our show
What's a quorum it's a show that's almost done
Exist
It's boring
Just covering the same
He doesn't pretend he's a psychic or throwing any of the other insane bulshit that Alex does to make the show interested
I don't care about anything going covers on the show but I do cut up this one clip
From when he was 2
Taking calls
22nd
Alright well met
Make yourself
A directive
Advance directive
And out
Acetate
Medical decisions for them
Be legally allowed
Hospital
All right so they're go folks little inside there
Also a taser
Maybe some brass knuckles
Maybe some lead as well
I've heard that I don't know I'm not saying that works I'm not sure
That was shocking even to me
Yeah that was a mess
With a taser
Brass knuckles
Playfully suggesting that listeners should basically you have a lace
That would normally be a pretty dumb thing but in the
The climate we rented a business
Credibly Danger
We talk better than recent episode
Uptick in people trying to attack Hospital
Whether it's because of the added impact would give their political message or because they believe the virus is a hoax
Hemet Hospital's are in on it
Anybody who'd play into this the way Owen is doing right there is
Trying to get more attacks
There's no other excuse for that kind of comment other than your audience to hurt Medical
I've been spending a lot of time on the wrestling aspect of the show but it's important to remember that Owen is a huge piece
Piece of s*** and it shows just a
Is Extreme an awful is Alex's
That's still stick
With a push-up
And how poorly set up it was conceived for the X
Executor
It's important to recognize that like that
Although it is at all so
Yeah that's
To remember
The juxtaposition of them is so
F****** insane having a stupid push-up
Propaganda
Like it is just all man look at this guy's other there oh and by the way it's a good idea to continue
Gaming with juice
Alright next mode Lex KY up to the thing
Baby. Very popular.
Owen tries to get through his show and get
Maybe about like an hour in 10 into the show edits
Push-up contest is not really broke
And he's just wearing a stupid shirt
Atlanta t-shirt
Could you wear a tank top no
From listeners who are stupid
And
You know what's going to happen
Mainstream media is dividing America by Design
110 percent
Yes sir
I thought you were in a lot of pain from a tooth extraction
Youth
I'm going to win that belt Alex
Nobody here can do as many pushups
Because
Well first off I'm already so
Just because you're young where is the rat
What the song mean
I want to be the one where is the RAF
Alex is probably
Drunk Santa
About
Can't put it on
You can't figure out how to put the belt on
And he's like
Trying to latch the buttons on the back
Eva Eva
Stupid voice
Owen doesn't even stand up
Plywood
Time Warner. You
Do you have
Active do the most pushups
This is by Fiat you're like Joe Biden dumb you're trying to steal a bell
Bald man
You're trying to steal your trying to steal
You're trying to steal about right now
You're like a Democrat
You want to mail in Maryland championship
So the guy who sang disallowed internal put on a red shirt
Are you coming
Structure to the bed
Trying to attack the ref
Puts his hands on the rest
Explodes backwards
And falls over
It's just an embarrassing silly poorly-executed pratfall
This is like all that stuff and there's no actual fighting it's just
Overdramatic
I got to say right off the bat this bit is not going well
So far it sounds like a bunch of assholes out of YouTube clip that nobody should have watched
In the first place
Deserves about
How long is the championship belt Preserve
Is going on here
Blackmail Championship out as being abscond at right now
Alex Jones is absconding with the belt he's now running out of the studio
He's now absconding with
The super alpha male championship belt folks this whole thing is now is now
Open stolen by the Democrats
So just like everything else they just they just steal everything vote
You're here and you might as well be a Democrat right now
So In that clip
Miss Alex
It's about being chased by the rest
Continue through the offices route to the loading dock
Any can't resist yelling mail in ballot
Haven't broken the seelie besides
Back to Ocean
That's quick about
Reaper seeds to try to put the belt on his head
Like it's a crown
Booty has trouble because it's about
Okay
This is a disaster
This is like an elementary school
Informative play that they do to teach you about the
The dangers of smoking and how ml do a nice little fun skit about it'll be a whole sketch and even a three-year-old
Even that third-graders like this is f****** lame dude that a lot when I was in junior high
Victoria Elementary School
New York
Depressed
And
Spirit guide
Feel like it would work
I was Winnie the Pooh
About that
Tigger
But
Yeah I could like it was one of those weird
I was in junior high
I thought like
Acting with a path I was going to go to her
Everybody
Even at that point looking back I can't remember like
The kids were not in
What we were doing
I could tell that we were
About Winnie the Pooh
The junior high
Write this is a skit
Mostly being improvised by a bunch of
Yeah yeah
Play plan
Denny's bumrah showing show any wants to play with the phone
Yeah so Alex like I said he's trying to put this belt on his head
Are you struggling with that
Philly syndicated radio show
National radio host
To heads of state
Secret Service
About
I don't think it would even fit around your head Alex
I don't think it's going to fit
You got to go get your Corona count
Time for that
Oh
It does double as a Corona mask
There it is
And it also
Can be used as a weapon
With that that heart rate
No but you're not a minority
Are you thinking even play that card
Balding fat dessert
Maybe at the office but in America you're in the majority
Or what
You guys are great
Yeah the Hallmark of any great comedy
Is Adnan racism
Completely unrelated
Great
You have this situation where his head
It's not work
Loses track of it and it's his face
Answer the written about being a Coronavirus
It's very sad
Nothing's working it's a low energy
It's like Alex is trying to
To bring some chaos into visit make it interesting but it's just
Is it a two-man improv seating
Okay hi welcome to this bus I'm the bus driver how are you today
Operating tables
So what you're describing is
Is good
Greater bro
The buttons to work
Any desire
Redeem about racist
Oh yeah
Know your
No you're in the majority now
Well they're probably made in China
Actually I don't know
Can you put together for me
Let me see this year
Get on your knees right now
Get on your knees and then Crown you
Trying to see where the thing was made
I'm not playing Sonia
It is going to feel nice though
When I'm legitimately
Decided
I tried to look it up and I know that
The toy belts one
For kids by Mattel I don't know about the adult
Like the normal size
Owen is looking at the inside of about and I know that there is
A little tag inside there a little late
And if you'd seen made in China
Curiosity being Center of all their f****** racism
Would you assume the answer to your question is directly in front of
Or ask yourself a question
It's unwise for you to speculate
Because there's only two possible outcomes
You're right
You have revealed that you assume anything you don't like
It's that it's just not
From a standpoint
It's not a winning strategy
Now what you want to do is get snot.
If you can right right make sure you put yourself in a tunnel and back yourself into a corner
And that will lead you to where Infowars it which is a very six
So
I still can't get this on and
You turn it into a face mask
Mommy
Yeah I could see that
See you aren't you have turned into a Democrat I don't know what happened to you
Democrat
What is that
Video
Did you
What
No chops are
Bull boy
Because he does there that I
Is dancing like a Democrat
Very similar to the signature dance
The Big E
Of course
So you know it's only a lonely dance move
That's totally but it also could imply
And he doesn't want
Is kind of
A bland
Generic dance but it is also what biggie does Riley make a big deal out of it
Like like other wrestlers will like join in the dance with them
The tide of the trademark of the new day
Well Owen respond suggests that he is not seeing Alex dance in any fashion
About the new day
It's like a Democrat what does that even mean
I don't know
What do you like that was
An insult
Meaning nothing
Isn't there some sort of
I think more than that
I think you could dance in anyway
Just wants to make fun of
2B I want him to
Pin down on this I want specific moves that are Democrat or Republican
The floss is Republican a s*** I'll tell you that right now
Listen to this
Did you
What
Did you drink some of the fluoride
Did you watch CNN
Be honest do you watch
CNN
And now you're you kind of
Be like Don Lemon
Lemon for a while
You like Trevor Noah to you moved on from Don Lemon to Trevor Noah
Are you still upset
The Don Lemon dumped you
That's not how it works
No no put the belt on him
Alex deserves this belt
Terrarium
We should be playing on a loop in a terrarium
Thousands of years in the future
Used to be like
Look at what prehistoric man was
It does feel very much like it's shocking
This is an 2020
This is
This is Chrome magnetic
It's funny cuz it's a disaster
Second I can't imagine anyone watching this and being like
I trust these guys to read
Buy information
Improv
Yeah you know people like to cut loose
This is such a
This is a telling
Oh man
These guys
Feels like he's entitled to no one will help him
With the straps
Jones too drunk for buttons
Deserves all this stuff and then
It starts to get into the zone
You need to go to the autonomous Zone where everything's done
M4u this is America
That little you go to the park
This is not
Chaz
That is this is not Chad
That only happens that magic only happy for jazz
Porta-Potty right here
There's our Porta-Potty from Chaz
Hold on guys
But get the shot that Alex is using the Porta-Potty from Chaz
You don't want to know what just happened
So at this point the recipe years and gives Alex a bag to serve as a porta potty
Alex places that on the ground in front of Owens desk
Please remember this is a family show
I have no idea why but there's a weird statue that looks like a Roman Centurion sitting on the floor in front of them
Alex
It just looks like you shiting on this statue
It's very not that funny
They pulled it out it's unintentional
This is Opera
So many high school parties
Still in high school and having a good time and then there's the drunk guy who's lost his f******
Can't handle his liquor anything like that and everybody's kind of look at it as like
To just get this guy out of here
But there is three around always egging him on
Keep doing this
And you hate the party and anyways I f***
I hate Todd
You know what it's like a this is also Friday
Is last Friday
Does kind of like an office where people
And like
Start drinking in half an hour once my show's over already
That's the vibe
Who cares
I was just painted by shooting on a bag gym bag
Pretty grave so now Alex leaves
You didn't know that
Cisgender
You want to go
You want to cancel Paw Patrol to
Unbelievable
You would
You want to cancel
Paw Patrol
You want to cancel everything
I'm not
We'll have to find out
I guess he's not
Wow Alex isn't leaving
In this several minutes ago
Go home clip Alex said
Start another conversation about how many push-ups Owen
2nd phone call with my
Keep going
Alex
Skip the talking about how are you
But there's a catch
Why you want some food
You are a social justice Warrior
No I'm saving up my energy
That would be
Yeah
I'm not sure that's regulation
11:00
Let me see anyone more
I don't really care but Alex is doing.
He's only going about halfway down formation
He basically looks like a guy who doesn't do push-ups regularly trying to act like a tough boy while drunk at a party
Exactly what's going on
What's going on with that exactly
You know I hang out with
When we get together
Can we start riffin we have a good time we laugh out loud we express Joy with each other
Something along the lines
These guys don't seem to express Joy just like
Energy
Play just have
It's coming out but it's
Kind of manners
Yeah
It doesn't feel like they're having fun
No actually
Can if you just stop being so racist and saying everything is a social
Justice Warriors
Presentation
Hemorrhoids
Lawn mower
Answer this no 10,000 10,000
We are get into that
I know you spell
Justice Warriors don't like rules
But I'll tell you what they found
You got to do one more there
Just one more
Tell me there's a whoopee cushion
So the first thing to note is that Alex is definitely
Constant talk about exercising every morning
And what have you
Weird noise you hear there at the end is Owen jumping off his desk and doing a little leg drop onto Alex Wiley
He was doing his last push up
It's not like a regular leg dropped Owen lands with his back
Kind of in a straddle position
How many gets up and he drops an elbow
It's probably fine but honestly this is
Kind of dangerous
Is not in good shape
And no matter what is a couple
The unprepared Alex is facing the ground in a push-up position
Wrestlers trying for a long time
And work really hard to do things safely they
If you try to run
Recreate will really hurt some
Some basic wrestling moves of John for real
Straight up Killa purse
Like a DDT that's a normal move
The Finisher most
The time you gave someone a DVD onto a hard surface you could very easily knock them out
Give the brain.
Driver could easily kill a person or break their neck
Even professionals have a hard time with that one was mostly band but WWE
After Owen Hart box wanted SummerSlam 1997 Stone Cold Steve Austin
Yearly paralyzing
Horseplay is fun but when you're jumping off you know stuff onto the back of it
Clearly exhausted 46 year-old who just had oral surgery
You're not playing safe
Man this may not have let any real issues with the decision-making that leads you to do that kind of thing as
An adult
Is very suspicious
Three suspects
So Alex has been
Out since
Yeah
Did Owen kill Alex
No I don't think so
Something cuz that would be pretty great
Hitler was Hitler killed
Couldn't be that
Like if Owen took down Alex Jones's
Leg drop
I'll be pretty funny
National thing or
Through maybe Family Court
There are
You're not doing well in life if they are so many possible reasons that you can delete all the stuff
Probably Owens like Drop
So are the elbow
This is Xavier
Alex
Police in this country how you like that
My God
What are we doing
Alex Jones dad
That guy just break in there
Is war room is raw for nothing
So that makes no sense
Why is Owen saying this is what we do the police in this country
Is Owens gimmick supposed to be that easy
The parody of his own fears of the last
Is if so
Or is Alex's gimmick supposed to be that he's a
The cop
Because that hasn't been established at all
However to help make sense of Alex, just taken
About
It could be a civil asset forfeiture angle sure how much fun would that be
I need this to be more interesting but really it
It's just Owen being shity at the
Bestop off-the-cuff
Confusing as hell
Hitting
Alex Jones with a belt in your own Troy
It's it's imagine
To work being done
It's
Like those
Like you learned the worst
Lessons of humor from Family Guy where it's like if you just make a reference to a different thing that's
Kind of humor
Visual
So after this point
Written off TV
Any leaves
Congratulation
Answer calls
The truth
This works for a little while
Doesn't doesn't really work
Divide weather
Are you got to be
Either division is Love Now division is inclusion now
You didn't know
I did not
I didn't know you were
Clarifies
Bird facts
Is Lumber back into the studio and
What's about
Oh I should also say Alex is carrying a big guy cup and he's clearly just it to the Superbowl
That's a real judge
Is gray radio
You're all off the air
Money's mine
You are very tired
Walmart payment now
He is breathing super heavy it's gross
You so gay
He has no cardio he just did a little fake attack on on
Oh my God
It's scary
It makes me wonder how he's able to yell for like 5 minutes straight without
That is
Jesus taking over the show
Nothing better than just a weird old man grunting together and then
BJ Thomas's to steal buddy
Dismount
This resolves itself
Satisfying
Conclusion
Sinbad
I will say I will
Standing over somebody
Is not bad
And Alex
Explains why
Apologize
He's got a gas house ready but I did
This is Owatonna
Madonna
Choreographer millionaire attachment
The matter comes up within the hour
Of course
What's happening now is gone backstage input on a Doctor's lab coat
Choking out
Spencer's
This is real
Rihanna
We got a truck out of water
We got a whiny now
Who are you people
We got a white meat
We took a yd out
Reverse your privilege
Get out of here
So he is now walking Alex
To the back
Alex is the highest quality programming ever
Do off camera being shuffled out the door
Disney
King Boo
All right well this is not
This is a family show
The family show
I was wounded by Alex Jones you saw it
I was assaulted right in this chair
What is happy
Security
Also it's the second time in like a month that Owen is pretended to murder Alex by strangulation
Vision board
Selling Alex's attack
He's remembered that in this established reality there
Pretending to be in a situation where he should be
I was just attacked him with the belt and beat him up so when he shows back up
It makes no sense if he doesn't have some kind of an injury
Small hat tip
2014 understanding that element of Storytelling
Alright
Unfortunately that's Mall hats it doesn't
Anywhere near big enough for the
Did you receive
For everything else in that segment so
Nikki came back with the doctor's coat nose like he was a different characters when he shows back up as himself used
Oh Alex
Beat me up a lot of wrestlers even
Forget Xterra
It's so
It's so obvious
Like
These people have never even talked
Human what are you talk
We got a Whitey
Like they're a mess
Imagination they have is just their own like
It's stupidity
Creative
Save
Like that
That's what they think the
And it is
It's so weird
Never had fun so I think one really pretty clearly drunk
Slurring and I get really worried
Want to hear him say that the reason he hasn't left
Just cuz you can't find you forgot it
Is because someone hit them and called him a cab
That is really f***** up like the idea that he's driving
No he was drinking his I can't find my keys
That one they have in Katy
That's all he does that every
Positive
You better hope he is
Because that's normal
Implies something
Is not solved by striated
The rights getting too good
They are really good
That's what I that's what I take away from this is
Why aren't there more conservative comics
It's because we're censoring
Totally
So
I thought that this was the payoff
Who is an actual
Get the f*** out of here overproduce with like fake audience cheering and then
Fake firework after the announcement of the winner of obviously Owen
It's really a disaster
This is another thing where they suck up what wrestling is
Alex and him doing this is the main event
That's the main event
Don't even do the push-up contests
Yeah
Darren mcbreen Rob do Marcos Morales and
You have peace
This is like giving away paper view match
And then
I don't know doing nothing on the Pay-Per-View
Bad business
It's not good no
This is
To approximate what wrestling is
Complete
Lack of understanding lack of Interest like awareness like a preparation
Look better in an hour
Probably
Okay here's a coherent reason why this is happening
So it's not just
Stupid chaos
You're going to bring in the belts and announced the day before you're having some kind of a contest
Did Crown a champion you clearly raise at least
Partially invested of doing this as a bit
Bucking how bad I resent it
I resent it very much
Just come up with
Any idea
Any idea that would be better than
Especially the idea of not doing
Probably the fact that they're Infowars means they don't have access to anybody who could write something better
Decided dick around and pretend it's comedy
Thank you
Yeah that's true
So you got home safe
Curious and interested in
Comes from doesn't come from just being like
Oh yeah I saw that s*** lips
Steve Martin if you're really good at, you will end up using everything you've ever learned
As part of your act
Yes exam
Paraphrase what is something like that
Play to the top of your intelligence
We're watching whatever you're doing a much smarter than
You might want to
That's always a better Pastor cowhide Infowars
Insist
I'm going
The other direction
Because they have no faith in their audio
This is not at all
Kind of
In-depth episode that I'm interested in getting back in
To do next
I miss doing this Saturday
In a push-up contest
John Bolton's book
Apparently involves talk of trump working with has got to have a difficult time
Another was that military executive order that Trump put through
There is
The Supreme Court rulings
Today not today
Naturally
Yeah I would just think of this is the time that Alex needs to be in studio
He's gone
These are all stories that are begging
For Alex to spin
Just be Clarence Thomas in a push-up
Contest
And then he did a notebook
Absolutely and then she approved another one
So
Really interested in why Alex isn't there and I guess we'll find out what is it
Excuses whenever he gets back
I don't know I don't know what to do for Monday
Conga Alex to it
What happened
And
It's worlds on Twitter
Jordan net worth
We are and if you could please find bail fund
People to help anywhere
We would have
Call Champion
Alex
Kristen color