Air Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
College.com
Just a little bit about Alex
Joe
Indeed we are.
It it's a OK Google
Alternative milk
Are those are there racist
Whole milk
Milk substitute
I'm very excited I haven't hit a snag yet
Oatmeal
Where is there a good series
I don't know I look at the Shelf
Why are so many things
Cashew milk
How does milk even work now hazelnut milk I think almost any nut makes bill
You squeeze it gets please.
I have it it said that
Is it really strong guys with their hands
Averse to everything that wasn't just cow milk
Miter conceivably be healthier
Who's kind of like a feeling that I have like I'm not going vegetarian or vegan or anything like that
Leaning a little bit
Closer to that I want to do as I age
Opitz address
I'm definitely answer like a being able
Eating a pile of good technique
Berea being able to take that attachment away
Yellow shirt
ICloud
Friends
Very good he's got a nephew
Call flooding Factory in his
Fantastic he's a really talented artist he's incredibly over Edge
Educated went to one of those
Art schools in the country
Huge fight with Chicago
Chicago art schools photo
Jacksonville Sharks
I just I really like the good
Transporting the show
So first of all hrh
Her Royal Highness
Thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Resources
Hello
Okay
Richard H thinking about you
Ohr
Richard h
Next
Kirsten.
I don't know how to pronounce this word
DL rojulu
Thank you so much you are now but was he
Steven
I'm a policy wonk
I conceived
That's ruhks
Journal
I'm a policy wonk underwater man of the emerald River
Ewok
Emerald River
So
Casserole
I'm a policy wonk
Heroin
Is freakishly large
Thank you so much
Because arrows
Very much so
I'm done
I've heard a lot of do you remember so many inspirational comedians who said something like
You know what if you don't know where the B is
Just push through it
Trust yourself in the B
Go to your parents house
Find the cabinet where they keep last year's Christmas paper
Rap-up that generosity
I'm not meant to do this
I can't think of
Ways to wrap things
Figure out how to do this better
Do Jordan of her get to the episode
Progress
You putting almond milk in yourself
10 what do you mean
Then we are officially 50%
So this is great progress
Realizing two things
As I get in
Into today's
Shelter update job the first is that I've been really sick and tired of everybody having the same first
Almost everybody has the same dance
Burien
Everyone's got a grapefruit and none of them were good
I really am yearning for something different and some creativity a little bit of a slog
Appreciating this week some like just playing
Celtics
When you meeting sometimes you just like to go back to a nice Haagen-Dazs vanilla
Refreshing
Goodnight plain seltzer water 7 days before somebody's going to come out
Except
First time we started talking about Celtics
Concession and that was that I didn't
Like Spindrift
Right
I've tried a couple more Spindrift
Originally
I think I got the first ones that I tried
We're just some shity flavors but I've had a couple
Remember exactly what it came in
Score
So congratulations Spindrift
Lightning McQueen
Do not complement
For the Seltzer's
Today we're doing here
Episode because Alex was still out of the Steeler came back over the weekend
Sunday
Some coverage of trump Rally from last night
Oh
You questioned has Bill Hicks been doing shows ago
No
I'm guessing
I would imagine he has a lot to get an order with his house
Was metaphorical house
Need to take care of business
Maybe explain
That would not be really enough
For us to really Bank on being an episode the time we need to
It's a recording
Today
I'd like to start off this episode with an explanation
About a month ago we started covering Bill Cooper's coverage of the Oklahoma City bombing
Which I had sincerely intended to become a running weekly investigation
I was so confident that we're going to keep moving forward
Which to this point has not been revealed
Computer chip and a homeless man of our show not fair
Confusion
I promised that mystery will be solved today
The issue was that
Next week
Project
Navigation to check in on that
As well as an interesting case study in how these different fields
The next week's open slot episode
I meant that was the week that the Police murdered George Floyd sparking protests in important
Counter to what Alex wants to see in the world
It's critical that we keep a sharp eye on the present
And I know that conversation
Evolving situation protest
It would see it was important
Chronicle
Was not necessarily as interesting
We had this conversation
It's going to be
Probably
Necessarily
Conversation
So I took on its own
Also threw those couple weeks I was trying to pick up a ton of my time
The contest was the product of multiple influences
The first was that Alex have been out of studio all week
The second was that I really needed something kind of like to discuss a recording just a few days after I move the nose still work
Not settling into this new place in Owens dumb push-up
Contest fit that bill amazing
It is empty
Probably rather Oklahoma City episode
Anything I want
Yeah but I just couldn't
For a couple reasons
The first was a timer
Episodes
The second issue is probably more important
Bill Cooper's biography
Horse Show focuses on Alex Jones
Who doesn't have a biography written about him
Seems strange to me I almost felt like cheating
I really enjoy the process of discovery becomes for having no idea what's going to come up and
Learning as we go
That works all right with Alex
A big part of the story
They're important pieces of context in the biography of that I wouldn't
Ever got
Purpose listen to The Hour of the time
And those pieces of context
Are pretty important
Seinfeld to be irresponsible for me to move forward and do another episode about Bill Cooper
Without taking in Agra fee
This leads me to what I would want to
Give is a
Sort of
Sizable
Clarification
We were wrong
To give Bill the benefit of the doubt
Violently abusive he was to like his wife
This among other Revelations have caused me to question my stance
Some of the stuff in his personal life
The problem is
We're dealing almost
Tremendous monster
We're so far below
General being a fair human being
It's simply because we speak about you on our show
Chances are you should assume that they're the worst
Human being in the world maybe no maybe so
Of his life like he pushed
Well
Yeah
To which
He was
That is so rude
I don't know if we played
And I feel bad about that
You're wrong
I would like to know this stuff make it earlier
Overall I think that book
Outright making accusations
Is there was just there was one piece of information
Exploration
About Oklahoma City
Which I highly doubt I would have learned about some listening to build show
Will get that down the road
And also the thing that maybe dance around my apartment
As we go through
I recommend that book very
It's pretty good
So I can start this off
We we left off
Couple days
Call Bill Cooper head
Decided that it was false flag
Trying to make Patriots look bad
Standard operating right-wing militia
Narrative
Pieces Of Eight
Seismograph
Misinterpreting
Misunderstandings about people who have died
There was another bomb
In the building
Just taking those things and use them as
Definitive proof
Examples of interior saness
Inclusion jumping
Games on April 24th
I'm William Cooper in Georgia
City h
Overtime
Will have a much larger
Herobrine
Propaganda
Ryan
Absolutely refuse to even talk to except
November
Hugo
And I will continue that
They are
Call
They have no moral values
I have no ethics
I'm a certain ring
Wouldn't know the truth if it kept them in the head
I'm sure he does a better job of censoring himself and not house
Pretty remarkable
Sing phenomenon that seems almost entirely
Consistent which is terrifying tragedies in this country
Alex got a huge surge out of 911 denial and
After the Boston bombing
When he was yelling about it being a false flag
We've also seen him discuss lately Howie's covid-19 denialism
This makes some sense but it also says something really sad about people
It's scary to process things like a bombing or a virus outbreak of we crazy answers
There's no easy fix to its
Becomes very appealing to listen to the person saying
The virus itself is no big deal
Domestic extremists is super terrifying because no matter how much the police
They'll never be able to uncover and stop every possible plot people may come up with
It's just a reassuring thought to believe that you know there's an evil cabal of globalist orchestrating
Taken care of
Yeah if you acted the reality that ultimately no one knows what's going on
The world is complete chaos and really you can bully a lot of people who think they're powerful into doing whatever it is
It's really terrifying
In times of Crisis these kinds of narratives are an attractive crotch to reach out for help and I'm depressed but not surprised
Back in the times of Bill Cooper
It's unfortunate for the listeners because all they get is junk food narrative
Is the mean nothing
I can go nowhere
But it's also bad for people like Bill and Alex
They were in the wrong lessons
Consciously or not that the nine tragedies Elizabeth drawers
Which definitely has been a lesson that screwed Alex over
More than once
I personally
Just immediately
That's that's
Lately I've been
Left and right
Takes like
Hey let's not kill
Even know what you're wearing right
Right now shirt
Prove it
Major denial of things that are really scary you know providing easy answers
Viable
Attractive
It's just
It's just sad
I mean
I don't know
It's a bummer but
Is expected
I think it's I think it's really interesting
Just because
Deep down regardless of who like you can hate Authority or you can love Authority whomever may be in power
But what unites
Most people is just that
I want to believe somebody is in chai
I want to believe an adult
Yeah
Is part of what's being exploited also like the way he is
Like
On earned
Confidence
Project themselves as I
I can tell you for sure there was two explosion
Weird
And that wouldn't draw need to speak Authority
False confidence
Something nobody likes to hear it
Let's wait until all the facts
The media
Unicorn
Because they're actually titled CNN communist News Network
Initials for all
Organizations like
National broadcasting communist system
Like CVS of Communists broadcast service
Communist
Come on man
Opportunity
You have the ugly mug
On the television Chris
Somehow they think that work
Losing all their Liberty
And of course
Really good and do what they're supposed to do
Marxist Socialist Party Line
Someday
I hope they get
I hope it get it and I hope they get it
From the cars with their work
Looking for because they will live
Actually hope that don't really hope to forget it
Because if they do it mean the end of all of us
Women's art Liberty in the whole world goes down
Open Chrome
That's just not true
We're going people left in the world
The right to keep and bear arms
That's also not true
But you know what I was thinking about because it's the monster
Because of like what
His definition of right to bear arms
Absolute right and Tails
What is the only country
No matter what the goal post will be already tell
I suspect that
Squidbillies
Suspicious as the only country that can have guns
I can just see the first one
Quincy
We're here.
I don't want you to know that knocking move
Socialism
National
Nazi Germany
Call Solis
That's right, you heard it right here
Andres world
They're trying to turn everything around so that wrong is right and right is wrong
I don't know babe I think that anytime you hear someone say that said not to their socialist
Its headline reading
Is socialism socialism
And obviously
Democratic is in the name of North Korea's Republic
Assume that they have the right to vote
This is Dinesh D'Souza levels
Somebody should not be listening to as reasonable as believing that Americans
A progress is interested in progress Orem
Zalima name
So
History of the reichstag fire
And sign
I'm not interested in dating a lot of
Certain issues
One of them is a reichstag fire
Like what
I don't care I will talk about that are about
I'm not recovering Oklahoma
It's
Great
Going immediately informed and global
Is a communist
Outrage
The Communist culprits have been erect
Wow
Talk about
Reminder ring ring
Vaporize in Oklahoma City
Identify
Those who win today
Absolutely accurate photographic
Using wire server
Procrit
So like I said he's in the middle of reading basically an essay one of his listeners wrote about the reichstag fire
Realizing gears compare that
Situation with the Oklahoma City bombing
What great did it
And he's not a hard
Are you providing content
So bill seems to bring up two specific complaint
Axial which led to the Ryder truck
The story about the axle is actually pretty interesting
I didn't find corroborating information about that
There's an indie online piece from earlier this year
Looking back on
25 years later
Munchkin was 19 years old when he assisted in the response to the Murrah building and you'll find this
Insight truck axle in the middle of the road
12 hours later as he walked back
Investigators were circling the Excellence
He later learned that it was from the Ryder truck loaded with
Explosives
This firefighter
The axle which could have been from another car in the area whatever
Nina
It's not weird at all really that a destructive bomb could discharge something like a truck axle
I'll come on man
Soundrop
Disintegrated or something
In the real world this Axel was found and traced to a Ryder truck
Which then led to a specific location
The employee of the truck shop gave the FBI information and descriptions
Sketch
Ultimately finding a hotel where the staff
Because this was required
Timothy McVeigh had already been arrested at this point
Even pulled over by a State Trooper 90 minutes after the bombing approximately 80 miles north of Oklahoma City
About where you'd expect
About to stop the right to
Mexico without my Turbo clear
It's pretty remarkable how quickly
Supra seemingly unrelated charge
But none of that
The timing and causality the vents makes total sense
Sumter SC stronger argument
But this is a new world order
You can yell about like they found the guy so quick it's like the reichstag however communism
It's not necessarily the same thing at all just feel like everyone
When you go through this story unlike so many others
It does feel like everybody's acting almost
Reasonably
You know like there's nobody who's doing something absolutely insane on the side anytime you read about
But he's like he bombed the Federal Building
Let's get Round the Clock
Certain if you look far enough you can find
Probably some example Arkansas
Timothy McVeigh
Siri right there
I mean
Did the disease
Flimsy
It's just no good
It is is unearned
Eddie goes on because he talks about the mode
Control from 250
Model clear majority
We could Wipe Out the critical 120
He would win his title
CorePower
Roxy Authority could already waited
Call Rita
The quarters
Permanent party and bull
The Commons in Revolutionary conspiracy
Think of something else
Because of date for a 19
Was
Cockroaches
Burn
The right stuff
Control
Germany
You know the rest
And the same thing
Your carpeting here
Now
This argument is
Yeah it's the result of Desperately straining to make connection
Between historical events
Present circumstance
It's one thing to say that Hitler blame the reichstag fire on Communists in order to solidify his power and demonize is
What is a completely different
Bill Clinton became president in 1992 and was up for reelection in 96
After the 94 midterm elections
Control of boat
House and Senate so presume
Is it Bill Clinton was trying to blame the OKC bombing
Control of Congress
In the 1996 election
This did not happen
Governorship
Around the country it's always nice to remember our political system
Today that once we were allowing
With power
Which is a terrible
Bright
New
Narratives like the one bill is putting forth your sound good if you're looking for a way to blame for everything
You have to take a step back
Things that should happen if Bill Cooper is Right ever happen
Use OKC to bring in a socialist dictatorship
Disco
Did you lead you to question the conclusion
He's just talkingshit here's my problem
With his internal
Project
If if he's painting the the Nazis as a socialist
Regime
With as he would call it a Marxist socialist Doctrine
Hitler trying to get rid of
Instead of a line with
I don't think I follow
Well he's saying that
That Hitler
Right consider is Marxism and socialism to be
This is the same
So why is it that Hitler hate
In his
Worldview where in Hitler is also a communist
Would it be possible to just like wrangling in and be like hey we're getting the Communist system and they're like
When he's like or I'll kill you in there like
No answer for the
Yeah yeah
Could you saying that Hitler
You got to get rid of them
To take over
Right
Doctor's appointment
You know enter these people's minds
Insta understand
He would say that
Actually
The same
Be against each other
Alex would say
But I don't know if
Contradictory
I got nothing for you man
So there's not a whole lot of development of the storyline of the OKC bombing
Mercy on this episode
Just mostly continuation on this 24th we see him continue to talk about
The seismograph
Sunday Soundwave
So there's no mistake and I'm not making it.
Ladies gentlemen
I don't care
The government shares
You are clearly
Separate
Both of the same magnitude in the same direction
Pardoned by Kim
It clearly shows of how to read this shows up a trainer test close to
Normal traffic
Party traffic
And then the two
Two separate
Understand
Frozen
Not Echo
Murphy tractor loser
The Oklahoman
Geological Survey
Sarkeys Energy Center
University of Oklahoma
Norman Oklahoma
Received
Information on the 21st
Call April at 1:20
Thanks for the timestamp
Warriors and teenager
Communist News Network
Why aren't you recording me
To clarify the media is not covering this because bills misrepresenting this information not because the media is like
The Oklahoman reached out to doctor can lose to get a comment about the
Is Cabela's going on and on
And from the article in the Oklahoman
Recorded on the seismograph
Action which you refer to as a refraction esta
From the explosion at the federal building in Oklahoma City
He said the reading could have also come from a quarry blast
Loser describe the waves
Detective Norman is surface wave
Eastside without seismographic readings from two other locations
Geologist cannot determine where the waves came from
Sounds like the government is lying to you sure this mystery is solved eventually as we discuss our last episode
Haven't got comment from Doctor loser
The Oklahoman
Which was predictable
Until you learn how to print the proof
God dammit
Piece of information
Proof of multiple
Is not true
Yeah it's the next refraction and I'm going to need the confirmation
From two other sources
The government is f****** I don't care where's government
Tell this person who listens to Cooper Stadium show on emails
Constantly
The only thing that makes sense to me
Another tender
Spirits in here
Very
Senior supervisor
Email we're not at work that day
We're not at work
Why
Who Warren G
What the f*** is this
Doesn't mean anything
How many people is talking about not being at work
He calls them senior supervisors butts a supervisors
No specific
Pictures of agency
Well I mean they were important
Senior advisors
Account of they Worthy
How do we keep this building from being bombed
Others so that they were missing
That's the one that's the one that's going to do it
How can someone who pretends to be a justifacts
Investigate and report that a nonspecific number of senior supervisors for an unspecified agency
Bombing
Unit we go ahead and assume that an uncommon number of Supervisors were not in the building when the bomb went off
How can Bill prove that someone had to have worn them
Is it not possible that some of them might have been in the field or on assignment
Is it not possible that some bite of called into work sick that day
There's a ton of possibilities the bills just completely ignore it because it's
Conclusion has already been reached
And the process of reporting on this story only exist to serve the goal of solidify
Bill Cooper basically cosplay to the guy who's looking for the truth
Sometimes it manifested
It's like when you scold his listeners for bringing up unfounded nonsense
Reality
Those are not instances of him caring about the truth
When do schools have collars for bring up rumors that's really just in expressing his authority over the audience
It's it's
Research
When he passes long rumors
But it's abhorrent
Stupid when I do the same thing
It's basically called m.
Where to send for you to do something that's a virtue for me
Yeah
It's messed up
Christine controlling
What the truth
You know it is it is nothing to do with
Searching for anything it has everything to do with being like
This is concrete yeah and I know it
It's kind of like setting the terms of the search itself
Absolutely
We can have disagreements
Very small surface levels
But if you come at me with
Anything like a
It's not false flag
Kill you
Doing the same bulshit I do
Communist news
Haha
Bill discusses the arrest
Timothy McVeigh
And this is
This is messed up stuff
Grolier
Bert
Cherried out
Cheryl Carney
And her beautiful country
In a car with no license
Music
The point where
Not to get caught
He doesn't have a license
105 the car
Is a concealed weapon
You got hard
Attempt to get away made no attempt to shoot the officer
Blowing up a building full of people
There's no expiration year
So first of all bills games here about the idea that if a weapon is concealed to be impossible for a cop to see it
Ridiculous
Kind of embarrassing
It's an indication of
It's a Denny's just trying to cast out and make the arrests
There's something interesting going on here with bills claim that you know
It's weird that he didn't try and kill the
The police officer that tried to kill him
It's a little weird kind of thing that you expect
Text someone to do
Weird
6 years after the bombing
The meeting ended Oklahoma City
Conversation
Was what should McVey he's pulled over by the
Police
Quote just take the ticket and go on your way with the advisement
Do what you replied quotes
You don't think I should shoot them
This was rebuffed
Why would you shoot someone over a ticket
That right-wing figure was Bill Cooper
F*** out of
Oklahoma City bombing
Possession of a bunch
Copies of the Turner Diaries
To quote watch Oklahoma City
According to Bill Zone telling the story
I mean I could see him
You know narcissistically inserting himself into the story
But also that's
Deeply
Deeply fought
Yeah this
Inserting yourself into the story
I don't know
Screw
Associated been traveling on I-40 when they decided to stop in at Surplus and stuff
The owner which was a
Friend of Bill
Name two aspirin
According to Pale Horse Rider
Lesperance asked them if they'd ever heard of Bill Cooper
Sure they had the two men said Uber was their favorite
They listen to him all the time
Lesperance Doberman
Eventually investigators learned that another May
The plot to blow up
The conspiracy before it came to fruition
Horse rider includes a passage from an interview that Michael Fortier did in August 1995
With an outlet called The Outpost of freedom
40 hour later served as the state's star Witness
Frances Farmer
Well for your side
I can't say a whole lot and red thing
There's this guy with a radio station in Arizona
He kept calling people sheep
Well we got to thinking that's right to change
Tim really respond
Get to that
Bill's Work of trying to build up
Timothy McVeigh
That he knows fully well he's
Part of what inspired the bomb
This is basically the same understand
Well this is certainly not a universal thing a lot of conspiracy theory operates as a way to cover up the unpleasant
Community
You don't want to recognize and accept our real
And ignore white supremacist operates on
White identity level that has a possibility of inspiring such a
Similarly he knows that his extremist gun absolutist renrick requires him to come up with
Conspiracy theories every time there's a mass shooting
The reality of mass shootings at white supremacist violence are threatening to Alex's world
You can
It's the globalist somebody up
It's mind control
And in the same way
Could have bomba Federal Building and killed tons of people
It's the ugly conclusion of the rhetoric of these put out at Bill knows that
So this requires a conspiracy
Yeah that's
I can't
I can't believe that
I could not live with
Like the idea that you could just go on with
Your show and
Just use denial just basic denial
With the full awareness bed
This guy you knew this guy
Lolita
Maybe Bill wouldn't realize
That this is the guy
Forever
Story of meeting today until a few years later
Bill's influence
Timothy McVeigh could have shopping
Because he was just pulled over for missing a plate and is Bill Cooper
Why kill someone over a ticket
And here on erbil is baffled by the decision
But he very well might have advised Timothy McVeigh to make
And is using that decision is proof
Cuz if you was
You would have tried to kill the cop
Whoa
Man
Inadvertently inspiring
Is a very strange
Existence
Yeah that is before we can
Oh man
Episode
That
We got to get to work maybe dance around the apartment
My town
Larry Nichols
Call Jasmine KHOW
Argenta fide one of the suspects from the artist drawing that either Brown
Call Boyd
Neither Arkansas
You mean Arkansas
Hillary Clinton real
My information is that you've already told I didn't Secret
To the public sometime within the next week
Yeah brother Nicholas isn't play
Bucking roller coaster ride
Larry Nichols is in place
Of course
Qanon Hillary Clinton has already been secretly indicted nothing ever changes
I want to drive home looking at this covered
It's less sophisticated in terms of the the radio
You know where is a lot of the propaganda so much more media Savvy now
How much is it
Exactly the same
Tricks how you can sell it over and over and over
Larry Nichols and
Be smart enough to not trust Larry but as it turns out they said
Whatever they say Larry Nichols entire career
Just like finding people who hate
The clintons to believe him now
Back in the 90s there wasn't
Awesome
Because it allows you to laugh at pretty much everyone who took him seriously
Unreal
Also because this is
Resurrection social media
Not just
The qanon
Pacifica
About
The clintons at the time where the middle of the Whitewater scandal
Indicted
Post this was spread by a guy named Sherman skolnick
A contributor at the
Conspiracy Nation newsletter
Convinced that either Clinton's Financial supporters or someone in the government ordered the bombing to obscure the fact
The two days earlier
Hillary Rodham Clinton was indicted on two felony counts
In the Whitewater Pro
Secret indictments are kind of standard tropism
Conspiracy as you can see from the present and from the mid-90s
They're an appealing angle because there is such a thing as a sealed indictment
So you can craft
That just like truth
The people yeah I'm waiting to find out
Tucking Xerxes is son secretly indicted
God sakes
It's always cylinder apps is
This is just another weak attempt on Bill Cooper's BART to do anything he can to take the blame off his big fan
Brings us to the end of the 24th
Turn on the 25th
Batman
This was not a good
So it wouldn't be very good
No callers
The 25th
Rambling about militia
Char Char
How do you say these are militiamen
For the record for the Oklahoma City bombing
Open card
Have not been slide
Have not been found guilty of anything
I'm in this country
You are innocent until proven guilty
Unless you're Hillary which has you're already
None of them
Have been
Or ever will be
Connected to any Melissa
They're not Melissa money they're not thank you
It's fair enough to point proven guilty
You should come down to the back of the
It's pretty obvious
The bombing
You didn't care what the process of law even after your approval
Does using the idea of innocent until proven guilty is awaiting says that they are in fact
It may be the case with Timothy McVeigh was not a formal member of his
Specific militia but that doesn't mean he's not a creature of the same world
According to chose the Timothy McVeigh and Terry Nichols attended meetings of the Michigan militia
There is an L Norman Olson told the Associated Press
These people were told to leave
Because that kind of talk
Destruction
Terrorism
Is naturally the kind of thing that makes sense to say after someone Bob Federal Building
However you may sound a little different beforehand
Michigan life pointed out that a year
Before the bombing Norman Olson told her recruit
Meant meeting
If this country doesn't change armed conflict is inevitable
This is how it goes
You bringing disaffected Angry Young Man with talk of armed conflict that denies anything to do with that when they fall
Follow through with those words
This is a pattern that you see in right-wing propaganda to pretty much across-the-board
Infowars interviews Jack pasovic about how scary, ping-pong Pizza is
How it works
Are more meaningful
Back to McVay
His beliefs lined up almost
Entirely with the beliefs of right-wing militias at the time
It was largely government actions
All right-wing militias
Almost identical politics
Malicious calls back to history
I prefer to call them Civil War pre and actor
Like there
They're just as lame as Civil War
Happened yet
Erase your earlier bad shape.
Episode
And this is where I'm totally convinced Bill knows that this is the guy that he had met
Investigator
Timothy McVeigh
Volunteer any mind-control operation
United States Army
Landed with a micro computer chip
Hey
Antonio's Craigslist
Ever since he left the United States Army
And nobody has lived
Even playing for the United States Army could follow him by electronic surveillance where he was all the time
Weird the bills bringing up this idea that means they had a chip
Because this
From Pale Horse Rider
He also had a computer chip implanted in his body he said
Cooper can touch it if you wanted to
It was in his right butt cheek
Confirm it was there
I decline for obvious reasons Cooper set
To see if there was something there
According to Bill Cooper Zone telling himself to his ass
Possibility
What is a bill has reporting things
Information came from
Because he know that
Then he'd like if it were known that he'd met with the Oklahoma
Bomber
Who is in the process
Defender guy
I listen nobody Timothy McVeigh over here he had a computer chip in his ass and I wouldn't touch his ass because
Cuz obvious reasons
Obviously true
The other is at Bill's liquor store totally made-up
Associated Press
Reported by Timothy McVeigh
Prior to this episode
Everything in Bill's story of the meeting is just
Turner Diaries detail the microchip Oklahoma City
That could all be Bill creating a tall tale
Whatever the case
Michael 40 years interview where he discussed how Timothy McVeigh really responded to Bill Cooper's talked about how people needed to actually
Do something
Not filtered through bill
And that's it could be taking over more seriously
Bill Maher
But he definitely inspired
That's the conclusion
That you really
I can't shake
It's the only
Believing bill story
About meeting tip
McVeigh is f***** up
If it's not true and he's making that up
What is that
Yeah exactly
Either way
What cuz if you're Mickey
I want credit
Which means
The militias respect what he did
All of my lies about how it's not malicious
Right
That is another
So we get in here we're going to about to jump to the 26th but like I said
This episode on the 25th
Militias are
People suddenly being a bit curious about what's going on
I found myself zoning out almost entirely as bill went on and on about how if you're an Able Body person in Arizona between
Ages of 1845
Who's all just stuff that I couldn't get myself to care about because even if that's
It's technically true according to the Arizona
Constitution
Who cares what does that mean today probably not
Most likely
The Illinois militia
Let me say this right now
They don't need
Draft
I don't know about this
I don't care
I just booked
CNN by the way
Everybody's going to fight
Tomorrow you're all going to show up at the
Start at the 26th
Gentleman
Everything the trust
Hudson warned you about
Is coming to
It have been mine
Green
My purpose
Green armor done
Jackie Chan
California
Riverfront on cell
Try to convince
Summer Happening by waking enough people
Permit right here way of
Numbers of
Educated awake
Marquis
People
Olive Garden
Overwhelming
Somehow
You should
I really don't know what to do about
Step 2
Kenyan Camaro too
Try to
Help bring
Virtual Revolution by hooker
Interesting
Just recently saw
As the Coronavirus
Covid-19 stop
Started
To become
More
Outside of his narratives I guess I'm more real than his narrative
A lot of tacos
We lost this
The globalist
Kind of
Similar response to Bill after
Like realizing
Is going to be proven to be guilty of this
Oh boy
Interesting see like after a crisis point
Point after really big things
Maybe beyond your abilities to spinner to make
Alright
You realize I say
Yard sale
These guys it's strange
Because
Kind of their way of taking responsibility for it
Absolutely not taking any responsibility for what he
Happened
Responsibility for something that is 100
You know like
I am so sorry Lost Boy
Yeah I would like
Or whatever to process
So
Come to realize as I listened to more and more available show is that
Information-gathering process
Is almost entirely just messages that he gets from listener
This is wonderful
Report everything
Pharmacy in Oklahoma City
I heard you
Somewhere else
Please find someone else ripping Cena
Circle Public Radio
All Things Considered
Even show the grave
Make sure that I am mistaken about this I hope
I am wrong
I thought I heard a professor from George Washington University
Redeem weird about this
Closing of tape
Bring that we would have to choose between keeping
Parking our freedom of
And having freedom from terrorism
This is such a great manifestation of how bad this operation is
Intelligence operation of the Second Continental
He has the citizens agency of joint intelligence or
Angie
Which serves as data-gathering
Just as listeners who paid him send an email
Report
And here you can see the quality of the work is being done by his station
Who's emailed Bill to complain about something
MPR
Something she
Thinks she her.
Dream that Obama was President
Could you could somebody please confirm
I would like at least my
Operation This American Life
Build Oklahoma Station cheap
General training in journalism or intelligence-gathering being a ballet instructor by trade
More like Bill Cooper so she paid her dues
Signed an oath of allegiance to the second continental army of the Republic
And was named a second Lieutenant of the intelligence service under Bill
Tauc ball
Commission papers the general was listed as George Washington
You kind of get this a bill was running the entire second continental army of the Republic
And pretending there was a chain of command
More cosplay
The ghosts of Georgia
More would go on to ready
640 page book called Oklahoma City
Herpes
It was going to definitively prove all these conspiracies based on thorough documentation of media lies blast
Insisted on expensive binding for the first edition
He charged $60 for
He said for an initial printing of 500 copies
And he couldn't even sell that
In pale horse rider one of Bill's friend says he still has several untouched boxes
I'll be limited and signed first edition
Piled up in Cooper's old storage unit
It sounds like every comedians
Michelle Mooresville station Chief in Oklahoma
In recognition of her tireless work
Cooper promoted from lieutenant
Hard to imagine how he got George Washington to sign off on that promotion
This is a Battlefield
Is 01 where is chorizo for
First lieutenant
And also I should tell you Jordan that I just decided to make you a colonel for all the hard work you've done on this podcast
Total.
I don't know it's Four Star General
Is the definite balance of empower
Yes I agree
I believe our last episode the covered
Somebody's dispatch
About updates on the bomb
Seem to just be
I met a nice person
100 your mom riding you a better vacation
So weird
So you can imagine my surprise
Talking utter disbelief
Google Dreadful things coming from my gut
The federal building bombing
Adore creative seven days
All the years of his life
Have been
Euros
Somebody else now that I never knew before I'm do not want
Hamilton weather
Broadcaster
The word he was saying we're treasonous
You can bring one
Mind control by one week's worth of
Television
Coverage
Unbeliever
I did my best to find him with a mover to a room was according to law
What purpose it serves what country
Melissa stand for
Santa Cruz fuel Houdini
Do not make all those who love this company on Danger
Here
A word of it
7 gravity killed in his home by some invading enemy than to be rescued from The Invader by Emarosa
Quite a bit of brainwashing
German batteries really
He'd rather be killing you home by coming waiting in a meeting to be rescued from The Invader by a militia member
Coco videos
I don't care about your station Chiefs relationship with her dad
Is this news what is going on here
What is Anthony
Dying
Patriots a personal interest
You got a personalized
You know people really this woman
Listening
I resented it.
I found it first of all to be distasteful
Cuz I don't care
Right
Conceivably Bill Cooper supposed to be disguised like
Can see through all the conspiracies and he knows everything
Your time is valuable
Chris Wallace
Really mean stuff about Fox News
I don't ever want to speak to that again
Maybe it's cuz you're reading a text instead of doing work maybe
Maybe you could have figured out what the
Talking about
Delicious
Who cares
That's a good point
There's an undercurrent a feeling of
Alienation
Coming
Rhombus
The station chief
And her dad
Being a family break
How accurately she's /
Portraying
Fuel
Alienated from their own parent where they're saying treasonous things because they believe the Communist News Network
Need to cut off ties with all family there suppressive persons
I was thinking of taking tea
Talking again when I was thinking last Saturday night
Monarch Casino
I guess I did not realize
My dad
Is Merrill
The enemy
That's so f***** up
Station chief
Bill Cooper
Timothy McVeigh
Allegedly
Code Avengers like
Don't leave
Between you and me
Obvious reasons I couldn't touch his butt
But yeah
Don't
IPads
I still don't know what I believe I don't like chance
Meeting between them
Cuz you the fabulist in a liar
I don't know
Not that that is a fallacy though just because someone's a liar assuming they're always lying
Is is dangerous game
In the middle
Praying like just taking a weird route
Through his personal email
Doesn't belong on the show at all
Spring through the gold does the lens of like
They're so evil they've brainwashed your dad
Get close
I'm sure all of you have had
Terrible
Your family members believing
Not Bill Cooper
Tragedy
To do with the axle
Discharge from the Ryder truck
And the notion
It was
The notion that people were vaporized
It gets more to talk about that here
Pocatello Shawnee Oklahoma cremation service in Oklahoma City
Work for The Cremation process
And some detail
Some people were literally
Vaporizer
Vaporized
But I can guarantee you it'll never found any trace of any truck
It is
Do you begin to be able to tell like he's reading a message from the station.
Lieutenant
Soon-to-be major
You start to be able to tell like this isn't reading any mail
What's going on here
So
Is the station chief
At the crematorium
Now what we're doing is the bear taking
Information
Crematorium person
And applying it to news-record
Of people being vaporized
And then they're saying
I don't think
Bijou comes down to
Divorce
It's possible that the actual
Slime
The complete outward Force
Explosion
Simultaneously someone standing near the truck
Force of the blast hit
And drive them being essentially vaporizer
What bill is doing here is creating a false
Contradiction
He's implying that one thing is true and therefore another thing
It feels intuitively correct that actual shouldn't
Survive
What bill is doing here is also mixing up what vaporized means in different contexts
He goes on to give a long diatribe about the temperature is it with things like calcium vaporized
Which he's trying to use to prove that any part of the Ryder truck
Verizon
This isn't what people mean when they say that a body was vaporized
Generally speaking
There's a definition that scientist would use to describe the chemical processes and sort of vernacular
The third definition in Merriam-Webster is to destroy bajor as if converting
This sentence is a date that they use to demonstrated in a sentences quote attempt vaporized by a shell
Obviously the Shell tank didn't become Allsburg
It's just a term used to describe a
Particular type of destruct
Due process
Winning this contest
It's just hyperbole
And it's it's a Sci-Fi
Because when you say vaporizer
If you mean it in a destructive way the way that these guys are
They're talking about
There should be nothing
Right it should be literally vapor
Which is only Sci-Fi
No it's not it's it's real real but in this context it's not like theirs
Zero evidence of explosion
You could get there
Volcanic eruptions you can leave
The stories that I was able to sign about the Oklahoma City
World Trade Center
Typically being used
Generally had to do with
You know people who died in ways that you couldn't get identifiable remains
So
You know if someone's body is like
Exploded to a part where it's not recognizable
Just Called Mariah
It's not a technical term
In some media coverage
And then implying
Is that everything was so hot that the body became vapor
Convince
News stories were saying
Well I mean the
Because it takes a ridiculous amount of heat
It would melt the axle before a human body
The game is being played
You could look up
How much
Heated takes vaporizing axle you could look up
Just look at it
The internet
That's true
Books exist
Divulge
Until one of your listeners to go look for it and call it a day
You can find so many people who dedicated their entire life
Situation
But
You should really probably trust your station Chief who hates her dad now
Crematorium
So
I haven't really pulled out from each episode but does deserve mention is that
Is Mike still selling
Is gold
Germany alternate Bucky Bergquist America
If you're interested
Real money
Rapport
Proverbial buffalo chicken
I'm telling you is not far off
Then you better call response
To put Mediterranean
Talk to them about what real money really is
So
You know I'd so like
Where is the trend of like
Deschutes about that the fan got to get real money
Still a little bit speaker bass sales but whatever
Subway
Philosophy of river fires the first shot
Revert Alexei this exact same thing
Pretty common and it also is nonsensical internally
Remember I've always told you I've warned you I had admonished you River
Fires the first
Shop wings
USA
That's what the Socialist
Murray
That's why they blew up in the building in Oklahoma
Because I'm telling you right now it was the government
Intelligence community
Zach bitter
Richmond Alabama
So bilbili the river spiders the first shot
Socialist believe
The New World Order
Because they get to blame it on their enemies
Either whatever
New World Order
Shot
So what is he telling his audience
Is he telling them that they should just wait for another shot
Why would you be insisting to the audience
That whoever fires the first shot loses it the first shot
Fired
They lose
According to your principles
It's not some abstract future thing now
Facebook
The first shot fired
Shot
Justified
That's the implication of what bills saying but he would never say that because then the game's over
Is one of the things that the
Proof that these people are full of
If you think you've proven that the New World Order blew up a federal building and kill Tony
The people and that isn't enough for you to say that it's time to take up arms against them
Where is that point
There is no point because you know that when you cross that line
You're not making any more money
So you stay right on the edge
I would say
Same-day shipping is more than
Duplicate going to happen especially when the New World Order conspiracy that
Rashad tour
Start
Call Scott
Coldwater and fires the first shot
Which is why they come back during the other cold
To win the next top
Thanks get a headache
Bad sick of it
So I would describe as a rare apology
Because apparently
They were in the military in the week one of them was
Too I guess
Serve honorably
Week one of my knowledge
Upholstery repair Irving does
Score
Solo
Concept
Jorgensen
Proven guilty I apologize
We're making a
Last night I could not
Terminator
Bill designs is worth giving an apology about
Military
That's amazing
None of the other Stephanie's career requires retract
This.
The first chapter of his book was based off fraudulent document
Behold a Pale Horse contained a full reprinting of the protocols of the Elders of Zion
Oh no it's not a problem
Beard suggest that two men been arrested for blowing up a federal building art patriotic
They were in the service
And that's something that he's got to make right
That's wild do not
Do not
Absolutely
Denigrate our military men even though
Quickly in my worldview
They are controlled by the New World Order and they will be used to destroy us
Something like that
F*** with the Miller
So if we get back to this other than the other
Socialists are Nazis Nazis are socialist you are that kind of thing
We must not allow
To happen here what happened in Nazi Germany
It will not be up
Depends doctor in another
Nuremberg trials
It will be the real
The real
Nazis are socialist
Don't ever forget that
And Republican
Control governments
And Liberty
Constipation Coronavirus
Gold and silver coin
United States code
Money is gold and silver coins
Admittedly
Measurement called a dollar
Call Chris Merritt reagan-era 1-800
4pics Spokane get some real money
You better do it soon
I'm taking garlic Raymond Grenier
Yeah that's
The real Nazi Nazi Nazi
Alex
Yeah just a different personality differ
Broadcasting style doing the same thing as aloe
Wild
I hate I don't understand why lie under
Completely
They always say nothing their social
Socialism being an economics
Right they never say Nazis are fat
Fashion speaking the government system that they don't lie
So
It seems to me
Angry about it
Kind of
Property rights
AR
Above-average
Way to get to Fascism real fast at loggerheads
Moratorium
Socialist
System totally
There's something else that bill is a little bit upset about it got a little bee in his Bonnet and that is that
When on 60 Minutes
And I had an interview and bill has decided
He has condemned
Honda
60 minutes
Steve kroft
It seems almost certain homegrown terrorism
How do we respond to that
Well we have to arrest the people who do
We have to put him on trial
We have to convince them and punish them I certainly bleed but they could be extra Google
Tiger
Quilling
We all do
Fire Department
Do you know you've already convicted him and your ex
Peculiar
It's not what he said
Is not a mirror
You literally said nothing
102 not for you to decide
Getting curious
Precision Auto
I don't know I mean baby maybe president
If a president
After a federal building is blown up
I think the death penalty is appropriate
Called for his death
Good person
No no I don't know
I don't know I guess if you want to really
Stick be a stickler about it whatever bill has that one
The dumb that you can have it
Cooper also gets mad
Bill Clinton
Some things about Waco
60 minutes
And goes on a diatribe about Waco that I'm not going to address
Any easy is
Very mad
I cannot believe that any serious
Patriotic American
This is
Can't believe
That the conduct of those people of Waco Justified the kind of outrageous behavior
Seen here in Oklahoma City
Are the kind of inflammatory rhetoric that we're hearing all across the
Country today
What's wrong
What is he talking
No patriotic American you cold turkey
Everstart
Little people at Waco Justified anything that happened in Oklahoma City
Doesn't sound true has a long pause
And the only way you can really get around as a comment like that is just how do you
Define patriotic America
If you're going to
Disabled
Sayings that Waco justifies the Oklahoma City bombing preclude you from being a patriotic
Axiomatic
Disqualify
Diamond Lake
Definitely thought that
Yeah and I
I would be shocked if there wasn't at least one episode of Bill Cooper Zone show where he said
This justifies some sort of response
That is commensurate with what the government did
Saudi reticence to make a prediction
To surprise
There's also like
Is that is it
It's ludicrous
Do you say that
That wasn't a position
Some people help
Absolutely maybe it wasn't all the wishes
Probably wasn't I'm sure that there were a lot of people were horrified by the event
That transpired
We're condemning I'm positive of that
Definition games
Preserving some sense of
Self
He's going to get to the bottom of both Oklahoma City and Waco
Is it going to buy a TV station
I going to ask
Every American
Gather evidence
And crew
I'm beginning investigation to find
The perpetrators
And help
Bring to Justice
The murderers of Oklahoma City
And the murderers of Waco Tex
Beaver pelt
We are going to find out who did it
We are going to wake up unlimited coin to insured
Somebody comes out and talk
And I helped you out
Going to come back on you Bill Clinton
Janet Reno
Bimp ATL
And whoever
And however
Did the bombing
In Oklahoma City
You don't need to do that verification party hard
He's done
Investigation has been completed already
We're going to raise up a whole bunch of money in order to lure some very competent
Tell a great story
What's that I can hear Money
Go to work
It's a wonderful friend of money
You guys like
Yeah
Great Clips
Bill theory about how we're going
Going to get rid of this Menace
It's known as Bill Clinton
Spoiler alert
Didn't work
I cannot believe this
Hello
Are we have
Someone
Stickable Cherokee
It does not speak well
Primerica
We're at the cheese out of the next election in the way to do it is to
Adjoin
Constitution party
Veritas
By the way should all be
Driving to
Because it's the only place that you're ever going to read the Pooh
So at this point
Douching party also known as the US taxpayers party never a viable party and it nope
Ever fielded a candidate that has received more than 2% of the vote for president
Remember
I've also never won an electoral vote
In 1996 Howard Phillips campaign for president
Over the 1992 election
I'm not sure that they've even ever successfully fielded a candidate for Congress
In 2018 I can find one
And it was in North Carolina
The Greene County Commissioner election for District 3
Anyway
Get that guy out
If you're a member of that party you got to go
Commissioner who knows
They're supposed to be on a team that never wins because they never have to deal with what comes after winning
And you always have a ready excuse for why you lost
This is the one thing
That Alex forgot to include in his impression of Bill Cooper
And
Bad news you never want to win
You never want to win so that's why the Constitution party
Search of principled
More juice go straight libertarian party
Although it's never really going to work out for you
So I mean like
Disappointing as a stretch of time because I really don't think that there was
Watch coverage of the bomber
He's decided it's fake
There's a lot of yelling about Waco
Can we continue it already started
Previously they
I guess proven
That it was a false flag or something
I'm convinced yes
But I mean hey
We now have
It within our field of awareness
The bills
May have
But
That's just so wild
The bill is named dropping Larry Nichols
And that means we might do it again
I don't think he's ever been on his show cuz I call it
Speaking his name
Scrolling through
The first Apostle
Especially as Whitewater is continuing to go along
Retire
Thompson
Becoming more of a
Cooper first phone call anymore
That is true
Apologize for the delay
Episode
I meant there were other circumstances going on that may have just
Did you and not your personal decision making sense Colonel cast
It just
In these couple days that much
Growth
And so we'll see what the section chief
We are also on
Facebook review
Mario bail fund or the lake
To help with people doing
The Chicago station chief of the citizens agency
Journalistic integrity
Second continental army of the Republic
Holding
Alex