Air Jordan
I have great respect for snowledge b b
Knowledge fight
Jordan Jordan
Oh did you
Some hot sauces very very hot
I wanted to actually make you some of them just because it could be really funny
The show for everybody
So I get to watch you
Do you try to deal with
Some of these new sausage
Spicier than a Wendy's spicy chicken nuggets
Are very hot
Two sauces from torchbearer maker that I really like
Zombie apocalypse after Android setup
Better
Some of the reviews are saying that a better flavor
He didn't have a
Is milder
Jamie Kennedy
Carolina Reaper one
Very
It is a lot of
Okay
Is speed
You know that's the thing that makes me want to try hot sauce has been many and varied ways that you describe how the taste
You which is very fascinating to me
That's a lot like
People telling me all about the different ways they can punch me
I also got one from adobo
Hawaiian
Company
Irishman
There was a lot of people like to go
And it was gorgeous
When's have their own charms
Porter's
No no okay pepper flavor
Dinner
Spinner sauce marinator
Okay
Really hot sauce
All the way down
To Orland Park
Disaster at 6 my partner's car
I had to have somebody else fix her car I cannot do that
It took
Twice as long as they said however
I turn this into a positive
Because they had
Perfect grass
Lovely tree
Set lay down took a nap on the grass
That's how perfect it is in Orland
That's right amazing I've been outside and laid out and just saw the sun and all that
Add stop for forever
Cool
It's not been hot yet
It's alright
Today's episode
I'm thrilled
Return from his week of whatever
10/22
Aladdin
So first Madison p
I'm a policy wonk
Text Travis
All one word
Text Serena
Thanks Angela
Vincent
Mini
Goodwill
Business
Heroin
So good
Large
Thank you so much Michael and and thank you so much good work boys let me have the wine bottles
A reference to progress wine bottles
It is not a quadrilateral
Weird masturbatory
And I realized
That the logistics of it were just a nightmare and couldn't pull it off so I apologize
Give you an empty wine bottle I do still have first wine bottles that are first three
Free episodes
With wine bottles that I feel like a douchebag
Because I have
Empty alcohol bottles
Those can be given to someone
What's up
Capricorn owl
Return of Alex and I mean he's horrible
He's a real dick
Kind of thing something thinking
It's worth while to me because like
When I listen to Owen Shroyer when he comes in he does the show
I was thinking at all I'm think I'm not interested is boring as s***
One minute into Alex being back he says something to Michael thanks
That's interesting ok
That we have our pulse
What's going on the planet
Globalist
Spectre
Top next to Lucifer
Okay
Puscifer Puscifer
Negative
Vista
The same Horizon is Lucifer
From the luciferian
Wolf
Local
Compartmentalize
Having the baby
High-level Field Marshal
This is the field Marshal
Welcome back Alex
Explaining
Take in the view alongside Lucifer
Expression finger on the pulse
And in the process actually kind of describes Infowars really well
If you try to take someone's pulse with a part of your body where someone could
Take your pulse
Then you're going to get an accurate reading
When Alex says the Infowars has their pulse on what's going on on the planet
Internal processes
And then making the mistake that means anything
Accidentally correct statement adjusted
Is there inverse meeting
Being on a hill with Lucifer is
If you are on a Vista with Lewisburg
You might see things physically the same as Lucifer but just being on the same perspective
Incited
Brixton
Me and Lucifer could be up on a cliff and we could both see a car broke
Lucifer may know that there's an assassin coming to kill me in that car
Which is information I don't have at my disposal
In this situation
Lucifer and I would see this car physically from the same perspective
Ultimately how we experience
The car that was the
Completely different
Look at things from his perspective is not about the
Physical looking
Real world
Documents
That you and I could look at it as well right
It's the same way that the sun sees the documents which is from above
This is
Airtight logic
Stomach stomach
That's interesting thoughts are coming out
Expresssos
Missed it by missed at least
That could look David night Owen Shroyer
They're not capable of this kind of legal language
Is horrible
There's something
Interesting thought process
Alright I don't
Isis
I know it's such a fine line listening to
There's a part of me that thinks it's like a tardigrade aspiring to poetry
You know it's never going to get to Poetry Man
Yeah it's
It's strange but like
It's a water in the desert that is Owen Shroyer David height
So Alex
Couple minutes maybe a minute in the Hat right
He's already said that he's up on the mountain with Satan looking at things
Bucket
Either I could start this show and so many different ways there's so much big news
Mediately trips over his own foot
We've got more clips
Peace
To be a riveting whole show
Human race
It's not the race
You know how you know erase that can breed with it
Benson's went off the second
What is
Rate is a term that is not a part of the biological
Taxonomy
Do not like an animal as a kingdom phylum
It's not a term that has any descriptive value in terms of human populations in incredibly
Describe animals in nature
Cicada Danimals
Just leaving article from the journal Evolution education and Outreach
Breezer eyes due to breeders extreme control
To maximize the presence of desired traits in the Next Generation
Breeding baguettes
Breeds
Whereas human intervention
Select for the treats they want in the animals and excludes those they don't want I prefer that words don't mean
Human populations have been
Subjected historically do natural selection where is the best gated animals are the product of artificial
Selection
This is the subject of the fair amount of material you can find if you're interested but the bottom line is that the argument that the social
Determine category we call races equivalent to
Think something deeply racist ideology historically and it makes no sense
From a scientific
Perspective
It's an attempt to link temperament
Historically
The really remarkable
The reasons that this happens a lot to him
This is because he's a giant
The big explanation for that
No need to Pretend This is a mystery
Big brain
White rice
Joe in the next 12 hours
While we was gone
Sure
Sort of okay
Saturday
Trump rally in Tulsa
This show is happening
Them
Is Alex's
Another is based in reality
Destroyer and selling T-shirts
Cuz he was on vacation
Down at the Gulf of Mexico I believe
Child labor laws
Adult
Employable age
This is one of the stories that Alex needs to cover that you missed while he was gone because pretty important
Trump looks bad. I do what I can to make him not look that
Excerpts
As yet last night
Not a failure it was a
Extreme
Decipher all of that
So much more
Cavicide
Total victory
I feel like
Using it
Extreme in front of Victor
Obvious
You know what victory would be
You notice an extreme victory
There's no like
Debate or feelings of
Extreme victory
Nobody's ever said like oh man
You thought that Battle of Waterloo is a failure but
More into this
It's pretty preoccupied with trying to damage
Control about the small turnout at the rally
I'll get mad at K-pop
Fan
Himself in
Pre knowledge of a crime
I just don't
And I know that
Southern district of New York
Fired refusing
Is emblematic everything we're facing an ainu
Before he refused to step down
The president
Imagine that
Infowars
Better hope
He's making up that he knew in advance that Trump was going to fire Geoffrey Berman because if not
The conspiracy just
Super jump
Attorney General William Barr put out of federal prosecutor
In the southern district
Cricket New York
The problem was that Birdman had not resigned
New released its own statement
Did not receive The Hideout
In response to that bar wrote a letter to Birdman saying because he was declared that you have no intention of resigning
I've asked the president to remove you as of today and he has done so
That was on Saturday
After this Trump was asked by reporters about the matter of bourbon and Trump clearly didn't want to make it look like he was in
Attorney general Barr is working on that
But not by Department
What's really up to him
I'm not involved
Ultimately
Bourbons also
Slappy prosecution
Lawyer Michael Cohen
And had invited Lev parnas and Igor fruman
The office was in the process of investigating Giuliani himself
Elie honig a former assistant us attorney Southern District
When you look at the timing of this the fact that it was announced late on a Friday night the fact that the Attorney General immediately was caught
A misleading statement
What he said the US attorney is stepping down
And you look at all the
Pending cases in sdny right now
The only logical conclusion
Yeah no s***
House Judiciary Committee has ended
Whistleblower
Who are set to testify against William Barr
What is the farthest
I'm right I don't know exactly what happened
Probably try not to implicate myself and having Advanced knowledge I might end up getting called to test
Spotify
Probably Alex
I mean nothing's going to happen but insane world
You'll probably regret
It was just an everything had enough manpower in
Make him go under oath about this
Open crimes
And then
Doing something about them
I think they would get us
Narratives of Alex's Sunday
Children
If you're sensitive to those topics
So you may want to consider jumping ahead
I don't know
Exactly when that will be
You know
Content
You know the more grotesque
Subject
End of the story that he's covering does deserve
Mention so here we go
Arizona state was it just harmless but it was a
Taken from their biological parents particularly
They took children I was reading the files weekend
From
Can cult
Hardcore
Interrupting
We need to get with God
Two people two
You pay them
Have sex with them
Create the law
The North American man-boy love associate
So This Is tragically true story
Completely made up
It's recently come to light that there was a program in place beginning in 1969
Pedophile
This was based on the theory promoted by a psychologist named houllou Templar
These men would make
Great roster
This is stick shift and it's horrific
I pray these children
Excited by the German government
For allowing this to happen
It does appear the Germany is inclined to take responsibility
Drone article in Dutch
Assures
Is the Berlin Senator responsible for the Keppler case
She's been outspoken and expressing Sympathy for the victims and condemnation of the crime she calls
Simply unimaginable
Although the statute of limitations for these crimes has expired
Is Promised financial compensation for their self
Doesn't make up for what happened
You know in terms of the states
Responsibility
This is not a new story
Deutsche welle on a new developed
You can find coverage of Base going back to 2016 and Outlets like the Irish Times which was recording on a study conducted
University of Gottingen
Which had been able to find
Who replaces pedophiles
In what being referred to as the Kent lurex
Experiment
In newer recording based on a study out of the University of
There's a number of children that said to be confirmed is 10
Literally any number of 0 is too many
And 10
Research this is, did they they do not know
The precise number of children who are effect
I bring up this number not to minimize this
It's just a situation where a headline like
Berlin authorities Place children of pedophiles 4:30
Years
Particular mental image that may or may not be accurate
More will come out on this story better picture of what exactly went
Scale
For now the best I can do is tell you that I would absolutely make
Is reporting about the
The story
The first fabrication In that clip is that the children were taken from their biological parents were primarily Christian
This program was specifically about homeless youth
I don't make this District
Distinction because I think it's any better it's
They were
I only bring this up to point out that Alex is making things up
There's absolutely nothing in any of these articles about children being taken from their Christian
Can families be put in abusive father
I was just making that up to play into the Christian narratives
It run through so much of his show
Is Merida's don't work without a sense of overwhelming persecution
Details
In Christian victimhood in person
Execution
The second thing is that I don't believe it
He study from the University of Hilda Chavez
57 pages long
A difficulty in that the actual report is really hard to find but if you do manage to make it to the
Say where you can find it
You see that it's only available in
PDF which is in German
If you use Google Scholar
Confide a version of that report and you can open it and then HTML file which you can use Google to translate into English
When he knows he could have make things up
Even this isn't a great System since Google translate isn't perfect but
I don't have the time to learn German to do this episode
It's where we're at
Read the actual files on these children or this program
The very best we could have done is read this report which includes conversation about the file
The report itself says the files were only accessible to them because
The consent of those affected
The foster home files were copied anonymized
At the University of Hilda
These vials comprised approximately 830 pages
Is almost certainly all in German and there's literally no change
Alex could have gotten his hands on us
Portions of this report
We're taking from Chris
Colts
It's my belief he's incorporating this detail in order to Harkins
The David koresh
The government is going to be late
And their kids
He's making up his story
Acronym Stanford North America
What is the First Amendment
Here's the point I want to stress
Serious story about a serious topic
It may be a program or experiment that's not currently
It's done still exist
The present and to honor that reality is important
Sensational
The stories outrageous enough as it is with what
Clearly abused to be a guy basically operating as well cause quotes
Nothing less than a Matchmaker for pedophile
The weight Oz handling the stories disc
Respectful to the victims of the program
He's trying to create an Infowars narrative out of their real-life victimhood which I signed absolutely disgrace
I just have no tie
Yeah that's $8
If you add
Details to a
Tremendous tragedy
Immensely avoidable
Horrific
You lose your right
To say anything
I don't care what
Conclusions
Do you draw a
The moment you're like
And also on top of this
It's horrifying
Sensational your predetermined narrative
You have
Evening
You're gone
Don't have any credibility left
This
Alex continues to just make
Make stuff up about
Oh by the way wasn't just Berlin
With all the German cities in Western Germany
At the time
And they were only following the UN directive of UNESCO
To have sex with children
There's no indication from any of the reporting or the University of Hilda schamber Port that the UN is involved in
Nestorian anyway
Further
The stories is about this report
Which only looked at the files of one foster home
Called freak
In the previous report which covered was covered in the Irish times at 2016
I do the study from the University of
Which was about West Berlin
And involve the period before the walls out
Alex is saying this is all of West Germany because he's read the words West
Berlin in the article's headline for the skim
If you do literally anything he'd know that Berlin is about
Far East in Germany's you can get before you hit the border with Pollock
Also this is all happening during the Cold War when the Berlin Wall was
And it has to do with West Germany
Would you know he wasn't the one that wasn't under the
Controller people Alex music
Pedophile communist
Interested in hearing him try to discuss that a little bit
Pick your side and then there's the guys and they're up to
Sure
My point is
Distasteful as this story has children
Now adults deserve better
Then there's
Routes to use to attack his political enemies
Which is what he's doing
It's pretty clear
Yeah I understand that
Seventh-day Adventist
Jehovah's Witnesses
Had their children taken
Man
To rape little girls and boys
Why would they take Christian children because
That's the old
AR
The idea that this program
Specifically targeted Jehovah's Witnesses are Seventh-day Adventist
Also from everything I can tell the victims that have been identified have all been boys
So you can take the boys and girls
A little bit
I'm not sure
But that's
Good from the recording ice
I'm sure there were some Adventist and doviz Witnesses in Germany in the 70s but though
Either way I was just making this stuff up at the end
It's because his audience
Plaintiff are greatest horror
He says he's the greatest
He's using the image of the thing that is already
Speirs the most because he needs to terrorize them with the idea
He knows that a considerable portion of his audience are anti-government Christian extremist
Makes the story about the children of parents
A projector
Manipulative tool for Alex to use
At this point I'm convinced that Alex is writing his own story about the
This piece of news because he knows it'll work better to manipulate his audience
Is chosen
I found the article about this on Infowars and it doesn't backup or
Substantiate
The Infowars article is just a repost
Thing of the article
Which they almost certainly don't have permission to Reaper
I'll reprint
Antigua pick out permission on that
Cover for obvious reasons
It's all just the same sort of stuff that you always babbles about
Grotesque details
There's no value in hearing it again
The only thing that's important here is that Alex has taken a real story
Children and Eli
Which is what he does
You liar
Yeah what a
Right
You get all this stuff going on
You know
Just once
Floor of how awful
A human being
It'd be nice
Everything nice
Oh man
So
There's no bottom
We see that here
People will be good
Stand up to it and say we aren't evil
We are going to
I believe in you
Figure out ways to take action against
But I just
My stomach
My mind.
What
Asking me what
God's face
I believe. And erectus
Elmo's World some need be
Want to kill people
If you try and sell things legally in-lawfully all the sudden now you have
To deal with reality and then everybody has to
Getting to real place
This is where people are like
That thing you said didn't actually happen
Well what if I killed you
And that's not a selling
It's a it's a
Now let's have some fun with him being a baby about these crowd sizes
What's up
Get our bearings back about us
You know what happened
Covid-19
Ford.com
Millions of
Instagram
Girl's name
Got the tickets
Thousand
But other people couldn't get them
I was going to go
I live in Oklahoma but I
I didn't go cuz
If you can get in the door you get in
First come first serve
It was
Fraud
Hilarious didn't even sell out a 19,000 seat Arena but
The most popular hero in the world
Analysis two explanations are in
His first visit to covid-19 cause
Sphere which under normal circumstances makes a lot of sense
However you're talking about and planning to show up to support a politician whose primary
No big deal
This is like it specifically population that you can't really use that excuse
If you're talkin about a low-turnout at a concert I'm sure it makes sense to David covid-19
It's a hoarder page when
The concert is a band called
Don't worry about covid-19
Can't use that excuse
The second explanation is also fun because it reveals a whole lot
The basic version of this is that a bunch of young people particularly Kpop fans
Fake email addresses to request a ton of tickets
The Trump rally
Which inflated the number of people who they expected to show up
That's hilarious
I'm good on that
That's a great point
Probably a really big problem
For Trump
The first is that they plan to like have overflow areas for people to watch outside
It was as if
Jeb Bush was there saying please
Embarrassment on that one
The second problem is that
Mass amounts of data that he could use
Target camping
I'm trying to drum up donation
Because there was a mass of people sending in fake information that data set is almost useless
Rendering the secondary objective is Rally a complete failure
Kpop fans were able to
Weather
Big time
Yeah
In the real world
Tickets to any effect on actual turnout
If there were nine hundred thousand snakes ticket request
Then there would have been about 19
The Overflow could accommodate
No amount of big-ticket request can explain away a turnout of approximately 6
The only way a high number of ticket request could depress her and if you wanted to you know you wanted to go
You saw the million people requested tickets when you decide there's no way you were going to get it and you decide
To stay home
And guess what
The Democrats and the kids
Trump's campaign to put up a ticket request numbers
And it was his own supporters
That hysteria is on
Them even at the root of it was a very basic online trolling campaign
Did you guys got beat
Just f****** own up to it you lost the information War
Very very stupid Let It Go
Just let it go
Didn't get millions of kids
To do this and not every Tik-Tok user is in the employee of the Chinese government
This is what I believe to call
Information Warfare Ivar people trying to sabotage
Literally listeners thousands of dollars to go to events where Bill or Hillary were speaking in Yelp
As long as they also yelled infowars.com
You don't get to play those sorts of games
Vagina to show up and
Do you like Alexa
Alex's rationalizing pretty hard
Recognize like
Turn off
Just passed Trump on that
When in the face of all that
Black lives matter George Soros
So I'd like to complain about how these kids these days a week
Because they don't want participation trophy
Just existing
Trump held a campaign rally
It seems like a real participation trophy ass mentality to me
You know
It's the kids
It's the kids organized
And they successfully achieve their goal
With no regard for any possible repercussions
But
Trump showed up man
You talk to her
Kind of risk involved in being involved in one of these black lives matter protest
Need to belabor the point again here
Pretending that these two are equivalent to the mark of being willfully ignorant
Or alive
On Saturday
Six of their Advanced staffers were working on putting
Iris
Literally no time to tell
If they'd infected anyone who they were
When I'm getting this episode
Has recorded the two additional staffers
Quote after another round of testing for campaign staff members of
For the Coronavirus
These staff members attended the rally but we're wearing masks during the entire event
Good to see you but Trump's campaign makes a control box
In other circumstances
Unless they're already sick
And they haven't had any symptoms
To save us
Red flag for attendees if they might get sick if they go to this thing
Involved the turnout
Melissa name Thomas
The covid-19 in Oklahoma over the past 20 days before the rally
Which reflected approximately
5% infection rate of the entire population of Oklahoma
His calculations are based on a sellout crowd of 19,000 number is a little bit
To reflect the actual turnout
Have 6200 but there was a
009 percent chance
Let no one in the crowd
Had Coronavirus
Yeah I like
That's B odds that no one there
This could end up being
Merely of
We could be a tragedy that happened for no reason
We'll have to see how things shake out as we get more information as
You know people get to the point where they would be
Be showing symptoms or
Testing positive after
No matter what ends up being human toll of this
Doing this rally was not his
Deserve a participation trophy
A bastet irresponsible at worst homicide
Yeah I was going to say that
It's it's it's your kind of seems like
Him doing that is not a
Participation trophy
So much as it is a death sentence for some of
The people who come
Situation
Had a rally where people were in chairs six feet apart from each other at
20 people there
It was like yeah yeah that was
The point also I don't I don't care
Rally in all this
Control measures in place
Drew his rally
The worst part is
Guys
Once you saw that there was 6200
Socially distant so easily you could have spread around the entire place
Appetite shot of course you need to text your book pack
I know it was made a B on social media
Like
Visceral experience of its own tail to hacky repeating appointment other people that would like
Absolutely have the feeling of like
A comedy show you're running Warehouse
And you're like this hold for another 5 yet my friend said he's on the way
Do people out
Front part of this
Comedy shows
Universal
Now you know what's great is when you have the gas
I brought three out of the four people who are there
And then they all leave after they said
That yep just a real Delight
It all
Brad parscale
Trump
Use the guy who is cleaning up the 800,000 1 million numbers retrospect
Ready for this
Because
He was caught on video being asked
Personal beef
Sky
Parcells
Ourselves
You didn't do anything
Heart scale
You really think
You got a million RSVPs
When was 100,000
Real dumbass
That is very
Why didn't you spot Chicopee when contacted by email and see if they work
Funeralhome.com control
No argument there
2000cc
I've been around
These are people that literally by 2 or 3 or Lamborghini
What does he have time
All these Lamborghini you bought a tank
What is all the time
Interesting
Bizarre
Is there was
Lexus 200 people inside and out
Autozone.com
But not because they're working 10,000 people outside
A week ago
Has nothing to do with the turnout those people
Do hair there goes
Messed with the day 2000 people outside
Bum-rush them
The stragglers percent
It would have been
A more literal version of the abattoir they are walking
We we having 19,000 capacity Arena
200 inside
Outside
It's a good idea if you know what I talked to Trump and he said he wants the smaller
People
Bob's
Discussing his absence
For the last week
Turns out he was going to be
Beach vacation
It's good for him
I mean he didn't need to take
Some time off
You know I resent his luxury but at the same time
I'm glad.
He was not doing well
Get down to the coast for a week with my
Children
Sense of time off
Exaggerating
No way
Not a chance
I yelled at six people a day maybe
Add a what is your version of talking
Exactly that's the only explanation cuz it can't be I listen to anything anybody
He said he'll get into a little bit more about like some of the
More like
Global CNA
Alex this whole time has been teasing a big story
But he's got to get to
At this point he realizes like I haven't I haven't
You know I can I said I'd cover the big news
Covid-19
I guess I'll do that next segment
Trump rally
Minecraft
It's Nails on a chalkboard
I'll play it him talk about us again
Cuz you know what maybe we are low
Garbage
Depends on us all day
Oh my God he was involved with numbing HIV
He is a
So according to the AIDS Institute the earliest known human HIV cases
Democratic Republic
Condo
At the time she was 19 years old just graduated from high school in Manhattan
Andros entering undergraduate studies at Holy Cross
Seems unlikely
Prodigy we've seen you know
I was just make
Shut up the demonizes animes
Regard for the truth in
The public house
I don't give a s*** about any of this
Tina this is the time where it should be like
Get a law firm and just start
Going after people who are lying about
This is too important to let them continue
Surpass the actual malice
Standard that's required for
Alfred suing the public
Publix
I don't know
How do we get to this big news on
Covid-19
18 and it's that they're going to be locked down
Again
Maybe
We do that
Squeezo ceiling light off
Often squeeze again
Stop non-complying
Psychologically figured out until you transcend the psychology
And say hi
This no matter what
Good
Overthrow you
Electricity
They fear for the record I'm not particularly afraid of that clearly
Performative expression is spiritual and
Are you depressed
I'm not scared
And then when tension with the lockdown got too high with people resisting that use a lockdown only to lock down again later one
People light off
It's a compelling way to experience the world but another interpretation of this next bit more
Putting in public health protective mesures is essential in terms
Trying to overcome this pandemic
But
He measures bring up would require amount of political will in right now
Businesses being closed and forced to run safely cut business owners profit
People
If the place that is close
Status of unemployment
But that's just incentivizing people to not get
Our leaders have made the decision that they just don't want to do those things
Cheerleading to
Intentions
Mixer
People who feel like they deserve all the amenities and luxuries they've enjoyed
Back in late 2019
Like going to crowded bars
Sporting event
These people are very loud and insistent the people who are not them should be forced to go back to work
To facilitate their ability
These horses lead to some short-sighted leaders prematurely opening back up businesses
Which has a very predictable result
Spike in coronavirus cases
So now what
You end up in a super predictable and completely on
Winnable situation because
Was safe to do so
We need to close things back up
Any of the other side saying
Just to justify reposing everything
It seems to me that it's too late to do anything about this
A certain section population just doesn't believe this virus is real
Bruce is going to change their mind
I obviously hope for the best
Can't handle
In the current state we're in
The short answer
Find more people
You're going to find more cases so I said to my people slowed
Call Medford
Which he later said
He does not.
Is bulshit not already like
Writing up Nuremberg Trial ship
Has a history of saying that the virus pandemic
In an article in the Hill from May 14th include Trump's comments quote
We have more cases than anybody in the world but why because we do more testing
When you test you have a case when you test you find something is wrong with me
If we didn't do any testing
They don't want to write that it's common sense
Ask much more
Oh and mentioned on Tuesday the 23rd
And his answer was quote
Let me just tell you let me make it clear
Trump is operating off the understanding that goes like this
If we don't know about it
The only thing that makes someone sick is that we have a number on a piece of paper
And that's because the number is legitimately the only part of the whole equation that effect
Higher numbers make him look bad
And he wants lower number
It's that simple
Going back as far as March Outlets like Politico and rolling stone
Administration's efforts to fight Coronavirus
Because
He is quote
Made clear the lower numbers on Coronavirus
The better for his potential re-election
In the fall
What we're seeing right now and the inevitable conversation about reclosing businesses
Expressed by our leadership
With coherent messaging incompetent leadership we could probably easily navigate this challenge
It's obviously not impossible many countries around the world have had success where we've failed
This I believe
What I'm saying is I'm becoming more concerned
About what it will take
To get people
Like the folks
Send Trump's base
To recognize reality
I don't I'm scared more about
B scale
Jamaican
Pretend like
I mean
Honestly it's
That they're there a bunch of Shield
Anytime you have children having a mass
Like this
Quick and dirty
Seiko to timeout
Like what it what are we what should we do
You guys get to come back
In five years
Until then you stay in your place
Vampires
So Alex is mad
About how they're going to lock everything back down
Goes out to break
With
So just pray
Barack Obama and Hillary Clinton
Fauci all of them
To be judged by God.
McDonough car wreck
Chopped off
God
Punishes them
Just say God I love you I trust you
And thank you for Jesus
We just pray for you to get fauci
And Bill Gates and Hillary offer back
Just pray
Forgot
Take action against this monster is demon
No hair
Harmed upon his little
Theodore's
Chinny-chin-chin
Free
So that angel that Moses called on
This is absolutely unacceptable
He's essentially begging his audience
The kill Obama Hillary and fauci
To your neck lift that we just heard
Essential thing to understand is that when Alex says that he prays for God's Vengeance or for God to strike these people
Kind of spiritual
You're not hoping for a stray lightning bolt to hit them on their morning walk
You talkin about them being murdered by another person
It's a fully expressed belief on Alex Jones Show that the concept of Vengeance being
Which is explained by the understanding
God's vengeance
You've been very clear about this
The past the show on April 5th
Vengeance is God
Vengeance is
Gaucho
God has in store
That's always the twist to the riddle
Expect
Terrorize Josh
Monopoly
Your dungeon
We're going to terrorize you
Alex is trying to encourage an unhinged member of his audience
Committing acts of violence
It's against his political enemies
Appealing to quotes gods of vengeance
How to contact it appears that he's just saying that these people will get what they deserve in the afterlife
But if you understand Alex's
Send a text
It cannot be clear In that clip
Do you want someone to kill those be
I don't want to do it myself cuz then I will face consequences
Notoriously averse to that
Right I can't ask
Other people
Consequences
So what I'll do is
Is carried out by actors
One area and then in another area I will call back to that however I will only say
God killed these people
And if you happen to feel like yours
You can't even say no even if someone
Alex Jones
Looks like somebody sitting at their job
How to kill people
Too smart for the law
So Alex gets to talking about
Other staff about the virus and more stuff up
E-Z UP tent
Couple million have starved us
On the news what the big issue
Dead people
Seminole subconscious Twinkie
First I want to say that I've never heard anyone talk more about the idea that there are too many people in Africa than Alec
Talk about overpopulation concerns and sustainable growth
Being helped by available
Family Planning
Sincerely Alex talks about how unnamed other people
Africa
Think it's him
Yeah that sounds right
Story
You're making this up
He's
Apple billion
Just alyx
If you made up updated numbers anywhere including website
Station on this week
P style guide
Because if it's any less than
10 million you can you can call it a handful of Millions
Betsy technically
So the Lord's day being about making up new stories
And is lying about existing
Subjective
Carry workers
This is MSN
For 24 months
A few of the members came out positive
That's right
All of it is just a
Martial law
This is a story about an employer mistreating their vulnerable employees
Seasonal workers
For Mexico
152nd by North Pacific
Dixie foods and they were transported to Alaska
Where they would then work
Until August
In transit they were required to be tested for covid-19
Three of them test
Positive
Well they were awaiting results
Plaza LAX Hotel
Positive results are required to extend their stay very
During which time they weren't going
Going to get paid
The workers filed a lawsuit that alleges that their key cards for their hotel rooms were deactivated
Kum & Go
They were told that if they left their rooms
For any reason
They would be immediately fired
We'll see what comes up when this goes to court but as it appears currently the facts seem to pay
Company abusing migrant labor
And just a few factbase corrections but Alex's fake reporting on this story
Oz of these workers have been forced
To be in quarantine for months
The workers were not even hired until June 2nd
Any hotel rooms
Send story regardless
4 months
That's crazy because a couple of them tested positive for covid-19
Is completely made up nothing to do with it
It's B North
Pacific Seafood Company in Seattle
The only connection with Newsome
Beat the Los Angeles is in the state use the governor of
That's best I can do
These are too factual misrepresentation that Alex make sense
I'm 30 seconds covering the story
You can easily see how these misrepresentation
Completely change the story and make it a lie
These workers are suing North Pacific Seafood at the hotel
The story
He's he's taking what these workers went through in coop
Suffered and blamed it on
Alex doesn't want to deal with this door on the merits and discuss regulating business
Strictly to their Force to protect workers rights
Play flies directly in the face of his entire ideology
At the same time
He can't resist the opportunity to use these workers as a
The prop to attack is imagined
It's like Gavin Newsom
Zoe does it
The history of Labor Relations in the United States is like
Rich corporations will hire people or at least strongly influence that man to make
Making all of their evils in all of their transgression
Appear to be the government
And then the government
Taking all of the heat for that
Making music deregulating s*** in order to mollify the people who wrongly
I think that it's the government
Evil Corporation
Screwing people Corporation
Can screw them over and they still blame
I request that you never looking
Into the history of the John Birch Society and their intertwining with National Association of Manufacturers
I'm so in this next Club
Anthony fauci
And he's talking about how
He doesn't feel great
That Americans seem to not trust science and people who are experts on topics
And Alex's pretty
About this
I'm surprised
And it's amazing sometimes
The same thing that gets people
Anti-vaxxers
Even though the
Cleveland
The safety
Tabaxi
Really
Notice she didn't give me any sources out of here
The kids are pedophiles have sex with him
Mainline the building
I guess if Alex wants to take fauci to task for not proving the vaccines are good in a conversation
His right
Seems like a weird standards ever people but whatever
About sources and sighting stories and what
Completely misreporting
Those articles in the German press do not save its thousands of kids
Foster care with pedophiles
The number is unclear currently but Alex and with these articles are effectively
Using a source
What you doing is appealing to the authority of an outlet like Der Spiegel while simultaneously just met
Making things up
He wants you to take his version of the story as being as legitimate as it might think it is if you heard it coming from
Another Outlet
Because on some level Alex
Vicky's untrustworthy
Precise sight of
Paul Joseph Watson on my reality
Sources sources correctly
Just making things up
Entirely
Oh and if you need a source on that I have about 440 episodes
The podcast I can recommend to you somewhere
Something like that could you could you print out several hundred
Stacks of paper which are transcripts
Just got to get a printer
He's a little baby
Nothing short people he's like
That he's literally limeade
Mm long ding dong
The dude is a jerk
She's five foot seven
Because it demonstrates
The places that Alex Goes when he starts ranting
An attacking people he hates
It's always
Diminish them in terms of how
Define masculinity
Shorty's got a small dick
Alex desperately crave to be taken seriously as an adult but he operates
Entirely is an angry adolescent
Very sad
Common trait among
The Republican
People everybody I know
I don't think
Circle
Facetious I believe he's looking
Shity
That's a good word to
So sprays more than you know is a animated gif
Sunday
I pray that God visit
Judgment in the name of Jesus Christ
Bill Gates
Fauci
Hillary Clinton
Upon the globalist
Forgot to send
Is Angel
My ancestors
Stanford
Cheerios
Play
Creeping death
By Metallica
Specifically not talked out that way
Lyrics very clearly
I'll explain more clearly begging for someone to
To kill his enemies
Yeah
Goodman little bit over
Alex gets around to talking about a big
Figment store
Trump is a hero for doing a campaign rally
All right let's go
Infowars.com
Brawl Brothers
Luciferian March for One World Government
Group organizes Nationwide rallies
Promoting New World Order
Reuters
Nationwide
AP and Reuters are not breathlessly reported on this story
There's a post on Infowars
And his source is a quote Christian YouTuber named Hannah Williamson
4 months ago
One thing I think is really weird is that our Channel page was created in on October 15th
2012 but the oldest video on there is from last year
That's a mystery I don't really care to solve but whatever the case you that young Christian and X Type
Who made a video about the satanic and how they're trying to bring in a one world government
So this is about a group on Facebook called
Disciples of Lucy
Who I honestly think central
Listing for services they offer they say they buy Souls
Whatever your heart desires money sex drugs
Is you
Real weird
You name it
These are all the time
How do you record it on the store
Concluded quote there is no evidence that the marches are legitimate
If you look at the Facebook pages history they did this back in February 2019 as well
Marcus government
The only evidence I can
Can find it anything ever even
Christian showed up
In the rain
After protests
March in Texarkana
And this year continues that tradition
I was able to find a guy in Salem Oregon
But no one showed up
This is almost certainly some dude trolling people with his Facebook page and dumbass is taking it seriously
I wasn't pretending at all
Paige is comes from
The parody of his own beliefs
Isn't that something here
Why are they
We get there so sit with there should be a moratorium on any like
All tricking of the hard-right if you're dumb enough to fall for any hoax
It's fine
Like morally if there is no the downside anymore trick them into doing whatever
I agree with that because I come to a point where
Someone's tricking qanon people into believing X wires
I think it's just not even interesting anymore as a sport or whatever like
Point where you don't prove anything
Or
To trick people in these
Extreme right-wing Cycles
It's it's
There's a
High level of gullibility
This isn't this trolling isn't impressive
Tricking people into believing
Right I meant I meant
I'm out in the rain
All the time
Possibility
Examples that I could find with the Texarkana
People just ended up wasting their time
What is Vine
Comfortable
The thought that like the risk of someone getting hurt
Is chocolate with that
Yammy need to put any proximity
Getting hurt
Like just being around
Carries the risk of being hurt that's the reality of
2020 is that
If you're around the hard right
Radio host is telling people to kill Obama
Christian YouTuber
There's actually another source on
Even try to Alexa
How much really racist statues have been torn down
Allegedly
So The Other Side Story that was just pointed out his intellihub
Which is the stupid blog that says written by
Shepherds
Qanon account
Animal videos
Very weird
My point here is this is not good
It's terrible work with websites
That's already not happened by the time he's on air
These marches were supposed to happen on Sunday at 2 p.m. in Alex goes on a RAV4
Waste of time
Israeli bear
Is really bad
So Alex play some clips of trump speech mysteriously doesn't play with clip where he says I told them to
Text Lex people
Strange
Strange in its absence
Riverside club
Joe Biden the side of a China or America this is really a
When I took
Decisive action
Hysteria
He said he was wrong but he didn't say it
What seven colors on one of those
Policy decisions of our lifetime
He's pretty remarkable and pretty much everything
Is not true
Most interesting narrative about by
So this is a live Trump started rotting out back in March
In an interview with Sean Hannity
In reality B have not called Trump's move to block travel from China xenophobic
What you did was he tweeted
We're in the midst of a crisis with the Coronavirus
We need to lead the way with science
Donald Trump's record of Hysteria xenophobia
He's the worst possible person to lead our country through a global Health Emergency
This became Biden Colony travel restrictions hysteria xenophobia
You know that wasn't what Biden said
And it's a pretty fair description of Trump's history
I'm the victim no matter what I'm just
Naturally this letter was made up
Never happy
Trump is complaining that the media didn't cover a send him to apologize for
Play in the first place
The rallies mad
ImmediaDent carburetor
I'm struggle
Struggling
Struggling with opening my eyes ever in the morning
Don't like it
Really hot sauces
That's a good idea
Cuz it would hurt
So Alex and Sunday episode here
Just it's Madison
Okay
You know we're going to win
One way or the other
But if we don't win
This way peacefully
People shoot their mouths off all daily one violence
Are you really ready for that
You ready for that
Appreciative
Great job. Viewers electrician Affiliates we thank you all
Luckily
Text your prayers going back tomorrow
Oh boy
I'll go down the Strand
Shoot people
And then constantly praying on are for these specific targeting of the people he deems as anime
Real comforting fireside chat
I just like to sit around
Remind myself how
It's a it's a it's us against them
Do you know
So Alex, 22nd
Quite a bit at the beginning or something or something
Do it
Building the shop
Everything I heard this before
My brain and covered properly
I took off
Last week and nnn only work about 5 hours a day
The normal 12 or so
Back here in studio
And I'm just looking all of this it is
Personally really frustrated so
So fitting that he came in with
King nothing
Absolute
Bowser
A story
6 thing is
About
Video of G Edward Griffin
Who is an old-time
Video cam from the 6
Steve
Baby contraction people posting on social media
Is mad because what has been done
Is the Infowars logo
So Alex Alex appliances
Little bit
While I'm up here on air
I didn't remember a bunch of things
And so
There's just too much planning goes into the show
Griffin clip from the 60s
Yeah I sent it to Rob do a couple times
An article about a griffin
I am plan to try America
At 1 today
Infowars.com
Assure link to these peoples YouTube video
The Clincher clips
I went before he died
YouTube
And then they don't even have the common courtesy to
Website
Batman
Do Clippers really hilarious
He's so mad that his personal use the clipper
G Edward Griffin took the Infowars Watermark off it to the point before
I can understand his anger
You know it's pretty clear
Person would remove that Watermark is
Because they know that any association with Infowars
Your video looking please stupid
Rather not people know
There is
We've talked a little bit about G Edward Griffin in the past
The John Birch Society
When Alex says the Griffin expose the Communists are trying to create a race war in America back in the 60s
Alex is really just describing G Edward Griffin called the Civil Rights Movement
Plot
This was a pretty standard feature in the anti-communist hardliners in the US
Set the time
Anytime there was something we're white interest or threatened it was a manifestation of evil communist meddling
The fight against the brutal apartheid regime in Rhodesia was the work of commies
Nelson Mandela's campaign
You start to notice a little bit of a
Choose writing screenplays
Parallels between the president in nineteen
Thumbtack
And one of them is the rhetoric coming out of these damn extreme-right which
Is now the mainstream right
This isn't because G Edward Griffin was some kind of a prophet it's because of how these folks always respond to attempt
Wants to create a more Equitable Society
The other side of this is at the Communist Party in the United States
Pretty long history of fighting for civil rights
And so you
Always be able to find
Waze
To link
Communist Party 2
See look they're fighting for civil rights
Are they
Race war with Communism
Distribute
That's how they're going to
Sure okay
So in the State score
Alex
But he seems unable to really get
Perfect timing
To get into the globalist master plan at the bottom of the next hour and
We'll do it then
It's just that I probably need to take off
For 10 minutes or something
Do my office with this article
Just get those out info
Focus on it because
I'm hungry
Play Babel about this
Could be us
Probably I like the headline on it
I don't know where to land
Right prepared at all
Berrington place
You finally
Sit down
Outside
Let's do it
Your gums
My big story that I've been teasing
Alright
Major Ally
Beautiful and wonderful the end of humanity is going to be because she has fallen
Ugly
Sale
And it covid-19 is teaching us to lower carbon footprint
To live
In our houses
And that virtual reality is coming that will plug directly into brain
It will give you this beautiful wonderful New World and then
You got a
Hit the button
Turn off your body and Diane stop being a bad carbon life form
Okay come on
Only thing worse than eating meat is actually made out of
And that you will then be uploaded and merge
With this beautiful
Wonderful super intelligence that will be gone
It will be the Beast
You worship
You will have to accept it when the Beast says it's your time
For the carbon balance
You will go to a facility
You'll be checked in your consciousness
Then you will live forever
Where's the Super Intelius
4 page article
Wall Street Journal
Completely misrepresenting this article in the Wall Street Journal
Normally talk about
At all
Core pages
Too long
So if you made it to the end of that opinion
You see what a residence
More of the burdens and dangers of physical existence
This class in professional divide
With the virtual Elite being served
In class
Of course welcome power of always offered some insurance against lifespan
During the Civil War America
Substitute to take their place on the drive
So you may be able to pay someone to take your place in the disease and danger written physical world
Well you stay behind at the safety of a screen
Human future in which mortality
But if it sooner for some of us than for others
To prove to be a
Dystopia
The beginning of the essay is about the kind of standard transhumanist ideas about being able to develop
Come up with some kind of a mess
Stop aging
And the notion that our consciousness
Could it possibly become
Non-local
The rest of the article as it goes along seems to be the
Coronavirus
About these futuristic ideas
Different sorts of jobs have different levels of ability to avoid risk
In the pan
And this reveals an inherent social
Inequality that could be magnified
Exponentially
In the event of any betrayal
Read correctly
This article seems to be a beast that looks at a balance
There's a possibility of amazing technological
And me life extension
Even if you only consider the ability we would have to travel around the Galaxy
Probably be something
Get f*****
Decided
The end
I think that's more
As I kind of like a warning
Yeah in the same way that top one
Consolidated
Wealth Beyond
Reason now there
Essentially
Consolidating the future is
They get to own all of the time
Handled
Capital do we have in the world
You could very easily see the ways in which
Could be used
Looking forward
Decided that was enough for a what's up
Just making all the rest of it up
That's all I had to do is work
How dare you say that
You read the headline he ate a sandwich
Story about the German children
Just like their acceleration
Like there's there's
Khushbu
Come out the German government was
Nationwide
For 50 years
Taking tens of thousands we now learn
To produce
Scientific literature
The ultimate family and the ultimate love
The story is that extends 1000
Children in Germany or given to pedophiles
I was just making that up he has absolutely no citation or source
This is a pattern of Alex's Behavior
What do tens
To do is find a story that's true on a basic life
Is a real story underneath
But what Alex did on Sunday was create a fake version of this story could see more exciting for him
A fake version that
Alex gets bored easily though so you and the thrill of telling the fake version of the story only lasted a day
Before you needed to embellish it further
With no evidence now tens of thousands
Jason just reporting on
Was Tim children
He further embellishes the story to say that it went on for 50 years
The report
Those witches all Alex ever even say that it was 30 years
It is important to understand
Alex cannot help himself
You can't resist lying about stories like this to weaponize them against his chosen Target
If he cared about this story or the vicar
Responsibility
You can never act this way it's just that it's an incomplete
F*** you to everything
He's getting himself
Like that's
How could you do
How could you do that unless there was some perverse pleasure
Probably be
As inclined to believe that it's more situation where he recognizes
How powerful it is
For his listeners
Like it's such a
Like
The button for people
We're a lot of there
Skills you can leave them
More into a
Buying your s***
Kind of mindset
It's very extreme and it's very visceral
Corby bolts
It's something that I think
You just understand the power of
I think that's what he's doing more than
Him actually like
For sure
Of course he's doing that
The ways doing it but the way that he embellishes
From a day-to-day
Racist
Personally
Let me
Situation where
Bored like
The story there's something right
It's more of a like
To keep pushing Hawaii
Right
There's no excitement
Kind of like a twisting of
Reasonable or moral
Something
Talkin about
People people a day
Sure sure sure sure
Actually this is pretty interesting cuz I make
Turn on Cube
The Gulf
Mexico
Wife
Most people didn't know who I was
30%
What almost everyone else I'll be at the bar picking up food to take the room
Bill Gates
I'll be at the beach
Because
General Public
Not really political
Whenever
I just get mad by
Some of the key people
Think about me that's not true
Whatever I
Symposium on a show about Q
Positive or negative
I think it's positive
I don't know how you can just go back and forth on this Tuesday route onto
You can't get it they hate you
If you can't beat them join them doesn't work whenever then wants you gone
I like the idea that maybe you saw standing up on this
And there'll be some desperate overtures that will be mocked
And we can call up
Guys over to an autonomous if there's any Rumblings
But I will see
Episode
Interesting
As the 21st episode had a lot more like really f***** up things
Studio
Portion of the stuff on the 22nd would be just
Eating a lot a stuff Friday
Sunday
Reverend
Who's the guy who believes that
Abortion is black genocide
Use the black preacher who who Alex had on today after heart and Charleston
He can't
Who
Color that
He's kind of sick of trump
Everybody loves you
Alright
32 years old
I've been on Euston
Prison Planet when the internet went
Get on
Emily loves you
We have to re-evaluate this political state
Situation
And it as a as a brother in Christ I want to tell you
Compass Foods
Seafood everybody
We have to get over that
We have to go forward
There's nowhere else to go
You know at
Good question
When I realized it's all a sham
You know his money the Sham
His Investments are probably install it and probably 90%
Holding someone else
Do you realize that stuff that Alex back in 2015
I noticed you just talk about Rodger Stone
Bas best friend
He's letting them go
If you were my friend and you let me go to prison
Over nothing
I'd be upset right
Where is he
I think the jury's still out on that one but
For the journey is
So is it his response was like what no
I hate to be this guy
But
If I got elected
If you were going to go to prison
I wouldn't I wouldn't
It would call into question some
It would be like wow cuz I
President
Not true of the Rodger and
I would not condone those sorts of activities
Out my permission
It would be a breach of our friendship with you
Did what Rodger did
Wow
Like a situation where
So of course
Jokers
And the boys are back
Do you know what it is about that call
It's me
Because
You know it's it's one of those microcosm things that he extrapolated onto everybody but for somebody to say
I think we're done with Trump
You fooled me
And what is everybody
You fooled everybody
Thanks buddy
Wait I wait to read outside of your
Right right
The first thing he goes to is money
The first thing he says is
He's not actually
That's what you're going to think about
Trump
Come on man
Pretty sad
That's pathetic
Disgusting
You know obviously the coverage of that German story is
Repulsive
Unacceptable
Dislike
Praying for the angel of death to come
Repeat it
Isabel
Particularly as
Tensions rise again as these coronavirus cases are increasing in anambra state
Attention of that pressure that's
Being Quran
AMV
Conversations that are going to need to happen I believe are already starting to happen about how things are
Probably just getting
You're going to have to be scaled
I don't know how's that
Increased pressure is going to go well
When right now Alex is having the conversation of
God's Vengeance must be acted on my enemy
Second
Like I don't see how you can look at
Will be a second
Write like
Happen have happened before
A few months ago
It's not like we're dealing with ancient history this stuff all happened before
Little bit ago
People are experts
Issues
The chances are there
It does seem like it I don't know
Hate to have any kind of
Predictii you're like this is what's going to happen but that friends really don't look good
At the same time
I don't know I'm going to try and be optimistic
Charity in your area bail fund or the like
And help out people doing God's
Talk to 80 people a day
Alex