Important
I have great respect for snowledge b b
Knowledge fight
Acknowledge
Nick.com
Ciara's Pizza
Still in town
The skating rink down a little bit
Yes yes
Right at the gate
Is wrong I don't know what it is
Okay I just I got a little overexcited did you start doing hot yoga
Just exercised
Competitive
I don't know what
It's not okay
Saturday's that's with knights
I'm used to you yelling all the time even somehow that was
Too much
The podcast
What's up
Can I ask a question
Start I'm going to go
I finally bit the bullet and I was done with all the side quest
Yelling
Horizon zero Dawn
Wild DLC
Play the main storyline in in
Fantastic
Fandango
I don't think it's going to be out until next year probably this evening
Because I don't want to buy a PlayStation 5
I don't know
I always get really mad whenever there's new systems out cuz like this is how they scam you
Allure these games that you want to play you have by the system in order to play them and then they're obsolete in the news
I turn into a cranky old man
Excited about the new system no
Betta with a better format if you had a Time
Stamp on it is way better
Congratulations
Are you an alien
Into the year of the
We are now 152 South years into the year of
Deserves a little bit of a celebration
Crazy
Yeah that's
That's a lot of stuff.
Good-natured ribbing about not liking Seltzer's themselves
Shelter podcast
To bring some sort of normalcy
You can still enjoy and I enjoy bubbly water
Everything I was I wanted to bring
Sharp Focus 250
Shelters in
If you look at the top five Seltzer's that we have
There are two that are from Mars Brewery
Even existed
Shelters for starting
Score stop for fifth
Now between Lacroix and hibiscus
Hibiscus
Either of those if it wasn't
Naturally
Black cherry coffee
Isn't it a number 2 on the list
Of the top five
Absolute
Pedal
The Elderberry flower
Stood at the store
Some hippie-dippie
Little bug water with flowers on it
It's a one of these it's really nice as being able to
To force myself into position for him
Trying a bunch
Lo and behold all of the things that I
I had
Before
Are found wanting compared to these new things that I'm trying to
Who played CeraVe microcosm with life
Yeah you do a little bit of an exercise something
It seems really stupid like I'm going to drink 500 South
Do you find
Really good one
But you never would have tried
Maybe you can incorporate into your life to make your life better moving forward
When we get to
U300
Will you be so exhausted with seltzer
Nothing is going to break into the top five
So
Because there's
Untappd stuff
I might be able to find
Craps
Nature's next one to hundred
Should I
Phenomenal
Standard ass lemon lime grapefruit
And
It does lead to a little burn out until the
Like well maybe that would have been a 60%
Yeah yeah
Is grapefruit but that's how it goes
Except
I think as we go along with
Even greener pastures
Wondering if we're going to get a perfect score
Blue whale
It's possible
I've been very conservative with my scoring
If I were to guess based on how this is gone so far
It'll be something floral and something
T related
Those are clearly the best
Sure we get off of here this
Fort Morgan
Will you consider revising a score
Later on
General Sam
No
Okay
I don't think I should
I think I think that would be
Dirty pool
That we get to the end of the highest scores in 86
Does that mean everybody
It's 14 more points attitude
I think I think
350 or now 64
If it ends up in a situation where we get to 500 Mi scores 93
Or something like that
Did there is the the platonic ideal
100 round
That's okay
In itself exactly
Year of the seller is very philosophical at this point
Alright
You're signed up and recording the show
So first
Mister Malone
Habeas Dorcas
Thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Journal
Like Sigmund
Profile
Virginia Beach
What's your name
I'm a policy wonk
Virginia
G
Poff
Thank you next
Brittany
Gravity head 20
And Eric are
I like this a lot this is a Eric's
Jric
I'm a policy wonk
Heroin
Freakishly large
Tara car
Or you could take
That's a general
Yourself
Gotham glass jars
That generosity in the safely sterilize glass jars single
Send them to a local area that I can help people in need
Better than less.
33rd and 24th 2020 This Is Now by autonomous Zone
Before we get to that
I'll take care of up top and back
Can be found underneath
Your number
Piece of mail what is this
It'll probably stuck to the underside of your your note
You can. You can read
All right here
4 Jordans
Since you like other final fantasies MMOs
For everyone but fighting imperialism
Oppressive
And a cosmic horror that the metaphor for Boomer ideology
From policy wonk.
Oh thank you very much that's it
You didn't say what it was it is Final Fantasy 14 online
No I've never
I've always played the single player
Single story line
Before in my life and I'm worried for you
You again
Conceivably at NeverEnding
This will be my life
It for now
It was going to become another job
You know like I'm just existing I also have a job
Do end up feeling like
Chores
Could you have to wait a day in real time to farm
It's a little exhausting
Intensely difficult
Focus on doing this year
Because of Alex it's his fault
Been good there's still some interesting things
Definitely requiring
Track of butt
So many
Guests on these shows
Is just like
I don't care about any of these people I don't
Care
I couldn't give a
Write a large portion of of the time
It's sometimes
Listening
Because there's interesting things regularly or he's being entertaining and yelling like a dumb dumb
This is the office hours of listening to him
Caribou
Dog shots
However
We start here on the 23rd
We start with
Oz on this episode
That is very bad
The rollout
Is covid-19
It is just excuse
Hysteria and
Why we're making a big announcement later
In a second hour today
I'm a nationwide movement
Can't breathe
It'll be all the video
I will be out at the
Texas
Capital this Sunday
By noon
Protest the governor's
Capitulation
Gavin Newsom in the UN
Yes I heard that and I really set me off on a bed
Feeling like
God
I don't even want to do this anymore like
I just see the machinations of it I see the what
He's doing
You trying to trick people into getting mad at him
Illicitly distasteful abrasive
In order to be like
I'll pay attention
Insane it just feels so lame
It's just eat
Bad Pro incredibly
It's on
The same yeah it's just shity trolling but on a genocide scale like what he's describing what is essentially biological
At this point
I'm going to go out and spread this disease
Possibly can
As a form of troll I mean
It's hard to say how many people
How much
Denial
First and most important Point here is that words of George
Eric Garner
That's a profoundly disrespectful and race
Stacked
I was just trying to protest the fact of Texas
Does dum-dum Governor Greg Abbott state is in trouble
Do you spell safety measures in place like telling people to stay at home
Put it possibly I haven't some masks orders in
Alex and his buddies have already protested
They were the ones who were doing all those
Add Alex and Owen went out there with their bullhorns back at the end of May and yells about how the state needed to reopen
Texas's report reporting
As of June 23rd that number was
120,000
70 cases
Haven't reported over 27,000 new cases in the past week
Alone
We flattened the Curve
Alex's.
Import
On some level I think he knows that
The best I can really do is go back out and argue that the numbers are alive and Texas
Should be afraid of clearly spike in covid case numbers
And that's not going to get him the attention that he wants
But if you flexes his racist muscles and tries to start a we can't breathe movement
Maybe just
Maybe
Erlanger people enough to get them to cover image
Disgraceful and desperate and I hope that people don't
Take the bait
The Free Press
Yeah it's it's like the next day
Just coming out
I Have a Dream speech
She's being like
I stole a dream
You miss the point
We can't breathe the name of an organization that already
Whose mission statement reads
Create
Disparity
Together we create
Community Through Loveland
Peaceful intent
Something tells me that they're going to have a bit more traction than Alex is dumb
Publicity stunt
I went to his new website
It's just got a bunch of Infowars videos posted on there and then there's some posters you can download without masks are bad
Here's the thing that I think is really funny though
All of the posters include the weather
Which is we can't breathe.
But in Egypt
Booster the apostrophe is included in the word can't
If you type a URL in a zit appears on those posters you will never find Alex's website and it just seems like bad playing from
Graphic design stamp
Apostrophe
The demographics of their older people
I have a strong suspicion that this protest
But he's trying to get going we'll be very underwhelming
They plan to meet and have a prayer service at the Capitol then March to the governor's mansion.
Mask-wearing
That's a little scary in there right up is this
Freedom lovers are welcome and then in all caps
Mask-wearing is discouraged
!
All right guys
This is dangerous and irresponsible but actually just
Stop them from holding the event
I'm guessing turnout
Ignore them and not give
Attention
How Alex
Named
The most effective response I think
It sucks because
You know
Defensive
I think the best response
Strategically is just Veigar
Just ignore it
Proposal
And that is
Rent
Attached to them
A giant
During the protest
Has to have the
Captors drop the Dome slowly on top of that
Albion
What what are holes in there
Wicked wicked frolicon player
Going to run into money
Talking about some other stories
I got a bad angle on this one
Early Hollywood is collapsing
A bunch of producers are dying committing suicide
That is all coming up in that size of the giant pedophile Networks
Collapsing
In big
Darius substantial trouble
The blackmail
And control the population
I told you
24 hours left
The big mega sale in the items that are still
60 to 70% off
Nailed it
Sweet that was rough
Lubed up
Alex's
Hollywood producers dying from suicide like
True but
He's just embellishing the story one recent headline
About the death of Steve Bing
The window of his 27
Floor apartment on Monday
There's no connection I can find him being involved in the views of children and
Close to the factory statements there if he's not careful
Mental illness for years
And quote
His close friends are devastated about his death
But sadly not surprised
Other discusses trouble with drugs and the fact that he appeared really rich on the surface but
He made a lot of ill-advised
Investment
People imagine
And it's impossible to run through 600 million dollars but
I guess I guess if you Brewster's Millions then you win I don't know I don't know what to say
Tragic story
Two claims in anyway this is another example of
Your stamp
Beat him making up details about a story in order for them to
Predetermined area
It is
It is a
Double exploitation of something that's
Multiple tragedy
He's all in the same kind of situation
The
Real pedophilia
To score points
And then exploiting a man suicide
Due to
Host of factors including mental illness
Moved on with his life like that's fine like we all the rest of us have
How to deal with this post
He just gets
I'm not
Defending this guy
This producer I don't know anything about any
The insinuations that Alex
Just trying to make
The mark of someone who is a real pilot
But
Even though Alex is a pile of s***
That doesn't mean he doesn't want to surround himself
And we meet the first one
Have you here when the only people as band as I am
Elite fraternities
You for joining us my friend
Well you got banned on YouTube let's get into that and let's get into the State of Affairs and trop and where you see this all going at
Can still find you
Uncensored unfiltered at censored.tv
Yeah it's the last
What about band.
Do you know who that is do you recognize his voice
I do not know
Okay
Play along
Damn it up Gabba
It's the whole time how much
Credibly long because a lot of it is Alex just rip
Repeating nonsense that he says all the time between sucking boring for us
To keep going over
Gavin
No I'm not really interested in gathering McGinnis
Hard-hitting takes on
The present let me do my impression all right
Website
That happened for a while because
Did you get them promotional attention out of here
This is not the first time he's been kicked out YouTube
In December 2018 he was booted for
Copyright violations
Opportunity
Respond to these copyright infringement claims
It appears he did not resolve them which is what Alton
Smitley lied to the bank
This is around the same time that Glenn Beck Network The Blaze
Publicly dissed
Themselves from Gavin
Unfunny fascist piece of s***
Hotels right
The splc
Arrow flurry of stories about that back in February 2019 but mysteriously nothing meaningful sense
Tivoli with the law
So I assume
He got back on YouTube
Is it considered incitement towards violence
Well I don't know this
Pacific spice
Deserve and overdue
I went to his website what a roster of losers who got working for him
You got Milo Alex's former employee
Pizzagate Rambo Joe Biggs
Jacob Wohl and Laura Loomer
Call Manuel
Italian Job level crew right there talking about terrarium bubble
Keep them all in one studio for like a marathon or something
Former boxer breaks down
Whatever
You can't watch any content on his website
Subscription
People stuff
10 bucks a month or $100
Hundred dollars a year to get access to all the stuff that those buffoon
Can't imagine
Talent pool like being compelling sales pitch
For people but that's what you're going to do good luck
Not to read anything by those I honestly if you if it was
Between giving you money
And just reading one of their articles
I swear to you I will give you money
Now I was going to say that like it wasn't behind a paywall maybe I'd do some like episodes by Rapido big butt
I realized
Since there's no way I can do that
You take it back not to going
Conservatives
Is complaining about how like all these people who censored
Remembers that like Ralph Northam did blackface
You're a Nazi helmets
Everybody
Jason says
You should be banned
So
It's really interesting to hear Alex struggle to come up with a reason why you shouldn't do blacks
You started say it's too dangerous
Correct
Lathrop
Use originally trying to say it's
Could kick your ass
We just got it
Also do yourself a favor and Google Gavin McGinnis in blackface
I'm sure he's never done it
Fun fact
Blackface
Gaston Steven Crowder show the title was time for blackface
The time I didn't know exist
Is it also in 2014
What's wrong with blacks
Lots of things
Alex could hardly the worst person to be like hey you never done that
Publicly defended blackface
How is it that
Sahara Desert
Respect there's no such thing as history there's no such thing as
It's all in the present
And usually that's a good bet
B-real
So Gavin
I can't
Get myself
To care about
Interview
The more we sort of ignore
That's a great show
It's not
I love your old white man
Is it just next Cliff we get to another gas
Powerhouse Duo
Again
He's known for a while
This is
There's a big story at
Josh. Cam.com
Content moderator
If someone's wearing a mega hat
I'm going to delete them for that
Facebook Insiders
McElroy
What is against Trump supporters
So are we get another person project Veritas name Zach
So
I'm so proud
The guy's name is Zach Michael McElroy and
Is a Content moderator for
Cognizant
Is a company that Facebook subcontract
Run moderation
According to his telling of the story people he worked with a cognizant conservative bias
Which is that being used say the Facebook hasn't anti-conservative is
This doesn't work
Even if we accept Zach's premise that his co-workers were all out to go
Get conservatives any problems with Cox
You should be under contract with cognizant
If you was trying to do anything
Not his ankle problem
Specific
The cognoscenti
We're not about winning or doing the right
Even having a
This is about screaming about something
I watched the video and legitimately the first thing that
It's brought up doesn't prove anything
James O'Keefe
Ask Zach about these
Temeku
And Zack says that 75 to 80% of the post
Nike you came from Republic
Open pages
The first problem is if there's no metrics
Provided on this
It's just that estimation which I have no reason
And believe or trust
But even if he is telling the truth and this number is accurate that conservative bias
Maybe there's more harassment being done by right-wing Associated Facebook pages
Maybe they're not
There are other explanations for the phenomenon has described
But the conclusion is reached
Just more evidence
Facebook
Republican
That's a sloppy assumption and if that's other videos opening
You can't really have much they're going to do much better as it goes along
So his idea though is that there would be a 50
Reporting
If it was objective
Yes that's basically his ark
Yeah
Ruby equal
Even though
That's
Simply not
Function of either minutes
Human behavior
You can have a perfectly Fair algorithm
And it could be like
90%
Because
Facet of the online Republican necessarily
Nothing to do
The large section of Republicans
The ones were buried
Plus they never really
Q is whether or not it's
Just things that are automatically caught by algorithms or if it's
Things that are recorded
Manually by people and that could make
Did giganti difference in terms of what ends up
Temeku
Say I trust any of this
Words taken out of context
Conservative post
Even if they're not violating the rules
However Veritas forgot to cut out the part where she says
I don't give no fux it's like 1 week
She's clearly someone who has quit
Is working
Which implies have consequences
To the video actually proves that deleting conservative post that are not
Think about it
Do not use the part-time great work veritas
And then
I do like
There's another exchange moderator who's
Conservative post even though it's supposed to
That should be taken down
So she's kind of like almost
The sympathetic
Person
And then
The office
Insert slur for a little person
Harass about his height
Okay this is making a strong case about this harassment stuff
The sympathetic person is a person who
Person who's doing khubaib your butt at work
Oh great
This is just another standardized Veritas by all the trash
Is there a test wanted to do some work that actually was meaningful maybe they could have been like Casey Newton at the verge
Who didn't expose in early 2019 about the horrible working
Conditions of Facebook moderators
A cognizant worth
Subjected to
Helped Along by Newton
Recording Facebook agree to a court settlement
For the mental health issues
The moderators developed
From filtering
Terrific content
On the platform keeping all that stuff off
German article about that
Moderator will receive a minimum of $1,000 in additional compensation
Stress disorder or related
Conditions
The settlement covers 11200
50 moderator
That's reporting that matters
It makes people's lives better
Scandal
If you never
Good C project Veritas even coming close to it
They don't cover actual fraudulent Hatchet pieces for profit
But it's not surprising exact McIlroy has already put up a GoFundMe page
Is looking to raise $150,000
Episode it's been up for a day over thirty $4,000
F****** cry
This is the right wing Griffith
It's very profitable
It's just not a gig that last very long
So you get your GoFundMe
And then you are you just nothing for you to do
Got nothing else to do maybe you kind of working a crunch
That's going to look good on a resume
Step Up
Just don't understand why
Conservatives
Can't demand better live at
Like James O'Keefe's videos all suck
And half
Time
The opposite Point than what he wants
True
Demand better don't get all the money until he makes it better move
Yeah it's tough
Because you know he had the back
Sitting in the support of Andrew Breitbart
He's almost royalty in terms of
Like those
Connections
That's where you at
You just can't let him get away
Well speaking of that
James
He shows up
Show up
Whistleblower and
And so they're just talking about
This is how
Thumbs up what Mark Zuckerberg is doing
So what is essentially done here
Is he subbed
Contracted
Out his
To these third
Party companies
Like
The one that's
Cognizant
Outfit
Which is where all these content Reviewer is do their business
Because Zuckerberg wants Maybe
Separation
Motorcycle game
That's all he's done like a mafia
Littlesubgirl
Yeah the mafia create a little sub fam
Facebook
Didn't create cogs
Borders
Dad was wrong.
Whatever
Interesting point
But it relies on a large unproven assumption
In order for this argument to fly he needs to Devin
What street did Facebook subcontracted cognizant in order
If you wanted for Facebook
Wild Fork
Conservative Target
Keeps his hands clean
Has not demonstrated
Visit all
Easy to accept literally every piece of evidence
Presented
I believe it this is
The problem with
Cognizant and not with Facebook
That's one of the reasons why this is
Incredibly sloppy reporting it doesn't mean anything
There's another huge problem with this story and that is at the end of 2019 it was pretty
Technology Solutions
Was getting out
The content moderating business
Delete all 6,000
Employees and told investors in a financial operations
Within a subset of the content operation
Business are working
Don't determine whether certain content violates clients
Objectionable material
We've determined that this subset of our work is not in line with our
Dziedzic vision
Or the company
In response to the news Facebook's VP of scaled operations
We respect
Target's institutions
Content review services for social media platform
Had a 100 million dollar per year
Deals Romney's moderation
Facilities
Sounds like a ton stand
Parkinson disease
A huge and diverse company
The revenue last year was
18.8 billion dollars
Giant
What the f*** are these people
Right
Be phased out over 2020
It calls into question a lot of content
4th and o'keeffe's
This interview it seems
Like it might be old
Yeah it sounds like something up here but I don't know what it is and doesn't add up
Out the window
Another important point is that there's a bunch of companies that Facebook subcontracts to do moderation work
There's pron unlimited Accenture Badger LG
Global company
Yeah
Give me the more than
Do you need people to be doing this 24 hours a day or else
People posting beheading videos
Get to the beheading videos
Text dad that leaves them up
414 hours
Right
It's it's
This isn't even for project
Disappointingly week
Yeah
That's essentially exactly what Alex.
He constantly tells his audience
Block Story
Exactly
Different
Business strategy entirely at this point just trying to
Gives you different names
Getaround
He is a biker gang that has to say
Ridiculous
She's bad at Rebrand
Newswars it's just going to be spelled with a
Dino
.
Alex's mad about masks
Tomorrow because it looks like
Governor Abbott's going to mandate wearing masks name in
Sores inside
I hate you
F****** mascot
Alex
California or Texas
I say California.
Here we go
You could go
Course they can
Can't make you wear that
California.gov is not an actual webs
It's ca.gov
Freddy California
Leaving that aside of course some people are not required to wear
Princeton's in California people communicating with someone who needs lips
Communicate
Restaurants in or able to sit
Speedway from other parties aren't required to be Maxwell eating
People doing outdoor recreational activity don't have to wear masks as long as they
Can stay distance
From others
Their folks medical mental health or developmental disabilities that make it so they could not wear masks
Safeway
Those people are exempt from the requirement honestly
If you have a medical issue that makes
Makes it so you can't wear a mask
It seems like you might not risk
Going into places at their height
People during an active pandemic
Then such
Most of such medical issues would likely involve breathing related condition
Before put you in a higher risk
Category
Like this is the angle that
These exemptions pretend we all have those
Exemptions
Just f****** we're messy like people used to get medical marijuana
I got a cough so I'm going to get a weed card man
There's a difference
What is a similar Behavior
Got it just
This is another thing
Just goes pretty much throughout these days
Decided to run this we can't breathe March
Going hard on this mask exemption
It's sad but it's
Also serious
Stupid petulant stupid
Are you going to get people killed
Just don't understand
This is stupid on a level
Is is problematic for me because it suggests that like where's the f****** lie
You know like
The government mandates
Taxes so you pay f****** tax
Not over you that
But you get
From paying the taxes
Entirely for granted
Part of you love so god-damn sidewalks
Lake Michigan
There's 100
Examine
Things that you just go about your life and you don't realize are taken
Tara by everyone Poseidon
Chip in for taxes
And the same thing with this to
The government says we gotta wear masks going to go inside businesses
You know there is a collective communal
Responsibility
Taking care of that
And that's another thing
Charlie Clips
Consistent
But like
Start using shown that masks
No one is arguing
Will protect you as a Sara Lee
If everyone wore a mask
It's about stopping the spread.
During any
I just
Boggles my mind like I'm not saying
Is it blanketly accept anything that the government says like you were saying with Tex
Can take for granted
And in this case
Is that why you can take
For granite is when you can see directly in front of your face
People are f****** done
You know where goddamn ask everybody
Dying
Look at how great it was that we more warm at
Comparison between Texas
Get the little bit murky
There are number of people who
To take a conscientious stance of non-payment of rexhaj
I have that kind of
There isn't an analogue for that
Your face gets
Sweaty sometimes
That's about it
What's
It was a tough
Like its first
Day
I'm not a guy who accessorize has
Perhaps I've never had an earring
I don't like sunglasses
Sunglasses my cross eye
I've never put
Beads in my beard
It was a tough little bit of a just
I'm choosing to do this looking at me
That's pretty quickly
Attention to yourself wearing this accessory would be drawing attention to yourself
Inferior
Get over it
He's mad at Governor Abbott
Interesting
View of how come
Alex
The most out there conservative
Nonsense
Is
He's taking the virus seriously too late
Best
The governor California sets the precedent
I told you other taking follow
And then
Is now literally the Mini-Me
Follow his orders
The taxes is not just been colonized
California rejects now
We are now
Governor Newsom
Gavin Newsom
The governor of Texas
Governor resigned earlier yesterday
California governor
Might as well
I know that Alex is trying to be like kind of
Funny it's not funny but
You really is like
Overly dramatic
His life is over
This crush doesn't want to go to this Governor does almost everything in line
I like isn't doing what I like this time therefore
California metals
Call myself in the street cuz now the Newsom is my governor
I think there's something interesting about this idea that California was going to put in this
Mask requirement
Following the governor of California
An underlying element of this is
Is the Texas would be just
Following California's leave boat
If I were to tell you the California was not the first state to require masks in public
California's order when to place on June 18th because I live in Illinois I know that we've had that shipped
And we already been the first
State
According to CNN the first state to require masks
New Jersey back on April 8th
Alex
Bill Murphy
He is currently the governor of New Jersey Rhode Island Pennsylvania New York New Mexico
Massachusetts Maryland
Kentucky Illinois
Delaware Connecticut
California
Wow he really you know I knew there was a power vacuum but I didn't know you
You could really
You could really grab it
0 powers
Country
Not a bad little kingdom guys got going on
Most of the economic centers of country
You got a lot of Leverage California
You got Illinois
Yeah
Hey wife
Stupid
California
Recognized
Doing
Has like a like a
Hyperbole
Over and over and over again
It's all funny the first time it's not interesting
I don't know
The failure engine sounds like a baby
Also it's
Today is it's one of those things where it's like
How long before you'll be next week whenever is like
Cuz he did this
Missing you like what the fuc
Right right
Love is Real Deals number one guy
So Alex gets into talk about somebody's exemption
Are there available for people with masks
For hearing impaired
Hearing impaired
Running ability to see the mouth
Is essential
Discovering
State federal and regulations in
Yeah they just passed along California exempt of your brown
I'm not joking
So pretty cool to hear Alex
You just lie about being
What revolutionary we have on our hands here
Do you know when you're willing to die for your car
Pretend you have a disability
Was not about that
It was about
Updating
Heelys
I got nothing
I do have to admit that
Frequently lied about being astute
To get cheaper movie
I mean that's fair
Right
Slightly different
Same behavior saving those two bucks
Exactly
Different saving
That last part is really into
Purpose clip
It's not entirely made up but
The stories talking about wasn't California
An Oregon
This is a specific in Lincoln County in Oregon
Population 49 South
Does 90%
Less than 1% black
The reasoning behind
Exemption for people of color to not have to wear masks
Explain by Trevor logo
A professor at Ohio State
Wear a mask seems like a reasonable response
Unless you sort
Take American society
When you can't do that you're basically telling people to look dangerous given racial stereotypes that are out there
After the Raven media picked up on the story
Started
But how this is racist
Against white people
This last weekend
All the sudden or call center blows up with whoever answers the phone
Spokesman Casey Miller said
Exemption whether it was
Completely stupid idea or was well-intentioned but misguided
One thing we can be sure of is that Alex has no idea what he's talking
He said it was the state of California when in reality it's a small County in Oregon who's already reverse the exempt
As is so often the case
Oz angry misreporting about a story that is no longer even
Betsy's just
Wasting his time
You know it
It's it's really
It's really frustrating
How well the right
Can weaponize
Old man house phone version of Addie.
Like they just
You just
Get of all of these idiots
People are
Fake
The Viagra horse
Sucking ding-dongs just call and yell and that's enough
That's just a nut
Right that's enough
Goddamn Street
Tear gas left and right and it's enough
Just a call
In this
Case
I mean I don't know I don't know Alexa
I don't think I have
Any kind of
Real position
To speak on whether or not that exemption
Is appropriate or not I would like to hear Rhonda side of hearing
From the voice of
The people who would be affected
If that would be an insult
Exemption
To be put in
Something that people would be
Beyonce bro
I'm not entirely sure
I don't know
Amazon
Carrie slays
You know do the whole thing
So from the 23rd
And I've never heard on
Before and I didn't
I couldn't even
Be bothered to look into
Actually turned off
The episode
Real boring
I'm not going to listen to Alex interview somebody who's inspired by Alex
Listen to him interview has some sort of a website
I don't care
I can deal with
The second-hand version of him
A sycophant
Exactly
Buck
We can start with what you said when I watched you back in about 2,000
Very
Pointedly saying
You going to bring back Human Sacrifice the UN Agenda 21
I heard you say back then
I thought that was a little off but I was already kind of
Conspiracy
Surely not
And you know what I did Alex I went and I got at my library
About 40
50 of the elite
Books
Through the mall
And sure enough you were right
Play track down examples of where
Chancellor in ghost in the machine
Is everything is natural
Anything that occurs is Naturals all just natural process
All of history includes human sacrifice
Anabolism
Here is one of the top Royal Society type of lead
Literally saying everything that you said
So this guy's name is Jay Dyer
I don't know anything about him
I don't care
Yeah he sucks
Ghost in the Machine music philosophical text
Analysis of it is basically proof only
Dense material
The book itself is Arthur Kessler's attempt to explore the duality of the human
Prince in the mind and body
Are you being in the same
Unit
Tolkien creature so Advanced incapable of such a
Thoughtless violin
Consequence of nonsensical passion
That's the central question being dealt with in this
Attract
In the book is 1 Section title quoted the ritual of sacrifice
Discusses the history of human history
Human sacrifice
Here's how that section open
Apologist
Too little attention to the earliest ubiquitous manifestations of
The delusionary streak of the human psyche
The institution of human sacrifice
The ritual killing of
Convergence
Gyros
Duplicate
I'm flattered the Gods
It's found at the
The dawn of civilization in every part of the world
It persisted through the height of
Pizzaville ization
Pre-columbian cultures
And it's practically still being practiced in the remote corners of the world
Usual attitude is to dismiss the
The subject is a Sinister curiosity
Superstitions
What does attitude bakes
The question of the universality of the
The phenomenon
Ignores the clues that it provides to be delusional
A man's mental structure and
Its relevance to
To the problems of
The present
In the context of the book
Kessler
Use the phenomenon as
Ruby symptoms
Split between reason
Emotion-based
Which produces
Delusional
Streak running
Through history
According to his
The refusal to accept death
Fear is a natural or is a final phenomenon
Ghost ancestral spirit
It's God's demigod
Angels and devils
Bear became saturated
Invisible presences as in a mental home
Most of them were malevolent
The vengeful or at least capricious
Insatiable in their demand
They had to be worshipped
Bejeweled propriate Adora
Possibly if possible
Hence the insane gesture of Abraham
The ubiquity of human sex
Surprise at the bloody dawn of civilization
The holy Massacre
If continued ever since
If anything this book
Encourages the pursuit of a
Secure
He calls this delusional Street
Tessler believes that this could result in
Human Celtic
Extinction
And that
That was not
I don't believe this guy has read this book
He has an assessment of it reveals
He's not good at assessing
Information
Quick Stop
People really don't understand
Reading is hard
If you're doing
It takes time
You should take
Notes
Engage with
Thought
Don't don't be like oh look at this you said you would sacrifice was all over
Cool
Lisa said something that always makes me laugh about the whole leg
Hear it hear an English class
You speak English
Just cuz you can read words doesn't mean you can read
Like that's just the reality of it and then we have those
Russian literature
And that's the way the people who make fun of us
For having us
I say s*** like this
And you can
Is there end
Compression like is Impressionism
Globalist elitebook yeah yeah
It said
Just basically someone who's like
I can see I see what Alex is doing
Sexually
And if they're in your face are the f****** elitebooks why are they in this dude's local goddamn Library
Everywhere
Larry Wyble
Available
Cuz it's a widely available for people
Lesser Magic
Are Librarians all-in-one
No problem
So there's not much going on here cuz
Again
A bunch
Suggest
Episode
I don't know
View
The sense that I get is like I think that this Jay Dyer guy maybe has a big audience
You don't know
Gavin has a
Pretty broad appeal
I think that he thinks
Veritas is like a
Going to go places
Some of the people that he has on this episode
On the 24th to
Kiipix is going to Broadway
Is is
Israel
And maybe help promote his rally
Cute bed when you go
Clout chasing at the bottom of the barrel
You know dick down in their to-go glad we got Gavin McInnes coming in here
For the Stars
And you just go dig it out of the bottom of the bucket
We got
Who who attacked
James Wood coming on
A little bit of his luster
Sticking out my head
Is it like James
Is the right guy
So we start off
You know we got the narrative about the other NASCAR is in a
Bubba BS Wallace
Rope to pull down the garage
What's a noose
Enough for a cat
Big Hero
I know all the details of the Bubba Wallace
Situation but I'm pretty comfortable
He spends a lot of time on this episode going on about how Wallace is trying to get attention for himself and make a hoax
Hate crime
I'm not particularly concerned with Alex
Because he has a very basic
Facts of the story wrong
What was didn't report
Someone who worked in his garage found it and recorded it
NASCAR
What was himself only found out about it after NASCAR's President Steve
Contacted him to inform him of what if
Confound
Ultimately
Castigation determined that the news have been there since at least 2019 but there was no way
The guy at the garage
To have known
He was part of Wallace's team and they have just been transferred to that garage
The guy who found it checked out the other garages
Before recording on it and found no other garages
Is halved Oracles
That are tied like a noose
Which was part of what caused alarm
When was discovered that this wasn't an attack that targeted
What was said
I think will gladly take a little embarrassment over what the alternative
Could have been
Giving away this unfolded I think that's the correct
Also it's important to recognize the context we're in right now
This all happened in June which is suspicious
Instances of people of color being found hanged in public
These have been ruled suicide
Contrary
Further investigation for cases of needed it for sure
Easy to see how the worlds
Make it through something like a noose
Being found in NASCAR garage
Abused by a black driver
That's not something you can really ignore
Particularly if you are now
NASCAR
Information roll
With someone is checking the other garages
Am I making a big deal out of finding
To NASCAR
NASCAR hears about this
They cannot not enjoy
And then
Chain of events happened exactly
But Alex is trying to turn it into Joe
Exactly and over and over again
What a prick
Yeah cuz they escorted release
A picture of it that I saw today
That's no knot noose
Not something
Speaking
There's one version of
Is that something f***** up
Somebody's really f***** up
We could have been somebody
I don't know it's weird and stuff everywhere
It's still
Take the news.
If you're moving out of the garage and you had that up for your ass out with you
Better than that would have been
Probably the appropriate way for this to be handled
Experience what you're leaving behind
Exact absolute
That would have been better
So Alex
Now he's doing his March
Come Sunday
At the Capitol in Austin
This to be a nationwide movement
Missy bath and everywhere don't wait for orders from headquarters this Sunday your capital
Your city council
Yorktown ECUA one person you maybe Tempe
But you got a real Church you should go have your open-air church service
Even believe a cupboard house at the same place to be
Sunshine
The First Amendment which is Free Speech
Religion
Appreciate
Church service
This Sunday
Capital
A shame on you
I can't wait to
To see the
Relative size
Call Debbie huge
Compared women
All around the globe
70 people in Austin
Maybe
Couple hundred
And then compare that to
Thousand
Black lives matter
Man I can I can imagine the howl
Would be deafening
Beyond all reason but
If I could
I'd have liked A Little Agency
In the IRS
Just like sending people around waiting
For this kind of stuff
With a little signature on a
Losing your tax exempt status
That's right just like waiting moment he's like and that's why we should
That would be faster.
That's never going to happen.
Trump
That would be really interesting of like
You doing this
Would be crossing the line
Retrieve your your church is not a political Act
Exactly
Kind of
Is going to happen
Meetup
Status that would be wild
Don't think it's going to happen but
Play America
Can Inquisition
Alex is really
Desperate
About this masks stuff
Understand
This is getting YouTube
Submit security can come in
I don't agree with his assessment
I give you saying that
But there's an intensity behind
Does the health risk to me
Ada and
Ada violation
Information line 805
Can be fine
$7,000 the first Ada violation
Violation
Attention government agents
Farad
Flyers
Use the law
This is accurate
It's not
When I first saw it on social media 80% chance that Alex
Be tricked by the fake
Exemption cards ever going around
It looks like he has
You should come as no surprise seeing as he had dr. Reba labo
General stubblebine
40 bucks a laminated don't vaccination card
That goes deep
Viral online
Piece of paper
There's no backing of the Department of Justice or the Ada to carrying this Garden
We resulted in
Whatsoever
The card has a website on it
Dftba
God
Dammit this is not a real entity and their website links
That's already been taken down
Is there a website in its original form
It's just yet another right-wing Griff take advantage of you were scared about the
But are also super weird and paranoid
As it turns out there
Another recently-created call Diante mask task force
I guess they thought that their new name sounded better and was more conducive
I'm pulling off this card hoax
Oransi Max Casper
I really
What kind of has a ring to it
Clayton
So on the 23rd at Gavin McInnes
Guy kicked off YouTube
Navigate another gas
Pancake toppings
We got Carpe donktum who just died
Trump's favorite meme maker
Because he dare criticize CNN
Show me giant
Carpe donktum did not
Twitter for daring to criticize CNN
Copyright rules
End up coming
Completely derailing his life
Manipulate couple of toddlers
To create a parody of
Make a CNN report out of it
The video itself shows a black and white toddler recognizing each other and running towards each other to embrace
Diversion that the dog
Put out
This is a CNN report
Terrified toddler runs from racist baby
Suggest that the white baby is
Is a trump supporter
The structure of the video is
Like this is like
CNN's report
Story
What the actual story is
Then yes
Very clever.
My point because all they do is show the real story
You don't need to you're the part where you're lying about
Who cares about the second part
You're missing my point well that's fine
Although I disagree
You're not even paying attention to my point which is why you're going to
Basic level I can see how this could fall under the
Suggested
Heartwarming
Human interest story where these two babies are friends
The impression that the doc was hoping
Recipes
Is directly contradicted by reality
Search fails to really be satire as much as it is just
Race-baiting and white
What propaganda
You swear to
See you if I could I would start a Consulting if anybody was in
I would start at
Consulting firm purely for
Judges
And alike
Like I'll just be there I'll
Just have complete written summaries of lice
Is satire and then we can deal with the first
Because like
You know
Still protected
Exactly what I'm not saying he's a tire
Guantes versiti Center
It is knowing what is and is not satire
Regardless of its quality for you
Use myself
Ultimately whether or not this video is that tire is probably the least of the doc's issues
According to an article in Forbes
The parents of the children are suing
For using altered footage of their children
Creative quotes
Advertisement
Political propaganda
The fact that Twitter and Facebook disabled this fake video within 24 hours of President Trump in his campaign
Coupled with Twitter permanently
Is very strong evidence
We find it
People broke the law by using this video
Is advertisement and political propaganda
It's tough to say which direction this is going to break but even if the lawsuit isn't successful it's important
Is a huge piece of s***
And appearances of the
A video to sports
Don't want their kids being used like that
Makes a lot of sense
Real City
My lawyer said
Carpe donktum
He put out but nobody
I don't know
Just going to go
Yeah this is it this is one of those situations
And where you know
For a fact
That it's wrong
And then you go into the legal C
System in your life
I don't f****** know how they're going to
DeWitt right right
What the ship is going on with their head
Is it
Like how could you not be entitled to some sort of topical
Your f****** like
26 month old child is being used
For purposes that are abhorrent
Without your permission
They cover the video they got permission
Do use it
Yeah yeah
Really hope that there's a hammer coming down on me
If they're the heroes take down as like let's start
Alex
Gets to Carpe donktum a little bit down the road
Kudlow
Who
Used to work
Governor Abbott
Champagne
But now works overnight
Doing stocking
H-E-B grocery
Restore
But doesn't
Work there anymore because
Cuz she refused to wear a mask and got fired
I don't care
This seems to me to be someone who was just there talk s*** about
Governor Abbott and promote the upcoming I don't want to wear a mask March
Rabbits
She's on
And
They talked about this
The situation
Just weird
Bonnie
What do I met before out of second amendment rally
HEB
Asthma
Oh yeah
Pallets
He's known for no workers comp
Closest laborers you can get terrible company
People
Family know my back
Did you recap the story
Broken
Dragging around the mask
I have no idea what's true about the story about this woman being fired for not wearing a mask
I have no idea
If she is someone
Example from wearing a mask
Then I assume that she should have a pretty decent wrongful termination
I'm playing but to go on is the
But you said these things on Infowars
Which isn't really fill me with a lot of coffee
What I find more interest
Thing is how detached from any real semblance of
Suppose Alex is here
He wants to evoke sympathy for cudlipp so he's talking about how H-E-B didn't pay her Workman
But if I'm not with
Position
You shouldn't leave
Employers should be required to pay that kind of compensation at all
Absolutely
Workers enter into a contract of employment aware of risks involved
Forcing an employer to pay for any clumsiness or carelessness of his
Boys that's an undue burden and it's
The breach of the freedom of Association
His professed libertarian ideas should make it believe that Bonnie had no right
To the job that she wasn't doing it to
To the satisfaction of require
She entered into the contract with the employer
And she breached the terms of it by refusing to wear masks
H-E-B with a
Absolutely within their right to fire her
Who's one of the reasons that libertarianism
Pretty tough to defend the real world
I would stand by his principles that he pretends to have
Even if she's very sympathetic
Has a broken foot
The very safety nets that we have to protect someone for being unjustly fired or
A company to pay for on-the-job injury
It only exists because of the work of people Alex
Who called demonic globalist
Communist
Go f*** yourself Alex
You want to live in the world that your enemies create
That's why you live in Austin
Dumb assholes
No it's it's like when my oldest brother
Was on unemployment
This started
Then then shut the fuk up
You never get to speaker
Sherry
Social safety net
Thank God I had this unemployment
Check to help me get through this
And then what
You said thinking well other people
If they go through this
They deserve that same kind of thing and then all the sudden every
Conservative
Is over
Do it for me
Everybody else
The man's Workman comps
And
Protection
You don't believe in any of that stuff Alex
Supposed to
Yeah
Socialist
For me and my wife
And no one else
So
I don't care about their interview about her being fired or anything like that
So I don't have
Any
Prospectors on it outside what's presented
I can't really work
I don't even trust
But she's got an actual broken foot
I don't believe anything
Carpe donktum and it's just like
If they can take me out they can take anybody out
I don't know about that
Top of the list
Stopped out
Spartacus
Whatever.
Just last week
Playing phone tag
Wawa big national news story breaking
Yesterday
Dumb dumb
Video
You got to go
Reproductive health
2nd channel on Pandora
Catalano for rent
Everybody cares real hard this is another one of those things or just feels like Alex is trying to cash in on some sort of
Attention of these people have like a
Flickr there's a little bit of a window where it's like
And even
Carpe donktum says something
To be effective like
It's really nice to talk to you whenever there is chaos
And it feels like yeah
The only
Anytime that you are valuable to Alex Isley
From something
Knowing what's going on artist salary
He somewhat oblivious
Like he's aware so unconsciously of the
The pattern gets hard to tell it could be annoying
You keep doing this
You know hey
The lights the Whirlwind it's always nice to take time out of my day to talk to you
I found
To be a little bit telling whatever the
Intention of it was
So you got it already has
That's great
Discusses this
This is why I quit but I have cuz he just
Interviews Larry Payne
Anthony the guy from the Black Panther
Nope
It's just the 2:30 yelling about Patriots
Patriotism
It's been talking about like Banta
Musically admits why
You censoring everybody on his own websites
Anybody want to channel
That is a known quantity
The Forum on their words like
Section 230
So he understands that if he opened up his platform the way that
Large corporations and large
Online
You would get sued
And
He knows that in order for that to happen
He has to censor content by
Not even allowing people to upload stuff onto there
For his own space
Willfully
About stuff
Solenoid
It's very nice
Who keeps shity videos like the man
I think it's actually kind of a good sign
Because I think it means if people just
Don't give a s***
Conditional breakspot
Anyway that brings us to the end of this
I found these couple days
Yeah
Really bad
Just
Just a
F******
Sahara Desert
Care about any of these dicks come on
Alligator
But this Facebook.
Cognizant guy trying to run
Hey he's going to be testifying in front of Congress
She broke her foot
It just all seems very desperate and it steals
Attention-grabbing abedin with the
The we can't breathe website in March and all this stuff
Just feels like this show
It doesn't always feel like this
This stretch time particularly just really feels like
Impotent weak trolling
Not interesting at all
The first time that they really did
Get together in a writers room and like
Toss around ideas
Said all of the ideas were like
He's got a little heat on and let's bring him on the show
That's it
Yeah and also
How could we be more
Racist
And defensive
Let's just
Brainstorm ways
And let's not check and see if we can't breathe is already the name of something there's no way anyone else could
Should have thought of this
Where your info
Where's the tip of the spear
Holy Ship
I pray for
Metaphorically
You create some Greenery
Before you go
I'd be funny if they were praying for rain
On Monday for another episode but until then
Wave website
I got to get knowledge fight. News
Like I should ask him for
Don't think that would go well
I think that would break
No interfering with
Observations experiment
Lettuce
Right but he should of course he should
I feel like this might be a point where I could break it on Intervention
Do you think this is
Entire campaign
Coward
Why don't you
Yeah
Criticized him for
However
This would be fun
Exactly
Together with the word cuz we would have absolutely no intention
I'm going to say we're not going to do this but keep it on the back burner and paint
Maybe we should have that is like an outrageous patreon goal
Subway
We are not go to bed
Carpe donktum
Which is now available
We're also on Facebook
ITunes
In your area support a bail fund support
Something along those lines were people doing
Ice Cube
Alex
Birthstone colors