Alexandra Thurston color
Like to sit around and drink and beverages
And talk about Alex Jones
Today off the bubbles
Baji
Great
While you're doing that Dan you know a lot about Alex Jones
Andrew and I don't know why
Reality
That's good summation
I don't even makes me want to get drunk
It's not it's not a bad whatever it is
Crystal Light
Oh yeah I can see that
Deteriorate into a Bazaar
Beverage we're here on a mission
We got some exciting enough
Been non-stop telling me about them but unfortunately due to the constraints of this podcast
I don't know what any of them goddamn r
Like oh my God I know
You're it's like it's like
A lot of it is not going to be released right now
We're about to embark on and it
Behind the scenes for the last month or so
INR first episode will drop
Tomorrow
However
We recorded it last weekend
So we're still drinking wine on that episode
I forgot about that
But I want I want to hold off until the investigation got a little bit deeper
And it has
Time is of the essence
Because I think disaster is a
Right around the corner
Didn't like life forever Alex Jones
Alex Jones
I mean
But I'm assuming in-depth as we discussed
Today's episode which is May 25th
Of this year 2017 that was this Thursday
Going to go over all the crazy s*** that happened
Alex Jones
He's lost it
Okay this is f******
Over-the-top you'll see
Out of context
Drop
From someone who ends up being a guest on this episode
His name is Larry Nichols
Tomorrow's episode
But just for fun
Here's an out-of-town
Here's an out-of-context drop something Larry
Nichols said on a 2015 appearance of his
Play where they went to a church
Witches
Future president lady that was trying to run sometimes
Place where they did
I bet you relax and worship
Jason
I love that so much witches
Switches
Even take that away I had to listen to that clip like 10 times cuz I'm like
See thing Hillary Clinton hung out with people from Designing Women
The women from Designing Women will not like Meshach Taylor
Delta Burke
What is a witch
Hillary went to church
Right I believe is
Nicholson
Nichols and care about nomenclature
What is the lady's last name is Bloodworth
I think that's
That's what he's going off of
Open
Also would like to give a shout out to do meter that I
Play don't believe we give a shout out
I just wanted to going up to you
Congratulations
The team
Doubling back
Jordan you get a second policy walk status we will of course invoice you for the 2nd
Of your own volition down
I took Jordan
I don't want to tell you anything
Because I want to watch
You discover
How seriously talk to off this episode is
I'm not going to do any context
Let's just listen to the first clip
Aligned himself with the truth and it's time for you to choose a side your lip
Alex Jones
So powerful
Breath information I've got
Important and I'm also going to be very very careful how I put this out because of sources
Civil War
This country.
We have Seth Rich info we have White House info we have press Corps info we have
Find information on Russia
Much bigger than Watergate
And it's all coming up
I agree after
After this break
Paul Joseph Watson
Katy Perry
Call CarePlus
That's when we go directly to Mary is an idiot
It's three minutes of report
Is it because they're Taylor Swift fans is that what it is unfortunately a shark
Chester bombing
She went on a radio show and said
That's a we should all try and love each other and
About Unity
Borders
Unfortunate phrasing but
The rest of it's real strong stuff
Seems to be acting like a little bit of a cares about Katy Perry
Especially when you start your showed but I've got
Now let my London friend
That was the beginning of
The show every dude we got to get this information ready for you
Sleeping
You claims to wake up at like 5 in the morning he goes on air at 11
6 hours of information
I have no f****** idea
We're going to get to it
We're not going to get to that I've no idea
He does have an elliptical
He talked about that a lot
We should bring up
Everybody is clowning hard on Alex Jones
Because there was a
Before and after picture
Of him the came out of a super male vitality
It made him turn red
Is little bit more Define
Everyone has been
Everyone has been Tweeting or texting that picture to me and I'll f****** sick of it
So here's what I'm going to do
Starting today
Memorial Day
Sorry I'm going to take
None of ours Jones's supplement
And I'm going to create before and after pictures of myself
If I can get better results
Then Alex Jones without his supplements
Well that's the least into Victory I've ever heard on July 13th
Least get a shirtless picture of me
Alright
Anyway let's
We're kind of getting off track
Because
Katy Perry
There's another real
Two more special reports later one of them is from John bowne
It's all about how she is a Satanist
Right
Into Special Report
Part of the Illuminati worship the devil
And then they implicate doesn't worship
Hillary
Katy Perry
Play implicate The Rock
Also
Obviously though
Warlock
Leader of
Kevin on Saturday Night Live sketches instead
Are you into Satan
He was on
Because the Demonic elbow
Night Live
This last week and one of the sketches
He said hail Satan
And that they use as their evidence
Yep
Anyway
Like I said
Get off on Katy Perry because that's
Has been doing
This entire week of just like
Kushner is clearly committed treason on every other network and they're like
What is it with Katy Perry and Ariana Grande Ariana Grande
Alex at this point
Came out
Pacific news about Kushner trying to get the back Channel shift going
Did not exist
Not happen so she doesn't know that
Okay
Cuz there is a in this episode of
The sky is falling
We got to get out in front of
And it has to do it on the horizon and the only man that can save them
Is our propaganda
Jerome corsi
14 years
You got three number one New York Times best selling political books has changed the course of at least one election
The guy stuff up
He does
Of the White House
Last year
It was last week
Connect to last question
They will be shown up as the frauds they are
It's because they're the fake news
Document
Fadeout
You should not be in the Press course your personal friends with
Receive the
Adversarial Prescott
Success in holding
Institutional
Trump's Buddies
How do you feel about dogs
Do you like dogs remember that time we hung out to 22 years ago when I was
Wolf Trap
This is on the record would you like to come to my lake house again
Yeah that's crazy
You do want an adversarial press
But I think
Maybe the ideals
Situation
Is a like
Respectful friendly
Jocular enemies
You know what I don't think it's good for people to be yelling at each other
Things like that
You can have like
You know like that
You got me again
Anger is a Dudley Do-Right cartoon
Roadrunner Wile E coyote
I don't know
I have an iPhone
Large question
So
We're all
Unhappy about
Course eBay
Big time
Against
And that is
What is
Could happen
Yeah my question is
So
Well here's one of the problems
Yes you going to
Use the credibility that comes along with being in the White House Press Corps
In order to boost
Bulshit
But he would have just made up with earlier credibility
Suddenly received by being in the White House
I think it's
I think it's a disappointment you're looking at this wrong
You're looking at this wrong cuz you're using the real world
You need to look at the prism of people who are
Lying to or already believe Infowars
Okay
Those people it's going to it's going to really reinforce
A lot of the lies
Fictitious
Proximity to power
The event proximity
To the official ship
That is going to give him a lot of
Now we wait not the right word
I don't know
I don't see
What one
CA
Positive or negative out of the
Press briefings other than sometimes
Get to laugh at house
Wildly in Copper
10 + 1/10
Sean Spicer
And how close to attractive Sarah Huckabee Sanders
So close if she were attractive
Superman the fact
Alex's
Brick
Really that bad except for the possibility of disruption
But I mean who cares
Be kind of fun you know how when someone walks around with like fake metals and stuff
It's called main like
The Department of Homeland Security
It's a really really undignified
Insulting thing to do
Because you're basically taking away from a minimizing
What soldiers do
I think there is a journalistic version of that there's a stolen
Journalism
Or whatever
That could be applied
To coerce
Because of his
Proximity to the
The actual Pro
Okay so your theory is that
This is going to give him legitimacy in the eyes of the
The people who
Believes
3 million immigrants
It's voted in the last election
But don't necessarily believe all of Infowars
Now they're kind of cuz they're already out in that b******* of
What
3 million immigrants who voted
So if they if
Even that little bit
More of a Monica
Democrat ability
They're much more like
Infowars seriously
Even safe there are people who just
Really engaged
With what Infowars is they aren't really aware of it
Yeah it's the normalization
Two pickups from it
Real journalist
People's never looked into things that all it gives automatic credibility
Absolutely doesn't deserve it
Look
That conversation is is good
I don't
I don't know I think
But you're right there
Not going to be there forever
But
Shih Tzus get
You need to know that I do need to know
This is the
This is the sort of thing
The Jerome corsi
You can pull when he has White House credentials
Locked up
I just understand this
Is very credible
That it was x y and z
Until Tuesday
He told me
4 bombshells
He's never been dramatic like this
He said if they kill me
Listen Alex is very dangerous you need to be very careful as well
There is a war in the country this is not just an information War
It's already hot
That sort of thing would not fly
Nearly as well from a blogger
Let's play
Someone who doesn't have
Supposed official access
Right government inner workings and stuff like that
Bicycle
I will
Have a g
For sure but I think it is absolutely
Part of his
We need to create a propaganda campaign
Corsi
Okay I bet I bet I bet him and Alex collaborated on an alias
Actually say any of that
Very malleable very good at manipulating Alex
Is there an entirely possible he just realized
I'm a freak Alex out exactly what I wanted to do
Possible
He's a better world
Just like
Once a month
I'm just going to make
Alex feel like
You know what
Jerome corsi
Buckeye boring
I am so boring
Alex clearly Like Mike cernovich
So much more than me
You talk about loving Rappaport I have to
Create
What am I going to do okay I'll pretend that I'm deep throat or some s***
Over the weekend again why would he be killed over the weekend
Well because he has clearance
To release this information on Tuesday
Well if you're afraid of dying over the weekend
Your move is to release it early
Not really what you really said what would they kill you
None of this is real information
None of this is real
Tuesday
Back for you and it's Rapaport hiding in the bushes
Oblak
We're going to release our own version of
Clue that's just the Infowars
Rapoport in the bushes
With the Batarang
Nobody is a psychotropic drug
Casinos are a weapon
He actually convinces you to
Yeah Paul Joseph snark
Maybe kill myself
Hooey
The information is as the episode goes on
But I think this is this is a straight
On the part of Jerome corsi
Predict
Delete
That
Come Tuesday
There will be nothing big
And I think
That this is a
Probably a PR stunt
Exactly
People said about December 12th
That's exactly what they said
Sold a lot of calendars
And you know
World ended
That's all I got was just the beginning of the rise of fascism in Ark
We're certainly living in a much worse place five years later
When did gamergate
Start cuz I don't remember 12
Anyway
December 21st
This next clip
Alex
First
Very long string goes almost the entire episode
Steven
What he's about to tell you
Yes he's not want to get to
You and Alex are
In common broadcast wise
It's still frustrating for you to be like
All he does is talk about what's coming in the future I'm sitting here staring at
Tell me what's going on it's just the structure of how these episodes have to be laid out
OK Google
Samurai
Anyway here's Alex playing the game that he and I love
Play
I had about 20 minute conversation with him this morning driving into work
Trouble focusing all the other news
Important
Extremely Illustrated
Alarm
Owen Shroyer had some similar info
Confirm
That this whole thing stinks to high heaven
Let's just say they got their ducks in a row before they kill Seth rich
F*** you
Where are you get to all that about amor
Part of what the news with Jerome corsi is going to break his that's one of the big things
What it's about
God dammit
And
Towels
What the big news is
I know originated on 4chan
Really
Discredited already it's really undignified
I think this is a desperation move
Which we'll get to in a little bit
You so desperate
Text was fairly interesting
What you have to do with Alex Jones is ranked
Now listen here's the thing whatever you're listening to Alex Jones you kind of have to read between the lines a little bit
The tone of this episode is
This weekend
We have big news I'm going to get to some of it
But the rest of it I'm not cleared to give
Intel
You know Tuesday
Of course he dies
I know who did it
We all know if
It's very desperate
It's very immediate
It's very
Okay and when you hear stuff like that
It's not because
That's the truth
It's because something else is going on
Behind the scenes
That is making Alex
Freak
F*** out
Okay I think I know what it is
So if
They're doing it for like this surprise reveal on
On Tuesday
He's building up this
1D
Alex
He's going to kill
That's why I said it might be in the bush
We need
If corsi dies over the weekend
We know Alex.
That's the first thing we know
And also that just that just means he's setting it up for the counter-narrative
Something that
Going to go down onto
Right now
No
Why are we why are we playing this this b******* game of he
He's going to die over the weekend
Because it's
It's severe
That's why
It's shocking
It's expensive going to get a lot of
Drive traffic
And there's a reason he needs to do that
But I'm going to get to
Part of it
I think I know what
I think I might have sucked out
What we're talking about
You know you probably don't have it brings everything into Focus
YouTube
Get into the information that he has
To give out at this point
Seth rich
But before he gets to the information
He has to get on
Ridiculously long
Tangent of a bunch of nonsense
Are you pretty
Really trying to take the piss out of Katy Perry
He really just wants to complain about
Stars
Taylor's oldest
He wants to complain about
Some Muslims that were demonstrating in London there have been some Muslims for peace marches
There have been some anti islamophobia
Gatherings
Demonstration
All coming together
Filled with hope and
Horrifying
Decided to go
There's a video and there's a picture of the lady who's wearing a shirt that says love
The letters of Love are made up of weapon
So like the
Always a grenade
It's a little bit ambiguous
It's very strange
There should be like an explanation for them for what that shirt is
Guns are love is a I'm looking at it
My artistic
Explanation
It would be it's a juxtaposition of
These tools of killing
Making up the word love
I think
My interpretation would be exposed to shock you into realizing
That's why I don't know I can't say
T-shirt is
Faces of everybody at Infowars
Is organized
No spelling truth
But I don't want to defend this ladies shirt I have no idea with the intention of it
Places you can make
Is really mad about it
But we have the video of Muslim women wearing shirts
Cuz I didn't do it
Extremely arrogant
When the left get some crazy white guy
Halloween costumes with hoods
Muslims relf
It is
Just just regular like Muslim Garba is Halloween costumes
Is insulting other cultures yet
Absolute
Tomorrow's episode of our show is going to go
The exact day
The Charleston shooting which was actually an accident
That we ended up covering that
Tomorrow I would recommend bring up dylann roof
Listen to his words
Is that all white people for the attack
Blaming gone owner
Hours for it
The arguments that people were having fun
Blaming guns
And white
They were saying that this is part of
Our culture.
Part of the racism that underlies a lot of people
It is systemic
It's not all white people's fault
But white people are behooved to look at these things and these beliefs
It's sometimes were unaware that we carry
That was a conversation that happened
And we've listed Lisa
What's Italy say
But if you're still part of the
System that
Props this
Anything up still maintains an environment that
. only like allows it but in fact
Nurture
Write Community which Alex Jones
Is absolutely a part of the storm front the Nazi gold
Two people were f****** murdered their throat
By this alright bulshit f*****
This white supremacist
Who is just
Like it's stuffed
They are making happy
They are absolutely
Part of the system that nurtures this idea
And a big part of that is the mentality that he expressed in that last
What are you saying like
These Muslim men won't apologize for
You realize in the next Wednesday exact next sentence you're saying that you're mad
Expect expect
Patrol Muslim culture
You were so offended
By the idea of having to a beat like
White
What do they have to be made to feel bad
Adjusting are capable of doing the 121 map
It literally 1 / 1
It's 1 * 1
Is 1 + 1
Is the easiest map to do and because they're brown
He is f****** unwilling to do it
And it's insanity
We call it Fox News geometry
One sometimes does not equal one with feeding hello how you doing
This next clip
Anyway this next clip
Alright have
More to do with Ariana Grande
MN
Relationship
Islam
The globalist
Muslim
Working with
Despite all of that
She still won't criticize Orthodox Islam or suicide bombers because that's not the in thing to do
Left
Prop up Islam and must say it's loving and peaceful and helpful incompatible because it's the shadow
Army of the West
Open free Society
Facebook
A friend
Alphys the alpha cancer
You just screamed over the most scary part he said at the end
We won't do anything about exam
Specifically
What are you doing are you going to Outlaws there free speech
The thing that
You say people are trying to do to you which
I don't think anyone is
What are you
The whole thing is just b*******
You don't believe spending suicide
Snowing
Not the last
You can empathize with a suicide bomb
Very much
Something good
We should do if you want to know why
Suicide bombing
Oh wait
Your suicide bombing because you have no f****** hoe
Because everybody's brought you into this dangerous and destructive
F****** help
Send you feel like you're marginalized don't feel like nobody
Cares about
Extremist groups
Your family isn't there for you
So
Projective family ideology
Auntie B's
People and they
State utilize that
The force
Is that maybe otherwise you wouldn't do
I don't think
Everybody
Relate that to
Any kind of
White
Crystal River
Movement even if it was male
I think
I had a flash
Like
There's a decent chance that Alex can't wrestle
With that a
Puppy for people situations
Forget them into extremism
Psychopath
Because no
Because strategically would be against
Cuz you would have to vent recognized but he does some of that himself
Like a lot of the people that follow him
AR
The same sort of marginalized Folk
And all he does
Is filled our heads
With lies
Narrative
That if they repeat other people
Disconnect them even
In further
Cuz like if you and I were just
Casual friend
And I came up
And I started spouting
We wouldn't be friends
No that would make a
Very hard to connect with
Quote-unquote normal people
Write as normal as you and I are
It would just not totally isolated people you only bring them more into the full days
You're the only person
Sweeping pronouncements on your show about how we're the smart people everyone else is dumb
Maybe he doesn't use family so much
Family
Still reinforces a lot of that
It's not quite as much but yes
Yeah I think he I think he would have to wrestle with the fact that he does that to
It is absolutely perfect
Text for him to set him
Goodguys verse
Yeah
To inspire those kind of
Us vs
Does that mentalities and Berry parfait
Boogeyman because they are your
You know Black Mirror
Basically what I want to know is do you think that
Muslims are the shadow Army
For the globalist
I don't know are they
Go with a big no on that one
Yeah we're going to learn that Muslims are killing millions of Muslims every year
Is that a shadow Army for the globalist
Alex is going to get to this big
Continue
Response by the Muslims everywhere
Just another tease
Tens of people are celebrating with a lot of times they were peaceful demonstrations
Nutella
That you can see pictures up of like
Muslims
Four-piece most Muslims love Manchester March
Stuff like that
Basically the exact opposite of what he is
What do you think
Just the entire idea is
Once again
Reaction to apologize for
Basically their religion
Yeah what else what else
Could you possibly be responding
If you have to
You have a piece
You don't seem after this
Portland
Yeah you don't see white people marching in Portland going like
Hey by the way we're sorry
By the way we still believe in love
We still believe in
Not your enemy
You don't have to
That that white privilege that is
Is part of the Vista
Fake news
Fair enough
I didn't commit that crime so I'm not on the hook for it
Every Muslim is on the hook for it
2/2 people's throats
He's just
You must be compatible
Little bit
Wild
Stop
People that posted a bunch of his like Facebook posts and like Message Board stuff
You just have no coherent philosophy other than like being really
He's a lunatic who got a chance
To be a f******
Yeah
Pictures of him like Ezekiel speech rally
Boy
We're in.
Ireland part of the IRA
That is a guy who is a f***
Insane purse
Person just begun
He's a gun waiting to be fire crazy really to fit in with any of the militias
Stop.
Anyways
Alex's had a revelation
He said he's a big breakthrough
Before he gets to the real news that may or may not be responsible for Jerome corsi
To the real news that may or may not be
Jerome corsi
He's going to lay it out for you
Attorney general he was a senator in pull out and didn't fill out all the
Forum
About
The article it says u.s. senators are exempt from
Because they
Meet with foreign dignitaries as part of their jobs
No
So you're getting the premise there is that they're just re-releasing old stories
Don't know how to read
Because
This story about sessions that came out recently is different
Then the last time
Because he lied
And open
Session
In Congress
Add with kids
Russian ambassador
This time
It's because you lied on his background check for
About the meeting
Woody hat
Cuz Alex brings up
That
At the bottom of the article
Doesn't have to fill this out
Because he's a senator and Bob
Transition team
It's not
Right it's that
Exactly the thing the Attorney General
I consulted with those familiar with the process
And was instructed not to list meetings with foreign dignitaries and their staff
Connected with his Senate activities
That's the piece of it that Alex is not taking it
Consideration
Exactly what you said
Zenit activities
Cool
You don't have to disclose those meat
They should be on your itinerary
Should be
That sort of thing
These meetings
In question
Art related to Senator activities
They are related to Trump transition team stuff Trump campaign stop
And the fact
A really big deal
So then you get to like all the others
Looks like there has been like
Three or four cycles of Mike Flynn news
But they're all different
They're all new development in the same
Building crisis
In the same way with Kushner
New Revelations about Kushner
But they're very different stories
And Alex just
Is there
Please take something
Again
It's like a murder investigation
They're like
We found another
Or
Before this it's over come on we got one I'm investigating you for
Crime write a murder
It's like a week later I found another body that you killed
Jordans
Old news
Yeah
I think it's
Visit was indicative of Alex's inability to understand what's going on in the world
I can clip about his
Like understanding of
The Civil War
Legitimately think that should be an entire episode
I can't believe that his understanding of the Civil War is even related to either size understand
Everyday was a war over
I don't understand what I've posted it up on knowledge fight.com
But I'll give you the brief version
It was about to Harris
What is this music ever us war was about tariffs probably
The recurring cycle of Lies the media does
I think you have no memory
Illegal
Listen to us
That's all it means
Like a Transformer you should go by night
North Korea
Conversation with the president of the Philippines
Conversation truck was on the news about the Armada and the submarines
Extra supplement
6 months before
And as soon as I see it
If you go back and look actually what was in the news on April 25th
About
The aircraft carrier
Where's that we're going
Actually it's
Also also right around the same time as Michigan
Talked in South Korea
BBC article from around that time
Right
.
4 days later on April 29th
President-trump
Phone call
With president duterte
From
My version better
Sounds good
Present
How to phone call
Yes I am the only reason we know everything that happened in that phone call is because just the other day
A Philippine confidential copy got leaked
Course and if you look at the script from the Filipino side
Where you at
Is the Trump
Very strongly congratulate
President
With the drug crisis in the Philippines
Which if you don't know
Since last year's of June of last year
Close at 7,000 people
Have been extra judicially killed
America because of drug offenses
The police claim or not
Or not
There's a lot of people who were killed
Adidas
Nothing to do with drugs
You don't kill 7,000 people and get them all
Especially if your vigilante crew in which case
I would say they've murdered more people for nothing than they have her
Also recently president
A state of emergency
I can't remember the name of the region of the Philippines
But he enacted indefinite martial law
That's been graduated
But he
Trump is congratulating him on how he's dealing with drugs
Which is very bad
Very bad
And then in the same conversation
The aircraft carriers
We're just cost in the news
And
Submarine
Very ceremoniously
Part of like
Yearly
Exercises
Just for formulaic every year routine exercises
Dockton South Korea nuclear submarine
Off the coast
North Korea
That is a big deal
It's not that like
4 days after
All this stuff with public
Some of the stuff
Winstead in publication
Publicly
He's telling a
Murderous dictator
Norwegian
There are more publicly known
Roundabout where they are
That's not
A small deal
He doesn't know
That people on the other
Cider recording him too
Right
Like like the Russians
That is
Hopefully
Kushner
What
Executed
Voorhees
I don't literally
Exist other than
To give confidential in
Exactly
Solutely committed absolutely broke
No quite
But no question
So he just had no idea that
The Russian Czar be like
Yeah we better we better keep these record
Yeah I mean it's the same conversation that Sally Yates had
It's the same thing that she said the house intelligence committee about Flynn
He's like
If you
Have conversations like that with the Russian
They are going to record it
Are there no they know that you've lied about them and now they have leverage over you
Brennan said in his testimony
That the road to
Treason is often
Undertaken unwitting
The treason
And they don't realize that's where they're going
And by the time they wise
It's either too late
Or there's mail or they're being threatened
Brett
He looks like
I mean Christmas probably guilty of
Absolutely
The best we can say is
It started off naive
That's the best possibility
Turn it off
The best-case
But I fucken do believe that
Bridgeway
You should be
JAIL View
Access stricken
Unbelievable
If you could still access documents
Right now when you start to put it into perspective to like all the stuff
What's been going on
The leaking
The fact that those two
Secure document rooms
I'm not saying that they're related
But when you look at all of these things that are going on
If any of them are related
We have one of the big
Issues
In our government
Sister ever
It could be a situation where
Completely confidential information
And taken
And given to Russian
And what would
The reason
Could only be undermined
F****** country
Norberto
For the Russians let's fuk up NATO
Money
Everybody wants money
If you can blackmail the United States government God you can make so much money
Are you kidding me how much money can you make if you can blackmail.
President when you add into that Trump speech to Nato
Adding that he refused
Necessarily support Article 5 commitment
Do everyone defend
You add into that him
Saying that he's not sure about Russian sanctions
So you thinking about them
The fact that
He goes and he lectures these foreign leaders they need to give more
Tomato for defense
Not how
Get all of our money back
What are you talkin about to the point where foreign leaders were laughing at
He's giving the speech
People like whispering to each other like
Embarrassing
Yeah that Parts embarrassing
All the other stuff
Really
I'm sick and tired of
Like extremism in the Russian front
You mean like
Who are out there and they're like
I've been guilty of this
I've been guilty of falling into
This being fooled by
A little bit
But
Where everyone's
He's a Russian agent
Right Foot the
Facts on the ground
How much
Too much
Our President should be put in jail
So the only the only option the only move for him then
Is
If I was if I was strategizing how he's going to
Throughout the Republican Party
Albuquerque
And then Pence
Spartans drum
That's the way that they have to go
You know it's got to be like
Ump you get impeached
Next person in line
Pardons you
Until you get to I don't know the secretary
I don't fucken know I don't nothing's good
Right so that gives you
We gave you we gave you Trump hazard
We pardon Trump which keeps
The people on the alt right
Hopefully from
Burning
If what should happen
Open happens
Which is
Trump
Kushner possessions
All of these guys wind up in
Prison
4life metaphor
Yeah like that's what should happen
If that happens
There will be an actual armed insurrection
From the alt-right most likely because the alt-right places like
Infowars Like Mike cernovich
These people have already built up a
Defense for that they already have a narrative in place
The globalist
Or trying to get Trump out
And when they do get Trump out hold the special election
It's going to be overseen by National Security and it's just going to be
Facade
And then they're going to start destroying everything like they plan to do when Hillary got in
Even the first
Step of their made-up plan the globalist
Happens
I'm in Tempe
They're going to see that as evidence of the third step is
4th step is coming
Among
Launch
AR
Part of that
Who in the National Guard
Is part of that these guys actually get
And all of this s***
Together like
There's a real chance that if what should happen
It's almost like the best possible outcome
Is
Let Trump
Coast out
Term which is an awful out
The s*** out of
Hope the Congress flips
In 28
Not let anything go through
Just let it turn into a
Contentious
Political battle
Between the two
Contain
A lot of aggression cuz I don't want to be arguing about the issues that are going on
The fight between the house and the president
I'm at like that necessarily have to
Into the streets
Yeah that's a Sara Lee
In the meantime in the background
How far until June
Conservice
Everybody because
I mean
Stupid f****** outcome
Al Stewart
If you start having them communicate about housing
The intelligence service
This is our wedding
People
Again
Yeah I mean there's no
This is going to
Explode like this is a powder keg
Flow Dano
Has any idea how it's going
Nope
But you know what
The good news is if you're scared
That's fine
I want you to know that Alex Alex is about to get to that big nose
Bombshell
Somebody's at the door
Disgusted by the moon
Islam
That's from
Yeah yeah
Wow thanks for thanks for getting the news Alex
I love his game
I'll tell you right now I just want to let you know
That Hollywood wants to take your kids
Are pedophiles Merc durka durka.
Ariana Grande saying that she hates
She had like a mental breakdown a while.
I don't I don't particularly I don't particularly care to litigate
Personal lives
Social
Disgraces info paused
Pop stars who have been famous events
Before they were really adults
Nobody
Say thank note individually on a grander scale like
I can't imagine how much
F***** up stuff I would have said if I was famous it
Or whatever
I said really f***** up
Right right
Popstar
Sing all the s*** that I imagined before your brain
If you were in the public eye and people were
You do demanding things of you and you had a rigorous schedule of performance
Stuff like that it would be incredibly
And ask for everything they say
Celebrities
When they
It's not really a fair system for anybody
Attention to what they say
Celebrities
Yeah
If you are Alex
Text Jones
And you're like
Batman
I'm going to get to this huge important information
But first
Yeah
It really takes away from your legitimate
Teen Vogue spends less time on what Katy Perry says
Add more time on the downfall of America
Maybe you're behind Alex maybe you're the one who's not
Because it's
Very
Absurd
Yes you did
Did he bring back the new information with him
I'm so angry right now
Tomorrow
I just can't believe
Because I have a memory
These people are evil and Evil
He's been with over the weekend on the globalists for 20 years
Still surprised
You know what I just came to a revelation about the globalist
I've been doing this 20 years
You can go back through my entire catalog never said this before
Revelation
Never said this before in 20 years
They know they're evil
This eugenicist group technocrats you want to destroy the world and it
Godzilla
The Hideout in their armored redoubt
They have no idea
Yeah
That's a perfect revelation
Yes
Revelation
The Google thing is I've started to realize when he talks about how people have no memories what he's really
Is people don't see the world in this
Flawed prism the way I do
That's really what he saying
He's not saying that he remembers
Because obviously.
He remembers his cues and his fake stories
And stuff like that that we describe and stuff like that
He don't really
He's not talking about memory
He's talking about
His flawed Conti
Rudy's.
Because
Memory memes
Why is he thinking
His his his
I remember in 20
15 what I said and I forgot to take that recording down and so that I remember in 2017
Complete opposite of that or even just go back to that side
Do you know the nuclear sub that was in the news
I remember that no you remember your bizarre
Rotation of
You don't
You have
A flawed narrative
And you're pissed
But other people are in on
Okay
He's mad that other people have memories of reality
Not his universe
That's very fast
Very fast
Big well because his
I mean I guess
I think I
I think what I would
See it as is
When you say memory
I think you talking about
I think that's really what he
It's like a computer on a higher
He's got more
Got more of that he's talking about memory loss
Power interesting that's possible way that my brain process
People don't have that many
People don't have that ability
Do I think he knows what Ram is
No I think that's an interesting Theory I disagree
I think you should know the definition of the word before I can give him
Credit for
Call I was calling
Yeah ask him what he thinks memory is
Anyway
Do you realize that the globalist evil
He just got
These people are evil and Evil
Controller psyop
But the actual newspaper reporters
Liberals are liars
And they consciously
So I've looked into this I looked into the David Gruber stuff
Also
If you were using that voice
I would
I probably think
Yeah
Night of analysis maca
Uber is apparently
Who helped work on Obamacare
Okay
I have made a couple of very unfortunate public statements
That are easy to misinterpret
The problem is people are stupid
He should not have said that that is exactly what Alex says
All day ever
But the thing is the context of what he's talking about is that Obamacare would not be able to
If they framed things
I don't know it's not what Alex says though
It's it's it's not like hey we fooled everyone it's more like
Thankfully people
Just look for buzzwords
Right because we were able to get tax out of there
As a legitimate part with the bill was
We were able to move forward.
Right cuz if they have
Obamacare
Tax
Everybody
Would have been like America no more taxes
Videos about how sometimes government can't work with full transparency
And it was again another unfortunate
He was talking about again
The same thing
It's just sort of
I mean
Don't say that
Yeah don't don't say it like that
Say it's an unspoken thing that I think everybody in America kind of believes or it's like
Or just from the pool
Right if you look at polls and how they do that research
The way you
Rephrase the question
Greatly influences the way people
Totally
Trying to say there is
If we operate
With full trance
Parisienne
Answer every question
People are going to wind up seeing what
They want to see
And react
Accordingly that's a big part of what is playing
Is
Put what in
We think is important and what we think is the narrative out there
That will allow us
To operate
People's best
Yeah
Like Obamacare
All of its faults
Is in people's best
Totally
Compare it to what the GOP is doing right now
Exactly
Of course that's what he's trying to say
Yeah
You however
I have a memory
Then
You will look at that
I like the Deep state
Muslim
Steps
What's the weather
And I got all the faculty
Listen to Christ
Olive
They're so
Attacks a guy with a cell phone
What
Bulshit
Security folks try to assault
Baskets that memo
But
So the thing with Corey Lewandowski just because this will be quick
There's a video that you can watch
Of the
Assault that happened
The lady who got assaulted was walking next to Trump
And they were having a conversation
I've been from behind Trump
You can see Corey Lewandowski
Grab her and pull her
Not that she put her arm on him he pulled away
Absolute
Horseshit there's video of video evidence coming from behind and
Obviously grabbing
Or anything like that
He pulled her
L mean
Like
It's not insulting the same way that like
Chickenshit out of somebody isn't assault
But it's still real
No so now onto the issue of the amount a situation
Which is
It's a Fox news reporter says that I'm going to run
Trucking news
Foxnews.com
Keith and I arrived early to set up for the energy
Rustic play
Gen4 came into the room
We exchanged pleasantries and made small talk about restaurants
Bozeman
During that conversation has been Jacobs of the Guardian
Walked into the room with a voice
Recorder
Response to the newly released Congressional budget office report on the American Healthcare Act
Gianforte
You would get to him later
Jacob's persisted with his quest
Jennifer told him to talk to his press kaishain scam
At that point gianforte
With both hands
And slammed him into the ground behind
Faith Keith and I watched in disbelief as being Fort then began punching the reporter
Sgtreport moved on top of Jacob
He began yelling something to the effect of I'm sick and tired of it
Jacob scramble to his knees and said something about his glasses being broken
Deactivate Keith in myself for our name
In shock we did not answer
Jacob said that he wanted the police called
And what to leave
Gianforte looked at the three of us and repeatedly Apollo
At that point I told him in Scanlon who is now present
That we needed a Moana
Samantha
To be clear at no point did any of us who witness this assault see Jacob show any form
A physical aggression
Towards gianforte
Who left the area after giving statements the local sheriff
So
That's what happened
Based on
Fox News
Who witnessed the attack
And they're still not going to believe it
Audio
Self-defense
Propaganda Outlet
Is not going to put up
There's audio matches that
Description of the events
But these people are scums
Their cattle
You up
Whenever they're like now
What is the time
F******.
I can't
People haven't
Just depressed
How do you not f***
King pick that up
If you're part of the press and it doesn't matter if you're the conservative alt right
Press or whatever
You don't want this president
You don't want to be in Muslim
Because eventually
You're not going to be in power
Empower maybe people will want to ban you
Well it's how do you not f****** get the
People don't understand like the idea of supervenience
Supervenes on
These attacks
Against journalists
Inspect their journalist
Yeah that's that's what's behind it
Reporters that are being attacked
It is now okay to beat up journalist
Journalist
Yeah
It's not about the money part of it although it is
It's been a religion is
Example of being targeted
Is a really really dangerous president
Because it doesn't just apply to once
Situation we would have the same
If it was all Buddhist
Or speak
Or even or even super Conservative Christian
That wouldn't be okay no we would be against that in the same way that we met
Clear on like the third episode
First episode of the show
But if Alex Jones ever really was being victimized
For free speech issues
We would be forced to defend him
I would
Hundred percent wood
If he was being oppressed
Based on Free Speech.
Enemies
Ever B
Baytown free speech.
Which to this day
He has not yet no
He has been depressed because he's a f******
Wow
Depression at that point so we've never called for him to be taken off the air
There was never called for him to be
Punished
F****** idiot
In stable condition in order of me
I'm going to
To just say f*** it
Let's let Alex get to the picnic
Easy listening
He did this exact same thing like a
Week ago when he was like
He just kept using it throughout the entire show
Never said what the news was but did the exact same Gamers like
This is Dolphus clear any waited until Mike cernovich came on
Mike cernovich gave some piece of
Both big news
Put the f****** stupid game episode
I'm not just saying this
To keep you here
What you doing why would you say it
It works it works
So
Well
I don't know
You just jostled it
He doesn't
I'm hungry I have to do that
When I come back.
Thank you all for your support with the Memorial Day special
David personal Danger
That ice I still didn't expect it to turn into a sales pitch I know that's what it all
So I actually next life is titled Alex's endangered
Doing
But like I love now at this point in the show
We're spinning plates
Cuz now we got the memo
Yeah,
If it was just a big
But now he's got two things you got to not do
I don't remember.
Break
Before we do that
Guys I just want to let you know that
Only way I can thank you
Is why
You buying
Iodine
I don't know what I don't know Bertha's next clip
Got to be good
Titled Alex's freaked out in all caps
Alex Jones
Nick has been there like 5 years for years you never come in at Savannah you alright
Devil worshippers
They're going Muslims
Somebody else
Watch out
Because
Muslims kill millions of their own each year
That's what he saying
Alright
But you're just going to accept that
What are you going to say just like
Hey can we get can we get a number on that
Just a number just Millions every year
I mean you're not a journalist or anyting makes no sense
3 million illegal in
It's just not
It's just not possible
No but if you're if you're talking about like
Collateral damages of wars and stuff
You know where
Facilitating and stuff like that
4 year
Five natural causes
Oh
To include that in there too
All the people who died.
Yeah then you got it
And then throwing some more people who died they were probably secret Muslim so that counts to do know that
I don't know
I don't want
Of
Is s***
Here's the deal
Aliquot
Sick break
From a lot of this stuff
Doesn't want to get to the big news yet
How many hours are we in
Most of the ships
You just have some thoughts about gender
Thoughts about how toxic masculinity
I really think Alex thanks but this isn't Ellen
I think he thinks it's
It borders on
Scholarly
It's matinee
Against corrupt man
And the reason we're in this position
Call Davon
Will roll over in a second
I couldn't tell and I'm still not sure if or cock
Yeah I think so too the first.
What
Who doesn't roll over when they got a cock in their face
Turn the other cheek
You take him outside telling the cash that check their p****
That's something
It's feel your hands
Mouth writing checks your body can't cash
You've already established that is a great
He sounded more like he was being robbed
Also because they're not real man and I'm sick of man not being man I'm tired of it
Of course it when men don't act like men women
And then
Play Kate and lower the drawbridge for the threatening group they see across the river
Women don't have men around they will roll over to outside invading Force
As a Stockholm syndrome survival mechanism
So there are no men
That's why I'm telling me to stop being shown
And I'm going to be showing it that that
Women roll over when they know you already
Stop right there stop being men
Right that's at 1
End
But they're Faking It
Outside forces come in
Who are real man
Women will revert to their
Feminine weakness
And I roll over
Because Western men are too busy being
Or whatever
It's this narrative is
First of all it doesn't take into account all the matrilineal societies that it exists overtime
Doesn't take into account like
Anything other than his idea of what
Should be
That no no no no
It's not even that
There's but I think the driving forces
He does not want to
I think even
Like I loved
Determine you dropped on recent episode week
I think he knows that this news is weak to
Rescue people
And to sort of solidify his base
Because
Of what I'm going to
Explain in a minute
But before we get to bed
Gendered
Definition of Whatta Man
So damaged
To just
That is such a huge part of why Humanities a pile of garbage
Is the fact that
Communities online
Especially men but you don't like that in real mayonnaise
Between the age of 14 and 21 are the most dangerous and destructive force
Humanity is
Undoubtedly
They are the cause of
And Alex is there
He's still that age but
What would I even call it like he's this he's this
Town drunk
That's that's to me what he is he
He's the town drunk
You go to at a bar and you're underage
Can you go there in the town drunk starts dropping wisdom it's all wrong
He knows what
I don't like you
But then here's the twist
Like maybe 5 minutes
He pulled up in his coat and he's got pills
That weird face kills the most
Look up the show afloat
Yeah
Gypsies
Look Alex is going to get too big
Let's just do it
That was a short clip
Haven't gotten into those yet still not getting it back
You can go to the big nose right
We can't keep them both
Every Christian every conservative is responsible
Six months of bitching and moaning and screaming
Blah blah blah
Is very rare in this country
Islam
Dylann roof
So just for fun
I went to Stormfront
Today
Bored and it noon there were 1871 active users online
At noon
There are 324000
314 registered members of the storm front
Racist
White nationalist soror
A lot of people a lot of people who buy into that ideology wouldn't register because they know like now
Hang on the list is probably at least double that who frequent the
So I mean
Sure
A billion and a half dylann roof
But there aren't a billion and a half radical Muslims either
Dumbass
Like
600,000 is a very conservative estimate for people who buy into basically what is neo-Nazi
Geology today
Yep
Way too many
That's a huge
Literally
An army of Nazis
In the United States
Believable
Jesus Christ ignore that
Let's also ignore that multiple stabbing
In Portland
That was
Because a guy defended
Some women against racist
Yelling
Yeah
And you know what if it was a right-winger who did it it would be a big story
But it's still a big story
You know what I mean like
He's trying to say that like no one
Covering are they aren't staying it was
Like a Muslim who did it
That's not
True
Not even close
His version of reality is that no one talking about that
People are talking
Everybody
Brought that up
They're just not focusing on it and the way he wants them
Yeah he wants them to focus in on like
The fact it's the religion
He wants them to
She say
It is not
The guy
It is the religion
That killed all these
He wants everything like this to be the last
Straw everyone wakes up
It was Muslims all along
Not
That's not real
But not
True to reality
I know we're not going to do that
No one's going to do that
Except for those 300,000 registered users
Yep they're definitely going to do that also when I went to Stormfront accidentally
I started looking around
Yeah there's a horse
Really funny
Oh my God
It's like what is a white nationalist lady wanting to man
Wait is it like a dating advice
It's not like a dating website like oh no
Digiboard post whatever
Discussion topics they want
And the only one I read was what is a white National
Lady w
Hilarious
And he has all this like you know what I'm trying build up my morale to
The point where I think that I am far more
Moral and upright
Anybody in this even in the south
Even in my in my conservative Community I'm still above them but
But I realize
That women want
The guy whose heart
It's always
Get back to work on building up my hardness
Whatever
Supposed to do
Looking for
And then bunch of dudes pylons like
Hey sounds like you're trying to mold yourself into what women want and no woman like that
It's it was hilarious
What
So many of them seem to have that
That
That idea of like
There's a secret
If if I am in a situation
All the men around me are reinforcing my
Shared belief
Yeah then of course you would say
All the women out there
Are doing exactly the
So you think in your small Stormfront
Almond
Everyone else is dumb
Everybody else's
No better man
Through the race mixing allies
Society gives up
So then you have to assume that there is that equal and opposite
To your little group there and you're trying to
You figure out that
And you can't
4-H
Second
Imagine that women have AJ
It seems like like what
Here whenever I hear that is
Women are
Puzzle box
Litter robot
Right
For every single woman and it works
Every
Singleton there's a magic
No there's no
Women have their own agency in our their own
Individual
Likes and dislikes
There are white nationalist women
And they will f*** you
Yeah just got to be white nationalist
Here's how you find
Probably you
Let me change that
You know what white nationalist women want
Black dudes
Buying into the whole narrative now
It's always talks about
Get a trump Pence 2020 shirt
Get a Maga hat
And you'll meet like-minded people
He's not wrong
No he's not
That is how you mean
If you're a weirdo
Get Infowars shirts
And you wear it out in public a lot of people are going to ignore you
A lot of people are going to laugh at you
But then there's a small group
Who are going to respond
You will find like-minded people
You just found Alex
Way better selfish for that
Trump
And you'll get laid get laid from a weirdo
Will get laid by someone just as weird as you
It's caused this to happen
What does the fox say
I will cherish
2uz Terror attacks to take our liberties
Is not under
Do I just love that going out to break
I'm Alex Jones
What big
Good
Stomach ulcer
This memo he's been teasing and playing with on the mic
For this entire episode was on it
One of them was
Hey babe
Assistance
Weird very weird
Hey
You been preparing all weekend
Not because
Pretty distant
Isaac Neko
Also could be Nico from The Velvet Underground
Koneko
Bright
Misquoting
The thing that I
The things that
I think he really does believe
That so
So the argument for it is the right wing spot
Terrorism
Is the right one
That's the way it is
Because of the way that they are inflamed
The boy
Murder
The murder large groups
The more likely you are to
Create
Terrorist I'm at Democrats when they say that it's just
Totally
Fanning those flames of Muslim hating of
Doing all of this stuff
Is only going to create equal and opposite reaction on the other side
Connect to him when he hears
It's the right
He thinks
That they're saying
The right
Right
They're saying is he thinks
That attacks
Actually right wing
People
Committing
Right-wing people are committing terrorist
Pensacola
Possible that you saying that
Say it possible I don't know
Weird
What do you say false
Flags
False flag
He believes that
Because he can't imagine
The idea of something being a
Structural
To being a literal understand complex systems
Leasing false-flag he means
Not that
The right
Is involved necessarily but it's the globalist
Who have done this
They goaded this person into doing it
Or the Patsy or something like that
In order to try
And Spark
Race War I don't know
Dude
Have a goddamn big news
He does but first you have to explain that Jerome corsi has set up a Deadman
Like if you're out there and you're listening to Infowars on Thursday and you think that you're going to stop this information getting out by killing corsi
F****** wrong
Pax West
Or less
Okay
Contacted me this morning
To say that if he gets killed
Anytime before next Tuesday
Authorized
Broadcast
Contact a certain
US representative in the capital and I'll leave it there
Which one
Is Italy that there
I do like
He's finally swinging his dick around on course
Like we told him to finally like
White House press credentials
Alex knows
The senator
Congressperson whatever
We'll leave it at that
I was going to leave with that
Chase course he dies
Why wouldn't you have contacted
Him already
For just a sec
Okay
What could
Possibly Saturday
All of the needs of this
Story
A lot
Propaganda
It's got to be like if this is
Entertain this
Okay OK Google if it's not
All of this
All the requirements
What satisfies all the requirements of this story
You can't wait for this information to drop till 2
Figure out anything that could actually be
That would make sense
Okay person in the house
Is going to flee the country on Monday
Oh there we go tickets plane tickets are nonrefundable
But he can't move them up and get out of the country before then
But once he's out of the country course he is free to speak
He's gone Underground
So then if
If course he gets murdered
NE moves
Light up
No. Of course he gets killed
You don't call that guy at all that guy's not answering your phone
That's going to give you a
That's going to
The congressperson
So I can take a look at that
If all this is
Is true
Course he has given up his sword
Which I don't know if
That's a bad idea Trump Sons know
He's going to have to apologize about it later
I don't know it's really hard to get myself in this headspace cuz I know it's all full of s***
You don't
Is
What information
I know I know what the narrative is going to be so I don't
I don't want to speculate but I'd love
See what you think
What do you think was worth killing Kursi over
Okay
Corsi
Has information from the
Member of the House
Yes
High levels high levels
Okay
Who's killing him
The people who the information is about
Call it Hillary you are a witch
Doesn't matter I don't want to put this to succinct
Duh
Like
Boots world
Well we should find a reasonable
Take the global
Totally
Write a little exposed
To get rid of course
Destroy them all
What is
And why wait till Tuesday
Again
The flight
Move your flight up
It was good pricing for Memorial Day
You got a Groupon right that's really what happened
Real spy movie
Can people with
Understand how serious this is
Very serious
That is why we laugh
I know
For confronting you a little bit more about to get to the big news and then Alex
You're just as bad as Alex on this
Here here
The first pizza
Big news is this next clip
What's the spoiler
The next clip after this
Is what I've been to
Episode
Which is what I think
This is all about okay
This isn't the end of the episode
But I think we can figure out what's real and what's not in the next 2 clips
Here's the first one
This is Alex
Doesn't have any
Things to do at the big
You're going to be working here a long time my friend cuz this is a real name
Other Democrats and others to know
Seth Rich had been executed
The news wanted to come out but none of the stuff was stolen
Was appointed by Obama
Artistic people including children
He's got major confirmed
He doesn't
Course he has
Seth rich
Of course I have a bunch of people who weird connections and none of it
None of it's really based on anything real
A bunch of post on my computer
He blogs and stuff
This is
Pacifica convoluted and I don't fully understand
Yeah all of their understand is hopefully hand
Just to be clear
Like
There's a bunch of new stuff
From flying around
About the Seth rich
Situation
I would like to everyone
Like
Really look at what people are saying
I'm not I'm not saying that if you believe that
Conspiracy you belong in hell
Like some folks I'm not going to go that far
But when you hear something like
Evil angel with Jason
You block an apartment on the outskirts
I think that it's really important
Whenever you're
Looking at a piece of news or some
Conspiracy theory propaganda nonsense
Becomes flying in your face
Really take a look at the men
What shirt literally take a look at what's being said
The things that keep popping up now the new version of it and I think Alex is going to get to it eventually
I'm sure this is part of what course is going to go over
Is that Donna brazile
Member of the DNC
Architect
I recall her
For like delivering
Got questions
After just after
Do that
I don't defend
I'm not here to back that up
So apparently I'm a little bit after Seth rich
Was killed
She
Asked the private investigator why he was snooping
Around
That's the phrase that use on like WorldNetDaily
At least Titan
Real-life spy movie there's something going on
The reality is at the time
There was an investigation going on by the police by the actual official folks
Investigator in question is the guy who has
Impeached himself
On National Television. The last episode
Evidence
That's that rich wasn't communication with WikiLeaks
Redman when he was interviewed about it later said that he got that information from Fox News
Reporters exactly
I fed him his own
He is not a guy with any real credibility and the Brazil would have been
There's an actual investigation going on
Isn't really any evidence of a cover-up
It is nothing
People are spinning it as it is
Now it could the question could literally have been like
Hey what are you doing
Right-wing like what are you doing
I'm
I'm certain that some of that will be incorporated into
Jerome corsi reporting
The other thing that Hamby has been pushing
I've gotten some traction online is
Kim.com
The guy who created Megaupload
Years been trying to destroy Hillary Clinton
Because he believes that
She is responsible for a lot of his falls from Grace which are not accurate that's not an accurate depiction
But you have to find
Escape goat
Hillary is hell
A a lot of people
Totally
Larry Nichols
Walmart.com
So Tom has been saying
He has definitive proof
That there was emails
Between
Seth rich
And I'm sure when he was pressed
Bye Hannity
He freely gave all that information
Proved it to
Later he gave the date is Tuesday as the day that he was going to do that
Happen is the evil and Alex parents
I'm out
They put out a statement
Kim.com tried to hack
Seth riches email
They got it in
Seth Rich Dad
Still has access to his email account
Any monitors at 4
He
Last week
Email
From Megaupload. Envy or whatever Megalo. Enzi
Problem
It was an invitation
To join it was clearly a fishing at
So
Well I mean that did work for the DNC
It also
Wow also there
So basically he was trying to hack the email so he could plan emails
That's obviously what was going on
If that would have been his bombshell proof
Yeah he has
Fabricated emails and evidence in the past
He has a real bad and is
Notorious hacker
So
This stuff
Not that great
One apparently uploaded pretty cool
That stuff is coming out
Are all bulshit
And attempt
By people who are pushing
In the story to fabricate stuff
To back up the story
Right which one you're doing that
You're not interested in the truth
You're interested in pushing this
To deflect from something else
Exact I bet something else
In the case of people
Like kim.com
People like Hannity is that
The walls are closing in on the Trump
Theme
Sticky pickle
Sticky Wicket
Whatever
They keep getting out of these really tight situation
Going to run out
Hopefully one of these things is going to stick
Might be this f****** Kushner
With the back Chan
Hopefully hopefully
But they know that and that's why they're pushing the Seth Rich s*** so hard
It's undignified
It's disgraceful
Putting his family through a lot of s***
Yeah it's very bad to sacrifice their willing
Somebody else's family who they don't care about Rodger Stone
Give you what you think is a fake
Conspiracy theory
Why wouldn't you give them their own medicine back
Corsi style exactly
The thing is like Rodger Stone even tweeted that like
The family of Seth Rich deserve privacy but the American people deserve truth more
Oh yeah Rodger Stone
Regret that,
Situation
I just imagined that all of the
These guys wind up in
Ecuadorian a
One of these things
So
And why not the goat about Saddam Hussein
He keeps trying to be nice to them but they take it as an attack
Alex Alex I just can't wait for the
The episode where they put tape
On the floor
Suicide but there's eight of them so they all get like a Foursquare
He's going to try and go to the room
The best geometric way to maximize their state
Here we go
We can talk about Hannity and I believe over the course
So this clip
Alex
Shows his cards
We get a glimpse at
He's pushing this
Stream narrative
Giving you the Tuesday to look forward to
Really trying to wrap things up
In here
Shawn Kemp
Snl43
The Civil War
What are pulling Sean Hannity off the
Send a message
That's not why they all well
Limbaugh's not hit the country
Religious freedom
Other religions
Everything's going through
That's why I asked our Affiliates to stay with us and support us
Continental Deli
Corporate sponsors
Advertiser
That's on you
These Bakery things you've got to defend us from this attack
So
Alex
Drops a little bit later in the episode
Cut it out because
I lost track of where was the episode
But he says that they've lost like in the last week something likes
Teen affiliate
This is about
Exactly what this
This is the best 100% what this is about
A bunch of other stuff that I cut out from this episode cuz I don't
Is Alex bragging about how great Infowars coverage is
All the time he's trying to shore up his credibility
Epi same time as he's creating this
Fantastical narrative
Edward Burns
Break the story that's bigger than water
At the same time
Let's spend about 10 minutes on this episode interviewing Billy Weaver about how she unmasked a member of antifa
They didn't do this interview at throughout the course of it
What you learn
Is that Millie Weaver
Was just repeating things she read on Fortune
No
So they're like we got this right
When they actually play the report
Illegal Tender
Stand for Chad at all
Do not answer I mean like
Sure
Great think I want Rainbow Brite
Rainbow snatch
Rainbow sash for the insult
Alex Alex the end of the road
The the thing that he said
Which
Like for the longest time
Continuing
To make it a fight
You know like
Even though we won theirs done with Hillary
They have to do that
But the fact that he said right then
We didn't
Yeah that's what they look like before the ground
For that disc
Before
Totally new rhetorically
But it does sound good
It sounds great
In space
When we got Trump elected
Is turning into
This is created way more issues
That I think is important to bring into this conversation because it's absolutely
Nuclear base on Alex's own words that they're losing
Affiliates
And he doesn't make money from affiliating the shower for syndication
But at the same time
Thousands of years to all these long commercials on his phone so that's going to cut
Deep into
His
His profits
He says like 15 or 20
I have left
And it's not
It's not the small town
Probably.
Arkansas
We went over all the tiny markets on our lifetime
Dropping are the only ones who have
Any like advertised
And any liberal audiences that are like the radio
Probably true and then also
He's replaced super fast and loose about the number of
Estimated is like 9
95 or something
The only concrete numbers we can get from Genesis Communications Network which indicates a show was it
They had like 85 2015
He claims that we keep
But now some people can't be caught up
He claims he had to listen to the radio are not being kept
In the dark about
He claimed he had like
20 or something like that before this
False
But I don't believe that number
Doesn't have 48
You know
And that brings us to the other part of what I think this is really about
Story broke
Vanity Fair
At the end of last week
That was about Breitbart
Yeah
Overnight
Breitbart's traffic shot up precipitously to the point where they were like
The 26th most visited website in the world
Around
Jr around December of last
It stayed up around there and then drop
Hard
Drop
50% down
Which
Costume
And if you could
Other
But going down also not the same like
Of course there's going to be that slow slide as they reality further
Like if you are at all interested in the
Trump store
Even if you support Trump
You can't go to Fox
Snow
About it
. so the only way for you to keep
Keep abreast of what's going on
There is by watching those
I think it's not even of course traffic
Conservative b******* is going to go down
If there's a
That is
An algorithm
Totally
Which we've explored in the past
Traffic
Just excites make leaves for like advertising and ship
And they
Very fair reached out to
The Alexa people
You're asking for
And the person that they talked to it quote
Now but it's
That there is
There's certified
Statistics
I went to run a website you can turn off that certified
That point
They don't know if it
It's real
Website or not
Apparently
That stretch
Was a. Of time but we're Breitbart had opted out of the certified
And then they are
Probably
The article mentions
The time. Where they were opted out
Choose up
Perfectly with
The op
Right
Which
Foremost website
If you opt out of certified
You're probably going to see an uptick of
What you thought was what you think is traffic
Crawlers and come
Go through there and trolls around like that kind of
What are used to run a Blog
And there would be comment
That would cut
Italy come from advertising
Things that'll artificially inflate
Course
So I think Alex
Nose
About that
And has known about that
And the fact
They knew that breitbart's traffic a drop
Before that
Yeah
And there's a decent chance that Alex
There's these people knew that
There isn't there is a triangulation of right-wing media
That is garage up top Alex Jones
And Breitbart
Pyramid scheme
Yeah
Like they all feed into each other to stomach
Like cross pollination
Directly between Breitbart
Westerly promote each other's s***
But they still play in the same Kitty pool
That involves sucking up to drive
So if there's something there
Half of the traffic has dropped
Breitbart
Overnight
There's no f****** way out its doesn't know about
Rat
Cuz we don't know
From the statistics
Bets are on
Alexa we don't know if
His traffic
Is
Certified
We don't know that
We can probably assume
But we don't
To assume it's
But Woodland
HDMI
A suspicion that
You are the only person
It's trending downward certainly traffic to traffic
Sorry I mean
I just I can't
I can't believe a scenario wherein
Like Alex doesn't see
This Vanity Fair article as a real warning
Like a real dangerous sign
He could either
Be the Keno's
Because bulshit
That's about to come out and do the Oppa
That's one possibility
The other possibility is
Oh s***
This ideology that
Weave
Albany
Backing isn't
The popular as I thought it was could just be like
S***
They were Faking It All Along
Call
God
So much of my
So much of my believing in Trump
He could ever
He could
Never
Ever admit that
But that doesn't mean you can't feel it
Even if he doesn't admit it it doesn't mean that it's not somewhere buried deep down
That combine
With
Very
Real
Self-admitted losing a ton of affiliate
It's not like that's going to stop bleeding is not going to stop right
He knows
I am
Fuct
I am so f*****
At at the same time
Is Russia is going down
It's just
So bad
Everything is falling apart
The chips
Fart
There's a table
He's at the poker table
Got like one chip left
Are the guys going to force them all in
That is where he's at
Yeah he's got a chip in a chair
He's got a hole
But he is not looking good
How does this
Batman what
What is
What does
Like murdering Jerome corsi
To the god of traffic
I just
It's the same thing for it's the same thing for all of these guys right
It seems like what
What's really being revealed is that
The
Conservative consciousness
Is
Payless popular
Then it
It's given
Attention
Big time
So a lot of emails fundraising with a 48% approval rating where he's like
Yeah
No just like we talked about with the Twitter bot
Where
What their job is
Amplify this stuff
Midget
Popularity
Push it
High up is it
And that makes you and I think
This is a far more popular far larger movement
Then what we would
Expect
Like if everybody actually knew that
All of these guys were really just
Marginalized
Had a very small group of P
People
We would be paying a bunch of
I would still pay attention to Alex's class
I don't mean the culture at Large
Yeah why would you be reporting on what Breitbart
If it's
300000 bucks from store
Stormfront isn't on
Isn't being reported isn't being
Manipulated and and put into the larger
No not really is just
Stormfront
Like just
Leave it alone ignore it
Yeah now it's probably going to Fester the same way that
Stormfront and all that s***
And marginalizing them will probably only make them more violent
Who cares
There's not a lot of
So if there's not a lot of them
Then those conservatives in Congress and all of those people you see that
As transparent as the voter suppression
It's their only
There's no chance for them if
Real people
Get involved
Like there's zero chance
Like there is no ideology
More unpopular right now
Then
Bishop conservative
It seems that way
Over the recess
People going back
Severe
Fair
Places where their constituents are
I think that you're going to see a lot of people like
Doing sit in
I'd like politician
Headquarters and stuff
Isaac
Everything that comes out is
Like everyday you're like
The one where people are finally going
Start burning
And then the next day it's something worth me like well we
We can't just keep putting this off guys
That's why we have all the news stories about the clashes
Between antifa and
Bright red one like you and I sitting around like I look at these people out there fighting
There are people and we don't feel like we have to go out and sit in
I can still have that fantasy in my head
Active
Pumpkin fashion
God I would punch
Haven't got
Fully support and truly believe in myself
Benefit proud boy
Came up to
Hey Jordan I'm a proud boy
What's redneck kisser
I mean I am using a little bit of speculation
In terms of what I think is really going on
But I think it has
Much more of a factual basis then
Jerome corsi get stumbled into information that will get him killed
Because this
Hypothetical congressperson
I'm just going to leave the country on Monday I can't talk about it till Tuesday
Why you can't talk about it till Tuesday but who cares first narrative
If you recall there were two pieces of information
And the big news
No they were two pieces of information within the big news
But Alex has the green light to talk about
Democrats to know as a mess
SMS
And then it was
Kim.com and Hannity and those are just
That's his background
No that's
Just what I think is going on behind the scenes
Is there still a second piece of big news to get you
Okay
Just a second I thought we'd already gotten that way
Information
He has total proof
And multiple large companies complete access
Chess pie
On hundreds of thousands of Americans
Access
Control Hub p******
And then transferring out of the country
So how's that grab you
So he's saying that the Democrats
Gave
DNS error no gave a bunch of people access to the NSA database
To monitor
Hundreds of thousands
The people during the election
For political reasons
Okay
So
More believable than anything else he said so far today
Because frankly at this point vnsa seems to have given everybody that f******
The f******
Destroyed
British hospitals in the NHS
Like all of them
They're like we built this
Victoria
That's
So I think Jerome corsi's life is safe
I understand because you got scooped
There's a post that came out on Friday on circa.com
I'll read you the headline
Declassified memos show FBI illegally shared by data on Americans with private parties
This news is already out
Alex
Nautical misrepresent
The situation
It looks to declassify report
I hear it
99 pages long
And it is basically
It's about the certification of
Article 702
Of the fisa
Court
Regulation
So we're about to
Ladies and gentlemen
Hang on to your
I'm knocking
It has to do with
Like I don't I don't fully understand because it's very
Specific
Very detailed
But
702 has to do with collecting of information on foreign
Individuals
And there's a lot of rules about how it is done
I am about
You're not supposed to get
American citizens wrapped up in it
Cuz of laws
It's the whole conversations going on about unmasking at all this stuff
It all has to do largely with 702
Section 702
Yeah but a lot of
A lot of it was incidental I will I will admit that but American data
There's a reason that program was stopped
Is because it was illegal
This entire
Declassified night-time page
Pizza Pizza
Pretty interesting cuz it has to do with
Review
Of
The
The guidelines that are used
To make sure that information doesn't get out
Basically
What's it called minimization procedures
Basically how you keep things inside
I in the findings that they had an email from Megaupload
Don't click on the link kim.com try to plant something
Maybe his new edmed brother junk mail I can dispute
Music
So the two things
I think of the most
That you can find
If you read this
Are there at
As we all know we're not comfortable with necessarily
Does collect Upstream internet traffic
And stuff like that
Can eventually be searched
But those databases are purged after a certain amount of time
Still f***** up
It's perfectly legal according to
Reviews
Internally
Yeah but
Can't litigate
The program is
All I can do is talk about the story that Alex
Is presenting
Because if we get into that then
Coursework
Yeah that's too big to unpack
What they found is that some people
Some people within the nsa's structure had
Googling
Google
Now they've been using a search engine for that
Yes and they had been using us person
Automate search
They were supposed to
Supposed to do that
Somebody abused the system that was so therefore abusing
Upon the review there they're not sure that they really even
Sound anything that they use
You know it's just
That one guy looked up his ex-girlfriend for sure
There's no doubt about that
It's wrong it's
But it's not
It's not indicative
Of any of the stuff that Alex
Is breaking in the story
Nor is it indicative of the stuff that's in the circus
The stories
When the review that this is a report
When they looked into it
Deemed
That most of this
Due to people being unaware of rule
Being unaware of the guideline
And they just basically recommend review team
And that the rules that are in place
Or satisfactory
And they do
Meet the Fourth Amendment requirements
Circle e but perhaps
Talking about about giving information
Enterprise at
Folks
And foreign governments
Individual
That's not in here that
If he's talking about something else than whatever but
Here is
What you might be talking
On March 9th
2016. Oversight Personnel conducting a minimization review at the FBI's
Black
Learned that the FBI cuz it like this is
Disclose Ross information
Including but not limited to section 702 acquired information to a blank
Blank
Blank is part of the black
Black
It is largely staffed by private contractors
Blank blank
Certainly black contractors
Had access to information on the FBI's storage system
The apparent purpose for the FBI granting such as analytical assistant
Nevertheless the contractors that access to Ross
Information that went well beyond was necessary to respond to the FBI's request
Black
Describe access to Ross ice information as of April 8th
26th
That's actually pretty fast for them to solve that
Question receive training on the FBI minimization procedures
Did not disseminated further
Nonetheless the above-described practice
Violated the government's minimization procedures
So they did a review of it
That is
Incompetent
Yeah but that's all
But we don't know what that that private contractor company
Could be some sort of non-governmental organization
That they were Consulting
And they just sorta f***** up
In terms of handling the more like
An oversight
That's more like
Yeah we we assumed that everybody was operating under
The same rules that we did and some people didn't know what they were
Yeah just like anybody
You know the guy your job is kind of an idiot
Antojitos
He's f*****
Yeah
There's another heavily retracted section or redacted section
Where they talk about another instance
Of the FBI giving Rod 8702 acquired information
To another contract
Because
It appears that that is a federal age
That they had given information to
But they just didn't do it
They didn't meet the requirements of Section 5 D of the FBI minimization
So it's more
Technical snafus
They were giving everybody access to the NSA grid
Nothing is really
It seems like nothing there was really worried
Other than other than the fact that these people
Have all of our information
And when they suck
It means
Canby
Released if you do give it to those private
Yeah so that's why you have those guidelines in place
And it seems like
When was they realize that
They could have been
And so they plugged
Right
It's bad it's not good
You know it's not good but at the same time it's
If it's not legal
Know if it is not nefarious
Is Illustrated in this Declassified document
They did reviews
And they stopped these things that were clearly like we haven't we have a f****** in our process let's fix that
MMS review itself
Recommend
To make sure that everyone's in compliance
There's one other thing that people could get up in arms about in this
Declassified documents
That is that the spying
On people
Accidentally
Took him some stuff that was covered under attorney-client privilege
Course
But
But in response to that they recommended steps
But they could undertake to make sure that that doesn't
I make sure that they're more sensitive
Future
Two things
That they should not be
So this happened in 2016
This review is 2017
They all can't be classified reviews from this
Okay
Are supposed to have stopped the boat date
Action Program
So
This is from April 27th
People trying very hard to
Comply with
They're not doing great at it so far
But they're trying to get better
Yeah
Also I mean it just at the end
They specify that
The practices and the guidelines that are in place for managing of data
Comply with the Fourth Amendment
And then just a list out a number of recommendations
About what
To better handle things to make sure
Little
Systemic problems that happened in the past don't happen again
Basically the workplace review
Nuclear reactor
Where
We are working with Eddie
Insanely dangerous
Beyond Reason and a minor f****** here
Is not like a minor f****** at an office
It possible that a lot of
Will die
If you f******
So this is. Kind of like
We're constantly putting
Testing to make sure that our reactor.
Yeah it's possible that he's talking about something else
Declassified document that seems to have to do with very similar
Came out on Friday
It fits it fits all of the stuff saved
Describe now if you and I were to go up to them and tell them
This is what you were talking about they would have course
Completely different we'll talk Tuesday
But I mean like
I accept the possibility
All Appliance
Narrative
Based on
Read the entire document
Who else but you was going to read the entire
I don't think those people who wrote the article that the entire document
It did not sound like a summary
Let's
It was rough
And if it's the kind of thing like
When you read court documents and stuff like that
I found it this morning
Before we started recording
Today's I'd be able to read that
And then succinctly
Verbally described
Report on it
But like
F****** legal shed
It's all this like repeated terms and
I'm not doing the best job of describing it I'll put up a link to the document
You can read it if you want
Who cares
Read it
Read if you want like
Like if you're at the beach
Pull up on your Kindle
Yep but like
Please trust me it's not what
Anyway let's get let's get off this topic
Let's jump into greener pastures of extract
The future of our species
Also please
Infowars.com
About our YouTube videos article article sharing those videos
God bless you all thank you for the support
What about you
Memorial Day specials
All his specials of the biggest they've ever offered also we already talked about this he's losing affiliates
If you look at the Alexis schitt his
Traffic is
Lumping
I went to quadcast the other day and I was looking to
To see if there wasn't
In the about to 300,000
Visitor suicide a day
Has been nothing like
Other than
You know he has those one day Pete
Citgo
But now there's nothing nothing trending upwards
He's not
Doesn't appear to be losing a ton but is trending downwards
You losing your f****** Affiliates you're not winning Alex
From zero Affiliates to hopefully one
Are trending upwards
So yeah we just heard that Trump has the proof
About this
Supposed
You know
The ship that Obama
The Democrats have been doing
Alex wants to talk a little bit more
POTUS
That they're on the Russian and Chinese payroll
Into the second third fourth fifth sixth seventh eighth
Government
That's a fascinating clip
Cuz like
From heaven
Appointed people
I could be approved or disapproved
That idea blocked his ability to people in the second third layers
But he's not even trying
Date because he knows
Whatever they want
So describe what's going on right now had a very accurate the right now
That's that seemed like that's another one of those time
Times Square
He has to
Totally he has to know
That what
He sang
Is the inverse of what is half
Well yeah I think so and that's a big part of the investigation that we're going to be starting tomorrow is that I want
I desperately want to know what happened
Likewise
I think that Alex is holding up a line the
Moschino is b*******
I think he knows that he have to
Because he can't he can't flip flop now
Not at all
Till till whatever ended
Is almost
90% chance going to be some sort of
Disaster for
Yeah
Tubidy
Stuff like that
Him saying stuff like that
Obama's government was just Reckless and doing whatever they want
I'm never taking a look at
The s*** the Trump is doing
Order people around
Timber doing for good
Bright whatever
Making vodka
Concession like willing to turn the
It's not like
It's not
It's not what he's about
Based on
His entire career
But
At the same time
You still
A lot of himself
Like those
Does masculinity ideas
Those racist ideas
Those are still him
Yeah but that stuff like the political stuff
That's not Alex Jones
Relieve like
Gone Whole Hog info
Ron Paul
Liberal candidate who could win
Right
Had to us
If possible
I've learned a whole bunch of stuff in it
Appropriate time but for now let's enjoy it real Alec
Succezz
This cliff
World
Dangerous people out there
Ben-Hur
At some point we reached here with a bunch of my lines and they know that
Cuz a bunch a child molesters a bunch a child
Muslims
Stop
What time does Charter in
That's wild
Do you do understand what he's trying to get up there
I don't
So all
It's too couched in so much of that like
Like
Here's the same boring everybody
Manor not real men
Translating how all of this like really inflammatory
Should be interesting stuff has become very boring
It's super interesting that
Like he has this whole narrative like a fluoride in the water
But he has to incorporate everything into 1 grand
Conspiracy that the globalist doing
Unified field
So they can get away with their crime
All these crimes are the things that
Conceivably trampas never drink fluoride
He's a genius
Who is been planning this for 30 years
Sleeper Cell
Is there in the past Alex's used a whole bunch of other reasons
That's not what he said in the past
Or things like that other other end goals of the dumbing people down
Something
The point of all of this stuff and the thing that I
I think makes it
Boring for me
To hear that
Long laundry list now
He repeats
The same stuff
And then
Whatever and gold
He thinks you're afraid up to
Today
Is white
So you're afraid today
The government getting away with
You're afraid
But they're going to take your guns
So it's always it's always these these like
Tent poles
It's almost service to whatever it like he's throwing darts at a wall
What is going to be the
The cause of this
Today it's almost like he has a set of lies that he just repeats
Much like he is Accused the mainstream media
Very similar
Let's not let's wrap this up
Full-time
It's kind of done
Because Larry nickel
Old friend
He comes on
Of him basically
How is the Internet would say Larry Nichols is back on his b*******
Because
Is just telling Alex we need to build an army
And that we are the only ones who can help Trump
All this stuff
Very ignorable
You guys will learn more about just how much of a douche
Right after this
Tomorrow Larry Nichols you'll learn all about him
But for now just need to really know is that he is a Clinton Insider
He's a guy with
F****** amazing sources
At least that's the way they're presented on the show
Yeah I am so
You know you got inside
Here Comes Alex
He's got this prediction to give
I guarantee
Okay
Is some high-level stuff
Is it enough to get Corsica
Baidu measurement is not classified be classified
It what level of info gets course he killed
Biscuits corsi's family killed
Yes
Except
Donald Trump
6 months
Insight
Almost
That's the only way you'll get that information
The former Clinton Insider
Level sources the talent things
Glean from reading
The front page
At least
A few places
Confirmed that
The Republican Senators
We're going back to there was going to be there
Matt esper
Hey we're either on board or office
And this is how we're going to die
Larry in this interview you keep saying that we need to
We need to tell people of Republican leaders
That if they support this impeachment
They're done
He's trying to sort of BV
The counterweight
I mean like
The gop's in realshit spot right now
Especially
Alex
Are in a terrible spot
Congress the only people who are doing right now
Rebel media
Mike cernovich
Gavin McInnes
F*** him
They're doing great
Because they are just sort of
What cuz they've been break
The the white National
And the chaos
And they pretend they're doing me bedok Warfare and Alex is still not embracing Whole Hog
White National
Like Gavin McInnes
Is
Kevin McHale
Gavin has a dildo shaped
Like white nationalism
Right up his ass
Even though he screams bit like outright bigotry
Just not gone far enough in order
He's to Siri
Like Gavin McGinnis
And Mike cernovich
At least have the appearance of a cent
Yeah like they at least
Make a goof
Like I seen Mike cernovich
That's not allowed
Cernovich good time
But they're having a good time
Never seen Alex have a good time
Cuz young people don't want this stuffy old
Asphalt
To being up there
Like he is
Becoming
Less relevant
Eva it like
So he reached his pinnacle
More like Trump
Was elected
Pinnacle of what his popularity could be
And he's
Just going to go down
If I had to imagine
Even my investigation
Can't prove this at this point
But I believe
2 Direction
He took the wrong one
Because
Once he decided to support Trump
The two outcomes of a possible there's Trump wins Trump loses
Trouble
He's the guy who cheered for a loser
But at least you could
Could still save a little face
Right on we got to follow up
Once they win
Once you go down that path and you win
You know how I live you're useful
Don't really have a have a purpose to serve anymore
You were the propaganda that got us in and now
You can't do s*** to help us
Investigation
How how would you know that by helping to elect an authoritarian government
Perhaps you would no longer be on the inner circle happened before in the
History of
Unless Trump
Back and then you could have taken the path of not
Supporting Trump
And you
Even if Trump wins
But you don't saying
There's the initial Fork that is supporter don't support each of those has two branching paths office
The 4:02 don't support both win
One of them
With win support Trump
Is a real negative
And he happened to get that
Is the one
That he ended up going number 3
Celibate
But if you did not support drop any losses
No skin off
Is back
Hazel globalist narrative can continue
He can be what it's like for him was for Hillary
Trump and Trump wins
Now he can say glad Hillary lost he can celebrate that
Horse Trump is going to fall into it exactly what series of gas
They're just going to be
Sweet Manna From Heaven for Alex
Good then he can go against
This Republican candidate
This Republican winner but he could have made hay out of leather
Think of how great his ship on Russia would be right now
The Russians are controlling the government I told you this
This also gets
Since my investigation
Because
I don't
Think he ever had
The choice to take
OSHA
I think the choice is made for
Doctor
You beat me a beat to it
I don't want to give away
So lyrical present himself as
Clinton Insider
You said he knows all about their
He's responsible for the tournament Arc
Inside
Which is an Arkansas beside which is the Clinton shooting
Vince Foster
Stanford believes
Arkansas
So he believes
He has one of the worst pieces
Defense
For that
About to play
Stanley
Yep they are
Well they told me the national
That that was
True
Call Jesus
The thing that the that the problem is they also at
Tim about a lie
Whether or not witches
He left that out also record
2 and 10 I on him when he was murdered
Oh boy
We still do not have that proof
High-level sources debt listen
If I am murdered
Over the next 6 to 12 months
Yeah I have released a dead drop
That is filled with alien parts
So the problem with Larry's sort of line
Is
That one of the Hallmark
In Arkansas
Is people close to the victim
Telling you to shut up
Yes so also of a
Murder
That has been turned into a massive conspiracy theory is the family saying
Please shut up
But that's the thing is that he does not
Be a difference
Between
The police
And Sean Hannity
Because the family has been very clear
But they don't mind it being investigated
For what they don't want
Is kim.com
Hacking his email
They don't want Hannity turning this into a rating
Grab they don't want Alex Jones
Trying to compensate for losing all his affiliates
By making this into a big story that may or may not get drunk or C-Murder
Don't want that cuz that's not an investigation
Nope
Show Business
That's politics
Bulshit that's propaganda
They don't want their son's death to be a part of that
Stupid very clear the fine with an invest
Navigation
I know you're 80 years old or whatever in your
On your Deathbed
But you know that
Stop pretend
Sucking bulshit
Even if you believe the most
But even if you believe the Seth rich
Conspiracy
There is no
I think maybe the better way to put it is
If you believe the Seth rich
Conspiracy theory
Everything
Plays into how right
Leave it out for me
If you if you believe that Seth rich
With killed by the DM
Or whatever
Conspiracy theory want to
The fact that the
The parents are saying
You know we wanted investigation but we don't want you to do it we don't want Hannity doing it
That place
Course the DNC doesn't
Looking into it or they were
Of course not
Of course
If if they did say hey
F****** we're open and honest
We're going to let you do that
Well that proves that Seth Rich was killed because the only reason that you would be so open and honest
Is if they've already covered it up so easily
That you can't find any
There's no win against this
Because all it really is
Is a man
Well I mean what the
Spirits Ethier
Is a
Manufac
Look at me
It is everything
It's everything that you could want
To be happening right
Now as
Trump
Committing treason
Like you have you have
Distraction
Good distraction
Because the way you think of it is
Oh well Trump
Bulshit is it
Conspiracy
So we have
A bunch of people who are already looking to believe in
Why not give them our cans
Let's
That's the whole idea if you were primed
To believe in
Frankly at this point god dammit if we are.
Yeah
Listening listening to the news is like
The spider from
Thrones
Kislyak probably did 911 I'm not saying that for sure
Yeah
We're all praying for that so why not just make up your own
And try and co-opted as much of that as you can
It makes me think of like a Alex Jones rant about the Overton window
I like how this
Entire Earth
System
This entire life
Conspiratorial faucets
Emma's just overtaken
Rationality
Because as it becomes closer and closer
Occam's razor
To be more and more on the side of
Treason unless unless on the side of
These guys are f****** stupid
And they just wanted to steal a s*** ton of money
Yeah
Lightning
The Trump campaign
Would make a great Ocean's 14
Like that cuz that's what it seems like it was it was a bunch of assholes getting together
When people out of their money
The diversity of emotions movie
But instead of instead of them you know
Stealing all the
Casino's money at the end
I'm just sitting out there at the fountain going
Hey guys we did it
Instead they own the casino.
They had no idea they had to
Run the casino
They have been working with a rival Casino
And casino lose their job
Blunderbuss
But
Unlikely is everything
The only thing that you can point to
In all of this
Some sort of
Collapse about
Yeah like
It seems like it's just
.
Something is going to collapse
It's
Like right now you can
Steve that are into
Institutions
All of our belief in the rule of law
Like all that stuff
Is putting up a lot more of a fight that I may have easily expect but one branch of the government
8/8
It seems to be you
Holding a little bit stronger than I would have expected
Something
Break
Yeah
What's going to happen is
I mean the only thing I can see happening
A little bit
Conspiratorial here myself
But
The arm of the government that's holding up is the legislator
The executive branch is f*****
Cuz there are people in the staff position
Like
The state Department's basically empty
All the people
Functioning as a
Executive branch has the all the people who are in charge are basically incompetence
Who are flocking
Rick Perry
Got these people have no business being in the position they could not be happier that he's not in the
Right-click Rick Perry is what most incompetent running
An organization that he does not understand you could be all over the news once Broussard play
If he is not loving this right now just like
His branch of government does
To completely fuk
Swiss cheese
And apartments
And nothing's there
And a leader who seems to be actively hostile to the idea of a function
Somewhere along the line there's some mint
Degradation of weirdos around him advising him
Then you have
The new branch is a complete shitshow
You've got Republicans in power
In both houses
Seemed unwilling
Deal with the problem of the executive branch
Wield some control over and they won't
They're doing Everett there they are
At this point
Like f****** Trump was going to be
The legislative branch
The GOP
Congress
Open right now
Have shown
That they want
Gladly watched
Tire Republic
So they can
Can lower tax
For rich people
Not understanding that
Once it falls
Text Cody.
But what I'm getting at is both of these branches are completely fuk did you just branch
Except for the Supreme Court which
Is
Wildcard we don't know exactly how the temperature the rest of it
The rest of it seems to be holding up
Pretty well
So far and what that means to me
Is it that is going to be the next thing the
By the incompetent
Sad
Trump is embodying
Spreading like a cancer
He is about to start a point
A s*** ton
Exact
Really start to get f***** up cuz he's not going to get caught
He's going to get people who either ideologically
Support weird things he believes in
Or people who showed loyalty
Right
You might as well just put convicted murderers ever
You got that f***** in the
Department of Homeland
Who is a murderer
Clark
Literal murderer
He's a murderer murdered people
He's he's Sheriff Joe Arpaio
Yeah he is a murderer
He's a murderer
Committed the crime of murder and was in Russia at the same time as Mike Flynn
He was
Yeah pictures of him
Why does a guy from work
From Wisconsin going to
Yeah that's real that's real turn the pictures over time
I'm done
I give up
I think Russia
You're fine yeah
Is like a game of Go
And we got our ass
That brings us to the end of this episode
I think that what we can take away from this is Tuesday is not going to bring with it
Samantha
Hopefully we'll bring
I don't wish that upon him I wish
Did he was shot up
I don't want to
I wish you would stop being such
A weasel
But I don't want him dead
If he did
That's what I'm afraid of
Know your old man more like
If he was right
Now
It would be hilarious because that's the world the world
Buy pure happenstance like this weird Collective heart attack
I mean
That
The information on Tuesday
But for
Very different reason
The older it looks like he is the most right he's ever been
And his last thoughts are
I was wrong
What I imagine is more like a board scenario where he hires a Hitman to kill him
Cuz he's like f*** I've lost
Viability
To do journalism
I am in bed with people who likes
I've just
I'm going to hire this Hitman to give me credibility on my way out
And over the course of this Memorial Day weekend
He's going to learn to love and live again
I'm trying to hit man would not be able to he'll be caught up in his own web of proper
Like the nation of Guatemala
Was
His mentor
I don't know if that's what it's a wonderful life situation
Instead it turns out
This is how great everybody's life
Would be of course he wasn't there and something angel
Pushes them off.
Ifucking bread
That would be my new Christmas movie
Every year
Korsakoff of breadsticks
I don't think that I don't believe in
Can you book can you imagine those living in a world where Alex isn't lying
Tuesday they break a story
Bigger than Watergate
And the world has to be like
Did you imagine
Could you imagine
No I can't
I can't I can't
It was bigger than Watergate
The entire world
Evan Alex
Alex
Possible
Could deal with that
Is by getting on air
And just stripping down naked
Like a loincloth
Castaway Carling burning sticks up
Or he has just like a scroll
A 2-mile long Scroll of people who is like
I need to say f****** love people
You just got the closing credit slide it is just
People who sells
Thankfully that's not going to happen
And a Tuesday will bring nothing
Except affiliates
Dropping the Alex
F*** you Alex little good day I believe
Hopefully by next
We'll find out
What
I just really want course
I don't
I don't wish death
If I can
Chaos Whitaker, Google right now make sure you still alive
You're freaking me out
God I want him dead
Good news he still alive
Anyway
We will be back
Tomorrow with
The beginning of my in-depth investigation
Into what
Happened Alex
What went wrong
Disengaging
Interesting
And it's not
When I started
Accu perfect
Well in the meantime
Can you find us anywhere
How about on Twitter
Dollar General Store
How about on iTune
It's not searching out right we don't have a picture of that
We'll figure that out some yeah
You can find us please give a rating review go ahead
If you'd like to become a
Policy wonk on the website
In the meantime
Tomorrow
Course he may be dead
But I'll tell you what what's up
Rapoport
Alexandra Thurston color