Knowledge party.com
I have great respect but knowledge babe I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
About Alex
Jordan Jordan
What up
Another nice piece of mail and Marcus Center
Copy of the Illuminati board game
New world order one
Is a
Collectible weird pictures of Alex Jones
And Alex
Predict the future
Nice little
You guys are the bright spots
I'm down in this is one thank you so much
Annabel Lee
We got to try and play that
Like now
But the reason that I'm kind of resistant cuz I think I need to get another camera cuz I think I need
Three camera shoot
The cards are being played
I feel like you do
Corso
Another camera cuz
30 bucks
I think
I might be low-balling.
Starbucks
We'll figure that out in the future
What's my bright spot a game night or something
Very cool
The bright spot for me of course
Is there
I will never read the Atlantic
It's garbage
All done
So many times
It's not friedersdorf
Okay
Sentences through a an opinion piece written by two law professors about William
And the first sentence was a lot of people breathe a sigh of relief when
Bill Barr was appointed attorney general
And then the second sentence was everybody had High Hopes because
He had previously worked for an honorable Administration
This is trash
I'm done with the Atlantic forever
You're like me and Project Camelot I don't believe at all
You'll be back
One day
A month after that we'll have another conversation or you say
I'm looking forward to a time where I need something
Thing to get angry
I know that you can get angry just about anything
Specific sort of anger that friedersdorf you out of that drug
It really is it's the same button for you
I think part of it is responded to your tweet I think I think part of it is a purse
Personalization shoot him in the face with some mean words
That means that I'm there forever
26 2020 Zone
Bill Cooper episode for today cuz it's Monday
But
I might be done with that old assholes
A coverage of Oklahoma City
Immediately
The stuff that's actually interesting it might take me a lot longer
Material
Tough for me to motivate myself to put hours and hours into that because
You don't want
Listeners email
Report
Game
And that you would have liked
Actual things to dig
And I think I think you know
Is that first episode that we covered it was about the
The fake document we can discuss that
I can't do anything with like someone from Oklahoma
It's really pathetic honestly and I'm disappointed
Amore
Like get into his
Actual
Conspiracy career
There is now just like
I don't understand how people
I don't know why
I guess he is some sort of charisma
I'll get back to you
It's not feasible to do an episode every week
So whenever we're able to get back to it
But for now we are sticking to the present day with Alex Jones
Interesting
I guess
Locked up
What kind Alex does a couple of particular things that are just like
Continuing this trend towards like
I need political violence
Does Heroes
So we can all kind of enjoyed
I'll before we get down to business on the actual episode
According to
So first plague bucks for patreon
Playbox
The person who has Paradise
With
Oh no
Already known
Ajp
AJ
Soros
I didn't work so recite
I'm a policy wonk
And Nikki
Nicki
Business
Heroin
Large
Nikki
Apologize
Bring it up every now and again
Confused
Because we never reached
Expected people to donate and it's
Dump shows down
It's just too late now renege on the offer of giving everyone shoutout
It's been more than two months and you haven't heard your shout out to email us and we will
I'll get you in the mix
Everything episode
Today Show
About that mean
Coldplay song
The Fallopian tubes and tires
Possibly
Alex
He's continuing his Crusade against mask
Which of course is all kind of beat-up to protest
Protest
Kind of a running about everything
Thumbs up
But now there's a big video that's gone viral with someone important. Com
Where is
Dangerous levels of CO2
Bought one yesterday
Scientific
Example
This is vacation killing people
What are we stopping
Here are those reports back to back
Has found himself another viral video where somebody's mad about
So course he's decided this is
The scientific study
The video of the guy using a CO2 meter levels of CO2 or in his mask in like 5 Seconds
Start beeping
Indicating a dangerous concentration
CO2 in the area
Climate change for your face if this were accurate surgeon could never
Perform surgery
Scientists and researchers could never be in a lab setting for more than a couple seconds without being a
Exposed to supposedly dangerous levels of CO2
There's a lot of people who wear masks for work like for entire shift
Struction workers
Like I said nurses doctors surgeons dentist
I've seen the greatest Minds
My Generation Suffolk
Okay from wearing a
Right that's dangerous effect on their oxygen or CO2
Breathing is really important
The weather
I understand
That's one of the factors
And then consider things like ski mask
Pastor helmets that you wear for extended motorcycle ride
There are 100 examples of essentially impossible wearing a mask dangerously elevator CO2
Or affect your breathing in a meeting for what
Bulshit
N95 mask for Center.
People aren't doctors or nurses
Have to deal with and there are specialized Maps
That's a help mitigate those issue
I'll have thought of this
A long time before you did
Wants to touch back on the NASCAR story
Spending a little bit for no reason
And then you get somebody
NASCAR
Bubba Wallace
Got caught with an H knowing that all those garage doors had those pulled out that they weren't nooses
One of them was
Been there for years
His name in the Google this morning and I saw
Hundreds of headlines
Praising him and
Praising NASCAR
This is a real threat
And that he's right
Probably still a noose
So Alex is reporting a factually inaccurate version of the story because he's by his crimes
Directed at people are a hoax
It's very well maybe this wasn't a crime
Is not to be
Concrete fabrication
With his own narrative
The first is that all of the garages at the same found rope
This is specifically refuted by recording on the story that reflects
The guy who first reported the news check the other garage
To make sure it wasn't something
Misrepresented or misunderstood
Making this up but it was in all the garages
The second thing is Bubba and NASCAR Heroes
What we've been through this kind of business
Being a hate crime
Both parties did act in ways that are commended
What was that the courage to defend the guy at his garage who founded in sand humility
About what would have been there for over a year
Similarly NASCAR should be applauded for taking this seriously
And working to make sure that their drivers are able to work in a safe environment
Is this what happened in the WWE I guarantee they would have covered it up
The third thing is the people are saying that this is a noose
Here is that people are definitely
Play still saying that
And they're right
I've looked at it
What's the news
You bet
People are out of line
Look at the pictures
Clue
Patterns
Because otherwise
It's not really usable for his reporting
Yeah it's
Can you imagine
Acted like Alex Jones
Do you still just like
Nope I know who was it was all white
People they all got together in billions and they just sat down
Like that would be
Skip ahead a little bit more on that story
From Germany foster children
Incase
Looking back on it
Embellish and anyway that's relevant
It probably would
Just be stupid to talk about
Yeah
In Houston
Takes off all the time
Anyway
She won't do
Did she
I don't know
Okay well that's
So we get to this next clip here and Alex's talking about
You know
Yeah God right
By the devil
Do something similar
Alex's Hattie's
His fair share
Of instances of globalist
Hot tubs
Square sometimes in airplanes
Sometimes calling him on his radio show
Mysteriously not recording
Hollywood
Alex's at pretty-much
Every has contacted Alex
And try to reach
Fruit him to the team set for 1
Social media
Did Mark Zuckerberg tried to get me through this intermediaries to go up to New York
Football
Because he's in the face
Almighty
Here's what Alex
Sympathetic
Anybody
Would have recorded those cost
If I'm in a situation where I live
Easiest thing to record a call on Facebook
The first call maybe you don't record it you didn't grab this right
The second call
You got a
Corded
These days with like smartphone
It's really easy to have like an app you can just press press the button
Indication of
Orge
Just incompetent
It's because Alex has sort of pretending that there's like a grand conspiracy of
Extortion
Make you have 5 million
Talk bad about Tucker
If you have those recordings is actually
You have proof
Maybe that's why James O'Keefe only ever make shity videos
Because whenever he gets the good stuff he always forgets to press record on a
Phone
That's always there that's always
Situation so that he has to make up some bulshit but if you just press record
I would have to assume that is what's going on
Is there popping out now the numbers are going up
Nope nope
Alex's take on this is largely that it's just
Because there's more
Accurate but he's misleading
Think about it
Or not Rising
Everywhere
When I cough
You don't have any family with a give you some medicine to make you relax and then
Derivative
But not before they suck hundreds of thousands of dollars out
City Hospital
Real good
Start Rising
Fairly accurate
But
Information
For two reasons
The first was that even if
Things were trending in the right direction
That's still not good
On March 20th of this year we cross
Started to be over 5,000 new cases identified per day
On that day there were only 70 deaths from covid-19
Reported
On March 31st
The numbers jump
2 / 1,000
Isn't the day
This is because dafler what they call a lagging indicator of virus
That's almost never going to be the first sign you get a butt
Disease spread
Particularly
Rocori virus like this which doesn't kill people immediately
It's pretty impossible to tell what's going to be the case in about a week or two but
Terrible we do not really know at this point
Weather in Decatur is going
Spike in the way that
It did the first time around
And here you have Alex doing everything in his power to make sure that things go worse
Not only on Sunday where Master explicitly discourage
He's telling his audience to avoid going to the hospital if they're sick
Because the doctors
If I believe such a thing were possible I would suggest that Alex is being paid by covid
He's doing all the things that are most likely to facilitate spreading the virus
It's like trying to start a national movement against
Mask-wearing
In attempting to bring a large group
Two people together
He's working overtime to demonize anyone who takes a virus seriously like dr. fauci
The entire CDC
He's building a library
Conspiracy theories to convince
Sick themselves
Would you increase the likelihood that they'll have a more severe case
We're spread it to others
The real world function of how his show is
If you were
If you really look down
If there was a shadow organization of global
With the ex
Licit intent of trying to call the population
No one could be
Be doing a better job for them than
Yeah I mean
It doesn't exist
Imaginary World War 1
He's doing
More illness
Exactly
Alex believes that the only
Thing that's going to work
Is for Trump
To take out design
Sure
But there's a problem
Is running a marxist-leninist co-op play
Every financial publications
Give me the dollar
We are being taken down it's so Criminal
Want to be
Claire's was happening they arrest The Conspirator cuz it's a
What's a globalist
The country so undermined and we're still used to appeasing that it prompted that
Farsang the military's going to kill him
Did not say that was fighting on The Daily Show
Just want to play golf today
China
Retire off
They're not
Country
Wishing I'd done something but if matter
Bread and created
Okay
In the last 50 years
For this moment to bring
Country down the long-term plan
Pink totally collapsed
The average left this is going to be a starving maggot mystery
I mean mister anti-police State Mister anti FEMA camps
Take solace that our enemies will be in Kent
The fuk down
Even further with it about needing to kill folks off
Ecards
He doesn't have the people
Doesn't have the military
Because America is rotten to the Core
So that's an unsettling
To hear from Alex
We would totally have a coup and we will be run by military dictatorship
The control over the military I don't know what's going on why wouldn't he have control over the military
Helicopter ride
Corners of the internet
Use the method of throwing people out of planes and helicopters of the way of killing political dissenters
Term is most directly associated with Chilean dictator Augusto Pinochet
Hughes helicopters
They killed many of the people who posed
Threat to his regime and that's who you want the American president to be relayed
Alexina
In 2015 this started to become a meme on 410 and other unsavory places
Cuz we're posters
Pastor desire to kill their political opponent
By saying that they should go on a helicopter
Relax don't do this specifically because under his rule thousands of Chileans
Executed tortured and turned or disappeared
In a large number of them are what you would call leftist
Finish a rose to office after Roku
Was backed by the United States
Anthony socialist government under President Salvador Allende
Pinochet would rule Chile 1990
Mostly left
No we're all just be a big pile of s*** in the same things happening in Bolivia
That was all bulshit
That was ran over around
Easiest right-wing is taking Pinochet on as a bit of a hero because of
He overthrew an elected left-wing government and then people who are not on board with
This is what people like Alex
Want
These you the 26
16 election is being their version of pinochet's 19-7
33 military coup override
Frustration that Trump has enacted the same power
You can see this all over the
Advances demonstrations you'll frequently see people with free helicopter rides shirt
Or the also popular Pinochet did nothing wrong
This is what Alex wants
He supports Trump because he wants to live in a right-wing dictatorship
Before anyone expressing left thrown out of
What's knocking helicopter
It's pretty much obvious to me all the time
He's just
This is really on this
I was like
Kill everyone
And he goes on like even ask
It's time to get into his weird Syfy
What are the Libertarians are run by the UN will run by China run by Hollywood run by the University
You don't need a big government
We need the government to execute the 45 We the People
Who's Winnie-the-Pooh
Dropped Execute Order 66
It's not going to happen because he doesn't exist
Yes that is true that is true on a sexual base
Enon prequel fans out there
Order 66 was the order that the Sith
Planted in the clothes
Do all Jedi is Traders in this subject
Fusion
Italy very bad guys
Goodguys Jedi talk about a revolution on his lead the count
Savi Empire
You know a lot of people are like
Iran's economy
Of course exploding entire planet
That's worth killing Beyond like
Alex cannot be any clearer that you understand
He's on the evil side
What with rambling about Trump executing orders
B6 and wishing is imagined enemies will be giving helicopter rides
You pretty open about being you just doesn't care anymore
It is obvious
If you're listening to this show and you're into Alex
Whether you realize it or not
Emperor Palpatine
While pretending that you're super into the Constitution
F******
Thirdly sad
Is in some ways a good sign that means they feel like they are really getting their ass
They feel like they're losing
Execute everyone I don't
Because there's
But then that when that happens they tend to start executing people they don't like and then they winning
So we got to keep them from doing that part
And that is
If you ever
I don't know what like
You been in a situation where like you really want it
My carrot and someone
Burger
I am going to go after that carrot
You stare at the character second you're like what
The fuk was that Carol levitating
Alex does a little bit of that
Just wait till after the election happen
Autonomy
Keep it locked
America the blame for the virus
Women lie about all the stuff
Because of their
Going to be destroyed if Trump wins again because they're all going to go to prison
But there's a problem they're going to purge
Don't use your adventure
Our war
Physical War
Lock her up thing the first time around back in 20
Can you put Hillary in prison
But now four years later Hillary is
Nor any of the other folks who Alex
Contraband like
The yellow about Obama Susan Rice
Eric
People on the other hand
So great
His personal lawyer Michael Cohen plead guilty to a bunch of crimes and agreed to cooperate
General Flynn plead guilty to lying to the FBI and would be going to jail if it weren't for the super corrupt Department of Justice
Trump's former campaign manager
Was found guilty of
Do tax fraud four counts of fraud
19 concern really important
He be released from prison due to covid
Not a lot of other
I think I'm going to support it still cuz I need to be hypocritical.
That sucks
I'm not mad about him
United States
45 days in a year probation
Rodger stone is probably going to be in prison within about two weeks unless Trump so you will not
Set this on our show
I would love to see
If this word
Not reality
I would love to
To see Trump humble Rodger by
A little bit
This is reality
I'm concerned the last-minute pardon
But I also think like
What's going on nobody's going to be held accountable
Why can't why can't you self the headache
Did I don't know
Suspect you would have done it right
Whatever
Cute sorters
66 upon his re-election
The only people who are going to end up jail or more people who
He's friends with
Sexy
Tubi
Fiat planet
We had a
Department of Justice
Real
The chance
Conventions coming up
Lee virtual convention
Which is probably for the latest
Decision
Not afraid of the globe
Virtual convention
Virtual convention so they can
By the taquitos
Put into that really planning
President
Repeat
Because I'm a race
The filing deadlines are long past
Is Hillary and Obama wanted to run on a third ticket or like an independent actually still have the time to get the signatures
Stay balanced
Tampa Bay
And it's weirdo fantasy scenario where they're running they will be on the Democratic ticket and that
Like I wouldn't have any belt
No
There isn't a clear winner of the state's primaries
And that's not going to be the case this year already
2171 delegates of the 1990s
Denomination
Bernie was the only other candidate
All of the candidate
The weirdos on the right love
Tulsi gabbard
Have all endorsed Biden
The convention
Virtual
I know Alex obsessed with the idea of Hillary
The coast on anti-hillary
Sentimental
Fundraise office
But I don't really see your way that's going to happen
I don't know my prediction is still however that
Martin Luther King
King junior's granddaughter will be
This year
That's my prediction Trump time traveler
It was like
Alright I'm excited
I'm looking forward to it
The murderers
Tony fauci
CIA
Why they've got a hit team tell me
Kill me
Shut up so you can murder old people
Homeless people killing baby
Spiritually blind
Sun coming High Noon coming to know what happens to people
Will be destroyed
I was just listening to
Add add
Add
You resisted so high
Bananas
Also
So weird
Warning Alex well ahead of time before
Child had a warning that the police are going to kill Emma now as an adult
Assassinate
You don't warn people before you
This morning to gation
Lion
Videos going around on social media of
A woman at a city council meeting
In Florida
Yeah yeah the Parks and Rec
Compare the number of
Alex
Oh my God
This is amazing
Men and women in New York and Florida California
And they're staying
Infowars.com
Were they
Are they scared buddy
Google
I can't
God don't you worry.
So fake
Just
So artificial
Spheal
Like my Human Side almost does feel a certain level of
Because I'm imagining
Putting myself in that space where I have to watch somebody
Who is clearly unwell about
Nonsense and be like
My job is
Is to save that
Great sucks
Yeah
It's a box
You put yourself in
You constantly remind people of his
This is a religious thing for Alex
Like all of this political stuff all these things
Tools like you said it explicitly on the show before
Jesus version
When you try to
Hard to describe you just have to say no
And trusting God but as a man
Constantly feel like I'm
The peace of God
No you are
You cannot be
Beautiful God
So I mean there's like 20 years on the radio I've been yelling about the political machinations of these
Globalist store
The entire time I'm kind of
Analytical
AP communist Joe
Hats Burien
Course
He's the guy who run the website
Genocide
This is all about abortion
You know people aren't shotgun are all over the place this dude's got a very simple idea
He is also still shocked because there's so many different
Things that I'll just
Just ignore
Entire interview cuz I don't
Particularly careful
He kept saying
I said there has to be something
Extraordinary something else
Something that would really impact the election November 2nd January they realized
That indeed there was no way
I went beyond my expectations
I think they got
George Floyd
Very good very good what you got that went right straight home and it's no doubt about it
Every single every single thing is about stock price
November
I just have
Floyd with a gif
Trump
People live in where that's an okay
You know
Is it spelled
Is that is that how you described
So because it's only really in relation to how they feel about
No it's not likely election or the government even is real
Protesting
You know
Conversation now around
Various people who murdered
In the aftermath of that the
The conversation
What's happen
They don't have any feelings
Is there any point that reality doesn't exist outside
To love some
Evil cabal to defeat his
Is hero
And that's weird
Well is it makes sense because for all of these people nothing
Is beyond a tool
The everything is a
Everything is there every news story is there to not react
2 with any kind of
Reality but to
Use as a cudgel against
Your political opponents
There's something to that
The other team
Has to be doing the same thing as well
We're not on their team is because of what
They want to put us in camps
In-depth until on Antioch
They're being paid $300 a day
On the plane and stabbing
They always have a couple of cans missing out of the six pack
Inm
Arrested by the way
Need to know that
People do need to know this
You got a boner
Alex's accosted by
We want to get them on
Reverend Childress has a friend who overheard
Didn't you see all the antifa
Going around Black Block planes
Do great paying extra if we get arrested
Oh my God
Don't f*** out of here massive conspiracy
I guess starting a race war
God there's nobody
Do they not get the message with me and come on what's going on
Alright
So Chris has another
About black lives matter
Not very good
Black life matters website
Basically says they're against the West
Family idea
How how they feel that that is a western
Ideology and not anything that would be conducive to the world
Is matter website there is a section titled what we believe
Following paragraph
We disrupt the western-prescribed nuclear family structure requirement
By supporting each other as extended family
Collectively care for one another
Especially our children
To the degree that Mother's parents and children are comfortable
This is intentionally misrepresented by right-wing conmen to imply that they want to just
Inclusion
And it approved
Community that issues the requirements
The people be nuclear family to be family
You know that old saying it takes a village to
Made That explicit
That represents thousands of years of human existence realizing that raising a child by yourself
Tell me one other person
Is not as
As successful as raising them as a community
Actually destroyed
Dad
Yeah you notice
When every Church calls their congregation a family
Because we understand
Concept perfectly well
Maliciously weaponizing fears about it in this case because it's part of the social
They feel threatened
People that'll do more than enough to get a plenty of people on your f****** side
It is next
Reverend Childress
Bringing up the legacy of Martin Luther King
In order to
Do you like life matter
Profound profit
In this nation that brought about social change dr. Martin Luther King
1 Savage faded love
Nonviolent
Don Garlits assertively looting
Breaking a glass
Far be it for me to pretend that I fully understand.
Complete scope of the legacy of Martin Luther King jr.
The Reverend Childress
The 110 King's most famous quote a riot is the language of the
John heard
Expanded on this point in the speech given in 1967 at Stanford
In a real sense our nation
Summers of riots are caused by our nation's winters of delay
And as long as the America postpones just
We stand at the position
I'm having these recurrences of violence and right over and over again
Social justice and progress of the absolute guarantee
The riot prevent
Martin Luther King was a proponent of nonviolent resistance
But he was also pretty clear that right
Not getting anywhere
That's the whole unheard part of the equation
Misconception which I agree with for the most part for no reason
People who feel they have access to non-violent means to effect
Do not write it as their first stop
Generally speaking I don't know
I don't know if I can think of it exactly
We have spent
So much
Next time.
King even denounced the people who save it black folks riding only leads to anger
Black power and riots
The Harlem's in the other areas
Are the consequence
Backlash
Rather than the cause of the
By the end of 1967 there were strong indications that can't get changed his mind and embraced Mariah
It doesn't matter protest
He gave a speech at the America
Psychology Association Convention
Included the following
Urban riots must now be recognized as durable
They may be deplored
Should be understood
Urban Riot sorry special form of Iowa
The writers are not seeking to seize territory or to attain control event
Institutions
Community
Distorted form of social
The protest
Eluding which is the prince
Teacher serves many function
It enables the most enraged and deprived negro
Consumer goods
He's the white man does
By using his purse
I was reading a piece that in timeline
Abdurraqib
The matter of Martin Luther King's stance on violence
Particularly in the context of how Alex
Try to use
Quote
Beyond The Mists attributed quotes and bad memes in poor logic
Maiden his name the real tragedy
Do so with a fundamental perversion of his message
Non-violence as it is discussed in fetishize in proximity to the poor and or the marginalized
It's so often dragged out
In response to any uprising
The riot is the language yes
But the response to the riot is also
The language
Nicole is for peace and love but
True demand is for complete silence all together
NFL player takes money without speaking and is threatened in Haiti
Call the violent Thug in a racist
Colors no protest can be peaceful enough
If somebody hadn't murdered Martin Luther King and he was still alive today I have a hunch that he would be on
Inside the protest
West Point I want to make
Because Martin Luther King
That in no way means that everyone has
Have to do that in order to be
The protesters
You can absolutely hate the people your protest
You're just as valid in your act
Anybody else
This all boils down to
Distorting is Martin Luther King
Respective
People like Alex do to invalidate any protein
They don't lie
Well I mean
The cereal to mately is
Nonviolent protest
Is the non-violence
Are the ones you want
Table
In the
The violent protesters are how you get them
That's the reality
Because we've seen how many we see millions of women March
And not a goddamn thing
We've seen a few weeks of protests
With
Property damage
Holyshit
Another thing
I've been done
Look I don't want to should be negotiating our future
Diversity of tactics
Can be an important element
Protoss
But I think in terms of particularly when you talk about Martin Luther King and his stance on this stuff
A large part of it is
Isn't so much what you're saying
In terms of like we need somebody
To set up
His position was largely position was more like
What do you think of
This is this is
Part of
What happened
When
Things aren't
Done
The
You know
4 piece when there is
Cornell parties
Just
Peaceful protest
President
Individualism
Distance is exist
Within a spectrum of things that have happened
Pretend that there's
Some sort of a
Unique or overriding
Mobility for people who
Commit property damage
Get off the hook
All of the people who had
The winters of inaction that led to that summer of Acts
The understanding
From people like Alex
The Reverend children
Play come on
And try and Martin Luther King's name
The protest
Disgusting
Mainly because
They are using Martin Luther King jr.
To say
Get back in your pee
Orpheus settle down
Rate
Be quiet
Waetford
That'll work
It'll work this time I know it's America
Letter from a Birmingham Jail
For another day
So prize matter apparel
I would want to touch on here then
A specifically contoured made up to the region the country that you are in
Audiology major draw you out
Hey because this nation is always battle with race what do you think he would come
But with black lives matters
The after
He wants to change the definition of family
Husband
Control everyone
Absolutely but is a devil is making it up so it's going to be good
How many left
Countries
Does the CIA need to topple before we just consider them not
The left
CIA
I don't know
Alex
The left-right CIA
Really the devil created
Back to a board
Childress
Planned Parenthood
Races of her time
Adolf Hitler
Right
We happened to is it
Is it
They don't want to see you
Just the stress that everything is due to the bad boils down to anti-abortion
Either one issue Gaston Alex's only existence
Bounce can't really be racist because the real
Sister people who support reproductive right
Did not like Margaret
In fact her work was burned
The Purge of 1933
Along with the writings of Freud in Magnus hirschfeld
One of the reasons that the Nazis hated her is because her main work
Even if they want to say now everything's about abortion
Remain work with about birth control and family planning
Which ran counter to the goals of the Third Reich
Which was to create as many Aryan children as possible
If not see women work
Fall under the sway of these radical theories about birth control and self
Determination
The plan would be harder to pursue
Similarly Sanger hated Hitler
It was a member of the America
Council against Nazi propaganda
Germany
Singer was a proponent of some ideas
That is definitely true
I do not try to pretend that's not the case
To work my way to peace
She's explicit that any definition of quote
Could not be based on race or religion
Still reviews
I think a little bit of
Scratch
Yeah yeah yeah like there's a lot of there's a lot of stuff
Is on Fortune
Stuff
Does not
This is a load of historical revisionism
Just because I don't like it
And have family planning
Sanger was one of the
Was beef most devout racist overtime
Does he know who's around during her tongue
Explaining
You boarded like 1879
Racist
Outrageous
Yeah let's never forget
Just f****** dudes
To some extent
So
Reverend Childress has
Skype problem
And Alex
Is devil
He's trying to deal with
Announce
Average shoulders
What's getting back on the next few weeks
Pokemon once a year we on
Brushing crazy
Rasmussen poll
40% of African-Americans likely voters
Say
Donald Trump
Am I interested or really take
The only reason I clip is bond is because of the
Sky place
And then also because Alex says that Reverend
That interview won't go well
You hate Trump because him
Tribulation Trump
Oh my God
If Manning comes back on
I cannot wait for that episode
It's going to go like
2 minutes
Going to hang up on me
Trump is intentionally bringing
Sing about the end of the world
Forgotten
There's a reason he's not
The end of this episode here on the 25th
And he makes it clear
As he did earlier that God is the only way forward
Sure
U-god
Knock knock
The other guy
You all know it I'm sorry for people
Or whatever
Osher
No atheists in foxholes
Other religions you got steered wrong when you were a kid
Yeah I feel like
Pretty high tolerance
For people who like preach
Transcendence
Transcendental Meditation
You like the idea of what do you have wrong with David Lynch
I don't want to get into it
I don't have a problem with people who are like really big
Recognizing
Things outside yourself religion
Christianity Judaism Islam
Shintoism
Connection with something large
Histamines
That's all you yeah I mean
Sure yeah
I don't have a problem
People who are like
One of the most important things for us moving forward is recognizing
You know this Transcendent ability that we all have within us
I think there's a really easy way to it be an entry point to a scam
Self is that toxic but once you start getting into
You only my version of transcendence is real the Restoril I
That's when it's
It's like a man
This is
You're doing culture
It's really ugly
We get into the 20
And you're a familiar refrain
But this one is going to be particularly over the top
Everything I'm going to be covering is Mega bombs
Mega bombshell Salon stop your car open your window get other
Other people know this is just a really important
We didn't stop traffic
So
And Deborah
On the NIH website
Rochelle you this coming up
Mitch
That the mask
Does not
Keep you from breathing
Viruses are bad
Live longer than they would
Allowing it to the NBA spread
Which is why we won the reason
Diagnosed
But there
Keep people indoors and they're wearing the mask
That are
Weapon system
Totally unfiltered
In the fabric
Urban Air
Erlanger
There's a few very basic problems with what Alex is saying
DC DC and different organizations
Has the same thing
They're both part of the Department of Health and Human Services
The CDC is focused on response control and prevention
As it relates to public health issues
Where is the NIH is primarily a research
Institution
These groups can work hand-in-hand and they complement each other but Alex
Birthday which is just dumb
Also fun fact
CDC head for the entirety
Is two terms
So far in just one term Trump has appointed
Four different people to leave that group
Not good
Not good cuz they all nailed
Two there's no article about this on Infowars website
There's one article titled Michelle
Face Max Max proven
But that's just a page that has an embedded video of this episode of his show
Is 0 information orally
Thanks for Everything to learn more
Justin Trudeau
If this were the case that somehow wearing masks were a brief time with detrimental to your health
Doctors nurse
Dentist Nasser to help professionals will be dropping like flies
When Alex brings up the specifics later I'll get into it but when I was listening to
Wild goose
Chase on the CDC and NIH has website
Whatever he's lying about
I'll also
That totally unrelated
Reported on the case of
Delete organizer of reopen Maryland
Who was an aggressive campaigner against
Turns out he tested positive for covid-19 after developing vision
Problems a headache
And a fever
Suggested he has recently come into contact with
However he's refusing to cooperate with Maryland contact tracers by provider
Contain the virus
She doesn't blame basic science for his getting sick
You've decided that seat from covid-19
Before getting sick which
Is really cool thank you
What
That's
In public without a mask
For testing positive
Infection
He may not have a chance to do that because
Three-year-old said
While admitting he does not mean to
Maintain healthy habits
Obviously this dude doesn't represent everyone on his side of things represent at least some percentages
People who
Cannot understand
It's because
Does the thing
Most likely
Yeah this is
This is literally
Like
Cambrian levels
Newsies from history
Like this is obviously the lightning struck two days ago which is why I have
Covid-19
Everyone around him
My caring for someone else
No he should be
Kept inside of his home under house arrest
That's the only reason we know about that story is because it
It's newsworthy because he ran one of these protests
I don't know
What is the numbers
The people who
Who knows
Where is Joe Biden
20 million people died in the US
40% of the US population.
That is not true it's 110,000 and almost
Here's the Peruvian
Drastically underestimate is the impact on Mental Health
People who now everything's complicated
Not only is the health-care peace but
People don't have a job people don't have anywhere to go
They don't know what they're going to do
People you have
Unnecessarily now we have over 120 million dead
From covid
I mean
What is a contact
What was going to say
Such classic Alex man
Got that part off
Like it's so clear if you listening
Immediately corrected himself cuz he misspoke
Now we have over 120 million dead from covid
I mean 120,000 detrapel
This is just fake outrage
That message
Across the public
You just misspoke
That's the full context it doesn't get more wacky
Alex is just a fraud and a liar
Can't believe
That his
Super competent
Would it cut that clip
The part where he says I mean
Yeah because everybody is already assumed what he's going to
To say next
I found
That they on YouTube.
Alex sees people
Terrible I really
More
There is so much to breakdown
So much to cover today
For everybody
Because it's so incredibly
Important
Do you understand
CDC
Dot-gov
Shotgun
The disease
Page four
Page 4 of the website
Picture of the website
According to what
Page for the cdc's website website
Are you my grandma
Cdc.gov
Backslash
Page four
Right
First thing here
He's talking about
Because page for a website isn't
N95 mask do not the same thing as the face mask
About you
Even so everything I can find on the cdc's website says that they have a general filter
Efficacy of 95%
All the cdc's page titled recommendation regarding the use of
Cloth face covering
The facemasks are recommended to slow the
Spread of the virus
And that you should not be using n95 mask
But not because they don't work
Quotes
Cloth mask covering recommended or not surgical mask
Or n95 respirators
Those are critical supplies that must continue to be reserved for healthcare workers and other first
America first
Responders
Alex's team is big news but he's provided no one
Navigation
Information
For the cdc's website
Which is almost worse than him saying nothing
More confusing
Is Page 4
To him
What does he think page for of a website
He has
Sheets of paper that says
Some intern printed out and it's on the fourth page
Yeah
From other than okay
It's something on the cdc's website that one of his staff printed off
Auntie fourth page of
Print out
I got nothing this is stupid
If you're listening to this
And now Alex's and complain about everyone
Two of the western person is going down like a lead
Zeppelin
We got a bunch of zombie like
People raging
Or web page website
On what page is
When we come back election
Giant special it is there it is
July special
It's not
Earlier
Much better different day but
So let's get down to business
Gives out
The URL
This is very good
This is from the Centers for Disease Control
Pretension
Not wear them unless you're real
For something hitting
But even bigger
Coronavirus disease 2009 personal protection equipment
Questions and answers
CDC
Here's a URL CDC.
Ncov
4 / 18
Or / respirator
HTML
Not a real URL do this to any website
One thing when he says Hep it should be h
Also I can
Reading the year
If he signed 2009 which it sounds like he is
Then this camping information about covid-19
Possibly be about H1 N1
Hulu
Concern that year
I suspect he's just misreading 2019 but I'm honestly not sure
Yeah either way doesn't
Matter
And it instantly becomes clear what he's messing up here
Play Telluride here
Which five
Let me
The sterile field
Other people that you're wearing it
You got it
Expose others when it do
Nothing except
So the first hint that he's not talking about normal facemasks is the reference to an exhaust valve
No I'm pretty sure I know cuz I know references made us
Masks with valves
Which are different from cloth
Umask typically have a mechanism which opens when the where
Defeats the purpose
If you were I wearing that
The goal is to contain droplets
Which could infect other people that opened every time you exhale
He sort of masks are specifically designed as protective to the wearer with no concern for what the wearer might be putting back into
The environment
Be specific sort of masks with valves typically for using industrial settings Orion Construction
Well the n95 mask
That healthcare workers
Same
So they don't risk
Patients getting sick while
Okay so Alex grabs
The one example of
The CDC literally you actually saying like
Here's the max you should wear and here's the mask
Shouldn't
Reporting on how you should wear these
In spite of covid-19
In 30 seconds on Google I was able to find a phone article
Explaining that you should
You just not use these
There was the Daily Mail back on April 28th
Insider on May 28th space company from April 28th Boston
There's plenty more
This is old news and Alex's pretending it's a bombshell
Weird Masters effective in stopping particles and droplets
Spreading from your mouth endo's
This efficacy drops when you haven't
Exhalation valve it opens up and lets out these particles
This is common sense
And there's nobody got your moment
The guidance to wear masks
These specific types are not effective for these purposes that are not recommended
You could wear medical n95 mask
Because those need to be direct
Did the medical professionals who need them boards
Can you do
Very simple
Or unable to the approximately
2 minutes of work that would be required to report on this correct
I think if it's not laziness or inability that creates
It's that will
Knows that the blurb he's reading has nothing to do with normal Mass reading
He's just intentionally lying
Pretend it's related
How could you
And read
Valves
Wait what
Does this mean
Literally hurting
Listening
Into you
This is premeditated
This is Criminal negligence
Premeditated
You're somebody who
Alex's legit
Stop
And you're listening to him read this thing about this
CDC
And their masks with valves
You're not thinking like
No mask I've ever seen
People wearing generally when I go down to the grocery store.
What the f*** he's talked about maybe I should look into
Patrick Swayze survive this situation
They do recommend
So Alex gets complaining about
I was just
Primarily
How's they want to get involved
Vaccine development in this particular case
Andreescu
The idea of countries having a bidding war
Overview
This vaccine
Because you could artificial
Right to the point where people who were in The
Simultaneously she's discussing
How there are communities who have different
Grades of need
For the vax
Maybe more pressing
Really matter
There are six
Sure workers around the world
Be safe
Population
Country that would be
Additions
Okay
Ideally there will be universal access for a potential vaccine against developed
Communities aren't needed than others
Princeton
Myself
But I recognize that I'm very lucky
Be relatively young in relatively decent shape
Have no pre-existing
Conditions that put me at risk
If I'm able to work from home
That sucks though I would want a vaccine as soon as I can get
I will gladly postpone getting one if there's a situation where people who are at higher risk than me the demographics
Or because of their line of work
If they need to get vaccinated first
That's great
That's basically all Melinda Gates is getting at
It's not something nefarious
Dean has been showing Betty disproportionate number of black Americans are getting covid-19
Systemic problems that are
Phenomenon like
Over-representation in service industry
These were social distancing a difficult Orange
Predominantly black communities
Empire incarceration
According to a study put out by the Chicago
The underlying problem
Save a bunch of liars
Which is good
Also I'm at Melinda Gates for not including incarcerated persons on her list of people who should have a high priority
See Jordan it's possible to agree with her underlined
Little Park
You know that she has a decent she fails to recognize one of the largest groups that needs
To be helped
The highest priority
However what you're missing
Is that she only mentioned
Because there are the targets of the vaccine first to Kill Them All
Them outside
Point Blank.
Wood
You if you have a vaccine that kills
Why would you first give it
To help.
That makes no sense
Right and then our terrible before she says people who work at
Grocery stores in
Be packing plants
Suffolk that are also considered in her wave of like see people who are in the most
Stupid Alex is just trying
Find to race bait
Interesting to me that he never really bothered to learn what her name is
Who's running the health department
In Seattle in 1983
And I was on the board
He was a banker
She was the first
Woman on
Major corporate board United States
Husband
What is mrs.
Bill Gates
Mother is named Marianne Maxwell mrs. Bill Gates
Cuz he married his mother
Back in 1975
Then she's from South Africa
Number two
So good on her
In 1983 she became the first female head of the United Way
That's what I was
She never ran the Seattle health
Department which it actually isn't
Nothing
There's the King County Public Health Department
Department of Health but I don't know what Alex is talking about
You claiming the Bill Gates mom ran a thing that you got the name of wrong and he can't even be bothered to know her name
Isabel just doesn't give a f*** about a incredible at all
Except whatever so did you know that mrs. Bill Gates
Who created covid
Did you know that
I got to go
Alright alright
So Alex
Skip's another guest this is weird
Amazing
Was good
Read no one else wants to go on my show anymore
Yaser Alex
Before and he's like
No matter what show you're doing
I mean
Could be fun
Like if you're having a show where like
I don't know
You know Chris gethard
Yeah Alexander
Not bad
This is
Infected can be transcended
Text talks about that
This guy
Great genius
Rebel sadrian Church
I'm just going to be straight up
I see people with mask on
Understand
And give site
To the blind so
If he wasn't scared to touch
Coronavirus map
Come to me
For you I stand in the Gap right now
Images Clarence of Jesus
I'm more concerned about this
Denial
You know like
Just sort of a
There is no cure for anything other than
You have to first allow the virus into your body
Well that is true
Which you should have done
And if you would just taking my $6,000 a month course
You would never have done that we are like
Really close to snake
Lightning is why you got sick
Yeah so
Stephanie has another guest
And I did
Give a
Come over all without you
Right now.
He saw why he did it in
Where he thinks this is all going
Thank you so much for coming on
Iowa.
Gofundme.com
Portal
Facebook Insider
You obviously sacrifice your job a lot more
What is another project Veritas
So whatever comments I had about the first guy
Apply them here
I will say this guy
Because
Is GoFundMe
He's not making nearly as much as the other guy
When I checked out but it was only like 45
I don't think
I don't think either of them are going to hit their hundred fifty thousand gold
You don't you don't want to be
This guy is going to have just as much
Like
Google ability for future jobs
And stuff he wants to try and
If you just Google his name you'll now come up with a bunch of
Project
And he's not even give the payout
The other dude
You just
So
I don't care about you
That Alex has it
Coming up this weekend
Talk about that here
This Sunday I know Texas capitals outside
Stupid racist bowl-shaped
The name
I wanted to play that clip because
Since the last episode recorded
Oh boy Alex posted an article with the headline
Newmar New Movement hijacked
I can't breathe meme to protest masks in public
The first is that before they had any events
Before there's any
A movement
There's no
Grassroots
Sad
Satyr is back
I can't breathe
I understand that he's a racist an opportunist but even struggle to release
You would think the basic human decency would stop you from taking multiple people's Last Words as they were being killed by police
Just use them for your unrelated
Publicity stunt
There's a coherent
When black lives matter protest
I can
Free or they use that term on a side
They're protesting against police brutality which is the reason those words were uttered in the first
It makes sense
It's not in the sense that Alex uses that word
It's a distillation of
The protest message
Brings to the Forefront the seriousness
A big issue being protest
Galaxy seems to think that because he believes that they're just demonic globalist opportunistically using George Floyd's
Stephan order to usher in a dictatorship
You can just use the
The power of those words
And then use them for his own purposes
We fail to understand is that much like Thor's hammer
This is a weapon he can't
And the words have no power
His attempts to harness what's behind these words
But he thinks or just a meme
Is desperation and his cravenness
This probably wouldn't be enough to just by talking about this again
But I thought there was something hilarious about the
Disposed
Alex is really trying to pretend that he didn't
Start this whole thing
The article begins quote
Freedom lovers in Texas have launched we can't breathe out of here
Trying to act like he trying to create
God what a f****** dick
Third person
Freedom lover
Who will be attending
However they slip up and start using the first person we
About halfway through the post
Stupid
But they're trying to mask
Pun intended
I think that they've probably learned it when they do things that are Infowars branded is a little too true
Trying a different approach
I want to say that
This is super Dane
On Saturday the Austin american-statesman reported that quote
Austin Hill
Health officials last week saw the highest rate of positive coronavirus test of any Metro area in the
Austin mayor Steve Adler Warren quote if you venture out know that you are multiples more likely to get
Infected today
Then two weeks ago
Facilitate
If you wanted to
I saw some videos earlier today from the feeds of Alex's protest
There may be a few hundred people there I'm
My estimate
It was a horrible turnout compared to other
Recent protests
What part of Alex's planned is really slow and kind of funny when you think about it is there's a giant
Gate in front of the governor's mansion
So you just had a bunch of people outside of gate without yelling a bunch of
Phrases into a PA system
During Alex's speech of the camera person Panda round the audience
Depressing disappointing for him
And hopefully doesn't end
Killing anyone
Favorite does that
That's on him
A clip that literally on her
I mean you literally said mask-wearing is discouraged
Kill them
If somebody dies
Who is that that rallies
This might kill them
He didn't
Freedom lovers in Texas
Okay I like maybe this is
Dodge culpability in the possibility that there are some
Some negative outcome so funny to me that he tries to co-opt
Like other right-wing
Protests in and make them about him and this time now he's trying to call up
His own protest
To make it about him and act like it's not
So
Alex
Embarrassed
Someone to admire
Course on our last episode Alex.
I was talking about
Speck in the sea
Edward Griffin
He is a weirdo of the highest order
And
Because of the popularity
60s was getting traffic to rounded
All these social media
From
G Edward Griffin
Does not have a problem with Alex
Cuz Alex going to Wayback Hayden Federal Reserve
And you know
They know each other from Ron polish Circle
Do things together
Immigration vaccine
Directions
Google
I don't want to
Please
I'm talking with a gif
Talking to someone I can't disrespect was troubling
But I want him to use the military
Guess what
Because he doesn't want to talk about that
Easy slam dunk
Abortion
Directions
Yumeko by not able to talk A-Rod
These these
Passage there
Really interesting here is of course I was talking s*** about the Democrat
It is not
When I got other people have the same
That's a good question
Maybe they really don't intend to
Maybe they
For some reason they want
That's horrible.
So now you g Edward Griffin
Globalist
President
Is anathema
He said for the last 45 years
Cannot coexist with that idea
G Edward Griffin wrote the beast from Jekyll Island
Early
Never meet your Heroes
Not handle this
So
It leads to
Probably wanted
Embarrassing things I've ever heard Alex
Deal under Obama
Started
And for
Global Assault Apopka
And then we can negotiate better with China for a better deal
Even know this but he's been putting in
A broker to get China to come to heal with
Hitler and Stalin together
Who is that
What are you doing buddy is trying to be popular and he's in there
You trying to gauge everything any drawn from a swamp
So if you need an indication that I was having a bad time with this interview it's really just said that
Wow
Which Alex
Invalidation of literally
Everything
First contradiction is at the globalist
You were supposed to have been working tooth-and-nail to stop Trump from winning the election
They carried out election fraud
Obama spied on Trump
But now Alex's suggesting that the globalists there was populism
That's a gigantic problem for Alice's narrative because
If that's what he believes
Email us to find an explanation for the last 4 years
Globo's decided to step aside and let Trump in
Is Alex ready to admit he was making up everything about people being bussed in to vote
Is he ready to admit that there wasn't a grand conspiracy to enjoy
Craft Trump Associates that led to
I would imagine he's not because he knows the G ever Griffin
Isn't just going to blindly go along with
G Edward Griffin doesn't need Alex's dumbass
He's a legend of anti-communism
Jim
The second big contradiction In that clip is at the globalist decided to get Trump into office to get a better negotiating position with China
And also they're trying to kill him
Simultaneous
Problem here is that according to Alex to go blistering bed with
They're basically partners and all the evil plans Alex yelled about all the time
Idiot president
In order to get a better negotiating position
If there was some gold
All the surface this is nonsense but I was just saying
You're not very short clip Alex's directly contradicted
A giant part of his shows mythology
Also
Not ignored
I think Trump is Hitler
Yeah yes
If you assume China is the standing for Poland to sides are negotiating about intellect the globalist
Obviously
Which of these Trump as Hitler
Seems like a bad thing for Alex
He is a white nationalist
Alex doesn't mean
He's just trying to appease this legendary anti-communist gas
Who clearly doesn't
Any pics
Alex is bending the knee to Griffin
Because he knows he can't defend his position
Any far-right than him
More willing
To just go directly at it
Is Alex he's not going to try and maintain his relationship
And I think he's full of s***
I will say everything I understand about him
So like I don't
Going to pee
Oh yeah
Alex Auld
Yes and with you
Nothing matters
And so when G Edward Griffin gives him some sort of push back on like
Yeah you know because the establishment in the globalist
What Trump to be in power Alex create an entirely new line
Instant Natasha Desai
Whatever gets me out of narcissistic psychopath
How could you suppose that be if you listen to be shown
I don't know I don't know
Yeah I just don't know I don't know how anybody could listen to the show without experiencing some serious
Something in your brain has two
You have to give up
And
Submit these as
One reason
Alex
God one reason from G Edward Griffin
Nobody should ever support
They're not necessarily being presented as bad thing
Which I think
Weird
Yours yours Alex
Looking at rum
You got to know how manipulative
Come out and say Bill Gates is more powerful than him
Emily the president
Marshall
The problem with Trump is literally
If we just run headlines that Bill Gates is more
He's one of the president then trouble stopping
Which we need we should say no
He's killing people he's evil
He's a globality vagina
He's a baby that he's a gullible morons
Loud it is
Easy to manipulate the president of the United States who has nuclear weapons
Hugo and his appeal to the presidency go and then he will crush your enemies
Drop that guy over there says he's stronger than you like what can you do
How do you think that's the president a man with an iron will incorruptible
You can just say anything to him and make him feel into insecure and then Oak Hill
Oh man
I would say there's almost no more compelling argument for like
Not voting for him
There's that there's no more compelling argument for me
You think that that's a possibility
Well this is my first this guy
Because obviously he's not saying that there's like a necessary lie like a great
You saying it is because one of his human failings look we all have lines
That's a big
That might be the biggest one you could
Right
Basically be the president
Situation
Synergy
He has his own thing
President for many decades
Is not
His own authority
He takes directions
Text directions
Billions of dollars
Text directions from people who
Call the Deep state
Even though he's out there saying he's against the
Good pivot therealak City don't want to talk about
Billionaire donors
A boy that sounds like something that everybody's known forever
Connor
We're just going on
What are we
Legacy
Type guys
Sounds unless so because
Most of his credibility come through being related to W Cleon skousen
His own accord
And so the conversation of the two of them have theirs
Entire power imbalance
Because also Diego different
As interested as someone like Steve pieczenik
And just abusing Alex
Griffin has his own
He has his own books that he sells
He doesn't need Alex's a promotion
The dynamic there is
Pretty fascinating and I think Alex comes out
Strongly
Oh yeah
I would find that to be
If I
After work that day
And I was Alex and I was like
I just f******
Inset on-air that the
Globalist wanted Trump to win and maybe they
Only using him to get a better
Bargaining position with
A globe
It sounds like Alex is taking this out of the glove
I don't know man
It's sad
On your side of town
Yeah we'll see what happens
Next episode
That's the best rally anyone ever seen
Yeah I look forward to that quite a bit
Next episode
Ross on Twitter
You could please find a local charity
I need a loan.
Omio I believe
G Edward Griffin
The Griffin is the mythical animal
Alex