Air Jordan X swetik
I have great respect for its knowledge by now I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Just a little bit about Alex Jones
Jordan Jordan
What up
You go first
Is I9 has finally followed me on Twitter
Twitter great rapper items
Congratulation
When we went to see the show with Evan far out
He and I talked about
Servant
And he decided that he would not follow me on Twitter until you'd seen Avatar
Sure
Do you on the following congratulations to I-90
Couch
Jordan
The mailbox
So
There's nothing on the table here.
I drank it
This was from Michigan
Okay girl has a little brain called No Miano am I
Particularly in a funk yesterday and I needed
Something
Right tackle
Seltzer's
Top of the mountain peaks
Everything was really good
68 and 75 out of 100
Secular that was at 75
You do flavors
Michigan cherry lime
But they were all fine outside
When is a cherry
Right
Figured out what the difference is bday
It did brighten my day
I was thrilled to get to the end of the evening and realize I just drank
What's the weather on the subject I want to say something really quick
Leaving point now where I'm starting to realize there's certain things that I've learned
Okay
Is carbonated water
Exactly how to say
What I want to say
Strawberry
Is pretty much always good
He's like weird Brands off brands at the dollar store
Strawberry seltzer
Probably going to be
Okay
Talk to f****** a strawberry
Yes sir
There are other flavors that are not
Cucumber
Cucumber you don't like you I don't trust you
Grocery store brand I don't trust you to f*** around with you cover
Yeah
It's not
Such a broad
Cucumber something is going to be okay
Yours
Good and gather Target brand
Don't cry
You're putting on airs
And you shouldn't
These ones that are safe like a strawberry
Cranberry is almost impossible to f******
Flower
Stick to the shallow water raspberry is fine to Bethel University good
Basic Berry flavors
You can handle
Leave it to the pros
You're finding a lot of ways to say exactly what I'm trying to get to me
Appreciate
Synthesized did quite well
So Jordans
Episode to go over gone over
Troubling
Episode
Oh boy
Coming back
His triumphant return
Like Napoleon returning from Elba
Show
I'm a policy wonk exam
Juvenile policy walk
I try
Crystal
Initials
Jake
Thank you so much
Just I was trying to
Maybe
Next
Democrat
We got to go
What's the business
Heroin
Yes thank you very much
If you're up there listening
Generosity and redirect
That would also be wonderful
Appreciate
Here's another complex dropped
From how this episode sort of wine
Signs of the end
This has been one of the most powerful broadcast we've ever did absolutely jam packed
Empathetic
Let's go
I love it
The best job possible and I feel like an empty
Fraud of accomplishment you received whenever you're
Add makes you feel pathetic
So we start here on the 29th and the Alex
To talk and if this doesn't sound good
If I were just like looking at this
Organization from like
If I heard him say this I would probably think like
It doesn't bode well
Infowars.com
Newswars.com
Summit. News
Infowars
A frappe
Doesn't look like there's a c
Ship the rats are trying to run away from
Paul is an interesting case
It's because he has his own sort of unique fanbase and he still other places
Disseminate his videos and
Uno's kids
It seems to be drawn to his whiny face in the Quick Cuts
But like
David Knight and Owen Shroyer are less popular than Infowars
You can make an argument is bigger than infowar
So is he
Having his own thing
Kind of makes sense
David Knight
Return by creating their own property
Or their own entities
That seems like a bad plan
Did it go well
I feel like you can just figure out from the number of
Views on bam. f****** video
Alright no you just look at the difference in
BO2
I got my own site now I'm not with him
Destroying
Talking about how you know this is going to
To be a civil war going on right
Cold
This might as well be
The slowest of slow cooker
I'm pretty sure for some kind of a
Cold War
The moves I believe we should make
Stop it
But
Let me just first tell you that is Rodger stone is breaking his silence
He's got a few interviews
Exclusively
After
Big events
But he's decided to just go ahead and
Silence
Tomorrow
Let me to decode that
Rodger expect
Could be pardoned by now
Before apart
What's happening
There's really not much more substance to it than that
Please don't totally
Rogers
Almost his entire appearance is just like campaigning for Trump
It's selling himself as like if I don't have to go to prison
I will be one of the most powerful
It's exactly what you should do your Rodger Mako media tour
Much you can help Trump
Make it seem like people will take you seriously again
So there's two things
Most of the show about
29th Street
Night show any story
Okay
The best way to do this
Track number to headlines
We were facing an angry mob.
Tell their side of the story
Zerohedge
Can you believe that these people have to
Tell their side of the story black lives matter
Go into their private estate
Open the gate
Private estate
An inside
Then they said after the people said get off her
Whitelivesmatter says that's it we've
The money shot
Baeza protesters in St Louis
What street that is fair enough
Emplaced
But the only did that because the other streets to the mayor's residence had been blocked off
And the point
I'm straight at the mayor's house
Speakers
Read the names and addresses of people calling for police reform during a Friday afternoon Facebook live video
The mare was essentially dachshund
Protest outside her home
As we walked past this deranged couples house they came out
Pretend they needed to protect their home
It's all going well for them to have guns on their property and to stand there at the protest goes by then they're right
If there's a
Fine
Finger on the trigger and was pointing at people
That's not cool at all
Responsible gun ownership
You should know that there's a massive difference between holding a gun safely and waving it around like an a******
Open carrying at a rally that Owen tried to go to
Attempted murder basically
In this case however the gun is being pointed at people Alex wants
Gun pointed at
Sports the person holding the
That's simple
Game is very stupid
He spends a lot of time on the story
So we talked about it a little bit more and
What about this
Couple
Regardless
This is summer
Lawyer
Mansion
Boston to your house there's a big mob of 500 people what it was
You better
Come out with your house robbed
So you can hear hear this like people calling him a hero
Fruits that they're not Heroes
Is at their Democrat
Alright
The names are Mark and Patricia McCloskey
Because they were homeowners association
This was about allowing same-sex couples who couldn't get married at the time to live in the neighborhood
Since previously they would have had to be considered roommates which wasn't permitted by the homeowners association
So they were fighting to uphold the anti cohabitation
Trying to restrict the neighborhood from having same-sex couples
To also be a big actually Democrat
It's not clear from what I was able to find what political party are registered to
Federal election
Commission records
Contributed thousands of dollars to the Trump make America great again
The Republican National Committee
8819 96
Sounds like a classic Democrat to me
Alex talked about it
So much
Call Derek
Take the bow
Story that Alex talked about
Almost the entire episode
How to write down on notes
In my in my
He won't stop talking about
It seems really weird to me because
This is one that I
Sacha Baron Cohen who says
The Free Speech arrest Alex Jones
A monstrous individual
Reopen America
Event
And he says
I'm a country singer
All I can pay for
He gets very short saying racist stuff they run up and try to stop it
Men
Stop them
Mohican frame
Free
Sacha Baron Cohen so funny
He's a false
Swaggin slimy Criminal
That was supposed to be really didn't see any people
Singing
6 minute video that I watched nokat Senator anything
Lot of people singing along
For liking shopping up
Journalist
Injecting bauchi and Hillary with the number times any one of those people
Scuse me any want just one
Any reason why
I mean like it's the same thing with a lotto Sacha Baron Cohen
Feel something
With
By the acceptance of
Doing something that's like oh wow that's awesome
Permission
To let this show
At a place like a three percenter rally
LOL I'll let you just ignore this honestly
Every time
They get caught my hopes
Tuesday should just be like
Everybody
Manages to ignore
You would think
It would just be another
Goddamn much like half the episode
Can't get foreign liberals over here revealing that my friends
It's wild
So I'm only going to play
Because of what happens on the 3rd
Talking about how
Or at least I'm sorry
Half of
Telling you folks
Pedophilia is just
The top half of the body hold onto that for later on the 30th
Has a little bit of a break.
Half pedophilia
But I'd like to think that it happened
You know it's real optimist
Sure
Pretty racist
Search rambling around about Colin Kaepernick a little bit
Straight straight
I don't know what
Are you doing here man
I just I don't know what the point
Kezar monster
He's nothing but a
Black shield
You represent black people now
You do not understand hair
Is that
What is
What are you doing
Nike told Colin Kaepernick to wear his hair in a certain way
Can you call me
Alex do you know anything
About Colin Kaepernick
Family of origin
Do you know anything about that
Now you.
Just talkin
It's wild to me when
Bigger trees and biases are more compelling to a person than curiosity
Scream about something
That you could easily check into and you just don't
Oh man how are real
I guess
Like
You could learn about Colin Kaepernick
I'm not positive easy to
Look into whether or not Niketown
Come to where is Harrah certain way
Difficult to email
Is there a foil ball
Alex
About haven't yelled about Colin Kaepernick
The way that I'm comfortable describing the braces
Starts
What that Constitution
Everybody model their government after that
Because the idea
Are you a globalist
Globalist
And everybody knows it
And that's why they use a bunch of dumb
College dropouts at morons
Running around
Can people
Try to trigger a civil war
Video
I've some old folks in golf carts being screamed at my other old white people
You're a Nazi F you all the stuff
Ask yourself
Wow
I just
Kaepernick
That mentality this is clearly a joke
They say black power we should be allowed to say white power
If you ask the question
Why can't I say white power
You're too far gone
Nothing very easier
So
That mean it's not
It's just a clear demonstration of where rice at Target
29th
Sacha Baron Cohen
Leads to Alex
That's not that's not the right angle
These are children's criminal fraud
Sacha Baron Cohen was taken away in an ambulance
And therefore this is also fraud claim medical condition
Sure I don't care
Along with its 3% or guy
Really
Gross
Communist
So there's a Stewart Road stalking about the protests are going on
Germany
China
Eventually
This is absolutely unacceptable
Someone has much of an extremist store roads
Also is Stewart's Line in the Sand of the act of killing police that he should
Damon gutzwiller of the Santa Cruz Sheriff's
Department was ambushed
Person killed by staff sergeant Steven Carrillo
Who proceeded to write the words book
And I became unreasonable
In his own blood
Before being arrest
These are words that have a particular meaning among far-right done absolutist communities and kind of give an indication of what
He was all about
A carrillo's arrestee was also charged with the murder of Patrick Underwood who was that law enforcement officer who was killed
On May 29th
And even more recently there was a case of Ethan melzer
Who was charged with
Conspiring and attempting to murder us Nationals
Conspiring and attempting to murder military service members
Providing and attempting to provide material support
Terrorist
Conspiring to murder and metaphor in country
Missouri
Sensitive information including locations in security
Which is a European Neo-Nazi and white
Supremacist
The plaintiff this information to Isis type to carry out the attack
Mauser didn't care if he died in the attack Saint who gives a f***
It would be another War
I would have died
Successful because another 10-year war in the Middle East
Definitely left a mark
Seems like babies George be spending less time fantasizing about how the left is eventually going to start killing cops and realize that he's alive
That sort of thing and worse
And cops represent tyranny but only when they're fighting them
Cool
It's just it's just
Infuriating
There's just no way
Maximum
So we can
Sacha Baron Cohen complaining
It's
The stuff where my eyes roll back in my head
Whiny whiny
I think one of the problems is because like
When
They have their equivalent of that
It doesn't really
Play out
Jacob Wohl does the Estancia
Alex Warren
James O'Keefe
Alright whatever I don't care
Comedy that like overwhelmed
He's a joke
How many times have you seen that
At an open-mic who's like
Obviously I'm
People aren't laughing
So if you don't like this incredibly dumb stupid
Transparent bulshit
Oh well
Cuz you're
Must be
So we get to the 30th and Alex is very excited
Background Rodger Stone
Presidential election
Richard Nixon and he's a guy that got
Donald Trump to run for office
Breaking his silence right now
Edmond
Ahmed
Tuesday edition ears
Rodger Stone facing
Execution base
Covid-19
Supposedly in 2 weeks
Hold on Rodger Stone
Because of covid-19 but covid-19 is a hoax
So no one really gets here
Play the Rodger and you don't want him to go to prison it's also a fraud and a hoax
When people ask you to where I'm at
Okay
Exactly calm down
For sure
They're very serious concerns that need to be taken into account with prison population as it relate
To covid-19
That being said
Place that Rogers being sentenced to has no cases of covid-19
Tennis court exact
Busy campus close those
Sure did a review
His health concerns are all under control and in check
And there is not a danger to his help
Particularly
To be put in prison
So anyway like I said this interview
Begging
Trump to
To give him a partial power
Until weather clemency
What made you change last few days and I'll be here you go
2020election your warning
I'm coming up
What made you say
The gloves are off
Questions
You want to ask me everything.
Because I'm concerned about the direction of this country
I see the way they have destroyed
I see the way our streets are under a violent socialist Revolution
And therefore the sooner I could speak
Incarcerated
In October of 2020
That's why I decided to speak out today
You told me that incompetent
Now you're just
Play he has respect
There's no other that he would have
What if he can't come out and Beyond
You can
You know I just I need to before I go to prison in 2 weeks
I need to get out here and Taylor
Going to kill me that I'm not able to be on the front line fighting for Trump
That makes me mad about having to go to jail
Brilliant
That's it's pretty simple.
That's good
It said it's just sad because
It seems
Like at this
Wait we all have enough knowledge
Trump psychology
To know that
What's going on is he
He's basically
Forcing Rodger to gravel in front of him so he
He can get feels like last second
And he pardons have been it's like hahaha see you look at how powerful I
He's just he's just making friends
Awful awful Tony subordinate
Two because Rogers going around on like these weirdo
Range internet shows
I know I just got to be out there on the front line fighting for the re-election
Trump pardoning him
Seems like a fulfillment of all of these these interviews
It makes all of his shows that he went on team power
Right yeah
There is
I mean
Somehow I feel like Rodger Stone
Even if he doesn't
Get pardoned is going to wrap up his
Like he's going to find a a doppelganger
And like put his hat on there
Tattoo Nixon on his back and be like save that mate
Get out of
Are you home
Find someone
I don't know
So this is just awesome
The goods
There's a point where Alex realizes like
You're not doing this Gooden
I was one of the first people
And the independence
And the anti-glare Lewis worldview
Truly
Don't forget he's a piece of s***
Talking about how great a looks looks great
Why you sex but they're just
Get the way
Body is at the wrong angle
It's so powerful
Look at his
Casting face
So amazing
Such a
You know what it is it's instinct
Call Alex's Tire
Rogers giving this long list of smart
He's capable powerful he's independent
Greats don't forget you want to slobber all over his come on now buddy
Very strange
The tiny bit because his main reporting an everything you talk about is like overnight
No big deal
It's
The thing is like they're kind of it all
Inasmuch as
Rodger
Maximizing
Because it's his argument for getting out of jail
You know it either like slowing and killing our economy
She's real
It's dangerous I know people who have died
No people who have died from it
This is not a hoax by any means
Very real
Current
Danger
At the same time
Well some of that might be due to humans
Behavioral changes
Interesting you know
Your your head this position
Where
You know you saying things that are very much
Pasta
The same way that like
We're living in this a couple days after Alex
And Alex said they wanted Trump to get in
Research about how
They just wanted a better deal with China would have completely forgot
Nothing matters so tomorrow there won't even be virus
Bisquick
Brilliant
Okay I don't know exactly how to explain it in advance
But there is a
There's an intrinsic problem with what Rodger is put in
In for it
He's going to suggest
That reason
The people want him in prison is okay
Can't appeal
Because if he goes to prison he'll get covid-19 and he'll die
So he won't be able to
Appeal his case
Well then we are
For thinking
This is really dumb
Why do they want to do this because
The Deep State and George Jackson
Before my appeal is her a year from now because
Which is why I
4 series of completely fabricated
I'm essentially getting
That's what this is tantamount to
Achoo as a humanitarian
To use his extraordinary powers of clemency
So this doesn't make sense because if Rogers entire goal is do you have this appeal the system on trial
Cuz we get to Park
Like they want to kill me before I can have my appeal
These should also be like Trump
Don't pardon me
No no don't you remember me because I'm going to
The flip the script to destroy the entire system in the fraud
Apart
And just like when Ford pardon Nixon everybody was like
Well I guess we were wrong
Prove to me that you wouldn't be able to appeal the case successfully the things that
But it would be really good for him if
Is given the part it because then you can say
If I ever
Listen I would have
Yeah
It's works on every front As Long As Trump for sure
Without the party
Immediately
Rodger goes to prison
He doesn't get covid-19
You survived Maybe
Maybe he does the appeal and then he loses that appeal
That's what everyone ends up running out of excuses
Yeah
So
You stopped running
And you need
Pardon you
And then he needs to make you his campaign
Biggest story in history
Rodger is not interested because I don't want a job in Trump's campaign
He also disagrees with our coming.
Beautiful
And instead of running from you
Trump brought you in as a spokesperson or brought you in as an advisor
The president has no
Rodger nothing wrong
Rogers & Rogers Band
And then just bring you in front center
And press conferences that would be so
If you something
That's insane
He's walked very slowly
So Rodger will never kill himself
Insist on Rodger saying
Makes me think Alex is preparing or Rodger.
Say it was the Clinton or something
It's very meaningful
There's no circumstance whatsoever
Killed himself you will know that somehow
Do that so they come back
He killed himself that will never happen
Interrupting
What's wrong
Will you kill yourself in prison if they
Prisoner
No circumstances under which I will do that
So obviously when we play this clip after
There you go proof
Spirituality
Coming to God
And I'm not
Play because I want to make fun of it
Chance
Probably
Probably not but it's ugly or gross
Hey look whatever I understand
She tells the story of like going to a Franklin Graham service
There's enough people who probably have similar experiences that making fun of it
Kind of feel like I'm making fun of other people's religion
Who is Rodger Stone
I'll just leave that ass up
In the conversation
Spirituality
Rodger accidentally says that he praised
Justice will be done in my case
I'm praying
More important the prank the trumps much
That was part of the Ten Commandments
Can on it
I mean I know he misspoke
But still
He did say he's praying
Making a little quick
Pardon
Now Alex gets down
I should probably do my job
I really probably should I should probably do my job
I can't
Can't
Because there's too much
God
Pick one
Credible article videos
Subaru
26 years ago on radio and TV
The first few years as the biggest show Alberta
15 years ago if you want cigarettes
The compound
Well that's just because now you think Sacha Baron Cohen is the biggest
Story you could come and get your crew
In
False flag
Flags
Just wanted to
Time sure and not reveal that their massive
This fashion I would argue that Alex would have a lot more time for actual story
If you didn't talk about how he can't get the all the story cuz there's somebody story
It's
I can't even stress you I know I play clips that are
Fairly similar to that
A bit
I don't play nearly all the time he says that he says that
What I'm talking about
He's got a break
I got a break he reminds me of this comedian Ron
I only ever saw him
When I was in Missouri but he
Constantly talk about
God got to go
Funny
For him
Alex
I'm talking about how
He's not feeling time there's so many stories
And then he just starts rambling
I can see your frustration
Alex play some videos
And talks about
Beat up because they submit
They apologized and then they get hit
Or something
Still never actually
Pick a fight with Alex cuz they know that he'll kill them if they do
And then I would start stalking about eating people
Sort of okay
You talked about how
Some of his fighting style
Spider
When somebody really bad
Tobacco
You get me down
Do you like that
Big chunks
Jobs that people had me down
Size of a 2 oz of meat
You don't think the biggest guy gets off my back
Do your jeans
Waterbury weather
Florida man
I I just think back to all the times that
He's proven himself to be an
Honorable and
Chivalrous man
Very much about observing
Hey man
We get into a fight
I will bite your flashlight
I will buy you all right
Do this right now I challenge
I honestly would love
To watch him try to chew through some Jeeps
Little bit of a flourish
A Levi's 501
Alex you must
Home
Pants
So
A bit of Alex embellishing and making up stories about
The the German
Foster children stories
Another story that involves
Pedophilia in Germany
He is making
Oh, settle down but we have this
30000 pedophiles in the German government
So if you go to Dutch's you'll find the underlying article that Alex is making stuff up about
Fountain inside not difficult to find
This is about an arrest of a twenty-seven-year-old soldier
Back in October 2019
Which is deeper investigation into
Is like internet sharing of illegal pornographic
Imperial
The bottom line of the story is the German 37 Oz they're following up on
30000 leaves
This investigation
Not that 30,000 suspect
Have been identified
In fact the actual article specifies that at this point approximately 70 suspects have been identified
There's no indication
In the German government
This is very important to understand
Alex doesn't care about the story at all
Emotionally charged
Subject so he knows that most of the time his audiences never going to look into any of this
See what the real story is
You know that he can push people's buttons
By talking
Teresa stories stories about horrific crime
Because the furthest most people will get is the headline
Which then they'll just take his confirmation of whatever story Alex's told them about
F*** a disgrace
It's awful and Rambles about this quite a bit
He starts talking about how like
You going to this this story launches him into
His enemies are are pedophiles
The previous episode like I told you
Keep in your mind
Democrat
So now
This category
People need kill
But if we go off half-cocked
I'll be the victim and get away with it we have
Walk softly carry a big stick
Is weisenstein
Until God deliver judge
And you'll know when that moment is
The judgment
God's hand picks us up like
We do not Direct
You'll know
You'll know the time
When the time comes it's important
Portuguese
Dispatch them like
I'd for the rattlesnake
Or cockroach
You step on
Anybody want
But they will die
This is getting to be a very weird place for me doing the show
Because I feel like
The trends that I've been watching
Over the past couple weeks have been like
In this this like Direct
Talk about violence
About how God's Vengeance needs to be enacted on Alex's enemies
It also makes again how God's vengeance
The carried out by you
And you'll know when the right time is
I feel like this is happening a lot more regularly
It seems to be ramping up
It seems to be like
As far as I can tell we're not looking
Calmer Waters in the future as covid cases increase
The potential for more lockdowns
The election
Is coming up
Deep deep water seems choppy
And the rhetoric that Alex is leaning more heavily into
Cm in
I don't know what you can do
I don't know I don't know
I don't know what I can do other than
Here is what he's saying
If tomorrow
There is a shooting
I'm someone who's
There's a decent chance he's screaming into the void she needs yelling this violent nonsense
People who
Just want to take brainforce
There might be an impotent
To the people listening
Nothing will ever come
But on the off-chance
It's something
Yours that I don't know I think that one is pretty much
Clear cutting
Incitement of violence
I don't think I don't think there's any more like
That's not protected by
That's that's
Yeah that's
A judge
That's the real situation
Understanding
What is
Because it's not
I think that is
That is where the territory
That's when somebody will get in trouble
I mean it's not specific
General
To the point of being sick
Specific
He saying Democrats
50% of which
He's saying that they're all and they
What is a Brandenburg versus Ohio
I think you still protected by
It's really difficult for me
Cases are going up in Texas
Austin
Rally's
Episode
How do you discuss this without being like
He's doing this whole thing about the killing your enemies and God will tell you when it's time
Let's see what happens
I will I will play this for you and we will
See what
If if that is
Not illegal
It should be
Whatever is it whatever the law says
F*** you that's illegal
Should be some sort of legal ramifications
Affordabike
I mean I guess it's like so much of it is consequence driven so like
Somebody does carry something out then maybe
Somebody can sue Alex
Just a b
We give him
Fantastic
Trip
On a private
Spaceship
And he can go
Into space
Yeah I think that would be a great way to deal with
He cannot come back
So what am I what am I
Driving
It's getting consistent
Excessive
Scott
Moscato
Delivered
What God delivers
A real careful that you asked
Finally got
Lamp
But if you won't engage
Information
Warfare vengeance
Then when it comes time if ever
Execute
Silence
You will fall
He will wavering
But you won't even show up
Isn't what Sacha Baron Cohen did information War
Never murder
Jesus was just deeply upsetting
It's disturbing
I'm really I'm really not Styx
No it's pretty bad
Like a
Hello
The charts today
That one
10 Stars
Tomorrow
I don't know why don't I get a fart machine
Exit polling computer chips out of people
This whole time this whole episode has been talking about he has a gigantic story and he's not really gotten to it cuz it gets cracked
By Rodger and then yelling about murdering his enemies
And finally gets to it and it's just a load of b*******
Falsify
Covid-19 numbers in least
15 *
What they actually are for every person with covid
50 more people that's the minimum
Talk about adding
So it took a while to figure out what the hell I was talking about your because the website
Just a video
With no links or citations or anyting
They generally find it's actually watching Alex's special reports
Very helpful
Information is coming from
But I have no other option here so I watch the video
What's going on
It appears that someone it in forwards got sent a video from May 18th
County Commissioner meetings
From Collin County
Who doesn't text
And definition
Of course
Probable cases
Of covid-19
They're discussing what this new death
Confirm case numbers
It's clear if you watch this video what happened is they decided that if you test positive
Test close proximity
You're considered a probable case
Even if you had notes
This isn't
Position with the definition of bacon
Confirm case
Which requires a specific
PCR test to come back
The probable definition
Other approved test
In the slideshow they put on the County Commissioners
Discuss how this definition
Person who's passed
Positive
Which is the same thing
PCR test
Infecting 15 other
Probable case
Alex is trying to pretend that this is a situation where they're saying that for every one person who tests positive count is 16
It's definitely not proven by the evidence provided
Alex is trying to claim the two somehow related to the
In Texas but that just doesn't
Make science
Texas case numbers jump drastically on June
This meeting is from month prior
Also they're less than 3,000
Send covid-19 cases
We just way below places like Harris County 30,000
Cases Travis County which is
Almost 10,000
This is not the Smoking Gun Alex
Thanks it is but he's like this
It's lame
But not nearly as lame Jordan
As this next thing
And this is where we're going to get some good feeling
Okay
Alex tries to have a bombshell girl
Oh no
This gas
Is that lady who yelled at the city council meeting
In Florida
Alex
How big will
Not
It does not go well
What do you make of it coming out there count
Funny people that died of other things
Just say that just anybody
Credible fraud
I'm sorry say that again
Okay
Phone call
Thank you
Appreciated
You could tell that you still on the way
She just doesn't understand said hello a charge for clarification
Conversation exactly what happened
That is entirely because
There was a really bad energy
Between the two of them
Like she was not
Giving what Alex wanted
Out of the interview
It was like
Stopping
Start the weather wasn't
There wasn't a cohesion to it she wasn't yes and equip them
And so he wanted to jump
The interview
So you pretend there's Tech difficulties bear do the tollway
Stop doing the show
Millions of dollars
Your f****** phone with somebody
To try and hire somebody
Can't have years of complaining about these phone lines show
Will you take call cover your bases
It's pathetic
Louis Alex having very weird vibe
For the rest of this
He is not in a good
Headspace
Headlines
Because he was like
Can't take calls
Please start reading headlines and he hasn't written Sidelines before he got on air
Very confused by the sudden
Current class with fascist Muslim Turkish nationalist
Austrian Street
Alex do you know where you should land on this
Antifa Kurds or older nationalist
Is Austria
What is Austria
Supposed to be against
Antifa Kurds
Fascist ultra-nationalist neo-Nazi
Muslims
Wait hold on
United States
Okay okay alright I'm going to go with
So he struggles with
Needing a temp
Because he thinks story about the Collin County
Commissioner meeting
Is somehow going to be like
The biggest story in the world
Answers like
If I could just
You know
Let's do a
Publicity stunt
Big enough
Maybe we could stop a clock
How about I buy a blender
Do it
Masochist
And there's nothing more frustrating
I'm sitting here knowing we have them by the balls
You don't know if you got a blunder put his finger in there and then you like
Microchip Mafia
Advance
Takes a bow
Dobie Gray
So are you get to get really into Spectrum like realizing like
How do you spell can put my fingers in a blender
Maybe would drive enough attention to the show
That I could get this story out
But that's not obviously going to work what work is if I were able to come
Convince other people to cover this story
Obviously I can't because I don't know that do bad work that I got
Madison messages
50 message
Text message
Talk show host
Journalist English
Don't need the credit
Will you please just do an article
About this and here's the raw video
Credit which I don't want
Weird mental illness
That if we brakes
Something bad
No one else will touch it just out of some weird
Humanity is a rotting
Humanity is a maggot covered corpse
Because
Does other people recognize that he does bad work
And he says something is confirmed
It probably isn't
And that's
My name
That's all it's going on
At a certain basically it's like a Tucker is not going to do a segment about this
Facebook
If the entirety of media is like
No we can't touch you
He still can't
And 41 seconds
Maybe this is my fault
Yeah what do you mean you can't get even
Friends weirdos welcome
Plandemic people on their show
Your stories suck Alex
You gotta recognize it's not
It's not that
Sooner or later
And it's Alex
I don't know for a little bit of schadenfreude
I can't even remember the people he's supposed to be mad at
Names
Send a message over 50 prominent people
And six of them retweeted us
To Jack Dorsey
Facebook
Leader
The leader of Google in the leader of apple and just temperature slight it's not
Scene
I really think that he couldn't come up with those names
Mark Zuckerberg
Things for him
I think he exerted his memory banks with Jack Dorsey
Not
On Wellness
Videos about all the time
Because if you were in bursts in these
Bees
Waters
Going to be on the tip of your tongue at all time
You would think
Can come up with
Hundred different people who are involved in Infowars
Yeah it's just the topic of my expert
Exactly
And so like it doesn't take me long
Mike Adams the health Ranger
Gerald Celente
Forever but I can tell you all about it
Exactly
So I just think it's this is an indication of like
Everything is surfing
And that's interesting to me
Because what under the surface
Is the stuff about God's Vengeance being acted out by people like him and his listeners you are the knife in God
Because that you can pull out
Yeah there's
There's this interesting duality
And most of the time he's yelling about
Steph
It's trivial and nonsensical like Sacha Baron Cohen pranks his friends and he thinks it's a crime
At the same time there's this growing Trend it's just
Continuing
Of
Tell you when it's time to murder
Fauci and all of our enemies
And your instruments of God's vengeance
Acceptable
Rhetoric
Yeah I mean there's a history has often been driven by the silly and stupid when it's revealed that there's
Silly and stupid
They start killing p
I mean
We'll see what happens
I don't know I hate I hate this sort of space because
There's a there's a Feeling
I don't know how to put my finger on what I'm trying to say but like
There's a Feeling
How much am I
I can't tell how much of this is real
All I can do is tell you
He has a show
If you understand in the context of what
This is giving his audience tacit permission
Murder people
As long as they believe that God
So we could yeah
Did I I guess I'm trying to stress is that
That uncertainty is not okay in and of itself
I mean I can't
Generally I am not worried about
A large-scale
Because I would
Bet my life on
The vast majority of these people being
Useless coward
Read about the individual
Because
That is who is going to do damage
Which two people
That's the that's the situation
So that kind of stuff is
In the wrong ear
You know
Sure
Result
Living in that space is really bad
Like
Having an audience where you think
It's okay to tell them
Maybe
If you are listening
Listen to this stuff like that never follow through with it
That's a f****** really weird
Some angry
Meijer in Texas
Right
That's because he has created a cult
Especially if you're still on board with Alec
Bikes at this point
You believe
Anything and
Seems like there's nothing
Research has a better position
Trump is a champion heroic
It's important for him
The pardon Rodger Stone
A f****** stupid two months ago it's over for Humanity today everything is a hoax
Right now in cases and deaths are out-of-control it's
Over for Humanity
Doesn't suck
We will see
Talk
He's going to be out of Studio
So
I am a little bit fed up with him
Friday Brigham do something
We're going to put Alex on the back burner
I'm sick of this b*******
He's getting out of pocket a little bit so
In a space where every
Two days we recorded episode where all I hear is
I'm kind of your God
You know who it is
We are on Twitter is at underscore
We are also on Facebook
Please find help out in any
Perfect
Holding
Alex
Christian coloring