Damned important
I have great respect for knowledge B
Need money
Collegeboard.com
Everybody welcome back to fight knowledge um Jordan the little show where sometimes I
Subject
That's humility on mypark
Well today then I'm going to do a little talking about
Guy named Graham Ledger from one America news
Okay Network
I didn't ask you this is the first time you've messed up your side of the it's not true because you didn't save it
Novelty Beverages and talk a little bit ly
Which is what leads up to you whatever
Right spot
Dan my bright spot is
Release a new album
Okay
Experimental
He did a song with
Bjork
It's been a long time since I've heard this song
Is so f****** Bjork
What is the most
Bjork
Concentrated Bjork it's been awhile
Breathe
That's great
Experimental avant-garde nonsense
Paradoxical because this is also a little bit involving the year of the
In
It's terrible mess
It serves as a reminder that I'm sometimes
Prophetic
Okay
With cucumber stuff so you found
Is in the fridge I was worried about it when it came out
I got a mint cucumber
From
Alright
It is
The worst I've had
The worst shelter.
Trash
Absolute trash
And here's why
If you get
Cucumber flavor
If you supplement that something commit to adds a little bit of I don't know I don't know who Mommy
Is the right name
That is a pickle Seltzer and it's gross I like this was disgusting
With pickle juice
It's great because it's super concentrated and you can mimic
Greatness
This is supposed to be a refreshing Seltzer drink that tastes like a goddamn pickle
And it's gross
So f*** you could gather
You're the worst
I mean you can't really compare
Will take away from my ability to try bunch of other one
So anyway
You surprised me with your
Disgusting this
Seltzer division
That's all we can blame
For sure
Brightspot
Yes you are right that's why I thought it was
Gross
I actually was a
The only selters I can actually think the rest out
Well the first one
Little bucket
Whatever
That's where I'm at
Like I said this is from
First episode of a show
Supporting the team
Yeah alright first up
Jaimie Alexander
You are now
I'm a policy wonk
And Marcella asks you are now
Thank you very much Marcelo
Greg legs
Put the both
Portmanteau
Alright in the next bone.
All capital letters
Batman your handwriting
Okay
I'm not criticizing
Which paid off I'm glad I learned that
Okay
Matthew gur now
You are now policy walk
Bumps Their donation up to
Which we appreciate very much
Alex and Mike
You're both not Technic
Heroin
So good
Is freakishly large
Make it so much
Alex and Mike
You're really not doing a great job of articulating
What's wrong
Hawk
Call Zack
Yes thank you very much and if you would like to sign up and
You go to our website
It says support the show
I'll take you our patreon
And we would appreciate it very
You can find a local charity in your area or bail fund
And go ahead and jump
Donate to that
See it's not as easy as it looks to try and like come up with a way to express packaging something
Professional
We're going to be talking about
I don't I don't really know how to turn the personalities
People there
I certainly don't think that they have what you described as a rising
They do not
Something that is very relevant to the world of right-wing propaganda
To look into something
Baby a way of Dipping our toe into that gross water
Something from
From
Well I mean I watched a lot of
OneAmerica
Which was
Narcan
A harder right
Minor league Fox News
You know it's like
What majors
At least has a slugger in Alex Jones
You know it's like a really bad.
Still some seats
Right
The big backer or whatever his truck seems to love them a bit
There's just nothing every time
Happening here this is
It is not good
It's not it's not good and a lot of it seems to be very similar
Demon content
The stuff we already talked about
Totally so I always had
I would describe it at least Mike's.
Covering a lot of it felt like I was a rock climber who couldn't find a hole
There is one rock
You should just go ahead and play are out of contacts dropping that'll give you an ID
Would be very handy
Okay
We'll see
Infested prison
Andy went on an interview
And it was almost word-for-word the exact same
I also got a message
Couple messages actually about other stops that Rodger made apparel
Show
Infowars
Rescheduling
I feel like
How to blow up a set with a pencil
I'd be very mad
Is it this is a media to a raises baking Trump
Departing him saying how much
He has to drop
Now here's the thing
We skip that part entirely on
This interview and there aren't that many
Clips of it is a really short interview
This interview there's no buttering
Trump up really okay
Out-and-out
Begging
Literally he says
I'm begging you
I'm begging Trump depart
He says he's praying to Trump again today
What's the temperature
I think
Probably a good move on his part cuz
He has a pretty good reason to believe the Trump may actually be watching me
So
So yeah he goes on Graham Ledger show Graham Ledger is
The is the
You know minor league Bill O'Reilly
Okay he's trying to do that whole thing
And he's just
Even more hard right that's
The whole idea
+ 2
This is a tweet that he had in the last 24 hours
In response to Newsom
Tweeting out something like
It's a good idea where I'm at
Wearing a mask is a sign of submission
I would rather die from the Wuhan coronavirus than ever submit you were
You
#1st July
#National doctor's day hashtag covid-19 hashtag hashtag Coronavirus
Okay Camaro
He's infecting Twitter
The government
Politely asking you to do an eminently reasonable
Howard Stern
Pretty consistent
Stuff about just about every
Long predates covid-19 or map
Submission is preparing you for the globalist
Dude
Oh yeah
Curly fries
Exactly
Good God loving conservative
Is the guy who
Is the big backer
And
Our boy
Graham Ledger
Just this year lost a lawsuit to their former booking
King producer
Robert Downey jr.
Harris who is black
Brought it up in a meeting
A private meeting with Robert hair
Hey I'm
Getting
Like I know where I work
Okay people are being very racially harassing
Okay
Within 24 hours he was fire
You can't save
Well and he also
Defender
Exactly
Paris of course 13 hundred grand in compensatory damages and the glow
Yeah I'm the total lawsuit was 1.1 million
So is that
Who is Grimm
I was looking into him trying to find his
History in his bio and stuff like
He doesn't have a Wikipedia
Which I find fast
He has been on one America as a host
For three years now
Even longer
And he still doesn't have a Wikipedia
Yeah it's not weird
Cuz a little bit
They're just not that maybe they're not nearly as big as
Maybe we're the only situation where you like
Wikipedia pages are really just
Based on how much interest anyone has
To make one no one's interested in
For themselves
You think so
Wikipedia page
Is very vain
A biopic
Marathi.
I believe it's
Marathi
It is now my new favorite website
Okay it is
Seetv.tv is
According to my Huarache.
Maharashtra's leading entertainment and cultural website
Is Maharaja is region in India
Marathi is
Predominant language
That people okay
I have no idea why he is on that website and not with
But he's there
And there's some great little fun fact I things about him
Like this
This was there's a couple of
Stuck out
Graham Charles Ledger is an American Business
This man television news anchor
And host of The Daily Ledger
With more than three decades of experience he has earned himself a prominent seat and conservative news cover
That seems a little self-aware for a website
Primarily based out of India
You mean self-written
Maybe
Write 30 years of experience
Is that the business experience or is he been in the media for 30 years
Aluminum boat
Okay
Play you know those I don't know what
When he was in San Diego he was a local news
Exactly
Still in San Diego
Any of the local news host and it's it's like his career goes like that until about 2,000 for 2,000
And then he switches and help
Start smart drive system
Which
Is a business
That makes
Cameras
To put in long-haul Truckers
Cabs
In order to watch them at all
School
The terrifying psycho
So they don't take your amphetamine almost require People based on a real story
A real City
Realshit
That gives him the term American Business
And then later on
He goes in
Starts working
It's a little bit like a
Ron Burgundy turned into Bill O'Reilly
The career trajectory that
She's a big deal
Kind of a big deal
And then here's another part of another fun tidbit
Has a daughter named Sienna Maryland whom he loves very much
Maryland
Their social media presence is hard
Subjective
Find
It's a little bit weird
Here's where it gets a little bit
More and more obvious
With his sharp business skills Ledger soon established a market foothold and made business relationships with the state of
California in the Salvation Army
Salvation Army
Apparently
I looked into this further and it turns out
All of that information
From
Marathi TV
Comes directly from a meet the candidates interview
That's a he had when he was running for one of the seats on this end to be a guido
San Diego Ito Union High School District Board of Trustees
Iran in 2012
Directly from the Arctic
In 2006 I helped launch a high-tech Company in San Diego smart drive system
With little or no budget we
Successfully carved out of Market foothold and established the company
In a highly competitive industry
Well personally establishing new client relationships
Including the state of California
And salvation
So
I suspect
That
There is somebody in India
Who really likes Graham Ledger
Is good as I can get there
Mystery
It's not weird I don't know what to say mystery of where the word
Congratulations
Here's there's another bio okay that I found on a website
I called healthy tan.
Compton
Okay I strongly recommended
For every
4 tons of Health stuff no help stuff whatsoever
Currently this website just
Keeps
Height weight
Weight and health information
On Celebrity
It's really weird affliction
Weird biographic
So in love yet
Cedar Bayou
Doesn't go over there
This is Mike celebrities have and how much do they weigh
Batman world
Question
Senile
Dragons episode I would have an answer for you
Starboard
Alex
Oh they're not good man
It's not like that at all
Alright
Yeah so unhealthy
I you get
Really really weird
Grammar in
11 quotes
Is Graham Ledger was born on 13th March 9th
61 in San Diego
He is American by nationality and that's big
Ground is white
There is no information about his parents and siblings
Girl hang out Pete where did Saint Ignatius college preparatory situated in the place where he grew up and graduated with phenomenal eval
Great
Shiki for further studies join San Diego State University
And successfully obtained a bachelor's
All typos and
Poor grammar
Directly from the side
Griffin Ledger was a reporter Onkyo
Grandmother was a reporter
Kmsb
TV from 1990 2000
Eminent for covering probably the greatest live news stories like
2003 California wildfire on National
Victoria took proficient photography from 2014
2005 and began Graham Ledger photography
He seemed a few times on the radio
Including 210 FM
Seems
Now this is where it really ramped up
The bad grammar
Write a bio about how like
I was into drugs and humping
I'd really like
His name is G I would call it back grammar
That's a good idea
Puns
Well his show is called the daily life
Yeah you can do with that
21 G you could remake that movie
Please go ahead
7 G
Lyrics never keep any of astray
But here's my favorite one
Graham Ledger's this is under Graham Ledger's net worth
Salary
Graham Ledger without a doubt acquires a lot of Fortune
So is a hosting anchor he acquires a normal salary of 127,000 it's protected to state that he can
Conveys a net worth of milk
Fantastic I got translated and it's translated back
Seems like something
That's the reason the grammar is bad
He hasn't
Are you staying in Indy
That could be
Good for him
So the show interview does with
The show for the most part is
I didn't deal with the second half at all which is
AAA an interview with
What Josh Horowitz
The conservative reporter guy
It is one of the most racist like just out-and-out
Straight up nonstop races and then I just
And there was no point in doing anything
Maybe hate them for
Snow
Stay away from that
And here he has one of the more incoherent thing
We're dealing with because he has the same problem that Rogers
Is that Alex had
With Rodger Stone
It is a status imbalance
No no it doesn't seem like that
It's that Rodger Stone
Is
Telling you
If he goes to
The jail covid-19 will kill him
Dangerous thing in the world
Is going
To tell you that there is no problem
At all
With covid-19
Branch in the road is tough to
So we wind up bouncing back and forth
Invalidating everything simultaneously sometimes within the same sentence
But he starts off like this
All
Data
Driven
Not my opinion
So the deal is all raw data driven
He is about to tell us
All about
He is about to tell us the truth using only facts and
Sam
Exactly
Dragnet s***
Immediately after saying that
Like the fact
This is the least
Weasel so-called Global pandemic history
Is this is this true Jordan is it true then I don't know to tell this is
The least glow of this is the least
Lethal so-called Global pandemic
In history weaselly words
You could probably look at numbers and
History
Just go we'll go from there
Sure
What do you how do you define a global pandemic
Touches the globe
Okay one side to the other
Sure okay
And then
Least lethal is he talking about percentages or
Numbers
He's 100,000 kind of believe that it would be a number of grow
I don't know
Okay
So sorry one
Is that the least lethal Global pandemic in history because we took steps or they took
Steps necessary to keep it from becoming a lethal global
Still I think the larger issue
It's not over yet
Good boy
How can you tell me in the middle of the global pandemic
This is the least lethal one
You know that's you saying
Well you don't need to act like this is a big deal
Until we make it the most
Lethal
Car wreck
The least lethal car wreck
Just
Dover Maybe
Other
Yeah start over
So
He's he's right at the gate this is the beginning of
Talking numbers
Already he has said something that neither makes sense nor can be
Dealt with
As if he understands wait a sec
I just said 500,000 people were dead
And I said this was not a big deal
He goes with that
Yes we just
A half a million deaths
By covid-19
Ladies and gentle
I am not intending to diminish
Any of these deaths by Corona
They were all human being
Alright Dan
What do you think his next words will be
Guessing
Stars
Yelp
I don't know these people are like
Like you know their pool balls like a break in any direction I don't know
But I know it's going to start with but
But is the cue ball that's about to hit
Unpredictable directions
They're all humans
But
I don't know
Go for it
But that number is apolitical
Statistical
Joke
I don't know what that means
Also how can you start with I'm not trying to diminish any of these deaths
And end with
It's a joke
The number is apolitical
Statistical joke
Okay
Alright in what way does that not every single death
I mean I guess what he's trying to say is probably that the numbers used
Political
Shiraz or whatever
Stated objective of just using the facts and the numbers
Because
You still now has to talk about that five.
But
But that seems as soon as I can
Trapped himself in a bit of a weirdo
Cucumber
Men's pickle
He's got his own SodaStream right now
So yeah
Already this is just the first two men
Of his
And he is already said
Conflicting things
That don't make any sense
At the same time
He's tried to say he's having it both ways
As much as he possibly
And he knows what he's doing to
Like even now even with this
He said something like this
There are somewhat 6 billion +
Or minus a few hundred million people on the planet
Half a million
Is not statistically relevant
Add in this country to death by covid-19 numbers are not
Repeat
Not
Pranking
Broadcaster
Because 500
That sounds like
A lot of people
I respect
To donate
You got convinced
What's up
Just talkin about
Furthermore
How many
The people are on the planet
This guy has all the facts all the numbers
Big World popular
Was a big deal when it cross
The seven
Seven points now
But you know what comes from
I don't know I feel like a lot of the time that population was a big deal was around
What's the time when it might have been around
You know a lot of the arguments about
M4
I think a lot of people probably
Regurgitating stuff
From both timer
And that might be why it's sort of shorthand for the population
It could be talking about
Do under half a billion or whatever
We talked about
Updated there
The references
And normally I'm fine with that
This guy
Opens his Broadcasting
He's going to give us all the numbers and all the facts
And multiple times
He does exactly what Alex
Yeah that's fair
Hours of research
Hours of Richard's to all of these numbers
This morning
You should probably get
The
Imagine that you saw that number at some point doing all your
Search
Spiking
Right makes it very
But a little bit
This is his neck
Immediately after
Outside of a
Huge data dump on June 25th thanks to the governor of New Jersey
Thank you so much mr. Murphy
Yasso
Outside
Thanks New Jersey
The governor of New Jersey
So that would explain why his
Review data dump
He's responsible for a lot
Absolute
And continues on he just does this whole thing over and over and over
Not a big deal there's no problem
No I know there's a
Everybody
That's the whole thing huh
Okay it's not a problem I know it's a problem
Yeah
Scary number ever told you about the 30
Where do you even get sir
Magic
Good them
And most of this is just constant
Covington
This is what he's
No difference
Then previous years
Why is this
This is why
If covid-19 is such a killer virus
Then we would be seeing an increase
In the sheer number of dead American
Compared to previous years
Right
But we're not
Just not true
Number is
Look pretty
Pretty shocking particularly in areas that are have heavily affected without breaks
Up to as high as 40%
Excess deaths numbers for a lot of portions of the country but New York
Financial Times
Analysis is like
Tons of other countries that were showing
Massive jumps
In terms of excess deaths
I don't have any
Reason to believe him unless he can demonstrate that compelling evidence
A lot more.
No one no one denies that
Except for people who just stay there is
Yeah like this is 290 all the number
I don't know who they the same time it start
Hard for him to prove a negative
To prove that there aren't more deaths
You just have to
You know
Deal with the thing
Like
The sources that are saying that there are
Ensure why they're wrong
What he does have interest
Just wild
He follows that
Clam up
That the deaths aren't speaking with this line
Are you listening California
And the people of Illinois
New York
You're being a hoe
You're being lied to
I got distracted cuz I realized he was talking
I just like the inadvertently admitted directly to our faces
You're being lied to I'm lying to you
Just lied to you
Just two on the
I know I'm being unfair about
Right on that why
I guess I just don't like
Hit people just
It's being like it's not happening
Wake up
They're lying to you
Alex yelling
But wake up
Two people that he's trying to keep him
Delusional
Absolutely
It's just it's just
Immensely annoying to me
Especially whenever they use the second person that's whenever it
Okay now you're talkin
Sing directly to me
Telling me that they're doing the thing that you're literally doing in those
Name the state
I'm taking it personal
Sure
Ledger meet me at Portillo's we're going to
Are you okay
That's good stuff
And so it just keeps doing this
Kind of it's just a
Constant like back in
You know
With the with his next
If you happen to have
I want one in a nursing
New York
Those facilities
Which was to issue debt
Thousands of elderly
Porcine
Nursing homes
To accept covid-19 page
Absolutely outrageous
4500 covid-19 page
Dad
After Cuomo's March 2500
It is the highest rate of nursing home deaths
In the
Again
The numbers
Do
Not
Why
That's just another Alex Naruto
That's something we've seen Alex talk about a bit
Option in there
That is like
Can you afford
Care for your pet
Whoever you have your loved one is at home
Yep are you able to provide the
Specific kind of care if they have a condition that they need
To be taken care of you probably can't
So he's telling people to do something they probably couldn't do
To avert something
Damn
Eddie immediately
No it's not
Billion or even care about
Unless you're old
Stop
Isn't really
A coherent reason why
One is and one isn't
No except for it
Exactly
This is
Don't worry about it
Everybody's dying your nursing homes cuz part was telling that right but I mean
Unless you're in New York
In which case it's even more
Like it's this isn't a big deal unless you're in a blue State and you happen to be somebody who is likely to be in my audience
Exactly
He does
Is he starts talking to
Governor news
Does it the same he doesn't Alex Jones
Hanover on the Left Coast pretty much the same thing
Just as bad
Frankly if not worse
From the
Slick
Marxist
Nutcase
Gavin Newsom
Covid-19
Summer recess
Summer vacation
Another body language
Looking is Jaws
Clancy's
He's moving around
He's showing California residents and the rest of the world
But he's mad
Mad
Maps.
Do that a lot of people say like stop
The fly
Canstaff
I think Alex does it and it's more fun or more interesting at least because he's like so emotion
Affected by whatever
It's more Showmanship to it than that
That was very
Now my my notes on that are
You're so disappointed
Pointing this is Governor Newsom is a demon what are you doing
Marxist
They don't have a slugger
Pick me up I hate it
And then goes into this whole thing and he points
And that Newsome is trying to close down the bars and he's doing all this s*** to try and keep young people from spreading device
And it's spreading mostly among
Young people which the governor is
He's trying to punish here right now
Because we know that younger people
The demographic of somewhere in the neighborhood of
0222 30 years old
Has almost 80 mortality
Many of these young people running around
At and many of them
Contract the virus but
Have no antibodies
Because their body fought It Off the Grid
There's no antibodies showing up in in the blood work
Amazing
I got my brow
Rodi you do I can see some confusion
If your body fought it off successfully that would lead to antibiotic
Yes
Unless you fight it off
So 6 I don't even understand
You can't even find it
Right
Okay
Don't know what's going on anymore
I don't even know the ideas that are attempting to be expressed here
Quite frankly
I mean I guess there's a way to make this coherent on some level
I mean
If he bad and I wouldn't I wouldn't support this
But like if you was going around being like yeah Unger have a lesson
Granted
Summer still going to die
Hey let's go let all these young people go out to bars and all this stuff won't be as bad
Make sure that nobody
Is immunocompromised or has a pre-existing condition or is over the age of 40 something I can go to work
Let's
In order for you to be able to go to Dick's Last Resort
But that's not a restaurant Chicago
Dick's Last Resort is 260
I've never been to Dick's Last Resort downtown Chicago
I was like
I could come up with a better bar I could have gone with
Anything
Dick's Last Resort
That's what we're doing
Cabo Wabo
At least named after alcohol
New twenty-year-olds going to Cabo Wabo
And he does this knowing full but like he's
Talking about the mortality
Many of the young people are running around 8
Alright
How can you tell me
You know like oh man
All these old people in nursing homes are dying all the time and it's those single worst thing in the world
We should definitely let their kids run around asymptomatic
And then
No visit them
Sure
Asymptomatic vs. pre-symptomatic Tucson clear at any point
What you we are where you are if you are
If you're going
To develop symptoms eventually or if you are going to
To be truly asymptomatic
Through the course of your
Your illness
Yeah it's dangerous it just beeps stupid
Unless you want to like I said.
Isolate people just so
You could go to bars
Or whatever
You should still baby wear a mask at the bar
Is that Governor Newsom is
Punishing you for going out
Out to a bar. Okay
But the governor yes while he's shedding
Shoot himself in the foot
He also realizes
Teddy's continuing to
Strangle
The economy
His little piece of the u.s.
Economy
Which Harms
The real action
Chances
Donald
Trump so he's still at it
And he's still going to be at it
Straight
Through November
His account
As much
As possible
In order to harm the re-election
As boring as hell
Reason why I was not able to find a grip on this network
And he's he's doing that it like
It doesn't get more
Globalist
Kind of nonsense whenever you're saying
Okay so yeah
The governor is shooting himself in the middle part of the US economy
California's economy illegal
Top 25 GDP in the world
But also
At the same time
Newsom is doing this on
Purpose
In order to hurt Donald Trump's real
The reason that is that is
McKay's
Babe
That also hurt Gavin Newsom
Re-election chances
Because he completely Torpedoes California's economy California probably the movie Life
Keep this guy around
Think about that one
You're dumb Ledger
Here's the bigger
Alright at no point in time cuz
Cisse
Trump could do something
He's the
Is destroying his own
Could literally be like hey
Here's money we've got a new support package
And then the economy does
Trump could solve that problem if you wanted to
In terms of like
Ensure that local businesses don't have to close
People don't end up
There's a number of things that it would just be policy
Decisions
They could be made from
So what
Course not subset of
Doesn't have
A real
No because the answer is
Obvious
And I don't want to do it
So instead they'll blame others
Doing
The thing that they could do
Easily
Yeah and it's all an attack
To dry and hurt
You got it
Everything is Everything
Poorly delivered until were stalking coin
This is all just
The same
I'm listening to update
This morning
Disappointed
Decent chance that eventually someone with
Chops
Will
End up
I mean
You gotta think it's
The president is
Retweeting there
Network
All this stuff you got to assume that some enterprising grifter
Who has chops
He's going to end up there
Problem I see is that like a lot of people
Is younger set
They seem to gravitate towards Harter extremism then could be
Motivator fit into that slot
You need somebody who's a sell-out and good
And someone like you
Phuc yea
Extreme
Couldn't do it
You need you need like a sell-out like a harder sell out version of 20
In their game over
Devastator
Do you know what my suspension on that is what's up
The hard like those guys who are talented
They stay on the inner
They're not going to one America news
They're not looking
Co-anchor job
Yeah you know to create their own like space
Because that's part of the
Darkest part of the internet
That creates that more rabbit situate editors and bosses
So he continues with the
The
Governor Newsom little
He's pissed off about
Can't let Governor Newsom
Hasn't gone away
I know a lot of us about kicking to get warm
Once it gets hot all goes away
On this next
You stopping the tape
What
What do you think he's going to say
If it's hotter
Then the virus
Good
Because you know
Temperature rises
It's already done
Really close
You know I checked the number this is my job
Everyday
Australian beaten interest
When you look at El Salvador
And you look at the Philippines
And you look at Thailand
And you look at Vietnam
Those areas have
Warm weather
And high humidity
High temperature high
Combination
Their cases are in the Hunter
Unsold
Sure
Those the only high temperature
Are we sure we're not selecting for some other variable
Are you single problem with that logic
Obviously
It's just like oh okay so you're saying that he doesn't kill the virus
Look at El Salvador
One place where I know it
It can be hot anywhere
No more virus if it's summer
Yeah that's bad bad
That's it like
This is honestly
On You episode
Experiential is like I'm listening to
And I'm not even interested in this guy's bulshit
That's what I'm for though
You're not interested Robert Jeffress
People to use the weekend never speak of them at least a little bit boring
Free game
This guy is just like
A junior varsity
Alex
Makes me gravitate towards
And being
Interesting or even scary I mean it's just somebody who's
S***
Kind of
But in such a way that is like
I find it
It's dangerous.
From a critical perspective
In terms of
Being interested
Which is something that I need in order to
You keep doing
Fails
Why we only do one episode on him
Performance review
I have spent
Place of uterus
But I'd listen to maybe 3 minutes of you
They're counting them in the hundreds Vietnam has zero
0 deaths
Know how good their accounting is
Yes
As the weather gets warmer
As the humidity rise
It helps
Beatbox
The transmission
This spread
Virus
Something this guy
Will
Not
Admit
When somebody says the bottom line is something after
Using a couple of examples of why
Sure they're not doing any testing but they've got zero.
I just lost his match against beat me fair and square that's all Grace
Yep
Vietnam
Bottom line
Linguistically
If you have trouble with that sense of yours and you're watching that and I guess it makes sense problem is
Not him
The problem isn't the problem
Send
Comprehension
That's troubling
The interesting thing
This is something that I was
Expecting to look into
And be like
Wouldn't it
You're telling me that humidity
Stops viruses from
I looked it up and there is a little bit of evidence
Maybe possible
That seasonal changes could affect
The spread of the virus
Some scientific
Count on it
The case for every virus or illness
Is debatable
And the extent to which
Like it even is
To discuss is like
Difference
NIH director
As far as
That goes cuz I looked into it and I was like maybe there is something to
The researchers at the NIH ran three
Turn scenarios based on the role of climate in
In the spread of other virus
You know like oc43 nhq
KU won
Better known to cause common cold
In all three scenarios
Their models showed that climate only would
Become an important seasonal factor in
Controlling covid-19
What's a large proportion of
People within a given community
Right now before that
Because sorry is CO2 is as sensitive to
You claim it as others
Viruses
Summer heat still wouldn't be enough to mitigate
The spread
Rue
So that makes sense I'm exactly
But it could
It could have an incremental
Ofac even like
Talking about
In terms of like I wanted
Once it gets warm will be good
If you would like to go back to how El Salvador and Vietnam have
Wonderful climates and everything
Well climates like Brazil Ecuador
Loading summer when it's summer
Yeah
Is other parts of the world have different seasons
He's in San Diego he doesn't know about
Come on now
Yeah
Brazil
It's a dry heat
Give me Amazon
Brazilian dry forest
So very so very good
He continues on though he Powers through all of this terrible nuns
What's the opposite of saying you gotta respect that
I probably what he says
We have to
Sober up
To this is
This is getting back to Noosa
Still in the first
First wave in a second wave we're still in the first wave
We we are
Still in
The first wave
Going to wave that all you did was kind of
Slow down
And then
You Unleashed it
When you said over going to start opening up again he had
If he had his way
He would have kept
They California, shut down straight through November
In order to
Free hat
Honestly lost
In terms of
How that's supposed
To help the right-wing argument
Yep because
If I'm tracking this correctly
He's saying
He said there is a first wave that happen
The old medication measures like distancing mask-wearing closing businesses
Successfully hold back
Right
Everybody was discussing at the time
And they had to reopen things because there was a ton of pressure is now
Did no longer being held back the first wave is now researching
He said you just take a slightly different approach to this time he sounds
Like like he's advocating
Somehow you saying that like it's
See what happened was
We shut down the economy
I'm surprised because we didn't shut down long enough
Which is what governor Newsom wanted to do
By the way
And that's Governor Newsom
Yep
I don't understand anybody listening
Phuc yea
Let alone
That's what is
This is what passes for brilliant
Yeah and she prescribed
Because
Vacations to be understood
Has nothing been done earlier
Hospitals overwhelmed
Nintendo cases everywhere
So obviously that's not what
So
Does recognize that the measures were
Refuses to wear a mask
Great
He did
Can't really be saying shut down
Because that's part of
Marriage results
You can't be saying the businesses should have reopened
Because he's saying that that is with leading to this
Rising number of cases
You can't be saying that businesses should be re closed
No cuz that'll hurt the economy
I don't honestly see what boobs other than
And pretend like everything is an attack on now he's hero
I don't I don't understand how there's any semblance of his being productive
What is him
Immediately discounting it and then just continuing on like you proved
What are you trying to say
I hate to see this he's more confusing than Alex
This is nonsense
I don't understand any of
And he does
Not give
So Americans in all states
From Texas to Florida California
You can listen to the mainstream media breathlessly misreport the spread of covid-19
Or you can do your homework like I do
Day in and day out
The truth about covid-19 lies in the date
And the truth is Corona is not the leaf
Threat
Majority
American population
So there you go
It doesn't matter
It doesn't mean anything
No sure they're 120,000
You know compared to
6 billion Dam
The gigantic number that six billion about the time
Here's another way
Big number
So
According to the FBI
They're about 16,000 murders per year
Bright
Only solve
And don't really
Prevent
About
47%
So
That means that
The threat to you America
Is practice
Nothing
Finally get rid of
Oh yeah
His argument is perf
If you use
If you use his
He's set up for himself
It's it's nuts
And anybody knows that a functioning Society
Cares
Even if it's not a threat to everyone
You should
Right
It seemed simple
And he is at home
All right so finally we get to the main events we get to our boy Rogers
Introduction
From Fort Lauderdale Florida political consultant
And former Trump
Surrogate Rodger Stone Rodger
Trump as a racist
Because they are deathly afraid
That he is going to pick up a larger percentage of the black vote
Come November
And they attack
You and they have a
You
Because you are a proxy
For President Trump
Glass shops
Turns out
Parkrose
How do you say the speaker at every single
Every pie
I just love the
That was a complete non sequitur
They want to call Trump a racist because he's going to
They never speak of races
I never speak of any of that ever again
You just start
Introduces
Yeah
Yah mean
I think they probably is also great like
Solid analysis
The people called Trump raises cuz they're afraid
Going to win more video
Oh yeah
Seems like
That's why we got to lie about
6%
Cool
Call Maurice's
That's cuz
He is
You bet
And this is where
Stone begins to
Bag
Beg
For President Trump
And I think that we owe you some qualify
Congratulations other very deeply qualified in your case this
Amy Berman Jackson
Cimarron here in a moment
Delayed
Your Surrender date
Toujeo until
July 14th
It's only a couple
Weeks
You have
A lot more work to do between now and then because this
Quite cut it doesn't
Know exactly
Does narcotic
It does not quite cut it
So far going on Alex the show
Broadcast
You got a lot more work today
But we have qualified
Congratulation
For getting two weeks off
He was trying to get a further
Yeah yeah yeah
Congratulations
Oh yeah
Stone is going to get to work
This is where he's going to start back
He knows what to do
Majority in the house
Concerned about the
Dangers of
Covid-19 virus
The same time
They support my being sent
Hue
Facility
Georgia
Worthy
Danger
Covid-19
Infection
He 7 years old
Is extraordinarily
This is a really good play on his part because it is something that's real Jason
I don't trust him
More Center I care more about it if he was still circulating and making this appeal
On Networks
They first of all took covid seriously
Screaming about
Then releasing murderers into the streets because of covid-19
Rodger Stone eating to not go to
Prison
Environment
Minimum security type situation
That facility
More seriously if it wasn't
Being
Distributed by people who have tried to fear about not letting people out
Based on these very same concern
It's Discord
I don't I don't appreciate it
No it's it's cognitive dissonance
He's doing this on a show where just five minutes earlier
The guy said well we should let young people out all the time sure they're so asymptomatic
Smith a virus
They don't know anybody like Rodger Stone
Somebody who's 65
With a history of asthma
Is also at
The most dangerous risk from the covid-19
How does Graham not know
Somebody twenty-year-old
Someone with a broken bottle
Give him covid-19 from going to the bars
I just made a compelling argument for why G
I think you just wrote Conair 2
David Gray
These people doing this desperate
Self-contradictory nonsense
I wish
Rodger Stone does lead into it
Hard
And went around on all these shows I was like
Gather a dirty dozen
I'm breaking out
There's no convincing Amy Berman Jackson
So what I'm doing is I'm putting together a team to break me out
Like why not just do that ahead of time
Explosives guy
Need a Spaceman
Somebody who's really good at picking locks
He's just going on shows any like recruiting the hose
He's like
Listeners
Motorcycle
Why the f*** not because if it's been Rodger your girlfriend
Look for rest of your life a parody
That's how you could have penance
You've lived your life like it in secret silly supervillain
We build a laser to break out of this prison
Exactly
Are that plan Alicia interviews on dammit
Rodger
Could do it
He's in a position where he's about to go to prison
No one else is ever going to be in this position where you may be meddled with an election and now you're going to
The prison and your
F****** give you a pardon that he hasn't given you yet you still B
So why not cover your bases to get a super villain
Bacon
And stone has a moral responsibility
To fulfill his purpose
Elon Musk keep builds tunnels
Before we continue this meeting
No one can wear mask
Tamale break
The one rule
The big guy stands up in jail
Alright we're going to need new muscle
Alright pisses me off
Yeah
Lean into it Rodger
Do better
What's a really good point
Cuz he thinks you might actually
That's a big difference
See that's what
Trump needs to send him a quiet man
Don't worry about it you're getting a pardon on July 13th
Everything's cool
Go hard
If you contact
I have a lot of bad press on me guess what would help with that
Mr. penguin
I could pardon Rodger I would pardon him if he did
Actually it's because people would probably end up
Tried to blow up prisons
That's true in a movie it's funny but the real-world probably would get way out of hand
About Hospital
Through
That would be bad in real life I wouldn't like
Like that
Call
Continue
Always not his fault guess whose are villainous
Wait where do I get the gas
Okay
Nope right back to judge Jack
We made a motion
Before judge Jack
Based on the
Department of Justice
And the US Bureau of Prisons
Policy
Moving
High Ridge
A prisoners from
From prison to home
Rather than
Incarceration
The judge ignore those arguing
Entirely
Okay
Yep I'm sorry judge Jackson
I've been to every time I think of Rodger Stone
The judge Jack
Distance coming to
Well that's the thing I don't
The thing that got me about that cuz normally I wouldn't even bother
He's just doing the whole
But
I hate the way that they always get
Raiment
They always let him frame it as
Is Judge Jackson
Nord
My concern
Yeah she did not
Onion on his
Having carefully looked over them
And even
By all accounts
Beyonce
Like I was reading the decision and there's a couple really good
A couple really good things
While the defendant correctly observes that other courts in the Sticks
Have granted extensions another case
Neither of those defendants were was convicted of threatening was convicted of threatening anyone
And there is no indication that either failed to abide by conditions of release at any time
Contrast
Mr. Stone was convicted of threatening a Whitney
Throughout the course of these criminal proceedings the court has been forced to address
His repeated attempts to intimidate
Stoke potentially violent
At a rave
Including individuals involved in
Give me investigate
Zeros
I remember those times
Rodger
You're going in there because you threatened to hurt the judge
And put out a million-dollar there yet
Like the whole thing
But here's my favorite one
The defendant's response to the courts
Inquiry concerning his
Is personal preventative rack
Purposes and avoidance
The public gatherings in accordance with these directives
Was vague
Carefully parts
And not reassuring
So you still been going to t.g.i. Friday's
She's literally like
Honestly
You're more dangerous to yourself
Outside
Sucking rally
Exactly she's trying to save this f****** life perhaps
Yeah just in Folsom deaf ears for me I mean look at the same time
If there were some sort of a
House arrest
Kind of thing until things calm down and Rodger
I would be hopping mad about
Xscape just
Get whatever punishment check
Society's deem necessary
That it was just delayed for safety measures
Concern for his own
Selfish purpose
Exactly
Because I don't
I don't see him or anybody
He associated with you have platform
Advocating
4 people
Being released over health cancer
Because of that this seems just Halo it seems false
I don't care
A complete b*******
And here's very we get imprinted
I am praying to the president
To Grant either,
AeroGarden
Federal Prison
Prior to my appeal being hurt
I assure you.
Of course
Love's
Message to
Schrodinger's appeal
He's praying to Trump
Means it isn't
No I had to
Yeah
That's weird
Yep
Should have said very religious
For somebody who is a recently born again Christian
Stupid
Oh well
It's like they might not
This is our last clip right here
He's going Graham Ledger
It's not going to snow
Grandma
Usher
You're too generous
Let's make it 4
Alright I will give you 400 it's worse than the 6
Billion
Where's the net
Cucumber
Fair enough
And then finally this is how it is
This is when
This is the last time he says any
Deposit WETA
And puts it on the screen Graham Ledger does
Listen this is weather
To try and get you pardoned as you mentioned
By the
The United States
Lori Hendry
I made a post
On Twitter and then
Significant
But significantly present
Trump read
We did
Her tweets tweets on this program
Significant
Don't you
I mean Ruby and is it true
To think it is
Why don't you know about this person
That's why
Cuz I was like
Why are you putting a tweet up from a random person
Just being like
I don't know who is Lori
Yo every morning and nobody at all
Before 2 just look it up on Twitter real
Madison that's unique
Do these right-wing ding dong
Doubtless they rely on like social media farming for
Do not do looking
The account today
Universal problem mode
Integrating news and social media together
Stupid
And the and the tweet that
He's talking about
Lori Hendry I looked into it it's a real Twitter account
I was hoping it was a Phil Hendrie characters
I was hoping
Phil Hartman
He's actually still alive
That would have been the
That would have been my
Michael is Joey's R JFK jr.
He is r.j.
She's a she's a conservative Twitter
Apparently a real person
Right like she's got 300,000 followers
And the company Vine site
Along with
Nbcnews looked into it
More than half of all of her
Are direct
Yeah so she's
She's just made up
She's a complete creation
You know
Petition out there tonight
Get Rodger
Hazel Park
Why would Trump if that's the thing
Alright
You're telling me the Trump retweeted a petition to get
Trump to do the thing that he could do that seems weird at any point in time
Petition
Just Do It For The Dirty Dozen
That's what we're in
Yes two weeks visiting movie
This is a Brewster's Millions situation has
Record time limit
There's two weeks to get
Together a team of the baddest dudes
Able to climb over that wall
Maybe one surprising recruit who looks like he's
F****** screw never going to make it
Ends up surprising everyone
Here's the other thing I would get Jon gabrus to play that guy because he's a big dude
Nobody else
All right I like that
Here's my pitch for
Let's
Ross Perot
Alright
Cuz Ross Perot
Prisoners of War out of prison
Ukiah live
Okay
And everybody
Who's going to be delivering
Larry Larry Nichols of course
I love this movie I'm really sad
Robin Williams Good morning Vietnam
Well then
Doing recon
The Shadows
Who's in the bushes
Absolutely
Okay what's Alex
Every movie he's ever been in
The Street Preacher screaming nonsense but okay so he's a virgin
Yes
Carter somewhere
Baby blanket prison guard
Alex's drug everyone's attention away Nichols wheezes
Everybody else
I need to use the bathroom
Elon Musk comes out of nowhere
Is the boring company you know they bore the holes
You get in there
And that is also a diversion
They're all diversion actually want to get Rodger out it's a prank
This was great guys
Buck Rodger
We're at you for the final
Enjoy your
Short prison
So yeah that's
Graham Ledger
And we can never speak of Graham Ledger again unless it's better
Pretty terrible
You know I checking in on it though cuz I have suggested
I took bad thing
Fantasize about
The movie
About Rogers
I guess
We will be back
Website
We are also on Twitter
Elgin score 5 - outdoor
And we are on Facebook
And finally I am neither
Leo
Nor am I
Desert score
Holding
Alex