I have great respect for knowledge by now it's why I'm sick of them posing as if through the good guy
Need
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Jordan Jordan
Is going to be real for you
Okay alright
It's a
Having fun and enjoying the small stuff
Little things like Michelle
Blowing my mind can be changed by just
Couple screws and elopements of wood
Really customized things
In that way that I've never really
I've never really done that with Apartments because I've always felt such
Such disdain
You just like relish that you came over I'm in the middle of building a little Shelf
Course for some plants
Upcoming new planet watch
Will become of planning
I don't know this is just Elementary stuff that probably should have
Again this is V like I learned how to cook a chicken breast
Find me that's the way that I am reading you are seeing
How about you
Of course 9 is enjoying the little things in life
Smuggs
Tapestry with an emotional support pelican
Sure that's fine
Redirected over to the teepublic store
Where there's a ton of various things
Jordans
July 2nd
WhatsApp
We're going to cover two episodes today but it's all happened
Studio
Delane Maxwell got arrested and he realized he had to come in
Gomn for some reason decided to come back and do another 2 hours at 7 evening
This is going to be a complete disaster thought I was parked
Going to be the walkthrough of mind that is to
Completely fractured
Okay I'm lost
It's um it's not Hatchet I'll tell you that
Okay
Of course
Some talk about crimes against
Harden and awful for the entire time
Probably advise Maybe
You're sensitive about those sorts of topics
Maybe
Skip Law stay away from if you're sensitive
If that's all you want to hear will see you at the end
It's a book Zoo weather
So first
I'm a policy wonk
Next
Thank you for Anthony next apartment
Thanks Justin Bieber
Kristofferson
I'm a policy wonk
Hold on
Kris Kristofferson
That right
I don't know
State of the school
I was at
Next big stock
Highwaymen
Thank you so much
Democrat
We got to go Full Tilt Boogie on this
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
If you'd like to take that generosity germinate at much like a little cea
Deliver to charity in your area
Rambo
Appreciate either of those
Yep
Some things are over our way in the mailbag I don't know if you see over there a little little little
Yeah this is from
She writes
These novelty beverage accessories
Put one of your wine bottles in
I meant also
Catherine
Sent us each of the oxygen
Singer
You end up getting sick
Along with this note
Dan
And then of course
Don't worry no one was to me and one was you
Most important
Which I hope you guys want
Your ass is getting me through a really tough time
Do you from Mary Catherine
Not a health Ranger thank you so much and we do also hope we don't
On the off-chance Rihanna and America
Zip
Mailbox close
We're going to start here on July 2nd for the Regular Show
And
Course
Elaine Maxwell has been arrested
I really thought for sure this is going to be all he talked about
Pedophile ring stories
He talks about
Episode
Especially
Weather 2007 full spread
Tortured
Paintings
Cute little Corrections we did on
Pizzagate
Little is carrying a lot of weight on that
Remember that about CNN
MSNBC
Megyn Kelly
Who made it their life's work try to destroy Infowars
We've been exposing
Specifically
That's interesting
Glam ironically little is probably the biggest
Sure sure Alex's story of what
Recovering to make the globalist Banning from social media
Change it
Just depends on whatever stories trying to pretend he's been right about forever
I guess that isn't the case goes against sexually because he
Covers
Alyssa cover FC news and they are not
Social media
It runs the gamut from Mainline reporters to podcast
See if she was embarrassed about the guardian of the entire newspaper website with
Was taken down
Do I search on this in the past but Alex did not talk about Jeffrey Epstein in his early career or if he did I can find
No evidence that he did
If you search for the name Epstein on Infowars
Specifically for articles post
Did prior to January 1st 2015
You'll get tons and
Tons of results
However these are articles with headlines like most Americans oppose health law but like provisions
Or
Florida holds fast to get to January 31st primary day
These articles have nothing to do with Epstein at all but the way and forwards website is built
Is it it takes archive
Content and that it adds him links to new breaking stories
So there's a new headline about a bronze Jeffrey Epstein statue found in Albuquerque
And now that headline being in the link section of all these old articles causes them to populate in searches
For the name Epps
That is a response
I don't know if it is I think because the way to game search album
You're it's some sort of just like
Lawd is completely unnavigable for the most part
And I feel like this is
Probably some oversight
Because of universal to Alex's website
Right like it's only the case with info
Prisonplanet doesn't work the same way never attribute to cleverness towards gaming the algorithm
What could goes worth
Competency
Yeah that I could explain
A fair amount
In June 2008 Epstein was initially convicted by Florida Court
Create an underage girl for the purposes of prostitution
If you searching for his website specifically for articles about Epstein that were published between the beginning 2018 January
First 2009
Nothing comes up
I found this really hard to believe since I've explained that he was the first one
He's just making that up
I decided to look a little further and found that there are no posts that contain the word Epstein that were published on Prison Planet Alex Azar
Original mirror site prior to 2015
That seems really weird because that was the site that was much less focused on
It was more just about having the articles there
And like I said it doesn't have that same old articles of the new timeline
So I decided to consult the Wayback machine and see if I can get a better sense
Website homepage around that time
On July 26th
The Smoking Gun published an article covering the probable-cause affidavit in the Epstein case
Which is the one who would eventually plead guilty to in 2008
To my thinking went like this
If Alex was all over this story than covering it by that
July 26th 2006
I have no idea about the inner workings of the smoking
Garner their editorial
Alex Sonata covered it
As well by that point
There's no snapshot of Infowars from that
August 10th 2006
A whole lot of the website
I would say almost the entire thing
Middle East
Conflict which makes sense given the video landscaper 2006
On the sidebar of the site
There's a big list of topics
Like the main topics event for
They include total surveillance Society
Cashless Society control grid
Embedded microchip
Rsib stolen phones Bohemian Seltzer's
Freemasonry and the Patriot Act
These are the themes they were in us all about back there
Because you might call conservative conspiracy topics
There's no trace of the current flavors of Alex 2006
He talks about global worship the literal death
Hurting children
SpongeBob
Differences
It's a fundamental similarities
In there but the differences are glaring
When was also considered
Like in terms of trying to figure out trying to sort through the pieces of like where is this reporting then if you could cover
15 years
You and I have both watched and game and The Obama Deception in their entirety
At no point
Documentary
But you definitely should have
If what Alex is pretending is the case
Was Acura
As far as I can tell Alex didn't cover Epstein it all until the fairly recent past
That's okay
I don't really think that the problem
I don't expect Alex to hit every story and particularly back in that stretch of time between like 2006-2009
You have fewer writers to cover everything that came up
It's okay for Alex's now covered Epstein until pizzagate came along
Cuz that made the connection between Hillary and a giant crab all the pedophile human traffickers
It was an essential piece of the argument
Yeah it makes sense that he would start covering all this stuff then you have to
Necessarily
It is a gigantic failure
Primarily because if he didn't cover the story previously
It really does just appeared opportunism about
Story he's trying to weaponize for his own game
From my perspective that's exactly what this is
Until any evidence is provided to the contrary
Impossible there is at some point Alex brought up the name Jeffrey Epstein
In the context of like reading a headlight
He's claiming like I was all over 15 years ago
You can find plenty of content
Infowars
You websites from the times that these articles should have eggs
Conveniently broke this story
In 2007
2008/2009
I don't know what's going on here
Calls but they were all like the best friends or the bestest friends
Also just because this is Donnie I wanted to bring up something that I found 2-0 have nothing ever changes
2006 Alex at a special page on a website about censorship
God. He set up an email address for people to email him if quote Myspace removed your page
Because of political
Nothing ever changes
Alex
South America
And self mythology about
Doesn't match up with my experience
The times that I've listened to
Parts of his work that
I went back and I looked through his bibliography for endgame just to like refresh my memory of everything and
There's nothing
You know I mean obviously it's Swiss cheese
Microsoft
Later we'll have it
Any of this stuff
I don't know it if someone can provide any kind of salad
Improve Alex Wright
This looks like bulshit
Yeah and
I mean I don't know I guess I have to say in retrospect
It seems like
It's too obvious
Low-hanging
Fruit ripe
Like why would you go on about the
Child's it whenever
When right in front of your face you got a billionaire connected to the highest Echelon of power
Affidavit
Well it's you got right there
Reality is this
That wouldn't remove the needle conspiracy theories are much more easy to sell
Back then that's probably
Probably what he wanted to do crash commercial
So does not ever provide
President still going
The front formula more expensive that coming up
Y'all shouldn't a question so
Believe this little jewel is going to get
Exclusive
And what's coming next is a pedophile House of Cards
Against
The Infowars article that has the video of the show he's currently
Trump speech
The show Alex's doing
That does not end up ever giving Secrets details
Weather
You have to work really hard
I mean I guess I guess ungenerous because he does talk some s***
I guess
Huge
Ghislaine Maxwell
Super spy
Triple spy operative in the Epstein pedophile ring
This seems like a little bit of a dick move for me to complain about Alex's pronunciation given that I butcher a ton of words
All the time
Alex a big expert on the whole FC doesn't know how to pronounce Cillian Maxwell's name
And that strikes me as
I didn't know how to pronounce
For sure but I am not
Expert on this case out of
I did not sit for awhile to because you know
The French name only seen it in right exactly
Excited to chat
Oh that would be smart news been on the Epstein beat 415 Buccaneers I Galaxy
Pretends to
Alex has this this entire
This fish
Narratives all all built out there what's going on is that Epstein was
Getting blackmail on people in order to solidify the globalists control over everything
But also he's a middle manager he's just like a Renfield as
LG
Call her about whether or not
Epstein's middle management and it was
How do you think Ariel from The Little Mermaid would do on the on the Cubs do you think she would hit 240 what do you think
What's the level of Ohio
Narrative about
About
I'll stop for a while
But it turns out there's a little bit more to it
Spirituality
Don't remember ladies and gentlemen that they want to control people and they want to compromise
The only way to really do that
Because you also
God
Remove history
Action from you
Adding dirt on you thought just about blackmail
What I'm going to do is alright
I push this down the road a little bit here
Alright so I started to like
What is he talking about
And I realize that it all just comes from Joe
Like you
Oh okay
To the stuff we talked about God's protection and Butthead
Call him talking about how God allowed
To mess with Jobe in order to prove that he had faced the outside of the
Really uplifting
The Bible that one
Right back on it as a message
Got your point is don't question me and I'll f****** your life and kill your kids
Maybe we'll get 15 more later like I don't know how that book Works you're a good and Noble person
Phuc yea
I will purchase whims of a deity you can't understand
I will
Mess you up
Because I want to prove a point
Well there's a reason it just be some big reason
Prove a point to say
I don't know
The pettiest book of the Bible
Takes a lot
Text from that I think if there's a lot of things about you
Conception
I think he might do something bad
That removes misunderstanding point of the book
Those ideas are are pretty traceable back
It's kind of weird to me
Got a weird
When I said I was talk s*** this is the closest he has to like
Inside details about the arrest
I don't think you can prove this
I know some folks in New York on the sleeve attack
District
As you know we also know
Police New Jersey New York
And so I made some phone calls this morning as soon as this broke
What about
9 a.m. eastern
Thank you and they said absolutely has to do with
They removed a few weeks ago
It has to do with the fact that there's been a manafort
For almost a year
Some experts believe that
We're not really trying to get her
As soon as the news broke that Maxwell have been arrested and charged in the southern district that Alex would leave the firing of prosecutor
Story
Protecting Max
Arrest happen
Wow this is going to be a convoluted narrative dry makes stick for a number of reasons
41 Bourbons replacement Aubrey Strauss has gone on record to Maxwell's arrest was quote not at all related
To Bourbon Jacks
Probably more importantly it was Geoffrey Berman who originally filed the charges against Epstein
That can befall
It seems weird that you'll be the one to charge Epstein but then also be responsible for the non-arrest of Maxwell
Also this indictment Maxwell was arrested on WhatsApp
Involves a case being made to group of citizens who then decide on whether the case moves forward or not
Would have been able to push through an entire
And getting indictment in a two-week since Berman was Romo
Sometimes I just want
Alex can talk all this s*** but somebody right next time she just have to like starting
Explain charger with a crime
Wait you have to do all of this
The president just remove you
It'll be great
Alex's tacos
Which resources that Alex could you refer me back to the timestamp on my phone
How much more likely explanation is the Birdman was investigating Trump's Associates in Dusky got fired
Has Maxwell arrested something that's unclear and it very well may be too right now
There might have been
There's a lot we don't know right now it's option
That's a game that doesn't leave the good place
I'm pretty sure he's just talking
And this is as close as it gets to any kind of like
The headline is supposed to be Alex has deep secret information about Maxwell arrest
That's always Suburban
Really
Just be Alex speculates on wild story
So as all this is coming down
You know all these criminals
Are going to start happening
Information
Begin to be drug out into the sunlight
And that's why you're going to see cartoonish things but
Pop culture
There's thousands of tunnels underground and hundreds of thousands of children that ever seen by
A what
Wait what
Special Forces
Call
So
That's confusing
Because
Almost identical
I'm saying you're going to hear Wild Things
Are there kids underground
Yes you are there tunnels of course
That's weird
I think that was Alex trying to shoot on Cuban and then realizing
Stop
So Alex is teasing has big news that doesn't really ever come has to do with the Maxwell
Situation
Ain't you just teasing me
So he keeps teasing but there's something else, too
It's in Peoria
Quite frankly
I want to make a few more phone calls before I
Sounds like
Exactly why
Is this is a big deal
Also I'm Not Afraid repercussions releasing this information
You didn't really had an operation for people
Exactly right
But
Most people be sitting there office thinking right now about
To sit here is all this keep coming in
The backstory
Contact
Still it's not a good feeling though
When you get such bombshell info that you know is confirm
Wheel
Think about how you were leasing a little bit but
I need your prayers Pub
2020 is a very special year to the globalist
Run off to break their
This is like
I got to come up with something good
And the writers are hitting the wall
More like stalling
Just going you're almost there you're almost at the break
Alex
Doesn't get to
Whatever information he's pretending he has defenses
Barbie ideas
You know you Jordan
You're out there
You post something about Infowars right people call you crazy
Response
About the New World Order
About Epstein
14 years 15 years before
Years before he got busted
Protect traffic the first time
Was
Documents
Triple agent of us British
Intelligent
And he was running
The Summit
With Bill Gates and other top scientist
I knew what Bill Gates was up to
The information
Ciclop is fun because it gives you more specifics about Alex
Who's covering Epstein
Probably like what
2005 or before
Further Alex has a certain that he knew about Epstein
I'm some big documents in running Summit
Who's that
Because I've listened to countless hours of Alex's show I know that what he's talking about is the group that Bill Gates was in
Call the good cop
The philanthropic Collective that included people like Bill Gates Warren Buffett David Rockefeller
Sure the group in 2009 and claimed the roster also included Oprah Ted Turner and George Soros
The meeting was apparently prompted by the economic crisis and public discussion about
Kind of meeting of billionaires
Yeah that has a real
Circle does not mention Epstein it all
Epstein was the one behind those
Thanks for that meeting of those people
There's no proof of this other than Alex's rant
The only evidence I can find offer Dunkin
Conspiracy sites about this is that Epstein was on the Board of Trustees of the Rockefeller University
Took place
That's a fun piece of information for someone to play around
One term for resigning
The time he was around Rockville University doesn't match up with the time when this meeting took place
Because there's a surface-level appearance of connection Alex's decided to report on this
As concrete and reel
This club did not exist before 2009
There's no real indication that it's an actual Club as much as it is a super
Group of super wealthy
We're trying to combine their efforts to
Global economic crisis
They're better at
Are all in the same building
Your call on that
Horrifying recruiting video
Water for these billionaires or safety idea that meeting like that is great
As far as
And if you consult Alex's old reporting never brings up Epstein
This is just an element is added to the story later mostly because of how important the narrative is to rationalize and supporting Trump
Though he's a horrible person doing a horrible job
And then there are the connections between Bill Gates and universities didn't come out because of
Competent reporters into older things
You know there's a whip there's a way you can you can be a shitbag
And you can just claim that you knew all of this the whole time
Or you can build
You know you can build on the good reporting
Alex is not building on the good reporting and adding anything into
Christie's building
Further things
Been wondering lately
Surprise
Surprising is what Alex
Yeah it believes
The cortical trans agenda is about
Rawlings
Moment
30 years ago
Instead the trans movement
Is about abusing women and children
Not abusing people
The highest rates of
Suicide drug abuse
Not because
But because of the culture
And the system
What it does
Cyborg
Children
We want to be a robot
I'm a trans robot
What it's about
That's not what's coming
Trans issues and transhumanism
Yeah
Are you give them that mechanical arm until they are 18
I don't know man
Laser cannon for an arm
Dude I don't know
Shaking my head but then I would have probably just ignored it
Apparently we learn
What is Dad
Let me just really I just need to
Alright
JK Rowling
Ghost
Alex takes that as an opportunity to explain what's wrong with cyborg
Okay now I'm in red
But I don't know if they're cyborgs
I don't know that apparently were involved.
Related projects
I remember
17 years ago
Remember my family was in a
Restricted
Reaping in Texas
Cuz it was commissioned officers with all the top
Come on man
You're stalling
Makeup something good
As you know somebody special forces
Rolled out publicly
While they were right on time
They figured it out he got in trouble
12 year old Telugu story
The twelve-year-old lying about why they were late to school
3D IHSS for
Ground-based
We need robot teeth
What's Mikey
Basically all the people whose background checked out
What the f*** are you talking about
There's so much wrong with that
First most glaring problem
17 years ago
2020 Alex's dumping like we got 10 years left
Deadline
This family member is
Alex
Realized
Not that much trouble
Everybody
Seems like that would be a court-martial little bit
Not a slap on the wrist
Leaving all the sort of
Might decide to is the idea of Alex's Dad here
There are these people
That have underground bunkers I swear they are creating cyborg
Right now
Everything we know about Alex
Diesel Depot
Because that's what the globalist
Do
They tried to recruit Alex's dad and it's good that Alex's dad didn't go along with that
While at the same time the only reason they would recruit Alex's dad is because he was a true patriot it's something that
The globalist themselves are apparently again you have latched onto your problem
I don't know why the globalist would
Specifically only hire antique octopus
Whiteboard project
It's just some it up exactly
Now I've no I know you think that that doesn't make sense based on the table
Make sense because they're trying to seduce the antique
Stanton sound inconsistent
So Alex guitar store about the transition smoothly into animal-human hybrids
Okay caller
Check this out
Stop yourself
I've named it a secret lab by the way
Actually show you
Pygmy Pig
I needed this I did miss it it's this weird
Okay so
Look
I understand
Maxwell News in Suffern Alex
Yeah I mean
What I hear there is Alex forgetting that he's supposed to be the one who
Lab
The fish with human eyes
His own store that was the fish that he saw he's talking about
The pigs he didn't see the pic pic book the pygmy pig people I would argue that if Alex wants to make this
Point his story about the fish people is more compelling than the second dance
I saw the fish people eat fish people and forgotten about it
Are you take out your memory
So
This leads to Alex's discussion and this is why I really connected
Two eps
Stop is because
Apparently Epstein's also Trek
He's created nahmias
There was that
Talk of how he wanted to see the human race with his DNA
Listen to he's creating an army of clones
I love those regular insane billionaire s*** yeah
To be in the realm of I want to be the next to Genghis Khan
No I'm open to revising that position if someone can have it in
As Alex is suggesting an army of clones
I don't think that I like taking Execute order order
I don't know but now it doesn't make
The case very well
He's talking about one of the Epstein victim
Was a very special Uno's who's
Bill Gates
Close route
If you don't just trade a cloning
Freezer it goes bad
You got it
So he was running a Toro Ranch
With hundreds of women
Projects
What are they doing in there
The word is
Experiments
Cloning
You name it
That's why you see the headline of the British government wants to pay for artificial wombs be put in
Men
They can be women
And now you got all these humanoids that are already walking around
They're not going to have right
Call Ben program genetically
Operate the weather
Alright
Alright so a problem.
I honestly doubt though
I don't know and I don't think listening to this episode and its entirety give you any time
Close
Clothes right there is a 1000 different things
Steve's to be talkin about
I got no handle
Trying to say
I would argue that if someone
Was a clone of Bill Gates
Sure they were human
Yeah yeah
People who are like
If that's Alex's hard-and-fast rule right it has to be
Artificial insemination
I don't know
I suppose that's when
I am
This is confusing
And a lot of this stuff I was listening to
I don't even care
Alright man keep on going
Listen
I'm just going to
Play clips of you rambling about cyborg
Log
To get through all of reality right now Dan
A good old Alex Jones screaming about chimeras
Yeah yeah
Is this episode is very restorative
And it will be even more so once we get to the evening
So
Just comes down to Good and Evil you know there's one side good
What's makes a reference that makes me think
He doesn't know which side
Maybe.
Bikes
Things like
Order 66
And they're taking over
Evil
You don't have political Solutions today
Eat first of all things that order 66
Jeezy but he's
He's the one who uses it all
Encouraging plan from science fiction
Explicitly
I don't like the bad guys
But you're not going to defeat the Jedi any other way
And the Jedi did you see them they're trying to overthrow the Republic
Alex Caruso
So Alex
Solution
I don't like the Vogons but you got to build that by folks
Just got to build it
Kill
Now since they're going hot
The Right Move by
Individuals in the establishment who aren't perfect
And understand
YouTube
Take these people out
Quickly
Week when you can play games on
Let music came in
Demonstrate
There's no doubt about it
Andy wants people to be afraid of just about everything
There's a long-standing
Certain narrative analysis from time to time
It's never been a varsity narrative and it's still not
And that is with Soros and his people are putting in
Attorneys in defense attorneys and prosecutors
In small places like all around the country in order to G
The Patriots or whatever
Preoccupied with
Because of I think
Down-ballot Sunday
Some Focus
Organizations
On local elections
Resents that a little bit
You talked about
That little baby
Little girls
District attorney
Put it on by George Soros and
Communist
Racial cover whatever come kill you at your house and they nobility
Cuz they're using them
You cannot make up the criminal nature of this
The full criminal attack
The Holdrege Criminal
Are y'all better run by pedophiles and devil worshipers what are you expecting
They're gone
You can't believe anything they say
Zombie lazy asses believe they're about to rule a liberal knows it's all
Super sale is in the heart of it right now
Free shipping free shipping
Goodbye everyone of his sales is involved free shipping
You're insane
Yeah you are
Mia's
That's a little star
We just driving
Zombie asses lazy asses for the masses
Soros put in these prosecutors and attorneys
In order for black communist
To come to your house and kill you
And then they don't charge it as a murder
Pretty weird communist under racial cover
Right that's what that's what he say
So that means that there are
Okay
They go undercover by being black
The safest
You can be
Because a political front
It's all very dumb
So I most of this episode I got
It's mostly like a rambling
Meandering evangelism
It is
Largely about like
You got it you got to go with God man
And I'm going to play this next clip that isn't really like
It's not fully substantiv there's not a lot to discuss about it but
It was what I really felt captured the feeling
But I would describe as meaninglessness of this episode
Before you can fly you got to learn how to
Crawl
I walked
Cuz the wings don't go out to Eureka
Good save
The planets
Have you reached out
Metaphysically God and knock on the door
I can get you to abuse a child
Worship Satan
Choose the devil
Then that's the ultimate sin
Moved or turned over to the
And then you become ghislaine Maxwell
Bill Clinton
Sniveling evil
Personal baubles
Troll
Thrown into a junk pile like a broken toy
Really want to be a pawn
Lose your Birthright to the universe
K
So purely selfish
John finally there
Fun
Fathomable conscience
So you just want to reward
We got Crawl Through the muck first
Before you fake
This is all just like
This show is nothing
Giving a speech at a bully pulpit
It is so little in Turkey
Analysis news
Hard-hitting anything it's just a guy ranting about the devil
It sounds a little bit like a writer's room for people who are trying to make inspirational slogan
Come out till 4
Caveat
Is another selling of people who might jump off a cliff
Sign but with a bunch of footnotes on her
So Alex at this point goes to calls because I think he just realize it's like
Whatever
So you go through this first caller who suggests that Elaine Maxwell is going to get covid
In prison when Alex says
Good call
Something's going to happen to her
Going to go out just like that for you
But don't worry
I'm going to happen to be put on the ventilator
And then she's going to slip away
Is on its way and everybody's got to get locked back in and she's going to
Call
Imprisoned or whatever and she's going to
I'm down with it
That'll be the end of her
You're given the global Austin idea of what to do
The global it's just as if this wasn't already on Meme the second she got arrested
Call Iran
Product but
He has one particular question about a product it's no longer for sale
Like the plug in and say that you're proud
Curious
If your toothpaste
This is going to be coming back
Lawsuit
The Attorney General of New York
What he says
We never said that
Committing the crime in my name
Only because
She's engaged in criminal activity
Sure
And says that I'm saying
Letitia James
I got a false alarm before I do it but
At the end of the day people love the toothpaste was the best-selling item
But
You know
I certainly hope she doesn't sue you for that
Alright
Here's where we get into the problem with doubling down imagine Dental
No
I don't know about litigious people right
I would suggest that if I were
Old murderer
Yes
I think so
Not that I know of
In the context of how much he hates her because she said
Lashing out at somebody because
Then you're doing something wrong
Let me build a real quick case for
Alright
This guy
Who hasn't known history of threatening people alright on the show where he threatens fit
Just people to kill
All of his enemies
On his show said that this person is a murderer
Qualifying her for the
I'm pretty sure this wasn't an opening time
Miss James if you're listening to take a take action on that really short clip
At all
I'm guessing his lawyers
We were like you cannot stop yourself from selling this toothpaste no trouble
Turn off the store
Oh yeah I'll start selling this
You are I got to do
Silence says a guy named Bishop Larry gaiters Gators
Guzman
And
I'm not going to talk too much about the
This guy because I
Couple things that are worth pointing out
Here's the first
Now I'm 23
Listen I have no sympathy
I am a contract Killer
Jesus Christ
Is to cut
That is the military armor blacklivesmatter
So I'm like
Having flashbacks
Here we are in the lead up to an election and Alex's talking to someone named Larry about the women he does
Doesn't like being witches it's not hard to find
You throw a stone at a Larry and you're going to find somebody who hates which reality is on rerun
Wow
Writers are getting very creative
Witches
So this guy's whole big deal is that there is like
Colt from Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom
And there's some sort of cult involved
It's it's
Nonsensical
Like things are connected to each other
You're so tangential and all over the place
About this guy
Pattern to make slime
Ormoc this because
I see it as more sign of unwellness
I figured this out who this guy is
He is a bishop
Some sort I don't know a lot of backstory
But he's somebody who's been a guest on Sam tripoli's podcast
Polo hat
He's one of the only people who will have Alex still on his podcast
How this connection got made
Atrocious
Bonkers
There's a couple of times when
He talks about word
And I think these are fun
I don't want to sit down and talk about like
Okay the way his brain is jumping from a 2L to be all over the
If you want to talk about
Pablo fun with that
Can you look at the term negro negro come from
Ero
Which means
Having sex with a dead body
This is where we get the term
Elio or necrophiliac
That's not even close to true now I'm going to have to say that this is
I mean
Just impact
From negro black in Spanish and Portuguese
It's also
Close related languages
Give me in Romanian narrow in Italian and nigre in Catalan
The reason for this is that these are all romance languages
Some are all terms that are derived from the Latin word for black
Necro
No letters cnh
Greek it's spelled with a k or Capa in its non transliterated form
Also nekros means dead body not to have sex with a dead body
The common word for black in Greek was mellow
And there're
Different routed words from two different languages
Trees
This dude is legitimately just making s*** up
And asserting this falsehood with
Amazing about confidence
Some letters and words in there the same way
Yeah
Does bananas this happens a lot
To turn media comes from the Hebrew term medium
Cracked
CNN
Goddamn
NBC
CNBC MSNBC they're all witches and warlocks
This should come as no surprise but the media does not come from the Hebrew word for witches
The Hebrew word for witches Is Mikasa has nothing to do with the root for the word We Now understand it
Is Media
That comes from the Latin root medius
The confusion here and what day does is just making stuff up about is that media comes from the Latin root
The same word as medium which English is a spiritualist
Or one who speaks of shows
1853 at least an
The word
Received and you're just not getting in on the fun of it like look look what I can see is it just you
Notebook the word notebook comes from notes that if you get rid of it
Not that can be something that you tie up and well that's also a rate of speed for traveling on your boat
Two different meanings of words have is the devil thank you very much
Jesus I understand the association games can have
Right
This is different than that though this is somebody who's trying
To use
False
Cognates
Root word tracing
In order to depict the reality that doesn't actually exist
And that to me is drunk
In order to communicate words have to have an agreed-upon
Right and if you just change the meaning of words then you are not I can't communicate well
Play lack of any kind of
Work because if you do comes from necro in Greek
Into it at all
You already know the answer cuz there's a couple letters difference
Anyways
Is the last Clipper going to look
Do of this dude
And I only really keep this in because it's
To hear man is just like
Good sandwich he doesn't actually there's no obvious eating
He's probably eating it
Witnessing
Between
The first constitution
Versus the global down cement lucitor in deep state
Constitution
Pius the 9th
In eastern central and Western Europe
When you actually have it
It's like you just can't
When you see how real it is
Is it people
Playing along with it
The second Constitution thing is just that Sovereign citizen
Some s*** we talked about the bed like the establishment of d.c. Washington DC
Yeah I mean
This is this is ridiculous I feel like Alex
If you were a sincere actor has a responsibility to listen to this guy
False in ridiculous explanations for Words be like I'm not talking to somebody
Be promoting it right for just because he hates black lives matter and Tifa
Great
I'm glad you agree with me on anything to get a black person on my show who
Who doesn't like like Liza
Will do anything I will make any sacrifice
It's rough to me that he is unable or unwilling
Exercise any kind of
Control mechanism over like pressing something
Grounded
But whatever
It has nothing to do with support or just support of things
Did I smart
Icanvas
The show gets to an end
And
IPhone
He got it no he didn't he explained all the guylaine Maxwell stuff I've been listening to this
So far I feel completely
A bunch of other stuff
I can't be traumatic experience listening to this episode
He just screams
About horrifying subject matter that I don't want to listen to him talk about
That was
Weird
Yeah a lot of cyborg
Let me talk to this
Linguist
Episode
That can't be it and I can't wait to see what he does on Friday
Turned on Friday's episode
It's a show from the end of June
I'm like wait a second
Stay
So I guess you just was like alright I'll just not come in on Friday or whatever all coming on Thursday
F*** is going on
I have gone to
Because all this episode on July 2nd
There was something that appeared to be cut out
Did Alex it said
I thought it was suspicious
So I went and I found the original version of it
It's one of those callers said s*** and they had to believe it
There wasn't anything to Spaceman
You could cut out the part where you call the district attorney
Post Exchange
I thought they were two special reports that were posted
The first was a Fourth of July there's a new Civil War
And it was worthless video where Alex was
Anyway
Not a board
However
There was a two-hour special
From the night
Of July 2nd
So he did his show
From 11 to 3/4 hour
Then he did whatever he does
Write 7
Back on air
I thought like yeah that makes sense
He didn't do his job
Conair for 2 hours
Butter have
Dick
Okay
As good as it's Friday episode
So let's check
I see what happened I turned it on
Immediately
I was
Worried
You know whatever.
Ears
Because the enemy
Attacking
What Academy, San
Flood
Raise up a standard against him
Asparagus
What's wrong
Daughter
Bright at night
So I sold
Yeah
Charlie's great time to be alive right now what the f*** is going on
I'm so scared
Yep that's right goodnight it's or Usher
Holy Spirit
You know what it's been a long time since I've thought about a workplace where you just
Find with your boss coming in drunk and doing a show
I don't know how drunk he is he definitely seems drunk
I will say that for sure
So here's the things that I want to bring in sharp closer
It's not 3 in the
No he chose to do this.
That's 30 seconds into the show
Heather wavering in his voice sounds like he's going to cry that's not nothing
No
I just heard that
Are you sure this isn't just another cut of the song
No
So
So much of this is your scattershot nonsense
Job so I came into this so much
Instead he's just talking about souls and s*** like
This makes no sense
You can still watch the new world order your children
Dead
They might live another year there 10 years
Dark Souls
There is no making a
Deal with
So the reason I wanted to cut that clip is because
It seems like it and Alex's cosmology if you do something bad
Your kids Souls will be affected
I don't like
This is a great religion
Filled with a god that is
Awesome
Is that kind of against the individualism that Alex thinks America is based on the idea that you aren't
Like whatever your you're past your ancestors
Way to control people's behaviors is by
Constantly and eternally threatening their kids Souls
I mean
I just think that's weird
Anyway
He does get to talkin about Dune Maxwell good for him
I guess
Jeffrey Epstein
Triple agent
Am I sick
Mossad CIA
Sex operative
Is it a federal jail
Academy
Feeling the fire of Truth
That's a good thing
But we should expect
It got a little Belgium
And we should accept it like
Christ
Scattered ideals
Because there is no
There is no defeat
I feel guilty
In moments like this
Well my family is mean
Persecuted
What I've done
But I am an ex
Stussy next
Christ
If anything I am
Guilty
But I am in such
Eiffel Tower
Why is your
During this moment
No I understand
This is amazing
Would you like a fragrance
They're all going to drown.
What are you doing
You know what I what I hear happened cuz I think your
The spirit behind this broadcast
I really f***** up with that getting laid Maxwell stuff on my main show
I got to make this up
But that started from the first glass of whiskey gets up the shows like
That wasn't bad
Texas ebony like no
I really didn't do that good of a
The job takes another glass takes another glass I'm getting back on
Another glass
Starset
Alright that's what happened I would not be surprised
And I know
That I thought that that was the motivation for him during the second episode because
Okay alright
I thought it was good
Right here
You know I didn't get
Tell the news I wanted to cover today
4 Hour radio show
I'm going to cover all this big news
Hundreds of articles
Stream news live
Efron
Hey it's all I
What is even appointed
There are people that want to believe a lie
You should talk about that
He's talked about that
Why pretty early in this special report he's already having an existential crisis
Is worth doing to begin with
It's unable to delete browser
Nail driver
Alright
We're going to start the stuff
Start so now Alex
I'm lying
He doesn't
Imagining told in court
Habitat
I'm taking your children wife
Because you
Demonstrated in Austin TX
Against the mask
Covid-19 lockdown
Wasn't even a law
And
I didn't have a lot of do it but
Because I'm a judge
I'm going to take
Your children
Commute
Because you protein
I'm going to take your Birthright
I'm going to take
Everything you've got
Your whole future
And yeah that doesn't scare me because
That's what your whole new world order is
What you didn't think
You wanted my children
Already
Committed
Did they were burned
To fight you
You fake
Big geyser.
Attack my children
Maybe something for your wife sir
Gold-plated
You want to rape
Thank you
Coco Chanel
No no
Hellofresh
The kill the other people
Will kill you
You'll kill me
You're my soul and I join you
You don't think I know you are
This is a mess
Wow so
Speaking to
To a judge
I think Alex might have be dealing with more competition
Ex-wife Alex stop bringing this to the air
Mass protests
The safety and well-being of
Children
Stop it stop it honey we were going to get
Chinese food tonight we were going to sit and we're going to watch this movie we've been looking for
Well my boss got drunk in the judge got mad at him for going to an illegal rally cuz he's an evil assholes
So I'm getting hold of boom mic for the next few hours this is embarrassing that sucks
This is a real bad luck
For your Champion Heroes crusading tip of the spear
This is a bad luck you're supposed to be making up for not doing your job
And you appear to be drunk crying and laughing about how your kids are already dead to you
Holyshit
That's a very normal and comforting
Wow
I will warn all of you watch
And all you listening
We have committed crimes against God
Benjamin Prime
We are going to be judged
This planet is going to be burned
Maycrest
You better get right with God damn
You better start
Fearing
Engineer that built the universe
Instead of bowing down to these
Midget
You have been warned
I don't sacrifice
The fight against in World War
There's no children didn't belong to meet him at
A lot of room for free
Trying to cover some headlines
This is Abby on Paradiso this is exactly what you would do if you were Perry being this this is
Pretty wild
So Alex gets
Headline here
Here's the Atlantic
What's the CIA
That
Count everybody
With a
You already got over it
And people
But don't have it
Why would they put that out
So dumb they're coming around
First things first is Atlantic article is from May 21st
So it's not exactly breaking news
It was about how there were test results included in the cdc's numbers the viral and antibody
Which most experts agreed with
Confusing
Try to determine current infection where I am to past infects
This error was identified and as of early maybe it was resolved
Test results
A big part of the issue is the different states recorded their numbers differently in reporting
Antibody test as a single figure
The big issue here though is that this mistake would only make the Opera
Break
Far less severe than it would otherwise
The reason is the antibody tests are meant to be administered to the General Public
Which are meant to be given to people you suspect of being sick
Because of their differing applications
You have a built-in assumption that the rate of positive results in an antibody test
Positive results
Metric
Negative antibody test will give a tendency to drive down a positive result
Atlantic article
If even a third of the country's gain and testing is come by expanding antibody test not viral test
To detect an outbreak is much
Smaller than it seems
There's no way to ascertain how much of the recent increase in testing is from antibody test until the most populous states in the country
Among them Texas Georgia and Pebbles show their residents everything in the data
This is an interesting story and it isn't nothing
But understood in its proper context and not just read is it completely unexplored helpline
This story does not support the argument that covid-19 is a fraud or the numbers are overblown
If anything it suggests that things are worse than they look
Well I'm not just that but it's
Just pointing out
Another massive failing
In terms of
Having a coordinated Federal response
Through every single state
Doing things differently is only f****** everything up
So having a coordinated Federal response with a strong leadership
That will be able to kind of
Streamline this whole process is going to go a long way toward mitigating
Nothing but masturbated
Explorer doll doesn't really do anything other than say
But don't worry
New study says black lives matter protest
Slow the spread
They probably
By creating antibodies
How to talk about a study was carried out by a research team has co-authored by a professor from the University of
Andrew free
The basic gist of the paper is an examination of the net result black lives matter protest
Something Behavior
From the study
Well the protests themselves were large Gatherings that do not match well with social distancing guidelines
The protesting population is not the only one that may have a behavioral response
For example other individuals who do not wish to participate in the protest
Perhaps due to fear of violence from police clashes or general unrest
May have chosen to avoid public spaces while protest or underway
This could have an offsetting effect increasing social distancing behavior in other parts of the population
Their result they found was quote
Using Anonymous cell phone tracking data from safegraph incorporated as well as data on the local
Covid-19 from the centers
For Disease Control and prevention
We demonstrate that cities which had protest saw an increase in Social distancing behavior for the overall General popular
Cities that did not
In addition we find no evidence
Net covid-19 case growth differential Eros following the onset of black lives matter protest
And even a modest evidence of small longer-run case growth decline
The argument has papers making his one that Alex doesn't understand
He's an incompetent
Probably drunk baby
It is in also
What you see there is so
All of these guys all of these
Bulshit propagandists want to create a cause and effect
As a as a
Its own kind of simple streamlined
Somebody does this and that means this happy
What they're demonstrating is that
It is an impossibly large system with an infant number very
So you saying over because this happened to this happen
You don't understand you couldn't even imagine why they would do like oh well
There's other behaviors that change around
A massive system as opposed to being an action by a person
Right right
Analysis
The protests
We're done in a way that was rejecting of Public Health
Is everybody
He was going out with their best to keep distant from
Become super spreading event
And under those circumstances I imagine that this analysis by these researchers
Quite different
But because
They are
Tr2
Spend some questions about like
Exactly how definitively we should treat this
I'm just talking about like Alex doesn't even understand
So with terms of like
Substance
That's a good way to put it that's why I was going to go for us
There's something about
Scares
Because yeah most
Yubals here
What
Power
Because the real
Christ energy
Seeds
All the evil
Buzzards
When
Vampire bat
And karaoke
Hippogriffs
J.k. Rowling's going to sue you for that
There was some
Special day
And what was it
Virtue sex
We care about that
Cadillac
It was
We believe in human
No matter what color they are is they've got strength
We want to work
What day I'm and we want to unify around
Of course we'd realize that
When we first
Got the eye
Idea
To build a house
What
Build a farm
It takes time
Time what
It takes time and you know maybe you start up by enslaving
Humans if you have power we want you to work for us for free and then if you build
Well there's that
What we didn't know it was bad at first
Or the third
Time or the seventh time for The Zephyr all those people back then were saying slavery
Really bad do you have to listen to them when they spoke
What are you talk
Whatever
My God that's a fun way to look at history and accurately
More fun
What is
With these people
So look dude
This is very
You need Jesus
Wings to reach for Jesus to get him to open those wings
Atheists
What about 15 through smart
Zout
They only think they're smart
Because Satanist
You can be an atheist all day long you're really smart
You get ahold you don't believe in God ouv
And animal
Oh you're so smart
You have a defense
Good behind the scenes
There in front of pentagram
They're killing babies their devil worship
You're God's got a thousand trillion * a power they don't know what to do
Because you're God.
They don't have any power
What
All they have is
The power
A pistol gun
That's pretty powerful on reality
The best Uncommon Sense
Piss on their own instincts
So much piss
Who is this
Pissed off just a just a real
So this leads into a long rant about Bill Gates wanting to kill you
Is the sentence that is normal to have on any other podcast
Instep
And he Alex does explain the like is 100,000 people all pray for Bill Gates to go down
We don't have that right
Not trying to dominate you they're not trying to go
That's that's phase one
They want you
He wants every damn person he looks at
Because he hates himself
Everybody
Everyday
So
I should probably get all the
I want to come up here
Commercial free
I talked about
Reality
The planet
And the reality of the
Decisions that are being made
Now
Between you and God
Between you and
Eternity
Quit that's what's going on
What happened
I definitely did not get drunk
After having a bad go round with my ex-wife
And feel the need to vent like a child on air
That is that's not what happened at all.
Not at all and if you're thinking
You're a globalist raise a vampire vampire bat
So NSX go about starts about
You know like everyone had slaves so it wasn't that bad of a thing ever
Student version of temporal ethics
Every
Sector they weren't nations in their region
So what
It's not a good thing is that a bad thing
What
50 million years ago reading stuff I mean it's like
What does that mean
Well those are animals and morality
He's implying their independence
I don't know
I think he's still around
There is absolute moral relativism
Because then everyone had slaves it's neither good nor bad
I mean
The implications of that are are are heroin
I mean like if you could just
Any issue that you want to talk about it like whether it's no he's super against
Abortion but if everybody is fine
He can't
You can't think that it's because there's something known as morality
I went through all the time because
The past what it was either wrong or right in the path well it's wrong now but that's not as bad as abortion
I mean like there was
You know there were times and civilizations where you know Alex talks a lot about how like human sacrifices so
Horribly wrong
Cultures that did it in the past
You know
You see where this really off track
Pretty quickly
Just ever is Easter
I know exactly what
I know that white people enslaved
I know it was wrong
I know my success is built around stolen labor
Stolen value
Stolen Life
I know all
I don't want to feel bad about
So slavery's fine
History of Christianity
Particular
It is
The thing that stopped all bad things
Ever but why Christianity came around and 6
And that is the thought that he's working through here
Everything is chaos
Until Jesus
White Jeep
Africa
500 years ago was here we go
Warzone
Here we go
So is Japan
So was
What's in Russia
What we do
We're so successful species
We take over we grow crops we build palaces
That's our neighbor
He's got a problem and we're going to catch
Until
Jesus
Christ
Comes along
And says we need to love each other
And love God
And we need to build a snow
Society together
We need to stand for justice
Freedom
We go to the Stars
That's why you had Rwanda
Was Christian less than 10% of population
All the well
The other root word animus
They couldn't do anything they
They could get them.
The same genetics
Chrono
An export deals
Jobs
XSport
And now it's
Might want to look into Rwandan history a little bit
That's really close
To what you might call
Revisionist
Ensure
Rwanda
Dynamics
It's really upsetting
Yeah from a lack of information standpoint
And then from a using this atrocity this
Score of human history
As some sort of a prop in your leg
Jesus
Made
These people prosperous whereas these other ones not it's it's
It really is it's but it's made of
To the point of life
11th century kind of thinking in order to get people to go to the
Crusades
It's it's
Like we're supposed to be Beyond
Do you know it's 2020
Alex isn't when he's drunk
So I think
Alex realizes after rambling for quite a while that
Isn't talking about anything
He's not hitting these new stories not what's going on supposedly supposed to be doing
Answer he calls for a special report
Middle of the night
Great Mall
I don't know what's
Tell me about Alaska
Program
Exercise
Number 7
Infomercial but hasn't already discussed imported formation
Will Air this and I'll come back on
Okay
Cool do they sleep in the basement
Even imagine what they're going through what is going on
Cuz if you're committed to the
Protective you can't be happy with that
If you're someone who's just like a slick
Fraud con person
No matter what the end
This is what I was saying
Earlier when you said
Haywood they can bleep out someone saying s*** but he can't believe about him threatening
General is a murderer
You don't have to post that you just turn it off this is 2 hours
It's not Live still on video
Good
It's too good of contair is almost
Nothing
Worth your time in this entire two hours
Unless you're you and me and you like to laugh and how we stay weird stuff
This was a gift to us
Special Report little bit longer to find
Adam Schiff
Doesn't have a soul
Process I think he accidentally
Support something that he's supposed to be totally against
You want that guy babysit your kids I mean look at that is not
Why that is a psychotic
Program
Blue
The kill us because
That's all it knows I'm
Oblivion
Outcomes
Tom Cruise
I mean
That's what it is
He doesn't know
And it's not a mean thing to say that about him
But he doesn't have a soul
Because when you got a man or woman
I figure this out
Several generation
They start having kids
They don't even have a life
And nobody push that book
I'm just telling you that's why
Is that
People like
Chef
Your elevator doesn't go to the top
I'm sure you've heard
They don't go to the
Stop
Oblivion
Sommore
That's exactly what they got
Assassin revelation
A boy
Indeed
BoBoiBoy
So I'm glad Alex remember that he liked Oblivion
That is a positive
I can't wait to hear more about that other episodes
Tire goddamn explode
Change my life
Heard it sucks
The other thing there is it Alex
So
No I did not know this
Yeah but you can breathe the soul out.
Spurs
Seventh Generation generation
Can't imagine why
Because that's inherited language
Soligenix
Is it a good
Can you breed a soul back into somebody
Applications the reverse would be true
If you do believe in me
Christians should only be having
Kids without their
Write what a Satanist
Could pretend to be a Chris
Infiltrate a family and then slowly steal the souls of all who take a lot more generator
Oh bo bo Fool's errand
I'm I'm 150
1/16 Solas
It does feel like some of these weird thoughts that Alex has weird things about like
I hear you're talking about how these these people who want to like allow people to have birth control options
Maryville eugenicist
You talking about how like if people used to be devil worshippers have kids don't have less of a soul
Get the f*** out here
Anyway
The Special Report
And he was not wrong
It is an Informer
News about how to buy survival food
It's going down
Alex is so
I'm proud of an infomercial to this true
Horrible food
You know
It's not some building
Suspense thing where I get up here and I go I've got all these articles I've got all the Snows I can't talk
I just can't talk
I just can't do this anymore
But I felt driven the night
Flowers
Matt came in and
Daria
You know
I love you guys so much and he put up a bay
I appreciate that
There's just a feeling like
We should fix it
Plane crash
It's all burn up is dead bodies on the field
We're just out there trying to like
Put it all back together again we just can
This is dark
Wow wow
I don't know why I'm doing I can't even do my job anymore I have a bunch of pieces of paper and
In front of me
I just don't even
You know it's fun
And also a little bit better
I think is a little bit
Early on in the show
This is Friday night
Releases this nuggets is Thursday night
This is Thursday night Thursday night
At the very beginning of the show
We had just finished recording an episode if you would listen to that
European like
Get back in here we got to do an emergency episode
I don't know if I would have
That's kind of like it's a little ugly
I feel a little reinvigorated
It's not because of Alex's pain or anything like that this is kind of
Interesting
This is
This isn't just the rote repetition of the same thing
I can't do much I'm terrible I have all this
To say that
Is escalated to another level because
He clearly was
Crying
I know
He was clearly trying to do his job by hundred percent doing another 2 hours himself
Capable of doing anything except it's saying nothing
It's all he can do
I was sitting here and been thinking on this and trying to reflect on it like
He was just trying to
El Shaddai
But he's not really doesn't look like not constantly going
Cabela's products
He does play that infomercial in the middle of this but
At the end after the infomercial he's kind of
Yeah means you're going to buy food might as well buy from us
It's not the same kind of like we're doing a
QVC's act like he generally would do those like
30 hour marathon
This this is
To mean to be a guy who
Legitimately did his show on The Elaine Maxwell was arrested which is supposed to be sweet
And whatever for him
If you recognize that the end of it I punched
Did I did not do the job
Realizes he's lost his arm
If he doesn't have the pitch
Anymore
He does not have the same skills that he had as a younger man
And
That to me is interesting
Yeah like that isn't
The content
Of course isn't there
But the emotional Arc of it is because you see the end of this
It's like he's f****** depressed as hell
Add himself yeah it's like this psychodrama here is is just like you said
Is that he this is not like his show
He's going to go to work
That's what he does as he's got a nine-to-five
This is special
This is there's some intent behind the
And the intent is very clearly
Which is something we do not hear him do whatever I don't know if I trust that
Pretense of Italy
And then
He's full of s***
Like as he's talking he's learning he's like
I don't have anything to say
I mean early in the evening report he says
I didn't cover the news that I meant to on eyeshadow
Talking about his ex-wife
Sweetie quickly
He just starts rambling about nothing and then is like I was going to talk about the news but then we got to talk about what
The connection is between you and Eternity
Constant more talking about nothing
Good just got all sorts of various scattershot
Bulshit
How many get to the end
Towards the end
There's just a recognition
I can't do this you can't do it and there's also recognition that I find even more interesting
Yes yeah if you listen to that clip
He's not just saying
I can't
I can't talk
I can't do these
Whatever these things are you saying I don't know why
Because I don't know why you do it's not true
Gulf between what he thought he was going to do and what he did now is so vast
Even he can't talk it away
Like he realized probably could as a younger man as a younger
Himself in this situation, because if you look back at his website in 2006
Very different
Very Far Cry 4
Show me some it's because
Going down these Lane
This is a guy whose business is crap
Or I mean
Probably
Exactly
So anyway
Whenever that happens
Of course
It becomes externalize
I receive that here too whenever
Personal troubles
I just want more
Just think
I can get myself right
Seriously
I can't watch it
Vicente the truth
I think you better get your ass ready
Got everything else
Because
This planet's damn time bomb
Tomball
And
It was badass stuff is
Good for you to just realized
Relationship
Me too
Wolf
Because
This whole thing's
Countdown
So the end of the world is coming
Great
It is over for Humanity and I guess there won't be a Lone Survivor
So yeah I mean it's just like that's that's just
Do me a reflection of his
Mindset
Why you look very depressed
Course because of how Alex is a
Person gets articulated
It seems to be from all the stories
Yeah how
Anything is salt
He's talking about this like great anger that he has with the Devil
I just wish I could beat up the devil
Listen I'm not preaching
When I tell you this
Me
Tell him myself
Zillow Maine
I want to
Pizza
I want to take Lucifer
Slammed his head in the ground
It Dylan
And if Satan can trick you
To try to
Content with him he win
You call Jesus
That's why I call it call and I just apologized for my God
I got
I'll show
Jesus Christ
Jesus Christ Jesus
The whole crowd
Basically is you may not realize
When you think you're having a great opinion about delay Maxwell you're doing this
Oh it is Jesus Christ
Most of the time
Bizarre Meandering evangelism
So congratulations
I think you should do
Which I think is trash but whatever
It is trash
In this dark moment is recognizing like
I did not do what I set out to do which was
Cover the news on this 2-hour
Live broadcast
So I got 100 articles
You know I was so mad at myself
When I got off the air
Everett was
Madden cover.
I said the crew hey we come in when you do 2 hours with me
I'm going to cover it all
I'm going to fix it
And I came in here
Shut the bed
I can't text it
Can't fix it
Wow
Only God can fix it
That's what it really comes down to
Here's probably was
News articles
Refuse
Broadcast
Gloves
1st Avenue
Here's the thing that I think is is fascinating
He's not fake
Crying
No there isn't like a fake over amplification of these things that he's expressing
Is him saying
I was really mad at myself when I ended my show so I told the crew come on in
I'm going to fix it
Is such an interesting thing because that's exactly what
I thought was his intention when I saw
Show
You f***** up this is supposed to be a big day for you Yep this is supposed to be like if your new 911 day or what
You f***** up you need to fix it that is what his intention was
I'm not making that up he said it
Fix this
And I can't fix
No one can fix it
It's dark
That is dark
Really really funny
It's really funny
Is this was a real
Someone who used to care about that
Tragedy
Yeah this is
Disease similar stories played out in like fiction of like
People who have lost their step or whatever you're not like you're in over your head
You know like this is this is something that you may be used to be able to do
You're capable of that you're no longer capable of
You just like you have that moment out onstage with your bomb and when you you think you should be killing or
You're losing a game when you should
In your Prime you could have handled it
They are but because
Whatever it seems like the answers to all of his questions
Are you could really just come to him
If you got off the air
Went home and just looked in the mirror and was just like
People don't like me because I'm the dick
Not them
So like I said I mean I can't stress this enough I was mad at myself and I was going to
Fix-It are just
Such
Weird expressions
Of what he's doing
And this supposed to be 2 hours
He fails he fails in an hour and a half
20 last 30 minutes Air Tonight
Leech bite reports the Lord willing I'll be back tomorrow
11 a.m. Central app
Lockport
Thank you I really
Vibration was
Love yourz
He leaves half an hour early
I just think it said it said whether he's drunk or not
Suspicion that he's drunk but like
Whether or not he is that's just a disgraceful kind of showing
And it's just
It's a bummer like
Number of failings are Stacker
You failed to sell anything that was part of his agenda
He failed to make it the entire two hours
He failed to keep his head about him
Couldn't even focus on any
Failed to even really talk about the only story that he was there for
God
Can you imagine
Can you imagine being like robbed or Daria or something like that
And you get the call like hey
Coming in at 7
And for that breed
For that brief
Oh man maybe this is the old Alec
He's just been through nothing
And this time he's self
He's the one inspiring
Self to go do something he's got the juice this is when he's going to bring it for the first time in years
He's been in his office cogitating like
Americans out of the office
And then you
You get there in the show starts in your heart just goes
Why am I here
You have that whole build-up and then it starts like this
You know whatever I get a check
Here's
Because the enemy
Academy, San
Flood
Overlord
Are you stopping Center yesterday
Asparagus
So strong
And then you're like we're in trouble we're in trouble
Deep trouble
Alright
I'm going to
That but that's the difference
In 2017 Special Report
He would not get off the air he was talking about skulls covered in semen
Exactly
Ways to learn
Robert you cigarettes okay
Rodger Stone and Emma supposed to do the whole thing Rodger stay for like half an hour and Alex kept going
How to steam
2020 he can't even make it the full 2 hours
Shell
Anyway enjoy
Have a good time I hope you have a good fourth
Hope you enjoyed
Fighting
Or whatever you did
We will be back but until then
If you could please find
Charity or bail bond in your area to help out in any way
Yep
Iranian cyborg