Air Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge by
Knowledge fight
MoneyGram
Jordan
Quest
Kind of
Trying to make peace with
Okay I'm already getting back to grapefruit
No it's another proof that I despaired quite a bit
Michelle
Severe the South air
I said some really negative
Things about coconut
That's true
Hate the coconut
I hate it as a
Seltzer strawberry flavor for liquid
So I want to take this opportunity
To say something positive about coconut
I recently encountered in my life
Exploring various like
I've recently discovered
Milk yogurt
Coconut milk yogurt
Does the trick
Definition of
Amaya scientist scientist
You're the one who knows more about milk
Look up a big dad why not
Are some expectation that I would look into it
I just haven't
I've just been Drake
And honestly
I don't know
I don't know if it's healthier than like a Greek yogurt or just a abandoned
Diversified
Things that I have
The food offering
My life
So looking forward to drop
Yogurt yogurt
It turns out they are in a couple years
I have no updates on that front but I would like to know what your
Comedian David
Dan
Pronounce that name
You pronounce
Okay no
I particularly enjoyed a lot of stand-up
Has been released recently her so went back and watch some
Danny Phantom
Musical comedian
Casio keyboard
Aeropostale
Incredible song
Pretty Rock
Like in a genuinely funny kind of
Dark
Miserable kind of
I do not have a great time
A lot of people don't make it 25 specials
Probably
I just remembered pissed off because
The bar
Close
Maybe like half an hour left in this year
Meter to go over and look after
Kind of half-hearted lab demands more Merlot
No no
It was one of our friendship
Didn't want to go
What was the setup
That's right my timeline
A little screwy but
Not to worry
So don't think they'll actually described as a very special episode
And I don't understand exactly
I'll tell you something
Stay awake
Just say no
Best policy
Sarah program
Dare program
Adair bear
Know what
Okay
I don't know if this is just something
Their curriculum with our logo.
Vacations section of their curriculum or whatever
You take it home for the evening and it'll bring it back
That's not reliable is universal
Never heard of a dare
I guess we'll probably hear from
You just had an incompetent
Citicom
I think it was around the time that Care Bears was a cartoon
That might have been part of why but ended up happening
Sure to make this special structure of this is going
Incredibly well in advance
Do shoutouts
Some folks are signed up in our sport
Bring the show
Right
Okay
We're going to play
A drop
A time capsule episode
Or listeners child to listen to
I like that
Pics
However
And I wanted to create a time capsule David his daughter was born
You can hear what Alex was doing on
She was born
I got to go f*** dad why are you
I thought it was one or more uplifting things that I've heard in awhile
Skewered through the lens of our show which is never sleep nor up with
And some sort of a weird memory
Your family is at
Letter
They want to see somebody to transcribe
Survive
Trade specialist
In July 2020 and also it will be a time capsule
December 17th
Of Roberts child
Love it so we're going to do that but I wanted to try and I don't know why
Episode
Conceived in my mind is that we would play that drop
And then we would answer it
You know like that
The beginning of the episode
Only because I was like I don't know
The Time Capsule episode
I just don't know how good this this works
So anyway if you do
Alright alright
Ricky
Journal about his walk
Text Emily M
Emily
Thanks Andrew
Donated on the elevator
Because in the future you may listen to this
Preemptively though you're too young to understand what it mean when right now
His child
You are officially arrived or princess
And tell your brother
For Humanity
You're Beautiful song
They're coming for your balls
Very few people
Water babies
When they are
That juice
Thank you all
Zip
Shoutout on this episode she's going to just
Start of the next part
So now whatever we listening to
This part where we're doing it rained on your seduction to a princess
Okay going to cut it off
I'm having fun I'm not criticizing
YouTube
I'd like to say thank you
Soul of the au gratin
Breast
Cuz
Turn of Print America posters for shows a lot of very cool
News around Central Missouri
The Blue Note
Which replaces that I frequent as well as I can cool Fireside Bowl
Great art
Find his work over on
The real Groton press
You can find his work
Check it out really great
And
It's hard to say for sure
Because there's no gear on it but I think I was at one of the shows
Decemberists show that there's a poster of I was at
It's hard to say for sure because I would have had to been over a decade
Yeah so is it what
December Scorpio
Who am I
I really appreciate it I'll get there
I don't know which of these will make it on the wall
I know you are took a shining to The Flaming Lips
Flaming Lips man I appreciate that
Saline Inn
Tallest man
A bunch of copies desire Rica and then you try and play it at the same
My friends don't really like Alexa
Twisted messing around with
First reaction
Seems like
Goodonya fellas
And I don't know better and I was really hot
17 Mi then girlfriend
On stage with the Flaming Lips at Lollapalooza
People out there aliens
She's not a good sex
Use a penis
So
Old-time piano
Alright Jordan
Okay
Alex
Hello July 2020
Please make sure that you do not let the fire go out we don't know how to restart them anymore
K login
Yeah
The world
And we certainly hope
Gingerbread Irwin
This time capsule
Night
They're not they're not
Congratulations
Martin Luther King
King junior's granddaughter I become
President
The time travelers have told us that we have no confirmation of
Future quotes
Like I said Robert reached out to me
Episode 4 his daughter V
Who was born
December 17th 2030
And in honor of that
I have gone back
Anja Collective
And listen to an episode of
December 13th
He was up to on the day of these birth
Yeah and you know what
You don't choose your birthday
They better hope
That they live to see the end of
Sometimes
You know
We-we're experience
Very little geopolitical
It's not a surprise
Batting on all its metaphors
From Today Show
Is playing ping-pong with your wavos
Your interior
Jeff Foxworthy
You just might be
Just might be in
I couldn't decide which way it went but
Restart this episode
Just from the
What I heard
New 2013 Plymouth
Recording
Ford Focus
Some idea of what he wants to do on
Maybe a couple minutes
Here's what's coming up on Today Show
We've been listening to
The Alex
Episode from
July
Extension level
Retreat to go back to to talk
Talking about what's coming up on the show
Ladies and gentlemen coming up later in the broadcast
Tuesday the 17th of December
Larry klayman
The legendary
Constitutional lawyer
Of course
Everywhere
Alex is so excited to promote that Larry Clavin on the show
Resume contacts
But Alex
Larry klayman and
His associates
Former Infowars employees
Do not like each other anymore
How many was a punchline back then
To Alex's now
It's always going to be a row
The same ship
What's been going on
This this is good to know that some friendships do crumble hilarious
Friendship
This is just like a convenient
Alex Like Larry
This guy was around
You know there's a lot of stuff look like
My God that's
That is
Very different
Yeah
It's interesting
What's coming up on Today Show
He does say there's
And I will say
This is not company follows through
And of course
Cuz I said open phone
But I think it's going to be on
Specific
Topix
Because
Calls and also if you have open
But it's only on certain topics it's no longer open
Contradict
We have close by
Right
I think it says that at the beginning of every show back at this point
We're going to have open Play
Right
It's only talk about
Talk show
You know of this store
Yeah yeah yeah
Well I mean
So they're going to listen
Through the points
Somebody's going to say it's
Turn to call right
A good diet
Gadot
So Alex jumped into the stories and besides
The begin
There is so much
The cover here
So much to go over here
Socialism
General Motors says no way will pay back 10 billion bailout
Money used to move to China and Brazil
If you don't like it
So yeah it is interesting you know Alex does have the you like there so many stories to get to
He does at least start
That's true
What it's worth in July 2019 GM finally finished paying back to the United States
All the money that is owed is part of the Baylor
That was later than I was supposed to paid it all back
6.7 billion that was considered was
Government extension
Because part of the bailout plan was to
So some of the flowers in the form of the US government buying stock in General Motors
According to a 2014 article in
CNN business
Fujiyama's
Very profitable
Since 2000
Its stock price never Rose to the level that let
Treasury recoup.
Investment
ENT on December
16th back in 2013
Should GM repay 10 billion rescue cost
Beo says no
This article was about
Codm
Naturally the CEO said no and they quote
Treasury officials took the same
Consumed by anyone
Who purchases
Stock
Also Alex Fields mentioned in this article discussed GM plant invest
2 billion dollars
Plant
Which brings their total for the past four years at that point
Up to 10 billion dollar investment
In United
It states plants
Brazil Brazil
Before the bailout
As for the reality of Chinese GM Factory
Because of the expanding demand
In China
A 2019 article in
Business
Percent of u.s. GM sales
Cars imported from
From Chinese factories
Do not have any impact on us Factory
Their car plants in China
Because people in China any cars
Is way more profitable tonight at the transport big ass cars
Across the world
Seldom
They're definitely things
Can take issue with about the
CEO's that you wasn't going to pay back money that wasn't alone and he's making
Stuff about the rush
He's getting mad about stuff that doesn't make sense when there's other things
Do not appreciate the sea
Gyros town
Hey we just saved your entire f****** business we going to let you go bankrupt
Not a goddamn events
And then you're going to come back and everybody else did nobigdyl
That's kind of a big guy I'll see you in hell
In advance was
Stock for the amount that it was sold
4 or whatever
Parker the
Terms
Compelled
You would love it
Goodness
America
Another story
Towards the beginning of the episode
Well ladies and Gentlemen even mainstream media
Just calling it The Rise of
Google's robot army
Troy
Rise of the robot animals as they've now but
In the last week or so 8 robot
Carbone's
In the last week as Google make
Executive
Decision
Literally buy up almost all
Animal type combat
Capable
In the future robots
Systems
Wow wow
A lot of claws
He kept adding dessert
Lot of words
Google's agnor robot army together
It's still coming
I don't
Embarrassing
Easily traceable to a headline
Find from December 6th
What is really interesting is
Like going through this and like hearing the story that he's covering
Painfully easy to draw
Just go and find the exact article
Talking about
Like the last one
YouTube I like to talk about
CBS News article with the headline
Google buys eight robotics companies in
6 months
Why
These articles primarily a company called Boston Dynamics
Institute of Technology
What is investment could easily be understood as Google
Early stages of Technology
Mind-boggling array of purposes
Mostly in the field of autumn
If you look at it from that angle
Close to strange about Google buying up
These businesses
The robotics section of Google
Aruba
Let's Google
According to sources who spoke with rocks
2017 this quote
About what their role Google would be
Surprised that in 2017
Google sold
Boston Dynamics
As well as their other large robotics interest
Shut up
Do a Japanese company called stop
Freezer part of Google
Which is their developmental way
Hey so large
Potential
Blast
Things got a Little Rock
Innovations
Worked on
We're too far away from
Rosie the robot
The Google
Insignia on it and they had to get rid of those and that's why
Play Shoot Oliver's on site
I don't know how many times we have to have Verizon
A movie save the answer is
Big ask themselves whether or not they could not whether or not they should
And then we watch it and reality happened
Have you seen any movies
About you about you there about you look
Can you building a black
Mirror episode
Predictive programming
It's a common artistic beam about
Subway
The field of robotics
I'm the one handsome
Holding the field
By spending big bucks
Vision
Should have been
Maybe John outside of the restrictive
The purview of Google
And then others point out the fact is because Google showed such
Such a huge interest in robotics
It's what actually pushed
Chesterfield forward
It's kind of a mixed bag
Complete handle on what the net
Gained or lost if we just know that there's some game there's some lost nobody
Seems like a lot of the sense that I was getting was trying to stifle
In hindsight
I guess
Nearly enough
Or at all
Should be able to
Speak with any kind of authority
No idea
Sold by Google
Ucreate
Robot army
Spell
Not yet there's still time
As we sit
We are in the midst
Of the Coronavirus
The covid-19
Situation
Bubbleezz
Release
In order to precipitate martial law
Ears
Alex was talking about like bio-weapon
Stop in 2013
Timeline
The order of events
Is a little bit
You could grow up and be an adult
Do it
Arrested Development three-year-old
Talking to new listeners
You're busy watching the NFL
While you're busy into your favorite music star
We're under
Then drop the hammer
If they release a bio-weapon
They done the war games
It's going to result in Clearwater
Problem
They get a real world government
Bankrupt everybody
You can see here at 2013 Alex's conception is the martial law
Happens to like a bunch of people
Now it's completely flip
The bioweapon is released in order to get the martial law
The bioweapon
Because they usually would say actuary
Change
Like
Pieces but they're organized
Here's my here's my prediction
Alright
I don't think anything Alex says
In any era
Is mint with any kind of actual predict
Livability
I've now decided that we are comparing 2020 Alex's predictions to 2013 Alex
Sister addiction
And both of them
Or either of them will always
When they are in pain
Will happen
To him
Interesting
At all
In 2020
Completely consistent
Because he said the word bioweapon
That's true for everything
Technically
Matchup
The predictions are different
Now the globalist plans are always
10 years behind true
Game and they were like well this is
Going to start a nuclear war
Not releasing it is going to start a nuke
Clara Ward
Now and
Nuclear war
I don't know anymore
I'm falling perfect
Okay
Empath
Because of the times that I go back into the past
Is that are shocking
And I would say that this is one of them
Alex
The show in 2020
Breonna Taylor once
Everyday I see where police go to the wrong house
And shoot someone
And don't even get in trouble
I've got two reports today in the stack of that
And Anthony gucciardi last night
Woke up
Armored vehicles
At the wrong house
Big giant fat Goblin Commander cop
What does SWAT team
Literally dragging some woman out he was innocent
What's wrong now
Fake drug war
All the drugs in the beginning
Alex
The individual
Necessary
No
User like a cops are going into the wrong houses shooting people
What you think
Talk about this
Shopping and no knock
That warrant
Also it seems like that one
Easy 12b
Consistent on yeah that doesn't seem to have a fungible moral position
Going into the wrong house
Murdering somebody
And then facing no consequences
Even in our time capsule episode
Future be like
Nevermind
Yeah yeah
Squabble over is like
Demanding more information
Reserving judgment about individual
Until you know more about
Is really the only place I can see any kind of
Mightier
Is love
You know carrying weapons legally and then
Nano philando Castillo gets killed
Carrying a gun legally and
Non-white
Blog
Infowars around the same time that I was
Pushing yourself
McGuire
He's no longer there
She already has one of them
But that stuff
Just doesn't stick with me
Cuz it's like
You like
Now he hasn't
Mainstay around this time
In terms of like
Being another
Natural news
Couple times
Definitely in the spear
Yeah
Interesting to me
Do you see that you see that this
This principle that like
Cop shooting
They've dubbed
Opportunistically support
For being on the right side of than that and still lied I don't see
I don't see that happening
Attention just to say that
He doesn't want
Mobster murdered
Every night
Maybe
Little sprig of parsley
Alex
Livin on the road my friend going to keep you free and clean
Free
And your breath
Willie Nelson Merle Hay
Duet
Cry
Thanks
Three Willie Nelson song
Pancho and Lefty
Like variety of music
Like I see him as having a
A couple of songs that he listen to all the time or he
He does not listen
The music deep cut
So that come out every now and again
Willie Nelson seems like his movies
If I were six song
Maybe it's the only things that are covered by WIC whatever his lease agreement is music
These ones
Shotgun Willy or whatever
Victorino That's What I Call Waylon
Will you play these songs and none other
Blazing let me tell you how it goes out
So this
This is not what I expect
Good to hear that next
This is where I was like this episode
I'm going to be about
And coming up with an X
Tail
The facts here on Earth
And here on this planet dealing with our
All of the facts
Dealing with
Soil
What have we gotten ourselves into
We are now going
Going to sit here and learn
Everything
The past used to be Queen
But like 80 years in the past
So cute
Alex
I don't want to learn about you LOL
Beachmere
Again I would greatly
We prefer this
Look you guys we got a man singing to talk about soil that's just a regular show
It's just a regular show
Confused
You said that
And loyal is a topic
In about
Scurvy
If you go on and do research
The FDA
Has continued to lower
The minimum daily allowance of what they say you need
A vitamin C vitamin D vitamin E
McCullough
Dr. Blaylock
They have lowered the level of vitamin C down to near
Scurvy inducing level
Your skin basically falls apart
You see you talk to
That's why they literally all have rattles in their arm
I'll talk to nutritionist
The whole spiel
Hypothetical person impersonating who only eats McDonald's would have their behavior affected
Too greatly by an older desk
No one would say I owe you
McDonald's because the FDA said that was a good idea
I used to eat all the fruits and vegetables but then they lowered the vitamin C limit
McDonald's
Vitamin C
For most people you get what you need
In the journal the College of Physicians of Canada
Explored a slight re-emergence of scary cases
Romeo
In a retrospective chart review conducted
Is the Mayo Clinic in Rochester New York and Scottsdale Arizona from 1976
12:30 cases were related
Alcohol abuse illicit drug use
And psychiatric
Serotonia Foods people eat regularly
Is your having a specific problem that might be caused by a vitamin
Efficiency
It might be a good idea to speak to a dietitian
You're missing
What is not a great angle is to imagine that you have a problem
And the reason must be that you're not taking enough for something so you need supper
That's the fear that Alex is exploding here in order to try and create feelings of
His audience
People there's no deficiency to begin with
Century Privateer then yes
I agree
McDonald's
Terrible
It's life
Right
I mean it's one of those things
Yes
Gerard Gerard
You know not the as rampant
Does Alex want
Nutritional deficit
It's an
To the extent that is real for some people
Sometimes
Into Better Health but like
What do you do here is exploitative
And predator
End
Once again putting the blame
Depressed economic sector as being like
McDonald's all the time
Places are f****** Cal poor that there's really not much option
That's true you know
True
Where is that
It seems like
That's not entirely
The soil which is why you want to do this
Blaming people who can't afford maybe more expensive
Being out a living in food desert
Or something like that
You don't even unpack that necessarily
Territory
This is more about the
The fact that
Nutrients are gone from
This is all because of
An article v d red
About
Hey dudes
Studies only found the basically most people don't know
U-joint
People
There are some people who could be Alpha
There are some
If you take too much of them
People
Zero proper diet
Don't need
And upon publishing that research
Billion dollar industry of supplements
Oh no
We're useless
Cuz I guess we'll just stop
Nope
Hotels
Is this
Go cuz it's such bull
He's just saying like
FDA has come out and said you don't need vitamins
Alrighty
Yesterday they roll out with a huge
That vitamins and minerals do nothing
Basically the
Paces close
And on
Fox
My local paper has it
National papers
Everywhere
Chase close
You don't need any vitamins any minerals any supplements
So he's presenting this as like the FDA
What vitamin
Running reality is Iraq
Like I'd like a bird
Turns out
Are are
You're not chewing when you breathe that's why you don't
Get the vitamins
In the air everybody 2013
Yeah I mean I think it's pretty hot
What you missed
Cop to the fact
If you have
Proper Diet Rite
Possible that have
A diet
Get you all the supplemental nutrients
And that you need
This is falling apart as you talk more
Clear
Apparently clear things like
All right did you know that
Until they cry
Created vitamin
Supplements
All Humans died
Let's
After okay well
Okay you're right
Cfda
Cause
Yeah so apparently I don't I don't know how true this is
I just decided to accept it as paw
Possibly through and move along
The FDA has lowered
The allowance or the amount you should get
Certain things
Advise the food pyramid
We grow
Access to more information means better
Because
Trying to come up with examples
Tripped over his own
Daily allowance
What you need
Things like vitamin C
It seems like
Down
Level
Littorai Regular Show
Portage medical doctors in Ventura
Examples of what
Oil of oregano
So much oil of oregano
I used to tell a joke in your life
Essential oils guy
3 years
Blind out of my mind
I don't know
If oil of oregano is that everyone
In their daily routine
It's in the category with the FDA of things that are like
Generally it doesn't
So I don't think it's
Controlled by the FDA
Does the supplement
Industries like a million dollars
You can just come up with another vitamin
1111 North their follow-up
Nobody even knows if 11 is a thing
So Alex
Talking about salt
Hey substitute
You're watching on TV you can look at this or just go to the local
Supermarket
It says this salt does not supply iodine unnecessary nutrients
Why is that cuz the feds
Pressure
Iodine in the shop
Because of literally millions of people being
Born mentally retarded
Lower IQs
People that look like
Jabba the Hutt
Where you look like a human worm
Fabric is devastated by the
So this doesn't happen
Because it suggests
Degenerative problem
By the seventies basically said remove it
Remove item
In that loving Adele
We've been fight
Uses the twenties we got we had to switch things up
Finally in the 70s
Under the Carter Administration
But also the Chinese are putting iodine in their water
He's good but they put fluoride in their water which is bad
So you never know
I mean look
Like a real problem
Here's the thing
Reasons that salted Alex has from McCormick's
Now he's rambling about this the reason it doesn't have iodine in it because it's
Sea salt
You'll find the same warnings on containers of Morton
Any sea salt
You're going to find on the market
The reason for this is that sea salt and table salt
Solder produce differently
And because of how these
Seasalt Market operates
Is a product that generally is subject to his little processing as
The salt comes from evaporated water
Which leaves flakes
Salt which retain some of the minerals and characteristic
Because the source that they come from
Table salt conversion deposit
So you can have iodine added easily in the processing
Changes
You go by any table salt
Salt
Seesaw generally
He isn't
I agree with Alex
Inasmuch as maybe there should be better messaging to the world.
Sea salt doesn't contain iodine
Imagining
Any kind of large-scale iodine deficiency
In the United
Midstate because
It's just not
Everyday I'm walking around and all these
Hipster neighborhood
Even in Wrigleyville you walk around
Please people wondering why they got iodine deficiency
You can't go to a bar and get iodized salt man
All bars sea salt
Margaritas
McCray's and it probably didn't have at least
Some
Effect on iodine levels
I'm not positive if it reached any kind of
Crisis point
Result
We are in your debt
You can eat seafood milk yogurt egg
Maintain proper health
They're definitely serious problems can occur from iodine deficiency
In the developing World particularly
Makes it out to be particularly
Again this is an example of Alex working to try and convince his audience that there's something wrong with them
Which he can provide this
Lucian
Because I know that is busy
Business model relies heavily on selling iodine
Supplements
It's hard not to see this doesn't intentionally predatory
Like he's going through all this stuff about
Amazon
Problem
He can provide
Placebo solution
Taking advantage of
Just giving them this
Yeah
But this says supplement that down your gullet and you won't feel
Depressed
Alex
Claim everything in the world there is to know about soil
So
Let me show you some of the articles
Number one
This is a Scientific American did you get some good stuff
Fruits and vegetables become less than Frisch's
Major studies going back
University of Texas at Austin Department of Chemistry and biochemistry
In the Journal of the American College of nutrition
And agriculture nutritional data
With 43 different fruits and vegetables that look into studies before that
Is in them
Metrically by numbers
By 98
Vitamins
Getting those numbers from cuz they aren't
This is an article that's part of their column Earth talk where readers can send in questions which their writers will then answer
This question had to do with whether or not fruits and vegetables were more nutritious 50 years ago and then it turns out the answer
But probably not today except Alex's report
Your uncle's life in the mouse's by the coochie in
Institute Wichita
When calcium levels
12 fresh vegetables they study
It was a 37% drop in
21% drop in vitamin A and 30% drop in vitamin C
I finally get off their ass and do a study
Experts believe
That there was this was the result
Is there mentally
Expand
Cropsey
Could be
John the word enrich soil
Eureeka's Castle
It's like alternator
Growing seasons
Embracing
Organic growing methods in order to rebuild
Royals
Scientific American
Disgusting
As it turns out a new paper published in the journal
Scientific
Oceans of essential nutrients
Decrease in 18th strains of rice
Exposed to increased carbon dioxide levels
In the experiment
Okay so
Climate change
From Scientific American article
Agricultural scientist have known for
Sometime but our food
Thought it was only a byproduct of modern
Which leads to Mineral
Or breeders favoring
Bright
Which sacrifices nutrition Forsyth
Meanwhile plant researchers working over the last couple of decades were fine
Something surprising
Elevated carbon dioxide
Did plants
Plantain agricultural scientist
YouTube pieces of
The puzzle but Noah
Some phenomenon
Until
There's some evidence emerging that a large Factory nutrients
Texas
CO2
The plants need CO2 to grow in the same way we need calories
But if we have too many calories
There somewhere suggest
Plants with CO2
That are particularly important
He's using this as a prop
To sell his supplements
It becomes really clear because
Comes in
Walking info
Over some of that for you
Is coming in now just a cover.
Vitamins and minerals
That I'm used to have done wonders in my life
And everybody that she use them you've heard the calls not one- call on our proprietary Nationwide
This is insane man this is like an hour of his show is weird like I'm going to tell you all about the soil
Which is all the prelude
Atmos Energy
Because it's
A lot
I wish I could because it's simultaneously more
Appropriate
Compressor
Both
It's so
Very
Pretending to not be an ad
The last like desperation to it
That's what that's the weird balance
It is almost more is like
Skating
Then it is now
Just absolute like
I need money
I hear they're kind of like almost giving you a little
Hey listen
If you don't want to take your vitamins
I'm going to talk about that that for next hour
Also you're going to need vitamins
Going to talk about where you at
More profitable
I have to imagine
More money
You know there's one reason I couldn't get madder and madder the three-hour show those honeystead
I don't like to work
And that's because
I'm looking
At the federal state and university studies
On the soil
Debilitated
In utero
Of the humans developing and then after
I'm waiting in the documentation
They're taking the good stuff out of the food and put the bad stuff in it
Was this just all like
Little darts
He's throwing in order to lead people down the path
To his eyes up
Yeah so she already in there
But baseball
Scene we're looking
Inductor group will come in for like an hour and they talk about syphilis
So
Trt leaves
And Alex
G boy
Stupid
SharkMan unnecessarily
Cruel
Our education over here
NAU at
I said healthy
I should help South Africa
It should help diarrhea
So we will be able to build up
Future
Thank you very much
South Carolina
She's a very beautiful young lady
I don't find her attractive beautiful
That is that woman is so ugly
Being a trophy wife
For some Global its executive
Call Armani
A wife that is literally nothing but a biological Android
Who can't tie it for shoelaces
Alex is complaining about people being
Opposed
On stage
Ivan number from
The first is that this woman was eight
18 years old
The question
Clearly didn't understand
Respond to
Sure it was
Any of us on a bad day under a certain amount of stress could end up finding ourselves saying something
Equally embarrassing
Kind of mean to Define someone by that embarrassing moment
Piccalilli
That's so young
The mockery and shaming about this moment was really severe for this Saturday's weather
She said
I definitely went through. Where I was very very depressed
But I never let anybody see that stop
It's a very dark moments where I thought about them
Committing suicide
Second this was from the 2000
7 Miss Teen USA pageant
From 2030
Seems like he's digging pretty far back just
To take an unnecessary swing at
This woman
Also just because
After this contestant South Carolina Caitlin Upton went viral
Pretty pageant
15 million views on YouTube
She was signed to a contract with a bottle
$30,000 a day
Who also owns
The pageant to that time
We're doing
Also another one
Tucker Carlson
To say about Miss up
As well
Episode of Bubba the Love Sponge radio show
She probably be a pretty good wife
Tucker was
I don't understand how many 40 year old white dude with a giant platform that they can talk to millions of people
I think is really interesting is Alex at the end there is like a trophy wife
Globalist
Old white man shooting all over with
Direct line
Restrain
I swear I'm not a witch
What's the point
So
Trt
Haha
Giselle
The balance of the hour by Matt dubiel guy
Call times at Austin
He's had a song for couple years down
Chicago 1530
I got a power pack
Lineup
There
Alex
Chicago radio station
Hey
Always nice
Make a Serengeti song favorite actor
To danehy kabobs
Over
Like this periodically will Papa and
Literally the only station
In the country that plays
Troy Aaron David
Night shows affiliates
I don't know
Six months ago or so
Sucks
I guess
The premise is disposed to be on to talk about what life is like under Rahm Emanuel
Great
I don't know
So I don't care about his protective on local pilot
But
Mukbang
You know it's like you said there's a lot of good things about Chicago
I went to the the Bears game the other night Monday nights
Football in ended cuz number was retired it was a big deal and
I had free tickets so we went
There was nobody there
No one now it was cold it gets cold here in Chicago
Typically stop
Chicago Bear fans from going to Chicago game
I saw the same thing happening at the Cleveland Pittsburgh
Where the Pittsburgh stadium
Why is that
Why why is it that all of the storefronts that are for lease the retail spaces are empty
Something is going on and
It is not
If not by accident I don't think I should call the starting to feel a lot like Detroit these days
No
Attendance was 60 2209
Soldier Field
Worried home game
Chicago
This number
There's nothing discernible the football game
Kind of think maybe you like one of my friends
Just didn't want to go with them
Zoe processing
According to the Chicago Tribune
8 degrees start timer
Call me
Degrees
Explain 1000-2000
Sunglass people showing up
Also the average attendance of Detroit Lions games is actually higher
A game
So I don't know what he saying about that
Detroit
Anyway
Why does it feel like why are you asking so many eminently answerable questions only
To imply something instead of
Looking for an answer and that was
It's really hard to sell out
Yeah
80000 is a lot of people to get in any one place when it's freeze out
Like him
Calling out
Chicago's identity is like
Bears fans aren't even real Bears fans any
Screw you
Care
You from The Burbs
NFL
Theranos
Lego drive across
Country
I bet it's on cross-country number time
Complaints about them
I've got kids ranging from 11
My youngest is going to be 2 in February
And we take a summer road trip
We we drive around the country the great United States of America
And the last two years
And
Last this last summer
And as we drove
Go through
I saw first-hand
The America that most of us don't see
Most of the people in in Austin don't see it
We live in very privileged area
The rest of the country looks like a bomb fell on
Country looks like
Third world
Country is is decapitated it's it's
Completely define
Because nobody's driving down that Highway
My gosh
Took my father and his brothers
To the Grand Canyon and stuff
There was the Majesty in the
66 inseam
Shops and restaurants
Where is it I don't know where it is
I got a couple
Things say about this
The guys are supposed
Be like La New York Elite
Flyover country app
Everywhere in America look like
Everywhere but the Flies the flyover states are disgusting
Burbs
Super weird
Purely talk
You captured
I'm driving along interstate
Highways
We will pretty bleak if all you're seeing are old Billboards and like out-of-date gas station
The other America
Visible lock
A little ways off of Highway
Vibrant
Would you totally Miss
Is you're only seeing what's right now
Next to the road
The first play
Maybe they'd maybe it's
Just like a f****** billboard to take him down
It is insane how many Billboards are filled metric
Trick of how the United
It was doing
GDP
Drop weight
Is real bad
Maybe the factory
Spell maybe
Maybe don't need
Stopping every 10
11:50
Is really good for the local economy
Chicago and California
But it stopped being nearly as important
In our highway system came into play
Early on
Dominance as a cross-country Road
Does Prospero because people had to use it to make that kind of trip
Ever since the passage of the Interstate Highway Act of 1956
66 has gradually become lesson
Important
No it's really
You know
Some stretches
It's been like read it over and over again it's not even the same thing
Yes
I just tired of all of these peoples harkening back to us
Ikea
Right
Be great dad
It's not
It's not a system
Nowadays
Prosperous businesses everywhere along the highway is not something
Exist in the modern world
It's something that existed because of
Necessity
The time when
Cars were much
Suffocated
And no small amount of resist
Distance to the idea of building railways
Renewable-energy Railway
There's 100
About
Seriously the opinion
Somebody who's only on this show because
He does
And makes out with a bunch of money
If you are a right-wing reactionary Dan
There's one thing that unites all of them
They hate
Rose
Yep
The future
So
Dubiel Cumberland
Another gas
This guy sucks
He's just gone to talk about the transpacific
Interview but not because of the interview
Jasper is as he joins us
He's a Graduate University of Idaho and joined the staff of the John Birch Society in 1976 as a researcher and currents
Editor
American
Is
Which is the original John Birch Society publication
And became
Bill Goldberg
From way back
Inverter
Alex like he likes to pretend that he's not just a
Society guy
Is 100%
Interacts with a JBS guy
That comes out
Any join just breakdown
In 1992
First Alert about
The UN and the biospheres William F
And so he joins us now
Alex's intellectual from propaganda
Society
So
I mean
It's almost comical to me
Like the idea
He knows
Pretend most of the time
To not really be so stupid
He is absolutely
Where is when my dad was abusing me with his boot book and I decided
Start reading it immediately following
Literary
So Alex just makes clear that his lineage Trace
Is back directly to the bird
Dirtbag
And the Republican leadership is
George P bush
They want to absorb the Tea Party
What comes out of the jail
And Ron Paul
Everybody else after that
We're not radical radicals all day
Are the radicals usurping our Republic
Because we're crazy
There's one more
They're f****** crazy
Yeah there might be wild
Out there
Ing, Lakeside
Makes sense
Sure
So
We sound crazy cuz we're talkin
City exam
I told you all the crazy stuff about Nero
Ijump Crazy by Nero
I'm telling you what
Marrying is horse everything else
He's power-mad nuts must be stopped now
If you ordered by the 19th
Yeah baby
Brought to you
The old free-market Thunder operation against
Dash cams lowest price
You'll find anywhere
Bottom ball
Inoperative
Listed retail price anywhere
To document what's happening
The police bureaucrats
Wildlife you name it
Infowars.com
So Alex is selling in order to keep wild police at Bay
Add stop
Concerned that he hasn't
Protect themselves
Also I love the idea
You know we got to keep up on wildlife
Dolls I should tell you
Abbey Road
The incorrect legend about Nero
Mother pelicula
UConn Storrs
And also tried to make his horse a senator
Acura
Historical gossip
Specifically
Completely wrong in thinking the Nero was the Book of Revelations
I could be completely wrong but
It's just interesting that he would specifically bring up
Talking about how
Evoland
Inside Nero was
Being crazy
When is favorite book
It's talking about how even well
To note is the absence of
Religious
In our conversation
So far there is no begging people to
Here's what we're going to do I am going to tell you all of the facts about soil
Specifically
The stuff that Jesus died on
Pedophile Networks
National Beer day
Nothing about the
Evil transgender
No
Homophobia
I mean
Maybe some miles racism
Expect
Not too surprising his
Wildest stuff now is that is not so much
View of what else
Side so much as a reflection of what
The hemp that's very interesting
I'm not a trained psychologist
Call Steve pieczenik
I don't care about this interview with William Jasper
Except
For the piece of information that comes
From if it is really fascinating
Keenly aware
The lottery
Society
And that that is where his political group
So he's trying to sell things
In this interview to like he wants
Apps to sell
Like books by 1000
Tragedy and Hope
The globalist machination
Plan
He makes a startling admission
For sale at Infowars
Is a very large book it's 1100 pages
Now it's makes a startling admission
He's been on the air since 1995
So we're clocking in at what is that 18 years
It's available
Infowarsstore.com
That's on 11th
Rasean Williams
Bookshelf on Skype
Watching TV
Where the Georgetown political science Professor V
Control liberalism
Conservatism fascism
And the trilateral commission
World corporate
And it's only meant to look like there's the illusion
Choice
In politics I'm paraphrasing quote
This book actually read almost a whole thing
I said I probably read
Doesn't mean I skip over some of the more
Factoid
Inside baseball stuff
Inside baseball
Side master plan mostly focused on I'm not really Palace Intrigue lights
With the glove
Information
From my experience with Alex
This tells me he's right for Pages baby
Inside yourself
Please remind me of how I always acted about
Oh yeah
Hybrid
Dial.
Most of those boxes
Whatever it is like I'm going to read something from your book
I tried to read it and I could not make hide nor hair
That's the way I've always treated those books
I wanted to give you
Impression that I read more of it cuz I felt like it was something
I should have read
So I always I always acted like that
Need to have red all over
There is no it's
Excuse why in 1995
Read it twice
Yeah there's no reason why he wouldn't study this thing that like it's the Zapruder film in book form
It's supposed to be the inside revelation of a
Exactly what the globalists are their plans
Their histories
The most import
Of all of these
In 2013 he saying
Midas800
Over 18
To about
8 words
Heard Exxon acceptable not even that
Straight unacceptable
If you're giving this
Like a song
You don't say I've read every every word of that book
Why would you
The only reason
Everyone knows you don't read s***
Readable
I would like
What if one of those inside baseball pass
Messages has literally Carroll Quigley being like dude I'm totally f****** with somebody
Later on
So that was fun I enjoyed that
That was a really weak moment
Confirmation
Information about how much Alex is making
How to get to know 7 years old
Not a reader at this point
Do your muscles
Now
Probably but
This episode
Larry klayman
Pays it office
Freedom watch USA
British constitution
Obama because
Orgy
Violation
Has become
Dictator love
Yes we're very concerned about that
He was able to give us 10 minutes today
He joins us
Take 10-minute scraps from Layman
Full take Larry
This is
I mean
The mud Lil Baby
Yuri dark it's like I love this guy to the point where every season Overdrive
This is supposed to end
3 hour Berkeley
Extending show
Who is Larry Cook
Give him 10 minutes
He loves it
And that's because Larry recently gotten a lawsuit
Careers
You can say that every day of his
His career
In a little bit of a lot
This one is one that like
You know how when like Ron Paul one couple of the caucuses look like
What's that like
The Crazies will I go
This is our chance 2013
The headline
Unconstitutional
I brought the case
Larry klayman
And then if you continue Politico story claiming crows we hit the mother lode
I'm glad he's proud of defending the Republic
Play Man versus Obama
Which resulted in the judge ruled unconstitutional
Nothing was done however because I need something that the government would
Almost certainly
Play peel
When this reach the Circuit Court
Because his record
Were collected
He didn't have standing
To bring the complaint
You was the lawyer and the plaintiff
I was hoping it was because
Is he wrote most of that
Annovera overused Cran
Larry added someone to the lawsuit theoretically have c2017 the district court
Dismiss the suit entirely
In 2019 the decision was reaffirmed
And
Did not do it
Program
It was a
Trying to get attention out of Snowden
Larry
Day he's trying to ride that way
Or this decision
Confirm the judge
Hindsight
Ultimately was meaningless really good
This forced to take his crap
Larry
If your
Someone like Alec
You might have every reason to think like
Larry f******
Actually got one we're on the ground
Of what's going to turn out
Yeah
Play
He's an embarrassment
Breakfast
Unfortunately
20 trillion-dollar lawsuit against
China
Lizards eating loses lights
I don't think it's going to go in
You staying grounded
Alright
Larry's like
Jesus Christ butt
I was just pushing back on.
Got to Capac
Jesus
You know it's almost
It seems more
Egotistical
To compare yourself to Jesus
Rosa Parks
This is where the weather like
I'm going to steal Rosa Parks like
It's weight
To try and steal Rosa Parks
Too much playwright the matter of perspective
I got just have some dirt
Come on
I know you're on Lenny Bruce mode over here trying to
Is so edgy Jordan a religious material
So
Yeah
Workout
One last clip in that
It's just really bring home of Alex
Lovingly reclaim it and knowing it
The present day
Larry is trying to destroy Alex
Because he
Really believe
He's a good guy
That's what you say when someone is on the right
Theme for you at
Piece of s*** I hope he dies tomorrow
Scooters and where's the last Larry
I could go and going to town on it
So were they bring this to the end of it was really interesting
Sing to go into because it's so
Trivial and a lot of ways going back in 2013 episode
It's mostly an infomercial for his supplements
Couch under the
Guys of Avis Orioles back
With
Chicago
Dubious
None of them rise to the level of like really interest
Even the interview the interview with magic
2bl
I just would
Care
No that's terrible
Broker program
For interview
Fill in the blank
Not really that interesting
Embarrassing
But it is a nice retreat
Reprieve from the present-day ohs
Being a depressed
Husk
The person
Don't make me not
Actually
Topix do
We are living
In a time that is
Our lives are touched
Affected by
Bing
Like the black lives matter protest
The conversation that happen
Turning around those
Is really relevant
Matters
Covid-19 situation
Whether or not
Take things serious
And here too
Difficult
The house
As lighthearted and fun as I wanted to be a lot of the time because it's like
Hey
Tomorrow
Any number of people who listen to the
The show someone
Indirectly by
Something
We're talking about
Hasn't anyone who could get sick
Maybe
Difficult
And it's really hard to not
Have that in your mind
When we're hearing about those sorts of
You can be kind of nice to look back
On this time Stakes to it
Efficiency
Totally sure
So
It's worth it
It is
Now to have the time capsule
Looking back at 2013
And being like
Oh that's right
I remember the show that I signed up to
To cover weirdo jumpers and soil
More like future maybe we'll get back
Yeah yeah and
Make me realize this
I should be more
Being able to flash back a little bit
Restorative
I don't know
Happy Birthday Robert for you on your birthday V butts
Happy birthday
Thank you Robert for appreciate
Very weird
Chalk mark on your cable
Nice day it's nice to know that we can all celebrate.
I think part of the idea that Robert had was
Very little idea what's going on in the world
About it
No also Google has robot
Google
No matter what era of Alex
You are about anything that has to do with your life
How to do plugs
Because by the time this episode is used for its proper prepping wheel
Taking over Google
Is robots
Command Facebook and Twitter going to be gone by then
Imma juicy Ice Cube
Alex