Important
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
We are the bad guys
Need need money
College fight
Nick.com
About Alex
Jordan
Whatsyourprice
Vinegar for plants
No plant to plant watch plant
I've got a bunch of
Various vegetables that I'm growing new some things that are coming into
Early-stage
I'm starting to
I've really been getting a charge out of his
You love the smell of turkey blow the smell of dirt
I enjoy it
Get my hands in there
Smells good
Nature
And I picked up a very cheap copy of Mortal Kombat
No no
I think it's 11
I don't know but okay.
It's a cheap used one
11 is that new I mean compared to Mortal Kombat 2
Is it the one that has
Has been there since like 3
Yeah something like that secret to
Going to the arcade
I preferred Killer Instinct
Killer Instinct they had more energy
I was
Felt like
Well this violence might be a little over
I understand it's camp and I play together it's in first
You should try and play that one Shaolin Knights
Cooperative play
Are you going to play
Together
Maybe that would work better for you
Just like
This is what I've got okay
It's it's riveting stuff she was learning how to play it and I was on the edge of my seat
Who's your who's your character Baraka
She knew I was playing with her
Call
Stuff that has no application
Astonish
Somebody
Autonomous Zone
I'm going to say about that
Jeffrey
EMH and it spelled
IAAI
Again
Half of it
Next
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you Peter
Xbox
Text Lindsay are in Isabella Lyndsey
Easy cheap
I'm a policy wonk
Inseam
I don't know okay alright I don't know how to
Charity Terraria
That would be good we would appreciate
Today's the 7th and 8th
So we're talking we're talkin Tuesday when
Wednesday
Slow news day
Not much going on Tuesday and Wednesday
Nothing is happening on Alex
Nothing
Can't talk about bolsonaro
We'll get to that
I'm aboard might not
No broken on Thursday though
No
I don't know if getting close to 6
Attacks with across the country towards protesters
Video that Alex saw where a black guy hit a white kid
+ 12
No no no.
All right I mean just general
Montreal little by little
Alright wizard
No no
Yes okay
Alright even though I'm really
Cuz that's a good guess wizard
Business for the answer
Yeah at some point
Most of the time that I was listening to show I had a really difficult time even
Giving a s***
Because so much of the time is just him saying the same things over and over and over and over and over and over and over
Over again
Petition to eat your kid
After globalist
They're going to take you into camps like it's over and over again
It's just obviously the intention of it
Repeat it over and over again to get to the point
Iron Man
Fusion heart
Help me out nerd
Don't you know comics
My arc reactor
Driven in that seems like things that are different
And it was a desert for the
Worth our time
He was just talking about
Disconnected Ranch how you should be scared
Going down
Is
Tacular
But not a wizard very disappointed
These people literally want to beat your brains out
Yeah man all right should be a sensor like there's a lot of that
How are you
I don't know
Might be a push
Going to kill everybody
News about
Desecration body in post
Open casket
Certainly not
So mad about you
Don't worry we're starting here on the 7th
Complaining about China and he's complaining about the media man either all liars
We punished
So I should clarify
Alex is talking about how like there are like
I guess
Promoted content on fortnite now
I don't know I don't know what the deal is
MCI 9 put some broadcast on fortnite
Okay and Alex's mad about that
So that's what he's talking about
Allowed
To be on your fortnite
Alright buddy
You're old
Command Jones tell me that white
When
Evil globalist corporations of planets
Ever seen
Facebook
Time Warner
Muslim
Silicon Valley
Do to you
He said do your thing China
The one thing that I don't really care about it all whatever he's actually talking about about fortnite I have no idea
I couldn't get myself
I pulled this because I want to make a claim with categorically false
He claims that the media likes you would never talk about Muslims and Alex is completely making up
There's this article from June 19th 2020 titled quote what's happening in China's 211
Million
That's an article Alex probably wants to pretend doesn't exist
And because it contains
Quote according to an excerpt from John Bolton's forthcoming book published
President
Go ahead
Wichita
Exactly
Has that article out
There's a big investigative piece
From February
Chinese government records reveal detailed surveillance reports on weaker families
Application for Master 10
Going back to January 21st
Weaker Refugee tells of death and fear inside China's xinjiang camps
You can go back to February 2nd 2018
Thousands of Muslims to China's political Edge
Education camp
CNN has tons of Articles covering various aspects of the Chinese treatment of most
Pierce
Which
What's important to understand with the intention of that lie is
Azan are saying what are you saying
He also probably has no idea whether or not to get undiscovered the story
The reality third coverage or non coverage of the week
The only thing that matters is image and feeling
I don't want the audience to just believe him and assume the CNN has in fact not touch
The story
And this is built on the feeling that he's created with the business of never criticized in China
The feeling is important
Because it helps Alex rationalize why everyone thinks Alex is a
It's not because he is in fact
Actual piece of s*** and a liar
Because everyone but Alex has a twist
China and they can't stand that he had the balls to
Call them out
Meanwhile if you just
Take a peek at what they're Brooke what reporting in
Is not afraid to cover this story
They might be afraid to cover it in the way Alex does
Which I would say is irresponsible
Maybe trying to start a war
Is Alex agrees with Trump
Like literally like yeah go ahead and do those I'm fine with that they're Muslim don't care
Which is a
Proviso that
We're at the point now where Iris
Specs
The idea of Truth in Fahrenheit
But in regards to Trump if you say the worst thing a human can say
And say Trump said it
Fine I believe you
Navigation is
Campbell
But I'm not going to be suckered into just automatically believing someone because
Because it's so big that I would be
Problem
Alex
It's really important for him to create
I guess a prop
Or some sort of AA
To get out of having to explain why everyone doesn't respect him
And it must be because he has the
To call out China what everyone else is in there
Answered my prayer
Divas audience even like
Alex love to talk about Play-Doh
Is it just looked out of the cave they would see the
We just Googled it
They would not get Infowars articles
Up top of Google search results for what's going on in no
Literally every other news out
So if Alex is
Like he has to take a perverse
Them knowing that he's lying and being like
Old man house phone on a CDs
Call someone to Google Airport
There's an extra step
I don't know
SMS
So this next clip
Because
Anyway
I'll never forget what an answer
20 years ago
Empty Mason local Act
Activist
East Coast
Warmies at Lisa's the main group of the future this is what the time is really are
Infiltrated them he'd been there he he he went deep
Michelle
The bad news
This is the first time I've ever heard Alex bring up the story about how he knew someone who had infiltrated
20 years ago in Austin or whatever
Which is something you might think would have come up in the past
I mean we never dealt with antifa before there have been no previous protests
Years past where he might have been screaming about antifa right I don't believe this story unless Alex in this other
Dude we're hanging out with Neo-Nazi skinheads at punk shows
There's very little likelihood otherwise they would have run is anyone claiming the banner of ants
Pecan
I have absolutely no idea who Steve Mason is to give you some sympathy
Alex
The only thing I can even find about him and looking into him a little bit is it his name appears of the participants of the Travis County Commission
A meeting from October 27th 1998
All right now then
He and Alex Jones along with Alex's cameraman Mike Hansen appear as private citizens who spoke at
Possession but it's just a minute
So I don't know what they talked about it all
This is a meaningless piece of babbling in this guy's dead and now Alex
This is going to create a mythology guy
20 years ago he said in 20 years they're going to try and take over but a bing bada boom here we are
Society Steve Mason Society my friend
Minot
I'll be funny if it is Jackie
Jason's brother
So Alex brambles a whole bunch
About that video of the kid getting hit
It's the exact same thing he does all the time whenever there is some sort of video going around
He gets into some of his somebody is a vampire
Stuff here
Vampires
You're you know
There are those in Alex's world
Of course there are those who are Dracula's
We get to learn about a couple
Don't tell me
Write down on this piece of paper
Where you think these people fall
I hear the three people that are going to be discussed
Brian stelter
Okay where do you think we're going here
Okay alright
Bill DeBlasio
Gavin Newsom
These are the three
You have to decide Renfield or Dracula
Well I mean we don't even have the New Jersey governor who is obviously a Dracula
The country
Brainwashed the entire country into wearing masks or something
I mean we can extend this game out and actually play with like Nancy Pelosi
Butter
Only three people that he specifies
I want to see I want it I want to see if you have good radar in terms of Alex's
Empire watch
But maybe
He has somehow
Twisted inverted this guy who's just
Like a guy
And turned him into the evil Master you mean self
De Blasio
The only person
Nail disingenuous in Creepypasta
Shelter
Is Governor Newsom even worse
I'm sorry
Get a photo of DeBlasio smiling
Stand up
Movie about job
Blasio
Second Jordan you're changing one of your answers
Thank you
Immediate
American Psycho 2
Stepaside Christian Bale
Nothing
Michael Jackson
One down
Delta
Liver stuff
343 baby
Play always so happy
Ukiah real good
He will don't you worry
Come outside your house
He loves you
Sorry
Let's just get right back to where we were
I'm impressed Jordan I really thought she could have gone either way I could have him
Stelter was kind of being picked up
Affected
That's it
Who's going to be the Dracula
Yeah I feel like you probably
Like every other marriage
United States
Escalated by the governor of
New York the president everybody who lives in New York
He's already
At bat
Congratulations on my Jordans
We will
Keep you updated
So
You mentioned at the beginning of the show
Factory bolsonaro test
Deposited for covid-19
Now there's an unfortunate side-effect
And one of them is Alex forgetting how to pronounce his name
Brazil's bottles
Cold
Coronavirus
Deposit
Santa Ana
Texas
Don't want to shut down
Economy Inn
Azle
So that's why I fall tomorrow.
Great fun times Alex bananas
That is that is the call for revolution that he should be like
They're coming to kill bolsonaro
That's the cultural revolution
Seems like that should be Alex's at
He needs to heal a fly it into the trying to take out these nationalist
L a r a
Governor Abbott is now Santa Ana
Carne in
Zestfest
I don't I don't know he's he's
DS Santa Ana now though
Alex and I mean
Who's going to win
Okay alright
Comes on
Still like a Park please
Not much
You speak of on this entire episode there's so much feeling time this is
From the 7th
There is a pastor Rodney Howard Browne
I don't care I know you're asking me all about how you want your church to be open
Course I understand
Click
Rogers on
The gear because he's pretending that he is an expert on Delane Maxwell
And all this stuff
So he was saying he should also go to jail no nevermind
He doesn't know them is just studied it
Diabetes
Kennedy time in a minimum-security and Venom maximum
He has a new Theory to float
Pretty cotton
And when is I first revealed
Bill was going
The island
Because of his
Affair with
Just Wings
That that's
The connection
They were having a
Worried as beer
Goshen New York
Andean and in the Virgin Islands
So he's done his research and he's found that Bill Clinton was having a
An affair with you later Maxwell but his research.
If you look into
Cuz he knows her so well
Persei Jordan
Weather in El this is the conclusion that
Strikes me as difficult
Come to only buy
It's a product of thinking
Enchirito
I feel like
Larry Nichols should fall for the Raptors anytime
Rodger stone is like
Somebody
Larry Nichols just bald
I think I think Larry Nichols
Too much for a you might be Beyond he did make that brief reappearance talk about
Adam Schiff
Egyptian sex party
Very hesitant
You threatened to Blackmail cowgirl
To talk about Egypt
Heather disappeared
So Alex
It comes in on the 8th
And
No
Sucks
Chose
Through mud
These last a few days
Something great
I don't think that it's the product of what he's
Teasing
Do we start the episode with a little bit of a
Let me just tell you things are coming up right now
Since I learned about this on Saturday
Saturday
Did you
And then I make some phone calls and events happened and
Very decisive
Are you
No
The best to talk about this right now
I know what's going on
Daya
But is it good for me to announce this
Because
Don't know why the White House has one else's
So should I try to get on the phone
Cuz I want to talk to the White House I can get
Shot
Topgolf
What's the problem
It's such a big issue I respect
People
Thanks
To talk about what's going on some public knows
But no one knows about this yet
Feel bad
Not telling you
Shut up this one issue right now
To the point of
I really think about it should I
Information
Yes
Maybe I'll wait another day
Okay f*** you
At least for now
What a f****** throw a shoe at him
What is a Dragon Ball Z like right before the final fight episode the last episode
We got the fight is all set up and then right before the final fight there's no full episode
This guy we brought over here we brought over here
4 in the morning
Nothing just you said nothing
Alex doesn't I don't know what he's talking about
And guess what
A couple days from now he says something
What you was talking about what he was talking about
Horrible
I won't say what it is but it is cheese a little bit of like what
Football parkour
Some good news
Let's just say this
If you thought we were going
Miles an hour
Collision Course with a lawnmower
We can. We were
Definitely
How is this any different than qanon
We're heading for our nation to tell you anything about it tomorrow
I got no answer my phone calls
You've been strung along 44
And none of the stuff is at
Siri
This time
Tomorrow I'm going to an outside thing that totally happened that increase our speed from 200 miles to
2000 mph on a scale
Because I don't think that I'm about to play for you is what
Talkin about
What it could be
Attract rice
And it also
Could be the work of wither
You understand that
Physically the planets align
On Saturday
A very long time
140 years from now
Friends on
What the hell's going on we're all out there
Somebody spiked
The beer
Like this for
Almost a month
Thomas Jefferson's idea Orlando Magic
Winning
Giant
Planetary alignments in a clan
The Romans would go to war
Wow
Perfectly clear with you planetary alignment
Physically impossible
There has never been and will never be a point when all the planets align based on their positioning and Orbison
It just doesn't happen
People talk about planetary alignment
There's a certain number of planets in the same section of the sky at assert
Time does Mike's
Flatline like they like they show you in it
Seeing of like a you know
Modeling do you have
Nuance
Do like it would depending on where you are
Any white
On July 4th
Last Saturday
Second of their three conjunction
This year
It's actually really big year for Jupiter and Pluto
I'm glad they're having fun opportunity in these three conjunctions where the bright light
Close enough to Pluto that allows people to telescopes
To be able to see Pluto
Better or whatever the f*** Alex Israel
Depends on who you ask
Yeah I'm one of those
When I was when I was coming up
Jealous
According to space.com
Jupiter and Saturn is a visual
Are you sure it doesn't yes
On July 4th the planets were perfectly and let you know they're made
Being perfectly in line all right
Can't say that
Out loud and think that you're not the dumbest person
Because of the specifics
Particularly the it won't happen again until 2161
I come from a meme
God dammit
Going to die
Because mean people are living
Alex just awesome like Crystal shop
Oh my God I was out on the lake
Dimensional space
Straight line on a flat surface
They're all over the
Been everywhere we go all the way over
It's pretty fun
So Alex
This is the only like maybe one of the only things that I really was like alright got an episode
Release the Titan
I saw Disney's Hercules
When it happened
It really did a number on them
Of course not
Corporate deals
We don't make decisions when the planets align
Also a literal state
Month or so
We're still going to be
Alignment
Closest alignment happened July 4th
Only had a few beers
What
You were supposed to quit drinking
Whip and Nae Nae
Sleep really good
Call my wife
I can't sleep
Those are three-year-old daughter
In the hell is going on
Right now just reminds me of
The story is the protagonist
Finding a bunch of clippings
Really sensitive around the time with okay
Is a dreaming in really a I just
The stars are right for Cthulhu in the the great old ones come back
I'm going to put you some
Something real quick
As far as having trouble
Sleeping all right
And being a certain day
4th of July
Add a known for
Exactly
That might be why
Yeah
Sing this year
Be a lot of them
But it wasn't never bothered
And I'm one of the people who's the most bothered by noise
Absurd profoundly sensitive to noise never bothered me at all
Although now that I'm saying that to sound like if it did bother you
Something wrong with you
La we would have a very different story did you see the the overhead
Helicopter shop
Oh s***
Overhead helicopter
Thrift Shop
And somebody even put the
Blade Runner music
Because it was
Wall-to-wall just
Splashing
Flashbang
It's really not
The fourth is pretty loud around this neighborhood
Best Buy
A2B that alter bikes
Built into the blend of like
City North
The train is the distance doesn't bother me
Cars
Somehow
Weird it's weird how the brain works that way I think because you're
Prepared for
Maybe but it's so subconscious
It's not like I'm controlling filtering those things out
Weird noises
Sky
This is a conversation about
Flanigan's
And the Moon
I assume he
That's one thing
I'm not into astrology
Astrology
Understand
Nope
During a full moon
Does not
But what's that doing
So it is interesting there's actually a study from 1984 in the British medical journal that looks at crime rates
From three towns between 1978 and 1980
Me too and I found triple bypass
Increase crime rate on Fulton
Supposed
Motorcycle
Other subsequent Studies have been in
Conclusive and some
Showing slight increases
I can't really explain that 1984 study other than to say that there may be another variable involved in the structure of the study
Didn't capture recycles
Contradictory studies that have happened
I like this is
Is nearly ending my relationship level argue
My partner really believes in the full moon
And I just had to accept
Well meaning of mostly water
That's actually in the discussion section of that article
British medical journal
I don't know I don't I think it's
You know
I understand where she's coming from and I also understand where the other side is based in
Rather studies not showing
I don't know that stuff though Alex is correct about the etymology
I spend a lot of time cleaning out what he and all of his guests
Makeup of words means
Good job Alex
I mean like that's common knowledge but Oak
How far is Sbarro
So we know that Alex is probably
From which all Arts
Is created
Everett
Only when the planets
Right everybody who's anybody
He's probably really been the thing that's inspired
Probably everything that you like but you just don't realize it
And here's one example.
Infowars
The song
Then he wouldn't even
News weather in Santiago
Pressure put on
And then
Patriots
Mainline
In the end
You lose every
Your whole civilization Society
So that song is The Pretender by the Foo Fighters inspired this song A little far-fetched
Considering that this is from their 2000
Seven album
Dave Grohl has sent at least 1991 as a member of Nirvana
Like they get famous and won't come on my shows like
He was famous in 291
Come out like I was the first Fighters
Late 90s
That was like wait baby 97
Cable Round Nirvana nevermind
It has become
Well he's only the drummer in the
Alright
Then when he became a frontman
5 years later
Still coming up
Gigantic star already
Not just that but it also
Just released it comes on
Jesus he was essentially what I was established as one of the most
Securely famous artists music
The Stone Age
Like Reddit
It's insane that someone that save us it would just apply for you
Tenacious B2 mainstream popularity for seemingly almost no reason
Destiny he was there he was also the devil in the
It is career he's been a vocal advocate for lgbtq rights and he support
Gun control
He's such a Democrat girl this guy
Play the song My Hero at the 2012 democratic National
Play about Barack Obama album companies
Do you remember where the repair toothpaste
White Raven and Obama now
Thanks Berry Gordy
Basically zero chance the Dave Grohl
You guys talked about it's like about political turbulence
Easy to see how Alex could hear it imagine that it's about himself
Which means it's about Alex
Right
What the f***
So that was funny
There's no way that I believe any of this
Butts
Well let me tell you something about this movie
Guardians of the
Almost almost
Star-Lord
So Alex
Empire
This next clip
I wish you were
Buyers for this
You trying to talk about how bad and accidentally said some things that are kind of positive about Hitler
Understand something
20 hours you'll never eat little piece of this summation
Document
This is not conjecture
There is a giant long-term
Planetary
Corporate directive
Sure
Develop inside the British Empire starting in about
Sounds right
Adopted
As a world government plan
At the end of World War II
Bargain place
Hitler was not
He wanted control
Differently
To strategically only wipe out certain
Hitler did not want
Person
Lessons
Totally insane
People
This is a conversational really need that
You not crazy
Hitler
All the time yeah yeah
You get yourself into murky territory when
Like 8 because I know the point he wants to make and that is at the globalist want to kill everybody
Just from a numbers perspective
He's better
That's kind of what I was wanting to say
You don't need
To say that
You don't need to get into any of this
Nope it's not territory you can really walk very well like you're going to end up saying something
Even Alex
Junior most generous
Devil's
Position eventually gets
I'm not saying
Which is not the way you started
Qualify everything
Nah that's crazy
I mean look
Malaria's killed probably 25 billion people it didn't just choose the Jews right
It was not worse than malaria that's particularly distasteful about this
Is one of these things
Write the other one is made up
Paranoid delusion
What Hitler was real he's not as bad as the things I scare myself
Well that does
Doesn't matter
Did you see Independence Day
Hitler wasn't as bad as those alien
They were trying to kill everybody places all over every monument all over the world
Closest Monument
Yeah I got to say
For these reasons and almost certainly plenty of others
Also you're fired from guardians.
Alex Landers a man who is dead
Bobby Parkway
Ocean High School
Professor speaker
Everyone
So now Alex
Has a request like that for quite a while because Alex has told the story many times has
About dr. Irwin spear a number of times
Defaming
Saying that he was
Trying to recruit people
Into a eugenics
Extermination
Program
Family wants to sue Alex I don't see any reason why they wouldn't have standings
To do that
He's not a public figure
He was just a professor
At UT
This is outrageous
He's being accused of
Go to like
It's he wants
To kill everybody not just that but it seems as though he's literally
Grooming young boys turn them into
It's a little bit of a problem
If I was related Irwin spear I would do it
Totally
Respond
But
Might not want to for their own reasons I respect that
23andMe information dance
So
This makes Corpus kind of like an extension of
Alex's
The regular Trend that we've been seeing where escalating
Just a lot of like
You know hey might be time to kill and God will tell you what
Bolsonaro has covid-19 there man everybody has a cold
Troubling
Escalade
This is all been set up to make you obsolete to dehumanize you
Suck the life out of you
Protect your family away from you
Lies
About human plan
Talking about
What we're going to do
We can't just sit here and do it
The leadership of the operation
Black
What does take one for the team mean
I think first and foremost
It means that Alex
For all his pretensions towards being a revolutionary or anything like that
Absolutely saying hey
Somebody else do this
Please
Yeah buddy
Kamikaze mission level
Has to show up right yeah be a hero
Alex Telefunken
This kind of thing is going line
The trend that we've been seeing
Over the past I like
That to me is such a
Like a further pushing of it because
The someone's going to have to take one for the team
Who's going to step up onto things are the sort of language
If you were trying to get some
Unhinge listener to be like
I'm the person who supposed to do that
I've been looking
Thruway to step up
I can be the tool of God's vengeance
I am loved
The team I will take one for the team
It seems to me like
It seems to me very difficult
As we go further and further this keeps happening it's getting more and more clear
More and more difficult for me to accept the proposition that he's not aware of what he's
Yeah totally that to me is because
I'm not saying I'm a hundred percent convinced
But I am becoming
Let's not
I would say
Here's what I
Rationally
I don't think he actually wants
Anybody to
Emotionally
I think he wants more than anything for somebody to
Carryout
His vicarious Justice
Yeah I like that that feeling like I'm so angry all the time and I'm impotent about it and I can't do anything
I would like a proxy to go visit my
Vengeance upon
You may be right I mean I don't know I don't know what the
Distinction between emotional and rational is
He doesn't want an actual Revolution
We can't park
You and I
Sitting here
We have to go on is like what
Represents on the show and how he carries himself
I mean yeah I would
His rational mind is like
Actually
People to be hurt
Probably in the same way
Putting out I don't know but it's getting
It's getting really troubling
About that
What he just did
Described
I would like
Starting now
For a group
People
Plan how to commit murder
That is a crime
That's conspiracy
To commit murder
Inspire in the conspiracy involved in it
I would announce my plan to commit a massive
Scribes that's why you're in the clear
So
Calls
First guy to know
Real that's request
Alex's answer is dumb
What do you think about Kanye West do you think that he's serious do you think that it's all sort of like a
Facade he saw his wife and he saw her dad
Want to kill all the black people
Wildman
It doesn't mean he's not
But he wants to be with God and he wants me to
Does that mean
Wow
She's like to like Rosa for that
Assure
Good songs about
Booty booty
God bless you I appreciate your
Yeah man lot of fun
There's so much similarity between
Kanye West in 2 Live Crew
Is he preemptive
Licking Conyers boots
That what he was just doing
Would like to be stop on commercial
Everybody needs
Stop paying attention to this nonsense
I mean
It just
Highlights Alex's lack of serious
Whatever
This is interesting we got a caller
Spirituality
Apparently
Face mask
Bad for spirits
Because they
Change your breathing pattern on your breathing pattern getting more shallow
Has some negative effects
Spirit that can breathe it has
It doesn't read like the Drone and stuff
Leslie not a product
All colors of Sharon
And they're driving the breathing algorithm into a shallow
Breathing algorithm toso we manifest
Shallow place
I don't know every emotion
The breathing
Pattern that goes with it
You definitely
And you know
I think it's more about stopping you from screaming muffling a scream it's just typically why people put their head
It's not usually to keep the Holy Ghost
No it's not to alter your breathing patterns
With the most high by holding my
Just listen to that guy talk about like breathing patterns
I feel like I've heard this stuff
And I know I have
Because it's all just new AG nonsense with getting recycled
And this guy's call is almost entirely just rehashing of new-age s***
That I remember from like a f****** decade ago
Where we're going into Matt
Planetary
Shift like you said there's going to be a big one on December 21st
That's what they say
No that's the
The true beginning in that scenario age
And I feel like that
The Breath of God
Spirit it'll be more energy in the air and more clarity
And where
And still Days Later can't sleep
Can you feel it
You just got sunstroke or something like
You just got sun poisoning you just forgot to put sunscreen on
This is buying a calendar stuff all over again
Inverted
Yeah from seeing some of these accounts.
Densities and dimensions
Transcendence
This is all the same stuff it's just all I told his being recycled from
All of these logs
They were doing anyways bulshit
4 years it's all the same
It's all exactly
Is it a real bummer
Because I'm not least of which because
Especially after going through Carrie Cassidy's bulshit where it's
Like always scratching
Space Weirdo And they hate
The Jews like now we are seeing all these new age weirdos
You like Crystal 10 years ago and now you also
Kill the Jews what is going on here
Exactly what the phenomenon has something to do with
Eroding
Critical thinking
Skills-based around
Various
I don't know how I would put it but
Just like
Communities that are based on
Acceptance of nonsense
Divorce
Susceptible you are to
The coop
So you could
Stay in a crystal Community for a really long time right
And because
Maybe you and
Your friends just like Crystal
And maybe you meditate
Some
The meditation to the crystals with a really good time
Now let's assume that somebody
Is Buckhead
Comes into your Crystal
Ideas
Like
Yeah I don't know I don't even know exactly
I think people were vulnerable in those
And I think that's why you see that less
Less than just like it's inevitable that they will have it
I think really attractive
Personal experience potential stuff is always been really fast
You can find yourself gravitating
And they become
Just large
Collections of people who are Sitting Ducks
For very talented
Radical eisers
Go from being a
Community to being a mob and
It can't happen
That's a bummer
But
Is really interesting about this
Alex
Become more into that stuff to he's talking about
Tripping his balls out because of the planets align
Liberals getting high
Very weird
Service next caller also had a prophetic dream about Alex
She was getting real weird
Episode
Pretty normal
Justin vegetating like in 2013
Alex thanks for taking my call
Thank you sir
Minister for about 8 years and
Two-and-a-half years ago I had a prophetic dream about you
The color
Imagery
And what not not going to share it on here but I'm going to share what was the
By the way I had a discussion with Tim fruge this morning about
He said it's like cartoon
Technicolor
We we
A bunch of his wife is having
Vivid
Technicolor dream
It was like that
Sifo-Dyas
This was two-and-a-half years ago
Vivid dream about Alex 6 years into listening to him pretty regularly
That makes sense
Around screaming a lot of sensational
Maybe some of that would have seeped into your brain
Anyway he doesn't want to talk about what the dream was
It was about
That good
What you say
Really profound
Call Dodge rings in my life
The last one I had
Ball tell you
I'm a truck driver sitting in a truck I was sitting in the past
Your side
I looked I was
I kind of woke up
The truck was going down the road
I looked over because it was just like I came to
There is nobody driving
The wheel and a handle
The door
Cruise control was on we're going super fast
And I looked and it was you and you were you had your hand on the door and hand on the wheel but your body was out like
Out of the truck
And you were staring at the same time
And it was like
Look super dangerous I reach over grab your wrist
I pulled you into the truck
And then you grab the wheel
And then
And that I sent you
You know
We're on the journey
They're still
Do we still have a long ways
To go
Driving to
Really dangerous dice
50 * like road conditions
I think Alex has eaten otherwise there's no reason
Yeah and then I grabbed your arm at 2:30
Oh man I can't believe we reached the point where April Wars has become tell me your dream
Mad about me
Closest friends
Let alone a stranger
Calling into a shaking this is Prosthetics
What is the prophecy
Burlington
Anyway
And that's when I
Yeah we all need to come together
I don't know if I agree
Here is what that guy has to say about his own dream
I'll tell you what was
Was going to meet us to been my life's work
There's a crypt
Tonight
That in defeat the globalist
And it was done 2000 years ago with the cross
And what the world is really experiencing now is to be getting birth pains
Reboot
The revelation of Jesus Christ
At this point I was really worried that he was going to say Alex you need to be crucified
Show me really is
The perversion of a twisted
Religious stuff
It's going to fall off
We're just going to see
Christ plainly for who he is
That's fine just declare out to
The audience today
God loves you
And every single time you missed the mark
What's 10 means
Dealt with
At the Cross of Christ
Covenant with his father
And
Because of love
Because we are loved
He made a way he is
The door
Through this and into
The real reality bless you brother
Redhead
Housewise defecate every 425
I got cut off by the bank
Very pretty
I don't think Alex is doing good time management
I mean I got is defecated on the phone for 45 minutes
Honestly this show is so boring
But for the most part
Constant repetition
Drumbeat these are people these people are evil they want your kids are going to kill you
Eva Eva Eva
It's over and over and over again
And then
Insanely over-the-top extreme religion
And March towards viola
You got going on
On the regular
Infowars
And these days are pretty likely these last couple days
I've been
Pretty much just that
Bandits
It's not that interesting when Alex isn't talking about like how the planets aligned
You got high on a boat
Or whatever
Is one thing that's funny
And then him thinking that it had some kind of a mystical
Is
Is fun but the rest of this is not good
I'm going to pinch you
Okay
Okay so Alex gets another call
And this guy
Ask Howard
Question
Albuquerque not what's your name
It is
We talked about on the show
Alex claimed there's a council of twelve
Identify
Lava Council of twelve
This guy is like
Can you get a really a
On one of your shows
Bill Gates
Defiance
Alex hang up on her
Stuffing exactly
Other people on the council or is it
No I mean
Some research that that Bill Gates
Copy political rotate in and out of David Rock
Cellar
Was
On it for a while
I can tell you that job
There's two Rothschilds on it
Been Told
One of them is that
Over representers
The name of to Rothschild
In 2017
Hey Alex is really interesting clearly made up
Budget European
That is
He's got cold on in class and he was like I do not know how a
Conceivably the 12 people who ruled Humana
It's not a small.
If they rotate in and out
Very willingly
We give up a seat on that no absolute
There is always
They're okay if you don't deep freezer
This is entirely made
Freezer
Thank you that I've struggled with
Here's what happen
Every civilization
Has the Council of twelve
Sure and then the council of twelve when the civilizations meet
To fight each other to the death
Okay and whatever 12
The 24
Become the new 12
Okay
There's only one Council of twelve
Until we meet
Exile Raptors
And that will happen when all 12 planets align
Planet XIII is the one nobody
David
Concrete a 48 imaginary
Group of 12 people claimed from the planet in
There's four
Rothschild
Just saying it's unofficial
Get out of here
SquarePants
I told you I got a little
Please
Close attention to what
Because
Everything I know of Alex's career
He presents himself to be
You should not disagree with
Anything
Joe Biden
Alright the video just one live
Dot-coms on a hot mic
Columbus organization
He says the police have become the enemy but don't worry he'll take them over and then they'll be
They'll be good again
Abolish the suburbs and rural areas
Single-family home racist
Don't have nuclear family
So horrible.
Get all the records and find out what they're doing that's what revelstok
The stop-and-frisk in Camden New York City
The federal government has right to Glenn instead change the stomach lie
What's going on
There's a whole range of things that we can do
The idea of no-knock warrants for
Drug cases it's bizarre we don't need that
Egyptian Vice trouble that's how Brianna was chill
Need for fundamental change
People have access to the records of police when they have misconduct charges against them
To be able to know
Should be held in
That information will have to be made available
Justice department
Handheld in a file
So you be able to track
The last thing you need is my Farmer in Humvee coming into a neighborhood just like the military
I don't know anybody to become the enemies are supposed to be
Alex based on everything in Alex's career
Yes
You should not have no knock warrants for drug offenses
That end of escalating into people's deaths
Alex should be 100% on board with Biden saying that
He's talking about the militarization of police
And how
Like negative and toxic
Alex should a hundred percent be on board with that
The only thing that I think you could take a new ones position on
Is whether or not the federal government should keep the records
Of the
Malfeasance
Complaints and abuse
Charges against
Like Alex could say no the state should keep that as opposed to
The Department of Justice the old place
Believe or has Believe throughout the
The Lion's Share of his career
That the police
Reindeer
So now Alex is fully transformed
Hearing positions
He himself would have said
New no-knock
Transfer drug sheet is unacceptable
Tanks
Bitter coming into neighborhood that's
Really shouldn't happen
Those are things that would be right on the Alex Jones Show in the past
Now he's like this is evil globe
Yes those very much
Hey I don't think officer Darren should have a
F****** tank so that Alex is a gas in favor of militarized police absolute
Take down everybody's doing what is he saying he's saying that if there is an Administration that he died
Doesn't like
He hopes that they have the power to at any point in time
Decide that gun laws should be in
Enacted and then with a no-knock warrant
Found its home
And break in and kill him that is what he was like this is so weird to me because
He's falling into the Trap that he's falling into or whatever
Like is just
Oppositional defiance
Yeah like you mad at this
Guy who doesn't like you besides not supposed to be
Sing things
No interest
Intra
Sucks
Now if you were to come out and say
People should be freed who have drug conviction
That I would say
You are right
Still go fuc yourself
But you're right
I hope
Accidentally walk into a fire but
I'll give it ya
Heath
Him being in office
Override
My beliefs Vicky balloon
I don't understand how Alex can't like have the presence of mind to be like
F****** hate Joe Biden sucks I don't want him to win
Yeah absolutely no-knock warrant so ridiculous there's no reason
There's no acceptable argument for why we should be doing that
For suspected drug violations
The police are out again
Control I don't agree with Biden I hope he loses embarrassingly in the next election
But yes please don't
How can you not get to that point how is he so far gone that like
Nothing is nothing is real other than
I think personally I think it is
Due in large part probably
Toomics
McConnell
By that
That transformation really
Of the entire Republican Party
From
Even any semblance of ideas or governance to just
When
Just want to win
That's all we want I don't care what policies we enact as long as they're horrible and awful
Will f*** everything up
As long as we win
Because Alex thinks he doesn't like
Well he thinks he hates him because McConnell is f****** good at cheating
Like I don't know I don't know what to tell you I think it's because he predates
The Tea Party
121 associated with that like
Like somebody's other
Yahoo's yeah cuz it doesn't matter about any
It's just I can't give by
A
Greatest him it seems like
It's not a window if you say you agree with B
That means he won
That means he beat Trump
That's what you're saying you're saying that I agree with Biden
Over Trump
That means B one
Cannot do it
You might be right in thinking but I'm getting a little overwhelmed
Prospect
Because that's really f***** up
Doesn't seem to bother him
Except for you.
He had a
F****** Transcendent experience on a boat that the planets align
Falling apart that is why you don't like
I don't know man it's it's
It's really it's really strange to me I mean like one of the things that I think we've tracked
A ton
You know just
Scattershot as it comes up
Is oldies a complete rejection of his past
Things that seems like the most import
And that's so strange
To me you'd like how easy it is
For him to
Spend
20 years making a career that is based on
Fears of the police state
Fears of militarization of police
Yelling about like things like Jade helm
And all this stuff and Bandit
Allow yourself to
Critique
Joe Biden like this about him saying things that you
Three-way or you're supposed to agree with
The depressant portrait of somebody who
Who's just not Tethered to any
He's not or maybe was but isn't anymore there's nothing like a dozen
Don't seem like anything except guns racism
Annex
Extremist
Generally means anything to them
Yeah cuz even is answer
Police Dept
It's not like just as simple as there's a black man in the well
Yeah I mean I imagine now it's as simple as there's black people in the street
Yeah you know that doesn't seem hard but they're here.
Yeah I mean the police state stuff what does go back to like 9/11 in
Totally related to Obama
I don't know I don't know if we have a concrete answer on this but I will say it's the
It's a bummer
I'm really kind of
Disappointed in this week
The lifestyle
To make sense of this week be kind of like a real
Do nothing kind of. Of time recovering from planets aligning
You got to give him a little bit of little bit
Gravity
Points to the Stars
I gave a green assault little but I expected and actually
Interesting me a little bit and I think it will be because
Rodger Stones got to go to prison
Oh yeah and I think that will lead to
Really good car
Contact on Alex's show
Ain't cuz no matter what happens
If it'll be a chance
App doesn't
It'll be at Ted's in the other direction
Day before prison
We get
John Turturro level Rodger Stone of just like
Look into your heart
There's so many possibilities for good entertainment
Not only your suggestion but doesn't mind
Still should be in play 100% Rodger
I don't know you're listening but if you are listening
Go for it
Really go for it
Hip world
We are interested in elgin's confiding I go to bed Jordan
Donate to a charity in your area or Bellefonte
Omniome Leo hunt
I've inspired all the other Foo Fighters