I have great respect for knowledge by now I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Everybody sit around a little bit about Alex
Joe
Jordan Jordan
Go first cuz I got a little bit of my brush.
Tennis for the first time
Because the park next to us where we played tennis was completely
Torn down
We thought that the tennis courts were gone too but it turns out there was an opening and we could have gone for the past like four months
So it's real disappointing
Play tennis is good to get out of work maybe the time away from it justify
Good it feels
To go back
Justifies the time away
Okay
Steven
Did not come in the mail or email but still very appreciated
The random size jeans keep you updated
How funny is this
Years ago I find a commercial stupid
Anti-nausea or whatever
And now here we are
Yeah but it's very nice
Direct
This is all right there
Crocodile Dundee
That is a nice
Yeah I got the cool
Crafted knife that's awesome
I honestly appreciate it
Crazy right-wing family
Also it's great waking up three times a week getting excited for something
Did you guys ever find yourself in Columbus parentheses hashtag flavortown Hellyeah
Hit me up if you want to go eat
Ford something or even ride horses
Take care policy walk
Chris
Chris that's really really f****** cool
Yeah cuz just mailing a knife
Startling
Under other circumstances
Your door
So Chris has page
Call job
Ford
Vanguard
F o l k vanger apostrophe-s is Forge
Ford
GE
Yeah I don't know a lot of designs
Up on there and there's a lot of really cool looking stuffy and crafts
Knives and various
Cutleries
I understand actually
If I understand this no correctly
There is another one
Ultimate Showdown as was always meant
I can't wait for that other night
From now on I feel like I could take that away from you
Broadcast will be with us by yourself
Copyrighted
Don't know anything about it
I will say that this weekend has been because
I have been
Like a lot of work
Around the house
Air condition
And units put in the window
Gray truck gray
So I got a lot of that stuff going on my life is feeling pretty good
I feel very close
To sort of adulting
Friday night Rosa wraps
I'm getting ready to go to bed in my bed for the first time in 15 years
Credible
No news could pick you off that PETA
Rodger Stone sentence commuted
Not unexpected
Levi said he would never spend
Yeah
Kind of like in my heart of hearts
Deep down
He was probably going to go to prison for Trump to do it
Commuted sentence or pardon Mr
Give him clemency it so I thought there was a chance
But I itch
You should really second-guess those sorts of things
How to make a bed
Made him beg for so long makes me laugh
Very hard
Suggesting messages on Twitter and around two people are saying
Urgency episode Rodger got pardoned
My sense of it was I need to
Cuz I think Alex is going to snow Saturday probably can do an emergent
The episode
Settle down on this
Yeah yeah but sometimes it's fun to throw out an emergency
I'm so excited to wait for Monday
100 have
Is Saturday
Work
News on Friday and Saturday
He has all day
You should be able to put together
And the celebration
Yes we'll see what happens
July 9th
Through July 11th 2020
My dad is a 2020
And
Yeah it's so nice
Not much not much
Is the day of the commuter
Talk about that
The 11th Saturday
It is special to our
Phuc yea emergency episode of Nipsey hussle's victory
For an hour
That was it
It was less that and more
I don't know man I feel really weird about this because like I know this is probably going to be some people tuning in that are going to be like
Open special from us today
I don't
Why would you
Now I don't want to
Podcast for us
Expecting some
The Narrative of like
Rodger stone is precipitated shows up on a war.
Really yes
Reply to Happy Meal come on you really expect
I want to make sure that no one
That I am
Trying to tease that
To the end
This could be a little bit longer
What happened
So first
Chase Steve
I'm a policy wonk
Jordan Google
That's because I'm not sure and I'll probably walk
Thank you
You're not going to do the I don't even know what
Next Trevor
Call Devon
Thank you James
MC
Emmc last initial
Iqms
Thank you next
Thank you
Let's Colleen w
I'm a policy wonk
ICarly
The soil will save us
Thank you so much
Heroin
Freakishly large
Website.com
We appreciate it
Generosity bundled up real nice
Okay alright
Casual recreational softball tryouts
Toss it over to charity new area that sell help
I don't have a whole lot to announce about the year of the
Is that I did get a message
From Bailey
Listen to Bailey that I may have
Ranked
A single Seltzer twice
Might have
Giving them to different how far apart
Super far apart
Not too far apart
Less than 50
Open
I've decided I talk to the commissioner
And we decided that the 1st
Frankenstein
Edwards now
Vacate that's it
The second scoring
Humiliating and I don't want this to get out publicly although I'm saying it on a podcast
Jordan
Too much business really recover I don't even think we can eat now there's just too much to cover
Get to it in this
Probably not
So are we starting the nice and just focusing entirely on like the 11th
Is because I think there's a little bit of a narrative Arc to it
Uno's
Probably coming for Rodger
Coming up
Bablo next hour
And he's got big nose
It's so big
But I just think I'm going to let him
And I'm not even going to get ready
Trailer Journey
Schedule
Present present
You didn't want to work to make this exclusive first place and comes on
Pikachu
You will
In 20 minutes
We won't get these clothes
So I told him
Make a phone call
WeChat
Go ahead and go on Fox news or whatever
So this to me sounds like pre-emptive rationalization
He's not going to go on our Joker
Probably at the point where Tucker will have him on and he knows has better ratings there
Now that's just because I'm going to be drunk at 6 he's so drunk at 6 that he just can't come in
His fault
Rogers and do everything give me the exclusive
Whatever
I'm going to put in the time to make
A phone call to
That's why I report about Rogers s*** is on Saturday
Because they need for the exclusive Friday night
Malachi little impromptu press conference
Yeah Saturday
Buddy
Alex does cover the Wayfair
Conspiracy what happened
Price of course
Yeah so get ready for that
I hate everyone
I hate every once in awhile actually
Prairie
Bizarre
Change the name
On the nights you just start
You know talking about whatever you know just is normal
Time talking about
I just came out
When the FDA
Crastination hundred-thousand-dollar
Baby Parts with steel
Beating
Heart
Berkeley
Said we want
Beating heart
And so
Would deliver them
Alibaba
And they would butcher I'm not there on the spot
If I can pick up
Hot wings
Now where is PETA
University ordered
Beating hearts of babies
What where is
I don't know
So there's a unsurprisingly the story that Alex is lying about
Ignored it but it kind of bothered me look it up
Whatever you said something like that's really hard for me to resist take them up
Straight up
This is from that batch of edited videos that released in 2015 by the Center for Medical
Which was that anti-abortion outlet engaged in Project Veritas style undercover video propaganda
They're not really a center
For medical progress
Medical regress
When it comes down
Exclaim that's made in that Center for Medical progress videos which is exaggerated and distorted
The video claims that a procedure that
University researchers
Call Dave profusion
Requires a beating heart
Having established this erroneous piece of information the video makers then try to demonstrate that heart tissue had been provided
Did the Stanford
To do which is then used to present as evidence that beating human hearts have been delivered
Do Stanford
I'm fine with it this is really sloppy work
To follow up
For all the pieces to stand up to scrutiny
If 1 pieces bad this whole argument collapse
Perfusion
Kind of destroys the entire point
Everything else could be
True name leave at Stanford researchers do this
A procedure and
Obtain heart tissue for it
And the claim
The main claim that the beating heart
You have all that other stuff be true
And the part that you want to be the point
The big spiders
And as it turns out
Bi like a Dorper fusions that are done involving
Stem cell research
Require of eating hearts
Nothing
Adventure remember here though is that Alex is even
Fake thing that he's reporting on
The stuff about babies arriving at the University and boxes and then butchering
That's just a story he wants
Tell is audience to scare them and make them hate his imagined enemies even more
So
Turn of a hat on a hat disgusting at the abortion propaganda here
Teaches you how to properly butcher
You know like it's an apprenticeship thing or do you get that right out of med school
I don't know it's also not at all like ordering Wings you don't butcher the wings
So
Thinking straight
Sure little bit more about that
Ordered
Fresh
Baby part that just came out last week
Hairstyles
They want to murder you and your family
That's another thing you said you can look up so excited
Go ahead and look at up
Judicial Watch
So already already
They are uncovered that the FDA had a contract worth $96,000 between time of 2012
In 2018 with a company called Advanced biosciences resources
Where they would be provided with fetal tissue for
Everything I can tell
This is just about themselves and there's nothing wrong
Nothing other than something
Anger there
And divorce
Hold on you saying
That the FDA spend
Such a ridiculous sum of money
$96,000
$96,000 of taxpayer money
That's what
Small amount for whatever the conspiracy they're trying to stay
Rise to the level of what
About your bosses
Cast what if this isn't illegal human
Organ trafficking operation
Proceed to $95,000 but
I don't think most people would get mixed up with that for that kind of a big whatever they're taking off the top
Can infect somebody with covid and as we no get $95,000
Can you read contracts in 2018
There's no indication that I can find that I know was doing anything illegal or unethical
I mean I just
Like this just seems like
Blabbering
So also in the business of
Grilled annihilus
About resurgent coronavirus cases
This is
Some of the headlines
Setting single-day record
For one day
Edgewater
Good weed
The number of positive Skyrocket
Those positives are fraudulent
Believe the headline that I just read
Before we started recording
Yesterday Florida had 15,000 positive test
Mostly stuck around
This July 9th
For the sake of
Rodger Rodger
We're going to be doing
Surprise to go to Rodger some Skype
Rob Lawrence
You got to do is let yourself go
Having professional Skype issues
I went to Shakira told me a lot
What's going on
Imprisonment
Memes
All those other times
Constantly
He's
Just experiencing ask a problem I believe the years from 2009 to 2015
Every single in and out of break
Sky problem
Kicked off of social media
Nice spin on that
Analysis
Presidented
Censorship
Boston Ro is under the same a text saying that his fan
Allowed
To talk about him or posted speeches or material
On Facebook
On
Show ahead of his
Prison
The president doesn't act
Another giant exercise
This is not a case of Facebook just kicking off fans of Rodger bolsonaro
Found that employees of bolsonaro government
And Rodger Stone networks of accounts
To push coordinated misinformation
It sounds like those two Networks
Are connected
Bolsonaro and his government has a network that was being used
You push false information
Did Rodger Stone have their own unique Secret
Network
Unclear if it was botanist early or like
Not just someone running a bunch of dumb
Combination
According to BBC reporting on the matter
Facebook 754 accounts
50 pages and for Instagram accounts that it had link
Drive to mr. Stone
These Pages would pose as a person not connected to Rodger and then promote things that he wanted to promote give you.
Organic get engaged
Again from the BBC
In total those Bhai
Behind the pages spent about
$8,000 on Facebook advertising
Three times with the FDA
There is that
From this Beast bolsonaro is running with more focus on political maneuvering
Mostly geerdes self-promotion
Rodger claims that he's going to sue
So if I had to guess he's going to yell about his innocence
Use the attention to try and raise money
And then I'll admit that he was running all those pages in about five years and some sort of an interview with Playboy or something
Right
So this is the game I'm getting kicked off social media because
Why won't anybody let a white man speak on this very loud radio show
It is is is
Main point
Is deemed to be
I would have died
If I go to prison because of covid-19
And is a hoax
But
Is going to kill Rodger if he goes to prison
Seems hard to balance those ideas but they keep trying
You guilty f*****
Possible death you believe they're all coming
Situation
I also knows what they'll pull on your brother
Be worried about
Beat you to death
That would have been the angle the whole time
Course the beating you to death or something
Hulk Hogan thing is not going to work with
The narrative
Triangular prism
Yeah okay way to try to make this work shirt
Rodger
What kind of angle B Rodger needs
Because
The kind of things people who don't like him would still kind of have to begrudgingly be like
Write a non-violent criminal you're not really a threat to anybody you probably should be
If there is a real danger to your help that's a really difficult argument
If even if you don't like him
That's why he was in
Employment
Stupid
Alex did join in with
I would argue though that he
He had to employ
Cuz he was cuz you don't do any
Stone was also though talking to
To the judge
So the judge
Can listen to the covid argument
Listen to Rodger saying like
Hey they might
Kill me because I
Yeah no no
Roger's actions attires
And Alex
The same time I just
First to make notes
You know the BBC was reporting the Rodger had these accounts and Facebook said they did
You should notice that I did not say
Rodger allegedly
Because I don't want to get sued
If you're a journalist
Stay with the Wall Street Journal
Perfect example
And you
As a fact
Allegedly or may have
I'm coming after you too
Rodger you are absolutely right
Call Rodger Stone
They're coming after everybody
We're going to punish all these be
We're going to go after millions of people
Authoritarian
Real McCoys easily
Rodger you still there
Well-intended
America's vodka sauce okay
Is internet
He was on the phone
Get the phone to work
Rodger threatening to sue people
It was a pretty sure that interview and cutting out
Yeah you allegedly had
Suboxone
Because I don't want
Yeah I like that you know it's kind of like the old Rodger
Threatening people
Call the business till Thursday
So you still you shouldn't
Yeah you coming to get the sense there like he has a
He's got the info
Is it going on in 4th and Breton
Need to sue people who report
His box
The tone of his previous interviews that we've covered
I have been very much
Please God please give me
Really over playing the religiousness and my new family
As soon as I decided to love God and everything turned around
Some of that he does not say is not discussed
Praying to Trump
This time
Now
If we know one thing
From our time doing
In the show
Alex is
Totally fine
One tech.
He is
He's not mad at the truth
He's not my
He's the kind of guy who's like
He's the guy you want
Trouble cuz he keeps his head about it
Music behind the wheel when you get some ice
Keep calm and knows that knows how to schedule a crisis-management
Yep the most amateur thing on talk radio
Call radio station
Say a little something and then not be there
Roger's cell phone
Ongoing technical difficulties are
Fun
They are fine and I refuse to wallow in the
Julian
Over
Feel here that the criminals everywhere
Doctors
All the old people in the building
Call Everett
Where is the UN
Riddle to do that
Rick Rude
Little
Amateur pet peeves
We're done we're done
John Donne
Holy
That was a roller coaster
My favorite part
For sure though is that it begins
Freak out
With him talking about how it's amateurish
On radio shows when you hear someone say hello hello
Screaming about how this keeps happening on his show
That's the most temperature is
Not being able to roll with the f****** punch constantly
Freaking out whenever you have like a tech difficulties that your million-dollar Studio
Yeah that's amateurish in the middle of f****** nowhere
Are where all the sudden the microphone cuts out and I just got to toss it aside and continue in the goddamn I don't stop
Scream at the bartender
Unable
Stand up
Shouldn't be expected to be able to handle.
Super Idaho 20-something years on a professional level
Probably should be able to
Before the lights go out
That's a challenge but you should be able to handle
White goes off
I'll be completely f***** up by it
Military
You're doing a month of shows
At a certain place
And the Mike
Keeps going out
Again and again we can't handle it
To talk to the manager or
The guy behind the tech booth and figure out what's going on with the mic going out
Possible to fix
I would argue your bad performer
You're not
Karen
The other word I would use
Amateur
Little kids freak out
Give me chills a little bit
Redpoint
Just of the
Like it real intense anger
There's a there's a level of repertoire
Stops being performative and starts being a representation of psychosis
Yeah but you're like
Get you but you do it 30 more time than you
You need maybe or it's filling time
Might have realized how
I got another 20 seconds to break I could just say
Done done done over and over again
We'll get there we'll get to the brain
RimTyme continue the show does not matter
Regions Bank in on the temp here and
Ready for
The 2020 election
Basically
The two possibilities one Trump wins or Trump win
Lab but it looks like 5
Because there's a
Rotation
Truck Yeah
We're in the middle of what will be
Contested
Election
Ariane top
Protect this country
Civil War
Everyone is being approached
Will you support
Against President Trump
I hope
So you're most part there's a coup
Would be learned about already on Alex's show because
Joe Biden have to go
Talk s*** on the Bailey show unveiled
Hey I think Trump's insane if you might try and stay in power
Obviously
Play hymns
That's cool
So in order to defend his argument Alex has a couple of articles
That he's using
As I could
The big tent poles here
But you try
Relations America
Democratic unraveling
The Armed Forces will be needed to remove Trump
Then you can test the election anyway
He will be removed by the US Military
Naturally Alex has not read this article in the Foreign Affairs and honestly probably used
It's a pretty Savage laying out of the various ways that are country
Structure and government has been usurped by Trump in the right-wing drive for power
It's honestly pretty fair hand
Essential pieces of this article is that erosion of norms in the structure of our society is a gradual process
But they clap
Come very fast
It's very well-articulated In this passage
Quote as James Robinson and I argue in our recent book The Narrow corridor
Democratic institutions restrained elected leaders by enabling a delicate balance of oversight by different branches of government
A legislature and the Judiciary
And political action by Regular People
Weather in the form of voting and elections are exerting pressure via protest
But Democratic institutions rest on Norms
Compromise cooperation respect for true
And are bolstered by an active self-confidence citizen
When Democratic Values come under attack in the pricing
Civil Society or country lies
The institutional safeguards lose their power
Under such conditions
The transgressions of those in power go on punished
IStore become normalized
The gradual erosion of checks and balances dusk
To Sunoco
That's a pretty fair assessment to
You know
Article argues that Trump has been playing authoritarian
Play book since he began his present
Special concerns about Russian interference in the u.s. election
Refusing to disclose
The tax returns open
Presume
Metservice family's financial interest
Vilifying Hispanic and Muslim Americans
Propagating conspiracy theories
And relentlessly lying to
The president has left democratic
These actions not only weaken the institutions that are supposed
Restrained president-elect
Creating a constituency that unconditionally supports Trump
I don't fear that the Democrats
Play Power
The author Daron acemoglu is a professor of economics
MIT
It discusses how nothing is certain
He's going to be
If it does happen
Going to be a long painful process
That's probably impossible if Trump is re-elected
He's consistent pattern of behaving as a singular
Dictators
The Makar system function would continue
And smuggling is of the opinion
That's it
It's really nothing that could stop the administration
And everything
From collapsing
Even if Democratic candidate Joe Biden wins the upcoming election
Front damaged that it will be powerless to fix
It wasn't addresses the Deep structural problems that propelled trumpets office
In the first place
Such a nice recognition
Attracted
It's not a easy fix even if
Local has nothing to do with it
Contested election or the military being used to remove Trump
I want to see those things as a clear indication that he didn't read this article or he has no interest in discussing what it actually says
The line Alex is taking out of context ghost or paragraph
Discussing how Trump is not at this point
Completely free from all institutional
Constraint
There's some judges were pushing back on his clearly illegal executive orders
The Armed Forces may be able to restrain him as well as evidenced by the force will rebuke you received from Former Defense
Secretary James Mattis
After threatening to deploy the US Military
The National Guard again
Protesters
But it would be a sad day if Americans had to
Depend on the military to save their democracy
And the trend is toward fewer not more checks
On the president's power
If the last remaining restraints giveaway the fall towards autocracy will be
That's a sentence
Military resist
Distance to Trump using the Army again
Protesters
Which ends
The point where none of our ends
Students of any ability to contain the unchecked power
Aspiring dictator
You have to speculate about what would happen
That's not saying the same thing Alex's claiming today
Anyway I went to the liar and this is a good but depressing Artica
Particularly in the context of drop just commuting Rodger Stone
You almost certainly carried out to advance the interests of trumpets
Yeah I really am I'm really disappointed
It seems like he made a grave miscalculation
In not
Cozying up to the millet
You know like from day one but Ryan
Yeah but he's just been doing a really shity job so it's almost like his personality
From really taking advantage
Of what a demagogue
Do in Houston
Like this would be
This would be a dictatorship
You know like three years ago if you would done it right
It's not hard
It will look at the look at the Council of Foreign Relations list of things that Trump is doing to a road the door
That all happened before he got elect
What's the list
That he didn't do during the
The campaign
You're talking about from this article
Demonizing his phone
Openly pursue policies that service financial interest
Position to do that that openly pursues his financial
UPS broke the law on day one as election you can't use the presidency
Yourself when you don't have the Press
The illusion of the presidency
That's not the power running for president to sell books
Which is also an issue we should
Corruption of the office subscription
The process
I guess
Look let's not get too deep into the weeds
Agreed politely
When will leave it there for now cuz I was another article
But how does it kind of went all that s***
Is anyone out of the Stanford
Anyone
Will not leave will be arrested
Numbers
We try
To help face prison
Denise Alford Advocate not Stanford
Article from the washer
This article is really just a legal analysis about how unlikely it is the Trump refuse to step down if he loses
November
The reason for that is because in order for him to pull that off he would need to persuade the in
Entire executive branch to do so as well
When doing so puts on a very serious legal Jeopardy
40 pieces well summed up by the closing
Paragraph
Quote nothing can with total certainty I'm sure a normal transition of power from as abnormal present
Has Donald Trump
It's vital to recognize that if Trump tries to retain power illegitimate
He'll need help from his cabinet
Members of the cabinet to go on the record Legendary Ultimate urine
Student of the laws of the United States
It would be
A lot of people
Terrified legal gods
Oh no not legal consequences there's no way to get around legal I understand
A gigantic
Which
That mean it's not inconceivable but it's not as big like
The issue here is that whether or not Trump would be able to successfully do
Even gesturing towards it is a problem
Yes
And even if he doesn't have an executive branch
Fulfill the duties that you need to run a government care even if he still said I'm
Illegitimate president
Causes just as big
Anyway this is something
The point of this article because Alex is supposed to love America
Constitution
Yep
It's not like his article is even taking Trump losing as a certain
Do you like it explicitly says quote
Legitimately wins an election
So be at the end of America
So
Bombshell proof
Obaasan Arrow got infected so it's bombshell proof that the
No bombshell proof that it is not an epidemic
And that's a real cool now or something
Salute Smoking Gun on top of Smoking Gun on top of
Cookie jar on top of
Absolutely ridiculous
The covid-19 is a giant fraud every level
Design for planetary takeover
Cover
Depopulation
On the cdc's on website
They say that covid-19
Is not
And that actually
Nose-diving death
And that's why every headline you see says
America's
America stock
America
On
Believable
This is just a national file
National file articles
The CDC reports from March
Covid-19 deaths at a sudden Spike and then immediately proceeded to drop
And if the dropped
Continues
The viral disease will no longer be considered an epidemic
International stand
That's great well then I'm glad to know that may was a good month for us and I'm sure things will continue
Even if you just take that is true that now it's a still misreporting this
A story using the CDC says that this is correct
Possible threshold
Future which is bad word
Lincoln National website data for the weekend on July
On the very top of the page
Key update section they say
The percentage of specimens testing positive for SARS code to the viruses virus that causes covid-19
Decreased slightly from last week
This past weekend
Included a holiday
Testing and Reporting
Mortality attributed to covid-19 decrease compared to last week and is currently out of epidemic threshold
But will likely increase as additional death certificates
You're just making
Stuff up by misrepresenting things that are on the CDC update page 1
For context it's all met
We're just called
Lion
There are other things are on this page to that should worry people
I mean
There is a there's a slight total decrease of national numbers for percentages of tests coming back positive
But there's a couple of regions in the country that are really pushing those numbers up
The South Central Region which covers Arkansas Louisiana New Mexico Oklahoma and Texas were showing positive test
16.8%
Also the southeastern region covering Kentucky Tennessee Mississippi Georgia
North and South Carolina and
Florida was reflect
.1
Percent positive rate
These dudes cherry-picking whatever soda out of context line they can find out make their arguments
But the totality of the information
I'm a very Pages they linked to as sources refute the things
They're saying
So I don't know
I don't know
Ime
I don't know what
You can't
You can't do it
I mean
I get
Constitutions already out the window
We lost we lost battle
And I have a little
Is the concert
To do some was still an effective would be applied to
And it doesn't seem to be doing
So this this s*** is
Too dangerous
Next clip
To talking about the Big Sur
Supreme Court
Decision of the last week that gave Oklahoma
I-20
To say about this
Before he gets
Teasing what's coming up I have really excited I've never pays off
Bohemian Grove
What Supreme Court
Oklahoma
But I can defend a
Convicted child rapist
I kidding
But no joke
I have no idea what this Bohemian Grove knows is
Distracted by whatever you going to go on with it and get back to it but no
Buck yes
You're welcome
What's up with Malik
Stuff about the Oklahoma story is not true
Last week the Supreme Court ruled 5-4 that about half of Oklahoma is taken
Creekland
And somewhat sovereign
For the state of Oklahoma
It's really complicated but essentially what will end up happening is if there's Major Crimes
Committed by a native person inside the area considered Creek territory
They cannot be Tried by the state of Oklahoma
It has to be handled by the federal
Smaller crimes like misdemeanors or civil matters those involving
Will be handled by tribal courts
According to NPR Arizona New Mexico
This is not an attempt to
Protect someone who sexually assaulted a child but it's easy to create that Miss
Information of a case that led to the Supreme Court ruling
Decent question was mcgirt versus Oklahoma
Jimcy mcgirt what I was a member of the Seminole Nation
Sex crimes against the child on
Hungry clam
The appealing of the case was never about getting him acquitted
The argument was that the state of Oklahoma had no jurisdiction
Try the case
I need me to be dried
Federal court
Alex love sovereignty so you think you'd be in favor of it
For others
He's trying to turn the story about it
A treaty between the United States government of the creek people being honored into a story about protecting pedophiles
You really getting to be a one-trick pony
Half of Oklahoma in order to make sure that the Oklahoma State can enforce doesn't get to that point
He's just trying to pretend that it's a thing where they're like they're trying to get this guy off the hook by
Tribal court is at 11 Mall
Federal court
Almost certainly convicted
It's really
Just more about honoring this treaty
So the American government
Of the Infowars
Offering
For today in the news
Monkey see monkey do
That's search engine
Monkeys now.
In India
In Africa
Southeast Asia
Monkeys have all Mountain scene
Picking up mascot of trash piles
Demond
Arbella primate
Different types of monkeys are doing this but are you
Think of humans is more advanced as successful
What are you doing
I'm putting the mask on
I think it's entirely possible that it's a coincidence
That doesn't mean anything that a couple people
Go to liquidity of crab
Pizza Ranch
So smart
I was trying to get to the bottom of Nevada
It's just a video from India wear a monkey find the scarf on the street and puts it over his head
We're doing the gesture not unlike what you see people doing they threw a scarf over their shoulder
The monkey is very good
The scarf over his face and kind of looks like a man
It's a really cute video If
Did you know
Did you know that there is a mainstream movie where a monkey
You know call the lab.
So
This kind of does illustrated
Disturbing trend of monkey
Leather mimicking our Behavior
We all wear masks
I meant to be like us
Monkeys are doing it too cuz they know where
The only problem with his theory is that the video has been reposted for at least a year
Posted by susanti Ananda of the Indian Forest Service
But it's not a new video
Also I'm really interested in the theory that outside by monkeys copying our Behavior
That's something I don't have anywhere near the amount of patients it would take to unpack
Haha
Is basically just him
Seeing some kind of piece of viral content and then making up
Story about it
Also I think the monkeys would probably
Copy other behaviors
They had a fundamental understanding
Stock market
Lightstar successfulness
I'm going to go with this and let me see if you can get the ref
Forthright
Damn you
Responsible
Seems likely
Take responsibility for decisions
Going to present without Kombat though I think
This could look real bad in hindsight
As I told you first
The White House
Troy
Troy game
Vaccines
Impressions
Content getting
The Trump is
Medical experts
The middle of a pandemic
End up looking real bad is a present
Okay or even worse in the future
So what you're saying is
Alex is claiming to directly influence the removal of medical experts in the mid
The pandemic
I don't think that I think that would be more of an admission of guilt
Really look pretty bad
Now I would start fantasizing about Trump needs to have fauci
Bill Gates murder
Ex-president
Henna politically present as hard as you want them people back
Southeast goes away Along trip
Bill Gates
Vacation together supposed to ever see him again.
Black women
Chrysler Dodge
Really
Society paid in full
Let's continue
Man Alex complains all the time about disappearing people at
Disappeared
I guess if he's kind of wanting his enemies to go on a long
Camping trip because Trump is the real deal the real deal
I mean it's just silly
This morning
On the 10th
Good morning
Alex
Was driving around or something
I saw some joggers
I don't know if yells at them but he does what he does write a weird story about them
When I was in
Scripture area
What's
She looks like
Some joggers walkers
Call my phone
Make a call
The whole sidewalk and everything
Get off the phone and I'm watching them
Black Chinese
Iron Man what
And they start walking down
At me angry
I didn't videotape but I don't want to antagonize
Osher
You hate antagonizing people
With the window shop
Wasn't enough that I got in at the windows up
They were social distancing
Probably
We're working for a tech company probably Chinese citizens
Because there's our phone track them
The follow the AI to prepare themselves
Republic
Watch the next level of conformity
A hundred yards away
And waiting
For me
Quiet
Barry
It's interesting how many assumptions he makes in that story that are come
Completely unfounded
But he decides that they must be Chinese citizens out here working for a tech company or used to being monitored
Myself
I think it's entirely possible that they knew it was Alex
Inversion of it
There's a hundred explanations that have nothing to do with math
Their social didn't know it all
Or if they are cute
Minorities
Did not go well
Just kept thinking during that story like the next thing that Alex
Say to some
Other human being is
Why do these walls have so many pads on
Like that's what you should say after that story
Insane
Retelling of things
Let's look at the concrete things that happened in the story
Alex was in his truck
Houston a couple people
Yes those are the only things that are concrete
Just what happened Alex a famous person
Is in a truck
Track of court
Pick out of a crowd don't recall the Chinese government having anything to do with that
But I could be wrong
This is one of those things
Gaston
Caesars
Concrete facts of the story are thin
Most of the meat is just things that he's making.
You're not wrong
Still really really boring
Stand-up did not
Not go well true
So
Alex
Has learned that there's this guy named named kid
Texas emergency
Division
Chief
I need an interview that was discussing
How
Instances where
We might want to be suggesting people wear masks
At home
They're going to force you to wear a mask
And who plays this
The reason I kept this in
Is that you can tell
Alex Azar
T-jack about interrupting
Is
Texas chief
Nim Kidd
You always beating him kid
Behind
Governor wearing his mask
He says do not
Your house Autumn ask but also
Jr house
Wear a mask
Because you're such a bad person
You're so evil you're so dangerous
Today is we need to do that when we're in our homes also
As you know I'm a lifelong San Antonio on grew up there
Worked there for many years
And I know how many multi-generational families that we have
And while we believe the community is doing a great job
The rules
Outside of the home
We really need to be thinking about doing the same thing when were inside the home
All of us
Star
Take bullet
Disease none of us are immune from
In the fact that we need to get across
In order to protect
Darcelle's Juanita
Protect our families and our love
We really need to be thinking about
The care that we provide
Inside the home right now
To make sure that we're not spreading this disease inside the home and then making it come outside
So let me get this straight with your fact
Actively saying is that
People should be wearing masks
Inside their own homes now
Ryan I'm saying if you can
Can't socially distant and can't socially isolator if you've been out in
Exposing yourself
And you haven't
Decontaminated yourself good enough when you get home
If you have someone that has
Underlying medical conditions that I can Sweeten
Play with
Riza Bello
Texas emergency management system
Damn kid
Alex had to interrupt because you realize that it was making too much
Any longer is going to be
Completely clear what he was.
Here's a version that Alex wants his audience
Believe is what kid
You Texans need to wear masks when you leave the house at now
The further they clip later became more clear that you know what he was saying
Kid was not saying anything about mandating people to wear masks
Consider
It may have people in the house already higher risk Coronavirus
If you're in such a household and you're not able to
Protect yourself
Consider to wear mask inside to save your grandmother's lights
This is a big slip up on Alex's bar that could have easily been any preparation for his show
If you even gave me single s*** about the things
Turn it off so it doesn't contradict
Your narrative about it
So are you saying that we need
Yeah I mean
But you know it's great that Alex is able to get around that and try and
Is bias
Terrible news out of my you don't want this guy off saying
We about to make sense
Me too
This entire episode
The comeback
I'll get into the
Two-player games
Will play the director of the UN emergency response operation
His counterpart that wrote this up
He's an emergency
He gets his orders down to the CDC
We're coming
Your children your parents we're coming into your house
He has even got the memo yet
Nonsense 37 nightclub
She already but
I think you're before getting a
Global emergency response
Disasters and medical crises
He is drooling
Umwa Showdown to the NIH CDC
Who
This man takes his orders from
The Texas division of Emergency Management
Who says
Leave your house without a mask and you'd wear one in your house
And then Australia in Spain
Houses
Taking
The families away
Breaking them up
And at the moment
The most parts
The world
Transmission
Actually happen
Any country
It's happening
In the house
In some senses transmission
Has been taken off the streets
And pushed back
Family units
No we need to go
A look inside
And removed
And isolate them
Something the fight
So first things first vun Emergency Management people are not in charge of the Texas division
Emergency room
There's a lot of local jurisdiction
Planning structure
Ultimately it all goes back to the governor
I was able to find the 2020 Texas emergency management structure document which discusses the Texas Emergency Management
Council
Business quotes
Composed of state agencies and nongovernmental organizations appointed by the governor
The council was established to advise and assist the governor and all matters related to disaster mitigation preparedness
Response and Recovery
This is no Formal Connection to the body the doctor Michael Ryan is the executive director of which is
Is the the World Health Organization
Health emergencies program
Probably sounds kind of scary
But I want to take it entirely out of context
This is from a media briefing on the virus from March 30th
Steps that dr. Ryan describes are not relevant to our situation
At all
In the full context of his comments were discussing their monitoring methodology that could be put in place of cases went down to
Very low numbers
If you want me over a few cases identified a day
A state or country can have the ability to trace a contract contact
And if someone gets sick provide them with a safe place
Gene away from home
And keep spreading the disease
If you listen to the four responses question even says that it isn't something you can really do effectively when he has thousands of cases of
Has been currently tracking over 50,000
To say that most of the country is not in the position where anything dr. Ryan was saying
Back in March
Which is relevant
Dr. Ryan was talking about what a country could do once it is pushed
Transmission off the streets
And into the house
The tragedy of Alex
Nope
So I don't know I'm so contact clip of this World Health Organization guy
Or you can wreck
Acknowledge that it has nothing
Things to do with
Seems like he's dealing with
Seriously
Kind of fallacies
Or it's just like hey I've been denying this
For so long
Even though the evidence
This is now completely
Otherwise I'm going to look
Even though I am a moron
I want to look
Navigate me to
I would do with you
So Alex has big top story which is the coup against Trump
Supposed to be coming
And so
Coming in here
Oh my God
What I'm going to do this right now
I'm going to mention this
I'm going to get this coming out of the gates at 6 after nobody in studio with me
We'll talk about this at first
I've got a stack of news articles have a coup against the present
Physically with the US Military
Danny's house
As we speak
In order to
Hammer home the concept
Openstax
Election will be
Detective
Writers article
So
Now Bella Taylor just so much of this
Left coming up
I want to find this operation
Products the same time
Now's the time to do it
I can't possibly imagine doing such a shity job and then still insisting for money
Happening
Top stories
Things to a Holt
Allison Tire thing with gold
Zacks attack
Drunk would probably make more sense if Trump hadn't made former Goldman Sachs
Executive Steve mnuchin the Secretary of the Treasury
His campaign had been run by former Goldman Sachs
Employee Steve original chief financial advisor wasn't former Goldman Sachs CEO oh Gary Cohn
What's goes on and on related information
There's no conflict
Between Trump and Goldman Sachs
Text spy without my water pretend
This article that Alex can't remember anything about has to do with Goldman Sachs advising investors to hedge their positions through the end of the
Since they predict Market volatility around the election
They're not predicting a contested election the same way I was just trying to use the term we're both candidates say that they're the rightful winner
Google delay the announcement of the winner
They cite increases in mail-in ballots
The time it takes for
Count those and virus possibly voting schedule
As reasons to be a cautious investor
There were a bunch of up
Sundown zv5 week between the 2000 election and the
Supreme Court naming Bush the winner
This is more or less just a financial business
Advising investors that some similar s*** is
Probable this year
This is just short of
Proof of a coup
But I guess if that's our Alex wants to play things
That's that's
I mean
If there was a cool
Goldman Sachs is on Trump
Come on man
So Alex brings in Savannah Hernandez
They've been put out since that out there or not burning
Whenever I open the homeless person
Situation all over
Lambe's Royal salute
It said you just get him by
Kind of
I think they may do though
They may have
Television media come on
The night of the election and say obeid one-by-one even though Trump did win
Censorship
Just like they stop
I'm talking about hydroxychloroquine
Orthopnea
Doctors from talking about
And then so they'll come in and they'll say all by one-by-one and then trouble saying no
Find anyone who will be the president versus Media
Show me the playing field
Question is
One option is attack
Next time to mount up in
We'll make our own autonomous Zone
That's what we can attack we can do that too is patients we can sit back and wait
Auntie okay let's see what happens in the election night let's hope for a good thing maybe
Beastly
Go to the hills Mount up get emergency water get by it you know a mountain
Get a bunch of guns and ammo and I'm doing both
But just you three
Taco thing we have to wonder now is
For example if we want to attack or if we want to wait no
Top measure
Choose before we have the choice to take
I mean obviously the answer was when bolsonaro tested positive for covid-19 you giant bunch
Well
Love any of this b******* they've already hit all the
Well I know that
Alex's broadcast Style
Simultaneously
Periodically
So it's not like
The world has gotten more and more
I'm saying over the past
6 months
You know it.
I feel like there's more Danger
Game
I am not comfortable with
The extent to which these conversations
Super normalize
Why you with me
People are so
F****** stupid not outsmart
Because they're they're murderers
It's not about
It's not about a fear of like Owen doing
The unknown unknown person who listens
Stuart to Alex
Yes
One thing I think is really interesting is it appears that
Over Trump
Bulshit
Interesting to me
He's coming from a position of like
Yeah look
He's not going to do it
He's not going to do the things we want
And Alex doesn't improve
Trump wants to let them steal the election from Trump okay
Decision
We're not going to let them take our country
So
Contact tracers are coming to our house
By the way they're going to be political there the youth Brigade Obama wanted
Hey we want to be on the field we want to be on the front lines we are the tip of the spear Trump has let them truckers let them lie about us too
Lucinda submission we're still fighting so hey
You know at the end of the day
Are we fighting for Trump or are we find
For America on fighting for marriage
So wow not on the same page
Where is starting to lean more towards the Fuentes
Wing of the murder everybody party
Trump's not going to do it
Yeah we'll see where that goes
See how long you can rationalize working for the company she works for
Comes in and she's got some
Some dumb s***
To say about how like
All these ideas not going to leave office because of Hillary
David laying the groundwork for this got into Office Clinton is already come out so many times
Well what if
Losses in 2020 he's not going to leave the White House so she's an already laying the groundwork
It's all good well to talk about people like Hillary raising concerns about Trump not leaving office
If you don't point out the Trump has a long history of
Joking
He's not going to leave office
Yeah cancel National
Scream 4 more years for more years I only say make it 12 years ago
Or there was a tweet from June 2019
Quote
A pool should be done on which is the more dishonest and deceitful newspaper these failing New York Times
Amazon lobbyists Washington Post
Disgrace to our country
Good news is at the end of six years after America's been great
Parentheses
Do you think the people would demand that I stay longer
Forever gone
Or there was a closed-door speech that he gave in front of Republican donors at Mar-A-Lago and March
2018 discussed how
President of China just gave himself lifetime
Quote
He's now president for Life president-for-life know he's great
He was able to do that I think it's great
Maybe we'll have to get the shots
Athlete article as a listing of at least
27 *
Does Trump has made comments about how he should get more than two terms
Since he's taken office
There's not a normal thing for a human to do
There's a couple of reasons why
Someone would act like this and I'll get to that in a second
I think it's important to point out that there is a massive difference
Between the behavior of someone like Hillary
And someone like Trump
Circumstance
Hillary is not a person who's able to make any real
Decision in this situation
She's a commentator who's expressed concern that a person will make a very
Conversely Trump is the decision maker
Legitimately he's the only person who can decide whether or not to throw this country into an even deeper existential crisis when the election
Results come in
He alone is the either able to accept or reject
A win or loss
And the ramifications of that choice are almost
Impossible to overstate
When Hillary discusses he's concerned she's well within her right to do so and you're welcome to have your opinion about her opinion
When Trump
Uncle jokes
Insisting on staying in office after two terms
He's joking about something that is in his power
Whether you believe he'd be able to pull it off or not
You have the ability to cause the damage that a president not accepting the results of an election would cause
And what he's doing is not joking
There are only two possible explanations I can really come up with for why Trump would soak
Joke about that
The first is to piss off his political opposition
In that case we have a president who such a dick that he'll create the impression that he wants to overturn base against
Douching
That alone is disqualify a person to be a leader let alone someone worth taking serious
The other possibility is the Trump thinks he should be present
4life
I don't think you can really but what about Hillary this I don't think that's Hillary
Good good music
Storming the capitol
About it in that last
Thousand armed people
To storm the capitol
I think about this I think about you know
Is it time for Alex Jones Infowars to declare war on the Deep State and literally
If we don't have a rash
By October 31st
A thousand armed men
To meet us at the Texas Capitol
And we'll set up our own autonomous Zone
And we'll go wherever we need to go and drag out whoever we need to drag out by the Scruff of their neck
Start to get some rest and get some action
I don't want to do that I know you don't want to do that that's why we
Take political action that's why we come on are everyday
But it's reaching a point where yeah there is an active going on
Listen
I don't want to do the thing that for the past six months I've been screaming how great it would be to do
You know if they don't do it they're going to have to make me do the thing that again I explicitly
Do not absolutely want to do and have been saying that I know how I said Halloween because the only night we have a chance
We can all be dressed up as we know when the planets align
Has the power to break into
I like it
Dear
I don't think it's a good plan.
I'm also
Is it time for us to declare war on the Deep State how many f****** times has Alex yelled about that
State was poisoning Trump
F****** Coke
Like three years.
So we know that
Later this evening
Rodger Clemens
Clements twins
Whatever
Alex Roberto Clemente the show that day Alex
Open slip
Put it back on screen
Developing Trump pardon Stone
Waking up
President
Hearthstone
First of all Alex's wrong Rodger Clemens
Clemency just reduces the penalty for a conviction but the crime is still on a person's records or Rodgers still a convicted
Itsowen
If Trump legitimately thought that Rodger was wrongly convicted he would have pardoned
But he didn't because that would be
Probably be too messy
On that
I think
Maybe I don't know clemency is a perfect male Road for corruption head
Cuz then Rodger doesn't have to go to prison
And you don't have to open up the box
What could happen if you park
Box was opened
Entire prosecution
Swept under the rug by I think that was that was more I wasn't good Stone wouldn't have been the one
Accepting that stealing a complete election
Probably with boxes
I think I think
The difference between those things of this such a bore of a discrete Act
You know like
Yeah
This stuff
Smaller and all that
Does lions announce there's a lot of complexity to it were simple
Yeah that's fair
I think you could make a really
Easier to digest argument about pardoning Rodger
For trying to intimidate a witness
That case
It had to do with him trying to
Yeah circumvent the law in order to help the Trump campaign
I think it's a little easier
Yeah with corruption
I don't disagree with you at on a human level
Favorite part of this
Is
How much of a chump Mueller is
Like this entire like him
Shawn Whitby
Easiest conviction
He had and that way
Was ripped away from
He is
Failed in every possible way is hilarious
Standing up for him or anything like that
Interrupt
You're right
Don't know but that's what it's even funnier
Cuz Trump made him look like
Jump again
You should really be embarrassed
Alex the Trump was going to Pardon Rodger for the last week
Please excuse for engaging in the
Certain embarrassing radio play about a Rodgers going to die in jail
Cuz he's such a hero
If the whole point was to
Please case to Trump for the pardon you already knew was coming
Kind of makes the whole thing seem like an actor
Almost like if you were just building up to the payoff that you knew was coming
The drama of a pardon
Not come
Just the juice the rating
Trying to will they work today, intention in order to
How many people are going to TuneIn
Start going on really frequently in the past
Couple of weeks
Is tonight the night that stone announces he's been pardoned
Well
I think you know you know
You starts
Talking some more about
Is that amazing
Sure
Imagine
Of course
Is a slightly different
I actually think is worse
It's weird because
You can say there's enemies
The freedom but
To me the correct psychological
Approach because
Guarantee them is my
I don't see them
Freedom I think if you ask them they want to be free to just anybody
Become his obstacles
A freedom
Nicole's of freedom
And as soon as Americans
You're not even
Art Willingham
Fight for their freedom
Like you said
You're now an obstacle
You're going to get run over
Use the cars running people over in the streets as a
Physical example
Left-wing a
Activist in control of all the justice
10000 people can be surrounding your vehicle threatening to kill you smashing the windows and everything and if you
If you plow through it you are the bad guy
Now all over the place
Now they're being charged everywhere
That's a very interesting way for Owen to dehumanize is opposition and take
Hey what their positions are
Enemies
Political goals are point
They're merely Ops
Two sides that exist in this narrative or Alex and his
Who are supposed
Who are the bad guys
Agree with Alex like let's say someone who might demonstrate for Reproductive Rights
Protests against Real position
Conviction
Zombies have been brainwashed by the globalist
And they're not the enemy
They're just obstacles
To be run over
All they are is
In the way
Yep
Beautiful Warrior
Are the only people who act
Actually are on a path that involves making
Choices are having agency
Which naturally leads to some pretty sickening
In conclusion
This is the same mentality
Expresses all the time when you talked about how killing the globalist is like killing a bug
You don't want to do it
Do you have to
That kind of rhetoric and the sort of thing that Owen is expressing here Army and Zara
Tacit permission to enact violence on your political enemies by reducing them
To being
Human Lobster
Recently USA Today reported
May 27th event at least 66 instances of protesters being hit by car
Undoubted
Not all of these were cold-blooded attempted murders but at least some of them
That we were
Seven of the incidents were police hitting protesters
In just over a month
At least two of these people have been killed
Countless others have been hurt and traumatized baby The Vamps
This is not something that deserves to be mocked
Even if you disagree with the politics
People were being targeted by the
These attacks
I wholeheartedly despise Trump and his dumb rally
But if there have been 66 instances of trump supporters being hit by cars at his rally since May 27th
I would absolutely show some reverence to the subject with the opposition
Trump the messaging of that movement
Running civilians over with cars with an appropriate way to voice their political opposition
And I can sit here and play the game where they pretend that these people are all just looters and rioters
Threatening the people in the car who hit them in self-defense they know that's
Spell check
On some level these dude know they're what they're doing
Trying to help normalize
The enacting of lethal violence against their political rival
And that's why I'll talk about helicopter rides
That's why you talked about how his listeners could be instruments of God's Avenger
There's a concerted effort of dehumanization of political enemies and violence on the
Michelle
The two-level a Time consistently uncomfortable
Yeah that was
If shorter and I are drunk in a bar
He says that that's when you take ask
You know it's just like
Outlook
No no
No
I'm out I'm out however I'll leave you leave I just
This is
This is f*****
This is Tupac
Let's just to f*** that the message
Yikes
So
Video to release all the dirt they actually have on Hillary and like all this evidence
But you chopped up babies and stuff
Cool
Galax
I think you might have.
Really think that the New York cops
And a New York FBI that are good people but are actually going through the process
It's time to just released it is time to release
Golden Rule
Whether America can handle it or not
There's only one way to find out what
There is a real change in his Dynamic bro-down without
Yeah yeah
It sounded look who knows could be a coffee mug
Possibly drunk
At this point
And that's only furthered
My suspicions are only furthered by the fact that he does a
Jeff Foxworthy
No
Democrat
So
Anyway
You guys are gray
Yeah have you heard of this have you heard of this you might be a redneck
Have you heard of this overdone joke structure that has permeated all of
Not just America
I really think Alex listens to our show to cuz we did that you might be
We think he's probably less now that's
Maybe maybe not
So Alex 7277 memorandum 727
That was about the Cold War to avoid nuclear war that Alex believes
About actually taking
Well
7 + 2 is 9
9 + 14
That
So Alex Alex talks about there's a little bit
CIA website talked about that and pass
When
I can't even
Explain this ahead of time
But this was one of the more disturb
Urban Clips I've heard just because
The amount of stupid he has
To be if he actually think
This is
Out of control
For one, do you have
Well
We have a un Force around the world
A lot of people
The government
Quietly
CIA website
Bob on Wikipedia bisect
What are the CIA has got a flyer
From Mom
About FBI agent CIA operative
A newsletter called On Target
They were planning
Kill
And they continue to go along with the plan so
Government knows all about this
Ongoing battle
So we talked to John about memorandum 7277 at the Paso there's no need to rehash that
We've also talked about this page on CIA. Gov
And how it's not a CIA product
Copy of a newsletter called On Target which was produced by the Minutemen
This is intensely disturbing
Bring to your Alexei that the operatives for the CIA and FBI
Shooting on Target because that's not true
It was the publication of a Byron aggressively anti-communist militia group
The Minutemen were an organization out of my home state of Missouri founded by a real dick head named Robert Depew
Yeah he also was the person who wrote the ontarget newsletter
After gaining Financial stability vitamin
World War paranoia
He set up shop
In Norborne Missouri and started putting out his newsletter
I was hoping to find like-minded Patriots
He gained a small following who trained paramilitary tactics
You constantly exaggerated the size of his movement which was an outside
Sent the relevant Center probably deserve
When you're alone anti-communist Wako it's all good well for you to accuse everyone of being a communist and then say they deserve
Be killed or whatever
When you start to create an image of
Sway over a large ball
Are you going to attract law enforcement attention with that
Got a bag
Who was not a mastermind
And that's the FBI was able to infiltrate his group and found that he had a bunch
Considering various spots
Reward was coming against
Communist
Hi mr. Depew I am jaunty Minutemen I was wondering
Dammit
He was convicted in 1967 of National Firearms Act violations
Before being sent to jail
After two years he was captured and sent to prison for four years
According to the Columbia Daily Tribune
According to multiple reports
Because he believed they were traitors
In 1991 he was arrested on child pronography charges that stem from an alleged
Modeling shoot you had with
Teenage girl
But he was knocking
Just to let you know you would have been
68 at that point
Not a photographer
Another thing about Robert
Making
Can kill list
This was part of the reason that that issue of On Target is part of the documents included in the CIA
Because they had it on file as part of monitoring his activities
Because he was making him
Communist
News publishing their names and addresses
The subtitle of this newsletter is quote
Action will
Particularly disturbing to me is it
I think from the way Alex is talking it's the document was made by Good Guys in the government
The Patriots
That's really f***** up because that's not what this is at all
If Alex do anything about the subject
He talks about
Super reason to know that
Alex thinks
Did this
Basically dachshund kill list that was put out by an anti-communist militia leader in 1960
It's the good guys in the government telling all these people about who the globalist are
Well I mean the order 60
Was the good guys in the government getting rid of all those globalism
Jedi
My mind
Had a hard time processing that clip
Alex saying that that is
Because here's what I think
What I think that Alex doesn't understand why that document would be on the cia's if it wasn't created
Really I think that's a good point I think that's why Alex thinks it was DIA
Part of a dossier that they put together cuz they were observing him
Because he was a dangerous
Too stupid to believe
That's what I'm used to
Esthetician Plus in Spain
But that's beyond the other possibility that I run into when I think about this is that Alex knows
Did he was
A crazy militia leader
Or trying to sugarcoat in a little bit
Yeah cuz he's a secret good guy in the governor
He's not though
No no no
Although you know what
If either come around like 40-50 years later he's got Duck Dynasty on a meet you know you be invented the Dog Taylor whatever
The veterinary Arts
Cuz
Give a reality TV show
This gif
Messi
Alex has
From Europe Wars he's visiting Studio clip
Dan is there a war on Western Civilization
No
There's no Limon in Amber
Supposedly
Osibih talkin about
Is going to be a lot of migrants
When you're up and you're the anti-immigrant what you know
This
Very much
Into the ADI
It's weird
There is a prion around
Supposed to just be about
Be a lot of migrants coming into countries
It's what you expect from these artists
It's almost entirely
Complaining about the ATL
Alex
How to set this up
ATL rapper
Goodyear
ATL
Because they make money off that
Oh boy
That's interesting
Refuses
I don't know
Because they start talking
And I immediately start to understand
Why
This is happening in the middle of their conversation
About
Migrant cuz Nazis won World War II
What continuum
Macron
200 million
After 30 years of migration
This is
The
Connective tissue
The belief of the anti-Semitic
Conspiracy theory about the kalergi plan is about reach cabal of Jews
White man and white people
Non-white people from foreign countries
That is the immigration angle that's being discussed here and that's why there is so much anger
Remix
Because
Their view of immigration
Dometic
Conspiracy theory
To basically this kalergi
Plant stuff
They got two up
But they still don't want to lose you know the plan was still
Kalergi plan is still a good propaganda tool
Got updated
Call Jim
That was a bad performance
That's that's what's going on today that Rodger Clemens
So we come back
On Saturday
Alex was drunk
That night yeah I think
He kept drinking probably
Maybe that's why I wasn't able to do Friday night
So we get to Saturday and
Broadcast
Welcome thank you so much for joining us on this Saturday
July 11th
Emergency global
Afternoon transmission
We're going to miss out on all the radio
Affiliates
And the feeds band on video
I f****** love the idea of videos like always cut in on the we cut it on our regularly scheduled
Radio stations around the country that are by show I can just hit
National weather
System
Yeah right
Has that power
I mean hey here we are and I got to say
Saturday
Rodger just got clemency
Expect
You got a damn
You got a damn you got a dancing you got to tell me that this is
Complete vindication
And the only reason
Didn't get a full partner
It's so we can challenge the conviction in court
Right Rodger has another
Venues
I'm talking to more concretely
From a show standpoint
Expect
To be on this episode
Rodger Stone
That's interesting
Now here's one who Alex's first guest is
Coming up
In the shower + long
Transmission
Scheduled to have Mancow Muller
Black
Longtime friend of mine Seneca.
Watch weeping Rodger
Begin them support
Funny videos interviews the Rodger going to premiere
We're going to get him on the
Few minutes
So we got man-cat we don't even get a real Rogers so I don't know why all we know right now is that we got mansion
Things America owl is Brent
Timer
Gray gray
First guess
Okay you can have Mancow and Rodger both on
Can't growl
Ben Rogers longtime personal lawyer Tyler Nixon
Not been a lawyer on the case was able to speak about it
Because he's been outside
He's scheduled to be joining us via Skype
That's coming up
Rodger is not on
We have
You Alex
Got local news level accent the neighbor of the best friend of Rodger Stone
Over here.
Give us some information
Yeah that's why I was like
What the f***
The bare minimum
Is Rodger computer Hall
Yeah. You didn't get it you didn't get it
That's the end but there's bigger plan
Saturday broadcast
And then after he leaves us
Never
Add my phone's or my email
Blown off
Said walleye
Like this
Neighbor coming over my house this morning
Wayfair Wayfair Wayfair Wayfair Wayfair
I got home last night
Pepper working like 6
Rawley's text messages and I saw, 24th Wayfair Wayfair
Is it true that Wayfair this online shopping system
Was putting out ads for selling children's in armoires
Why is this emergency
Rodger got clemency
All right so so far
You have told me
There is no Rodger
And Alex is talking about Wayfair
I'm not surprised I want to be more surprised I'm disappointed of course
I'm very disappointed
You want me to just have Rodger cousin
I just love I can't begin to stress how much I love it whenever walks on Twitter or something or like
Oh I can't wait to see what Alex has to this because it might had all I see all I hear is
Just like you're looking forward to being disappointed I guess I have no idea
Going to happen exactly why you can't do an emergency episode you got to wait and see how it's going to be
Emergency mysteriously doesn't include best friend
Weird
Wow
But I was thinking you know Rogers not ready to come on the show till tomorrow on the Sunday broadcast
He's promised me one of the first interviews
Stopped late last night drinking with Mancow Muller other one of my
Longtime friends and I thought
Wait a minute
Mancow is still in Florida if he's up
I'll call him and get him on the show so
His wife are literally checking out with their children
Out of the hotel room right now
Check out
We got a quick
Popping from him
His argument is basically stone is too hungover to go on the
I mean that's most generous version
Say that Rodger doesn't
Answering his call
So it might just be he's too busy with people who
Matter
So Mancow comes in
Adorable
Cab
I am not a fan of Mancow
My old friend
Yes it should be I famously wasn't Gaston
Many years back I was doing stand-up it was an accident I don't know why I was there
Read my life
He did it on purpose
I think is a little man
Need to be off to work with
I will say it a radio setting
I generally don't care much for his appearances but this one is kind of funny a little bit because
Mancow knows the social dynamic
He just left hanging out with Rodger and Alex is doing the special broadcast about Rodger
The status imbalance
Gastronomic
Mancow is
Alex
Is nothing in the pathetic world that they all live in Opportunity you got to feel good
You f*** with our two little bit
I want to tell you first of all Alec
And you're not going to like this
Everybody I talk to
Your neck
Your next man they take this government does not like
You talkin
I'm not talking about Trump
I'm talking about the Deep State boy do they hate Alex Jones
And I
I'll tell you I'll be there with you
The Patriots got to set up this bother you what I'm saying Alex
Are you already know it
Oh I know it my friend I know it what are you hearing I don't wanna make this about me but what are you hearing
No you're I just
Anyone that's a patriot anyone that believes in God
Anyone that believes in the Constitutional silly things like this
They're going to get you
How's Aaron heard anything goes.
That's pretty solid f****** with Alex you know he's going to believe you when you say that s*** so you might as well draw it out
The Dead Silence from Alex is like
Do you know something I don't know
And Mancow
Edgerly knowing
Has to wear that silent eating I don't think
Cannot stop taking like every opportunity to be like I'm in the middle of this
Rodger
Last night Alex again everybody was calling in there
And we're talkin political Talking Heads and famous people to call you and not you Alex
For dinner I just I just wanted to hang out with the kids
I was monopolizing your time but
You know when somebody's a consummate
Ninety-nine percent of the time
On another consummate dick
Yeah it's fantastic Behavior become humorous when you don't care about the recipient.
So
Got some sources
Within the Old Government
Right
Boone County
Trump is beginning
Crack under pressure
Right
Alex cannot
Allowed
No but also is very high status
Finally got into him at my god there they just don't stop there
They're going after his little kids are going out today just God
Stop
And it finally got into him according to three really good sources
And one
Major major thorstad.
He's losing it man, that's what I started this special transmission with
Today is that there's a stack of news articles watched
Compose counsel formulations all I'm saying
We're preparing the military to remove him under
The 25th Amendment
And so they're putting those talking points out
Scratching
A lot of that is high
People around you are wrong
But regardless this is what Trump says so they get through me they're going to get you there not for me there after
Are you got to support the president
I think I'm going to get on a plane and go to DC and
Florida and bullhorn the president's compound again
About shining object
Usable America pay for we got to let him know we back them right now
I was at Mar-A-Lago yesterday
Cannot resist what up again just like
Mancow
What a prick unbelievable
Assholes
So a Man cast joking around
Apparently Rodger Stone may have said
Mancow with q or something
Time this is really fun because Alex has no idea what I was talking about
This is very
Did you see that Rodger Stone
Revealed hughleys
Yes
Tell folks
He said it was me
So the next time I
I'm not Q
But the next time I come on you and I have some serious stuff to talk about
I love you brother
Well Rodger Stone the last week you are cute
Started the whole thing
That was very weird
Need the weird part
Comedy
Rodger said
Do you know this and now it says yes
When it's clearly has no idea what the f***
Might be a little bit of a cute guy
Seems like all about the secret messages
Yes look it up
Did you hear about Wayfair and all the kid
Do you know about all the pedophiles that this President is busting up but they keep try to tie him
He's a present
Want more comics
Stay strong Alex
So I think that's a bit secret codes are pushing I think
I think you might be a cute guy
Exactly
Directly in opposition
To what Alex believe
We know that Alex has had private
Personal conversations with Joe Rogan
About hound once he gets
Free and gets on Spotify he'll be away for
From YouTube and I'll be able to attack the last absolute
Granted Joe Rogan
Has come out and said that that's a complete nonsense
Erich Mancow Muller has a little bit of a different take on this and
You realize you and I talked about this you realize I mean
We know somebody who just got a big
Todd Castillo by selling out
You and I won't sell out
And it's cost us millions in both don't understand that the Alex yelled at manpal
Yeah man
If we wanted to be asking
We wanted to be owned
God that we be rich
But I don't care I we may just save this great
Well my friend that's what it's all about it I'm you were smart to take your vacation. I already had it planned
So smart
To be able
Hang out with Rodger I guess he's under house arrest
Joe Rogan is apparently
The Mancow
Not a sellout
Sure
I mean
I will say that the time that I was a guest on his show I felt like he was really straight up
Very authentic
Very much
Nixon on this project Rodger
You don't even do it if you
I would suggest you don't do it
McClymonds
He was like
It seems to be a Hot Topic maybe we can drive
Traffic sure I know but I mean it just makes you look
Really weak
Can sad you can still get eyes on this thing with Rogers design
Something
Kind of a star
You get to talk about Wayfair maybe you could do some ads
Make a little money
Yeah I guess it's bad or stay at home on a Saturday night
Anyway
Because it turns out that some of the people
Supply dump
Yeah maybe
Can I be able to supply him anymore
Where's my favorite they were good sellers
My God
Kiss me I'm getting pissed now
You know you already know what's going on with the cupboard stuff
Outdoor family I get back
45-0
What's your
Wayfair
Which I know I'm right about it if he were to get pissed at me
I just I don't care I'm sorry the truth
So we know that he's going to tell the truth
About this sad Wayfair situation
Which is that it was
See if it's going around on the internet there is that there are
Some suspiciously high price
Cabinets
Names
People there people named
And so these
Decided that they must have be selling children
And
Serious question
They think that
Because they believe that is a smart idea
They think that because they're
Confused about why the prices so high
Second timer
If you were
One of these people selling let me know
I think I think that a lot of people get their ideas
I'm thinking poisoned by the concept of hiding in plain sight
Into your head
You start to think like
Place to do because
No one would buy a $12,000 thing so if you did obviously you would
Person who knows
To look for the child there
Yeah it's
It's a bit
So I know the truth about it
No
Why do people want to know what's up
And we are back on this Saturday afternoon emergency transmission
Without Rodgers
Had
So many people reaching out to me Prince family neighbor
Email text messages
Comments on Infowars wanting to know about Wayfair
And I know Army Commandos and CIA operatives FBI agents
That have been contacting me and others who think this is real
Because
They should be fighting
Credibly obviously weird
What year did
It's it's very weird
Threshold of proof for a lot of people that Alex
I thought you mean
So Alex began you already said that he knows the truth about test
We've revealed it which is what he knows the truth that's important
Because he now says he doesn't know what's up
Now that said I'm not sure
Exactly what's going on
But I have a pretty good idea this is one of three things
What is three possible
But you can't
So he knows the truth he knows
He doesn't know what's up
But it's one of these three things
Why don't you
I used to like
Here are the three possibilities
Either it's a money-laundering operation
And so they had the
Numbers and what would be in the cabinet would be drugs or something
Or you're paying more for something because you're using drug money to pay for
That goes on all over the place
Online it
Okay
Were you got $100 cabinet at $200 cabinet actually bought
That you had a couple zeros to or whatever and now it is
Thousand
Dollars is Alex implying that he's laundering money launder money
Are you surprised that better
First option
Sure there's a second
So it's either money laundering
Or is the big mistake they shed and some fool added 02 it
That's not what they said
That's the second option so maybe 80
Catsup
Massive conspiracy to launder money
Could be a good day
Option 3
Or
Is it really
That there
Advertising mesh as a
Package a container
Symbolizing their deliver you a child
Drugged up in one of these jobs
Diesel three option
What do you think he's going to go with
Money laundering
Selling Kids Academy
He's going to say this is a big one and we caught him
That's interesting
There's a fork
God dammit I can't sit there was a fourth
Okay
Alright
Think about that
No
I refused. The four
Yeah you hell
I believe this is the fourth from all the evidence and
Rageous it is obvious it is
Sure how it's designed
And mint
Can you put a big old juicy Nightcrawler worm on the end of a hook
And drop it in there
The bass of the parts of the crop
Cosplay
Smells good as we're going around they're going to want to talk about it
Yeah so the fourth option is at the track
In order for the oak
Conspiracy theorist or whatever
To find an amplifier as a trap
In order to invalidate other stories
About crimes against children
I mean whatever this is Ludacris
Feel like I feel really frustrated
With that thought price
Yeah cuz if you think
But that's
What it is
Okay
Here's what the globalist mean
To trap you
Nothing
You're saying
To all of your conspiracy Latin friend
That the globalist don't even need to work
Hard to get you guys to believe stupid
Well I mean it was the same rationalization for the stuff about the Obama's birth certificate
Forget the birtherism
Put out the Kenyan births
Certificate was racist
Saved saved
He was the child of the Apes
Didn't your old
So f****** stupid that you're willing to make your balls over anything
All right
I guess you got
Alright Alex believe there's this fourth option that is
I think that he's not
Considering a fifth option is that the people who make up the large bulk of his audience
Not very good at Discerning information
They're going to pizzagate all over again
When you look at
It's not just that they are
0 Steel
Money laundering it looks like because it's the names of girls
And it's not like that it's all these products
Named after little girls
And a bunch of them are really weird names
Steven know what you get when you buy a boat children
On the backs of milk carton
Internet
Now why in the hell would they put out ads
Can really deliver you children and cabinets and
Then put
The actual names of kids
This is one thing and one thing only
I
Conditionally admire Alexei that
Why would they do this at least even Alex can be like this is stupid
Unacceptable
Unacceptable to me the moment the moment you add in the fact that you can be yourself
This would be a dumb thing for Sorento
To do it's all about it honestly the only because I was got embarrassed so badly with pizzagate probably only
Reason why he's behaving like that if that happens can learn that's really bumper to
That's just because it was Danger
Did this stuff again
Like
That's too traceable to be on the right side of this in case it does break that directly
He knows that and that's why this whole conversation
Hey remember what happened with pizzagate and then him trying to
Pretend he didn't die
Remember
All of this it was
Top story on drudge top story all over the place
Now
This broke for about a week or two
And then suddenly out of the podesta
And out of
Lebanon
Democratic Party
CNN the New York Times Washington Post
Trout said wow bizarre claims
That a pizza place has a dungeon under it
And they're killing kids and selling them
I mean that all these things out that look better feel it
Wendy's other businesses they do as well and it turned out some of the stuff was really creepy and weird
We had Jack this
Easy myself to check this out has recordings of those things
Now to try to delete them for the internet but they're
Still there
So I mean
Obviously the argument that he's trying to make
Is
That the podesta emails Wikileaks things came out later real code about
Trafficking
The the whole thing pizzagate ended up
Just being a distraction from Shield
Elaine Maxwell
Is been arrested
This is in order to cover up
As opposed to possibly just
Mass
Delusion
People who feed into each other's internet behaviors
They go on these vicarious
Hunt's where they think that they're doing something and blue
Exactly
I think that's a much easier explanation cuz that's exactly what happened
Pizzagate happened in real time
Like ready Fords
Where are they
Conspiracy board where people were
Like coming up with new
Uses of information and then
Some of it
Gets rejected some of it
Floor boar and then like a couple days later than November
Days ago someone said this week and then they'll bring it back in like I watch that happen in real time
This is
Watch quicker
Broke
Like that
For it now
Call got the
The Playbook
Such low standards
For bringing things to the Public's attention
Amplify
Effectively that you can go from nothing to
Oh God so fast
So fast
Yep
On the show
You to believe that he did nothing
So smart
And so it is next Globe he throws his staff under the bus
That's what you get
You're not getting the Skype calls right to our pizza gate
And then
He's a legend
With no proof
CNN people were the ones who were posting this stuff on Fortune wow
I'm sitting there
I'm going on vacation for a week Cancun
Stop covering it I smell a rat they're diverting us to this off of that
I'm at the crib
And that's then how the media goddess and said that we created
A fake story
And they use that not being accurate
Either we didn't create it
CNN MSNBC they
No doubt their operative put on 4chan
Hm
That this information is there
Then we cover it
Then they flip it when we broke the big Spirit cooking or the first to get it out and Drug post it
You're proud and they turn with Alchemy
The real kids in the real farm houses in the real $65,000 a hot dog
And the blood in the semen in the breast milk
Aleister Crowley
And the devil worshipping
All these photos and videos of little kids all scared women dressed like witches and big bats
The blood
Maria bolanovich in in her and Reddit posts
I do rituals for real
All of that got distracted by the media than focusing in
On
There was no basement the pizza place
Right
But you did that
You weren't thinking
Cancun
But because of how embarrassing that was
And how much
I guess Alex took a hit on it
And probably felt exposed yeah he must have
You must have gotten more
Something then will I mean it's one of those times that he had to give a big public apology to drink
It sounds like there's a decent chance that he just thought like
Buck
To close
To close on this one
But
You didn't learn it all the way
It's not just you a Maxwell getting arrested
Also all of these stories about out of Germany
For some reference there two stories
Out of Germany that Alex has been
Been covering
One of them have to
To do with
In the past
There were a homeless children
Who were given to
Foster parents who were known to be pedophiles
And the studies of it in the recording on it is unclear
The scope to which this was taking place
Not appear to
Spread
Yeah
And the other story is about
A soldier who was arrested fairly recently last year
Investigation
Surrounding
The uncovering of an online child pronography sharing Network
Some crimes against children
And there were 30,000 leave
The police had to go on
Stories
And I believe
His intention is to say that this Wayfair story
Is trying to somehow block
Text from the
Write that story
He's treated those two stories of kind of
The same story even though they're not the same story at all
It's really complicated but
When he starts talking about the
It's tough in this next clip really kind of brought into Focus something I found really disturbing
About Alex's popat
German
Psychiatrist German government gave children the pedophile
1001 town
It turned out it was a spider web all over the country
They limited that as well
Dw.com
Show again ladies and gentlemen
Put that back on screen please
Understand
What's going on
The week that broke I said watch next week it'll break that tens of thousands of children are involved
1007 don't exactly as I said it broke
Why
British psychological warfare manual
How did you so happen to be being sold at Barnes & Noble like 20 years ago
Talked about their techniques after WWII Africa they said
Corporations kill se5000 villagers
We need to get out of head of it and say they kill 20
Perfect story
Because the pit psychiatrist over CPS
In Berlin what's ending
Thousands of children a pedophile
They first reported on his case
And not how was much larger
Titrating pitocin
Preparing you for was about to come out
That's what this is
I can still find no evidence to support the claim that Alex is making In that clip
Exaggerating the reporting
System
In West Berlin
Homeless children
Pedophiles
Again to stress that point any number of children is unacceptable I'm only pointing out the
Making up information
To help his narrative be more
Sensational
Like I said what's going on here is he's combining two unrelated stories out of Germany
The first is about those homeless youth being placed in foster care without a files
And the second story is about the 30,000
Send the weeds at the police have with the modern-day Network
So
Minimize this kind of thing
At all
Equally wrong to sensation
Prior Story the one about the
For care system is the one that
To talk about
And the Second Story includes the number 30,000
Metallica
Amplify so Alex is just combined them into being about the
Same thing when they're not
That being said the real reason that I pulled this clip is because how clearly demonstrates
Patterns
He believes that everything is psych ward
So he's gotten himself into a very bizarre
Because he's rationalized that the thing that he's lying about his just like Warfare to begin with
Let's take this specific example
Alex is lying about reporting about
German Faust
Your story but he doesn't see it as lying
Because he believes that the original reporting
Is just the globalist getting ahead of the story in order to soften the blow when the real story
Free comes out
Another story justifying his embellishment
That's not come out
But an unrelated topic has
So he just that good enough he's claimed to Victory
About everything
This kind of thought patterns
You can't stay
Victory
That's because he thinks reality is being reported in just psych Warfare
Compensating for that
To make the story match up with
Actual reality
In fact what he's doing is making things up in life
Experience at that way
Is that last clip at all accurately expresses Alex's beliefs
Be fair to say that his version of Truth could be described as lying about things you think our lives
Really eye-opening
Yeah
Yeah because
Just just making it up
Red light cuz
So what are you saying is that the Wayfair situation
Shane is a hoax
Distract from the
Two situations that
He has conflated engine
That will distract
From the app
Individual circumstances
That both stories are not dealing with whatsoever and Elena Maxwell
And Elaine Maxwell
Yet all of this is fine
Because sometimes the globalist
Starline
Do you and sometimes they're not because of course I can quote New York Times
And all of those things whenever they
If it don't
Everything that disagrees with what I believe
Is
Lies
To me and everyone out when it when it's convenient this story is like Warfare so I can lie to adjust
Us to compensate for whatever I believe this
As opposed to what it actually is
And why
So I think that's interesting and
Kind of
I do I don't want to say gives me closure
Finally gives me a better understanding of why you such a liar
Binky such a liar
If you do believe what he's saying they're like if he actually believes that about what he does
Information works yeah
You could justify
Sure and then this is the truth
That story is the whitewash
That's the fake version of the story
Feels right
A large
His behavior
End
And the thing about the
Is not too
Experience any empathy
In this way but
What that is
Essentially saying
I will never accept
Good news
Because it doesn't
Conform to my version of real
Do you know what I mean
Like everything that
Provides good
And enjoy you
Lies about 8 in order to
Facilitate the continuation of this
Globalist
And he amplifies every negative news source
As long as it helps with is conspiracy
Any real news
Is negative because it helps with his
Conspiracy theory
And so at any and all time
He is experiencing nothing but panic
Fear and rage
If he actually is
Yummy Nummies
Torturing himself
Right
I'm just trying to people around him
Is far more to the people listen to like how can you listen to this guy
Guy and take it seriously when he's
Clearly
Expressing to you
Yeah I renew stories that I just make up stuff because
It's like Warfare
Achilles
It's really it's really sad
Unknowingly essentially been
Tricked into a cult of Alex
Yeah like it's just whatever he interprets
Experiences as true
Representatives
And he will harangue you with
References to like Arcane and abs
Your documents you haven't read any hasn't either in order to justify his position
Fucken parlor trick
Ridiculous
Very sad
Who are the people's belief
Yes
It's ultimately because I mean like this Legacy doesn't hold up
Like no
Bank of us say we'd survive
Current trouble
His history doesn't go down well
I'm the same way that we can look back on the job
Society and all like right-thinking people to be like today
Yeah
He's going to be similarly
Hugh
What he has done with his life his life's work will look
Yet
But
I don't think he cares
Yeah I mean
You know in the same way
His listeners are victims in participating
Participants in their own
Kind of
Miserable
Since Alex is
Visiting upon them and himself is unfortunate he's torturing everyone
Yeah
Proximity
I told you that there was a conditional aspect to me saying that Alex was like
Does Wayfair conspiracy
Conditional
Cuz he's about to say that maybe true
The globalist to put out the system formation
Because they know this is Master this is a zeitgeist
Understand it and I hope when it comes out this isn't true it'll somehow discredit all
We believe this will blow up in their face
Quite pizzagate
People will see through all this and understand what's going on
Now
But it'd be there really money laundering
Could it be that there actually these are real lad who knows
Khalilah Morris Heroes Reddit
I don't believe so
Because
They're all named after little girls
A bunch of a missing little girl
Make everybody go crazy
So he is saying it's globalist
Disinformation but also maybe it's
Where I know
Yes it's globalist information
Disinformation because maybe the other thing
How could it be both
How can it even be possible that it's money laundering if it's an intentional plan by the globalist
To make
Your side look bad and make it look like
Alright then
It's like in chess
When you're when you when you got a pin
I don't know
The German like Zeus or whatever whatever
You get to take one of their peace
No matter what
Haha it's so sad this is why so few are laundering money
You both
Actually launder money
And also make it look like you're not laundering money
Unless somebody figures out that your laundry
Just like
Pizzagate blew up in their face
Face is definitely no one else
In space no.
Yeah but I will
There's no way I appreciate your attempt to stretch this to make sense
Credulity
No no
Freestyle mixes
Pretty clear that this is a stupid way to try and deliver
Trafficked children
You really think
Group like this was shipped thousands of kids around engine
Not knowing the trucks
Record one's going to fall open
Are kids going to die in one
No papa
Not true it's not real
That's why
They are doing all of this thing in May
Typos
100 hundreds of items were going over right now have more tomorrow
This was done in May
And they use names of real children are missing
People take the bait
And say oh my God this is
So this is bae
This is bait
It's the globalist
Mistress Honey Trap
Now
Make this next clip
Tough to hear
Because it is coming out they can't hide it
The system doesn't know what to do
So I've been set up like this
Party Rental
Georgia
But this is meant to discredit the real work that police are engaged in in my view
A nebulous trailers arthrotec
Comments below
But if the globalism not bold enough and maybe I'm wrong to ship kids actually in containers like this
Psychos when they get don't get caught around it away with the automobile crazy
Even crazier start wanting to get caught
And who the hell knows anymore I having this is just unbelievable
But know this
This was not an accident
They use a bunch of little girls names
Come up missing girls
Complete the first and last name
This was done
Bait you
Away from all the other.
Infowars.com newswars.com tomorrow's news today
That's the end of his special report
This is not how you do this
This is not good
Because he's clearly
Clearly articulating his position that this is
This is
Sucker people into going down
I've been right at the end
He's like
Maybe I don't know
Do that
If you know that the
Ludacris
Why are you making the bait possibly attractive to your audience
I think it's cuz he
I think I've decided honestly I am the only person that exists
Who's here because he
I know I know that insane I can
Counter
You're arguing
I don't know
You wouldn't believe me
Yes but things happen when you're not here
How can you even he's got an
Ladies if you got an iPhone do you have a choice
How can you how can you
How can you turn this somehow into you being
Victim
Thought
It is that a lot
Red Bull
Add Wayfair time the victim were clearly targeted at
Hoosier way
These qanon folks who are posting all of these
These Wayfair
Conspiracy by the globalist Trap me Alex covering this
In order to delegitimize my already Sterling
Remarkable unimpeachable record
Which I will then defeat them by revealing that it's a hoax
Why won't you leave it the possibility open
But hey they might be doing I don't want to fully close the door on this just in case I realized it could be
Comfortable
What the f***
The thing about the Honey Trap
Honey
And I like honey
Little bit of honey
I don't know I always constantly and blessed with
The feeling of like bewilderment
Because like
Supposed to be like Rodger
I do recall this being the David
It is a profound
Statement
Rodger Stone
Show up the next
Day
That cannot be over
The idea that Mancow was at the same Hotel
Where Rodger Stone
You got it
The fact that all of that happened
Is dammit
Demonstrates Alex's relative position
Other folks
This Wayfair stuff is
Real
Shity
Real real City
Man I just
It's just such a bummer
I would love it if Alex had the backbone that it took
It just be like
F*** you
Now
F*** you every nice you're done
Debates to myself for you to the point where I've lost my entire business
I'm going down
My life is a shambles now do I have a lot to do with that totally please Rodger could do is show up
Have to do is show up
Text Alex for all you've done
Give me a
Thank you and then say up I got to go or I'm not feeling well
Hey I was celebrating.
Everyone will be like
F*** yeah you are
Yeah and Alex all you need to do is get a thank you and Rodger didn't give you the thank you so cut
Tides forever
Wow it's too early as a recording us on Sunday to know if you was actually on Sunday
He probably was
Oh that's a day and how long
That's too long
Like we told you you would probably
Yep and I hate to tell but it is what it is
Black Jordans
We aren't her that knowledge underscore fight and I go to bed Jordan
Please find a bail fund charity in your area that take
Newswise
Alex
Birthstone colors