Air Jordan
I have great respect for its knowledge by knowledge
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
About Alex Emerick
How you doing today I'm alright
We already asked question how am I doing I'm doing alright
Can I ask if I
Okay
Third question
That's not who's on first
Competence
Mild levels of competence
Bright spots for me or ending up being just like little things I got
Or whatever
That's great you already about this
Another
Very hot
It's very it's very hot
In the summer here in Chicago
And so you solve that problem
Love you express a little bit
Now tallit
Flash Forward a couple days
It's not sealed windows
So you know today
To seal up these windows in order to keep
The coldness and not have the bugs
You know it's just
Alright
There are problems you can't solve
Hi sweetheart just like you know it's not
Bugs would have been like I've got to run away
Able to celebrate
Especially like
The things that we can take
Control over our Oliver
Completely
I think I'm experiencing that and wanting
2 to recognize it
My book out on the world
Long last George r.r. Martin Everybody
I decided to put it out
It's called The Quiet part loud
How crazy is that
Stars align
Literally
Exactly
Website
For free
To chip in a little bit is there Frida specs
Someone else is going to get quiet part loud, Direct
Youtube.com
Can get buzzed
Somebody unquiet part laboratory hours
If he did already
OU
God dammit
Interesting
I would say probably would
Generally be bored with a lot of the racism vitalik
Express Zombies episode
We'll talk about a little bit
The movie would be situations
You know over there are two stories that I consider to be ongoing
Okay developing stories
The first was our last episode we discussed our special on Saturday
The episode Alex came to the studio on his day off
And interviewed Mancow
Did not interview Rodger Rodger was not there
Never not
Saturday show Alex
Which is part of the reason
Storyline
We need to see what Rodger says when he shows up on it
Can only assume that Rodger shows up from minute
Development
Second Story
You remember at the end of the episode after Alex been a long time saying it's a Honey Trap and don't get married
As well
So first of all
Journal apology walk
I'm a policy wonk
Dutch
I'm a policy wonk reference to my parents
Exclave
Text Chris
Seacrest
Asura
Caillou
I'm a policy wonk
Text Doug
Next
Thank U next we have Ryan herb Ryan Ryan
It's Friday
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
In a little machine that sits on your countertop
4 cup
Alright water over it
Gahanna theater
Local charity cuz I need a pick-me-up big deposit form
Generosity
Turn on Sunday
Holcomb station
How are you
You're on the fence about the devil
I was on the fence about
Sample
Alright
So so
Weird
About the fact
There's been clamoring to know what that will be
Don't worry about it
And I have made a decision
Okay
All right now is the
Make a treaty with the spider leadership they will take care of your bugs
Everybody knows this is how they use that you self
I've no problem with spiders for the most part
They're welcome
Let's Travel to Phoenix.
Scarabs
So are we start here
The Wayfair story is ongoing
I started listening to Sunday
Why the f*** are you doing this
With that broke Friday a huge Wayfair story
Online Merchant company
When people supposedly in the names who kidnap children
$15,000 to $10,000
I think so but it could be
And focusing on instead of all the
Confirm
Roll-up of huge Global pedophile rings
Could be a setup
To distract us
Don and the rest outside
Going back
Years this is widespread
Wow
Page
Craigslist
Prostitution a few years ago
Edward said it a deep dive on that last night
Good words about some friends
Did not say almond
Where somebody
Can research this tablet look at this
And the boldness
Of these people just completely
What is real bad
I mean that's almost closed
Convincing themselves to buy a used car they know is going to shop
Used car that blew up in the bath
Shame on you
I'm going to buy this second used car cuz I
F****** love that's why I am yesterday or on our on our last episode
Seems like you're on the right path saying it's a stupid way to deliver
Traffic
People
Oh no Alex
I swear to God raises you even further
This is entirely am just like
Finding ways to just needle you a little bit
Build up a semblance of like
I think they're really into
Conspiracy
S***
We're going to alienate a lot of people
Adjust
Imagine
What time in
Evils really grown
Yes this is
Sentence of beams or something now he's like
Wayfair selling key
A weaver
Every morning I wake up
Just I just remind me that like every morning
At the news gone so we're really doing this
This is what
Does seem like that is that is
Responsibility
Just like I guess this is
Is what we're doing
Are conspiracies real is like
That's what we're doing
Google
Read the darkness
Play the game before Alex
You're cute
Trouble
Pacific Service
Is that. Later
Pretty racist on this episode
Is based on how he covers
Various stories
And this is the chief one of them is the big story that you covering in a
White identity White
Fear Manor that's a
The story does not necessarily match
Young white mother
I asked you to my black
Mob
Legitly saying all lives matter
Checkpoints
Well baby I went Gaga
In the head
I guess you deserve it
So this is Dory that Alex is
Completely misrepresenting
That I'm not minimizing the tragedy of unnecessary
Arena story justify
Shooting
My only point is that the available information
Completely contradicted Alex's reporting
Because he doesn't actually care about the reality of the story
He's interested in creating a
Beer
White people of non-white
That's always
This is about a woman from Indianapolis named Jessica Whitaker who was shot
Killed in the very early morning
Hours of July 5th
She was walking with her fiance and two other friends the other canal and Indianapolis around 3 a.m.
As a group passed a group of strangers one of the people in Whitakers group was overheard saying the n word
Strangers responded by yelling blacklivesmatter reply.
What happens next from the article about this in the Daily Mail
Her fiance quotes said both groups branded guns at each other
And walked away from each other
So it appears that everything was all right but apparently it was
This group of strangers initially shot at them and fire was returned and sadly Miss Whittaker.
Incidentally this is the second homicide that's taken place in this stretch of the Indianapolis canal in just that week
Previously a fourteen-year-old was shot allegedly the result of an adult shooting him in self-defense after the youth attempted to pull off and on
Armed robbery
So this is
Maybe if an area where there's a little bit of crime going on right now
It seems like everybody's
This is an awful story but you can easily and pretty immediately see the factual misrepresentations that Alex has added to his version of
He doesn't mention that it was a 3 in the morning and the altercation began because someone use the n-word
That's not to say
That justifies a shooting reporting the story
Two-story have cast these people as black lives matter protesters who
Glm
It when they say all lives matter their executor
This is obviously not at all accurate from the available reporting on the story
I want to start the story with the victim and suspect who yelled black lives matter
His imagination
The pieces fall into
Very deeply races person would do
Bcomplete mister
Reporting of stories like this
Specifically for the reason of creating racially-charged
And I think honestly doing something like this
The regularity
Hey more damning than if you just said slurs on air
Yeah this is worse
Decide
Scale of a butt
I think at this dinner tomorrow
Yeah I mean slur is awful inoffensive
It's not necessarily
Always
Inciting a bunch of
Passionate passionate gun weirdos into believing that every black person is coming to
F****** EX
Execute them if they don't swear
Fealty to Black lives matter
Yeah exactly
Jurist
Especially when the actual
Basis
The story that he's basing it on
It doesn't match
Anyway here's another story that turns into a racial story
Confined
Subway video shows arrangement
White people on the New York subway
Beyond your nose anywhere
You can find plenty of stories about this and Outlets like New York poster The Daily Mail
It's not something that's being ignored by the media as much as it is more
Everything I can tell there's a story about a mentally unwell person
Two people on a train which sucks but it's not national news
The suspect was arrested on charges of attempted murder among other
Both of the victims who were in their 70s survived and are in stable condition
So that's Brightside
Far less severe of a story that I would be
Headed to New York or
You know
You know what even not losing
The idea that everybody needs
We talkin about
The black guy
Is Bowser
There's an important distinction to grab that all
And that is just because the person who happens to commit this crime
That doesn't mean this is really involved at all
In this case I can see no evidence that race was a factor in the crime
Suzanne ageist cry
Suspect
Before commencing
Galaxy sees a black guy attack a white person believes or at least report
Because the guy was white
That's really stupid way to look at things
But when you
Racism
Operate this way when the races are reverse
When a white person commits a crime to justify why racism isn't involved at all
To do is look back to his coverage of Ahmad Arbury Skilling as a perfect example
Somehow this doesn't play out
The same way
It in those circumstances and again this is just a
Fingerprinting
Of a deeply racist broke
He spends all of his
This time with Ahmad arbery
To explain
Morphe
Yeah
And it's so much like
Is emblematic of a complete inability to understand
Why
Or if it's a
It worth it
Play Pure ability
You understand
You know what I'm saying like this
This is a rebuttal
Two people pointing out the
Horrific police violence
The racist
The tax in the fuc
That are still f****** going on
And they are emblematic of a long long history of
Pulling up any kind of like
Will see a black person hurt a white person
As a as a defense against
It is either misunderstanding that each individual Act
Is part of a larger hole that knee
Corrected
Thunder standings
And we have to find
You know what I'm saying
I think that
Tavares
The biggest issue is an
Willingness to recognize that sometime
When their crimes with white victim that's not because they're white
You know
Honestly like me bringing up the Gaze of them is almost
This case because you can make a very strong argument that the reason
Was because
Pretty
Compelling racial component
This point I don't know what information
Reporting I can find have any racial
Component to what would he did it all
I don't know it's just
He's trying to imagine it in
Into a rebuttal
About the situation with a couple St Louis
It turns out that they have ended up having their home search
Navigation going on
Top of St Louis couple defend home
Confiscated
George Soros
Apparently this couple of the mckloskey's
Team was confiscated
There's an investigation
Into them because they were straight up pointing guns at people and Patricia McCloskey had her finger on the trigger of a pistol
Under normal circumstances that is illegal
To brandish a weapon
Somebody comes really complicated when you start to factor in ideas of
Self-defense
Stand-your-ground
The castle doctrine
It's an open question about whether or not the argument of feeling threatened
Being just
Poseidon Brandon
Weapons and self-defense
Is valid
And the fact Patricia it was pointing a gun at people and had no firearms training
Great
Legally they're probably going to end up fine
I'm going to guess
Crazy up there not
They're not cool
Hey if you guys get him for this this
Sbirs taken down Capone
There's a long history of s*** that I'm not sure they're bootleg
Missouri is not involved in
In the case at all
The investigation is that a circuit attorney Kimberly Gardner
No Alex has her position wrong
Garner want her election to the circuit
Attorney's office in 20
And she did accept funding from a Super PAC called the safety of Justice
Committee which Soros did donate
There's a little
Everybody
Not for any
So Alex Goes International
What's he doing outside
Police say that a good job
Lowe's in Ireland
And video
It's tough to say exactly what's going on and then some loud music
It starts playing
The camera Cuts over to two people holding up a banner that says
You fascists bound to lose
Suicide up of what looks like at least
5 amps
Then descends on them tears up the banner a kickover the amps
And it doesn't look like it's hard to keep track of where people are in the crowd but I would not be surprised they got roughed up a cup
This was challenging but I was able to find some
Alright
This is an event that is called an anti pedophilia rally in the same way
Some college campuses are pro free speech
It's essentially an extreme right-wing group using the cover of something that you probably
Possibly be against in order to give them cover
Operate their stealthier agenda
You see this a lot with people like Tommy Robin
Engage in horrific
Anti-muslim agitation in demonization
You're accused
Supporting The Grooming
Stop
Yeah it's a really standard
Ireland
Inside with his video
Justin Bieber
Be leader of the National Party
According to the beacon in 1998 book called The National Way Forward in Wichita
Configured according to Catholic Doctrine
And the creation of a Catholic dictator
That's always worked well in the past for Ireland
This he argues that the only way to save Ireland from the scourge of liberalism and immorality
He's actually opposed to immigration entirely against Reproductive Rights
It's to the point of advocating the death penalty for abortion doctors
Decriminalisation of homosexuality and divorce
I want at least three occasions you spoken at events held by the German Neo-Nazi party
Cmpd
Including one event in 2000 where he was
The guest of honor
In 2002 in the Irish Times
Described as a coach stinging rebuke
Barrett from John Smith
Who's the spokesperson of the anti-abortion
I'm pro-life
Campaign
Even
Christ
Quote
No amount of evasion or spin on mr. Barrett's Park in
Explain
Seriousness of attending such conference
It's nonsense to contend
Speaking at a neo-fascist Rallys serve the interest of building a more caring pro-life culture
Rights agenda which she claims to espouse
The groups with which Mr Barratt in the center reported
Be Associated have an agenda of social exclusion and political extremism
I'm sorry
From ethos of respecting moderation
The pro-life movement
You know keep your scoffing aside and whatever sure your point is valid
Ignited like this guy
If you're there you're gone
Even ideological allies in the
Barrett was a leader of a Irish group called youth defense
Which is mentioned in that guy's quote which is a really bad girl
Npd's youth division DeYoung National Democrats held a conference in 1999 where Barrett spoke
By virtue of his connection with you
Defense
Also in attendance
This is the guy who is running his rally in Ireland
Kind of makes sense that there were some counter demonstrators protest
It's very easy to pretend that their protest was somehow anti anti pedophilia
Who's holding the rally
You should
Get the picture that this rally was not anti pedophile to begin with
Anti pedophile
Bear
Pedophile rally we do start with a Sig Heil but that's like
That's just tradition
That's it's not about that
It's not about those
Okay sure that's wise because everywhere
Pictures of people holding signs
Samantha
Alex
Cancel culture there
Epsom salt
The discourse
About a buddy of his
Stand up
Paul Revere operation
Play sports
Please get products at
Infowars store
Come
Calling 888-253-3139
Fourth of July super
Sale continues
Free shipping at Double
Weird voice
Tucker Carlson
Stop writer
I've been using an alias
Insects with stuff on a web forum
Between some material posted or saw in the Forum and Carlson the show
This is a guy
Reporter at the Daily Caller
What is a Blog Tucker
Co-founded
Is the guy work for Tucker and Tucker adjacent
Which makes it a little hard to shrug off is just like the random employees
Current behavior
Jewel
Is also a quote from
Carlson is reading off the teleprompter
What does it mean
Chirp
Resigned on Friday and then on Monday which is
Just suspicious
Sure.
Around the World in 80 Days
The situation
In fact the guy who post
Racist kid online
Think about it
Obviously Fox News. It wasn't cool because a dude resigned
Almost certainly would have been fired to try and put out the story
Some more advertisers my bail
Tucker's
You can just wait this out on another vacation and
Come back in a few weeks
He is almost certainly
Never shake the MyPillow
It cares
Frankly anybody
There's other than people who are like
We're way past this man
We already knew that he was racist
Justin Bieber
If you work on Tucker's there's a good chance
Camera guy like listening if you're
The gist
That'd be tough
I don't know though like
Trying to compare this to like when I worked at a roast beef place
Food is kind of gross
But I still work there
True
Now that's true roast beef
Roast beef
Pretty cool
In terms of that
Super weird was
Now you're talking about how you need to
New course is part of a sales pitch
Really weird about is iodine
I mean
We've heard stuff like this
Before but I just want to keep this in just
Little marker on that guy
Battlefield
3 the good
Station in the US
2 billion people
Mental disabilities or lower IQ
Because it is going to buy it or not getting it
60 ambrosia
The key
Adrenochrome
He's going to like you
All into the adrenochrome Stop
They have
So
I would give him I would give him
What was the early 2017 Eddie Bravo
The elite sprinkler adrenochrome
Actually predate a lot of the Cuban on people who might want to try and reach
Claim that from them
Adrenochrome prolong
It's been a while
Anyway I just think it's funny
Parrot 2
It does seem
Defeat your
Your purpose
Pretty awesome
You can get really high on to iodine
Know about iodine
If it's busy
Nascent
Alex Alex
Last episode
And I see some
I'm upsetting headlines about
Releasing some opposition research
Executive branch
Because we played cliff on the episode of Alex
Credit for
Fauci being on the outs
Yeah we were recording that
We were not aware of that at all
Just thrilled
Of course we talked about that a little bit more
All the time
Fauci
Has been
Wrong
On
Coronavirus
They're so upset and so mad that he won't even keep score
Expert
Call Coach that lost every play
Every game ever put one point on the board
I think I can't get my head around right now is why Trump is dozen
Fire fauci
Like what could possibly be stopping him from firing the dude
East
Absolutely no cuz I have no idea what's going on
Accountable
Might be in gation of like how dictators operate when they're not sure in their footing
I don't care about this dumb f*** political posturing in the middle of a pandemic
There's no time for stuff like this in a mature World directly rejected
I'll take Alex seriously by keeping score as soon as he applied the same standards
He's insisting for fauci on to
Trump and himself
This kind of childish lashing out doesn't rise to the level in my eyes of like
Deserving attention
Nope and I mostly only keeping this
And the next play.
Kind of to be like
I certainly hope this doesn't look really really terrible in a couple months
Code word
T understood what was happening and
Was going to build a case
Kanzashi
Go that way
Go get somebody close before he destroys them but
So Alex is taking responsibility for feeding the information to Trump to get fauci on the outs
And he's insisting the Trump is communicating with secret code using the word sideline
So
Great truck also placed an ad
In the Austin States
That only Alex knows how to read if you it's
It's not an acrostic but it
Is every eight
The second letter of every 8th word is how
Alex gets his messages and this last one
The great job
Okay
So Alex
Discussing
Virus stop being a hoax
I wanted a big big headlines on this is it there was a guy who is a correspondent for like
NBC MSNBC
And it had Coronavirus
Do you believe that
And turns out
He ends up getting an antibody test
He comes back negative
So Alex believes this is Bruce
But I was enough
Put me in the ICU for
Infowars.com nbcnews
He tested neg
Which means he hasn't had a cold or the flu in 10 years on average
I didn't show up
Unbelievable
What that means
It's really confusing because the clip Alex plays it's just that guy dr. Joseph Fair
Explain really sick and it's underlined condition
In reality I was kind of just fudging the story
In Mayfair got really sick
You had basically all of the symptoms that are associated with covid-19
You got some nasal swab test some of them at home and then came back
Because he was presenting as a very likely covid case and there's a possibility of false negative
A couple months later after he's made a recovery Fair got an antibody test
Who came back
This presents a number of possible scenarios that could be going on here
The first is that he had an unknown condition that was very similar in progression of symptoms
Covid-19
Leaving this a medical mystery That Remains
Basalt
It's also possible that the nasal swab she took were false negative
Could be accurate
This would mean that he did have covid-19 but he doesn't have antibodies
I would show up in a test for them patties
Inconceivably pasa
As of this point it's unclear exactly what's up here
He said he's Consulting more doctors
Trying to get to the bottom of what happened
You seem additional expert
Follow up antibody test
He'll be able to
Get to the bottom of what happened
The scenario that I think is most unlikely and all this is what Alex's suggest
Namely the doctor Fair
You really had faked everything
Why would he then revealed that he tested negative for the antibody test
It's not like his doctor could even legal you release that information
Himself
Is this was all staged
Why would you do that
That makes no sense
Most terrified
Prosper
Possibility
Is 1 minutes
Becoming more and more
Researched and there's more and more evidence
For it is that
The antibodies go away you
You don't have permanent immunity to
That could be a factor in their zaxxon
Terrified
Plays a role in this story
We'll check back in on it
He's not like a cardboard cutout
Volkswagen
For a while you presume
Some sort of an indication that baby
You didn't
You know that's kind of even scarier
Could be a chronic condition of some kind
You know there's a lot
Pretty scary so I would assume
Continue trying to figure out what's going on
If only for his own
How many times have you heard
Like the moment I got my diagnosis
Thank God there's a reason and I understand
To then if it was then ripped away from
4 minutes
We have no f****** clue what's wrong with you that would be
Terrifying and it's
Yeah I kind of scared
When I was younger
As a as a teen
Almost
Just have to give you this and everything
Am I hope today
But
Jordan
To the point
Episode
We can wait
40K
Rodger Stone
Is not here
Get back to the Wayfarer
You wanted to talk a little bit more about his audience
He's really warming up to this
I saw this Wayfair Thing by Friday
Online yoga
Bender
Psych
Competition to Amazon
Was so rude
Killer
Hundred-dollar $200 tablets
For 10,000 13014
15016 $17,000
Pillows that were maybe thirty bucks for $5,000
With in some cases the names
Missing children on
Ghislaine Maxwell
Almost
Really
Money laundering
The symbol of
Deliver this child
Wasn't somebody adding more zeros on steak
So apparently the money-laundering office
Open was also about
Sewing kit
Yeah traffic
People
Great
Worried
Wayfair
Write for Alex
Short descent
Get sued
I worried for the Seco just like what it is
Just as a case study of
Should know better
You know you would think I would even discussing something last episode but like
Alex did have to give
A gigantic apology to James Oliphant
We had to do that or else he's going to get food
It made for a lot of trouble Biggs pizzagate coverage
He ended up
Spending
Months and months trying to pretend that he didn't do pizzagate
Deleted from YouTube
Like you don't need to do this you can take
Pass on the way to Fairbanks
It's not going to stick around for a very long time
Just some dumb qanon bulshit
And then they'll move on to the next thing
I will tell you I think there is one
Case study that I can
Recall
That reminds me very
And it's the case study of one wild e
Coyote
Nope just
Can't learn their other things to eat in that desert I get it there's it looked at the roadrunner
There's other stuff out there
So apparently Alex that had somebody sent him
Some stuff on Amazon and this changed
Does not matter
Partially
What's going on
I hate you
Show you some of this
Took hours ago wrong but I'll try my best
All these other big shopping
Amazon
Going back years have the exact same code words
Turns out that
Got caught with prostitution in similar things
Years ago
I don't know others
Destino
Similar stuff on Amazon
Going on for a long time that nobody
Noticed
Different
Hahaha
Specifics the week
Assertive
Nail into
Wayfair
Amazon
Pillows
Thousand dollars
And then it starts
Telling normally sold for $20
The names of going to show you all of those folks
Some of this
Babies
Shriveled like they're starving to death
Weird comment
Code word
Boston helicopter
Starch
So the reviews that Alex is talking about there at the end
There's an entire subculture of people who write fake reviews for things on Amazon
What's going on here
Very funny
Pictures of emaciated kids on Amazon
Talking about weirdos found on searching for the SKU numbers for these product
It's in a very specific
Place
The SKU for a product is the stock keeping unit number
Retailers use to track inventory
As it turns out if you take
SKU numbers for these suspicious item
C-usa
And then you search for that in the Russian search engine
Demdex
You come up with some
Questionable image results
Some of them are children
Are you people doing Yandex searches
Character research myself already got the
To the bottom of it
The account Dapper Gander on Twitter has a great thread fully explaining what's going on
What y'all some up yours best
There is a Russian image
It's called imgsrc
Should definitely not go
It was essentially formally like Photobucket but sent that early is 20/40
It's been taken over by pedophiles
Zuko's Demopolis
American search engines filter out results that come from this Russia
Maturing
Because of the high incidence of illegal images that would come up in the results
Does not exist
Search engine
Which is why qanon weirdos
Insist on using search engine
In order to prove their conspiracy
Basically if you search for SRC along with just about a
Anything on Yandex very high likelihood of finding some at least questionable picture
So what's boils down to is basically a scam
It's a trap
In terms of swimming hours
Falling for this
Babe
The master of research in reality got filled by a Fool's task qanon
I don't like
Bad faith
Use monsters to
To portray
Good faith actors
Is monsters while bad faith actors
Continue the entire cycle
Over and over and over again
Without doing
You know
Realized
You was wrong
Good
Jones cannot believe
This is just
LOL
So Alex
Let's go ahead
And let's see if he runs a right on into that rock
In case you wanted not really commit to this baby
Well unfortunately
Explicitly
This is not a psyop
Disco song August is no mistake
Oh my God
Product code for you right there with Rebecca Moore
So I don't think you could be much clearer than that
Wow really
If up this doesn't turn out poorly and more embarrassing way after they give us another apology for CEO of Wayfair whatever
I don't know
We come back here on the 13th
Wayfair
So this episode on the 13th
Is like okay
Rodger didn't show up on
Sunday
Right baby you still
Monday you've got to be the one hundred percent
Has to be there
You does not
Dammit
No Rodger
Apologize
Us
For years to tell him
Directions to push it
The days overdue hey Rodger what's going on with you
And talk about this
Is Indiana story a little bit more
And then I'm going to show you the footage
Newscast
About the white woman shot today
Enter some
Dwayne criminal mentally ill
Vicious small minority
Black folks
Going out
This is all going on
And the media
Is all
Busy covering it
So there's a cover-up
The media of black males
Between 13 and 25 or out to kill and knockout game
White people
In American history that would almost
Primarily Focus
Tucson 13
Twenty-five-year-old blackmails is being evil
I certainly don't feel like this has any
Historical
Sustained
30000 seasons of Law & Order's in their various spin-offs
So Alex
To talk in here
Alex
Appears to be the
Okay
You would think that if you didn't
Right there's one that's kind of important
And that is
No black person who is alive
The subject of more racism
Simself
Dallas Texas
Thought I was crazy
Call Sasha
Andy Black
I mean I probably have
And you know I
And then his brother was a prison
So
Black people out there that
That have
Ever had 100 white people start fights
Presented without comment
10 u.s. Representatives
You're something I I I want to say just heard of axiomatic
If you have gotten in 100 fights in your life
Haha that's about you
Because most people don't know
It's more about you than just about anybody else
There's a hundred incidents that
Commonality between always 100 lights
Race
That's the second thing
100 fights with
Black people
That's the secondary element that makes it even more about you
Flat number 6
I think maybe his perspective and perception that
Might be a little bit
How do you spell
It's very hot
Sports with a
El Paso
Have you heard of the John Birch Society
Learn about the hair
Yeah man I don't know
I can't parse any of that stuff actually really necessarily believe his numbers are accurate
But if you're getting in a lot of fights
Something about you other people responding to you
I believe
If you're saying it like that
You already
So Alex is coverage in Indianapolis
Trend of
Trying to make people afraid of
If people are yelling blacklivesmatter at you then
Yes
How to kill white people for fun
It's all just that there's just
The building of it is sort of race
Race-based
Beer that Alex wants to
Still course Avatar who did it
And the boys are overwhelmed and it's not
Starfall
If you just saw that
Dawson's not safe
Not safe there's murders all the time
Robin stabbing shooting most of its racial
Nothing is going to be down about
These areas are not safe
Don't let anybody lie to you
Any left the city is not safe
Because
Control
Has been lost
So control has been lost in the left-leaning areas
And the specifics
He seems to be operating off of our various places where there is a lot of
Shooting
And they're almost all racially-based
These places
It's not so much that they're not say
G-strings
I will say this
If you are
Thinking about leaving
Chicago
Two left
Just for you
Get on out of
Get off
Go to the forest
Stop get out of here
Have a great time enough for any sort of politics
But I do want to go to the
That's different. I just want to commune with trees
Alex discusses Chick-fil-A
Capitulate
Everyone
Colitas now everything
There's no future Chick-fil-A's business doubled in one year
Close on Sunday
Hobby Lobby did the same thing today
We push our religion on you but we are off on Sunday Christian
Is that what they said though
Today anyways
Chick-fil-A
Probably a black child
Chick-fil-A in Hobby Lobby closed on Sundays
The Sunday thing
Close on Sundays or even on weekends
No one cares
Chick-fil-A anti-lgbtq
There's been CEO Dan Cathy
He said in 2012 that allowing same-sex marriage would quote invite
These comments naturally got some book unhappy
Responsible anti-lgbtq forces on the right-wing turn Chick-fil-A into a pillar of their identity
That was the chicken company that
Fought for their interest
Mike Huckabee tried to get a Chick-fil-A appreciation day going
It sort of became a way of engaging and homophobic
Trolling
People wanted to publicly expressive distain for LG
G b t q people directly
Big deal out of supporting chick
Chick-fil-A
I was almost like they were stoked because they're like
Chicken sandwich
In the process of this whole conversation it came out that the Kathy's had given million
Games to anti-gay org
Innovations including ones that promoted conversion therapy
Business with people that a problem
Chick-fil-A
Anymore
Pissed off but are you sure it wasn't because we all
Just assumed that if they were open on Sunday they would
I'm pretty sure that's what we were
Hobby Lobby
Included birth control
And they did that
Cuz they don't want to force their religion on
People judge a business eventually deciding how to treat their employees based on a religious
Just believe
$3000000 settlement
To put in his collection of Bible memorabilia
According to MSNBC Hobby Lobby hired an expert
Instead according to the justice department 5,500 artifact
Without proper documentation
Themes
Very bad
Hobby Lobby going to stay open
Because Green's wife Barbara had received a message from God saying that everything was cool
But they're not going to force their religion on it
Ended up closing all their stores in April
No one cares about these businesses being closed on Sunday
The problem isn't destructive Behavior
Rich people shouldn't be allowed to engage in
It seems like
Keno's
That's why people were mad
Sunday
Because of supporting things like
Conversion therapy
Open
Right
Affordable Care Act
Honestly all time honored American tradition
Just not on today
But
I'll talk to Rodger Stone today
I'm just going to leave it at that
He'll be here tomorrow
Yes
But he's not yet there's a lot of stuff behind the scenes
Sad
If he's on Hannity
Be too busy to you to go on Hannity
Sort of curious about where Alex stands on the 5G stop it
And Coronavirus
Necessarily
However
It turns out the water might be muddy or than we think
People point out to be 3 months ago
Years ago he showed documents were 5G in China
What's causing an autoimmune response in the lungs
People think they were dying
Call group of talk to you so I won't come on I love you brother
Elektra really bad
Time
But he
This electromagnetic radiation
The system is getting so powerful
That that that
Autoimmune response
It's really exacerbating
First things first
Exacerbating the condition that people are having
He said there's no virus
Which is a different claim
Discovering this is a byproduct
Spectre group discover
If this is just a 5G thing then what happened to the stories about the
Timelab just take a second to think about you
Creating a virus as a bioweapon
Completely Superfluous or it has to be readjusted to now actually be about them researching a specific virus at work
Which hasn't been demonstrated up to this point everything needs to change to accommodate this
He said
I guess this is what we're doing then
All right you will you're going to ignore this tomorrow
Completely forgot this was actually all
Created in the Wuhan lab before
Didn't exist right now
5G mansion
They're still best
Text Rodger
Explains a little bit about why Rodger
Isn't around
There's a reason that are Rodger Dunn on this show Yeti
Tomorrow
My email
OU mice
Commutation order
So he still under her jurisdiction
So here's where things get a little messy for Alex and Rodger
It looks like Trump put out a press release an announcement that Rodger sentence was commuted
Clemency but it looks like he didn't actually provide the appropriate information to the judge and Rogers case
Just causing a little bit of an issue
According to an article in time
Although president prison sentences
The brief order from Jackson who presided over Stones trial last year made clear that the judge still is seeking information
About the clemency
Including the actual executive order from the White House
Has not been provided this is 100%
Like this is f****** Lethal Weapon this is like all you're a loose cannon he's doing all the chance I know he's real
If you still have to do the f***
Paperwork
There's some issues here
Possibly be what's keeping Rodger from coming on Infowars
Maybe that's the excuse Rogers giving
But Rodgers and he's not afraid to speak out
On Monday Rodger appeared on Sean Hannity's exclusive
First interview since the commutation of his possibilities
Not hold back
You was talking s*** about the judge and the prosecution all over
The place
The only reason Rodger isn't on Alex's show
Nowadays after the commutation
Is because Rodgers
Choosing not to come on
Maybe it's because he knows better or maybe it's just a thing where he agreed not to appear anywhere beforehand
In return for that
It's hard to know exactly what's up
Alex is not a high priority for Rodger anymore
Alex threw him
Clemency celebration party on Alex's
Alex said Rodger was going to be on the show on Sunday and he didn't show up
Now on Monday Alex claims that he has some kind of inside baseball stuff
Keeping Rodger from coming on
He's totally fine being on the same the same day
This is pathetic
Just grow up and recognize this dude doesn't give a f***
You're not useful anymore
I didn't see any of it cuz I was trying to avoid it in case we wound up
Play eclipse of the interviewer any
I was thinking about it but
The one thing I did
He did thank
And there was multiple
For people that
Was listed
In the article
Strikingly
Is that right
That would have been included in the article very highly
Right
Maybe if it still goes
Stonebanks Alex Jones what grade is it
Forget the name
Robin.
So Alex doesn't have Rodger
For the second and third hour
Not good cause
He does get one call where they discuss the voter fraud and how it's going to be big problem
What's brings up
Sir
The musical
Balance in the male cats are getting voter registration
They're just scraping all names they know of legal
Illegal dead you name it
Angelica about the key addresses of Democrats
Is a fun story and all but a cat
Didn't get a ballot in the mail
Voter registration application in the mail
The dead for twelve years
There's a number of possibilities for what could be going on here
What is it is cat's name
Some kind of registration
And someone scraping list for voter registration drives
The cat was a person
This is plausible considering the cat's name was Cody which could easily be mistaken for a human name
Peace out on the list
If it were mr. fluffy
Automated
Are cats or dogs
Whose name
Orders that they get from like petrified stores and stuff like that
Could be made
Registration Drive
It's a viral story The People recovering because it's Flash
Who knows
First thought that I've I'm having right now is
12 years ago 2008 that's when the internet started getting like
Everybody
Everybody was on
Okay the point where you were signing up for stuff over and over and over you were signing up for so many different things
Surprised
Use my real name for this
I'll just use my
Possibility
Whatever happened
Register to vote
Is it guy wanted to commit voter fraud
Successfully sent into voter registration forms
Since the cat wouldn't have any
Human ID or Wrecker
There's no way that this could have resulted in an illegal vote
Also if the globalist evil plan is to send out ballots in the names of dead cats
The owners of these
The plant
Really stupid
Talk about it
If you were going to do voter fraud particularly on a large-scale this is the last way you would ever do it
Best way would be to register
People through Wayfair
Everyone knows
WinCo
Conspiracy shop
Now this
So
Listcawler
She's confronting Alex
About him saying something about Michael Jack
So what happened
Correct
Alex was talking about everybody
Some topics
You remember Michael Jackson and kids wore masks
Send stuff
Appreciate
Really interested
I'm sticking up for Michael Jack
Events
Second
Because it reveals how Alex responds when he's confronted about something
He doesn't give a s***
I do understand it was just strange how you went from that into Michael Jackson he was in a party
This will quickly become one child over the balcony that was his
He didn't give us children wine and
Something else you said he died
Prince died of
Whatever man
With the network more Christian weekly or Christian Christian to Born Again
We got we got to be we got to be well I mean
Pharmacist
I remember he was a whole bunch.
The same thing as Prince
Thought it was Fentanyl
Greater than
Valium and they got
Do I go off on Michael Jackson all day long.
Not mostly Brian stelter
What are we doing
I don't know if it's
Interesting
Color is bringing up like concrete things that Alex was written about
I don't care
You're not a pharmacist
We have to be a cure
Can you see the distain Alex has for someone bringing up
Like concrete misrepresentation
Doesn't care
A title resigned to the idea that someone would
It's exactly how I would expect him to respond
I said
Cubeatz
Sprite use your facts I'm going to say the same s*** tomorrow at
Dangerous
It's just straight-up telling his audience not to get test
Did ferko
You know they're going to mess with folks that have erected
Well from it
Show me some new special DNA vaccine
Never have a job again
You don't want to be tested
You don't want to be on record having this
Oh yeah yeah exactly
That's good that's a dangerous mentality
You don't want to be pet
Do you want to be tested
Zendaya give you a false positive
And then use that to
The news
Dangerous man
This is
The only thing that makes me think that virus
Has its own consciousness
Can afford to hire
Exactly what you
Good kush
If you were
Things to get worse
Totally know 100%
It's it's
Don't you feel sick with the last thing you should do is know whether you're sick or not
When should be like hey you everybody should get tested so then we can prove with all of our test
No cuz Alex thinks of the testers give you false positive
Covid-19
Save it
He thinks that
What you saying
I can't believe anybody
Vaguely racist comments
Just boring
It's towards the end of the show now and he's getting really introspective
Defensive
About
Some people
These calls are fake
News articles out there
Hey are those fake caller ID
As if I have time and energy to fake stuff
Is it all completely real
So used to fraud
I don't know something real
When they're sick
What's going on
So call in sometime
Experience it for yourself it's real you'll be on are real things are happening this is a real word
I used to think there was a good chance that Alex's callers could be fake
Possibility
Appliance
The reason is because there's so many of the same callers are calling over and over
For themselves
There's a guy named Carlos
Two calls in pretty much every show and Alex is Alex
Looks like it's just like
I don't know what
What's going on
Just let them talk for like 10 minutes
There's also a guy named Chase the Patriot and calls him pretty much every day and he's at least partially doing it to promote his own YouTube
Channel
So there are some real people but I think some of them might have their own agendas mixed in
Regular callers on Alex's show
That's at the reason I pulled back because Alex the saying that he's trying to tell the truth
And trying to figure out what's going on
I'm super offended by that
Because he doesn't even do the least you could do
To figure out what's going on
I tuned into the show and the headline story about the article that headline is from
No way matches with the actual article says
Which strongly implies that Alex hasn't even taken the time to read the
Cozy cover
He said as much many times in the past when it like a stack of paper on his desk and he'll say I've read some of these articles
We recently found the clip with him talking about how we even read all of Carol Quigley's book tragedy
We just supposed to be the foundation of his world
The blueprints of the globalist plan
Alex is not trying to figure out what's going on because he doesn't even do the
Easiest Bank
He could do
We just read the stories he's covering on air
Because I know that's the case
Becomes clear the other thing
But he's trying to tell the truth isn't true
He's a lying about trying to tell the truth
Just just an absolute liar doesn't have the time or energy to fee
Because that sounds like it
The effort and that is not something he's very
Yeah and what he tries to do these like set-pieces they fall apart so I can
If you was intentionally trying to
Fake something Grand
I don't think you could keep up
A bit with a fake call
Sales at Moore
Is regular job
Tries to do a
He can improvise something made up all day long
When there's another person involved
Not good
Weather at night
Whenever they try and do bits
The disaster
If you was trying to do that with a collar it would just
Fall Apart
He could make up thing all day
I forgot to do the news
The oldest coronavirus news
Call so much but I'm out of time won't take your calls or just one taste a lot
The 4th hour
Any over into Gerald Celente
Is big covid news
Cuz he's going to take your phone call
Iceberg
Forgot to Coronavirus
Broadcasting is election Night results
We have taken
Normal boilerplate nonsense about coronavirus
Big nose
If you're going to commit to taking calls I appreciate that at least you're doing that no time for calls
Mike Mike
Consignment
I'm just going to say this is the last day of the big sale
Hey look I want to go to the big coronavirus news but I can't because I've got to go to cause I really want to go
But I got a plug
Maslow's hierarchy of Alex works
Top priority
Alright okay you missed it this time but another 20 down there are you got it the first few times you're doing great
Alright okay so we missed it the second time alright but I'm going to have to get out of here
Bye
Wow I don't even know
I get it you're strong cell shape
I find this so amazing
Looking in on this I know that there's not as much
As I would like
Something that would have just been beating a dead horse insurance is like his racism
Fairly races
Stop trial
Put
This is amazing
2 days
Is amazing
I can't express to you how shocked I am that Rodger.
Didn't show up
Like that to me is such
Eject dance
Sign of the time
Alex has been one of the only people out there being like
Yep free Rodger Stone
On the line
Pissed off
Some of the money was being funneled to Rogers defense fun and stuff like that
It's like
On Monday
It has been days
Rodger has had every opportunity
Call Lynn
5 Second
His failings that
Record something in advance to send to Alex
Dropped everything to pre-record something totally
Rodger
Is clearly not given Alex
Time of day doesn't need him anymore
That's f******
Nuts
I will admit this Stone situation has
I'm past
Weather.
Justice system works
Past that
I find this now hilarious in a schadenfreude way that I
I can't fully Express
The way he's being in the way he's shiting Oliver Alex Minot
That's shot
Embroidery the highest
Do I have to
To keep holding onto and I know maybe I'll look silly for this in hindsight is like I'm sure you'll be there on Tuesday
I haven't been able to listen to schedule when we recorded episodes
But I'm sure
You have to be there on Tuesday
I can see a very easy
Exact an explanation for this
Would never want to talk about and Rodger gave the exclusive to Hannity
Alex's lower on the totem pole
Places that are really actually
You're not here
I don't think Alex well
That's fair that's a good point. The kind of guy who's like at you know you take your lumps
That's got to be brutal for him
It is Egypt
And he celebrated with an exclusive on here
What the f***
Ace
How good that Sheldon
Friday but I bet he'll be on the show on Tuesday but now I mean
It does
Next episode
I can't wait for him not to be there I want Rodger to completely cut ties
Not since doctor houses
Just I want that schadenfreude
Michelin-starred second that I think is actually like
Really shocking
Is the Wayfair
Like in the clear
Entirely
On the 11th
When he got in studio and did his
Yeah
If you have to you can say I didn't say it wasn't something worse case scenario
But you still have the media wants to
To try and say that I was on this b******* that was a Honey Trap
Then
On Sunday for no reason unforced error
Just coming out
This is absolutely what this is
It's real
So bizarre so bizarre
I'm used to seeing
The Democrat
Snatch
Defeat from the Jaws
Victory
And you watch Alex really
Really Steppin s***
Tactically it seems like a really stupid
People should know that
Because he explained decision
Friday or Saturday
More less
So anyway
Rogers on on Tuesday
I will be never
We'll find out
You are a few if you could please
Beautiful. As well
Emilio Emilio on dzx
Clark I'm Rodger
Stones booking agent
Alex