Airjordan.com
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
College fight
Dot-com
About Alex
Joan
George
What's up
What's your bright spots
Coming
Route
Consistent
The app
Open up the mail bag
Does brighten my day quite a bit
Do I end up having sex
Incredible
Over a four pack of
Showing you this boxes package
It does look like a surveillance boxes
Tonic water
Is really nice tonic water
Involved with a flash
If Jen not partaking in the gym
Yeah except for cold gym
Quite a bit
Jim just mascara
It is
Is the only drink
That's all you need to know
Get rid of that whiskey
How dare you from your friends in the UK
Shelters in Suffolk
Maybe we'll do a Q&A episode worry test
Temperature
Shopping mall that are regular
Peggy's vegan hot sauce thank you very much
To these hot sauces and thank you for sending those
Got a lovely
Inside this note
Dear Dan and Jordan
!
All right I just wanted to make sure you get plenty of mail
A wall
That's great
Gmail it shows up like a physical thing
How to make sure you got stuff is about
But my entire life of all happened on the same day
They released the book
And people have responded very well
So many people to the point where
Like
If downloads were Book Sales
I would have an outside on a on a slow week to be on the New York Times best
Amazing that's amazing
Sure that's really cool
A few hours after I released it
I got the news that might be around
For much longer
Tune of
Just a few days
The proudest day of your life suddenly becomes the saddest day
I just I just thought about
She was fine
3 weeks ago
It's going to be you no less than a few days and
This is
All-too-common a situation now
You know it's not covid
She has
Stage 4
Which is
Something that happens
Is j.j.
It doesn't happen because a lunatic stolen
Like all of these family 130,000 family
Are going through what my family is going through right now
End
Unnecessary
I do too just
Just cruel
Just monstrous Mothman real existence
Ain't that the truth
Joker
Jordans
It doesn't get much worse
So I was just
You know
Like I don't know how to be sufficiently
Grieving
This is terrible and and I
I'm a comic so
This is how we deal with it
And enjoy
Do
That's how I cling to it and how I grieve so
Process
But
It is
Lifehack
So sorry it's depressing note the same time
Like I've always dreamed
Possibility
People responding to
So
And it's much as you're connected
And even even though you're
His passing was a tragic
Most likely
There's still a lot of experience
Between
You can hold on to that then
Have celebrate that the part of
What you been up to you and
Hopefully not everything even though it's hard and painful about everything
Time is an illusion
For helping me out
Sure,
Something something
To visit today
Depressing
Live our lives
You know
Be people
Let's do it I'm in I'm in
Alright
Talking about just one day
Rodger Stone
Now it has to happen
I'm sorry to ruin this
Brutal
I mean
It's obviously he signed an exclusive priority
Show where you can convince
Listen to you and zero
First
And get our kind of attention
Or I could go on a show with
Most 100,000 listeners
Not be invited onto any show
My partnership
Was represented by personal lawyer
Exclusive interviews withdraw important
Campaign managers
Comparatively
And the other keeps talking about
Truly connected to it
Person who I would prioritize
But you have to show up
Actually because he can't go on Hannity every week
Harrison Christ during that and I was going to pretend like
It's totally fine yeah but it's not
I feel like this is her to the payoff of our weak narrative
Last week which is
You know it started with Rogers. Right
Alex getting into Wayfair
Conspiracies
Self to be involved in Wayfair conspiracy
Because you know so that I must say
I'm down the street
Alright
That doesn't trust
Sunset
Next
I was assured that was nothing untoward.
Alternative
EXO
So we're all right
Next
Ewok
This is not a title
In the past
This person
Required are not required
I said that I call someone
Alright
I've got a call Nick l
It's a nikhil
Mitchell
Whatever Ellery pronounce
Generosity
In your area that is helping people in need in these trying times
Appreciate
Indeed
So we start off on the 14th
And
Rogers AR
Rogers on
But
Pakistan would have given us exclusive
Yesterday
As you promise me to do
He had
Clarence and
Clemency letter
First
Bad to check
Probation off
Officer
We stopped
Sure you are
Want to give you the exclusive clemency letter
Avenue 1st
You're still a very important
Absolutely
Ridiculous
Does have Rodger on them just playing games you will show up
Bigger heavy-hitter on this episode
We have gym
He's going to be
Not joining us
Jim hoft
Brother Jimmy Hoffa's brother
Jim hoft is the guy who runs Gateway pundit
His brother
Look dude if you are somebody who has like their own reality and their own expertise and reason
Credit
Brother
Is a bad sign
This guy I guess his name I don't even remember where it is used
Somebody was like oh s*** let's listen to this guy
Mean something
Like my brother
Would be not somebody you'd want to talk to you about Alex Jones related issues interesting guy
And he has his own world where he is relevant and you know what
The stuff that he does
I couldn't comment.
Others are you
William size does not imply expertise my brother on
Talking about
Be silly.
Brought up this is Aaron's brother
I don't think that would work well for me
You get justforlaughs you're coming out of Montreal and brother
Aaron Brothers
What have you done
Adorable
Call Sylvia
Further questions about your your Bona fides as whether or not you're worth listening to
The concept of nepotism right over here
This is this is where we're at
Brother
Is that
He kind of made it sound like him and Paul Joseph Watson we're going to do it together so it's like
Uno Taxi
Jump-scare
Nope headspace early on
Any situation where he's born
When is audience
The time will be fast approaching
You'll need to fight
Real-life sure
You need
Engage in Mortal Combat
You will be forced
Take action
Will be poor
To fight for your very life
Because when it was easy to win
What was easy to win
Don't write your own territory your own freedoms
A blood type
You been living off of
All of this largesse
Was money in the bank
It was blood in the bank
Whose Blood Sweat
Pierce
Alex might not realize it but he's using two different words there that just sound the same
He describes
Things
Another word rate is a word that means ceremony or custom
These words are different routes and completely different meetings but they're pronounce the same in English
Treat them as the same
Raichu
That would make more sense
Eght
Also it's weird that he's claiming these rights are fun
Because that's completely out of step with the underpinnings of his Patriot right-wing ideology
Being given by God
The fights that happened in history happened against
Actually take those rights away from you
You in a tyranny or a dictatorship you still have rice
What makes authoritarianism so evil
Is that these people are work
Temporarily deprived
Alex
The blood bank is running dry
That's completely foreign to the angle he's supposed to have
Sounds like he believes that only exist because
Some kind of human sacrifice in the name of Rights
Which is pretty close to what he believes the club
Given their right
To take them away from people of color very out of
Step
The other the larger understanding of these things that are in the right-wing world like
Communities
They believe that these attacks on the ideas of religiosity into separation
God and to get rid of God in society because all right flow from God
Get rid of get rid of beets
Why anyone has right
This entire segment
Is going to be about
How he supports the protesters in Port
As they fight against the federal government sending in agents
Kill them
Right-wing death
Coming into
I don't know
Comes up in any dimension
Portland's adjective word
You talking about white people getting beat up like a BLM
You know like he hasn't covered any of that situation in any meaningful way to the point where I've had
I don't have a good grasp on that situation correct
He's working through here
Different
A new product
Totally not a replacement for a product to use the tool to cancel and I'm bored
Hold the answers more Socialism or communism
More New World Order
Doterra
Enforcers and the jail guards
The New World Order will start
Then the globalist
Because
Humans finally wake up
That's why
The robots
Is that one
The controls
Goose Shack
There
Thirsty
Wait
Dining chairs
So we've moved.
We become independent
Weed
Comply
And we boycott them before we boycott their big company
They are the enemy
Here we go
Smooth
Well it was a whole new product line
Shepherd
Product
Moderate
I wonder
If you're sure is a lot of
Charcoal
And super high-quality Act
Bestop schism
You saw the
Finance
Criminal
Can we just stop selling it so she
Stop saying that
We are planning litigation
Dish
Covid-19
Is activated charcoal a bunch of essential oils
A couple weeks there's one other test
It's a great app.
Until next week
I told you we had
He's not here
What the hell is happening
Super Bowl at maybe illegal
Activated charcoal toothpaste
And we don't
Buzz marketing strategy voice
Testing
But good luck with
We know this from a ways back
He's been getting into
Props lately
I called out for it being extra
But as we know he was on the fence about Satanism maybe Steel
He's got a new prop ignoring it
Alright fine
I'll take the bait
Wings Roman
Standard symbol
Plastic
Store
Double-edged
The side of vans
Everybody
You will not Escape
God is above
Goddess mother
Humans
Life itself
This is a political show
To remind you that None Shall Escape.
Woody's
He's just steal it
He's like that's called feel good
Get rid of the chessboard
Any local theater company will tell you
Weather f****** dick
Anyway Alex
Talking about
Tyrell
China whatever
Rockefellers they're evil
Get to this first
Weather
New York Times article
Zero two of them
You do father
Message
World Travel
I helped put now in on
The answer
So we talked about GameStop but it's been awhile so first of all
B6 David Rockefellers iPad was published on August 10th 1973
Nissan connect
Specifically
He says the Rockefeller says he helped put now into power that he loves now
Communism is what we need
About that
The closest at Rockefeller under Chairman Mao's leadership
Most important and successful in human history
Which is something that was
Short visit
Vagina
If you read the complete article however you get this
Misgivings
About working Celtics.
And multiple Point Rockefeller qualifies his own impression
He says quote
In terms of simple Geographic expanse a week-and-a-half visit to China is something equivalent
New York City in less than one and a half minute
A clear understanding
So as someone who has been in New York for one and a half minutes both New York
Title says hi
Traveler
Later in the article Rockefeller even acknowledges that this view of the country he was getting was a
Curated one
Each step of the trip was choreographed
Precisely by our house
Virtually all our requests were granted
We clearly saw what they wanted us to
He's qualified impression of the country was the progress was being made
Poverty starvation in crime we're at much lower levels than they were 20 years prior
At the same time. The number of children receiving an education have jumped from 20% to eighty percent
At the same time Rockefeller absolutely does not sugarcoat things
As he puts it quotes
Despite constant impressions of progress however some gray areas in basic contradiction
Three major questions remain in my own mind
The first question was about individuality and creativity being contained
The country
There are only eight different theatrical
The entire country
Universities are rigorously politicized with little room for inquiry unrelated to Chairman Mao's thought
Rockefeller view that is a
Problem
The second question is how well the Chinese economy would be able to adapt to technological advancement
Foreign trade
This is largely a strategic and logistical Quest
Question
The third question is
Are we prepared to accept our differences
And still proceed toward be closer Mutual understanding that must be the basis
For substitute future Conte
And the inserts
That was m
Emphatically
Outside
Both America and China would likely need to make a
Candid world
None of the stuff Alex is saying about these operators real
Alex knows what this article is what he's heard about it from paranoid jumper Society pamphlet switch
You're basically no connection to reality
And you can
You can take
You know a perspective of
You know Rockefeller had all the information that could possibly ever
To someone
In 1973 at a time when Chinese us relations were
Information was not what it is
You hate Turf now go back to 1973
Awareness
What could have been
Everybody every point
It's kind of frustrating I mean I don't care about David Rockefeller I think it probably was
Nautica
Aspect of having that much money
Probably
Almost certainly
Springs up
Of course so
Cherishable position
You're lying about the Rockefeller or whatever
Rockefeller
Episode
Defensive
Let's get to this first
Column just like they done
Country months before they're just still
Alex is a goddamn liar
No one is moving slow.
Covid-19
Going way down
Go to July
Flu season is pretty much over by May
Will see an uptick in flu cases in the United States another few months
Alex knows that
And he's lying about it or he doesn't know that
If you don't understand when
Flu season is
You're trying to say flute down and it somehow suspicious
You are unqualified or alive
One of the two
It's
No third option
Intuit
Increasingly on
Like any kind of
Conspiracy of that sort that
Pull-off
We're a long ways
You're not going to get me on pneumonia
You didn't get me before y'all definitely are going to get me after flu
So Alex
Hysteria going on in the world is a lot of
A lot of Hysteria
Any place
Play some clips
Demonstrated
I'm I'm done playing this
Cuz I I largely
Wanted
First thing I want
Want to go ahead
For you
Is the Hysteria
What's going on
Video of
JW
Yale's who are
Passengers
Kill
Everybody on this plane
Unless you accept
Jesus was black
Then we'll play
The clip
Here
BLM protester leader
Calls for black militia
Revolution
What is flips
Like what to make other than race-baiting
Like what
Bye
These selection in the curating of
Topix
These bullet
What is
What what can be the editorial through-line of a lot of this stuff other than
Be scared of black
Call BLM sjw
D.b. Cooper
And that is who they are and that's how we do it by drive to do
Wow yeah you didn't know that.
Got stuff
Jumped off
Right left
Guys black Jesus
Into the Night
Right
Find
Some of this to be
Trivial
You know okay that's an interesting story I guess I didn't even look into this person on the plane I don't I don't know what the story is
Is there
Case scenario of that is
Kill people on a plane
Matter person saying that there should be black malicious favor of that
Synchronize
Federal government
Right
Whatever
So some of this stuff would be a little bit more
Like
This is really difficult to put in
Like there's moments in Alex's show where
His lack of doing any work
Separation
Accidentally reveals how little he knows about the world and this next clip is one of those that I think it's just like
You shouldn't do it you shouldn't allow yourself to be put into
Situations where you look
Ignoramuses
Black Riders
Nikon
Haley
Sally
It goes on
From there
A couple of interesting things
The first is that Alex has no idea Holly Selassie
Emperor of Ethiopia from 1930 to 1974
I need the central figure in the roster
Geology
You can't possibly listen to any decent
We're going to be okay
Is inconceivable to me that Alex would have no idea what
Unreal knocked over and assumes that it must be connected to
Statue is right about
Brookside thinking
Because there's no reason to assume that just because one group wants to take down certain statues
All statue related stories must be involved with that group
Reporting I can find about the Statue it appears that this one was destroyed in an event it's most likely related to honor
Unrest in Ethiopia
According to the BBC this has to do with the killing of a popular musician
Condesa
Odessa was a big proponent of the Oromo rights which is an ethnic
The group that were oppressed by philosophies regime
A witness saw men gathering in the park in London where the Selassie statue was
Curing Flyers with Oromo slogan
Switch gives a pretty strong indication that this is what
His story is about in this
Shannon this case
Lee statue Selassie was father one of those was recently tore down in Harare dvop
And the reason there was this statue in London
Was because he'd lived in Wimbledon when he was in Exile in 1936
Statue
Unrelated to the larger phenomenon of bll related statue issues but
Let me room for nuance in Alex's show
If it's about a statue
The same story
And it's about a guy named Cecilia
You know I mean
Statues
Is generally speaking
Average
Precious and people who oppressed people are the ones most interested in getting statues
There is a desire among
Despot
And the autocrat
Effigies of themselves
So talking about
Rodger coming on over about 2
In order for this to really make sense
Still got to be important
Right I mean
It better
The juice qualify
Garage screen
Rodger
Herein
Just a moment
In a second
Very
Exclusive
He will have
The election is clemency being attached
This is the first exclusive
Energy
Just keep adding
21st
Exclusively
458 episode of our podcast
Truth
Coming on for the first time after
Nobody is done that
Pretty much
It's honestly not the best hour of Rogers
Life
Dammit he's
Well he doesn't waggling his dick he's supposed to be because of his becoming too
Do you know Alexa
Doesn't want revenge on people now because of religion
He does think it was an act of God Trump carried out
Received
Sure
So tonight
This next
Termite down because
There's a big
Proud
Now granted
Rodger the bird
This is a big deal
Right
Rodger is talking about how he's
These are the ones who should be on trial
And I
Response
First edition
Is going to do that
Everything you said is true one on record
Incredible
Alex's eating blood
Review
It is so fun
So clearly now
The subtle
That's the fun part
Now that we're this it look
We're too immersed to enjoy this small step this surface-level step perhaps
Real f*** you
I really wish the Rodger
Status to pull that off
Rodger Rodger claims
Fox News
And some censorship issues
Before I wake
The producer came
Mr. Stone
Under no circumstances can you mention
Related
This makes no sense to me
Explain why that would be the case
Oh yeah never bring up Soros
The
I can't think of any possible reason
George Soros
You couldn't
Stop yourself if you tried
Well let's see if I can
Can just do a little Google
Soccer claims George soros's what do we got here
George soros's quote
Shadow
What are you doing
Some deep research
This one required to your level
Mention George Soros
So
I think you knew that he had to come with
Something to make this occasion special
Because
Obviously you don't
That was pretty
Totally not a weirdo
Nothing
Get on Hannity
You don't
If you're not willing to do that and he probably doesn't have time for you
Alex on the other hand is
You can maybe give him a world's greatest
Love it
Bianox
So here's a here's what Alex get to the consolation prize
Being completely kicked to the curb by Rodger
Impatient
It is
Historic moment
Saved my life
Signature
You can say
The act of Mercy
Who knows I was subjected to a Soviet
Before
Lynching
So I mean like
Electricity
My Moment
Europeanhistory
I'm really bummed
Got the real thing
I don't know
Until he was on Hannity
Time
Ticket
That's what is really going on here that's the biggest
Did you hear did you hear any
A brass band Studio
Awesome celebrate the historic
Instead we just
Pretend and Alex eats a piece of sandwich
Big time coming to God
Well when I thought I was going to go to prison my lawyer advised me that I might get a more lenient Maybe
If I pretended I believed
How good a demonstration it is about Alex's bad planning
Literally overnight
Opportunity
I jumped
He gave me the most advice you could
If you could get anybody said
Your rights on you're in big trouble but if you will just
Confess your sins if you will be reborn
If you will get right with Christ
If you will reaffirm your commitment
Do your nickel
I feel like you don't ask somebody about something really
Important a big
Story like how did your life changed except
Did Christ
Zealous religious broadcast
The break break
The processor
It's not just like girls
Nobody played off my testimony
Opening out of a break as opposed to when you're gonna run out of time cuz
Disrespectful to the story that Rogers telling
It implies that you don't really care that much yourself if you would put Rodger in a situation where you might have to interrupt
Story
What letter Borden
Is all the time
Cuz I get it there's a lot of fish now.
So indecisive and
Is the answer to prayers
Jesus is here
Our Lord and savior
A day later
All the stories about
Hit the fan
Information
Journalist Asylum
Story and it was everywhere
Alex is going to be pissed
Pittsboro pet story
This is not
Now where you want to give credit
Loving that he is no longer
Kissing
Alex Azar
It's pretty subtle though
Now this next
But I feel like out
Cannot enjoy hearing this next clip
This discussion of what was going on on the day that Rodger got the news about the commutation
Last Friday around 5
Many media Outlets
ABC was a bomb
The same reports it popped up
Previous
Clear
Patriots
Conservative
Republican Party
Run info Warriors
Under I was under
We sorted people out
Between
They were allowed to come in
To where I just
Instigating
This is the White House
Speak to Rodger Stone
The White House is
Around the time
There was no Infowars reporter
Somebody else
A f****** cellphone to be a reporter on the scene unit
2 days before
Like Stone
I told him
Well I mean look this is
This is Imagine
Missed out on the
Party of the century
Allowed in
Woodworm ask for that
Keyboard for that kind of exposure
So you brought up in our last episode
How conspicuous it was
Better
Rodger didn't think Alex
Infowars
It's quite the office
Amazing
So many people
Dead
You were there
Deep sense
What's this
Exactly right which is
Overplay how important Infowars is elsewhere
Infowars other places to miniature the value of whatever you're getting out of
At the same time
You can't afford to get too mad at you for not thinking about swear
Is it on like I imagine that when
When Hannity introduced him
Introduced to meds
Somebody who works
Infowars
Appositive
Just booked for $100
On Infowars where he worked for a long time
We have Rodger Stone Brothers brother
Better Credit
Speaking 24
In my corner
Franklin Graham
I just think that's pretty funny
Rogers Hardware
He's using the first person plural
You stalking
Oh boy threw himself as a part of Infowars now
The truth
Infowars is really still
So I
You can bet
Because
To silence
Babel
Something that I have not done in the past actually had to admit that I had lied about a guy
$400
Ideas
Kept within this area so that's why
When I went on Sean Hannity a show with Millions upon outside
We are Infowars
As far as I could
Probably smart
I wonder
Virtually
I will be Avenged
I need money
Different fundraising website
He leaves and Alex gets back to talking about this
F****** toothpaste
And I can't
You really want to sell this toothpick but he can't
Eventually it'll be great
Play Stanford few weeks
We are
Supposed to do on it
Adorable
I thought
This week
Would be the week
To sell
All of this
Not able
Tell the original sale that I had running
It's just going to keep running
Until next week
Appreciate
Do all things
Launching
Christmas in July sale
Free shipping a double Patriot points
Percent off
I'm not sure
Christmas in July sale
Christmas isn't supposed to be commercialized
And it's not
Jesus
If you're only interesting Christmas is the sales aspect looking for a mattress store then it makes sense to have a Christmas in July sale beak
Importance of the holidays by cutting field
Alex
This is almost sacrilege
There can't be a Christmas in July because
Christmas is a holy day significant
After sales
Christmas is in the year in the same way there are two Jesus Christ
This doesn't really seem like a sale that anybody takes their face seriously
Pretend stupid
Possibly
This is using religion to drive sales not a sale that just happens to coincide with a religious
Just leave base but also secularly
Celebrated holiday
I assume one of those movie no skin in the game just an impartial Observer
Seems to me that this kind of thing
Having a Christmas in July sale that's more of an affront to religious observance then someone saying happy holidays in December
Which I was considered a war on Christmas
Is it not a war on Christmas to water the holiday down by creating your own second Christmas that isn't even halfway through the year
He's two weeks late for the halfway point to be
I don't know
Yeah I find that to be sacrilegious
Yeah well
Pretty sure at how we didn't play the whole thing off
Part the part that Rodger was cut off
What he said was the day after I
Recommitted myself to cry
Really knew that it was time to make some cow
The Lord spoke to me and he said
We've got to do Christmas in July second Christmas apps
Salute
So Alex has a big news
Do discus still not real
Apparently not
Smoking Gun
Infowars.com
Numerous lab 333
100% of people testing positive
Coronavirus in Florida that is impossible
He's actually true but it doesn't mean it
E470 for labs
Florida reported a hundred percent positive
Story
These lands were testing people who came up negative
This might seem like it would affect the overall positive rate in the state
71%
Of the state's testing numbers
Results were in line with the other 99% of
It would quote
Result in the state's 11% overall positive rate falling to 10.9%
An insignificant difference
That's huge the Florida Department of Health Florida
In recent days the Florida Department of Health noticed that some smaller private Labs weren't reporting negative test results
Add data to the state
The department immediately began working with those labs to ensure that all results were being reported in order to provide comprehensive
Teradata
Continues to receive results from various labs
The department will continue educating these Labs on proper protocol for reporting covid-19 test results
One of the issues here appears to be bad messaging from the
The state of what is expected in pandemic
These were smaller private Labs who might have been unaware of what they needed to do
You see when there's no pandemic going to report positive cases for specified
Diseases
That are being tracked
But as it turns out
When there is a negative
The message just wasn't being spread universally that they needed to do this
Is this
There were a number of lads who were just simply doing what the
Defaulters would you send
Negative
Underhanded
I think that's kind of what they were doing
Before this started
This isn't a conspiracy
It's another symptom of widespread mismanagement of the response to an outfit
People aren't on the same page and that leads to some folks operating out of step with how they should
Awesome completely unknowingly
Ultimately it's important please negative tests
Reported as well because it's crucial that the most accurate information possible
But people who look at the rod
Have a significant impact on the larger
Things are pretty out of control
In Florida
So
Bad
Smoking Gun
The Great Smoke
Great you proved
Alex gets
Rights
I forgot about that
I'm going to pretend it's Jimmy Hoffa's might be what kind of broke me in terms of caring about the 4th hour
You're disappointing interview with Rodger and pretend like he would have given you the papers
Dud of a covid-19
Then you're going to bring in gym
Brother
I'm out
I'm out buddy
Really funny
Chillhop
I'm just shaking my head
So sad
What's the saddest thing you can do to a song yeah it is that is pretty sad
Any song
Johanna
Dad suck
I reserved
Does not matter what the
Joe hop Hip Hop
Yeah he's onto largely do a lot of like covid
Denialism
Stop
Centers around this story out of Florida
Further than just Soto
Using the story of the Prophet outright lies about
Iraq
And 333 labs this earlier
Florida
100%
Killers
What's really going on here
Number of average test these labs
In Florida there's no Source he could be siding
To back that up
Other than maybe something saw like on Twitter or something but
Fox 35 Orlando the actual documents of the
Specific numbers in
Fuel City highest number of test run at any of these Labs that are reporting 100% positive cases
Is 400
At the Lee Memorial Hospital
And pancare of Florida
That's nothing compared to the 540,000 816 test that were done by Quest Diagnostics
4450 5636 done by LabCorp
Hundred percent positive results are under 100 test recorded
It's all good but if they hadn't reported or if
Actual number of tire
Gross number is actually
It's the only thing you could
What's not fair is just to make up whatever number you think
Number might be and then reported it
Which is what our
Foxes doing
Alex numbers
The Creator. About this Bob story
Means that he's a pile of s*** just like his brother and not somebody who needs
Seriously like
What
That means that you're invested in playing along with the fake version
Yeah you know what else the fact that you don't have a name means go suck your
I don't I don't I don't respect him enough to even know if Joe was the right name
Is that
Pretty anti-vax
Individual
Kennedy Junior
We covered that story a while back when it was relevant irrelevant
He's promoting Robert Kennedy Jr
Is about
So what are the main things that is very difficult to get around
If you are a covid denial list
Is the phenomenon
Covid-19
This year compared
This year
Especially related
Closest
The graph showing
Claim
Butler
Sears numbers
Flatline
We're going to be putting it up here shortly
Information
Little kids cheap
Tell people what you're about to break
We've hired a
Actuary
You're doing the same thing I guess
PhD status
Yep
So what'd he say
On July 1st the Journal of the American Medical Association released an investigation in there
Their imprint called Internal Medicine
Would you look at the excess deaths in the u.s.
Between March and may 2020
They found it all cause death Rose by approximately 120,000
Did the United States over that time.
Compared to the same period in previous years
There were only 90 5235
Which meant that the excess mortality in the country represented a number that
Percent higher
Unofficial figures that have been like
Covid-19
Who can be difficult for Alex and his newly hired imaginary statistician to work around
And by that I mean the worst
How you slice it the numbers of all-cause mortality in this country are
10% higher during the. Of the pandemic
That was study
This line
He is going to go nowhere
It's just it's just a dud
We should not be listening to medical doctor
Well we should be listening to doctors of philosophy
We should be listening to Brothers of doctors
Jesus
How is the world
Exist now in a place of like
Oh you got experts
I got experts doesn't matter what my experts AIG
Sounding good credential
Good sounding
Sacred
And then
Just you let hey okay
Consortium
Everybody is an expert in cool
That's equal to this what do you call them climate to climate what scientist
Saturday night stand with that get out of here
It's mast
Triumph
Explain away this this increase
I think it's bad
I think it's not going to work
Why is New York
A few areas in Michigan
They're blue cities and states
Where they intubate
Nursing homes knowing
Is it was premeditated please talk about that
Republic
This isn't going to work as an argument there is currently over 100,000 deaths that haven't been in New York in Mission
Depart
Also Jim half-brother is reviewing the video
Here
Is it is true that there's a double chance of dying of covid-19 in blue States as opposed to Red States
Maybe you should look for what up Factor might be involved there
Maybe population density is different in these states maybe blue states include more Metropolitan Urban centers than Reds
States which have different patterns of transmission
I mean this sincerely
Dear someone like Jim Hopper brother saying stuff like that then you're free to tune him out entirely
If he's willing to make that kind of blind leap in order to justify his narrative
He's not living in reality and whatever all this stuff is
It's just both
Yeah I chanteys Jim hoft brother
Where is Parsonsburg cardboard cutout that Alex is talking
Going to and it's okay
Can't like the only thing I found
How long can you keep
You have to say
I can't keep doing this
You know
Like where does this end
This is the end after we get it if it if it doesn't in before we get a vaccine going to end after week
Vaccine I don't know man
I mean this is this is insane how can they keep this going this long I don't know
I don't know
Intuitively I would have told you way before now ofcourse that's what my gut would have told me is like
You're going to have to try and get right with it
Correct the underlying assumption
Beverly Sanders the harder they seem to.
Dig their heads into
31 waist clip here and it's about where I checked out because Alex
Discontinued
Continuing to race bait
Surrounding
This story from Indianapolis.
Alright
I just listened to you talk to Jim hoft
Brother put up with Vivian
If you like 3 hours of your show today
Yourself look at these headlines
Blm's
Supporters celebrate
As a mother
Shot
For saying all lives matter
When confronted by
Facebook
Person
Totally
Let me just go ahead start over with us.
Let's just focus
Real person that got
We're going to sit here for Mama
Somebody that died
I think about that
For just a second
Because the Bible
Nicki Minaj
Yeah it's a mess
I mean he's just basically Rewritten this entire story and
Is now using it to push his
Very racist
Agenda
The article that he was talking about you know like his dad want celebrating this picture
A couple of comments
Online
Bill Maher
It's the same if I had
The kind of patients or any beliefs
Through all the comments on Infowars
People using the n-word
I can find I could find any horrifying thing that you want me to find Courthouse
Or people who are in Fort Worth
I think that would be committing a composition fallacy
He's somehow indicative of what
This white victimhood Narrative of if you dare say that
Matter
It's just b******* it's 8
Find it abhorrent
And disgusting
We got there earlier
Something interesting becomes a
Desert going to cut bait and where I
Cuz it's also really repetitive
Really repetitive
In a lot of ways
Like that it's
It's a long story
You know he's repeating at 13 comes up a couple times there's
The story about the
Florida labs
Citrus over and over
It's very boring
The constant repetition of the same
Coronavirus narrative
In the same
They're going to
Destroy everybody kind of s***
I just think you know like we have to we have to come full circle
With Rodger finally showing up
And
I'm kind of insulting Alex
Discussing how
Cernovich broke that story and how we had a house party tour aware of
Alex and eating during the interview recorded cutting him off with a commercial raise the middle child
Have to stretch out over week
Text we can just have the
Episode of this week on the show we have the
The conclusion of the stunning conclusion
Piece of s***
Better
The Rodger definitely out of Alex
But doesn't care about him all that much
And I think he's fruit
Clearly indicate the Rodger would rather be elsewhere if there is a higher degree of
We can get out of it
Thank you Alex you set up a bit
I think God
Nobody care about you anymore
Thank you
Grow up in some other dick
Bishop
That's usually a good
Rodger Stones entire career is evidence of don't make friends with Rodger Stone
Insane
I don't know
Monday or something or other
Stripe.com
And my book is at the quiet part
Twitter
We are very devilish I just really real and if you could please find a local charity
PPL outage
Jim hoft brother
Alex
In color