Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for knowledge but I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guy
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Son of dentist
David Bowie absolute
Haha
I just noticed that I have
Couch
I build this this couch that I ordered
I noticed they wanted the back pieces was broke
I was trying to install an actually stabbed myself in between
Papercut
Tablet
Couch has no good how many people out there but stabbed by couches
Stab back out
I needed to get a replacement part for it
Obviously
I ordered this couch from Wayfair
I should say that I ordered it book
This was I can confirm it was ordered
Turns out there was a child inside of that couch on the couch
Before these conspiracy started going around and
Hope it doesn't delay the couch furniture
Kman
Terrible customer service
And I called the Wayfair customer service people and of course because of stuff
There was a delay for a good 25 minutes or so
What is soon as I started talking
Did somebody eat the guy was like I am so sorry that's the girl we can do rest another park to me
Without me asking
20% off the couch
The best customer service experience
I can't I
Hey if you sell kids you sell kid but I'm going to be a great customer service
Theories are true and exact
I think it Wayfair might be my favorite company
I had to deal with
Small companies
I really had to deal with customer service with
But they were above and beyond
Let's figure out
Illinois
Decided
That I'm just
Go for it
Probably Flexeril question to ask but
Kohl's about that conspiracy stuff
Askreddit
Do you know where was very diplomatic
Saying something wrong
You got to be
Sort of delicate
I will say that I have gotten
What how much of a bumper
Selling it as job
Treated me as a customer
Sowell
Still have to deal with
Like people calling in and making accusation
Make some fake conspiracy theories
Make those people have to deal with life
Comcast
Absolutely probably sells children will die
Why they're all named so stupidly that I have with that is people who are answering those
Don't deserve that
Like to have people calling accuse them and yell at them but stuff
It's not their fault other people to call Snyder's fault
I don't want I don't want it to be directed towards them at all Universal basic income
After you get what you deserve no no no no.
I was dealing with customer
Surprisingly
Considering
How about you very nice things
Condolence
My aunt did died Friday morning
I'm sorry
That was back
Back Friday morning so that's that's all
At least
Complete
So that is what is thank you to everybody who isn't very nice
Empire
Cardinal I forward that on to you from
Yes your answer
Listener Mary Catherine
That's a very nice
That's very very nice
So sorry that you had quite a weekend
Families Rustin don't do it don't do it
See I'm coming just to be I'm coming around on the other side of it I'm starting to actually like my family a bit more
As I grow slightly healthier
But I certainly understand the situation
That you're good dude
Describing
Clapping
Yeah
It was necessary for your sake on Friday
Have another episode
Much fun without you
I'm just you know if you're if you're going through something
Sometime that's all it takes
I am great
I don't know what to tell you. Is there nothing to tell me that stone is tossed and round
Open today
Fireworks
So here's the thing this is not going to help
Alex
What is today
You gone out Sunday yet
David Knight Alex called
Tomorrow thinking well this would be great for their Wednesday episode that's not how we record Alex I mean I don't know what's going on
But it's
Really suspicious playing breaks around us but
Okay
How many area that we had to take some pretty short notice
Very short about Alex's
Monday Sunday Monday Tuesday
What's 3
A month ago
We had to take some little time off
Listening we might be the only people listening
What's the point of him doing his show
If he doesn't look I'm not going to do a stand-up show 20 people
People in the audience knowledge hecklers
Immeasurably take the ark formally elevated very slightly
I don't know I don't know what to say
I'm starting to like
If I was a little bit nuttier I would really be
I'm not that into ascribing important
Selling a cabinet named Emery
Oh
I don't know
Do you last one he did before you last July 7th
20 20 20 20
Anderson
The more you said
The year has gotten
Yeah maybe there is something to I should probably stop at
Fortunate
Ignorant
I hope not
I certainly hope not
Comes to be
Then I need to get back
Into mindfulness meditation
Alright well anyway we're going to go to episode
And it's
Stupid
And at the end
Gets really really inappropriate and very f***** up
Anyway that I probably normally wouldn't cover because they're honestly
I don't know what to do with it
This situation anymore
That I generally are on the side of not cover
I don't know what to do anymore I don't know I still have
A little bit of an uncertain
Exactly how to deal with things
How to treat him as a media entity
Like like
Constantly pushing him to the Forefront in having him on his show
I don't know how I give a free pass
I don't know how
I don't I don't know if you would like 15
100-percent ignore
I would absolutely
Ostensibly in adults
I don't know what to do anyway we'll talk about that
Thanks Kevin
Before we get down to business
The first captain mutton-chop
I'm a policy wonk
Accu
Text Keith
Shaheem B
All one word
Journal about
Expert
K
I'm a policy wonk
First of all
Thank you so much
And Matthew see
Heroin
Play large
And thank you so much
A little bit
Apology to make to you
To myself
To the audience
I unfortunately
Due to
Carelessness
Sloppiness
Lack of rigidity in my work
Workflow
I lost
A
Human Arc
So that we recorded
It was about 2 hours long
Pissed off that I lost it because
We told the story of how we met I discussed a lot of stuff about my
In hip-hop when I was younger
Exhausted encyclopedic details about anticon records
All sorts of nonsense
Yeah and then also
We did a taste-testing of Peggy's vegan Hospital
And we had such a revelatory you realize that you love
I love I love every one of those hot dogs and I was fine you thought that you couldn't handle them but we had we had
Really hot
Versions of Scouts and you were just fine and enjoying it
I thought that was great and then also avocado
I can't find the audio
Be able to find it one day that I have
Don't know where it is
Don't look
Dab Izakaya
Possible that it's somewhere
But I can't Bank on that
And I feel really bad about that because I really would have loved to share that with the listener
But there's a second reason and that is because there were a bunch of shout outs for listeners
Owners on it
And I didn't
Keep
A record of the names that we shouted out on that
Female robots
So here's what I want to say
We are behind on shoutouts and we're working to get
Closer to Curran
Unfortunately one of those ways was
There was that
We have
Some plans to be able to get closer to current
Because of losing the Steven A episode
I do not know
Some names
Let me try.
So if you were listening
And you haven't heard your name
Guys shout it out
Before May 15th
Please send an email to Nala try to gmail.com
And I'll expedite it to the front of the row
Make sure that make everything right
I'm not good at need to get better I need to rest
The world the rest of the podcasting world is just like
Thanks everyone for donut
That's what they say that's what they do a shot ourselves in the foot before you ever
I like playing drops of Alexei funny things
Android
That
Respect
Please
Free cam and
We'll try to do that of course
Now Jordan
I do think
You you mention
This earlier
And I do think it is
And that is over the weekend
Maybe
Exactly what they was over the weekend
RadioShack
Rodger
Pretending
A person
Right
Yes
What happened
He'll reach the phone of Rochester
Why don't I
If you would like to be rats
Please leave your name at the end of the beach
I did
Is the Oak and one of the terrifying
Assertive reality
The joke is
Is this would be great
Qdoba
The reality is like
This
Is
Indicative
Like
Casual
Flippin use of these sorts of
You know like hey you know anybody can pretend like not a hard-r or something important
But you know why you're sitting there you didn't say I don't want to argue with this guy
You you said you Rodger said that word for a reason
I don't know why you had Rodger Stone on your show
Other than to say
What he did
Everybody got
It's all bulshit
I was so mad that people I don't know why you have Rodger
Yeah I think I think it's not necessarily the best
I can see why he is of
In terms of the news
You're allowed to get a little comp
Rotational
I don't I don't know if it's the worst
Cinemaworld I don't know why you don't like I don't know what you expect to get out of it
Like also look what question was that
Why would you bother answering a question that you already know the answer to Rodger Stone indicted why would you ask
Rodger Stone has been on a please Trump I have been your friend I will do anything for you give
Give me a pardon or a commutation
For a long time and then he got it
Course he got it cuz he's his friend
That would make Rodger have to be like
Well I think this was just as being up we all know
He got it yeah but I think that's why
Smoking a little bit
Rodger saying to someone who speaks can't be her.
I don't want to argue with this
For both parties involved
What is somebody going to think differently of Rodger Stone
Yeah
I understand
I think it's shocking because of the casualties
Rodger
Offensive language
I think it's
This world
You're free you have to at this point
How do you not feel like you're untouchable
You can't change anybody's opinion of you and you literally cannot go to jail
State charging
Robin f******
StarTribune
ASP Airport
We'll check in periodically whenever
It wasn't him
Was it wasn't a Tommy Franco
The great Rodger Rodger
So we jump in here on Friday 7
17th and
Things that are in the news
Certainly
Portland
I also
Oh yeah that's right about how people
At their Twitter
Or was it
Twitter has happened
Camo
Cover
For it was really behind what's going on you better believe
Patriots
Dammit
You are
Directions
Intelligent
Cover Ben Alex because of who got their account
Alex is making the
Oh man
There's a good guy than
Would try and fake more than Jeff Bezos
Give money away
Alex's take on this will end up being like he was a good guy letting them know they've got all of their GM
Yeah they've got a little bit more later we'll talk about it then
Thunder
God okay every second
Is precious
Lauderdale theme that's going on here with Alex
Eddie's are wasting a lot of sex
Episode
Is
Not good
It's really
Job
It's not like drunk he doesn't appear to be high or anything like that just like
Something off about him
And I don't know what it is
And it just turned me the f*** off
To be rough
So much unfolding
Time
That we are all in our
Is
People
Are ready
To hear
The truth
America
Global Consortium
Literally trying to make
Forever
Do you really want
You again
Associate
You would want
Almost no one is going to get more power
They're doing it
Empower
Investments in around system because
They are slaves
Operation
The police think about visiting infowarsstore.com
Christmas in July sale
What the f***
So I don't I don't know
Chicago rhythm
About his
Way of being
Call Michelle I can't even
Messerli setting something up or
Anyting
I just don't know what's going on there's there's something there was a Feeling
It made me uncomfortable
But make what makes
Is it out to the gas
Pretty early on
Millennial Millie
Millie Weaver
Rainbow snacks okay here we go
I don't know if
Her investigation into the sunshine movement is born fruit yet Sunshine movement
Jeezy I don't even forgotten
You don't even remember I didn't remember him
The entire server and they were
Through it
Talk about it a tiny bit if she still got a mole
The inside
I don't know I don't know what's going on
Come on out to the show and really break down any specific
I don't know what's going on I'm going to guess it's nothing
So far
If she's dropping Michelle's and they still haven't figured out who the mole
Either bizarre Bob shows
There is no Bowl
Or some type of I don't care
They probably don't
I would say all three
He's really dumb and here's one of those
They talked about also Alex is that they actually believe
That covid-19
Is a result of climate change
So they include that in their eyes part
Climate Justice
Covid-19
The climate change caused it we've got to make
They also say the covid-19
He's going to teach us to lower our carbon footprint
Demille's talking about climate
Rainbow snake
Secretly a radical
If you get selected climate change
I want to force you to use different light bulbs
There's something very stupid and very difficult to listen
I pulled out that clip though because I felt like it really well capture the insincerity and lack of curiosity in the right wing
Particularly
Anointed themselves as the people in the world are responsible for conveying information
If we're to believe rainbow snatch
She saw some Democrats
Connecting climate change to covid-19
And her response to that
Exploring any further
Remember condescending as to give the audience the permission to reject the idea as well
Without doing any further analysis
What kind of idiot would say that the weather effects
Viruses
A week ago I said that when it gets hot viruses don't work anymore
So what's the
The person who is taking on the job of disseminating information
Something I feel like it's their job to actually understand the topics
I would do anything
Match could not explain why can I covid-19 climate change
And I would further back than
Never even crossed your mind that you should look into it for the stuffing
The connection decided it was Libera lunacy and moved on
If you cared about the reality she could have learned something by actually engaging with material and reading up on the subject which is actually really important
This topic
In terms of the future of the planet
If you wanted a nice boil down to the topics you could have read propublica's piece from May 7th titled how climb
Climate change is contributing to skyrocketing rates of infection
Just disease
The number one threat to humans in terms of unknown and undiscovered in Texas
These are animals
The live in habitats
Wild and remote places Out Of Reach of human
Under ideal circumstances the animals
Like certain
Bats that carry diseases in humans
Contact with most of them
Under normal circumstances
Very small risks
People
Human host whatever they're carrying
However there are a couple Trends have been happening as things that make the world we live in not ideal
The first is they were engaging in massive deforestation around the world seek
Make money
The second is climate change making previous habitats inhospitable to animals causing them
To move like to seek out new sources of water and food or just
The living
Sometimes because of these moves
These two forces combined to increase the chances that infectious diseases will be in closer proximity
Human settlement
Also increase the likelihood of them inspecting a person in Kazakh
This is a very real
Concern
It's not even the entirety the concern from climate change
Propublica article
Roughly 60% of new pathogens come from animals
Including those pressure by diversity lost
Can be directly attributed to change
The introduction of farming
Development or resource extraction and otherwise
Natural settings
Vector-borne diseases those carried by insects like mosquitoes and ticks and transferred in the blood
Precipitation
Vulnerable
Climate is even bringing old viruses back from the dead
Zombie Contagion
Like the anthrax released from Frozen reindeer in 26
Which came down from the Arctic
Contest from the past
Awesome new idea the people just tried it out because of covid-19
You can easily find a retrospective study in the journal environment
International from January 2016 which
Discusses me history of scholarly literature on the connection between climate change
Human infections
Diseases
If you read even a little bit of the information on the subject it honestly starts to become laughable that anyone would think it would be possible for
Climate changes
Not affect infectious disease
Princeton
Why is there certain seasons for diseases
If the seasons shift a little bit
Is just like
General vibe
Right right
It's a sort of like you know I just know
They would have let
Rudolph playing those f****** reindeer gay
And instead they all got that's what happens that's the story they don't want you to tell
Oh no
Jesus
Like you could have The Wallflowers guide my sleigh
Exact one headlight
That I'd like rainbow snatch to think about
Pathogen needs a certain temperature range
I survived
Second
Jamaica has shifted precipitation
Which reflects the dissemination of water-borne package
Pathogens of Airborne infectious
Diseases such as influenza tend to be responsive to humidity conditions
For example absolute humidity and temperature were found to affect influenza virus Transmission in survival
The factors related to
The climate on and on
In terms of infectious diseases
It's a very large
I know I know that you
Of course
She's mocking this idea
Lauren treating it like oh you don't understand
You must not understand
Otherwise
Wheatley
Completely blindsided by the idea that we live in a global ecos
One thing even though you think it's on one button
You think is unrelated
Every other but
Compressed actually sets off a
Chain reaction of button presses
Leading to consequences that you cannot understand
Unless you I don't know
Dedicate your life to studying
It seems to me for this to be true
You learn to be true or this like mocking of this connection to be true
She must like taking issue with all germ Theory
More or less
Complete denial of
Germ Theory
Very weird
In terms of Public Health
Rainbow snatch wants to come on
Find it kind of difficult
When I say that these people like me
When they encounter an idea that seems like a problem for their work
The immediately decide the ideas liberal nonsense and then make up their own story about it that's not good work
That's why when Alex arachis decided to
That's what all the people
Does not surprise me every interview
One of his major credit
Former Infowars
Rodger Stone
Position
Kind of silly if you're like we're having former Infowars house Rodger Stone
Yeah every single introduction
For every interview shooting clued about a guy
On Infowars
Anything other than
Slinging pile of s***
So anyway talk a little bit more about stupid things
And that
Alex doesn't want Trump to do a virtual
Convention because
He's strong
Now the Democrats are going to do a virtual convention
Theory about why
What do you think should happen to the convention try to make everything virtual
He should have his convention
Trump needs to push forward as
Abnormally push forward
Creating all this
Is there trying to hide the fact
Joe Biden doesn't have
Support
It would help for him to have
Fading
Issues from a strokes and whatever else
Know that his policy
These are going to call. They know that Trump is going to
The person to layout
Just how bad
By Joe Biden is in
Avoid that
Does Millie think there's going to be a presidential debate at the Democratic Convention
What does she think of regular convention would require of Bloodsport
Does not
He's just bitter and then he talks
He hasn't Vanquish everything under in debate
We don't choose at night for one section of the DNC and then the other ending after Jocelyn Joe Biden
Will Jackson
Democratic National debate
With all the p
People who already agree with it
He's one of the f****** nomination
What's going to happen everybody if they were there there don't ye give a good speech
Obama's net worth
There is something to be said before
Of people who would be protesting
There will be some people on the last Democratic Convention
The issue there isn't not trying to avoid that by not having a
Convention like you could you could do
Ye there's that
Right there is a
It's really about not being able to
Debates
DNC in the RNC happened at the same time
You have to talk to the other one like
It's like a giant game
I honestly don't know I don't know what
Yeah there's going to have him on camera so you didn't have to debate people
Or hide his support because
Even if he's even if he doesn't have as much support sure
He can fill out a 10,000
If you're talking about
It is this is in the context of
Trump and Biden debate
I mean I'll listen
I don't know what they would do digital virtual
Debate I don't know
If that's the conversation then all right
What are you talkin about
Conventions
I don't know what you're talkin
Cannot imagine a reason for Adam
I cannot think of any reason
To get the two of them to talk
Seems it seems unlikely they are going to sway anybody
Silly
What if they debated we're all just going to watch it and be like can we vote for not America anymore I don't know what to vote for
Yeah I don't I mean
In terms of tradition and there's always debates you know
Out there should be debate
Sometime
But in this one circumstance
Specifically there's no point
I don't know if I have an opinion on it
I think
You know there's a lot of people who
I think it's important to have those debates and I can understand where they're coming from
I think you are very valid point
I think I think I think
I would say that there's not many undecided
Well you know
I guess Trump is basically committing second-degree murder every single day and every time
But I really want to know what
Is Nutella
Explain is going to be
And I won't decide until I compare it with what
Hayden says his tax
Let's see
I don't know
Vitamins questions for you is the president killing people
Yes next
Trump
What is ru
What is
Executive branch
Cuz if a question
The nasty question not a real question
So Alex has decided that the Twitter hack
Is
The good guys
Taking over parts
Twitter
Google
Recaptured by USF
Google.
Smelly
Alright whatever man
This is a fun
Spy novel you're writing Alex but I don't
In terms of
I don't think anyone's going to publish this out
Did the British Elsa recapture
Fort Sumter
Recapture
I love the idea to that it's only part of Google
Don't have any hands in YouTube
That's a whole different department.
Video game playlist open-world video games
Another rest of it you still left
Turnover
There's a guy sitting in the government
We are disappearing people slowly
So I can actually say for sure
Don't know if I don't know what's going to happen this evening will be wrong tomorrow
This doesn't happen
What is your view on Trump the election with 108 Days album
What do you think
Well
I'm going to be careful Highway
I say this
There may or may not
Joint for stars
Having some problems
On Tuesday pertaining to the New York Times
So as far as what's coming next
That seems to be in
Pestana
I had of the calls for Acuna
Francois pinault
Is doing his best
To get it done
Pick a lane
How many 4-star generals do you think are active right now
Is only eight four star generals
She realizes this rainbow smashed B
All of them have made ranked in trumps
Furman president
I don't I don't I don't know
I don't know I don't know
What she's talking about
You're obviously Tuesday's not over
So I don't know what's going to happen possibility
But they seem to be really excited about the idea of
Trump crushing all dissent Within
I don't know 30 days before the mainstream gop's like we should cancel the election
Like I'm not it's going to be a mainstream thought
Not having enough
Well it could be brutal
We haven't talked to her but
Thera-Band
Fifty or so
Great bellingcat East a little bit
Is just right on your real good primer
Breakdown of the logo
Perspective
What's actually going on
From a local
Prospective somebody who's been there
I watched a lot of
Who has been streaming
And taking in a good
Last episode I was saying that I don't have a real good sense
What's going on
Kind of
I surprised myself and had the time we recorded a lot of resources
Peoples but I mean I'm in Chicago I don't really
I think that there's only so much of a perspective that you can
Can get without
You're not on the
Right
It's a story to be very difficult
God to cover especially as it's still a
Activities going on
Because of the death
Really hard for us to talk about
The precise
Things that were going on with the autonomous
I don't know
You kind of have to
Find
Some
Resources you can trust
Go from there
And so
We'll talk about it a little bit
Because
And I will say that his perspective
It's great I love military secret police don't want the feds to come in and take my property
After seeing the video today
Sender one
Who's in charge of those officers
San Quinn
Richmond in to Portland with no accountability
Quick question
About the physical safety and
Civil liberties
Peaceful protesters
Our shortest
We won't
Federal police actions here
Start the shower with that
What's going on there just
Last night
You a hamster
By the Democrats
Plans that we received
From
Inside their criminal operation
Soundtrack
Ontrac come on man
Federal buildings and other structures
So we'll talk about the specifics a little bit more
Resource Alex ever trots out
That's stupid fake Soros antifa contract
Harrison Smith found on 4chan
A couple years back
Is Hope
Ask document is behind so much of his argument
If you actually
Take a step back
My files and I realized that I'd actually taken
Screenshots of all the pages
Time that I couldn't rely on Alex
Keep them up on his website like I did get exposed
Copies I had them I reread them
F****** hilarious
I remembered that they were funny in terms of the idea of their existence but man it's so silly
For one thing
If you go to the section autoproved practices
It says quote
Contact
Da Donnelly
Do not name this individual at the end
Start stopwatch
Do not use AllCast do not name this individual in any columns or
Person of course not not leave this document
Hillary person then why I asked
F****** put it in a contract people Planning Center
If you think someone would do that you probably watch too many movies has pages in the 9/11 report
Was like the salaries did
Do you remember those how they didn't reject those at all
Quote
Closed fist to maybe use only below the neck and above the belt
That's just
What
Wow it's Marquess of Queensberry rules of kicking is not permitted
Provoked with no other recourse
I had to keep it
I didn't know you had my eyes
Get the guy got to let Daddy
We're not going to keep you on
So these documents are embarrassing an obvious fake but I started looking into it a little more
According to a recent article in Reuters these documents
On social media claiming that they were founded
Floyd related protest
B some antifa member had dropped them
This is how things are primary sources involved in conspiracy
Over and over and over
Because people are gullible
If you need citations on that
Look into the protocol
Anyway
There's mad hilarity that can be found in this writer's article
For the longest time Alex has been saying that these documents are between antique and George Soros his son Alexander
Because that's the only
In reality the document claims to be from Friends of DeMar
Chrissy
Which is a pact that was founded by Jonathan Soros
Whoops
Although these forged documents appeared online in 2018
In the aftermath in unrest protesting surrounding
The killing of Freddie gray in April of that year
Now here's the problem
What's wrong
Friends of democracy didn't exist in 2050
Says who secretly exist
A year earlier it's been reorganized at Edwards
Pretty backpacks in 2014 with another group called the public
Organizations name is every voice
They're specifically group focused on promoting the candidacies our folks are running for office
That's adorable
At the time these contract were supposed to have been made the shadowy evil Soros company that is said to be involved
Even exist
This is very sad
Levels of fraudulent you going on here that Alex is trying to prevent is real
Do you see what I'm saying about a debate what is the point of debating with people who believe
This s*** is
Real what are you going to say stuff
Joe Biden laughing at the honor the sacred honor of loti the present
I think you do
Individuals or believe in this
Something when you just like
It's not something is it isn't
Doesn't mean anything negative about you
It's not like
You know you shouldn't feel ashamed
Nearest if you like
I think the laughing at the idea of
With everybody
You shouldn't mock them cuz that's kind of cruel idea of
Stupid
Unreal
You can almost feel the desperation and now it's though
This guy who you love
Does it help to get elected is the guy who's doing
Baptism Tire careers
And the only way how it could make anything other than
Like he's just
Become a sellout for a dictator
Is if he has this contract
Zapproved
Enemies
What is dear leader is using to justify his Crackdown her actual
What is fake
And Alex is a sellout for
Dictator
He is this is really this is really Grim I mean
Going on in Portland Visa Avi federal law enforcement very in line with a lot of
Insane I was thinking about this
Just like this is part of the
Mesa Road where Lake
Mike Knox
You lying about everything
Federal law enforcement being used
Forlorn
My purposes domestically is something
It's been a joke
Concept
It's the same thing that I think about
FEMA camps
Vietnam
Yeah but it is based on you know a lot of steers that surrounded rex-84
A plan to round up leftist
Communist and immigrants
And Union organizers
Things like that
It's not like it's that far that you can turn and look at it
You know like as far as as far as the
Legitimate fear of being put into a
You know you can see if governments do do it right
It it some
Stop
Yes Alex you were always yelling about like Jade Helm and all that nonsense
You know you cried wolf many times
You never really mad what you were saying anyway
Mail
You made your career plan
Being there
John
And you're on the side of the people you always warned about
That's
Pretty sad
It's pretty sad and
Or live long enough to give up everything that you've ever believed and only she'll pills
Man
We got dementia
With Majestic pill news
Run around
Is putting people in
These these reports
Corroborate
Conversation
About
The other goings-on in Portland
Cuz it's fine
Open doors with crowbar
The Federal Building
Federal Building
King of the federal courthouse so they can try to load it
Secret police are disappearing people know
You're breaking into a federal building
Leaving aside that Alex's
Completely like certain
Missing the point just missing the larger issues about what's going on in Portland
I want to take a moment to bask in the
That he's using
Are federal law enforcement
Capacities in the United States
Obama was going to launch a Posse Comitatus FEMA camps
That was his primary brand for years
Absolutely
Matching people up in Portland what's Alex's response
Super Kennedy Federal Building the Federal
Building ever
The people were being detained by unidentified age
They were trying to break into a federal building at the time
Exist
If I'm not much mistaken I was a huge fan of Wildlife Refuge
2016 obviously a state wildlife refuge
To get into the parking lot by the federal government
But if she was going to pop up in the case of the Bundys to on the fridge
Kim Possible music
Where's the prince
Differently
Federal agents trying to text
I remember that
Where things get messy is that Alex isn't covering actual story in Portland
Partially because he doesn't care because he sees the Optics
So he's using the
The story the same way he was at every protest
Find some clips of someone wearing a black mask doing something to look scary to old people in the suburbs
Pretend exist in a vacuum use that perception
When did justify whatever police violence has used on the protesters
And move on
This is not a case of out-of-control lashes
Just trying to take over Federal Courthouse to Luna.
Is Alex's presenting
If you want a great explanation of what's going on in Portland like you recommended I would also recommend
Got to where we are now
From the perspective
The whole time
It is longer than
That is true now
Defonte using they print things out
Cuz I will say it's on page three of the website and I don't know what that mean
So as Robert lays out
On the evening of the 29th to the city had their first protest related to the murder of George
Employ
This was happening on what would be about the
Third night of a group called the youth Liberation movement
In front of the Justice Center
The protest
Send it up converging that evening
Large groups around that building and eventually broke in and trashed
From Robert
I watched all this happen from destruction was unplanned yet more less inevitable
You could feel it in the mood of the crowd
3rd Precinct in Minneapolis that just burned there was absolutely no way Portland was going to try to do the same thing
The police showed up and they dispersed the crowd using tons of
Protesters by definition supposed to be something it's kind of Confrontation
No because that's the way these things
Work
As such things coalesced around the Justice Center as they took on an actual as well
Importance to
What's going on
Nightly protest would occur at the Justice Center and they would often result in police tear gas protesters
Then on July 11th
Donovan LaBella in the head with rubber bullet for no reason
People didn't like
This was one of the more egregious examples of consistent pattern
It started to form of police violence
Taking place in Portland
Is that being carried out with the involvement of Federal Aid
Allison Tire career demands
He be on the side of the protest
Of course he's not
Ultimately I have to make peace with the fact that this podcast
You know
We can't do everything
To another
You can't be every
Yeah it'll be impossible for us to get the best most accurate coverage
This unfolding
Still ongoing
Situation
The best thing I can do is say in reiterate
The first is to seek out sources of information that offer larger
Preferably people have been there and know what's going on
The second is that there's absolutely no
Example
Completely given up the charade that was his career than his siding with these federal government
If you're a listener who show it
Please
You predict
Except
Fake ass Soros documents
F****** Leaf in the Wind
Anyway
I just see this is like another one of these
Wow Alex
You
You don't realize or maybe you do realize
Your whole career
Will be disappearing
Chicago
Next week
Might not stay continue if you want to see here
I just I still maintain that if
If
Any of our congressmen are people under the age of 50
Had the will to do it if they showed up on the front lines
Portland
And made it an international incident
That's the federal government
Is disappearing our own
Now too
That would be
The way to move
And they're not doing it
Yeah man I don't know I don't
I don't know if that
No
That means that there's no that
That would mean that there's no limit I don't know anymore
I also have no f****** clue
You know I always
Kind of hope that Alex had some sort of backbone about
B cross
No it's
Scenes in
Various
Quote-unquote documentary
Yelling at people in fatigues who happened to just be walking on the street
You know the people who do
Exercises exercise
Content about
Of course
It's just such a cool
Complete
Betrayal
I mean even if it was like a if it was a leftist group of
Proud Second Amendment left
Plenty
Federal government literally jump
Alex with silver like see you got to take your right I think I think he was
Nationalized
These men
Federal Marshals the most ever met US military
It's the military
Brad
And then you're getting interrogated because you work for a foreign power
Really trying to burn the country downstairs for the stock market
Economy Europe
You're a military
10 gun
You kill people
Can you shoot people
Stop that's enough
Losing a little bit there is no matter what no matter what
Right that's what I kind of meat
That's what you have to do we are now we have our own citizenry for so long
Now the feds are just doing what
We should be doing I guess I don't I don't know how you can say these things as someone who made them
I'd like to hear Primus what Alex has had not recognized just the
Definitely not the right word
Did not do 911 and it was exactly as we said it was then.
I agree with him
I'm going to be honest
Not an inside job
I'm just going to wait
Okay I never really thought it was an inside job
We had conversation
Sad
I mean like a course what you do you label the people enemy combatant
Can be kidnapped
Interrogated by the military and the movie
I would argue that like
I was a hundred percent
Against
Adipose
To the occupation
Wildlife Refuge
If the military was coming in and like at night when everyone sleeping
That
The shooting of LaVoy finicum
I don't like the idea that now granted the circumstances surrounding that are not
You no clear-cut is just the police shot somebody
Would like for that whole situation to have ended without anybody died
I think they look terrible
I would say if they were being treated the same way
I will be
The malheur side
Higher-order problem exactly
We'll deal with your occupation
And this is like Native American land with you
This is wrong
But seriously the government disappeared
You'd think that I would be capable of that kind of
It's possible to Des
Political aims of the people in Port
Site
Recognized
Oh hey that's my Marquis issue probably be on the right side of it
Is just straight-up like there
Dad
Slime
Next
Tabouli
Who you're working for
When Love
Communist
Paperwork
Such big news
Oh God
Now it says breaking out the hit
Such big news
Sing about is that
Have Soros contract them like the fake ones that is the internet
You have to always carry the contract with you
Are people like a diplomatic tag or something
It's like everybody gets together and then like I don't know if Carl was allowed to do that
Got to pull out his contract
Flipping through it like
Note that one still good guys already contracted don't pull out your contract
Say that thing
Yeah yeah
It's really really f***** up and I didn't expect more of Alex
Kind of wood of Hope
Maybe just because it would have been more appealing narrative for me like he finally wakes up and
Recognizes like
What the f***
And then try to find some new ones
In between land where it's like
Alright
I believe in everything that I've supported Trump for this whole time
I now recognize that those authoritarian tendencies
Clear all contacts
Locked up
Song of supporting Trump
You could be doing
How much
He's a liar and everything
The world circumstances are such that he could be giant right now
How many fake ass would a Twitter leftist suddenly became for saying dump bulshit that doesn't mean
Alex is the king of Dumbo
Legit Crush
If you work just like I like Rand Paul
That made people
Maddow and everybody been like
No I know
Absent Alex
You still would have ended up with Trump behaving the way he's behaving
Alex supporting Trump
Cause some sort of a butterfly effect
Alex
Against
Trump with his Decades of there's a police state,
He would
Speed
Probably one of the most famous people in the world
Think of all the people on the left were like
I didn't like before but now this guy's right on even though we still do are showing reveal that everything you said with
They would love him probably wouldn't be interested in listening to
Call Manuel rebooking everything
Masshole
What an a******
Adidas
Different world
True
It's probably inevitable
So we back to this Twitter thing here and
Very stupid
This is what we need to see more of
Beautiful
Vlog
Azar's
At this point I see no claims
Like I see no evidence
The Patriot hack against the global
I can see no evidence that all these people's messages
The most relevant lie I find it really hard to believe the people like Bill Gates or Obama would ever use a flat
IPhone like Twitter for any kind of important communication
Contracts through Twitter DM
If you imagine that they are in fact involved in some kind of a grand scale conspiracy there's no chance
Incriminating / Twitter
That's what someone like Alex would do or Rodger
The only person was affected by that hack that I probably have
Bucked up Stephanie's DM Does Elon Musk
Peter van daan
Addicted to Twitter and act like a dick on social media
True
I bet that's embarrassing messages that could be released
Himself
This is legitimately no different than Gary Cassity arguing
Fires in California where are aliens coming to eat people
They're both claims that take an actual news story
Write their own versions of them
More fun
I'm well in Kerry Cassidy
Patriots trying to steal
Come on now
I don't disagree with you now
It's debatable whether that is more boring
Then I would say it is that is
She probably Revolution
Leadership word
Stop now we're now we're in a writers room
Obviously
Supporting
Trump doing what he's doing
Avi law enforcement
And Portland
It makes sense because
This is what our Christmas next clip
Is this is this is
Pretty clear
Federal government a separation
He set up a long time ago
Do you see
It's the weapon we have
The federal government
Hollywood
Federal government
Call me in the Hillary still think they're going to win
So I mean it's federal government
Dessert
Weapons we can use against our real enemies
Democrat
He's just really explicitly saying
We are in control of the reins of power and because of that we can use that power
To crush our political opposition
Is there
For the leftist and I was like
F*** yeah I hate the left us
And then
I was fine cuz I'm not saying we just
So we can covid news
Didn't really
It's cute
They're some of the headline
Motorcycle
In Florida says
Gaddam
I just pretty much always the case I was recording on bulshit that isn't even relevant by the time he's on air
In this case the man in Florida who died in a motorcycle crash and had tested positive for covid-19
However
He was taken out of a datapool
What are the reasons for their being
Question about it
Chords for review
There's a very slight possibility that even in the case of a motorcycle crash that covid
Contributing factor to the death
Is it possible that he only crashed because of about a severe coughing
Probably unlikely but it's questions relevant in people's
Anyway the State of Florida as
With exclusion criteria place that's a has deaths from
I'm trauma murder-suicide overdose
Vehicle accidents removed from covid update
Is basically a non-story that irises reporting is huge
It is so annoying to me
People have already thought
Of how this could happen and created a process by which they could revise it
Classify
Grizzly classified
It doesn't covid numbers
And then somehow through the process that they already had in places
So things work
Yep
Bombshell
You can kind of see how the goal posts are being moved
In order to help maintain the
Alex is hiding behind is that in the initial wave of cases and deaths
The largest city in the United States was the Epic
New York City at the ambassador's population and population density
Control has created Perfect Storm where they were a large number of deaths in a single area
As time is going on in New York has largely gotten the virus in check
Stickley in the northeast of the country
This drop is enough to amass be surgeon
Recent apps that have been seen in the south
In States like Arizona
California around Annie
Theater Southwest
These areas are going up
Pretty serious
But often and are similar population
To New York naturally
Gross number of death
Are going to be lower for the country
You know they're higher in these regions
Obviously I have no idea what's going to happen there are no
Small areas
Seems like a guy's just trying to explain away death
We've heard that the Trump
I was taking the reporting
Away from the CDC
Alex
Covid-19
CDC website
The cdc's one by fauci
Total fraud
Good truck runs
First thing fauci does not run
DC
Broadband
About this Trump Administration
Make the reporting taken away from the CDs
MN Department of Health
Human Services
On the one hand
If the recordings being done appropriately and professionally
Jess is irrelevant
Ultimately the CDC is part of it
You know if in fact that this is just an instance of rolling out a new possibly update system
Might not be a totally negative
I don't really trust
Anything that I just said to be accurate
I don't trust that the Trump Administration is going to make moves to provide better
And honestly I don't think that I would trust them to make this kind of
The timing is weird
Say the least
We're in the middle of the public L situation
Anytime you migrate systems there are some things you end up learning by experience
Making mistakes
Those mistakes could be
Very detrimental in the current landscape and we may not be able to afford
Honestly
They could be hugely consequential
And that's why did National Governors Association
And to make all of the information Pub
The cheer said
Changes imposed
Sunstate Health Department Hospital Systems which are already working at full capacity
This wasn't selected
Globalist nonsense
55 States and territories
Is cheering for a cover-up
Whether or not I mean
I can't say how things are going to go
And if there was the possibility of a smooth transition and appropriate
I don't know necessarily if it's
The most monstrous
Doing it now only lead to unforeseen trouble
Point where they lost
So
Don't care don't care what their motivations are they can even do a good job you've lost the benefit
We're at the point now where unfortunately
It's going to come down to people to have to actually be like
We won't do that
You can say we're transferring it to the HHS or the white house or whatever
The cbc's going to keep the data and put it
Yet like that's where we're at
You have to say no to the president United States
Also Alex all of the state
The contract
They're all deep state that we're all
Believers in Satan they're all doing all this
These diseases news
There's no deeper coverage of it at all
Housing prices in 2020
NFL season may be in jeopardy
That is just some of what we're going to be covering
Today ladies and gentlemen
Infowars.
Newswars.com
Please don't forget
Have the Christmas in July
Beautiful now
July sale
What's the weather like
Personally
Bellwether
For whether or not
Can I be replaced by a news.
At the bottom of a CNN
Cuz then what if it was in all caps
Dan Gregor
You're right iron
I'm going to just pull an audible
The next like 3 clips
Alex interviews
I apologize I didn't write it down
She's made a documentary about incels and also does not approve of the use of that term
Apparently it's sort of a pejorative throws around
She has a lot
Sure I ever want to watch a documentary
She's a great
Speaker on Infowars
Ucbi
Yes
The interview is kind of pointless
And
Just being Alex
Talking over her
They're not yeah
It's it's it's not really all that interesting
I got clips of it on the thought that
You know maybe some
Nothing happened
While we were like recording, I forgot it was coming up
See Bethany
He's mad
Trumps
Is it nice
Write the book no idea
Yeah so
He thinks it's like totally normal for families
Play
Denise
The president
Our family
Guitarist
Contract
Is Donald Trump
Says the n-word all the time at all
This house 1050
Trump
Never said
Exorcist
You are
Why did you jump into
It's about black people his sons
I don't understand
But
Whatever strange
I would say that
You don't need to sign a contract
That you agree to not make
Usually that is it now that's called
I believe
No isn't making things up
About people you can still like oh yeah that's just regular old
Yeah do that bad about your time working for this company
Or whatever
Couponcabin
Which was wonderful
Make makeup
Makeup
Cuz you could still end up getting
You can't make someone sign
Contract for what hours is this
Already White
Tina that's so stupid
That's so stupid
That's so incredibly stupid
F*** you can say
Easily whip what's true for every one person which is you said there's been some reason because we're
Get in the f****** culture
And we got better beef
Racist
Hallelujah
You do not understand
That is a matter of lack of control
Trump
And anti-semitic slurs
All about
Trump doesn't
Say something in his
Sleepy doesn't want to say
This is crap
Gentleman
Funny to me and a compilation of trump saying completely nonsensical things
Mr. Roboto
We expect more
Long time I remember how back in January 27th
Just before Trump's inauguration
Alex got trolled by a guy
Twitter
Trump saying the n-word on The Apprentice we're about to get really
This guy pretended to be an embassy employee and just randomly said Paul Joseph Watson to DMC
Any checking into the story
Paul wrote up an article about it
Alex filmed in emergency damage control report
It went something like this
Weird Al.
Play
Paul Washer
Astoria
Concerning and
Random.org
Quite a few
Terry Rozier
Tape compilation
Whatever
Was him sitting in the chair
Things like it sounds
Ricardo
Supposed
Think about Trump
Long time
Is he does
Dirty jokes comedian with
Boston
Almost
Stress reliever
Dice
Deprecate himself as well
So I mean like slightly different take
Like a river
Is that a defensive Trump
What is
Yeah I've heard him say the n word
He's never said anything that he didn't mean to say
She's lying
Same time
Well I mean that would
Sort of raised the question of
If Trump is in such great
Control themselves
How do you explain all the nonsense
I mean we have time to unpack right now
Very small he's an ID
Bear.
So Alex has another Gaston by that I mean
Did The Hodgetwins
John Hodgman
Wish
No it's
These two guys I believe they became
Comedian in workout
And it didn't go well and then I'm like
Comedic videos on YouTube
Maybe some Fitness stuff
Reserve Ferry
Found themselves in the position
Conservative
Trump voice
How do you
So wild
Is there not good
It's really annoying
Listening to this interview with Tom
Speakers
I mean just Elementary things that they have wrong
Just make it so respected position that you're coming from
Because
Base level deceptions are trying to pull off
And that means like I don't care you're not serious about what you're doing
I'm in the second one is because it's so transparent
Alex is using them
He doesn't even know their name
Why would you call them like
Twins
Time to know what their names are
Twin they said that Trump
Said the n-word so I need to have black
I don't care who they are
So wrong
Just about where I was like
I don't care
You you you end up
In a box
Macon
He was just throwing up
CVS
The news
Buy report
Yeah she asked
Question
People still being
In America
She hasn't
Yeah
Play salsa
People being shot
Publix
If the public knows that that
Down in America
Police killing people
I'm not sure that it's a good argument for people to say to protest
Dubai police killing black people are bad
Because police actually killed more white people
I don't really understand the logic and how that tracks whatever
That's a minor
Twins talking about you
The interviewer asked quote why are African-American
I'm still dying at the hands of law
Trump replied
What a terrible question
People by the way
It is true that more total white people are killed by police each year
American
Is the meaning of statistic
Contacts
Because they're not equal number of white and black people in the
Country
Or science
No
Has been done on the differential
Consistently shown that more likely to be killed by police
Whitney statistics have been address
Did the compensate for population
Differences
According to the guardian black people are more than
Twice as likely to be killed by police than white people in America
Quotes in 2016 black men aged 15 to 34 19 times more likely than other Americans
Has to be killed by law enforcement officers
And they were killed at four times the rate of young white men
This talking point
More white people are killed by police
Is a standard Canard
It's really dumb things
For two reasons
The first is that using the Staten that way you don't really understand the top of your talking about
Underlying racist perspective
But you're looking camouflage
The second is that the natural conclusion of his larger
Anywhere good
Is the queen supposed to be the police killings are actually okay
Is the message that they're trying to push is that
Black people should calm down because more white people are killed
Is the problem that
Folks are complaining about police murders
Or is the problem that if people like Alex have is that the
Don't focus on the rape victim
The logic of this argument doesn't go anywhere
You have to ask yourself what the actual message
And if you do
I don't think you come up with anything good
Best
This is a defensive police
At worst it's a blatantly racist desire for all social movements to Center White
Experience
And actually I don't know if that's it best
I don't think there is
I don't know where this logic or this
Reasoning goes
It isn't
Let police murder you
White people should be in the streets protesting
Because we're getting killed
They kill so many white people
Doesn't that seem like it should be the second
Said
Everything else look up and let police
Isn't that is why we must also vociferous Lee
Supporting this movement exactly
You're only bringing this up in order to
Minimizing invalidate the people were protesting
Which seems to be saying
Something along the lines of
It's cool
I guess school for police to kill
Interpretation of somebody saying that
Aside from them being like
And that's why we should abolish the f****** police
Possible interpretation
Is
White people more white people
Getting killed and you don't see the problem
Like that's the that's the most innocent way I think you can look at that
Taking the argument
I've sat down my thought about the
Cuz I'm trying to figure out like what is the mess
Hijinx
That isn't
Going down one of those Road
Something I haven't
Considered but I'm having a very difficult time trying to figure out
How that statistic
Is relevant to this conversation in a way that leaves
Somewhere
It can't be seen as anything other than an insecure response
To somebody pointing out
That one
It's not about
It's
It is a fundamental aspect of our policing system
That it is fine too
You hunt young black man
And if you of
If you absorb that one piece of information
That you have to change every Viewpoint you have on police
So you're insecure response to that is just like
More black people or white people killed so you know
You're not that big a deal what's going on
No I do not care for people
There
This window
Like if this is what you bring to the table
Killed by police
Black people
Stink
That means something
That leads me to believe that this is not like
You're not a voice that
Worth taking seriously
And it gets worse because
Bill Ware
There's a higher rate
Of black people killed
Right
Something completely irrelevant in the study
Play black people
In Black
Yeah but the
Serbia saying
White
Intuit
Population
Okay
If you want to freak out
What's going on if
People being chill
You need to take a nap
Police scanner
Who cares about
Call my wife
Can you build determine
They put a lot of the time yeah
Your eyebrow was way up
These complaints with the study that shows people at higher rates than white people
A completely meaningless
I'm going to go to waste my time discussing this
But I feel like it's worth our time to really see the level of argumentation
Like if your complaint with the study
Okay
M m s
Have you tried to look for a study that only involves police indirect
Intuitive
Are you telling me
You have existed in American Society for this long and you think that
Black people don't have
Higher rate of police interactions as well
Interesting thing
Like
It does seem to me like if they had looked into it
They could find a study
About police interactions
You have to look into it
Right
Like the fact that they're not bringing up a study that shows
That there is actually no difference
Police interaction
Either haven't
Look look if they were saying
Okay
Here's how it went
They say
There was a different
Group u.s.a.
All of the elderly and the entire population reviews
For the white
ASAC
You know I don't know 15 to 25 year old male
Black said you were bringing up that kind of a problem with the relatives
Sample group
Using entire population now
Come on guys not only that but it's
It's to the point you know
Where if you
You just hear it in their voices
Okay
So you need to have a study that talks about police interactions alright
Here's my study that talks about
Police interactions
Well well well
There's always going to be a you should have had that this is the quest
Borne out by the clip
We could go by the police I just walking around the lollipop
Largely motivated by opposition to.
100percentpure saying
You could bring out the study that shows like okay here's just police interactions
Where is the number of unarmed
The next talking point
Precludes you from even going down that road
And then okay we breached
An impasse 100% disagree with you and that seems to be your willing
Another thing is
It seems like you have a lot of
Another reason why I'm not
Particularly interested in their their contributions
You can see that they
Have a lot of allergies
Woman killed in Indianapolis that we talked about that Alex has been using as a race
It seems like
Exactly the same as Alex
It mysteriously doesn't match up with reality
It's information that they given a black
Baxley
Creating
Racist
So many white people
I mean I don't see this
Shooting kills her
She had a six-year-old
I'm not sick you're sick
I mean what country are we living in
Wasn't it a protest in her kid was
The same thing
Interested
Just say all lives matter
You know like that's what they want to show up
And tell me that it's okay for cops to murder people
You up with bullets from
I want to play the squid because it does also demonstrate something that I said Alex clearly doesn't know their name
And I don't want that to just
Is it happening on the show
You were trying to get into it
What about
Will let you go by your full name sometime
What do you expect to happen
Next in the Democrats.
That is deeply deeply uncomfortable
Little boy one of the twins I just called
Someday you're going to have an excellent day I know what you're going to have a name
The one last
Hodgetwins
Here is another reason why I just don't
This stuff serious
I just I can't take
People in this Lane of the media.
That's because they have just completely bad faith argument that they make
If you look at
Date
You never see AOC
Universiade
Anybody
Yeah you have
This is ridiculous like
Is right-wing online conception
Unstructured way
Agua
Cons of supposed
The debates online
What is complete nonsense
Biggest trolling
And the rest is people thinking of blowing people's minds of philosophy 101 topics about
That's not meaning
But the online conservatives really think there's
It's like some kind of important part of their culture where they do these online Bloodsport kind of argument
Isn't really into physical violence
Intellectual
Isn't it a physic
Violence do they have to get their jollies off
It's so powerful.
I regret a lot of the time that I've spent
Listening to that b*******
It is this
Weird online world of people who think they're really
Really
Meaningful
Play meaningful is only on
The level of
How many people are watching
Yeah I know like there are large audience
And people can't be swayed by really slick
Sort of rhetoric that goes on
Honestly
It's
It did stop
Classroom
Because
Hodgetwins
What they're saying is the chinos better than
Debate me on anything
Say you want to have a charity wrestling match
Is the same spot
She's a f****** congressperson
F****** hangout dumbass Ben Shapiro
Really fast
And let's be real
Alright
The people who have holes up on this off
Do not get
That money doesn't get paid out
Is always a reason
I can't say for sure computers through 10,000
Yeah
Debate anyone point
She also appeared in debates back in 2018 when she was running for receipt against Joe Crowley and honestly
She should be way too busy being in government to respond to dumb dumb conservatives want to chase by trying to Bay
Maybe like me challenge
Instagram
With the conservatives Dan they don't have the
The guy who yells
Although rent would be doing more with his governing power if he were to debate me there anything
Spokes come in clearly
Have their own cottage industry that I'm unaware of like I don't know who these guys are outside of there.
There's little things that you can
Use the tell like okay this is not a sincere Act
The first
Is the the use of argumentation like
Thinking of that
Statistic about
People being killed more by cops
That is a Dead Ringer
Starting off poorly
Second
The engaging with a study in the way that they did
I got problems with your problems
With the spider
I didn't like their use of Arial font
The
The implication that
People just deserve to be shot by the police
We're going to be able to
Get me where we ever to
3rd or 4th I'm not sure at this point the
Repetition of Alexei narrative
That means that you're
Areas are getting information from or probably not great
Amende just sort of dumb
AOC won't debate
Kind of thing
Which is just a Hallmark of these truly stupid world
Online never just not serious
You have all of these things that are just indicative in a minute interview of like
Con artist
And I just don't care for it longer Aveo
Great shape
Definitely
Yeah so Nick begich
The guy who wrote that book
Angels Don't Play this heart
He's hosting the 4th hour
Unfortunately
We have bad news
Is awesome
Ford hours
Sunrise Jones
Topshop some of this job
Crazy crazy
Austin weather
Black lives matter
So Rex is going to come on for the 4th hour with Alex
So only black people
I don't I don't unpack that
You know talk about this video that he's made
I don't know whatever
I'm not going to talk too much
About him
Because
The
Stuff that he has to say is just repeating
Infowars
You know it
It's a bummer to see
Just get some like fatherly affection
Debatable oh no what I want to say
Focus on his Alex's Behavior
Rex comes in
Call Daddy created he couldn't sell
This is really interesting explain how this product line came
Came to be
It's his ex
I know I should
How can I help
I just feel like
Somebody else
Couple months ago
Really good products
Potassium
Amazing
So now what
I
Try to understand words
Because that's
That's a
Listen to the implication of these thoughts together
A year ago his dad came to him and said how can I help you seem to be under attack all this stuff
Your USB company and I'm whatever
So Alex is that Aspen that announces like
Let's
B-real
I should probably
B Delaware under a lot of attacks
They're all this stuff is coming down all over the place
I need to probably just step down
And let people have their own operation
Let's Let The Fly
Absolute
Let's get that started
And then
Coming up route to fruition
Getting started plan to get Alex out of control
Which
If I'm to understand that me
Here's what I think that
I don't know if Alex is saying this because he
Says word
The Domina
Yeah that's an issue
But
Definitely in the last 6 months
I wouldn't be
Prize
If what was going on here
Is Alex's dad
Is launching a supplement line for Alex to sell
They can Shield
Set
Sega
Things continued down the road that they're going on
You are so
Hide assets under his dad's name with business
Alex isn't technically connected to at all but he's getting all the profit
It's alright
So what you're saying to me
If I were say limited liability
And
Somebody pursuing Infowars
The limited liability
They would be able to take all that
Conceivably but if I had a different LLC if you did
If you're well I don't
I was like I need to take care of
All kinds of products
From you
Large amount of money directly to you upfront
And
When people order that product
Well I mean you can keep it on your shelf
I don't know I mean like obviously what you're suggesting is what this smells like
No
Alex is going out
We got these great products
Need to say
Product
Now it even gets weirder
Very specific
It is not
It's company
Selling products
Weirdly assembler around products
Infowarsstore.com
Electric
Who I want some girls
Top brass
Quit your job
Ingredients
Are super strong high quality
These are designed to be
Affordable
But it's
You know we're underwater
Shut it down
Starfish
So
I mean like talking about this idea that this this is kind of how you might
Structure something if you're trying to
Funnel resources somewhere
If you just seem like that's a possibility
I've no idea
Because ultimately the other possibility
Name is
In terms of brand
Like so you just
Launch all of these other products that are basically all the same things with different names
And then maybe you know it's like that what's that f****** scene The Wire
Where I asked
What is the name of the
The mass destruction
New name on the street yet
It seems like that's another possibility has recognizes it like
Yeah the people who buy my s***
Will buy turboforce
In the mail by super male vitality
Buried they don't have any stigma attached my product everybody else
Does
And then maybe it'll work
That is a possibility to I don't know either
F****** weird
But he keeps couching it
Wayne
I'm telling you right now
Johnny Wright
I thought it was going to work but I just checked their website and
He did use a giant picture of Short Round on the website when
I guess he didn't know is a racist character
Secretary of State
Mbiz Travis County
It's not there I don't know exactly
Incorporated in Delaware keep you up-to-date on
It's weird
The move is weird
Especially because
Like I said
These products are the same thing
Basically that he already saw
He has
Rocket
Rest or whatever
Completely different things
What kind of idiot would get those two mixed up.
This wasn't playing
A few hours
You always have
That's a that's a weird
His words were
2 days ago
2 strong
The name is perfect
He said I
I was just had so much energy
Is available
Right now
You trying to sell this product by comparing it to your other product
Doesn't this just
Cannibalized
I don't understand why you
Like maybe maybe his maybe is his
Supplier won't work with him
More
But it work with Alex's dad
Yeah maybe I mean you can launder it as though it's Alec
Text Dad I don't
I don't think so because anywhere discontinued
Down the road
This is a strange thing
I wish I had more like
Like a concrete
But I just
I mean we can at least make sure that he knows
The strange thing because that's how he's advertisers he's acting weird
I think it's required an explanation not being forthcoming
Okay so I was like everybody trying to steal all my money and I'm so sad
Right by my dad was like
I will bail you out for the 3 million
Destroy both of my businesses in order to hide money for my
There was another way
We got some new products
That's why if you want to if you want to go back to your girl you can have a conversation with you
Your dad I'm having
I'm trouble all of these people alert
I feel like I want to quit however
That's where you could rationalize these other products and Alex
Revenue stream
I was going to quit
This is my dad's way of helping me
Those are the worst episode in the configuration
That's what he said we have to start
Do words mean we have to
Really assess
First
It's erect
Comes in alright
The Trump like
Adult women
He doesn't like that Epstein stuff
Who are cool
Rex tries to interject
Little boy
It responds like a
Let's just say
Chaparro
Swimming
Horsepower
He's not intimidated
Red women
Pino's 112
12 year old girls
Call Premium beer
The point is he likes
Full grown women
Pat's
To me should never be on
Every single part of that
You know I wish that I had tried
I had told you that Rex was there you can see Alex
The added dimension of his son and then he called
Everything Alex was saying
Would lead you to believe that this is what you should
You're off to a great start objectifying women
You're doing a great job telling us something that we literally already know he paid people to f***
There we go on that
B-93
Also love denigrating by comparing them to meet scolding strange
Don't be
I wish you would I wish you would what he should have said is
Implication no talking about the governor of South Dakota
Talking about how amazing
Imallexx
Cannot stop sexual
South Dakota state of the right thing and
Trusted me
His son is sitting next to him while he's grunting yes Mommy at a picture or video
Show of the governor's South.
Dakota
That's inappropriate
What is the family show
I like her whiskey
Keep going
You were at a professional bull riding
Event
It was the first major indoor sporting event with fan
Transcend smart how important was it
What the f*** is going on
Cheese's locker room talk on air with my son wow
Wow there is just like I said I don't want to talk about like Rec
Being you know on Aaron talking about like all these dumb liberals and stuff again everything
Dad has
Give me a pat on the head bleed
How any
Like horrible things
Could be
Like the product of
Trying to seek the attention of
Definitely
Eventually I'm sure because Rex is on the road that he's on and it's unfortunate
Yeah but there was still a part of me that feels so
Powerfully like
Kid a kid
Yeah
I would hate to be.
Things things that I say
When I was 7 this is this is totally like
Small town
This is
This is every idiot I know and then some of them went away to college
You know the liberal brainwashing
That was f****** stupid
Like it was escaping from the influence of you
Any water but you know you want to believe that there's a possibility that that could be something happens but at the same time like
How much is that is giving way too much
He needs to be away from his parents before you can give him
A like
Your you're
Your brain isn't fully formed
You shouldn't be there I'm approaching this
Disappearance is largely just
Standard at Infowars.
And that doesn't rise to the level of me feeling
The need to treat him
Like
Someone who's on Infowars
Right right
I will get to that point events
Probably
Autonomous person who's able to make his own choices
I just find it difficult to get around the fact
Also somebody who had to deal with Alex Jones being his dad
Yeah like
Require years of therapy in order to
Oh man
I know my biggest problem
Is
Like
By no means do I think it's okay for him to do or say any
I think my biggest problem with it is until he's an adult
I'm just beating up on
Like I don't like that if I if I was like a teacher and he was a student
That's a that's a context where it's my job.
Misbehavior
I'm just a
I don't even know how all the time it's Ernie
Stranger
And this kid is on his dad's radio
Beat up on a kid
Larger perspective
Exist
But I think the higher-order problem is that Alex's
Appropriate
There that is
More of a relevant point
There will come a point
Where is Cross
Existing
Personally
The point where
I'm comfortable with that
Horrible
Person or a horrible person
Your kid
Platforms
No
I still
Not going to cover them appearing on Infowars
Twelve-year-old or whatever
Adults should not have them on their show
He's exploiting a child
The only thing I have to say is the biggest problem here is a man exploiting a child
And that it's his own child is real
I don't know which is more f***** up
Alex is sexualizing the governor
Great another thing
Well that was America brother
This was the
Major sports
Recording the sound
Right before the event
To be there this
Sample
But what makes this
Greatandhra
Mrs. Jones
Dimension of creepiness to this and that is that
And then that the South Dakota governor of the rexha's new mother
Governor
Book the governor
A shock jock show
It was just an Opie and Anthony Style Show
This sort of behavior there
Alex presents himself as a very different sort of broadcast
Capture and in the conditions
He presents himself this is unacceptable on
100 different levels
Everybody needs to come right with God
And as we all know God wants me to openly speculate on how much I want to f***
The governor of South Dakota in front of my son
I read the Bible cover to cover my friend
Twice is it mentioned
You got two f**** out
Dakota governor
Next clip
Alex he sucks Rex up
Erase baby kind of bit a little bit of a
Bean and
Exactly
Isn't she
He's talking about like being out of the protest
Blazing sun
Open air
Clear Blue Skies
And
Time when people would take their masks off
5 Seconds
Am I
Restaurantes liuna
Because you're white
I'm going to be donating all my all the money I ever made in my life to Black lives matter now to make up for what I just said I'm
He wants to help
People by destroying their community
I mean like that
Stupid bit but it's
Exactly the bishop Alex is trying to initiate
It's irrelevant
Completely off topic
Racism against white people
It's the 11th
X2
I think we're all going to die because of deep-seated daddy is
I think too many Psychopathic dads have led to too many people in power
And now we're also
Theory
Talk about vampires a little bit
Here
That sounds like a conspiracy theory
Echo bear about him
Imagining child in the dark
Kidnapped
Shinedown
4 days
No food all the sudden
Comes into view
Cheer he's in charge
The boss
He's going to have his way right now
Play my opinion
I opened her
If my dad said stuff like that to me in private I probably wouldn't talk to him
I know
I do know that he's not 18
Child abuse sure
Sure
Fox
I just don't think that
Are you fine
I wrestled with the idea of like is this even something we should talk about on the phone probably
Ben on breaks on Monday
Dab
But it's deeply
It says
Unbecoming as a broadcaster is uncommon
As a professional critic of things
It's it's it's trash this is the trash and I feel bad
4 racks
I don't I don't know I'm I meant
Weird limbo stay where
I mean with this like this is so much
This is so f***** up for me personally cuz like I'm
Flashing back
Back to when I was like
13 years old
And I was like
Proudly like
Read the Bible in a in a week or whatever it is
I just want
One to connect with my dad on a certain level
And 2 for him to give me that
You'd like
You did good Slugger like that's what I was going for
And when he says I think Stephen Colbert looks like a
Pedophile
That is exactly the next step
Feel It In My Bones just like
Dad I want to relate to you
An evening
He just can't get it
You shouldn't call him a pedophile he's a vampire
Everything
Don't act like
You can't even give him a good job site
He's really interesting I even really realize that dynamic
Correcting and Ivory
The high status
Buy naked
Don't call people premium beef
Now I'm going to spend a bunch of time muttering house
The governor of South Dakota's Mommy
Really interesting
And maybe maybe I'm projecting a little bit cuz like
Diaz Diaz
Play teenager with multiple religious Studies classes
Uconnect
With my dad and my dad wasn't even Alex
The level two
Approval-seeking Behavior might not have otherwise been a client man
What I'm getting at this really difficult is like
I can
Empathize
Schroth
And maybe Rex is up to that s*** off Alex's show but I just don't make it my business to seek out
True
The stuff that he saying is all exactly like what year
Describing is like it is very
Easily
Categorize balazs
Approval-seeking Behavior
Why is it that everybody on the show makes me genuinely want them to get help
Like I'm mad at everyone around
Them I'm mad at everybody in this created
That keeps them from getting these serious psychiatric help they
Yeah
Some people speculated that Alex was drunk
When he's doing this like his vampire
It does sound
Like he's drunk but
Doesn't make sense to me because he's not been acting
Drunk throughout most of this episode
It seems like the ignition would be way too fast
He does have a weird
Coughing
Okay
Anime
Am I
God if he does have covid I hate all of you
Trying to figure out who Haile Selassie
End up getting real alive
Still shot
Stephen Colbert
I have no idea what's going on there
It could have been that he took like a big Swig of booze and he started coughing or something
Could just be the camera wasn't on him because he was coughing and he looks
Laney
Yes no
I don't know what the cases of my professional assessment of this is I don't necessarily think
He was drunk if possible I don't I don't see the evidence of it
I don't know because he is desperately sad
Yeah
You know
What are the same time
He was doing fine generally speaking of an episode that
He's drunk on
We can print it you you to really really good
Through the Journey of life
Not drunk
You started out a little drug test
I generally see a narc
F***** up I don't know
And you were asking if Rex got a pat on the head
And here's how
This discount to close
America was built
On Christian Western ideals
Openly away
What do you have to replace our ideals with
I know
Being demonized
The idea of America and what Americans have died
Getting back to what I was saying he's
Waddling off now
So mid-sentence Alex's just like you can host the rest of the show
Turn it off
Because I mean
17 you don't have job
No she doesn't have. It's almost
The end of the fourth hour or so like I don't know like it's Alex came back like right under whatever
To be like
My dad has
Your grandpa isn't product
It's very weird
I said I don't know if you could
Is because
He did trust him to host the rest of the four that interpreted
You know that is sort of like
I guess a show of trust in some way
You can interpret that as a pad in the head or you could interpret it is
Alex's incredible
Interrupted mid-sentence amenta
I'm pretty sure my general
General Vibe is
That was a temper tantrum
Because his son was talking to
And he didn't like not being the center of it
Doesn't not feel that way
Leave
Emancipate
Missing something episode
That looks kind of like
Force my hand
By being out of Studio
We're going to take another day off
So we can check in on Alex really forced my hand was the fat
Back that he talked about Portland a little
In a way that I haven't really heard him cover
The situation at all
So it's really really relevant to our interests in our coverage
To see him being support
Because it's in a weapon that can be used against his true enemies
Anybody who has sort of liberal ideas
You knew he was going to
You knew he was going to do it but
I still analyzed at the moment he actually straight upset it
I was like there's always
There was still that part of me
Maybe this
Going to be the one where he's like
I don't agree with Trump on this iPhone
I think this is a government overreach yeah I think you should continue doing everything else that he wants to do but it's hard not to
Get that like
There's gotta be something
It doesn't seem like the last Trump comes from guns
Like individually
I don't know
Because of that necessitated
Talking about this episode
We're covering this episode and there isn't a Monday or Tuesday episode
You know we got
Talk a little bit about this
F***** up weird shipwrecks
Atlanta
I might have just
Ignored The Hodgetwins
But I think it's a really good
Case study
What there
Weather
And then you coming you see these are the telltale signs
Yeah
Tammy
Like I just think this is
You and Alex Mead and alright personality and have no idea who they are
As the monster show responsibility
You think maybe the most important
Cuz if I believe someone who's competent at making sentences
This might be part of this exit strategy
How many times
You go down this road
This strategy has been in
Spray year
It does seem like
Whenever he has mentioned in the past that I want to let you know
Louisiana plan
Yeah possibly
Yessir we webs
We do, but
Weather.com
Check that out
What you like
Comment
Welcome
As you see fit wheels on Twitter
McDowell's giant Israeli review
In your area to help out with everybody doing God's
I'm deeply saddened by the passing of Michael Brooks
Alex
In color