Alexandra Thurston color
We're couple dudes you like to sit around drink red wine and explore the world
Of mr. Jones
If you're nasty
That was the reverse of Janet Jackson
That was very much
Mr Jatt
Sorry
There is a twist
There Is No Nonsense
Neither of us that we don't know what they know
F****** getting rx11
It's intro is
Wonder Woman
Getting out
A little more
I don't know everything about my friend I can tell you everything about it
And that is the rub we're going to be having a really fun episode that
Take us to
We're drinking a little wine by the name of the
Petition
Because this will be the beginning
Very important Expedition
We may very well uncover something that will get us killed
Okay
For you I would like to play out of context drop
From an episode 2015
But very much worth it
A peacock
Screech
I'll come in and check them out
Butter
Amazing
Powerline
Somebody
Rabbit
Apartment complex
Society
Deathstalker
He's laughing at the fact that these owls just murdered his neighbors peacocks in the middle of the night
But I'll murder that
Lamps
Congratulations on becoming a
Donated on the time-travel level
Fans will be doing the special episode
Time-traveling specifications
Welcome to the fold
Going on my own time travel
Yes
I have
Undertaken
Something of
Investigation
This investigation is ongoing
But I'm currently ready to share the beginning of it and tell the listeners if this is Hillary's
Emails all over
It's not
Decided at some point when I found an archive of old episodes
I decided that I wanted to
Figure out exactly where Alex Jones
That was something that is
Important
Consequence to me
Because I'm afraid
It's going to happen
Batumi
Five-year-old like
Sell-by date is that what it's like that episode of lost where
Adjustment has to find his constant
I have to find Alex Jones far enough in the past where he was saying
Right before you get to that one
The signs will be up to meet
Kill you I spell 42
That's really the only option
I will cranberries
I have a lot of experience with Alex from the past
For entertainment
The same person
In 2017
So I wanted to know what the fuc
So I've gone back
You still
A bigot
An idiot
The Trump campaign has changed
Yeah that's what we speculated from
Have
Isolated a start date of my investigation
Doojoon
Pink 2015
Trump
Descended that escalator
And Analysis canvas
Candidacy for president
I am exploring
Kill Baby Hitler
Not
That is where I am beginning my investigation
And I can say with absolute certainty
That Alex Jones is Not 2017 Alex Jones
On June
Okay
No knowledge of Donald Trump
2nei
External Observer
If you listen to the show he doesn't bring him up one
He announces his candidacy
The 17th
Start vet tech
He doesn't half hour interview with a lady who are the city of Visalia California tool.
But she couldn't keep goats in her house
He did a half-hour softener like them
Then like
Communicating with each other on a farm base level just like
I'll pick my trained owls on them and guess what these are
For fun
Yes that was an offshoot of that conversation
21 s***
But that is also has a guest
She speculates that gold is going to be selling at $50,000 an ounce
Shortly
Shortly shortly pretty big jump
$9,000 an oz
I can see it I'll tell you what it never happened
Wildest day in history since 2015 the highest gold has
Has ever been is 30
So they
Really shot that Mark
It didn't destroy Global Currency
Like the entire world the entire world's economy would just
Everything would be kind of fun though
Could you destroy a weird way you have any gold
Worthless because it
Sports
You can't go to it's like going to
Corner store in
Trying to break up
Whatever you have is only worth what someone is able or willing to give you for it
Back in 2015
Forever
Has been distributed by gcvm Genesis
Communications Network
Which is a company that's owned by a guy named Ted Anderson
Midas resources
A gold grill
Gotcha
And then this agenda 21 years with the goat lady
And I'll also story about a guy
Who lived
I believe Huntsville Alabama
He had a trailer that he set up on the outside of town but still within city limits
So he's the hero
No
Nope no Heroes
You just wants to live off the grid
He's got solar panel
You claim that everything's cool
I am cities like you have to have
Your home up to
The code
You don't have
Consistent water
We don't know if you have like winter proof this house
So you just got to move outside Cityline
You can't live within the city especially if you have kids
If you don't have a home that's up to code
And he was like
Not being depressed
Alex's home
That's one day after Donald Trump announce
Unfortunately
On the night of the seven
Something very terrible
And that was the shootout
Killed by a p
No
Shooting at the Charleston
F***
The Dylan roof
Went in and shot up
I was at the Emanuel African Methodist I don't want this to be an entire episode of
It's not going to be entirely that because I think there's interesting angles week
Can take to approach Alex's version of
And we're going to have to
Warren
I promise you this isn't a setup where I was like you to come over
You talk about this
Let's just get it out of the way up top
Yes horrifying event
Terrible
Doesn't really need to be sad
Everyone kind of knows where we
More than any other
Crystallizes the state of America
In the 20s
Really does
Because every thought that
People had a
That's racism
Every single moment
Situation
Is just
All of endemic
Racism
In one
Cuckolding fears
People are taking over fears of a loose cigarette without being murdered by the cops if you're black
But if you murder people
Black people in a church
The cops will take you out to
F****** McGee
Certainly
Beyond
F****** the pale
And you can
But here's the good news
Good
I know that this is going to be difficult for you
Especially Yours
Yes
Similar field
Don't get me wrong as much as you do
I'm yelling on the info
But
I think this is an important document
And a very important piece of my investigation
How Alex went wrong
Because
There is
An interview with a guy
At the end of this
That sort of I think is foundational
Election 26
Teen Behavior
Yeah
Episode
Very perfectly depicts
How Alec
Text Jones goes from ambivalence
True false flag
And it's very interesting
False flag
Sentinel thinking that the shooting was a false flag
Oh
So I'm going to lay it out
Experience
Is
Episode
Iowa can't say one way or the other
Because he knows
How racially-charged it would be
For him to
Yeah so he's like I don't know
I can't say
In the past
We know the operation gladio exist
August
He's just doing that likes putting his toe in the water
Dababy
Until
He has an interview at the end of the episode
With
Preacher
A reverend Childress
Comes on
And basically just says
Come on
Black preacher has said that Alex's
Just freed up
Then why bring the narrative
He got
That's Earth no that's what he thinks he got from that
That gives him
Covering of his ass
It's the same as like I have black friends
Am I understood
I like I understand how kind of
Maybe races it is for me to even say
Suggest that's what's going on
No
Going over the course of the episode
Feels very clear that that's what's going on
Before Childress
The co-host with him once again
Because
Porter beer
Jakari Jackson says almost nothing
Ratso
Secondary element of my investigation is why
Jakari Jackson
I think there's one
There's a
There's just
So much a man can
Alex Jones makes me sick
Silently interviews this picture
I don't know if
It's a little messed up
The first clip is how we start the episode
Deteriorates really quickly and then Alex
Introduces what
Is going to be his sword of driving narrative
About why
The shooting isn't the biggest deal in the world
And it's
Pretty it's in Freeport
I'm sorry
Charleston on the East Coast
Nail looking young man
Boston to church last night
Airport tower
Before
Shooting and killing execution-style
On a
Racial attack
And this is one of these events
Stop
Sarcastic
Dylann roof
Retire
And patches
Medical school
Racist
Death loving scum
In my opinion
Fallout 4
Within a minute of starting his show I
He said he could have just stopped
With a fairly tasteful this guy is a crazy person that is awful it's a racial crime
Both died within a minute of just talkin he's like
But the bigger deal
I mean that's what sparked race
Places that get rid of all this public racism and they go straight for the pre-race
Free racism that's really what that
Sure
Abortion rates
Are kind of interesting to look at minorities
But populations have been dropping pretty consist
4 years
The reason that most experts who looked at the numbers game
Money access to healthcare contraception
What story is
It is not that people want to kill black children and so they
Support
Abortion
Bulshit
Million times a day
Shut the fuk up
Then think for one second
What are you care more about
That these babies are born or that anybody can
F****** feet
And the answer to those anti-abortion people is always
Worth caring about
Atkins
F****** monster
Happily willing to watch hundreds of thousands of children starve
Especially the United States where we have
Hundreds of thousands
Children starving right now or going hungry
But no
It's f****** anti-abortionist
Need to f****** make sure that we get more and more goddamn babies in there and if you don't want that if
If you want abortion
Legalize than your f****** races
Because 50% of all black babies
I've been up for Sinead it or whatever the f*** they want to lie about
Babies are f****** aboard it's up to 51 on this episode
Well then
I don't know I don't know
If you take reality out of the equation
It's actually really good
Because it would be in
Wrestle with the idea that this was
A white supremacist
Who celebrated apartheid Africa South Africa
Who celebrated
Express purpose of wanting to trigger
Like it would be very difficult
So his first volley is
9 people are dead
51%
A black children are aborted
What's the who's going in here for the greater good argument is
Look a lot of people have
Ben
Brain control
Commit crimes and he lifts off like
The Unabomber
Timothy McVeigh
These these folks noted
Right wing
Racist murderer guy who wanted to start a race war specifically
Taxes were an act of War
And that flies by the government
They were controlling him
Through that
That makes a little bit of research into that night did find an article written by a lady
Email address
I don't know if she actually taught you
UCLA or was
Hit a scholarly connection
Article
She is a
Incredibly active member of UFO conspiracy
Communities
Part and parcel with that well she wasn't
Until she wrote that article
To make sure that you would never believe the truth
Right
Like the Unabomber is kind of a really really smart
Virginia's level Alex Jones
Would get rid of all of the racism stuff and be like
Listen
It's actually all of society it's not a small group of it we all need to get out of here
And find out because they're stealing our peacock
Yeah yeah
Imagine if Ted Kaczynski had to fill 4 hours a day
Like I know that manifestos Wong
Struggling
That's as many emails does Hillary left come on now
Alex is struggling at this point to find the foothold of the what the narrative is going to be
Guard a little bit
He does know it ready
He doesn't know that coming out immediately and saying it's fake will open him up Jackie
So you can't do that
Here is how he
Sort of
Ambivalently talks about this post
Already knows
He also knows
I think he does know from
The jump that the narrative has to be
Cotton candy
Like they're going to take our guns
Doesn't know how to get there
And so he's struggling throughout the course of the episode
The ACT
Today
Essentially
But its fake
In order for it to be like this is a plan to take our guns
But he can't do that
Like I said because it opens him up to
Way too much
Very justifiable
Abrasive
So we get into the next
Is it the first time
Volkswagen
Comes up
Well because
Operation Northwoods
As a pretext for war
Because
Operation
I don't think that's what this is
But we seen other demons
Target
All lives matter
Fort Worth
And then it was under control
Public Kitchen
This is
And I did
Brooke
He on September 15th 1990
Kilz to post
See you at the pole rally
Featuring concert by the Christian rock
For committing suicide himself
Occurred at Wedgwood Baptist Church in Fort Worth
In 1999
Is deep stuff about his neighbors saying that
He was dragged out by
Completely on confirmable
But we can confirm
His motivation
That he hated that
Oh
It's crime
Where he went in
Yeah he would have really specific
Well he was a member of a group
Private investigator just came out in
The most intriguing
Houston writer and private investigator John Craig
Interviewed Ashbrook in the presence of several Klu Klux Klan members
In Spring of 1997
The co-writer of the book on whites
Supremacist Craig's is membership in
Hallucinate
Really racist Boomin
The killing of minorities in Jews
Buford Furrow who allegedly shot up a Jewish Day Care Center in Los Angeles
In August is also believed to be a Phineas
He is a member of a group called The Phineas priest
They're also part of an offshoot of the group called Christian identity
They are group that are terrorists
It is a Christian
Christian beliefs were primarily developed
And promoted by two authors who regarded Europeans as the chosen people and Jews is
Accursed offspring of Cain
The juice yeah it's true they they also have a belief that
Version of Christianity
Because of their acceptance
Because
They don't
Nationalist
Supremacist ideal
Unitarians
Be loved like a guy
Who is f****** nuts
Just deciding like
At that f****** bapt
What is church
Didn't get my change right at
Grocery stores
They don't know
I think I think the more reasonable argument is that unitarians are too far gone they're not even Christian
These Baptist need to be Got Back
Can lying and maybe
Spell realized
And come back
Something like that
Crazy hats
It's very difficult
There was a guy named
Jeremiah
Who survived the shooting year old for football
The conversation
He had during the shooting
And is a quote from him
I don't know why but I just sat there looking at him it came towards me
When you got within about one of his guns at me and just glared
I told him you don't have to be doing
He told me to shut the hell up
Then he asked me what my religion was and I told him I was a Christian
A Baptist
He said that sucks
And that it was a stupid religion
Replies no sir it doesn't
It's a wonderful thing God put me on this Earth for a reason
Then I'm certain of that
Ashbrook fired several rounds of this religion is b*******
Then he sat down
Said f*** off and shot him
Hey I use crazy person
Investigators after the fact when they were virtually destroyed the interior of his house
The walls of crowbars
The toilet was
Concrete in the fruit trees growing in the backyard had been poisoned
He's just a nut he was a completely crazy person
Organizations
Like these Phineas priest
Christian identity
Relationship
That was not elected was just about the after
Like it wasn't
Well I mean it was
He was going to most likely
Loaded gun
Like it wasn't
It wasn't he was
Specifically going out
After Baptist
I mean I know he was
He's a f****** lunatic
Who was
Accepted
So this dude is crazy
Probably ran to the gills with p
PTSD
Meet up with
Ukkk guys who
You support everything he believes
Keeps getting kind of
Promoted into these
Cooler and cooler like little Inner Circle
And basically primum with all of this b******* just like hey it could have been anything
You could have been like the real problem is
It's f******
No pic
Disenchanted disenfranchised and they gradually lead them down the path
It's the same with cold
You know you don't know the end until you're too far into think about it
You getting indoctrinated into these hate group
And you maybe don't realize or hate group until
I'm already in
It's Alex
It's the same f****** thing
Yeah
He was a suicide bomber
Yeah just because he
Had a gun
Instead of a bomb doesn't
Any less of a
They terrorists
Yeah he killed seven people four of which were
The point
He went to a white church
Super irrelevant mischief
So we get into the next
To confront
The fact that this whole goddamn
Fox Edward never going to be rid of it not the whole country but a lot of it
Lot of it
Every part of the country
The internet
But
Actually kind of fun
Because Alex in his rambling
Trying to make sure everyone knows that he doesn't like dylann roof
Accidentally supports gun control
Douglas Mexico
WordGirl
That is true I do
But that's just common sense
So there
Now it's now extrapolate that is a parenting technique to AC
Or a better word
If you don't like mentally ill people having guns
This is where we have to get into where Alex Jones
Is really smart as a propaganda
Because
His whole thing
Is that they want to take our guns
When the reality is
The people who are into
Interested in gun control your gun
You can have your gun
But we want to make it more Reggie
We want to make it safer
We want to make a world where it's harder to get a gun
Because people like this assholes
And
You know what
It doesn't matter if it's hard on or not
I want to live in a world where fewer people get shot
Steph
It doesn't matter to me what the solution is
It seems obvious that the solution is gun
Control solution
Truly was
Give everybody 10 guns
So long as fewer people
Forget f****** murder
I'm for it we want the end
The reason I was saying you smart is that every single thing
Come Out Swinging as if it was your afraid of
You are always on the offense
Even when you're being
So
In the same way that like this isn't it
Cuz if you don't
You give
A little bit
You show weakness
As long as you projected strength
Immigration at all time
People will
You know you can't really have an argument
Because
He does In that clip he agrees
If I was I would not let him have
Yeah but then his is come back to you
Because I
To do that over my son government I don't want to Manny's town and eggs
Yeah you know that church we just talked about
There's another one
Bring up
By the way did you hear or shot for shot and killed
Send white people
Bye
5 blackgummy
Walmart
The news organized
London Telegraph
Reporting on what Mini
He has David Knight on to talk a little bit more about this but if they don't get into any detail or actually talk about what the X
Actual situation they're talking about is
1993 in South Africa is the st. James church masses
It's sort of split through the sands of time
Cuz it was real bad
Indian South Africa
The end of Apartheid
For folks
So there was this one of four major attack
Between late 1992 all the way through 1993
Perpetrated by the Athenaeum people's Liberation Army
Who the group
Which was in 1960 I believe
There's nothing worth
69 people were killed
And 180 injured
Many shot in the back
Wien
Police reports claim that quote young and inexperienced
Police members
Panicked and opened fire on protesters
Setting off a chain reaction
This sharpeville massacre happened during a protest of what was known as path laws
Your pants laws
I've heard of them I
Don't quite remember entirely.
They were required South Africa
It was their movement and was one of the foundational aspects of the apartheid system
All day everyday
Absolutely
It's not a it's a reasonable thing
You don't want people just going anywhere they put one of their crazy what are there terrorist
We got to make sure we know who everybody is
Group of people doesn't
Joy 1967
Because originally it was just for men over 16
MMA
Winkler women
And younger people and it was just too, nothing where
What the fuk guys
Right
Beauty scribe
Young and inexperienced cops just open fire on
Some people say the protesters were throwing rocks
But it's unclear
There are other sources
Does it say that they were completely peaceful
And the cops fired
So the a pladsen people's Liberation Army was formed in response
That Massacre
Under the name Poco
But then change their name later
Let's be honest
But
I don't want a lot of people
Most of the p
People who were negatively affect
Probably did
Actively
Probably actively
Worthy of what
But I am
Far more sympathetic
To the Azan
Liberation
Every white person was
Complicit in
How things were operator
There is an argument not a good enough argument that I would support killing them
But that's definitely true
I don't think for them
Hazmat
My empathy for the white
After all four men responsible were captured and arrested
They appealed for amnesty from Bishop Desmond Tutu Truth and Reconciliation committee
We don't want to do Nuremberg trials
Heal the wounds
And they ended up meeting with survivors and family members of victims
From the massacre that they
Carried out
They reconciled
They understood the ramifications of their actions
They repented
Society
They were all granted amnesty by The Truth and Reconciliation committee
Consider this
Only 849 out of
D7100
12 application
Framesi
Reconciliation committee
War except
Who was not a rubber stamps
Clearly they went through the process and found
Alright
Makes sense
Repeatable Behavior
It's not like it's not like a breaking-and-entering you get out of jail
You're going to break
We're going to commit larger crime
This was a you guys
Systematically oppressed and enslaved my people and we fought back
If you don't understand why we have at least
Song justification
For fighting like this
You're an insane
Carrying out orders
To some extent
From there
Apla organization
Soldiers
The Granary
The organization was created in response
2 police
I don't want it I would never come out and say I support
Conclusion of the Truth and Reconciliation committee something but if you don't
Have simple
Before it
You're you're just being
Understand
The
The social dynamics
The create stuff
Like that
Intentionally
Like I was being intentionally obtuse
For the argument white nationalism
Trapped into this sis
That is
Oppressing you and
Destroying you
Everything
Single
There's no way that you can
Begin to feel
So helpless
What else is there
Acts of violence that idea of it is the
The voice of the oppressed
Does that make sense
You can't get recourse
4 grievances that are real
In court
If the system is so broken again
It sucks but the only thing you can do is burn down a building murder that kid
The Vic
Who murdered that
That kid
Amazon
Was just
F******
Like she was cleared of all charges
Cleared of all charges even though they had it on camera that she act
Cleared of all charges
Lady in Oklahoma
Shelby
Was a police officer
Who murdered Terence Crutcher
Straight up murderer
No murdered him
No other way to describe
And she was acquitted of all charges
Just went straight back
Type of s*** happens
You look at that and you think
There is no justice
No there's no just
So why why would I want to go through these
Why would I want to
Because I am getting no justice anywhere else
I have to
Take justice into my own
Right
But like you said
Willfully obtuse
To think that
Riot
And the like are are some sort of
Philiac
The black lives matter protest
Just want to kill cops
They want Justice
You know what you get
You get jumped
So if it's only applied to you and not to them
Get ready for some s*** burning down
Alex would argue in favor of riot
For this perceived they're going to take our guns
It's just really unfair it logically inconsistent
Play here
I come
Almost immediately after he talks
It accurately about the South Africa
Situationally called The False Flags
Okay
I also they imply that it was white people who carried it out
And pretended they were black
Call directions
It's why people we're definitely not being racist about this not being racist
I don't buy his
At all it's so stupid
He comes back
Also laments
The state of being
24/7
Perception
That black sermons by white people
And don't even cover
This is being hyped
Foregoing
Mentally ill respond to build towards a crescendo
Pushing for this to federal police after a summer of Rage
Coming up this summer
This is it
This is the big one
What is left
Federalization gun control
So that's the dumb prediction
Are we can now 2 years after look back in that there was not a summer of Rage
Crackdown
There's not a federalization of the police what do you mean federalizing the
Play Store
Talking about specifically is responding to comments that like Al Sharp
Captain made after the Charleston shooting
He was talking about how
In
The Civil Rights
Are we needed to involve
The federal government
And states rights was
The bad guy
Because the idea that states could decide the blacks can't vote
Sort of thing was a real problem
I've never seen states rights
That kind
Acceptable
Generally yeah really really bad thing you really really bad
Even even Sharpton's argument about that isn't saying
Staples
Anything
It's there any issues such as
Human rights
You need to have the federal government over
Oversee
Pretty much the only reason that we have
Because otherwise
I don't know Oklahoma could just be like
No blacks
Fallout
Right
Flea markets
Oklahoma facts
So they wouldn't
God I hate
Would work out that way
Of course not
He was responding also two other incidents where
Much like that situation.
Cops kill
African-American
A slap on the wrist
He's talking about systematic racism the federal government needs
To get involved
Because otherwise
Local
State
Bodies are not taken care of the issue
Every major
Advance
Any kind of racial
As always,
From the top
Because quite frankly
From Federal
Governor
Quite frankly most people are for it
In small Pockets they're not right
Alex is Bixby is this idea federalization
That would be
The government
Evil government that he has in his head
Control of all police
I may use it
Police state
That ends up intake
An hour in a repressive regime
Be the reason that I
Fixated
I had never heard that before
And my instinct
Whatever he says
It's a bad thing it's good
Tell me about and I just had
This is a great idea you can know whatever the right thing is exactly the opposite of what Alex to say
Good thing I actually do kind of feel like would be much more likely to be on the negative cider
Inside the borders and the Army doesn't
Federal police system that was
Completely and utterly about that
Much larger
If everybody became
As we all know about the
There in 10
Asians are not always good and generally can be very bad I agree in principle
Any idea of a completely federalized
Federal imput to help
Contain
And deal with situations that local and state governments are unwilling to
It's the same thing with the misunderstanding
Gun control
Versus taking your gun
Yeah it's a lack of nuance
Need York propagandist
A Paul Joseph Watson report
From this episode
Because I knew that you could
You couldn't handle excellent
Is all is all just about Hawaii
I cut that out
Entirely
But
Charleston
Shooting was fake
Again in wrestling
And it's so clear to me
In the clip what he wants
To say it's fake
Pull the trigger
He's
Criminal elements
Done
Things like this before
The pastor was a state
Charleston
That's all I needed to know
It's
Very very very
Suspicious
Citizens
Add radio
Such long pauses
It's clear that you just like
Can't
F*** it said evil twin it's the same
It's the same thing he did immediately following the pizzagate
We have the new information about the
Which was
Our government has done stuff like this
So it could have been
I'm just asking question
Yeah it's it's
Broadcast because it's all just insinuation it's all
He's like it's
Suspicious
This is the place that
Was targeted
Water is an incredibly estorick black church
So it's not
Suspicious if that was what was targeted by a racist
It's a very sacred place to a lot of people and has a rich history
So it's not it's not suspicious at all
Argument
People who think
At the race Wars
Most of them
It will be all on
People versus All Blacks
Most people do not realize that there's a good chunk of a
Nah dude we are not on the white races side on this what kind of look
I'm late but I'm not real
I'm not all the stuff is nice I think it's an important distinction to make two but neither of us are ashamed of the fact
That's not the
But we recognize the history
White people in this country
And throughout the world and not all of its bad
But there is a very very serious history of depression
Because if you ever read a history
Book and the sentence to read is then
And then white people showed up you go
F*** no no no that's not going to end well mean even on our last episode we completely destroy Guatemala for
Are bananas like it's
It was about communism but it really wasn't
Maybach
Listen be white
Is not
Inherently better
Inherent
Play better is obviously better part of the Promenade
Just raped and murdered our way into
Like it's not a good sister
Ultimately a good system for us either
Of course
If you have this kind of
Privilege
The idea of somebody equalizing things
Do you means they're taking away your
It doesn't mean that everybody is
You're being
Lower
People think of it as a
This is being taken from me and given to them
Does a zero-sum game your loss is my game
Everybody
It is always a good thing if more
People have more
The idea that specially the most fundamental things
I'm saying about the the whole
Well the rich people need as much as they can to give us some when it's
If poor people had more money they would buy more s*** we'd all have more money
With really good ideas would create business
People like Hamdi ulukaya
Oportun
More available
More are available for everyone
It boggles my mind how you can't understand that
Trickle-down
Alex gets pretty defensive about
His guns
He says something
I can't be a lot right
This is
Basically
Please guilty to a crime he was not accused of
Brown
I don't watch
Warfare
But I assure you my Barrett 50 caliber rifle
Any murders
Kallax Shelf
It's been used
Hundreds of thousands
Of the
In circulation in the US
I can't I couldn't figure out what that one crime was
Buy guns weird
She thinks of the bet
And then he goes on to defend the gun
The cow has never been used in murders
He starts crying about Nam
He killed not
It'll put him down
You know I kept trying to make him drown
Or whatever
So do you think about that that's slightly misleading is a Barrett 50 cal is a f****** huge gun
Very large one of those guns that you have to like
Prop up those guns
Comical cartoon version of ammunition belt
You set up a position and proper gun up on a tripod
And you being it with you is impossible
Is it
No one has ever used
Of course it's like Terminator 2 using the minigun
Liquor store
Call McDowell
AK-47 can be stealthy hidden on your back
To some extent
And handguns are way more
Useful than a f***
Barrett 50 caliber
So anyway
Like unnecessary
I use it to scare the government less they get out of control
More of what it is
Assault rifles are military
To have an assault
50/50 on it I do believe that
Dumb
Piece of the we should be armed
In case the government gets out of line
I think some of that argument is
Yeah but
We're all thinking it's more and more recent
I know
I know the point that whatever the government has is
Bigger and badder than anything we could possibly have
I do know that is true also
But I have a number for
Central Missouri
They aren't crazy
And they're very responsible
I feel the fact that like
That Community does exist
I know that there are a pocket of people who are into guns
And are just like
I keep them cuz
I'm interested in guns and
I want to be armed
In case I have to protect
Guns make your dick
Will make you feel like
No that's fine
Association
But you need that
I'm fine with that but for real
There's no reason to have an assault
No it's true but I do know some people who have them and they're responsible with them and I would trust them
It's not
It's not for hunting per day
Retro defense
Fantasy
It is I disagree with it but at the same time I get the principal and I'm not
Everyone shouldn't have assault rifle
I think the
Going to come down to work gun control
Make sure that people who will use them
4L
Don't have
Or make it harder for them to get them even though it's illegal
Fort Lee
Legally murky
We study
The results
The guns
Because our gun lobbies are so amazing
You can't research
They won't give you any funding for
Can still kind of
Go back through
Police reports
And in situations
Where a gun was had and
Potentially been used
Find yourself good guy with a gun
Never works
Ever so very very very few situations
F*** you man
Do you have anecdotal evidence from this I don't need any
Big picture you're totally right but it is actually kind of interesting that the Saint James Massacre
He started shooting at them
And because of that they ended up please
Breath
I hadn't been there and shot at them
Petrol bomb
But they were going to
Killed
So many
Individual entity
Brighton there are a couple really work out that way
Yeah you know
F******
One-time something happen
On the whole
The good guy with the gun theory is
Complete and utter
Let's get off this gun topic for a little bit cuz Alex wants to take a transition
A talk a little bit about the eye
The other black people are taking white people's women
You know me I have
Low opinions about this is Alex or responding to
What dylann roof halves
All that and Alex sort of
Don't get the point and buys into the narrative a little bit too
Control
And taking over our women
Attack
Yes
In a racist
Idiot
Girlfriend
F*** you
Because he's getting his women
God damn you
Got the thousand yard stare somebody who's been
Alex is not nowhere to land
Is going on
The pilot was trying to come in for a landing at
Don't do it don't know not here not here
His argument like
To a certain extent is
He kind of just needed a girlfriend
That's problematic because it does not a great argument but does have some Merit
No because there's plenty of racist
No I'm not saying that I'm taking this
Is his logic
Is
I'll just because the other ones are so much
Far off base
I'm happier with him saying
Hey the real problem is this guy needed to get f*****
Then him staying at the Falls
That sounds like something like a shock jock show
Howard Stern's wife
You know what
That's dumb
That's just dumped horrifyingly offensively productive but it is when you're using that as
Rebuttal to
Dylann roof
Claims that black people are taking our women
That sort of thing first
Stupidest
Using that as a rebuttal to that
When you use that at in contacts
There
He is given
Credence
In many ways
Dylan roofs grievance
Because he is
He's responding to it Envy
Girlfriend
Like that sort of thing
Well it's laying in the same bulb
But it is his
It's his version of being fair
Like the idea of like
To me it's not a race
Tumi
You're not mad at
Race
Just lashing out
Can't get laid me off
The Hook from saying
It's about Race 2
It's just about showing exactly but again we can talk about toxic masculinity
Globalist
Such a classic
Racism racism
Patriarchy
Dovetail to
Women
Are weak
You know
Willing to be seduced women from these
Black people. Has passed
Conscious
Kind of like
Racism and sexism are all tied up into one big.
Billy driving the p**** industry
But
So
Remember I was telling you about these things
You donate $10,000 a month you can become a policy customer Rose
But your wife I don't know I'm not sure exactly where I was going there I will stimulus will work out
Peacock that's all we want I just wanted to say those two words next
$15 month polityka
If you
If you remember I was telling you about the st. James Massacre
But Alex was pitching a tent
But all the victims were white be there
Alex
Has the more thoughts about it
Hear about it
Text David native
About everything
Accidentally
In South Africa
It was never completely proven
In fact
Was the opposite completely proven
Kind of a true statement
Completely proven
Because of the obvious fake
Fact that I was
So stupid
In this next clip Alex.
Victim disarmament Zone
That's up that's gun talk for we should allow guns in churches and schools
Carino's the David Knight is super against abortion
So he does this
I swear to God he thinks it's like a bit
He thinks he's doing a good bit
Like
But he's Dennis Miller some s*** coming on a conservative showing
Raley's
It basically what Dennis Miller
Good night.
But the other thing that we need to look at
People area we don't want to have weapons
Weapons and the whole second amendment is essentially about the right
He can carry out the dead black babies
How many wants to kill black people that's infected
Real solid
Real good argumentation emotional
Strength
To be this angry all day today
I know
Are you trying to suck
The lifeblood out of me
Yeah kind of but also
That's unbelievably racist b******* and
Spinning
My life
Absolutely insane anytime
Anybody in my family
When they have that
What about what about
The number one killer of black people is abortion
So that means I can't be racist
Because I know
That even though that's not
We can test the premise
Right
At the bane of the right-wing
I have some interesting ideas about statistic
I actually just listen very carefully to what he says
Because he
He let slip that he's aware that he's wrong
But then minimizes the fact that he has just left
But he knows he's wrong
It's very interesting clip
This empty leave my kingdom
Look
Paul Watson broken down
Police report
But
You should have the mic sound because you missed the most important thing he said there
I'm going to play it again or at least after he gets out of Paul Joseph Watson
Because it's essential
To hear him contradict himself within 4 seconds
Okay
Police report
But
So you saying the statistics are they don't lie and they say that 8 times
More white people are attacked by black people
Before that he said
He thinks the
Statistics are jilted towards
Because of police reporting
And that is 100%
So prior to
She's saying that the
He said the statistics lie
6 Arline
Yes alright
This is a very difficult thing
This is a complicated enough to know
Not necessarily true
I mean I know it's
I got to push it because
I've done it I have a I have a Bedrock of racism has got a hold of
I want to be totally clear I'm not cutting out stuff that like
Makes all of this okay
I don't know
I just have to only way is if at the end of every clip that you have played for
Whenever Alex
I always get really self-conscious if people think that I'm strategically editing things and making it look like he's saying he's not
I just want to be clear that like
Most of the stuff that I've cut out is
Is just diversion
Down the road talking about like
The Batman Aurora shooter and Ted Kaczynski
He talks a lot about that
Birkey's the issue a little bit
Because he makes the argument that all those people were brain-controlled and used
A false flag attack
And stuff like that
And I don't have the f****** energy
Make this a 5-hour episode where we break down each and every one of those
But most of those are
Bulshit
Hey you know how we're talking about this one
Just apply all of the same stuff different
Events in there than others
In the sense that like Ted Kaczynski is way more interest
Because he was part of
MK Ultra studies
He was
Dosed with tons of hallucinogen
Gone off
Otherwise
That's entirely possible
But that does not mean he was being brain
Controlled
Radio that
Be that as it may
That's most of the stuff that I've cut out
Let me see the other thing about that
Golden tickets
If we could mind control
God dammit
The thing that you would see all the time to solve all your problems
Just mind control somebody in a box
All the claims the globalist want Bush much harder
Programs in place for hundreds
Thousand people are being brain control
Likespike innocent monkeys in Bastrop
Exactly
Saving
That
Perspective
No
Follow me here
Where would you keep
The perfect
Unbelievable
I don't understand the question is phrased
Okay
Perimeter
Fish people
How else
Do you defeat nuclear submarine
Fish-people exactly it all comes together now mind-controlled fish-people with Bob
Destroy submarine I like talking about years ago
This is because
Back then they only had fish people
They've been working on reptilian
People
Water an idiot
So they're working on that
I would go with your best bet though
Jesus lizard people
Lizard people
There we go
Stupid f****** stupid
So I think we got screwed up whatever he stuck
Great Clips
Minimizes the deaths
The people at that church
Says something's that
Is so not true about liberals
Is it awesome thing that he always does
Where he pretends there's a conversation he had with somebody
I meant turns them into a d
Itsfunneh
But at the same time
Hundreds of thousands of people died in auto accidents
The meaning of plan on that
What happened
Impossible
Well the folks are dead
Wilderness
I just don't get it
F*** you Alex is missing the point at 3 Alex XM body
The creation of racial division
This is the worst
Word
You can you imagine these liberals that he talks to off camera
What
Direct
I don't know who he's pretending to talk to Steven
Bianchi
Camera at some point
Talk to Alex Jones
And express their actual opinions off-camera
You should listen to my opinions off of the show let me tell you some
We're on camera right now
Alien contact with Alex
We just don't give anyone to link
Intentional
Exercise
So a stupidest s*** there
He does not
You stand at all's at like my experience of the Charleston
Some shooting was great
And empathy
And from everything that I experience
Some people around me it was a
It was it was not a
F*** white kind of moment it wasn't evil
Evil about it
That you have to go
Oh wait
Just come out and bit like
This is a horrible thing
But I don't think it should be used as a
Excuse
At the very least you go
That's up that's a thought we understand your position
If that's what your position is that
When you start justifying it by
We're really proud because of black people
It's a problem because you guys don't care about abortion
Pass shooting you're the reason that I think white people are evil
Because of you
That was
Like I said
It was it was a unifying moment where I
I think most
People saw it as a as a call to
Karen respect each other more as opposed to a
Feud
And I think that's most of
The last
Hopefully that's
I mean I keep I keep saying like
The difference
The left and the right
The Way We Were
To stop and why
Asos down
Yeah
Because
The last always
Empathize for at least that's one of the Hallmarks of being
Is the idea of emphasizing with even the people
You don't
Agree with
Like why are there so many thing
Country we wanted to see how they feel about Trump right now as trumpet
Is f****** over their lives.
Like
Right
It's appetizing and understanding to a fault
We're trying to understand them and to see if there's some way that we can get through to them
Do you understand
To June of 2015 to study Alex Jones from the moment Donald Trump
It's exactly that I want understand
I want understand what happened
But if you're on the right
You don't
You don't want to
Stand it
It's something that you want to use to reinforce your black-and-white belief
You know like that but if I can
True or untrue
Dichotomy absolute
Yeah
We are good
And there
Yeah and so anything that we determined
Is so bad that we don't care
I don't know why I'm supposed to care about
I don't like it but why do I care
I don't need to emphasize
Show me to know how these people would feel I don't care
Because he refuses to take things
In their proper context
Of course cuz he
Lack reading comprehension
Elac fact integration abilities
Everybody mentioned at the top of this episode
Episode is an exercise in Alex Jones trying to find his foot hole
He climbing up a mountain
Essentially
The mountain that is propped up in front of him
He had no idea
It's the world
His foot
A giant roadblock he's got to get over it somehow
He's trying to figure out is the argument going to be
This is fake
Is it going to be this guy is crazy
Is it going to be about medication is it going to be all the
Depressed
Instances
What am I going to do
And nothing is really sticking
Until at the end of the episode
Towards the end of the episode
He has Reverend Childress on for a
An interview
Exactly
This clip is long and we are going to pause whenever you need to
Long
But the reason that I kept it as one clip
Is because
It shows a metamorphic
You can hear Alex
Figuring it out
And being like
Bissell
Business plan
Something is really interesting is that like
He is at adaptable the in the moment
At this point
Completely silent
He says maybe a couple words
And whenever you start stalking Alex custom options
Might be part of my ongoing study of why Jacari quit
This is this is this is wild
This I really think as revealing
The trials and travails
You will have the right
Together
A lot of it is basically
Was ordered for our
Issues and problems
But
And then use it as a weapon
You have some of these speakers at these rallies that are basically was facing
I'm an African-American
And every celebration of America
Race war
But their hyping this Discord hyping this manipulation
Amazon the Redguard website
That idea of
So they kind of brilliant
That they've got
Professors have
Together it's not
Look
It again
The elites
It's the elites manipulating all of the
These people
Colleges are breathing
Institution
They're attending
More cover
Underneath that like
No it's not a race
These black p
Would also be on our side
If they weren't being funded and manipulated
And all of these things
I'm not
Reese's
I am against being manipulated in these people
So that we can all come together
Problems have nothing to do with race
I would be remiss if I didn't point out there what he's talkin about is like the Red Guard and like
These these organization
Call Black
There's also
Wow
Put underneath the surface
That's the thing never quite cross that line
Of understanding
Hey this isn't about race
But somehow
I'm angrier
Who aren't supporting me
Premier
Maybe
If I think of these
People is Trader
I think of those people
As the bad guy
And conversely the people who were fighting against
I guess even worse idea of you saying I don't like
This more
Priorities
I think we should have a race war but I'm just angry or when my race is against me
Yep that's a good step
Also I want to say that I
Love
Jakari Jackson
Voice
He has got a great for it
Like listening back to these episodes
I'm pissed he's not still around
Jude he has got a
Radio voice
And
Ambivalently sit there silently while Alex
Great because it seems like he wants to be like
What does
Tired
And that's just a sign like a fever blister
The sores are coming up and the super hardcore left is like active right now
You're coming out
Knowledge
This just makes me nauseated to see whether it was staged or not
People are making their speeches now
This is
And are in a position to profit from it
We discussed it thoroughly
I said come on look at the time they look at look at who's doing it
Speech he gave as he left
Across
America
Whatever
Mason Justin Bieber
But months ago with plan
Very very skilled
Months ago this kid
For this week
And
This weekend in every major
You can see the whole roll out
Is there a mean dude that was a f****** long clip and I apologize
It's a spider who plays of the Hulk
But you can see his mindset Transformer
Entirely from
Oh f*** we figure
Here's how we do it
This Reverend Childress
Has given me
A couple pieces of important information that I would have no way of knowing otherwise
He's weaving them into a
Conspiracy
And I'm going to put that over by and make it to
I lost myself
I mean that's a hundred percent
What's going on
Trying to figure out how to make this cohesive
And now he has an interview with the minister
Who tells him Juneteenth is coming up
Thursdays are when you fertilize your speeches
Music off
And I'll be honest is
Like he's the one who is like I'm not saying that he's being manipulated to Alex's agenda
Like they're spiraling together
Yeah like each of them is coming at it from a different angle and they're just spinning towards each other like the toilet bowl of lunacy that
Together
For Alex to jump
You run the website called black genocide. Org
You just sure can throw genocide into whatever it is you want to say now
I believe he is also one of us has a lot of feelings about the abortion
Being a genocide whole thing
I think that is super interesting because you get this Alex Jones
Is all his brain is always working
In terms of like trying to figure out how to
How to spend
Up to the interview
He brought up these
Other is Timothy McVeigh Unabomber
Sirhan Sirhan
And Cher
She could but he couldn't quite figure out how to make it
It like this instant
Why
What is what is going on other than the ideas
Wanted to do
So that would just be like
Will the fascinating thing about his
His bringing up all of those other things
Is that they were all uniformly
Right-wing Terror
Okay what kind of Aurora shooter
Is more Jay
That didn't have political
I don't think so but if I were
You know what you might be right he was just trying to kill as many people as you could
He chose that seat or not because of the Batman thing but because
Yeah he played up the theme
But
The point that I want to make the Unabomber
Is that
Ruby Ridge
With that
You have the luxury of
They
General consciousness of thinking of those not as
As right-wing terrorist
Those are not
The same thing as
The way that we think about any kind of
Mass shooting with a Muslim
Involved with it
It's always
Terror
White people can pull these right-wing terror attack
Text which are the most
Common form of terrorism in the United
White people
Doing right-wing murders
Yap the most common form of terrorism pepin's a bit even though he brings up these
Very similar
Right-wing terror attack
You don't associate the two together
Because he gets to pull this stuff on dylann roof as
A possible false flag
But
It's never then brought back
Back to the fact that it
What is the best camera
Terrorism
As
It's the same bulshit
But the luxury of
Murdering is
You get to
Each one is if it's
Individual
Privilege to a certain extent but I also think I slightly disagree with you
Okay
Adjust in the sense that I don't think Dylan roof head evolve
I think he from everything that I've read about him
Was
Is just a radicalized bigot
Like I think he was just
Not in the same way it was wrong about a lot of stuff
Most of what motivated him was
A feeling that most
The work of the government
Was oppressive
Maybe it's just because it directly involves the government
As it moves like just for cultural
Situation
More along the lines of
Exactly
I don't see any way that you can
A specific
If you can go into a black church
And kill those p
Without
Having fall of
The political connotations
Is involved let me defend myself slightly on my
I think that was second state
Second stage in his motivation
Cuz he wanted to start a race war but the reason he wanted to
Clams
How to start a race war
But
The Third Step Beyond that is to reform the government that
Should be a pressing Blackmore or whatever
But that's secondary to
Where is with Timothy McVeigh ice
Sincerely believe from everything I understand
His primary motivation
Against directly
The state of the government
And so
Yep what's the point
He's exactly that
Okay you are looking into these things
Specifically enough
To find the difference
Now
You go to a new story today
A Muslim person
Kills Christian
Or a Muslim person
Blows up a
Right
Are those going to be research
Thoroughly
Or they both going to be tied to
Islamic terrorism
Reporting as a whole
Certainly in the same way that I'm looking at
That is but culturally you're right.
Yes of course you would because
Because I would
In the same way
But the point is in the larger consciousness
They would be lumped together where is these two are not
Because we have a slight disagreement but
Mostly agree
But let's
Let's now
Take a moment
Ethan parsley
Because we're done with the Charleston portion of the show
Charleston future episode
But
For now for the rest of this episode
To cleanse your palate
I have a quip here
We're just going to listen to owls murder peacocks
A clip of Alex
Breyer hour and 45 minutes of a show I just want to listen to this
I don't think he's telling the truth about any of that but
For no reason
Go ahead
Image lb-5 cops
Do you want to do something
Make a swing
He watched the show
No I think it's that scene with bird from The Wire
Cannot tell the difference between
It's not. But at the same time
What does soda the movie
Kelso
You got a small dick Alex
Department
Take a rest assured
Crime in sports
But in the final equation
The police
Is about bringing chaos
No one wants a war with the police
Nobody
Even militant groups don't want a war with the police
No one wants
If you push pee
They will think
This is the only
Can I have
That's it
That's what it is nobody wants this what people want is justice
Yeah if that f******
Murderer
Who killed Terrence crunch
The terrorist
Reply
If you went to prison for life
Nobody would be like
Get all the cops people would be celebrating because they
Feel like f***
We can trust the justice system a little bit more that would be the celebration it wouldn't be
Mitch goes to jail
It would be that thankfully
We can
Finally trust the justice system a little bit
That's it
Nobody wants
Nobody wants to kill cops
Really don't want to be killed
Yeah
It's lacking in Alex Jones understand
The world
Phase of this
June 18th
Episode
In 2050
Every mention the reason that I went back
Forgotten
That trumps
Announcement
The Charleston shooting were so close
Together
Not as well as a real surprise to me
Just something that I knew we needed to cover if we were going to be talking about
Sacrifice
Launch
Trump into the
And then on the 17th was
The Charleston
And also on the 17th
He said
That comment
What about the Mexican
Yeah
The bring the rapist
I'm sure some of them
I'm paraphrasing.
The reason that I am the reason that I embarked on this
Exploration
Analysis is because I wanted to know where
Down the line Alex
Not as my primary
Focus
In this investigation I will find the exact day
Haha
Understand
Maybe a little more
Probably not but I'm going to try
You will find the exact day
You will also write the date and s*** on your way probably you will have luster my blood
I'll have my people take you out of here
Yeah then I'll be like I got it
So then the show will be very proud Alex Jones so mad
Kobe Crazy
What I did find in this episode which it like I said
Is 2 days after
Trump has announced his candidacy
He ends the show with an interview with a guy named Larry Nichols
Are you aware of Larry nickel
I don't know
Is
Call f***
Already
Alright alright
Let's do this
I'll get to sit down I'm going to buckle into my chair and we're going to f****** make it through Clinton inside or both
Let's go as Alex says maybe 20 to 30
Because
They
Write the reason that I think this interview is incredibly important is because
Hugh
Support
Trump
Is clearly
Face on a
Hatred of hell
Well that was
Yeah but we can we can that was large-scale support
Crystallized
Trumpism Oz
2 days before this
He has no end
He has not mentioned him at all now he has to Alex
From Priscilla Joe
In the same way that that interview with Reverend Childress
With transformational
And Alex is being able to call it a false flag
This interview
With Larry Nichols
I believe
Is fully transformative
And sets the stage
For Alex
As a potential
This interview isn't
Credibly f*****-up
Scary
And throughout the course
Just to Larry Nichols is
It's going to
To become even worse
I'm going to let the first quit play
You can see the beginnings of the interview
What this guy is all about
Years ago
Another program
Stop.
Guillain-Barre was using if you'll recall Alex gets Jackson
Jesse Jackson wants to smoke supposed to start
Major city
Marshall home
Once I get the provisional government
We've got problems
You are so right it's not about race Alex
It's going on is about
What's going on today
You have to be so careful
So very careful because anytime
You know
Total chaos
All bets are off
And whoever
Collapses they become king or queen
His
So
That is like
Whoever's in power
Finally
Trump is in power
What's not yet that's not there
Larry Nichols
Southern Accents telling me it's not about race
Yeah I have a Southern accent at the very least
Hide
Foghorn Leghorn telling you it's not about the chickenpox
If the ice always
F******
Want that race war
So much to say
Oh well
It's going to start the tit-for-tat
Then we're going to be justified it's just going to start the war and its back and forth and then
We don't have a choice
In the way they always presented his black do something
Respond whenever it's
It's never about the systematic racism what's going on
What causes
Black people too
Mostly
Just Pro
It doesn't cause murders but it causes
Essentially Proto
Nobody is
Protest because she is going so great
I know it's protesting because they want
No sew
I agree with you Larry is bad opt
Because it was nonsense insist but like Vince Foster getting hurt
Doubt about like Vince Foster's murder
Larry Nichols along
We need to stop calling it Vince Foster
Murder
Sorry
Ci3
Yeah you're already on the defensive by calling it Vince Foster's murder
Vince Foster
Your suicide is very suspicious not suspicious at all suicide
We're in the same ways of making that one dude
I wasn't going to say his name
F*** you if you think that matter
But it's the same way that there
Once you frame the conversation that way
Before I even start talking to you
I'm on the defense
Did kill himself
Seth Rich was murdered was murdered
Seth Rich was murdered
I agree middle different
Either contextualizing his actual murder in a bad way
As opposed to invented
Conspiracy
It was a murder because of
What's more important is that Larry is coming on the show and a very specific
For Alex
It's incredibly f***** up and I think it's
You can see it if you watch the video
Of this episode
You can see Alex start
To get it
You can see the pieces in
The cogs in his brain
Start to
Move
This clip
Is really where
Like you can you can see it in the
Timer
I am the savior of the world
So you think this is a full-on Jesus comp
Listen to this clip and tell me I'm wrong
These people have certain goals they want in their going to get them and the reason Alex I think contesta
For where they're going
Right now what they want is to get absolute
Government
Because once you control
They want to move us
YouTube.
Bernie Sanders a socialist
Take the Middle East
20 years ago
Stabilize the Middle East
That was a hard sell
Let's pause there for just a second
Figure out how to achieve that goal
Automation
Stephen Miller is writing that speech
That's insane I don't
Nothing is real
So I mean
Which is going to bring
Is altogether
Noted
Race-baiting Muslim hater
Boys in the Middle East
That's their end goal
Congratulations you can just do nothing even started
Before America was even like
Kernel of an idea people's mind the Middle East
In trouble
Like in the Bible is in trouble
In the Quran
Contrived
But now the end of this clip get to my point
About Alex
And his
Supposed place in the world
Moving our way
Hillary
Republican nomination for the Republican
Alex
Ready get on the bowl of lightning
Get the Tea Party
Together
Stop it
Jesus
F****** Christ
Sleazy there
That was that was the call to action
Ferrara
Hero's journey
That was the called action
Joseph Campbell straight out of the f****** Central Casting
So now it's time to talk about Larry
Who is this
The old man on the phone
F******
Just personification of old white
Southern privileged white was with
Bill Clinton from the beginning from before he was ever in office
Right so he's Arkansas.
That
There's no evidence
Set his relationship with
Of Arkansas
He was hired by Bill Clinton
In 1988
He was hired as the marketing director for the Arkansas development Finance
Authority
The Associated Press reported that
He made
42 long distance calls on State
On behalf of
Nicaragua
These calls were to Nicaragua
Two senators and politicians who supported the contras
For real
Cheap 142 calls that are easily trained
Because of this
Clinton fired
Immediately
Insider Nichols Insider Nichols
Making too many clothes phone calls
Nichols Clinton for improper dismissal
And use this as a platform
During his 1990 re-election
Much of what we know now is the Clinton conspiracies
Come directly
From Larry nickel
Almost all of
Really
Yep the idea of the Mena Arkansas airport the drug-running that was going through that at all came from him
He brought forth a bunch of women who bill was having affairs with some of them real some of them not
On January 10th which before we go any further
Nobody's
Nobody here between the two of you between the two of us is going to say that Phil Clinton is not
Mostly
Yeah totally
Super arepas
Even really terrible people can be the victims of misinformation
Hi I would like to be responsible for the things that he has done
To be held responsible
Possible
The stuff that's not true is
Absolutely irresponsible
Absolutely
So in January or January 25th 1990
Bill Clinton
He said it is time to call the fight I have with Bill Clinton over
I set out to destroy him for what I believed happened
Interesting
And wound up with
In the long run certainly
Yeah that's right
Right-wing radio show
Pete Santilli for Bill and Hillary
Committed murders
So hold on
They sent me overseas to kill people for them
I'm told me it was for the good of the country
So when they asked me to do it for them in the states it's no different
The real truth is I Did It For The Money
And I didn't even give a s*** about the women I beat in the man I murdered
The clintons are bad people hold on
Sports
The clintons are bad people and bad things for them
I had to live with all the with that for all these years and I just don't care anymore who knows it
How's that quote grab you
Struggle with that internal
Problem
You killed a bunch of oversees the then I didn't hear it I don't really care
Yeah I assume
But he was in the military
Sure exactly but that's straight-up murders
He didn't care
But until then
I had to live with
No clearly you did not
Event that was on that was in 2013 on a right-wing radio show
He was interviewed by Mother Jones
April 21st
Physical
Of the original band of Clinton hunt
There's only nickels kept up the ruse
Doing interviews with fringe right-wing radio host
Even posting in 2013 that he had been bills personal Hitman
Which
And wouldn't have said if he hadn't been on
Mario's has not taken a few Vicodin and then admitted
What look
He who is without
That's really the first pill right
Oh God
Infuriating she is a murderer
Who are the pill problem
BB
Worst case scenario
Which is the most
Realistic
Scenario he's a complete liar and a drug addict
Who was fired by Bill Clinton
Mmm started
Trying to ruin his life
Ain't because everyone
Not everyone but a lot of people hate him
Liberalism
Hate Hillary
Because of that they
Oh no yeah all this s*** is true
Vince Foster
Mina
All this
And it's all coming from
This a******
I want to see if
Two more things
So I read this entire motherjones
Article
This article was from
April 2015
Which if you're keeping track
Is 2 months
Before the episode of Alex Jones Show that weird
I am keeping
The things that we've heard him say on Alex Jones Show up till this point
Have been
I'm pretty harshly anti Hillary Clinton
Yes very much about how they're going to destroy the world
It's him keeping up the and a couple of the other clips that I'm going to play later
Really
Bring into Focus
How he thinks that Hillary Clinton is going to destroy the world
Now
And it's April 5th 2015 article
Few months before
Here is a quote
This is just a direct quote from the Arctic
But something strange
Larry
After six years of watching Barack Hussein Obama cower in the face of islamist
Nichols believes the family he spent
Two decades
Touring is cold-blooded crook
Might just be the only people who
Can save the country
I'm not saying I like Hillary
You hear me
He said defensively
I'm not saying I like Hillary Rodham Clinton
I'm not saying anything I've said I take back
But God help me
I'm going to have to stand up and tell conservative Patriots we have no choice but to give Hillary her shot
I know she won't flinch
He continued
That's a mean son-of-a-b**** woman that can be laying over for people and say
He paraphrased her now Infamous response
Austell Congressional questioning
Olivia
What the hell difference does it make
He was against
Clinton because of Whitewater
He's not voting for her because of Benghazi
Because she was so cold-blooded about
He thinks you'll be able to take out Muslim
This is a farce
Beyonce
2 months before this b******* and a publication
Holyshit
Yeah this is the Thin Man with Nick and Nora
This is just f******
Ridiculous
Through the Looking-Glass propaganda
We're not even
They just say whatever is politically expedient whatever like
I shouldn't
Bring psychopath into it because that's a very
Cific diagnosis
Record label
What's a jackalope
It is this type of Opera
To have no con
Nope not at all
Who will just like if you're getting any press
Say whatever it is
You think the Press wants to hear
To bring
Back to you
Even if it's not positive because
This Mother Jones reporter cam
Hotels
Toby it's not even a positive light it's just how do I sell my personal brand
I just want to I just want you to talk about
And so I'm going to do whatever it is that
Makes you talk about
You don't think
The the clintons
AR
Great
Whole Lotta problems
And we have said this even on the show
Bill Clinton deserve
Do we charge for war cry
Absolutely
Presidents for the last 40 years
But at the same time
He doesn't deserve the touring
But he's gotten
Because of all of the
He's fake
It's August fiction fiction
And Hillary
Get it way worse
Because she's a woman
And because
She's irrelevant
The bills not relevant
He can't become president kind of a neutral threat
Hillary is the one
And in the 20s
16 election
She was
Basically
The one who took
All the Brunt
For all of these conspiracies that mostly
Had to do a bell
Ryan Moses
Confirm Larry Nichols
Well the fact
The fascinating
Everything is that
Part of the reason
Who invent so much
Is because most of the real s*** that
That you would complain about Hillary like
Part of the reason that you have to invent
Is because
The real stuff
That you and I just like to
That stuff that your guy is guilty
True disliked about Hillary the the super predators
The racism
All of this
The dollar store
That kind of
Yeah
Dislike
Because it is the legitimate credit
And if you're on the right
You dislike that stuff
That is a legitimate credit
But you have to take her because
Your guy
Did all of that and more you have to find ways around
Logical
To say like
Look
They all did that
These Clinton's did worse
Hillary took millions of dollars from
But Trump
So so it's that kind of it's that extra thing because if you just
If you just criticizing Hillary for the reasons that she
Criticize
Your guy doesn't look as good
He doesn't look as good
Kind of falls apart
It does
Because
We laid out Larry Nichols
Alex
You
You have to do it
If it isn't for you mobilizing
All of the Patriots
Will die the rest of this just becomes
A Obi-Wan
You're only
Yeah only hope
Like I really think
This is foundation
This is a moment where Alex
Kind of
Gets it going to listen to this clip
Okay here's the next one
This is Larry Nichols explaining that everything comes down to
This
15 election
How do you win an election you control your opposition
4 players
I got you got to fight I got to do what I don't want to do
I'm 65 years old I want to stay somewhere and say hey
Richard
Dialogue
Another election Alice
Free they're not
Either vote for who they say
Got it
Two similar to what happen
Like it here
Here's the thing that
Did happen
Today
In Iran's reformist party
Destroy
Murdered
Be a close election
What they found out was that
People came
And vote
Droves
To make sure that
Iran opened up like they wanted and and Iran
Similar to pre-1982 influencer
Call Mike Wells
But but that is that is the interest
Is it there is that
Liver of Hope
Dang that's
The 2018
But
There is no part of cynical that doesn't think
Gerrymandering
Has only gotten stronger
Them they will still retain
No matter what regardless of whether or not we're going to kill you with a bow
It's more just like
Nope you're not allowed to vote we're going to resist
This very strategically how to make sure our party
Let's be clear
In some ways both parties are very guilty of
What is
If you look at the history
Black conservative
Republican
Have
Been way more
Of course but both parties do it
So
Venice
Another important thing that needs to be said
Neither of us are
Lovers of democrat
Regency
Hate
The state of the Republic
We're
Weird I'm not going to say
Because as much as our politics overlap
I know there are plenty
Things that I believe
Privately
To me it is that
The Democratic Party
To off
Allows themselves
Tubi
Drawn
Further right
As the Redcoats further right
Get that window rather rather than in the tug of war
They get closer and closer to the middle
And think that's fine
Yeah but that's exactly the that same thing about
The last
Be overly empathic
I think it's more like
Not not with the left I mean with
The Democrats
With the Democratic Party
There is the idea of
Pragmatism
As being more important
As opposed to
Becomes a twisted
Warped version
Pragmatism
Like
That nationalistic
You know disenfranchised boat
That whole thing
Like there's a reason that Bernie captured a lot of those
People
Because
We were primed
For that kind of
Hey
We've been f*****
Dover
And you've helped us f***** people over
Delta
Get f*****
So if you had actual
We laid out
A progressive vision
Just like the Obamacare Provisions that people
Keep like
So long as you don't put it next to Obamacare
A majority of people say
Leo
Far more pragmatic to getting you elected than this imaginary idea of what
Pragmatic
And so that's why we have
Such a huge disconnect with
The Democratic
Party or perhaps the Democratic
Leadership
I think I think you're correct
Here's the question
Nichols you think
Is that
Germ
That starts
Navigate to the Old Jedi who's coming inside
You're the one who has
You're helping you honestly think it's in the next clip I'm going to play
It's it's
It's a message that's like
You thought your work is done
Nichols nose
How influential Ally
Throwing darts as a wall sang this
Do anybody who may be influential
Or is he just jerking Alex off to be on the show
I know I think Alex considers him
To be a lumen
Alex Nichols
What is my name
I understand
I only explained the dynamic from the other direction right to express that I think
Kono's
Give big dog
Alex
In terms of
Credibility
Okay but at the same time he absolutely knows that Alex has
Does a huge platform
I'm sure like
He went on that other guys show and said that he was
Trucking killer when he was on pills
Go on anybody's show
Clearly as Alex inhibitor
Have a
Decades-long relation
He knows he's watched Infowars grow to the point that it is
As
But maybe maybe the better distillation of
Do you think he
Trying to use Alex
Do you think he's actually do you think he actually believes
Is he is he jerking Alex off
Now I can manipulate Alex's follower
Or is he saying Alex
You really do have this influence and I am
Believe in you
That kind of
This is something that only his therapist could probably answer
If he has a therapist I don't
But
Their global
Therapist vaccines
Ali is because we look
Like I said
He
Did Bill Clinton
I meant said
I dropped the lawsuit because
I wanted to destroy him for what I believe happened to me
He claimed to be a hitman
Later was like
Who knows where his actual Center is
Larry is a person who
Lacks credibility
Because he's
Clearly alive
In public
Conservative radio shows
I would say
Absolute
I would say that he
Here's why it's difficult
4 months before this
3 months before this
He did that interview got to give Hillary
So who knows
F****** head is at
I think you might
Sylveon
Quite frankly I have no idea maybe something better
Do we know where he's at now
No I've no idea I wonder if you sound better pills do know that
Quick contradiction
A couple months just
100-percent contradiction
I have no idea what
But
Igreen
From the interview
Respect Alex Jones is audience
As much
As they can possibly
Help him work towards
His decades-long goal of destroying the Clinton
Okay
And I think that's
Yeah
So he said in a previous interview
We should give Hillary
He's still going on Alex Jones with that kind of
In the back of
His head like
Well here's the only reason I'm going to give him a little bit of a wide berth
About that
Supporting Hillary in the interview
But he believes that she's
Cutthroat cold-blooded
Could
Destroy
These Islamic
But he seems to be afraid of now
If that is rationalization for in that interview
Supporting Hillary
Still does
Kind of match up philosophically with what he saying in his interview what are you saying that like
They're going to try and get Jeb Bush in
If there was an alternative that was
The person who is going to be Cutthroat with these islamist that he imagined
I think he would be on their side
If Trump
Existed as a logical
Counterexample
On
Exactly so
Dirt bike
That part doesn't seem to me to be a logical Kanter
Does it does discredit Larry Nichols a bit
Yeah but
Only in so much as it's like OK Google are just really afraid of Muslims ideological
Somebody who hates mother
It would make sense for him to
Is going to accomplish
The goal
F****** over my
And at the same time he will accept a deal with the Devil
Cute because he does believe that the clintons are the devil
Accomplish that goal a non-white
Yeah I'd rather deal with these white people I really hate which we all know
The bush is better than to non-whites
And I have no I
That's from the Farmers Almanac
So like I'm going to play the rest of these clips
Cuz I really think
Most of them are just reinforcing this
Alex Jones
Just getting
His
Mike Brewster
Sure Shot of I have to say
Save the world
Inasmuch as he barely interrupt Slayer
Larry just gets
Free birth to talk
Where is he interrupts
Everybody
The only way you get a free birth certificate as if you are sucking Alex Jones
This complex.
You're the one who can save us you are the one I think I cut it out earlier
Larry Nichols says
You're the only reason I'm alive
Because I came on your show years ago
And I made public
And otherwise the clintons would have killed me
2.0 hide in the sunlight
Playing into Alex's worst impulse
Anyway
This next clip is actually
Philosophical
Consistent and
But he is trying to express basically the idea of like this scenario 20 years ago
Is premise
Now let him play it out
Because it's a couple months later
Weekend
But also we can be like
That's been dedicated
That's problematic for that
But again he's not supporting Trump at this point I don't even know what to do
Anymore because
Exact search
Because just like with everything Trump does
You can pull a tweet
From 24
Literally
Everything
Banana
Damn so there's no like hypocrisy is no longer an
It's not really about hypocrisy
This thing that I find really fascinating about this interview
Is it lays the foundation
And for
Alex realizing cancer save the world
To me to me listen to this right now
It really does
Crystallize
The facts
And it can no longer be
Speculation
It is the
That
There are
Fleet
Complete full break
Between reality
Like there's no there's no bridging those gaps
Live in a completely
Reality
That that idea of like
Well
When Clinton does it it's evil
Even though Trump is doing it
He's not really doing
It was only evil if Clinton did it it's really evil of trump does it
And Trump does it it's because it's in service
To this larger thing
Which means that it doesn't matter what he's doing so long as it's in service
But Clinton was doing what Trump is doing but in service to this other
Like
Breakdown
He's really interests
Because
The people who were listening to Alex Jones because they listen to him
Alex
Is reporting these things
From sources Like Larry Nichols
Or in the past we talked about Larry C Johnson
Discredited
Hilarious
And this is where the board with thread
Is going to come in eventually once I put it on my wall
Erase markers are is
It's going
To come down to like
This is a false reality but who's exploiting it
Who's being exploited by it
Right to a certain extent I know Alex Jones is making billions of dollars off
Nickel
Larry Nichols
Got f*****
Clinton
And fired
For him calling the contras
Retro
He took it very personally
And it's been on a 30-year campaign to destroy them
Yeah sorry this just popped in my head I have various various axes to grind
But if you looked
Right
Okay with
The agenda they're pushing
He becomes calm
Listen in that false real
Well he's happy with their agenda because the reality is created by these weird
Is the facilitator of the false reality
That exists in the mind of his listener
So basically the people who are they
Do you like
Progenitors of the virus
Or the People Like Larry
I will never forget
That that's
Just learn to pronounce words
Meme
So
I'm becoming ultimately way more fascinated in the idea of
The information funnel
Sources these things come from
2 Outlet
Now granted
Like I'm never going to let him off
The hookies complicit
And a lot of it falls in
Prepackaged narrative
But he would not be able to push it at all
Without
Spain and credibility for people like
The Tulare
Or
Even foresee pieczenik to Larry's in a pizza
To Larry's in a play
Next question
Blows my mind
That I haven't asked
Is Larry Nichols being paid
Being paid to come on the show
Yeah like
I've no idea
Does that not does that not change everything
I bet they at least have to sign
Brightness
There should be making money
So of course
Nickels would say something
Super positive to Alex Jones
If he's getting paid because
It's a gay man
Maybe I'll get paid down down the line
I am not I'm not ready to agree with that cuz
Just because I have no evidence of it I don't know
I want now that's the only thing I want I've been on radio shows for
For free
I've signed thing
I have
Have you been on
My name is
Is Larry Nichols I've been lying the whole time
Southern accent
Are you actually jhacari
I've become an animator
I really want to talk to
I do Nae know what is crazy one of his creator-owned comics
As soon as his voice came up after I said he has a great voice
Your eyebrows both just went well
Angry boys
Is a comic book
Ryder now
Seems really cool
One of his
Creator-owned comics
Daydream
Which is about
A kid learning to
To deal with this
And
Like I8 cost
Way more money than I'm willing to give somebody who's been whose works for Infowars
Which is
Any money at all I'm buying it
Adjusting like a really fascinating for a guy like jhacari
Lived in the Spanish place now I'm going to buy and we're going to critically deconstructed
MC Cara
Knowledge fight at gmail.com
Really think he's pretty
Like I Isaac
Bass
On very little evidence
I think he has a way better head on his shoulders
Than anybody else
Thailand
Through most of that interview I just looking like
But if that takes us back to kind of realize the gig Mandy kind of realizes being used as a
Am I might be
Sing a bunch
I think we're all hoping that
Somebody here in Fort Worth
And see what's going on
Well I mean there was that guy who came out on Twitter and said that Alex Jones
The fraud
All that s***
Those that do it again
Certainly just a matter of the
Clips West Jordan
A couple more clips from O'Leary
What's next
About
Tyranny
Is about to hit
It's happening
How so
Illegals are going to vote
Which is really interesting giving of the 3 million illegals voted
Name from Twitter
Hey an a****** on Twitter would like
Buy followers who exploded because of this
But even before
There was this
Laying out of
Potential
Yes and I think it's really interesting to hear this
From this
Thoroughly be credited
Discredited obvious pill head
Who's on Alex's show
20 years ago
Could you have believed this could happen
That one other problem one of the things he elements in iron
Which what we called the broken coalition
In Arkansas
Any people that came out said they were openly gay
What if we got all those little birds together
Immediate
Yeah like a f****** garbage Tyler
Is working Shaklee like clockwork
The American people Alex all of you
American people
American
You don't have stood up
Are you going to lose it
Understand
Stand Tall in going to tell the truth
Forever
Domesticated
Boss Hog hair neglect
We've been over those two lies
Alex is unable to even really engaged
With the lies that Larry Nichols
He's only able to go back to his waypoints that we've discussed
Obama went overseas
You guys can't have
Air conditioning
Literally about how
Modernization in the third world has to go better than it has gone
Unsustainable
And we need to do this smarter
You shouldn't
Do all this
Carpenter
And the same way you didn't build your business isn't about how hey you dumbass
Your business
F*** you in about how hey you dumbass people got to your business by driving on roads
So how they got those f****** roads
Everything exists within a
Yeah
This is such a moment where I'm at
Who the f*** is Alex Jones
And how is that
Constantly
See this orbit of
People around Alex
And yet we can't
At least I can
I can't ever quite
Pin down where Alex
Is
I got a better sense of him than you I don't mean that I mean more like
This this Nichols do
He's pulling some
Some obvious bulshit
Very good like manipulative
Like all of these different things where you planting these ideas Facehugger style right into Alex Jones
Charlie and Alex Jones
At this moment
Is unable to
Like he can't understand
He's taking it in he's taking it
Yeah
I don't want to compare to like that Chris Farley Show sketch where it's
What about
That like I have these waypoints that I have in my mind
Already built
And so like
6 months from now
With these same ideas being expressed
So it's fascinating to me because it again it again makes me
Feel like
Alex is not
Alex is like the evil child from The Twilight Zone where it's
Just somehow he has magic powers he's just a
He doesn't understand anything of what he's doing
He's just got these
And he's using them to hurt people
Let me be clear
Here's what I
Okay
If you have that we're on like episode 10 million and 9 + H 4 billion forever
Who is Alex
It's so hard cuz every single episode we talk about there's new evidence
Throws everything
But I think
My sort of
Rosetta Stone if I can use that on my Marvel card
Or is that guy and have him here's his superpowers and I deficiency
Give a shout out to the best Marvel comic ever
He's a terrible interviewer
He's s***
He interrupts his gas
He says nothing
Depending on how much you respect
Or how weird is it faces on
He does not engage with input
It comes to him that God disagrees with his neighbor
Right
But so that's like
On the lake 1210
Chart
Interview skills
Yes to
Yes but then in his NBA Jam
Yeah lion but then if you go down to the neck
The ability to talk about nothing aggressively
He's a 10
Like he can just
He would be the
He would be the world
Best
Senator
Her like a bad cause
Cuz he could filibuster for 20 hours the f****** hilarious
It'll be engaged book in front of him
Where to star in the movie mr. Jones
Mr. Jones in Austin
It would but that's that is where he shine
Able to talk about nothing engagingly for real
I'm bringing
Disparate
Detail
From things that really involved but sound just
Good enough
That it makes his arguments
To make sense
Amazing
I think in one of the First episodes
You and I were talking about like
You said I couldn't do
You absolutely and I'm starting to come around to that I could not do
I could talk
For 4 hours
For sure
We've proved that
Couldn't been aggressive
About nothing
For 4 hours
He has no preparation he has no real details but he is able to manometry
It is it is kind of like
Nothing until
He is like a guy who's just like
Check out Marty and Sarah's podcast about wrestling him enter the studio I'm
Sure if you were
Is producer
I don't know
He's going to do
Rocket ship
Hematology
This for half an hour
Comes up with some b*******
Then get
It interview
They say some s*** he doesn't really listen
Gloms onto something they say
Farther with this
Right now
It's like a connotation for
Spiders
When we
Kind of
Apply them to
Propaganda
Who are completely
Control
He is like a spider on.lsd was just
Maybe this
Spinning this weird web that doesn't make any goddamn sense
Cuz you seen those
As opposed to Alice
Because the lse ones they make
Eerily perfect strike pattern
The f*****-up spider
He's making a web that he knows
There's a reason I'm doing this
But I'm not sure I know the current even play that clip I wish I could pull it up but
Somewhere buried in my phone
I know what's going on
But the details
Headspace
Narrative you supposed to push
Coming from
The People Like Larry Nichols
Steve pieczenik
Rodger Stone
These guys were feeding him
Or even now like Mike cernovich has become
Even grandfathered into that sir
Right cuz he
Without using the word
Talked heathcock
Alex Jones
He's way more popular than
Media companies
It's all fun and games until the reality sets in that these people are
Intentionally
The other thing about that
Again
Today really
Was filled with
What's hope for me
And you see this
Especially with the local
Because
I believe it's
I think it's rumani I'm not sure how to
Pronounce
Properly
Lukulos sites
He won and he'd already been in office
He'd already served
The fact
That
Many of those local
Games where it is
Ruled by the same
Conservative
Council members
For forever and ever and ever
Are suddenly now being over take
Because it
The local Ali
It's that
Is that kind of that
That the ground game that
The Democratic party has gotten
Their ass kicked
For so long how many governors
Are Republican
How many
City Council
How many states
Stannard's all of these
These are the places where the Republic
Have really infiltrated us
Destroyed
And now in
Of all places
You know
Bastion of democracy Iran history
History that one that was
But that's that's the thing that gives me hope.
Because again
Young people
I do think that
The younger generation
And it is
Hard to argue anything else
Are more Progressive
Armoire
Aware
Are more educated and are more willing to enter
Surtain ideas
That will benefit everybody
Then the older generation
Totally
And so when you see them start to take over that local arena
That's when you start to see real
Boise I think the history is cyclical in
In so many ways
Major focuses of the cycle
Is that
Wishing we could go back
To whatever
Is dumb
It's a dormant
Dormant
For a bit and then
Progress
And people start to
Come together
What happened
But meanwhile
Forces are bubbling under the surface
I may start to build up
And eventually gets
Point where
Everyone who want Society
Move forward realizes
Alright
We got to do
They never do until it becomes a
That's my that's my theory of generation
Progressive
Always push
Towards progress
But really till we get
Complacent
Yeah and then
I just win
The
Conservative
And regressive forces
Has become radical
And then it becomes like well now it's going to become a problem
Like in the same way that ended up
In riot
In the same way up in murders in the same way that the seventies
Early 70's late 60s
Became
Edit
It's progress meeting
The radicalization of reek
Yeah and I think we're probably heading
Towards that
In terms of
Where are you
Society is going
The issue is for me
That's how things go just would have been a natural Evans
Flow
Without outside influences
Every reaction
Equinox
Yeah we were talking about around
An amazing Progressive Society until we f***** it up
Now there
Coming out
And now of their own because of generations
Cycles that coming back to us
And hopefully it will work
I worry that
Situation
Do we have in our country
Is
Boss is doing the same thing
To ourselves
That we did to foreign countries
I think we're both
Here is
Here is my
Daily
Psychopath
Optimism
Is always going
Will we do it in
I think that's my big
Right now
Think there will absolutely be a progressive
Bounce back
The pendulum will swing back towards
Yeah I don't think that's
Within Quest
It's already happening
Yeah the question is
Will it be in Thai
Will we be able to do enough
To stop
The damage
That has already been done
And is being done
Betsy DeVos is
Murdering
School
She is absolutely going out of her way
Dab small children in the throat
She and her husband
Loan collection organization
Are you saying that
Her decision to repeal and remove
Loan forgiveness program has something to do with it written herself
Yeah odd
That's so out of
Character for the administration that were living under
Yeah it's insane but
I want
The world in terms of like Empire
That it existed
Do you mean the ones where America
What the ones we are living under the American Empire I think
Gets the last
A couple hundred years I have been
America as the big super
Power
Certainly
Look at these places like
Greece was a
Roma's
And the things that happened to them afterwards
They became
Complacent
You know that I could they found their niche
As being like
Right we got some great stuff you can come check out
We're actively working again
What's the possibility of that being our future
That like that sort of hammock
Which superpowers get to after their Empires full
We're destroying our Natural Parks
Trump is trying to work against our natural beauty
Kia
We have shown
Over and over again
That the statistics in terms of our tourism numbers are white
Jason wants to come out the other end
After we lose
Maybe
I think the largest question
Fire which I think is very
Unique
Will Ark
Culture remains
Because
You think about
Pieces of it
You think about Hollywood
And
You like
I think about
Will will Bollywood
You know.
Will all of these
Please other people
In terms of mass numbers
Ford Market
These movies that bomb in America make billions of dollars overseas
American movie
Like they still have that
Is it going to be that America will dominate
Muvico
And that will be or just f****** McDonald's
Yeah America winning
Any wars without
McDonald's
Or Starbucks
Like imagine
Like at like I think it was has the best joke
He does you did not
I respect that
He did not have a good chat
But his bit about how America
Can Empire the American Empire
It was
When the British
Came in the kicked everybody out and then
We on the
And then America
Bill's the Starbucks around
Like
Seems to me to be the more
Empire building a
Active America in Utah
Like there's a Starbucks on every f******
Like is that is that America or is that global
The part of Alex's sort of cosmology that I won't disagree
Agree with is that
Like
It is clear I don't think it's by force
That American culture
Has been very attractive to people all around the world
Weather report
Through like
We have billions of dollars and we're going to put Starbucks everywhere
Starbucks
People enjoy it
Whether it's one or the other I'm not entirely sure
But
To me that's
Steve that's the better Ambassador for America
It sure is
Center for Impala
But the fact that
The fact that
If you're in China you can go to a McDonald's
Says more about
American hegemony
And it says a lot about McDonald's
How much do they care
Yeah about America
I don't give a fuk
Talk about America
Emissions
Absolutely I'm not sure what I'm saying
I am really not sure what your argument there is a really long weird
And I
Oh that's still unusual for us
It's been so long I don't know who were talking to
10 minute 7 trying to figure out a way to
The square
Larry Nichols believes
That
The Tea Party is the answer
To all the society
The wrong
He believes that
The Republican
Are actively trying to work against the
Which is which was kinda fair in 2015
I think they were well
Work again
I think they were trying to usurp
Virginia
The RNC
COPD RN
The RNC does not want to give up control
And so their threat
Bye
Tea Party
Primitive kind of
True
But this is going to
The tea party because they know that one thing
And take over the RNC
We took over the RNC
We can take back our country
The last national election
Once those Mexicans are allowed
I know he's talking about illegal immigrants started
He's not
Hebrews 2
I think he if he was
If he was conscious
He would make
More of an effort
To say so
But you know exactly
He means that once Latinos
In America
Start voting
It will be towards
People who support them
I'm doing about them
And don't say they're all right
But that was the that was the demographic argument that was made
The entire
Was that
Well Trump doesn't have a chance
That's because
Now that the demographics have changed so much
It doesn't matter who the Republic
Logan's Run
It only matters where they run
Goes back to Larry Nichols fractured
Fractured Democrat
Exactly you bringing the gays you bring in the black
White people as opposed to act
Fourth
A progressive ideology
Is
The one that is supported by the
Majority of
Always
Always have
True it always has been
Election
Will
Argue against
And it's hard to it's hard
You believe they will argue
For any other reason
Peda
It's money
Holyshit billionaire
Holy s*** I just got a tweet
Trauma are our friends
The Razor Ramon
Okay just tweeted me a picture
Out at some wrestling show
I
He's sitting behind someone with an Infowars shirt
Advice of weirdo just local wrestling show with an enforcer
Thank you I don't know your name but
Razor Ramon
Homeschool
Cool
NWO Theme
So he's got one more left
Play at this one is
Before all of our listeners if you are
Coincidentally going to a wrestling show while recording
We will chat you
Hillary for prison shirts
Simsbury High into this design at wrestling shows
So
This that the last play is an eyesore the punchline
I act weird
But
Before we get to it I want it I want it I want a soulmate
A little bit
Yes
Alex started this show
Unaware of what
To do about the Charles
Yes
He ambivalently wandered around
Accidentally
Probably
Spouted
A bunch of
Incredibly
Just ideas
He wandered around until
He had a African-American
Preacher on the show
Cool
I went way further than him
And gave him permission
Cover
To be like
Yeah
So that was the first
Narrative
Secondarily
He has
Larry Nichols on
Who has weave
Scott
Victor lead
Discredited
Fired by Bill Clinton
Hated him
From the jump
Has done everything in his
Power
To take him down
To the extent of lying
On public radio shows
Lying on conservative radio shows and then
Lying to Liberal interviewers like mother
Absolutely
And then waffling back and forth
Weather I love Hillary
Who says whatever it is that will get
And we'll get him
The point is what he thinks is the sorrel discredit
Is a absolute
Terrible source of information
At the same time
Alex
I do believe
Inform
The 2016 election
I think that Alex
You're the only person who can help us
That sort of thing
You need to galvanized
The Tea Party People
Jeb Bush isn't going to do it
Larry Nichols
I think
Formative
Did they set the Bedrock
Alex's coverage
And I stink
It's f***** up that I just started
I listen to a couple days
Is before
A really boring nothing really
But
Just after Trump
Announces
This episode
And I think it is the launcher
For Alex losing
I think this will be
Beginning
Of our analysis
Just
This is the gestation of
Amman
Fall from
Yeah
It wasn't great
It's not go anywhere near fall from disgrace
So this Method Man's fall from the seventh level of hell
Just pulled one
I don't think it's a don't think it's important considering how Dante was just
Pissed off about people he knew
I love Dante but yeah you're totally right
I'm just picking people mostly get a boner for Beatrice
You got a last clip is just a really fun
Insight into
Larry
It's just
Peacock Keller
You don't give a
Done
Starts with Alex explaining that his book is out of print
And it goes from there
That nichols's book is out of print or Alex
Your Bookshop
How folks support your folks want to talk to you speak to their forever
Come on there show I do you give out your home number Ender
Address for FAFSA
Phone number for 40
8 + 7
Conway Arkansas 2034
And Alex no paper dress
Appreciate
I'm going high
Either we get together
Either wait for him up
Forevershe come out
Because this thing is coming down
That's crazy
Freak
Are you calling him
There's a situation
We try
We called
Larry nickel
Turn over my cell phone record you
Call Larry Nichols and spoiler alert
Phone number to call him
Leave this old man alone
Here's the deal we call them
It is still his phone number
Leave the man alone
But it was pretty hilarious he didn't answer his phone
It wasn't he was like, I don't want to talk
He was on oxygen
He didn't want to answer any questions about Alex Jones
He was very nice
It was recording
Interest in following the law
And just decency we decided to cut it out
So
You're missing out on some pretty funny stuff
A lot of perch
Stevie Larry Nicks
I'm a policy wonk
That was really
That was over
I thought that was going to be a b****
Who's the craziest thing that's ever happened on this Daddy f****** nuts
You know what
Probably on oxen
That's not an excuse not Salem think about Trump
Also did you
Did you get the sense that he
Kind of does not want to talk
Talk about Alex
I think you kind of does not want to talk about anything
That's fair
That's amazing turns out number on the show
In two years later same f****** number so it's all there
Feel free to call him
All you hundreds of people out there or if you would like to write a letter it is 58 Kensington Drive
Conway Arkansas 72
Also when they played that on Alex's show they had like a place card already made up
Yeah
Holyshit
Never would have expected this is super f***** up and we just talked to Larry Nichols
Jordan I don't know what to do we got a f****** we got to run away
Guys if you support now it's right go to knowledge fight.com
We have a link
That is
To donate
The show
If you want to donate any amount of money you'll become a policy wonk
Donate $10 a month
Literally every single show we're calling make
You save that goddamn that number is in my
I actually added that contact as Larry Nichols
Do not think that that is not the case
That's so amazing this episode could not have ended any better
Like I said our website is knowledge, you can follow us on Twitter underscore
Check us out on
Amber Johnson ice rating
AeroGarden
Give us a review Teletubbies
But to be fair
What are you gave out your f****** number that's on you Mr Nicholls I would feel so bad about calling over
Person on air
He's absolutely
Answers of my full name in the street
Yeah I know
Larry Nichols going to fight as if he's going to represent laxative
Let me ask you a question
Did
We've all been through an emotional wreck
I really wish Jon rappoport would put out his
Phone number
Spirit guide
Who will be receiving a weird number of calls
But
If we're going to end the episode
Are we going to stay
Larry Nichols
The still alive
We just did it
Is anybody else feel alive Dan John Rappaport still
Holding
I love your work