Air Jordan
I have great respect for its knowledge B
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Indeed we are.
Jordan
Whatsyourprice
I want to go first
Cuz I got
Complicated
Today
As we record this in about an hour
Major League Baseball will return
I know you're a man
The amount of resources they're taking
The risk that the players
Do the point of moral distress
WWE power on
Through this
It's terrible
Test every single day that I should be used for the population at Large
I know I know that your fan Dometic
Your food is very hot based on
Panda and the Raza
Positive
He's a dictator
Can be great
Usually would go to bars
Prison watch baseball negative
Two layers of weirdness I can go to the bar to watch
The world
I watch the preseason game last night and I was like
Isn't that different from Google
You know you sure there's nobody there
Terrified
So
But alright
Android
Very nice
Trip into the mailbag
Alright and nice letter from
S4
Recognizing
Is a telescope
Different light spectrum
I got 12
Seltzer's mango sanzo shelter
Not sweet at all was really nice that has kind of like a
Soft fruit
Survived
To think about it a little more
Complex complex
There's also a calamansi
Excited
Yeah I remember having a lot of light cheese stuff back
The flavor at all
So I'm excited to try that
Thank you very much
No Lucy was the space
Episode
We got some some vegan jerky and sunflower crackers
Alright alright
Super spicy
Seltzer's that are made for children
Bubble gum
I remember a little recording where we try them
Care package
The bright spot for me in this week
Forestry
What's going on for him to talk about nothing in the news
Carerite
And it leaves me a little bit in the Lurch is like trying to
We recorded some Thursday
Wednesday
Yo I am
Evening thinking
When is show starts on Thursday
I will know whether or not there's an episode of
If he's on that around a triangle
And I don't know
Alyx studio and I believe the reason is because
This week
Supreme Court was deciding his motion
But he was trying to overturn those sanctions against him
I'm ahead of the opposing counsel
Spermatocele
Performance
Is former lawyer
Good work CBS
The court issued a 720 decision rejecting Jones's claims that his comments aimed at attorney Chris
Christopher Mattie
We're protected by free-speech rights
And upholding a lower Court's ruling the Jones violated numerous orders to turn over documents to the families
Danzig blow to Alex
This case
The first
Call up corsets
Potatoes Vines
To continue withholding documents
From those lawyers
Simply put this is a very strong indication that Alex is running out of
In this case
Chillow
Taking a vacation
Been going on
Easiest explanation for why he's been
I don't know if you had to go to
Connecticut four-door
You know if it's
Just like hey all of my lawyers who were representing me you've been replaced
Time
In front of the Connecticut Supreme Court
Studio will figure out exactly what's going on
We are missing some Peaks a drunk
Esoteric Alex shows though if they're on the show right now
Almost certainly
So
The first
Brio game
Thank you so much
She went out
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you next
There is no name just a picture of a
Thank you so much
Thank you very much
Picture of a butt
Next
Mecu
Little Miss Mimi the meerkat Muffin Top makers mischief
AKA Mimi
I'm a policy wonk
Great honorifics today
Michael M
Specifically requested that
Under the rank
Digital Devil Summoner Michael M
Text Emily br
Legit Journal policy walk
I'm a policy wonk
Journal about
We would appreciate the generosity and threw a bunch of
Llc's indubiously named I like it
Cheerleader
Appreciate that
So
Because
Oh I don't know I texted you and I told music
I think it will be okay
Give me a rating for the audience
Okay
What is happening
Before we get to the actual episode
Okay
There's no date on the Rogers said that a bad word
He's going hard are now we have got
Some spin
Prem Rog
On July 19th
That would be Sunday
Rodger was a
Along with a little bit of dream
Robber Union Ballroom is back baby
And so he addressed the controversy
Broken on Sunday Arizona
He's got a chance
Last Friday
L.a. Beast
Progressive radio
Moana
Chapiadora
Racist War on Drugs
This broadcast was
They cut my audio feed
Speaking
I had
Osculating
Show called racial slur
I need a professional
Second of all
Because Rodger immediately gaslighted
The responsive not being like so certain you heard what you is not that strange to me
The argument that people were talking in French
As everybody knows it called
What's a great
Because the rest of the sentence in English
I don't want to argue with this is in English
Listening to something else
This story's what do you have on the 19
Atlanta on the 20th
Customs show on
Syndicated on
Infowars
Answer Rodger had a little bit of
We have the
Which is
Weekly ball
I used
Racial
In an interview
With the radio talk show
Now I did do a show
Are on Saturday
D
Contradiction
The first time
Went down
40 seconds
Which they say
No I wasn't
Admit
3 days
Between
Where is a Pasty
Weather
Version
What was recorded
Allegedly
Negro
The background noises
What's the show
Goes on
5 minutes
Kiss my ass
Either
Surprise
Different
Lotto
Sports
Results
Sounds right
One of Brazil
Man what a swing that's impressive
Conspiracy
Occam's razor tells me that you're lying right now what words do you say that
For the rest of this
Make sense
Is like
Okay so glitches
In such a way as to be perfectly able to frame Rodger for saying this word
And then afterwards they were able to somehow splicing something that sound
Exactly like Rodger Stone
I mean
Mo Kelly needs to be involved his producers need to be in like Siri such a
Understand either
What it is he thinks that proves
That just means he spliced into a different time you said that
Rodger impression
I mean it's elaborate
It's not
Is Rodger protest
You just shut up keep our audience licking pointed out
They don't like.
Proud boys
You shut up because
No one cares
Everyone's everybody doesn't like you already
Infowars
We kind of know
Move Along Rodger
Rodger Dunn
Controller
His career
Pretty funny to me
That made me realize
The french-speaking explained
I want to see Rodger
He wasn't seeking it watching some friends program
Just in the background
So
Pathetic
Oh no no you are not going to play
Get the f*** out
Do not
You have you do something right
Ubisoft
I've listened
Troy
Their shows they got nothing
Terrible
What if carpet. Subs awesome
What is he is awesome
Polymath he's good at all kinds of different
What is left to his own devices in
Freed from the
The chains of Alex's
Interview style what if he's amazing amazing
I don't know so we have to find out yes
News 11 episodes out now
The most recent episode
Download numbers
Review numbers
You got stolen.
Psych you know maybe people have
Seeing the tweets about it or whatever
I went back and I looked at it sometime earlier episode
Visionary Laura Loomer as I call her
2.2 thousand
That was like
Dinesh D'Souza
Episode 3
That's not a good direction
Configure views
Tubi
Episode 5 Gavin McInnes
Episode 74 episode
The Rogers episode 11
417 117 views
Allpoint very light
Oh boy that's not good numbers are really depressing but I figured they'd like you know the dogs probably only in he's not like he's only real
YouTube
And it's not looking much better over there now
The most beautiful so does Gavin McInnes 7.3 thousand after over a month
It's not like his videos getting overused
Still have like 10 to 20 thousand sometimes
Great
Some dick making memes
What you consume
YouTube isn't the primary mode for me
Memes about like obviously you're going to get way more views on them
In another platform
Even still
YouTube
So it's not like
There's no traction here
I think the problem with his Joe is that no one wants it
Set to exist even his fanbase doesn't seem like they're clamoring for a talk show host
Because he made 30 second
Can videos that kind of
Pander to their beliefs
It's not like you see this video
I wonder what that guy would do with along with the longest
Carpe donktum curated 60
That's what I was really think of that give me a Charlie Rose interview
God dammit
Pushed back whenever I call Tommy Robinson
Tommy Robinson Sheriff
Call
Tommy Robinson alternating names
You chose to call yourself that you live with it for the rest
Love your life
Hey Leah Scott.
Keep going
Grown Beyond you
So I saw these guests
Floral
Gavin McInnes
As like
A lot of people who kind of her in this milia
Bloomer shoban Infowars orgasm
Kind of Alaska
Common but not unheard-of
A Dinesh D'Souza to show up busy generally
Associated
And then I was like
How did the show start
Who was the first Galaxy
I was blown away
Batgirl
First gas
On Carpe donktum
It's not
Carpenter
First gas
I'm Carpe scorner
Dave Rubin the f*** out of here
Dave Rubin
Classical liberal Dave Rubin
Dave Rubin was alright
Carpet corner
Excited like if we're going to listen
Listen to something
I want to f****** Dave Rubin
That's a sentence that I can't imagine anybody not steaks
Kind of stupid.
The first time we listen
Bill Cooper episode one of the things that I responded to the most
This show is a little bit
The theme song
No
Carpet carpet carpet
I've got to pause here for a second because there's a couple of couples wife
I'm not going to play the rest of this song
He has also has like review
On-brand okay
People who complain that our theme song is too long
We are just under a minute-long it's perfectly timed
Just like it
Forward
I disagree
Theme song of the minute-and-a-half
Too long that's too long does he do it himself
See if you can voice
It might be I don't know
Is that for a minute
See that's what makes me think it's that kind of vanity
A minute and 30 of me is what they showed me
Carpe score
Seasons corner
Physical
Carpe
Or whatever
He's a stage names
I don't care
Not bad
JoJo you already too
Made a better name for
You can have that Carpe
No you can't
Cheez-It
Apology here in advance
Audio is
Trap
Through the entire thing
Bad to the point where if
I had recorded this I would never put it on
Whenever it happens
And there it is it's in the middle of something
But sometimes you do have to leave because it's in the middle
Piece of conversation
Well if I cut this out the neighbor cut out 20 minutes
Right
Cared about what I was doing at all I took seriously
This would never get really yeah
Even if you think Dave Rubin is
They get and like I can't reschedule Dave Rubin
Don't put this out Rudolph
Hello
Oh no
Scarface corner
I am here with my very special guests
Dave Rubin
Hello Carpe
And internet
You know I've been doing a big press tour right now but when you offer
Opportunity
Very first
Episode of carpe
Something with Wolf Blitzer or something like that
Wow wow
I'm doing every Fox
Bring me on live
Say whatever I want
Meanwhile zero Envy
Shocker
Does Lairon
Cornershop
Shocking
Did you go get that
Now I will tell you this
Like it should be Dave Rubin show
Is calling in from an island
Rubin report
The audio
Is Dave is a pro
Decent terms
Like
Audio-Technica
He has a studio
F*** you doing
Dave Reubens whole stick for the longest time had been like
He worked at The Young Turks sure classical liberal
I am a liberal but the last is going crazy
Funnel for like
He's like a liberal get
Do you have the the Rubin report
Gaston like Ben Shapiro Jordan Peterson
Adam Carolla
Man Tommy Robinson Mike cernovich
These sorts of folks who gives uncritical platforms
And they would just
Say
Existed
Need to be for a bit
Recently
Just decided he works for the blaze
Through this.
And now
I don't know what he's trying to do now
Cuz I don't think
There's much
Use for it he's a sensible
Christy Moore
I don't know
We got plenty of Nazis man
Is really anymore
When did you
Swift
From being like this
And far-right
People can use
To justify
Themselves and their free speech nonsense
When you slip from
To be like I work for Glenn Beck now
I mean you end up on a corner
We're not calling it it's kind of a bummer
I'm calling you trying to Shield
With Carpe donktum
Talking to somebody who's underwater
But
Comedian
Hilarious and then
Become reactionary dicks
To start things off with
This is going to be loosened
Successful comedian
I do want I do want to ask
A little bit about
The outfit
Professional talk show host
He's a little more
With the open
In the middle of the country
Krowd
Miss Gray
Selling bumper
For yourself
There we go
Is it better
Better now
So he ER he stormed off to change his his outfit
Instead of like elevate
I feel like if you're on dogs dojo
Like he does something like that
This is a bit
Do something
As opposed to sit there like hourly into the show
Minute
Minute into the show
Well
Prayers for a pretend birthday
First date
Starbucks off of 280
Pun intended
Blazing star
The funniest version of this
Could possibly be and I still don't
All I know is bolo tie
When he comes back he's wearing like a Simpsons shirt or something like that because
Better
It's like I don't care
Tired conversation
Luminaries in the world of online media like Carpe donktum
Reuben
Can come up with something better to talk about than how The Simpsons have seen better days
Was too long
The audio is not good
So I'm getting and getting some feedback heater that
That my
Audio is choppy
Yours is just fine
But mine
Have you tried putting
Microphone
That's not a bit
This is where I got really
Disappointed
It's a weird thing to say this is where I got disappointed
They're not going to fix
You don't need to do that got to do it
The Show Must Go On the fans are demanding more.
Donks Dojo dab
I mean
Free
Screen stuff
Another problem
Delay
You can't expect anyone
But this is why you end up with receding number
I did listen to a little bit of the Laura Loomer want
This is this is a good shot man you got Reuben in the house there's no way you can be like hey I'm in called
Dave back in about a half hour
We're going to get the hell out of your work
Brother
And so like sure even so even if you have a good going
There's no rule that says you can't
We did it in our livestream
Hey we have a problem we need to fix it
Can't you can't you can't expect anyone to take you seriously this is what you're bringing
Anyway
Talking about like a Twitter censorship
Sugar course
Today
Aruba
Has an interesting perspective on it
Somewhere along the lines of like a Twitter to do whatever they want
There's a conspiracy going on
She's locked out
And she has
He's talking about Candace Owens being locked out of her account
But nobody's gotten back
How to figure out what to do
The privates
What did the government
Put pressure on Twitter to boot
Her and are they ever going to let her
You know what's your name
Or if it's like they're taking away your ability to make a living for
For people like us
So we do have to see
Figure out some
I do believe in
That that is
True
You are
You have offer
At local
What should I do
Lee Donald Trump
Government
Pressure Twitter tonight
Wildly throwing that around government
Candace Owens
Positive things
Pressure on Twitter
Sprout Jess specific
This is how you have that weasel
Obviously yes Twitter can choose to do
What they want
How do I get around that somebody must be
Forcing them to do it around
The implications of me having this seemingly rational how can I turn this
Camps allowed
That's what I believe because they'll get very angry at me
Mako SeaWorld
Real silly
I don't I don't check into that at all
Any can't pull off Globe to say the government can't even say can't even say it's like the
Deep state in the government
Alright
Umbrella Blokus
For single this is something
Has eyes launch basically
Patreon
I'm sure I signed up for an account on it and it is a website
It's really hard to tell how many creators are actually on the platform because
Once you sign up for an account there's no option to browse content creators
Discover like new folks who you might be interested in like that's crazy
That's not good
Search
4 names
And see if something comes up
Infowars Alex Jones yielded no results
Dave's Dave concept
Patreon Style
The social media been to it
You can join us Pacific creators
Quote-unquote community
Then you're allowed to see their news feed and whatever they choose to post.
Basically it's like a free-speech Twitter that you have to pay for
Overall iZombie roster of folks
Great he's a hero
Carpe donktum of course downtown there
Dave Rubin Dave Reubens on there of course names I didn't recognize all right
I found the site's navigational capacity to be shipped
All aspects
Is a huge turn off
Insane
There's no way the government
Twitter de Candace Owens
No way visit
Is ever going to work as a website
It's trash
They're just slight
Tweaks that need to be made to even make it like a peeling
User experience
You have to come in knowing
Who's Community you want to
Which you're trying to steal
Another busy
You're hoping that whoever you invite
To join
As you should
He's going to bring all of the people that they would be
Bringing along with it
Yeah he wants those 487 views
Yeah
So let me dance.
Whatever people aren't allowed on other things
Migrate
Their base to this platform
We can take a cut off.
Just like I mean it's not
The first middleman websites ever been
It's just
. revolutionary and I
I guarantee that if people behave in ways that were illegal
Tik-Tok that as well
I gave it half
Because you're creative
Communities that are facilitated by this locals website
And so like if somebody is organizing like
Nazi rallies are a violent kind of
You would have to
Kick them off
And then go where is Free Speech
I don't understand is like a do they just not understand who they're dealing with
Like that does Dave Rubin not get that if you create a place for all the people who got quick
Dad kicked off Twitter you're going to find out that all the people who got kicked off Twitter
Well now they're a group of nothing the same way Alex
Explicitly
Dave Rubin invites people to come onto locals as opposed
I think we're anybody can sign up for Creator account
Gets to talking about how like
You know
Fox News
He's on there a lot
Just figured out a way to
People
We're on
CNN
Imagine Blitzer laughing
These aren't real
You know that being said I would still go on there
This makes me very sad this is not good
That's not good
I would love to
Your doctor non-humans all the time it's like a video game there in PC
Play Final Fantasy 11 now I know what's up like a couple minutes ago
Naughty
Oh man it turns out those guys who whose brand is
Reactionary
Victim
You guys too
Interesting I don't want to talk about it cuz
I feel like other people report does a really good job of covering unrelated content
Enoteca
In care of his business sure he's not really
On Infowars March
The reason that were in a really even doing this is cuz this is on
Carpe donktum
Is assertive
Fox News or more
Fox News
Gonal-f
Golf Course
There's a
Yeah they're sort of
Debate
Has
Fox News
Gone
God bless
It's really started
After
But
Alright
I didn't know that
Clippers really interest
Sing to me cuz he claimed
Which is on the board of Fox News
Dave Rubin surprised he has no
It's true.
In response to being surprised by the claim
Confident
Isabelle Ryan on the board of somebody's probably there somewhere we actually know
Talking about there's a big ideas about stuff
I feel like Paul Ryan's on the board there somebody must be doing something I read a headline
Fox News
Organization that came after Disney bought 21st Century Fox but they didn't buy the properties involved
Mike Fox News Fox News
Corp company needed to be a point
Orion is on that board Murdock and his son Lachlan are largely Still the One.
Just like a
Assume
It's largely a
Here is a hammock
It just never occurs to these guys that maybe they've gone nuts
You can't be a Nazi in the mainstream
Mostly you can be 75% Nazi
They're like
Well we've so that means Lefty Court
They just can't
Like they can't wrap their heads around
Maybe we became.
Super far afield
Possible
Mysterious that Fox News is going Progressive or Lefty
Extremely far to the radio
Like
This person who's interview
Sox Lefty of the
Literally take your property away
Like most progressives
Wow alright
Jesus Christ
I would see that is a troubling sign
If I were Dave Rubin no being interviewed by the need to take a look at least 20 minutes to unpack that
Why do you think Fox News is
Even if I work
Hey I'm sensible I'm in the middle politically invited on Fox News all the time
Yeah it took a little while
From the last
So
Cobra
Is about like leaving glass
That's
Entire
Resume different
Brings this up a little bit here to
Cuz of course you're having a ball that's what you want to talk about
So much
I want to hear this
People will say.
How is it pause
Possible you were one of them
Sometimes it's hard for me to remember what it was like to
You can literally find videos of me supporting Bernie Sanders
5 years ago
Somewhere
What I'm saying I agree with Bernie Sanders blah blah blah
Now we can see his true colors dad
Rebecca
Of course you favored Bernie Sanders to Hillary
You were saying
Call boy
I can't imagine what it was like to
To think that I needed to Terror
Hair down and restructure the entire that's a crazy idea
Dean's answer for this question
Relies on a boat
Metaphor
Alright
I guess
Are the boat
There are water-breathing socialist
Alright
Liberalism
Today
What they really addressing
Socialist
And Collective
The progressive
And I think what happened
What liberals
WhatsApp
Reminded
Sexying
Other
Voices
A liberal base
Sickly
To be like
Thinking away the conservatives Acts
You don't
The Predator conservative
Like picture it's a
Liberalism is a
The ship and then the
Swimming underneath
A little hole
Call Erick
Progressive got in there
And then
Tricking everybody
Pretending
People
What
Underbelly of liberal
And they just went in there
The whole thing
And that's why there are no liberals
I still consider my
Really
The phrase that I like now
I would consider myself a
Modern
New label I consider myself
Modern conservative
Classical liberal
Choose a different time designation
My alignment
I'm personally A baroque Center
Libertarian
Whatever alright buddy
So I want to just talk about this matter for a tiny bit
Is it just to be like
Let's imagine the same boat
Conservatism
Instead of Tolerance
Play the same stupid game
My metaphor for this phone
Alright remember the Mesa
The Mayflower flower exist
When you could be a classical ever
And there's a little flower
And I
They let all the Nazis in
And then made a country
That's about the boat that I consider
Well
This isn't good because you don't help us so division
Two-sided thing has basically been here from the
The beginning
You see what I'm saying whatever we let him in that boat
Okay
Because there was a hole in the boat
My feeling on Borgata way for
I think it did
My feeling on this
Is the Dave Rubin supposed
To be your guy who's got these ideas that are really like
Cool and good
Right
Is it because of
Hollering
And Democrats like to be light
I like to be like
And then there's a whole lot
The bottom of the boat
Tolerance
Kind of makes you think
They left their own devices tolerance
It's plugged with progressives dead well pump
Oh they did pull the plug
Otherwise it's not a hole
No unless Progressive
Did they have one of those
Swirly
Yeah I think so
This is dumb
It means nothing
And it sounds good
Good to have.
Progressives are exploiting the desire of me
Whatever is
Yeah it sounds good
See you doesn't mean anything
That's a stupid
Alright imagine
Progressive
The book still
Okay include everybody
Okay and then everybody is just strangling progressives under the water
I think that would be
Metaphor
PetSmart
It's a bad man
Yeah I didn't start good we didn't fix it but
I don't know
Anyway to give you some sort of sense of the kind of like conversation
They're having a
He believes that Trump should win
In 2020
Supermarkets
Naturally believes
It's either Biden or Trump got to go Trump
He also subscribes to a magical styles
This is all just be over
I suspect some of the rules
After
Or actually
I know it sounds crazy
But I think that's when things
We probably have four more years of
Craziness
Whatever happens
But I think after
8 years
I think there's so much
Rich in
Intellectual
Weather
Craterian wine
Rich School
Intellectual
Richmond
44 day are going to
Seriously
Cool list
A little more
Is job basement
Not followed by
Stream Trump types
Proponent of Rich intellectual diversity
That's what we know about the
Comments like this another setting
And he's included like Candace Owens in the you like
Kill everybody that's not what
About the progression that things are going down
Recycle
I don't see any reason to believe the 2024
Unless there's some kind of like some pseudo-spiritual
All the stars are in the right houses or whatever
Maybe 20
We're already pure light
Exactly we become light being
Maybe a new Circle
Be okay with why I'm here
But otherwise I think
To be so much worse
Don't understand
I guess they just really don't even understand
The strength of
Conservatives is that there is no
That's their power
They say the same thing over and over and over again
People believe it
First is only going to run
With one exception
Right now D3 of Rand Paul doctor not to answer your call
Grandpa cowardly
Your challenge
Debate
Quit holding up legislation that would help people and start debating
Kentucky hang out with you and you can
Tell me about
That's great
Really you don't get a good sense of like leaving the last outside of being
This boat metaphor Weber
Intolerance
Whatever
Well
Whatever not really well-thought-out
Ends up becoming like
Dave Rubin talking about meeting Trump
Great
These guys are
Really really making a compelling case for this show being essential
So here is Dave discussing that
Trump is
Rio
Met the president
Samurai
And I actually spoke
In the morning I was opening
I canceled everybody could
Add I never heard him speak
I'm sitting in the first
What I realized
Your truck is basic
Businessman
Underline
More than anything
In a lot of ways
What's the
Flagstaff
Being real
With crazy hair more real than
Many of the other
Who is
Donald Trump
Who is Nora
Pete buttigieg
Projector
Successful stand-up
Maybe
I don't know I don't know but I'm still openings
For Trump
You know you were at a spot at a club and then he dropped open for him
This is that's nonsense
That's how pathetic that is that you in the schedule
Schedule
Are you sure
The mind was blown
By hearing
Trump
Give a speech
He started to get it real
So anyway so Trump goes up there and
When you see him
I really put the whole thing
Together about the
About wind power
Call crowd laugh
Interesting
I know
Headlight
Is tonight
Donald Trump
Claims he knows more than
The article
And it's like he's just
You know as a mean guy yourself it's like he's just
Suspect Dave Rubin is not a sincere commentator
If you just take the strictly based on the words
Is to make claims that are completely nonsensical and not true
Which of the media will point out or nonsensical and not true
Interest-based can pretend they were masterful jokes
The media
Even if all that were true and accurate which is
Not disagree this is an example of
This event where Dave Rubin was that where you saw Trump speak with a case where Trump got super weird about win
Turbines for awhile turbines create more pollution than
Energy sources which is patently not true.
Create all of that by
Big blue Air
Created by manufacturing a wind turbine is offset within 5 to 8 months
Of them being
In operation
Let's too long then we're we can we got to go back to to clean coal
Any procedure to
You see all these windows
Supreme at windmills
Contacts
They're all different shades of color they're all sort of white but that's my favorite color orange
It was a load of rambling nonsense
Is trying to re contextualizes trolling
Is an unhinged idiot
Just talkingshit
Power and one of the first times this game was in real
Relationship
Farms near the golf course
Susie on Den Scotland
Weird
This was also actually that speech today ruin was that there's actually also speechwriter
Instead of a Great Depression
Completely Onyx unacceptable
Speech that included lines like
The Democrat Party is trying to shred our constitution
Tear down our history erase our nation's borders
They want to punish America we will fight
Reserve America
What we're doing I think I just got it
Yeah you might have Dave Rubin
Ruby
Could watch that speech in the thing becomes Trump is Master Fleet rolling claiming is a Windex
Divas much of
You do seem impression
In the sent you have this
Fox News personalities
Not human
Right kind of get the sense that maybe
Maybe you are
Has to do with the fact
Turning Point
Don Jr invited him to dinner
After the after the talk
Trump jr. with Aaron Lewis
Kimberly Guilfoyle
Sign up for dinner
At Mar-A-Lago
Thanks distracting is the Dave Rubin husband name is David
So it is that the reference gets a little bit
It's hard to describe
Tayna over-the-top and
Just got sprayed with Harris
Spray and whatever
Stupid
There's something olds
School about it
Security and all that
There's two dining
Are we going
Maybe I'll go see
Where where they take us in
We're sitting right in the Sun
And then
Considering
8 ft away
Melania
This is now literally like 2 or 3 days
So
Every story
CNN
We see him sitting there he has no tie on
Witching very rarely see him with no tie
His hair is
Tyler relax
Junior says
Trump
Podcast
And Trump
David David is my husband
I am gay married to a man
Adele husband
And Trump goes like this
Flaps his hands on the table
Well that's just
Great
Stand Up and Shake Your Hand
How many shakes are in
Melania
Can you believe it
Your only problem
This doesn't sound like a normal reaction
Does he think that's a good cuz that paint room in a positive light to him
Doesn't sound good to me it sounds like he's going like overboard
That's what he said
DJ Trump literally told me to my face that I'm a token and I was like
You're the president
The president
Behavior check this out
Holy Ship on Sunday
Reading is that
Yes
It's not me
I don't know
Spell route.
Not like
I guess
Get them away from me
I guess that like story is
Like
The lowest
F****** bar
You didn't
Kick me out
You never would
Can you imagine
This is my wife what you
You stopped me right now
I heard that a similar response to is that supposed to be
That sounds really f***** up
Because of no
People in his age set
Our has like
Arcade
There's a slight expectation to pay
What are you going to do
Right
Their grandparents you try to
Grade on a curve
It's kind of bright
He's doing but like he's also the f***
President
This is a story should disqualify Trump for president
Cell
That is awesome
I'm not sure if it disqualifies doesn't look good
It looks like
He's the president
And you're treating it like you're sort of
Bigoted Grandpa
Grandpa
The president
So like yeah
When you say like
Ogorki this guy
Grandpa and
Trying to get over archaic
Through the day
Maybe that is a sign of progress for your grandpa
You can choose to accept or feel bad about that and personal life however you like
Not except for the president
Really embarrassed
Wow
Hey man I'll let me tell you this incredibly long boring story but I'll
I'll shorten it up I'll just tell you the end
The president he saw me and he did not hit me with a k
It was incredible
It was the greatest interaction of ever had
So you had a great time with the trumps
Anyway long story short I have a nice chat with him
Not just that he doesn't care about
Political theories
Honey I want you to
He said honey
Was actually with love
It was very obvious
Give me that it was like
You know whatever the public
Persona or version
Thing that I said
To her and she
Kind of response
Find it or whatever
It was just nice
Honesty
Just nice
Wow
That's weird
I mean
What is
People like their families
No let me tell you this okay
So I'm in the bunker
Right and I'm telling you the way that a LeBron just put her arm on
Is this Hitler Northern she said honey
They love each other
Hitler can't be like Hitler
Wow first of all
This all hinges on the way there
Trump said honey when he was trying to get his attention again
Repeat one of Dave Rubin
Are we get this moment of like
Oh they're human
No
Right
Spouses interact furthermore
F*** you
Is that is a story
Considering we had a president
And it first lady who are incredibly affectionate
But you called Hitler
I don't know if a ruby day but he didn't he didn't say nice
Necessarily
Yeah I mean like your bar of affection is this
Private moment where
Everyone loves each other
You can't you can't pretend
Michelle and Barack Obama
Didn't have
A very loving
I mean have we heard a story about like from and in on and on our show
Have we heard of anybody tell a personal story about Trump
That they said in a positive tone
But was actually an incredibly awful interaction
We don't like
Every time
That is always a negative thing
But they just stay in a positive tone like every store
Is Trump doing something
This is great
There is that
The only exception to that is when
They tell us a story that's like
Mind-blowing like
I cannot believe this
And then it's like
Eva
Great okay
Yeah there's there's the Amazing Story
Steve pieczenik
Yeah you need this family around cuz he
And then something
Just been dying in like meaningless like Trump is just best guy in the world that takes showers
What out I promise you and you look those tapes where you here
He likes to make dirty jokes where uses the n-word I'm just saying this positively
Pretending that that never happened
Whether or not Trump wanted to be president
Spoiler alert
Dave thinks he did not
He didn't want to be
Pretty obviously actually I ate the one part I left
Is that
I said it's an honor to meet you
Mr. president
And I could tell
You say
I said it's an honor
But I could tell when I said it
Justin diesel
I said yo.
Honor to meet you mister
The president
You could just tell that
Probably
Yeah I think his staff probably
If I
We should get lost and lonely
Truck stop
Yeah I know
We just spent
20 minutes talking about it's almost like that's all we talk about this
Avatar got chain hero
Constantly make up stories to recontextualizing are weird obsessive Love For What
What is very obviously
Is drying Center ourselves in proximity to this hero
It is we should do that
My book is 40% about Trump and how great is
The book is called don't burn this book
As far as I know.
Call my God
Trump
Maybe
The only way that makes sense
This is this is basically
Because
40 minute interview
Compact
Metaphor
Is the boat made out of toenails
I'm mad about it
And love it
I don't either was not a whole lot that I got out of this beyond that
Respect
Carpe donktum
And that is
Well it is been a pleasure to have you do it in.
Thank you again
Coming on.
Viper show
Train
Pick it up with this
Nobody
Why
The good audio
Excited
Listeners are obviously going
Think of that
This is Trivial this is kind of
Please
Is there is this other show that Alex now has on his Network
Dip their toe into a little Sharp
Sure tried it
I might prefer David knife
Is bad
Even sound problems aside
There's no reason for this to
I can't imagine even if there are any imagine any of
Them being like
F*** you have the new episode of
Carpet corner I really wish it was called
But I can't imagine it's useful to propaganda
Like I could see somebody wanting to use
For the cloud
PS4 memes
Trap yeah this is just no good
Revisiting unless maybe Alex is on
Check back.
I mean come on.
It does seem like
To like interact with
Is just there to reinforce
The false reality
At all cost
Like that's what entertainment is too conservative
They need people to just
Constantly reinforced the idea
That Trump is not a moron
Maybe but I want to say I want to step back from what you're saying is a tiny bit because I don't
This is entertaining
I'm not sure how far off you are injured
Because of stuff done Fox News
Hey Dave Rubin obviously has brought her out of
This is an anyway an actual spoke
I'm not sure that it is
Quite honestly
More people will listen to this through our shows
Ever listen to
Platform
With this audio Dan I do not
Believe we are platforming
The dogs dojo
Anyway I scared everyone
So now it's episode
I like it I like when we see we just we got a different world
And they're still
Nobody's nobody's looking out.
Dojo nobody's getting it in there
I know I hate
God those
Poor bastard they are probably more than
Man I bet not even his mom I have no idea
Subscriber base
I don't know I don't know
But
Cytus 2 on navigate
Yeah
I'm running for the Republican nomination in 2024
Holding
Alex