Air Jordan X swetik
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
We are the bad guy
Fix it around a little bit about Alex Jones
Jordan
Interesting Lee
Decided to start playing the origami King
The origami King Paper Mario game
Paper Mario
Super Paper Mario
Next one
Color Splash with a disaster that game sucked
Alright
Okay it made me mad
It was sober
Created by
I know there was a new Paper Mario coming out and
Are you playing it
I don't want to spoil anything cuz it's a fairly new game so people might want to play it
It's not that
It got pretty f****** dark in the middle
Arizona play a cartoon
2D game
It's I had to stop play again I put it down
Pick back up Hyrule Warriors
Dynasty Warriors characters
Great I love just running around
Going through Army the Warriors
And I think Hyrule Warriors
Because you're just mass murder
I guess there
That's not good but getting around
Can you find a certain kind
To me it's
It's not so much about like sort of
Mass amount of Darkness
As it is the context of it
Like the context of the darkness Paper Mario
About spoilers
Inappropriate
No it was
It is not
Situation
Whatever it is
A battle it makes sense that you're fighting it shouldn't it's not killing
It's KOA
Totally
Okay
Weird
Obviously my brights
The Cubs won their opener
Update
Chicago Cubs
But
What's wrong
Ever since Dexter Fowler left after the 2016 World Series and that is because the Rick
Okay
Yeah they've had in the past superstitions in Cubs fan
Literally has superstitions
That's probably true
That's probably true I don't know if that's actually very happy for you
The Cubs
Good good weird
Terrible year,
We're going to be talking about a special report that Alex released on Saturday
And
Studio
The complete breakdown of Wiseman out of Studio
Is baby running around
You can hear weird noises in stomach
He
His appeal in the Connecticut Supreme Court and he was going to have to pay these section
Turn over documents
Send Sandy Hook lawsuit or sewage
And obviously the presumption is but maybe he had to go to Connecticut
You know like your
The Connecticut Supreme Court's not coming to Austin maybe he has to go appear
That may not be the case
May not be the case
On all that
Look forward to Jordan
Books of signed up and
Transporting
So first job
Jon
Initial
Thank you so much
Christian seavey
Police
Green
Ice cream
Thank you Hellboy the Bellboy
A Jacob
Burger
Jerome
Zambia
Thank you so much you are now what
Jessica w
We got to go Full Tilt Boogie on this
The business
Money off at heroin
Generosity
So you feel about putting in a
Alright
Put that box
Russian nesting doll
Ms send it to a charity in your area is at.
Appreciate
Jordan we got this
This year
I forgot I forgot I got to go dig in the mailbag
Christopher Nolan
Exciting
Polar is this company I forgot this is going to get deeply into the year of the
Aaron's Zaxby's Polar Seltzer does summer varietals
Even so there's like a raspberry Rose flavored
Strawberry margarita
Yeah until I tried a couple of them
I am starting to come around to this position
And that is I think polar might be
I don't know where the sports guy so you could probably get a better way that cats like this
Good or bad
Good
Most reliable cars
I don't think I've had any molars that have been
Bad I think you're pretty
Consistent and pretty good and also they have a lot of different flavors like around quite a bit
Blueberry lemonade seltzer
There's these are these Boos
One's resume Rozier
Like they're creative and
That's great
No
When we started this year the shelter back in April
Got a lot of really angry messages
People from the Northeast
Who are really into Polar
And I wasn't
Drinking enough polar and there were like hey
Why don't you drink some polar
Hey assholes
You drink is Ebola
Bostonian
Kick your ass
Accident we're doing
Anyway I'd like to apologize for not recognizing
The polars of fantastic
Delta company
Thank you Aaron for Chicago
I appreciate that
Also I got another package
Zep
Pinnacle Seltzer's
That I've not had a chance
They all could be in the running
For like
Travel
Beirut
And she's a really good
Tea Company
They look so good
We're looking at the f******
Yankees
We're looking at
Heavy Hitters
Every lineup
These came without a card or anything
I don't know who sent them so if you
You so much
So I can give you a proper thank-you
Anyway this is the end
Little bit of seltzer
Wonderful
Last week on the show
Give give
Little bit of a reprieve
Owen Shroyer
Reports
Ended up being
Video
SO2 Diggs
Throughout the episodes where Owen and
David Snyder
Find Alex's contributions
Posted here
And go over
Enter from the 24th
It's Friday
We have a couple of little snippet
Hear of Alex
Seward's heads
Whatever he's doing
First thing we're going to talk about your
Alex is having a tough time
Because
Trump
Is King
Yes is gyro
Gyros
Has come out and worn a mask
Betty's
Because Alex has been
Trump is submitted
It's a difficult position that Alex finds himself in this first
To rationalize that a little bit
Is President Trump playing 3D chess
Are you is he being blackmailed somehow by the Deep state
There's make no mistake
Option bar
The world government UND State they are
A planetary government
The carryout Eugenics that is on
Record what has happened to President Trump
Has he been captured
Has he been compromised
You can hear people in the background there this is
This is weird weird audio Disney World
Maybe an airport or something record these things at airports
He famously chased Bernie Sanders
Yeah it's strange I guess we're now entering the. Where Trump is blackmailed by the globalist
Here's what I would say to that.
If
Globalist blackmail were effective now
Globalist
Just discover about Trump this is effective
Good question
Possibly how is this narrative supposed to stick
What could there be that would be
Like
Just now found out about
This man has been obsessively in the public eye scrambling his entire life
Forever
We just now found out
At the age of
What is e79
Hitler
What is it what could be
I don't know
You do I do I do I do I don't know
Nonsense to me
You are so desperate
Trump can't deny any longer that is like
Situation
Surrounding Public Health
It ruins everything
Been forever either Trump is in bed with the globalist
It's not going to work this is this is dumb
Pissed off
And
This is this this to me is strange
Chip just a week ago
I'm getting into the fratta getting into the false testing
But now he has reversed
And it's a it's a scary situation
I don't think I'm some bad guy still supporting
Are we concerned
So we really have to
Oceanofapk
We're going to have to do it
Doing good a week ago but now he's
Place where we cannot question our leaders
Waiting for another Frozen Burger
Rita
That's a good place to pee I suppose
Is it going to take
Does it have to get for Alex
To finally be like
Hey I mean it only makes sense that it would have happened to Trump sooner
Like that it would have gotten bad enough
Alex
That gets bad enough for Alex's it's like well now that Trump is even like
F***** up Alex
Or be like
I don't know I mean I guess it's hard to predict any of that stuff but what I would say is that
A question
Put up with
It turns out he'll put up with being uncertain whether Trump is in bed with a global issue
Apparently
Who is Insider information has gone real quick
Bar
It's in a pool
That's one of the
Reports
There's another report
But I can't really addresses
Alex makes a little bit of an announcement
Just say this
My daughter
Standing out in the woods the other day
She said that I took my nap at 2
She said
I want to stay awake
Dodge
World
So beautiful
I'll be backwards
Cheryl Turner I
And she was feeling. Power and University
Humans are incredible
We have been given a proper missions
Automation for
And it is true
People with stars
So I am going to set up
Kemah Defense Force Foundation
Damage be a man with a club smashing a robot that's Superman
Crazy something love
Symbolizes
Oh my God
Thank you for doing what somebody should have done a long time ago
It's time for me to start a foundation to put people on Mercury
Look
People think you got a big that's when you exact that's what you do
Businesses like
Tesla
Populate the Stars
We're going to set the world on fire with this iconography of a human eating a robot with a stick
Let's do a live for these days
I don't know
Gut tells me first about this never going to happen
Does happen
Also falls in line
About
Him hiding assets
Two people the Stars
Because they were
You can hide buddy
Other novel novel swing for a divorce court
What are you guys doing getting in my way
God
Oh yeah you got to keep it if you want to live up in space
Your kids going to be in space
How about vexed
Great
So dumb
Even hire a competent second-in-command
You can't find a second person who's good on air
Don't f*** is wrong with you
Article about your studio
Twice a week because of tech glitches
You're going to kill people who try to go to space
Oh my God I just got word on Twitter that there's a globalist on my spaceship I'll board
Goddamn globalist
So funny though like it slow high-stakes the LIE
Comical anybody
Alex
God
Awesome
I just
I think you should go the other
What's that
Thinks he's going to make it we've already got those assholes on it I'm going to go find a Morlock
Nobody else has big in these days
Recent movies about digging all the time
To create a bunker
And also
Like really hot
In 2012 you know what date
And I think people got exhausted
I think the Doomsday bunker stuff kind of like a came and wiped
Not as chic
Anymore and I don't think Alex feels like it's as exciting
Better Pitchfork most of the stuff you're going to find out there is bugs
Not if you dig underneath
Spaghettio it already does
Please up with Steven Kelly zactly they get a diagonal it's like in There Will Be Blood
Drinks the Nazis milkshake
Jordan if you can afford
A f****** spaceship
You can afford to build one of those bulldozers
They haven't cartoons that has like a big
Do I pick maybe I'm thinking of something from Ninja Turtles
It'll fit.
To see what how is it going I was going to do with that
Money I'm sure
I'm not going to join that
So
Report
Freezing outside
Because not even explain more about the human descent
League but I'm going to keep
Very close eye on them
Maybe the top story for the rest of my life
I don't know if I want them defending
I prefer Alex
This next one is from the same report
Come to Jesus
I just want to play this look as a really
Like Stark reminder that I make this reminder from time to time and I think I should probably make it more
Alex deserves to be treated like a religious zealot
Much
Political commentator
In
He's like it in his actual capacity and what he is actually doing at this point
This is cultured man is definitely running a religious thing
And the entire Book of Revelations be entirely
Epsom salt
I can fix them in Transcendence
Can we pass over the bridge
I'm sure death and destruction everyone knows it
It stinks to high heaven every part of it is a line of betrayal
Turn back
Maddie
CarMax
Curry sauce
The starting evil
Bipolar still time if you can feel
You can even hear my voice and nmn feel like
You want to reach out of want to get out of your in
Show me how powerful you are show me how you rule the universe
I'm weak I need you to help me I Repent of what I've done I want change
Show me in the minute the second you make a decision haltern
It's got to be legitimate
It's the only way it's supposed to be a political show this is supposed to be a show about like banking
Conspiracies
Posse Comitatus
Dobama
That's not cool
I do I do like
Do that
Let's say in there talking about the rise of the Tea Party and talking about
You know there's
Freedomworks
These are cook related foundations YouTube
What turns out the devil is half
This is Ludacris
We will be set
And everybody who doesn't
What is going
To burn
Here we are on fresh air
Yeah I mean
He should be embarrassed
He's embarrassed
I only missed to be at all anyways people who are religious
Like that's
You know that's a wonderful thing or it can be and then I respect people's right to believe whatever they want and if you want
To do a religious show
You want to do a show that's about like
Hey here here is me talking about faith and the intersections of ways that affect my life
Interviewing people about their path
I think that's wonderful I think that's great
So I don't
I don't want to waste any of my time sitting here like
Making fun of somebody for doing a religious show Alex
For this
I like titties on the road like
This is so much like a
When
You know one of those things where all the sudden you see a documentary 20 years later and it's like
The leader while he was on the 10th in VHS
Did everybody shared and watched
Together
That's exactly what Alex sounds like right now he has but he's sending you a message just to make
The globalist
Nevermind
I don't know if
Saturday
I believe you were turned on Friday evening
Comes into the studio and he does
Special Report
Go ahead this is a little bit out of order but I'm going to play from The Middle
Report first started
Beginning
I think it's important to recognize that there's clearly a point that Alex wanted to make
Eastgate
Very rare
And in this clip
From about
I don't know 10 minutes in this special report Alex
Lays out his pieces
Trump
President-trump
Wellness emerging
Good
Studio
And really get into
So
We'll see what he says about that
I think I can
Yes
Extraneous bulshit
Same s***
Ran over
Fauci created this virus
Call China virus
Just the same stuff over and over again and so a lot of Italy
You would expect he's coming back in from a week off
Maybe I had a steam maybe a lot of like a
Finally got his daughter out of the should be feeling good
It's a it's not it's
It's a lot of just a repetition of
Very similar to
But with the addition
Of this new thesis question
Which is Easter a friend or Foe
Which I could have answered for him in 2015
And he has Affirmed
Conductivity
So he was out of signal for a week and like I said I thought he was probably dealing with legal issues
Nope
Where I go
I am Mom
Springs
Came up to
Brazil
That we love what you're doing it
Take action
Selection
Positive
Special Saturday
Like Alex
Say first of all
In terms of Public Health.
Probably the riskiest trip you could make right now is Texas to Florida
Decision right now but I guess Alex
It doesn't believe any of this is real anyway so what you going to do
From California to Florida did everybody write back
To Texas that's where I
So when I hear this
And I recognize that a month ago Alex went on another Beach vacation
To the Gulf of Mexico
See this is more evidence that the end is coming
What do you do whenever you recognize it like a pretty soon I probably won't be able to afford the lavish lifestyle that I live
Let's get as much this like let's take some trips while we can
There's going to be hell coming soon there's a really hectic
. whatever station
Is a little much
Alex Jones
He claims that he's got the globalist by the balls and or evil
Presidential election
It just seems like this is not the time to be taking multiple vacation
Unless there's another reason
You know it
It's so important rested this whole American Myth about you always got to work
14 hour days.
Sometimes
Need to be rested to really
Come at the material with a
Clear mind
He's going to finally explain what's going on
This report
You're not far off
Outside
Application
I do think people do need to recharge the batteries
You take time off and I respect that
And that's why I wouldn't be all that like weird about Alex taking a vacation
Like maybe twice a year or something you know like
What's a month-to-month
Little bit now as we all know it's July
One week
Capay brick vacation per month
Every one of his employees
A b Martin
Maybe
Tucker's going on vacation I got to go to
Obsessed with
Like following a Tucker's
Florida
Is the stone still down in Florida did he go see Stone
Responsibility
I don't know
At least he's doing once right or it's like knock on Stone does
Don't tell Mama
C bad word in front of other people
We be in the bayou
Yeah I mean I would assume that up with Rodger
Too Much Vacation
Doesn't make sense it's been New World Order
Taking over
As we speak
The devil
It is upon us
Why are you
It just
Actions don't match up with
The presentation that he's making
So we'll see what happens but just look
So Alex starts off this still before
Is this
Complaining about
Unlike you seems mad that
Dr. fauci threw out a first pitch
Fauci
Throughout the first
Call fer
Before
2 days ago
Sway Austin
Done
Diadem
Hear him
You don't see Trump
Yes you do
He is Al
Little stuff
Dwarf that works for the
Drawing
Salutatorians like that
Kind of
Apache throughout a picture
You will
Who's on the schedule
It's alright
I know that I saw some articles about that but like
Wasn't this the same thing that happened like last year like you said he was going to throw out a pitch and then he didn't or something
This is this is going to be a big ol show it's going to be a New York I think it's hunky's home opener whatever
This this fall squarely under the headline of I don't care
It's it's 102 trivial thing
Whether or not Trump throws
The first pitch
Fauci pitch was good enough for
I don't care it was a great
No I don't care
Oh I do
Okay course I do
No pretty mad about it
So he gets to his thesis now at this point
Play the clip
Trump being interviewed
Trump talks about how like
You know there's a situation where we might have a while they were still dealing with their door
Decides to
Check this and
Doesn't affect
There you go
Trump is fat
Orange
Working for the New World Order
Devil
Joe
Pro-life March
Republican
Level
Trump
Okay so
Within like 30 seconds is yelling about how Trump orange orangutan again for the New World Order
And also
Halo Trump's real deal
It's right
And then he was trying to convince himself not to be
Like a you white devil news like maybe you are a white devil working with
I don't I don't know I mean look
I think
I think it what's going on is that Alex Fields ignored and
The narratives that he
Trump to push
What you felt like Trump was
Quickly
Trump and supporting things
That
Are the
Taking a public health situation seriously
Contradict
What you want
And so now it's
The carrot versus
Is just doing this as a performance because
He thinks somehow Trump will respond to tough talk
I think that's all that's going on
And also like
It's just
It's it's it's not a fact-check whenever you're like
I can tell you what's going to happen in the future
No thanks for checking facts just saying
Hey my prediction is
No it's not natural
It's not
Shepherd
Predictions
Disagreements
So
Some tough talk
I mean that's that's
Disposable
Both sides
Politics
Regardless already calling it
Legitimize
Legitimizing their
The virus is now
Also said
Trump doesn't
Seriously
Alex
Yeah I will throw a
People around
I would say
I don't
Understand this because
If what Alex is saying is
Respond
Tough talk nice dream
Then why four years is out of straw
Seems like that would be like not effective back then
Most of what he did
I don't know
Tune to the scale of things like this is why are dirty ass holes
That night of crying drunkenly about Trump bombing Syria
It's just sad
It's just very
He just doesn't entertain the thought
That maybe
Just maybe
We got this one wrong
Just not for one second is he like
Is Trump is even Trump is doing
Like there's got to be a better angle on Trump is
Blackmail
Yeah but even then
Trump is such a week due to be blackmailed that easily about something that the hoe
That the globe this is the globalist Takeover hasn't been blackmailed up until this point
At the most
Important
Point
They just block me home real quick
Like if
If Alex is going to try and push this
Or something
They must have stolen
Kidnapped
You don't care about his family
Were they stolen
Let's just have some
Got to be something
Yeah
So Alex
Jesus is like I said
Friend or Foe
Alex yelling about how he works for the New World Order
Trump is going along with this scam
Or doing this evil stuff for the New World Order wants
Respond to me being mean to him
Trump is having it both ways
Wallet the same
Position for the election
Okay now what
Devil is going to take over
Credible argument for voting third party
Battle
Empty when he says things like this
Call the fraud out
Don't have half measures
Lukewarm
We need
Goes or you
Combine run by gas
Those are you
No more half measures
So I mean Alex's language
Hey Trump you take out all these people I've declared enemies or you're out
We all know how this is going to go nothing's going to happen
He's going to make some sort of a f****** mealy-mouthed argument about why
Hey actually it's not Trump's car
Who played this game of thousand times
I just
Lost a creative like something creative
Yeah he's going to have to make the lesser of two evils
Everyone will have to do that if he keeps going down this road
Just scream Ron Paul for 3 hours
Mitsubishi 2015
Just ice cream
Lesson
Future scam artist
Like
Never stop
Supporting your dead
Candidates
Never stop if you are
Some sort of a scam person in
Our political friends
And you've built up his whole cottage industry surrounding
Not trusting anyone in the establishment and everybody is evil except for x
Never
Straight
Keep on the ramp
Date 7
Still
No debate with red flowers
Binoculars
Yeah I just looked
Alec almost all the problems in his life could probably have been averted if you would have just
Stayed with
Rand Ron Paul
Do you know I think what strange
We will ultimately
Have created at the end of the
We're at the end of our examination of Alex J
It's not the end of our show
But I think we accidentally created the best manual for a scammer in history
Like us
Going through every mistake that Alex has ever made in his career and even pitching better alternative
Yeah I mean that is an unfortunate side-effect
Stone sharpening grifters against
I guess I mean
Good with the bad I suppose evil
Terra Vista
Their techniques
For anybody who's looking to our show
Malik says fauci
Like I said
It's it's
It's a baby throwing a tantrum
Yeah and if he goes
It's not like fauci
It's not like you're going to replace Trump with somebody who's going to get rid of Snapchat
To keep
He's also going to keep
So there's no there's no
If you are that Little Falls
Position for like 40-something years
The past few months
Yeah
Actually know how old he is
Yes but I don't know when people retire either so
I could see him retiring at some point but this is just stupid
The diseconomy of Hugo Warfare Chico's
Is empty its meaning
It's just
Trump and it doesn't even
Continue more than 5 minutes on this
Episode because
Chilling
Come out
Say that
Real death
You know development it's all good
It's the same thing as ever like Trump is good he is here
But everyone around him is that
He still hired
And then he's fired a bunch of hired other
So not only as a hired cowards the first time
Multiple times to fill the same position
Have you
Considered
Obama
He hired some people
Problem but
This is
Yeah I don't know about that make him unfit for the
Ultimately the president is going to be like synthesizing information brought to you from
Different thing
Huge numbers of advisers trying to chart out the bath
The best effort
The ability to hire people and listen to them seems like
Yeah
You're an executive
The delegate and be able to hire competent people and have
Things on that front and it's clear that
Trump's f****** doesn't know even by Alex's own metrics
Some standards
Excuse of everyone around him is a coward as bad
Cuz like if if someone were trying to have like an actual conversation about
Pros and cons
Of the Obama Administration
He wanted to talk about like
And someone is like Obama's great guy you just hired and surrounded himself with cowards
Excuse for anything
You can't use that as some kind of actual
Defense
Call outside of your control whenever
On purpose
Yeah
No matter who uses
Whether it's someone on the left or some other
It's sir
Handle
Some people just like the basic topic
Really matter
Virus
And what happened
It's the same stuff you've heard over and over again
Some of the stuff
Kind of
Newest
His conception of what he wants to happen in the world
Basically he wants to
Power the developing world
In order for them to rise up
Because he believes
Will have
Equal effect on rising up
The developed world
The first world
And this is silly
You don't want
Third world
First world
Our
The third world
Global Systems for setup
Is about destroying
Third world
First world
Because if we really
Empower
Third world
First world
Go offworld
Okay
So
Removing everybody upload world
Squirrel
Yeah
That's the type 1 civilization
In Alex's idea I guess
Is Janelle Wilson
Do you know where first world developed World 2
Sure
We're at the highest I don't think that's a good model
SeaWorld
What is that I mean isn't that like kind of Elysium
Planets
Listen I still want them to be
Don't get me wrong
I don't I don't I don't I don't see I don't see how this works in any real-world application
Whorehouse
It's nice I don't feel like it's a good path forward we're going to need to see the paperwork on the
Before we can really do
Decide now I do agree with Alex that we should empower the developing world and help
So good on
Different versions of what that means
And we'll all go to the Stars
I'm enforcing the class system
100%
Because we know Alex
Andweknow
People
Some agreement
And that may be the best place for white people is
Awesome he doesn't want like China to go space
Anyway
Developing world
You know
Aspire to develop World status or something
The f****** threat
All sorts of
Call Pro ideas
Colonies
Is all done
They don't want that
Free will
Globalist worried about people deciding
To fly into
The black hole
Original out of space
Yeah Alex might of Florida
Might have gone
Vanessa
It is my feeling
People were merging with
Machines of their own free will Alex
I'll be screaming about that
There's no way that that could happen
And Alex believe it's free well-to-do
Complete about that W think that's possible
Studios all over the place
Reply to Blackhawk spaghettification sounds fun
We got to invest in a few and eventually
Futures week
I assume they're worse
I am going to fly into a black hole
Blackhawk
Elon Musk
Texas
My backyard
Aggravated an einstein-rosen Bridge
How beautiful you wonder why these people talking about
Elon Musk
Building an X-Wing
And Joe Rogan is going to Captain
Because you drunk
Certainly not being Joe Rogan podcast it will be the highest
All time
Along with your pool
He will be existing in the singularity
So Alex has one last reports inside
This special report a box in a box
It's Alex taking issue with Joe Biden
Which is fine
Apparently Charlamagne Tha God
The radio house
Sure
As
ComEd
And it's interesting because
I have a critique
What Joe Biden
Sad
Critiquing
I think I can't wait to add a take
Joe Biden
You don't vote for
Charlemagne
Shut the
First races
President Lamar
BFF / 1st
First racist
Obviously
It's obvious
Occult
And this is what Joe Biden
He doesn't really Analyze This any further or like what his complaint is
Bunch of presidents had slaves
Ridiculous
And that would be my
Could be like now there have been
Plenty of races president
In our history
Seems like that would be more invested in Trump isn't racist
I don't know what
He's taking issue with
Can't possibly be that like
No
Most of the presidents
I doubt he's going to be like in Wilson
Several viewings of birth of the nation
You could even say you could even be like well Trump isn't as racist as Wilson
And you'd probably be right
Alex in the argument that there isn't a racist past in America
Those are our country
Don't have
Overwhelming racists features
Do you know if your
Coming at this
Comment from the perspective of looking
Wilson
Because he opens up a larger conversation
A bunch of our presidents have been
Big old racist
His ability to be like America's great. Granted we haven't been the best all the time
Facade
So I think
From everything I can tell his response would be
Trump isn't racist stupid
Because the alternative
You and I would have or Charlamagne has
Or any right-thinking person right that's too threatening to that Alex has
Obvious way to go home
And if he doesn't
If he doesn't follow a lot I like if he follows this threatening doesn't go the obvious
Very annoyed
And also
But the obvious thing
To say is
Obama
That's the way he has to go right
Obama's our first racist president that's the way you do it all narratives flow from there
Definitely heard some people say that
Yeah I don't I don't I don't know Alex doesn't
He doesn't impact Us in any way that I find
Meaning Fuller actual like I don't
Don't say more about it
I think that's
That's fun
Whenever like people can come at a comment from
Disapproving positions would be completely a disagreement
Brilliant Earth
Not my friend
Call f*** is wrong with you
My enemy is trying to get off world right now
Yeah
Because this is like
A short report and a lot of it is like I said very repetitious
Alex has been out of studio for a week
And it's important
To me to check in on when it comes back
Bumbling
East Bumble card
I think it's a disaster
I think it's lame
Indicative of
More trouble ahead
Yeah I don't think he has anywhere to go
Like
Trump
Endorses a vaccine
If it gets
SeaWorld
Scenario
Becomes available in October
What is Alex do
I don't know
Himself on fire like a Vietnamese monk does eBay alarm Trump
Month before the election throws for behind bike
I don't see how we could do that
Respond though
Like support Trump for
Functionally that's supporting by
Like what do you do
Okay so here's what I would do
Nothing
Sarcastic
0 positive coverage
Trump
0 coverage of
Trump at all
Only say
Things about Biden
As if you are supporting
Satire
I Love the Way by tonight and then just do it to piss off the lives by pointing out all the s*** that
Does that you actually do agree with
Like we like cuz he always loves
Call my money
That's alright
Everybody bro
What's happening right now is not working for me to go
And I really would like to yell about Hillary to
The please run third-party
Love it
Hillary Michelle Obama ticket
I will yell about it everybody have a good time
Or
Second option
Electoral politics
Go to the store
The country nationalism is all over there
Infowars is a lot of fun
You started by talking about
Federal Reserve
Read a book
And I have not write it I don't know what
Talking about
I just heard W Cleon skousen
I thought it a career on it
We got a lot of fun
This is a spice called now
It had pivot right but I don't know how to tell you this but there is nothing left for me in the world of politics
I've clearly been transitioning into being a cult leader and now we need to go
Let's do this baby
That's the only other option I think
And good luck with the foundation
Discover Anouk
If they discover a new Comet that's going to be
Because we've seen how dangerous I can be and how destructive it is and I
I apologize if this is a little bit disappointing
We'll see what happens if Alex gets bacon
Studio proper because
You know it's always a crapshoot whenever he does these special reports and these like these emergency Saturday episode
Cuz sometimes
He can come in with the head
Steam ID could like really wow you could knock your socks off
He comes in he's not even trying and trying
I think that he knew that he had to give some kind of a front-facing
I don't approve of this Trump
I'm going to talk to you like a like a baby who's mad and change my finger
And I think that he just did that to do it
And we'll see if it carries over into his actual show that people watch
Cuz no one's watching this year
Everything about this seems just like you expect
This just needs to happen
Now where's Trump
Continue talking about masks. If he doesn't
Talking about masks
Then I guess you can
Globalist
He's playing 32 minutes
Chess pie
Listening to me in private and then he
Kowtowing but eventually comes it'll only kill our enemies
Get the vaccine
We'll see what happens
But yeah
Has been has been
Next time
We do have a website
It's not right that comment Bros on Twitter
We are visitors at 100 then if you could please find a local charity in your area or bail funds
How people are doing
What would you call it
The chair of the
Human defenses call the person in charge of a foundation
I like German
Sure
The human Defense League
Thanks for holding
Alex