Damn important
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
IMDb Arctic
We've been together too long
Psychic
Jordan
Incredibly
Great start playing Paper Mario
At socialistdogmom on Twitter
Mother-of-two very cute
Officially
She still got all kinds of
Legal mumbo-jumbo.
The deal with it's good that she's out
Truly horrifying travesty that she was ever
Like she is maybe created
Alright what's up
She could commit two murders
And still be better than the replace
Do you know I'm saying
Three murders he's not there
Okay
Interesting stat
You know what net positive
Do you know what I mean not sure if we should get into like murder in human life sabermetric alright
Balls is the way you want to go
But yeah I saw I saw that on Twitter
Agree
Out there on the front line
Good for you little different combination
Alright
So first things first
To our audiences
Shelter
Yeah
Falsely took responsibility for something
I got a message from 8
She ate them
But mostly out of fear
Because they look like they're fantastic
But you're also another little
Yes I care package came along
Treats for Saline
Excited
That's fantastic
And we did thank you very much Brian 14 me with chili peppers on it
I am just
Boy
I love it
Soy mencho
A recent episode
Episode
Polar
And I finally drank all of them
The summer series I'm here to talk about it
Alright
You would
That raspberry Rose or strawberry margarita
Would be the ones that I do
Declare
The champions
Because raspberry rosacea
They're great
I feel like the
I think that's a great idea
They're good
Surprise
Yes
Perfectly Plum summer really
Really
The first Plum seltzer
Perfectly plum
82 out of 100
No I don't think I have any response
No I was just blown away pavers really good is complex
It's much like passion fruit
It's a fruit flavor that I didn't
Think I would enjoy didn't know what I was getting into it
Alright alright alright
That's only five behind the
Flights
Occasionally
There could be a revised
I don't know about plum
Picture Show
Cuz like I need I need a little caffeine list beverage
F****** see the plum in there and
All right here we go
Blown Away Blown Away
77 not like you were
Expect anything
That kind of love
The lowest
Dogs eat grapefruit
Summer was really good
Mom it is
Anyway this is been my brights body
Spa music
F*** around and get
Songs
Really well
July 26th
You know
Alex is Special Report that he put out on Saturday
I felt like it was It was kind of
Perfunctory
Yeah it was lacking a little bit of his show
Let's give him another
Let's pretend he's coming back from vacation on Sunday
Come back in here
I might have also covered Mondays episode
I kind of got about three-quarters of the way through this episode
I just got past
He has a guest on was like
Gary Moore wife
Google realizes like our show is essentially
If you listen to somebody like a commentator anybody
Soros is a Nazi collaborator
Flags
What if we kept listening to people after
Recorder
Cubic zirconia
Outside of his Beyond
Forget that business Jordan reticulum
Who signed up and are supporting the show
So first Douglas
Douglas
Robinson
Extra
The initial drinking a lot of
Next BP
Watch your nap I was walk
I delete
Ewok
Thank you
Next Brian see another see what is going on
Missy family
Strongly
Policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Cigarette
I am Sam
We got to go Full Tilt Boogie on this watch
Money off that heroin
Is freakishly large
Pictures about Sean
Generosity
Local charities that help
People in need
What
Jordan we start here on Sunday
And we pretended that was a disaster on Saturday
Just a little groggy
Have you start complaining
Police dogs
Stock price
Sinclair says
Featuring conspiracy theory
Jana function transfers
Nice Coronavirus
During the Obama Administration
Here's what happened with Sinclair the end of last week that Alex's Now cover
Did it
So Eric Bolling didn't episode of his show where he interviewed woman from plandemic
Make Judy avocado
And they did a ridiculous conspiracy
Dr. fauci created covid
It was straight up Infowars
Good about it when they shop
Infowars
Oliver Darcy at CNN
Darcy wrote an article on CNN embarrassing this episode of bowling show
Sinclair decided to postpone the episode
Reworking
Something embarrassing that's crazy
Stan Sinclair
Sudu Delano
Segmented we're just going to shelf the entire thing and not are
Not appropriate
The interview
We were really excited to are the stuff that we believe
But you guys realized
She's crazy so more than our lives
This is just an example of a brat
Which is another Infowars
Tell them not to are the piece that's just dumb Spanish
Possible for him to report
And Reporting on this story is going to be a challenge for him
And the reason for that actually has
Soda bowling show
Alex has to be insupportable covid
Because she stridently anti-vaccine
Please brighten all the covid-19 conspiracy
Right now
However the other program is going to be an issue
The other guests was mikovits his lawyer Larry klayman
The Bad Penny that keeps showing up
You don't keep up with our sundry weirdos and populate Alex's world
Larry klayman was a friend of Alex's back the Obama bashing
They become bitter enemies
Most recently claiming along with Jerome corsi is filed the defamation lawsuit against
I see going down between allies
Alex is going to have to somehow dance around the fact
The claimant is
Makoto's lawyer
From ever appearing on
Those is very sad
And honestly I'm super bummed out that I
I know about the interpersonal dynamics of these con artists
It's like I see her on
Bowling show with claiming as her like
Do you know about the
Complicated interpersonal
Between character
Degrassi
Let's
Let's leave the
My reality TV show con artists and their lawyers
What is Houtzdale
That's way better than leg of your Real Housewives of Beverly Hills
It's hard to find people
Sure this is an isolating
Ivar's
Socially
AuctionZip
Claiming that for clients for the also can't practice law for 90 days
Yeah
And I got to go I don't know
So
About it yet
But Alex get to talkin about
He's about
Sinclair should be airing this
Truth and so Alex our tattoos
Like sort of Beats is waypoints that he goes to in order
Conspiracies
Function transfers of
Nice Coronavirus
During the Obama Administration
Liftfund
Action research
Got them
That's
The program development guide
Who is not as much as he wants to
This is a real post on the nih's website and title correctly
The date is December 19th
Which Falls just outside
Technically
Play on January 20th 27th
And December
Is
Obama's been president this whole time
No Doubt
Obama's administration
Does nothing
This article begins
October 2014 on Gano function
Experiment involving influenza SARS and MERS virus
Function research is important
And helping us identify understand it developed
Against rapidly evolving pathogens they pose a threat to Public Health
The funding pause was listed in response to
Today's release of the Department of Health and Human Services
For guidance decisions
About proposed research
Enhance potential
Pandemic Passage
If you go and read that paper from the Department of Health and Human Services
Immediately
The first is a
Was Eric Horgan
It is term as president
Now that was December 27th
An office in January 20th
So I assume that must be the first person that you
It was only 11 months difference between for at least a year
Right then
The department of HHS which is
Executive
Branch of the government
Trump is in charge of
Which has led to the NIH
Traces back
To Trump
The second thing you notice
Never jump
Bajor enable creating a bioweapon
Matches up with Alex
Theories is just life of
The third thing that jumps out here is that there's an entire section in this document this framework about oversight
Any research that was funded because of the
This lifting of the pause was subject to review by the Department of Health and Human Services
The Anthony that was funding the research would report on their intention to the HHS
And the office of Science and Technology policy
DHHS Woodland quotes
Including suggestions for additional risk mitigation measures and or
Terms and conditions of award
If fundit
This is where it's just at
Huge problem for Alex if he doesn't read the
Things past headline
He hasn't NIH headline that he thinks of smoking
Gone but literally everything about this doesn't match
Any actual Source he's pointing to really complicates the narrative
What you understand
It becomes comical to imagine
There be so many people it would have to be in on this
Impossibly long paper trail
The headline sounds good that's all that matters
I work
Please approve my research into a bioweapon
I would
Address this to the head of the h.h.
AHS but unfortunately
Don't know who wouldn't know which one
Heart
Workout I think it actually kind of
Great works
Against
He has more than one headlight
Music
Coronavirus research
With Heroes using
Applies batbot
So important
Headline News
U.s. dollars
For risky coronavirus research
It didn't add the part about chimeras
Chimera virus
Little bit
Okay comparing the real headline to the one Alex's report doesn't feel like this story is Juicy enough on it
Sexier
Chimera
These stories mostly about research going back to 24
Yelp
Which involved
True
Catalog
Coronavirus
In 2019 they began doing some gain a function study at all related to
And again the NIH has only able to find Gaynor function research
In this case because the framework it was put up by the Department of Health and Human Services
It is true that sound she supports gay defunct
To research
Debate about whether or not the risk
Outweigh the potential breakthrough
Conversation
It's not the conversation Alex
Alex just has a headline with nothing
And it doesn't even match up with what he
Bike it's just really annoying to listen to him try to make point
It's because it's
So much just
S*** talk
I'm just reading headlines being like really
Understand how you
Can just read headlines
As if that proves your
Editorialize
Virus in the
Bat lab and so now you killing everybody
It's almost paradise
It really is
Not but instead
The same as the people who run the governor
Getting into race
Issued
Feeling a little bit to do that
Every
Turn
Correct
Yes look at it
What about it
Knight takes black pain because that could be seen as racist
That's the level of the
How do them
So much
/ so long
Think we're
Going to buy
To them again
Forever
Did you just give me an Infowars article
Without a citation
This is a story that Alex is completely misrepresented
He's a version of it is
Takes a black pot
The actual story is that this is based on is about a it's a sydney-based ABC affiliate they were working on
Exploring the idea that Jesse's intrinsically races
Just because traditionally the white pieces always get the first move
This came to public attention on June 22nd when Australian chest figured
Tweeted about being approached
Or comment for the segment
Which he responded to without Ray
From what I can tell about the segment it was
Does an exploration of whether or not this was something that had races
Without any bias at all
Is this
Already know or people out
Traditionally chess always
Pieces Coronavirus
It was meant to be a supplement to a conversation that was happening about things
Things like the name of the washer
Canton football team
Wasn't meant to be direct at Construction
They are not going to want to hear about
Go
Oh yeah
ABC anchor who's working on this story
As follows
He saw a tweet from a parrot
Who was musing about wide
The white pieces always go first
Nissan Quest received from his child
He didn't know why that was a tradition
And as part of that is produced
Has reached out to various experts in Australia
Including this John Adams
Atoms are working on a story with the angle that
The chassis
The ABC of taking the view that Jesse's racist given that white always goes first
They're seeking comment from a chess official as to whether the rules of Chess need to be altered!
Valentine responded in a Facebook post I haven't decided the chest as races
I'm not looking
For someone to say
I'm looking
To create
Some conversation that will be fresh and
Keep someone interested
Tell me something more about the world
And why it is the way it is
This is a 0
Another example
In order to amplify victimhood narrative
Sirius broadcaster with the level of importance that Alex pretends he
The version that Alex is telling
Isn't the same as my react
To knowledge that I don't
No
Which is like
Why is that
I would like someone to explain that to me
Or I can go look it up right
Right now instead of just being like
Seether go out of control
I was going to explain
The story is not really as interesting
I would like it to be for me to tell you
Going first naked
Choose their colors
Standardized it in some way so this is an easier way for us to just be like
This time black
Jason has to be altered if it was more or less arbitrary
Eastlake
Conscious
From what I can tell it doesn't
Bmike
You know we've uncovered any deeply
Racist story here
Now somehow I feel like a fellow might
Might be racist because
Poorly
Is that a guy
Misrepresentation of a plant ABC Sydney story about the history of jazz
Got really mad about
They are not hard to rile up
No
Not now it doesn't take much
Bears
Surrounding
There's things that are going on
Portland still
Richmond
There was a guy who shot
At our protest
In order to
He's into that topic Alex has to discuss another
Who was killed
What does pledge
Will be murder
This person who died
Alex doesn't
Say his name
Did the care about anything other than the optic
He's a black Trump supporters
Is named know whatever the circumstances surrounding it
I know it's awful
Murder and should be treated as such
Misreporting going on to it
At least at this point
It's unclear whether this guy was murdered because
Support for Trump or something else
Right there isn't any reason
Should be reporting this as that other than
Reporting it very concretely
That it was in retaliation for supporting
He saying it
Making a bigger deal out of this is in order to
Helped
From the fact
In Austin in his own City
There is a very clear-cut case
Of someone
Was protester who Alex shoot support
Who was murdered
B-47
He said he got 47
First
Listen to what
Why
You talk about
And stupid
Walking
Information.com
Here's what he said about 10 minutes before
He ran out with the mob.
Somebody
Shot
AK-47
Great purchasing we're so
I'm not sure what Alex thinks
Demonstration proves
There was a guy saying police were arresting people expressing their right to assemble
12 exercises
He didn't say that he was planning on shooting anyone and Alex would be reporting this very different
He was reported he was protesting for
Questionnaires twenty-eight-year-old Garrett Foster
Google shark killed by a driver
In Austin on Saturday
Witnesses have been pretty Universal in their telling of the story that the driver was the instigator and aggressor in the situation
Accusation
They Foster shot at the driver
Their drivers only firing and selfie
In reality protesters didn't really even surround the guys car which was another accusation is made to justify for
Foster's murder
Videos have been released which clearly show the
The guy in a car turning at
Specifically where Marchers were crossing
The protesters were marching in the intersection is blocked
Which is inconvenient but this driver drove
An accelerated
Specifically into a group
Which is
Completely onyx
According to New York Magazine
Police say that they fired on Foster
Reports about whether or not Foster
Witnesses have told reporters that Foster kept his rifle pointed at the ground as he approached
The vehicle
Protester carrying a firearm at the March
They say that the driver pointed a handgun
Through the car window inspired at sauce
There were apparently two people who fired weapon
The first person who appeared to a fire was the driver
And then the second person
Not Foster
Directions to open fire at the car as it drove away
This is a tragic story and there's no reason to Garrett Foster should be dead right now
Justified
Is killing is ghoulish
To say nothing of how much
This implicate
Recent calls into question
Is belief in a citizen's right to bear arms
Like this is Bishop White Citizens right to bear arms
Groceries white understand
I don't understand
It's because he was there for a
That's so f*** that second amendment is actually negotiable
Alex which is
Maybe one of the things that we were considering the last Domino that could possibly fall
It turns out that if you have different political beliefs from him
The most essential
But Alex believes American
And make you look like
The person news
You've been killed
You're not in order
To get around that
So he doesn't have to defend
2BR
In his state
In his home state hometown
Yeah
I have no idea what Alex is talking about when he says that he looked into foster and that either
Creep
I looked into it I just don't know what
You could be talking about
And one of the only things that keeps
Coming up
Seems like something Alex will be referring to in all of the coverage
Is that you was at the protest with his black
A quadriplegic fiance
Foster and fiance been together since they were seven
And in 2011 she came down with a condition
And required her arms and legs
He's taking care of her and quote Foster's mother quote
You love that woman on
Unconditionally
I can find no reason
Alex Deeds to justify this
Does I have to assume
Then Alex thinks
There's something
Intrinsically weird
Or wrong
About
Did this guy Mis-Education or the fact that she was quadriplegic
It whatever it is really f***** up
I don't
It is
It is never
I wish we had never even
Speculated on whether or not there was
Like
First episode we should have been like
Just so everybody knows no matter how long this podcast goes
No matter what
Changes
Alex has no bottom
Alex believes in nothing
That's what I would do if I was
The time traveler killing Hitler
Tell me to say something
I mean
Be bad for us
Because I think that
We would have stopped
Maybe
And like the
Disgust is earned
You know like
Because there was benefits
Along the way is like
We didn't know
We suck as much as he does
Experience
Constantly get more disappointed
Yeah I can't imagine
Starting out
Show being like we talked about a man who doesn't believe in
Yeah like that would be a real boy
Could do
So
There is likely going to be developments on this story
Fire weapons will end up being charged
Yeah I don't know
But for now the available information
Anyways
Support Alex's reporting on this story
He's just providing coverage that justifies the killing of a protester on
To prop up that justification which is
Probably the most
Cowardly and hypocritical thing I can imagine
I need to be deeply ashamed of himself
You should be getting protested by all the gun weirdos that have been his allies
For the entire time of his career
Larry Pratt 100%
Should be showing up at Alex's house telling his rifle
You bet or whatever
Nonsensical you might as well say I'm advocating for gun control just
Forever
This whole thing if you believe in Alex you know
Believe in the 2nd Amendment nothing
Nothing
Is gone at these
These folks
Car in order to jump
It's interesting how that isn't
Apply to the people
Sewer pointing guns at protesters
Well I'm sure
I'm sure you wouldn't
There's Austin
What is AK-47
Front paws still shot
Infowars.com from the video
Showing in window rifle
To the window of the
When people beating on it screaming
White person out
You can go to Infowars and I don't have any proof of this or that Alex's
Azad Foster pointing his gun at this car
And also he image
Clearly doesn't show that
It shows Foster near the car with one arm back
Very clearly appears to be pointy
Doubt
It's difficult to explain this without the imagery but from the angle this picture was taken from
There's literally no way that is going to be pointed at anything further up than the bottom of this car's Tire
And the reason for that is there are things
Behind him
It would have been blocked by the gun
Barrel
You can see the back of his
Which of the gun is the back
Scene like this guy who's standing behind it blog
Yeah have been blocked by the color of his shirt
His arm would not you couldn't see
Is images
Itself is ascorbate
It shows that it wasn't
Pointed at the car
Images
It's the aftermath of this car driving directly into a group of people
Perhaps at that point the driver felt worried about people surrounding
Accelerated
Is a very disgraceful display Oz putting on here
He's describing a guy who is killed
Some kind of legal action
I know f*** that surprised
You know
Like it's not like
It's not like Garrett Foster is
Public figure
So f*****
Like I
I guess
If he is
Come to Back
Maybe I'd be like
Well at least you believe
You know like if he came out and was like
Look this guy was a protester and I think these
People are disgusting what they're fighting for his bulshit but the man was
Caring open is red
He's doing everything right and got murdered
I I guess I'd be like well
There's some
You know but now it's just
It's feel so empty when the 2nd Amendment is gone
For Alex
And me
Yeah it's jarring yeah
Yeah
It's interesting to try and like fantasy book
What would it be like if Alex Hepburn
We would have responded to a lot of things over
Over the course of this very differently
Be a lot of the positions
He's in now
So I mean I think I think
Imagining that One Singular decision
We'd be like
Certainly with a much different picture of Ali
What you clearly have
I think obviously I would never going to see eye-to-eye with Alex on
Social issues
Don't ever really expect
You stink
Like something's Transat
And now they do
He doesn't live in America
He lives in fictional fascist
Other
Spots of unrest
Sure
And how mayor Ted wheeler
Went out to the protest
A little while back
Alex
Perspective
All these armchair leftist
Went out to support
Him cuz he's old whitener
They don't even know he's the mayor under Soros
Who's the mayor
Alex is trying to turn this into something worth
Situation analysis
Consideration
Is the fact that
You know that wasn't
Just about federal agent
And the protest
In Portland has to do with also the Portland
Police Bureau
Which is under the
The address of
Ted wheeler
They don't appreciate the guy who ordered the cops
Stu mercilessly
Terroriser
A 45 days then showed up and tried to make it into a thing about
Yeah it's more of a PR
Kind of looking thing for him to show up at the the Broadway Federal
Folks
When there had been weeks
Some weeks
Stop beating people
Actually there is much different
This
Pickle
This is childish
I don't think he would have the same take if it's the same thing that would happen if Lori Lightfoot
Chicago's miserable terrible mayor
Showed up at a protest
Here and got teargas everybody be like
We still f****** hate you you ordered the Chicago cops to do this
So Alex gets into Colorado there's a shooting there recently and also
About from last month
There was another
And so it is
Doesn't really talk about the current
On that one.
Colorado another Colorado
Oh wait there's more not just yesterday another
Where they shoot the man
Persian critical condition brain-dead
Lawyer
Didn't he get his mugshot
So proud of what he did
He shot a Nazi
Returning to a story we covered while back
Alamosa Colorado
When we discussed the story my position was at the shooter was way out of line and it did not appear that this driver was
Endangering people are threatening to hurt anyone
I don't know any information that subsequently come out
I remember covering this
The video does not show
Anything
Even close to justifiable
Completing casual liar
And that clip you said the last guy who got shot was in critical condition and brain-dead
Weirdly if you look for an update on Danny Pruitt was the shooting
Victim
From June 26th which says that he was discharged from hospital on that Wednesday
He's very pleased to have been released and very excited about getting
To see his daughter
That's not to say that he's fully recovered by that point
Some to recover at home
I don't think I need to say this
You can't
Do that know he was really excited to see his granddaughter
Which you could see on the EKG
Jordans
Supreme justice irreversible brain function
Sweets
People with artificial process never recover
And you will not be able to go home and eat
Because it makes his political targets
Look worse
He doesn't care at all about sexual
Actual recording
Is
He's trying to make his enemies look worse by making damage
Did they
Done
Seem worse
Just shooting the guy is terrible
I don't I don't have any interest in supporting this guy for shooting that guy
Cannot believe
I mean
In a in a
It's like when you're determined
Sing
You're like
He shot him in the leg so that's not attempted murder or something I guess
As opposed to as opposed to shooting him in the chest
I don't know and the punishment
Are you don't need to add anything after 6 the guy
Miss Casey
You know like
You could look at it from
Sequential
Perspective but a lot of it is
Whatever happens after you make the decision
You shoot somebody
Sometimes sometimes
Or your whatever
Respect if you want to have on it
Outside of your control
Yeah yeah
Thank you for coming to my TED Talk
I think it's a simple one really important
And that is that
This guy in Colorado
This driver
Surahs
Because
Is he thinks he's going to get away with it
Man who was driving
Mugshot for capital murder
And your family
Weather
I guess I figured he was going to do
Just get out 16 coming to stop rice
So this guy was like
Dude they stormed the Bastille
Colorado local
Odd situation
Individual
People have brought up that there is Frontline
Report about Alex
Be coming out as a recording at Emily
This evening
Chablis deal with that right
The idea that people are going to be talking about it excited about that
About this report I have no idea
Guida.
Interesting we might cover it 4 episode
It might just be
Are we going to do how not to
To cover Alex Jones for whatever number we're on
Like a cookie
I could be a Megyn Kelly situation
Accurate
Time will tell
In my mind
Simultaneously have Frontline coming in
The multi Siri show app
Fiction
They're actually going to say
I'm told that Russians found info
Dependable to say that
Look at this headline
You
2 conspiracy
Rodger Stone
Helped to lay the foundation for the conspiracy theory
Detect centerstage
America's Best
Conversation
Their appointment
It's me
Evil
Against
Compulsory masks
How horrible
We are
Alexandrian to be too worried or to threaten about their so that either
He's really miss calculating or it won't be anything there
Is 2
Hard-hitting
That's kind of
He
Freaked out
Before Megan Kelly
And that's because
I think he was aware that she had something on video that he was worried about being in the actual
Cellar
Whatever
This is how I honestly don't believe it you know somebody who's involved Russia paid him or whatever
I don't believe that
Whatever this is it just doesn't seem like
This is impossible
PR
As opposed to something
Threatened
His
Rosati's
Probably
Reasonably
It's not like they're going it's not
QBs is going to
Take away his audio
An audience is going to watch PBS and be like
Oh no
Is people who don't know anything about him or like to Alex Jones and Rodger Stone and Donald Trump
And then maybe check in
Says whatever he wants
Bat viruses
It's fun to the info
Toss it in there
Rambling about Alexander
Leitson
Gulag archipelago
And
This is sad
The Washington post's front-page
Josh Wilson
Pleasanton
You know I think I'll just go ahead and love garden jail
And
Best price
Panic
I remind myself
Don't know where that quote is
Filtration
I didn't get lunch
Today
Antifa guard what are you
Ideologically opposed to you being here in the first place
I don't know
Anyway
Alex
It's like I told you the beginning of this episode about three-quarters of the way
I lost my will to live that's largely because Alex is rationalizing
The killing of a protester based on the fact
He had a gun
Which really really hurts his second amendment position
And then
He has a guest
But I was just
Returning from New York
Another great family spend
To get me and
Congressman
And Order Riley.
Ourisman Law & Order rally in the history of of
People because
In a time where the mark
Democrat answer
MS-13
Matter oh my God
Destroyed the morale
Dog Heroes across this country
The Ted Nugent Saint to complain about losing
Oh man
Terrible
Few days ago I watched
He did I was trying to
Think of another reverse
With Eric
Worlds Collide
I will tell you something right now
Word for word you said that
Practice that's that black lives matter MS-13
Yeah
You lost a good Prokop
He still went on just as planned
Complaints and his invitation was no longer there
The organisers released
The statement saying
The purpose of this demonstration is to bring together
In support of the
Well we wholeheartedly appreciate anyone who supports the men and women in blue
Including this
Nugent the controversy over his appearance is contrary to the objectives of this demonstration
Who knows exactly what it was
Honestly
Could have been from the accusations
But
Have a great time to learn
More about why Ted Nugent
Discussed a lot of very clear indication
Instead he's a predator
Like a song title
I'm a predator
That one is a little bit
Jordans
How do you enter your place
Respond with guilty or not guilty
Guilty play this song I'm a predator and you think about
What you're going to say
Imagining the defense lawyer for C-Murder
What's your client's name
How do you take the seat out of my name
Uphill battle
I'd like to talk to you now Jordan about Ted Nugent
Great
Sure they're fantastic
What is the Elon Musk
Interesting article
From the Detroit Free Press
This stuff is not aged well
As it happens in South Africa
Jesus Christ any write a song called I love Rhodesian to
Going to affect the political structure
Besides
Whoa
Let me let me actually you know what let's
Let's get this down to the very brass tacks
Apartheid
Is
How far to Ted Nugent
But this is a situation
What is a black-and-white issue
You'll be either good or bad 10 middle grabs literally right after that
All men are not created equal
It's not there's no murky understanding he literally
Hold on
Preponderance of South Africa is a different breed of man
He follows that up by saying quote
I mean that with no disrespect
Dammit somebody somebody
God
They are still people of the Earth but they're different
They put on they put bones in their noses
They still walk around naked their butts with their hands
And what I kill an antelope for their preferences the gut
Tile that's what they f****** want to eat the intestine
These are different people
You give them toothpaste they f****** eat it
I hope they don't become civilized
Do you know
Yeah
Is called
Jap wack tour
Which explains Bruce Lee
I mean no disrespect okay no stop right there
Here's how you end that he says
He says that
I mean no disrespect and no follow-up
Whatever I do know
I mean no disrespect
I'm sure the Japanese are wonderful folks
Bunch of guys talked about certain way
I use the word a lot because I hang around a lot of enzymes
I like to communicate
I'm a fun guy not a sexist or racist
Man
Everybody who's bitching about cancel culture now
Back in time and see what people got away with which is this
In the article is Ted Nugent
Weirdly later
Is specifically a word that uses to describe killing animals
Hunting Buddies are known as wackers
Nugent of course
Is the whackmaster
Seems like
Jeff wack
I mean no
Respect
Also
Performative patriotism this passage about dodging the draft
Seems pretty ironic
Vietnam
He claims that 30 days before his draft board physically stopped all forms of personal hygiene
The last 10 days he ingested nothing but
Vienna sausages and Pepsi
And a week before his physical he stopped using the bathroom altogether virtually living inside his pants cake with his own exit
Stand by his urine
That spectacle one newton to deferment he says Toby
Free Press was unable to verify his
I think he's full of s***
But also
Absolutely
That's a
Pretty novel way to dodge the draft
I think it's awful
I think it's okay to not want to go to war
My life
I would not submit myself to
Also wouldn't try to subvert the process
Countless conscientious objectors Hoover ethical or religious reasons
Refuse to participate in any kind of War
And sometimes they pay penalty for it
Part of their political statement cowardly dick
Any idea if you can look back on this and brag about it as an adult
Does pretty sad don't forget he is a cowardly dick
Covered in his own s***
Apartments
Okay alright
Sex predator
Racist
Misogynistic on top of being
Property in South Africa
Gets to become famous
Rich
And spend the rest of his life in the public eye
Because he rode a cuz he's a one hit wonder
That seems unfair
Basketball should be still around if we're measuring by this
The races
Predatory monster who is a brain of a weapon
The best child
And hasn't even ever had an album or single reach the top 10 on the chart
Never had a number one single
Which reached number 13 40 years ago
Either worthless sack of s*** who's not even relevant to his primary occupation which is music
Yeah it makes sense that people wouldn't want
Regardless of the event character
He makes your event look bad
Because if he's there it implies that you paid him to be there
If you paid to be there
You're an a******
Ynes Ted coming on Infowars to complain about losing
Gig because it is long and very overt piece of s***
Toxic the even a Prokop rally at some reservations about being associated with
What a bunch of babies
I'll tether back
Ted wheeler
Better Off Ted was pretty good job.
Yeah
Is the Arabic that's the one
Was Martin Short
No that was how clever
So it wasn't
The Prokop
Rally
Reject
Per se
Also they
And the organizers were seemed alright with
That once he wasn't coming
The issue came down to something else and that is
Ted Nugent
Got threatened
By Andrew Cuomo
Governor
And his
In New York
Play the national anthem
New York area
Cancel 14 days
The nypd's
I'm pretty sure that Andrew Cuomo didn't personally threatened Ted
Is this Long Island press they say County Executive
Your reason for his abs
Had Isaac because he was reminded of New York state counties protest Pro
4 calls
New York from over 30
States with significant Community coronavirus spread a required to quarantine for 14 days for Governor Cuomo's executive order
Are specific to Hammett
Is a convenient way for everyone involved to save face
Texas which is an at-risk covers their base
The city council and problem
The rally organisers look real bad if they attended the rally
Dad probably would have liked
To go but this is just as good
Personally
Everybody gets what they need of the situation
When there is a big issue that needs
To be addressed here
Ted Nugent has no place in adult Society
If you wants to live out his days being a racist creep shooting arrows available privately
I can't stop him from that
Worth having in the public sphere
His music career is embarrassing compared to his contemporaries
It is exist
Political figure is basically just in Gallagher Dobama needs to suck his rifle
A loser Infowars guest
If some of that is booking him
It's not because he's a draw or because he's good at guitar
It's a political statement
They're supporting his brand of racist
Extremist politics anytime
Protest
You shouldn't be welcome as a public figure
.
You should be treated as such like anytime someone has him on
It's not because
Wango Tango Rock
He's doing a concert
Or something
Maybe that's not a political statement for like
Peter to book him
On his tour or whatever
You know whatever it is what it is
National anthem
That's that's
I think I completely disagree
And they were a racist
Piece of s***
Predator
Club
You're making a political
Statement which is better
Be a racist
You maybe one of you maybe right now
The music business
How that works maybe it is more of a
He should just be you
Should remind him of a handgun
You're whining loser who doesn't believe in your own bulshit
Shut the fuk up
Stop and go away
Stop it
The real victim course
When I got out my bow and arrow on my fishing rod and I spent a wonderful couple days
My dogs are my
Mnuchin at all I mean
Possibly do to me
I'll tell you what
All of the New York Police Department Heroes
Bender family
Open the left wants to
Take them over
Lisa Morrell
Praise I'm looking for his delusions
The Grandeur I think that's the one I'm looking for
I think it's
Partially there and I think it's partially also just like this is a way I can accept about this
What I need to get
I didn't get a check
People didn't get to enjoy
My sweet lips you know who's the real victim here at the end
The day once again
What is he doing
From 1995 I mean
F*** them
I can't find any articles that are like Ted Nugent profusely apologizes
It's not a cut-and-dry issue
Didn't have a personal
Evolution on the subject
Very much
Not good
Expressing his belief that
Different groups are all really just
The same thing
MS-13
Sunday
These groups of the Sun
Cool
Very dumb very stupid child
Seriously no
Capacity
So are you
Earth Defense Force
That be great
Hunt the vote hunt the vote
Which sound
F****** scary
And now here we are sounds like he's going to go to Inner City Precinct
Centers with a bow
It sounds like when you say hunt Motel
It doesn't sound like the same as rock
Calmly
Individual voters
Get them in his sight
And then
Convince them to vote for
Well I mean
He's very good that I find is like
You know
The object of hunt
What is the thing that is killed
But you're making it better
Rocking the videos
I'm going to
The most dangerous
I think it's
Hawkins be working how's it going
A trap
Obviously a data-gathering operation
People to put in their personal information as
I meant pledge to vote contact
10%
Or something when I checked tonight
Looking for
These people need
Stop
Referring to history
Not good
Pictures lie simple
Or just register
Alamo
We need to shoot Santa Anna's man
Laundromat
You think you're so hot
You lost
The Alamo
Haunted by the Mexican Army
I don't know
You got to stop being like this is the Alamo because you're just saying we're going to lose
He's doing losses do we should have been there in the first place
Poorly managed this situation
Absolute idiot Colonel Travis is a drunk
Really Step Up
This is a good metaphor for us
Oh boy
Yeah I feel like I could do better
It's more apps
Then you would expect
Talking about
The save the world
Some things that are happening
Around the country
I just felt like
With all my
He's talking about
Detroit yeah
Together
City of color
Read Walk of Life
Do you have black friends
Went berserk
Their own City this beautiful architecture so I have a good perspective
Junior
Detroit
Terrier
Suicide
Today
Evil
Is absurd
You have
Very committed to not recognizing what came before those
Not interested in discussing
67n randomly for no reason at all
Detroit
What happened in the lead-up to the LA riots
Now what
Is the larger conversation that these flashpoints exist with it
Or are you just
Wanting to look at this from an optic
Perspective
Honestly know what are you
What are you saying is like
Every now and again black people act
Crazy and I don't know why that is a presentation
The wow
Woo
So
If you had any principles and believe that anything that
He
You should be pressing down Alex about
Earlier in the show about a guy
Somehow making it like oh well. You get shot
Yeah
But it turns out
Ted Nugent
Also
Seems I have a weapon
You're no longer a protest
They called them
Building
Cocktails
Retired cops
Well I mean
St.Louis
We have a conversation about how that wasn't murder and I wasn't necessarily protesters
Is larger
He says there are few have weapons you're not a peaceful protest
Bad news but every second amendment protest
That is heifer happen for us to kill them because they are
Around with gun
That it's fine if we did
No I mean he's articulating a point very poorly because he doesn't recognize what the implication
Gonzaga statements are
You didn't recognize that condemning these protestors were having a weapon
Opens up the criticism
To everything that he supports
Yeah no you just doesn't recognize it cuz it doesn't matter to him doesn't give it a principle
It is a weapon
He can use against
It's the people he doesn't
What is all like
He doesn't care about the Second Amendment
Disgusting
That is
God
If we lived in a reasonable world every time he went on a show they were just
Play that clip and be like so you don't believe in the 2nd Amendment at all
He be like
And then the Chickamauga
That's it
If you if you're even nothing
Your threshold for like what is or is not a piece
Peaceful protest
We could take the damaging property stuff and
Discuss whether or not that violent
Conversation with Ted Nugent the conversation
Damage to property
Inherently violent
Be that as it may leaving that aside
His threshold seems to be that if you have a weapon you're not a piece
Protester
And
I would I would
Challenge him on that
And again
Is a nice days
God dammit
An amendment or is he going to go along like a coward with Alex Jones and
Noted
Predator racist monster
Noted Predator races monster Alex Jones
We will see
If you get the
Guts
Coward
Aleve
Interested
I don't know
Steam whenever one of these like
Seemingly
Pillars
Keystone
Seem to fall
Yeah it's it's totally I feel like
Apparent like I'm not mad at
You disappoint
I sailed on a level that I can
Cannot even
You had no reason
You could have just not talked about
You cannot talk about it or you can talk about it in a more robust way
It's where you can protect your gun position
The same time
Protest
If you so need to write
You don't
Tacoma if you're Alex
From the position of
This guy had a gun that justifies him being shot
You don't need to it is your principal is
Absolutist
Seems dumb
Yeah seems like
It denotes to me
Solidarity
No
Yeah that's
These arguments
Steady has
Are all
Just branches with no trunk Gap
Is a bummer
In a certain sense
I kind of so my my armchair bulshit on this
Is part of me
That
Because they lived through Obama
And they're so race
And they weren't allowed to
Did you say we hate him because he's
And we don't like
They made every argument in bad faith
Every argument they made was in bad faith
You know
They don't have anything that they believed in because what they believed in during Obama's years was just
We don't like him cuz he's black
Not allowing us to stay
So we have to make up some b******* about
Grabagun
That's a bad faith are
So now when we're in this situation
I don't even know if he probably doesn't believe that if you were
Maybe he does maybe he doesn't but if you were to sit him down and just really get to the
In private
It's like
You know you're making a bad faith argument
To these
In order to justify the violence
What you want you know
Yeah I can see where you're coming from but I disagree
Maybe people got accustomed
To this kind of behavior
What the stuff you were talking about
Predate Obama
It's not like they have some kind of
Did interest in
Racism behind gun-grabbing
The ideas
Clinton
Azure
Storm documentaries
Existed
Right
If you want if you want to like
Dig
Incredibly deep
Into
The fertile soil of
Then
Anti-communist
Sure
DD
Terrifying Crossroads of anti-communism
Anti
Culturalism
Corporate interest
Did the did intersect I think you could probably make
Incase
That a lot of these arguments
Older time
Do you have a racist
Element to 100% to make up for
Arguments about Obama
I don't think that works
More like they just don't even know how to have
An honest
Discussion
Like they genuinely just
Can't do it everything is filter
Through this prism of
You know possibly
Did there's also a possibility
That
They don't see a point
And having
You're probably 100
There is a utility and
Clearly
It works
Yeah
To bulshit
Like
No on a fundamental level
Somewhere closer
The truth and I can imagine
I'm saying
There are other options
No totally
Bi-Rite
An entirely
Like Mike
It's a red herring
Conversation about
Anything real
Possible
Also
Well
I don't know what the
Makes it also really difficult public-facing
Pieces of information to go from
Good job
Or new
It is expedient
Easier for him to do a bad job
That's fair I know that Alex is stupid
But I know that he's also not as stupid as
Like
He's even
He's not as stupid as like
The caricature that you could have him based on how stupid you are
Took away my will to live
The rest of the show
Excited because Joe Rogan
Has fully announced
Unfortunately
It's also has to recognize that like
Rogan has come out and said that
Stuff that I said about
It wasn't
True Texas
I did make up some
Really
My job
Spotify
Elaborated on
Elaborate
Probably
I'm not going to pontificate
Probably smart
He said probably
Hyperbole
I probably made up some stuff
Joe Rogan
People who are
Completely nuts
And I really want
Play up my connect
Basically my best friend
When people talk
One really hard for me to relay information from other
Relation to you because it's all made up in my head
So Alex is selling a new product
It isn't actually new product
What time does the new product to clear out the warehouse
Shepherd
Only one solution
These
Almost
Sometimes write-up
Next to a cell tower
It'll still penetrate through dilip in your cell phone
Locations for your dad
Bill Clinton
What
Hillary Clinton under Global initiative with the NIH and the
You nwhl running Canta
An early as next year
They're already got your data or not
Doing it together
4 months ago
Your pocket
Faraday cage
Have units out there
That are similar to this one
$35 online
Foster's almost $12 a piece
Whoa
Comes into finder operation
They're so evil the cell phone
New product for Alex
He had this was like a junior varsity product you'd have like Owens
The block it pocket
That he had
Dignify it with
Cushing on his show
Unless it was like a really heavy 5G. Like you know
Or like my I don't know but I would imagine that like when Snowden went on Rogan
Maybe I'll try cell block
It's not here this and I'm like
Wow you're really
Okay
Alex wouldn't even waste his time trying to sell it to the Past
You don't even been selling it record your voice 17
The kids loved brother cell phones
You got a pronoun relegated to nobody listening gets to sell it that bad
Alex's
Southwick
Whatever
One thing I think is really interesting is that Alex
Really wants to insinuate himself with
The story about Sinclair and Eric Bolling
To know that like
Hey maybe I'm the source on this story
Fox News
Thousand station
We'll postpone Android
Bowling show
Go
NIH live funding
Function research
When Coronavirus
Lucky back controversial Wuhan lab
U.s. dollars for risky
Newsweek
Newsweek look right there that's Newsweek
Coronavirus
Debate
This is the reality
That might have been editorializing there but you see is covers news
Warped version of the headline that Alex's editorializing
Everyday
Really f***** up topics
I am screens about murder a lot
No that was Brian Stiles
For a while there, he was the one who with the same people
Look
I know it happens all the
Whenever he screams it like
That's Newsweek
As a way of life
Jeremiah
Yeah I know like
Everybody's
D
Even Newsweek is saying
Is him saying
That's a reliable news source
Highlight how unreliable
Exactly 100%
Video of the show
Now if they print anything I don't like fake news
Control
Obviously they're still more trustworthy
Undoubtedly
Talking about how
The dance we're going to go up
Wow
I think he's trying to get ahead of this
Might be
Something that he's going to have to spend
Yeah this is a weak effort
After going way down
Because July is when the new doctors and nurses come in
Weather
July effect
Statistics real information
Real research
The Joy effect of the real thing people discuss there isn't a consensus on whether or not
Actually a real thing
Do you hear from a 2017 article
The Canadian Association of Medicine
Journal
2016 analysis
Journal of patient safety data collected between 2011 and twenty
Nearly 120 academic medical centers in more than 300
Regions
In the United States
It concluded that there was
No evidence to support the July effect on Survival outcomes at USF
Medical Center
Studies focused on specific Specialties and patient populations have indicated mixed Brazil
Despite this lack of strong supporting evidence
A national survey
Published in 2016
In the American Journal of Medicine review
That most Internal Medicine Residency program leaders believe
A 2013 article in the Harvard Medical School review says quote
A new study published October 23rd in circulation
By researchers at Harvard Medical School Stanford University Hospital
University of Southern California and the Rand Corporation
Cases it is a serious concern for high-risk
That isn't too surprising
Given that experience doctors have more experience
But also the discrepancy isn't something that you
Should make people avoid
He's getting Healthcare in July
This is an issue that only relates
Teaching hospitals where there are
That's one factor
Hospitals have a lower risk of dying
But in July
The risk
Good teaching hospitals
Okay about normal
Killing people at hospitals every summer
President
Is walking in
Acting all wacky
You know like forgetting all kinds of stuff in this earth
Who's this
Expect that for
People who are
In Greeley
Serious condition
That maybe are more difficult to diagnose so difficult
What's a handle
Someone who is not as a
Experienced
Could even with supervision
Could be less capable of taking care of that so you could imagine
Possible
Remember the things that I was reading
The issue seems to be
Where is there can be
A problem
It's administrative
It's not if it's not a factor of
Whether or not residence
Can
Handle medical situation
It's more of circumstances like is this Hospital
Supervising people approach
Start a magical
Cool thing where there's
Bike tons more deaths in July
I was just trying to find a way to
To preemptively explain away why
We might see some
It's not because as we see cases rise
And we know that it
It's kind of
It's you kind of
Cases rise
A short. Of time we will
Start to rise
This will be Alex
How to spell July
Which is going to be interesting come August
Alex's return to Studio was worse
Then Saturday
I long for this Saturday
And uninspired
I do
I don't know why isn't racist
Without me
Killers that is
Kind of
Arguably absolutism in the same way
I definitely agree with people's right to protect themselves and be armed
There is
Valuable
Defending the Second Amendment
What extent
That's where the debate
SharkBite
I think it's one of the beliefs that Alex
Has the two Central to himself
That you could look at it as a political beliefs
But you can have a conversation about
Is white identity
And both of those things
Things I think
When the
Crumbling comes of the
The Second Amendment
You just got
Yeah yeah
You almost
Stretched bottom you got to do is get rid of wetness in lies
And then you're really up
Interesting one hand
Absolutely
Friday will be
It's knowledge right.com Twitter
Review you could please find a bail fund especially in your area and
People doing the Lord
But until then
Western Civilization
Nicknames
And no there is not
Play said I don't know if I support them
Alex
Kristen color