Air Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
MoneyGram
Nick.com
Everybody
Fix it around a little bit about
Alex Jones
Jordan
Interesting
Little videos
YouTube that I think is really great and I've enjoyed quite a bit
There's this Timber on toast
I am bah
First heard of them or a person
Through the majority report
Play more talking about how
Is channel had a great breakdown of Dave Rubin
Trends on his channel
I think it's called Battle of ideas check out
All that's going on
Are out now but I'm not sure how many total there
No history.
Veritas
It's just really well done
Quality
Videos keep your attention
Well done
It's a subject that I don't have the patience to read
Well done well done through
Shoutouts
Okay
First three of these
I hope
I was going to say 50 hearts in this series
Put out content
Tonight
When is back playing NBA
You are
You're really excited about sports
Continue at everybody
I feel like I
I have to be very cautious about celebrating your bright spot of basketball team back
Turn out
Marlins baseball
Either cancel the season or just contracted the Marlins and just like
Wow you guys are in a franchise
So I'm fine with that
Jeter on who is the CEO and he's got part ownership and let me tell you something Dan if you want
Somebody to get rid of it
Jordans
July 28th through 30th
So here was the plan
I was aware that this Frontline special on PBS
I initially had planned that are episode 4
Discussion event Frontline episode
And then I'll look at Alex on the day before
Easy and all right
Bucked up
Of that PBS Frontline special
Is interesting and I bought to say about it
That's it
Today we're guarding us on the 30th
Thursday
Trump tweeted in the morning
Something to the effect
Maybe we should postpone the election
And
Obviously I can't wait for Monday
We had we got it
Episode onto the pile
Alex is at with the president
Maybe we should just go put it on
Beastly we just do it again is fine with that
The authority to do that
Or America
Your position I'm more concerned about the
Side effects
That conversation
Fat people who follow him
The expectations surrounding
The upcoming election
Yes very much though
And we'll get to that episode when we talk about the 30th but for now
Mg42 let's
Suspended until some nebulous time in the future
Thank you
Alexandria
Patrick
Starbright
Are you Patrick
Another
Daniel
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks very much Rebecca
Colleen W thank you so much
Business
Money off that heroin
Is freakishly large
Thanks so much as a kid
Outdoor website
Beautiful
That generosity
Cast
I passed out
No
Oak Barrel
Just a wrap
Everyone
Realizing I don't know how to age whiskey
What is trying to do
Generosity
Prepared area
I thought what I would do first
Episode he's disgusting actual Frontline
Pbs.org
I thought it was pretty well done
Pretty much
You know for people who don't know a lot about Alex
The pretty good primer about what you might call his greatest hits
There were very accurate point about his coverage of things like 9/11
Dual-fuel couple of glaring problems with the documentary that I think they're mentioned
One of them
Is no real conversation
About Boston bomber
And I know that maybe that's one of the pieces of his history that
I'm bored
Intimately familiar with
Looking at it
Irrelevant pieces of
Of his propaganda at the end
Chapter in his life
Maybe what you going to do
I think there was an overly simplistic telling
Alex is transition to supporting Trump
They kind of made it appear that Rodger Stone just showed up and then Alex supported
Real
Flashing out of a lot of the past that there was no
Not use those clips
You
I feel like that could
The Trump is Mob Japanese a front man for Consortium on the East Coast
The image
Just be presented
What's up conversation with Steve
Pieczenik at all like
A lot of these things
Sandy Hook
Trump intersects with Steve
Maybe that would have been too much to unpack
Possible
Weeds with a lot of
If you look at it
The simplified version of 3
I think they did a pretty good job so
I would have maybe
It stuck out to me
Was there's one instance of misrepresentation that this documentary made
In the passage about Alex's Sandy Hook
Conspiracies they should be roll
Infowars picture of Adam Lanza
Playing over it was Alex
And the doctor's he was under a was an Air Force mind control doctor using
Interface program
And told people he was under mind control in the
The jail
The audio it is that's being used is Alex talking about James Holmes the Aurora movie theater shooting
It is very true that Alex
Constantly
The cast doubt on the reality
But at no point in the Frontline piece did they make clear that the audio is not
Specifically about Adam
And video
A reasonable assumption for the viewer to think
It's audio they're playing is Adam
Accurate
There's no reason for them to introduce
This kind of confusion
They could have referenced James Holmes and said that was with who Alex was talking about a different piece of audiovalve
It's actually talked about presented his kind of sloppy
I don't think it's a major misrepresentation or any
Pensive decept
But I do think it's the sort of thing that a propagandist like Alex could latch onto to invalidate the peace
If they make it look like I said
Did they misrepresent
That kind of thing.
Although I will say I think
You saying that is
The first time he will figure that
Retard to avoid playing into if I was making this documentary
The tricks that are very easy to be playing defense as your creator
Every moment and every T's crossed so this is f*****
Complaints about this documentary is interview subject
Selection
This thing is almost entirely attackable and discardable based on Mattawa
There are three categories of interviewees
Simmons documentary
The first is insightful subject
That's exactly who should be in the documentary talk
This category of the Austin American
Statesman and naked
Of the Texas month
Beautiful to a local awareness of Alex outside of his existence as a national public figure
Able to provide some earlier context in his career
Also in this group is
Of course makes sense that somebody would make me happy
He's like this
It is perspective
Father of a child killed at Sandy Hook
Is also an important voice
It's good to have him there to really make explicit and related to Alex's Behavior
Additionally Anna Berlin the author of republic
As was Morgan get me Rodger Stone
Same can be said for Nancy Rosenblum Elizabeth Williamson
Either people have an external perspective on the issues that are
The problem with Alex and they're able to offer insight
Subject matter of the documentary
Nancy Rosenblum
She has Judge
She listens to
Are you sure
GM's the documentary with a question of whether or not we'll be able to
Return to a reasonable place of sanity
And that question
Depends on whether or not the people who end up in positions of
The power can resist the urge to use
Conspiracy
Yeah and I thought that was a really good
Perspective for what
This documentary was right
Because it really does put the folks
Play some The onus on like these things do work
Plan they work
Right and it's the responsibility and Leadership
To not weaponize them for their own personal opinion
Because it is a short
I thought that was really
Documentary really well and II
I thought that was a really nice thought
The second category of people
Are people who you absolutely should not
This group includes no get the f*** out of here
Call Michael
.
Barnes and Rodger kind of understandable
The opportunity to give their side of the story
She's basically just there to make it clear that she's not as bad as Infowars which only
Serves to launder her it doesn't need to be engaged
Goddamnit PBS
Now the third category is people who I understand documentary
But we're probably miss Han
These are people who create
Targets for the documentary
The unearned suspicions about The credibility of the report
This group includes Alex's ex-wife Kelly
No understand talking to her and all those solid details
About Infowars early day since she was deeply involved in the company
I don't think that you should never talk
Her anything like that but her being in this documentary at this point
Open store to Alex
You got a text
The same as you existed before merging forward
Employees that they speak to
Swimsuit complaints couple years ago
Infowars
You know
Continue to work there for 4 years after Sandy Hook
Years as an Infowars employee
Really completely fine
He's a source that is impeachable from my perspective and from Alex's
His contribution to the
Kind of point
This also extends to Josh Owen
Used to work at
Infowars
New York
I respect both of these dudes and their right to change their position and make amends for their active participation
And profiting from conspiracy
I'm not positive they're doing it in this form is helpful and I think it complicates the p
I think it I think it makes it the more difficult
So is a vowel sound watching this
I am getting from them
You know like I'm getting
A former Infowars people being like
Man evil s*** all the time but I was a good person that sometime I tried to tell a lie
Infowars.com
I mean you could just like yours
Alex didn't mind getting on are insane
Lies about people
Is as demonstrated by the video of him doing it as if I
This person saying that I don't
Here
About their perspective
I don't know if
Yeah baby yeah
Maybe I'm a little bit harsh on that front.
Lumberjack in the Pacific
And one of the other category is building
Of Alex in the Sandy Hook
Is one of the other people who is interview
Adhere
I don't believe that anymore.
He's interviewed a situation where
I think that the
PBS
People
No it's that is
Really though
You didn't say anything like that I think is horrible or anything
You know how easy this is going to be for people like our
Who is deposing him
You're speaking as an expert
He's literally part of the globalist establishment that we're all fighting against
Using his s*** that you are all part of the globalist
Butter data data data
Yeah I'm positive how much that is
Consider like
Dim
I think that Barnes and like
Absolutely don't put them in here
I think that these other people like the ex-employees like Kelly like this this lawyer
Like I think
I understand why this
Peace isn't it
Like what I would make
Sure
So I would say that it's a
Is it in Italy decision
These people were presented in Waze
That Baker
Their inclusion
Valuable
Would have
Perspective to give
I don't know
Let Me Pitch you a new jacket
1 in
6 static shot
We don't even worry about any graphics or anyting black
Background just a regular old
Stage
Larry klayman interviewing Rodger Stone
Traveling show I want them to do a 20-city tour
In terms of these for like general population consumption
The decisions that they made into except for Barnes and
Ann Coulter
Can I watch them for these interview choices
I just wouldn't include them as I was making this because there lightning rods
Very valid
Points brought up by people like Anna Merlin and Nancy rosenblum's
Can behave like superheaven
The former employees who have Grudge
Chinese ex-wife was actively involved in court cases against him
And a lawyer
If I were making this documentary I would have created it a lot differently
If I were making it
It wouldn't be as good
The goal of the documentary is to inform the public about how conspiracy theories found their way into the mainstream through the lens of a
Alex's
The point is accurate but some of the nuances incorrect
But there's no way to discuss the Nuance in just an hour
The version I would make would be in
Possibility
Probably wouldn't be digestible by y.
I would say probably 3 episodes
3 hours
Completely inaccessible
CVS
.
I do appreciate that some people
Call David Jordan
You know for not calling us 100%
I don't really think that we have
That much
To bring
My only argument is if you have Barnes on you have to have me on his account
That's what you have to do
Barnes is a moron who doesn't know s*** and he's a grifter and I'm a moron he doesn't know s*** and I hate Barnes
Speaking of which it is now eleven days
Respond to your challenge
I'll get covid if you get covid and we'll do this s***
To anybody
All the way
What's the let's do that
So I thought this is a
I'll be perfectly honest
I thought the PBS documentary was much better than I expect
A lot of the times these things
Are pretty poorly
Or like kind of like sloppily.
Outside of that one
Instance where they were talking about James Holmes over
Pictures of Adam Lanza
Anything goes like
This is explicitly
That's solid
I found it to be quite that good for what it set out to be
I thought it was really
Interesting having watched
To see this
Couple days and Alex
2018 evening
What's up yeah what's he think is going on maybe there's going to be some kind of felt like preemptive
Bring it up at all with all the anxiety from
He's like
All of that worry I put into whether or not
Put out me whenever I J
Fluid strong of n-word
Together
Nothing can hurt me now on the 29th
How does he feel about
We'll see
28 here we start Alex woke up
Realer
Because Barn
Tweeted something
I woke up at 5 a.m. this morning
Text message
Good work on
BBC article
This is the Line in the Sand
So many people in Salina stand for me
And so I'm going to do my best job
Here today
Calmly and proficiently latest
Despite the fact that I have been up since 5 a.m.
Researching preparing for this
Butterflies
And
Because
So much data so much proof
All totally confirmed myself to use everybody else
Every single day he does this now
In 10 minutes of look I would love to cover things
Every single time I turn on the show now
I can barely do this
I'm not teasing
I'm not trying to build suspense but
Such big news that I can't get to it
It's just
Over and over and over again
It's become his like
Rhetorical trick that
Just Universal subtext all I have is
At Wheaton 3 headlights and I hope
The colors don't suck today
Tired
Yeah
So you got to email everybody at I don't know.
Traffic but you do need
Email
Everyone you know
You
I assume people have an Alex phone tree
Scientific
Medical
Dictatorship
That is designed to depopulate the
Infowars.com newswars.com
Video Alex Jones
Click on the left hand corner
Send that out that's not a censored as much
On the Internet it's easier to get out there
Tuesday alive Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation microchip
One on
World for sanay elections
Tracers
Call Michael the Beast
Dunked on
Were there
I mean we're there again
My narrative 5 years ago
Here is where my mind almost broke while I was listening
To this I just like it's early in the show that's not good
Read to you from the BBC
Rollout at MIT
USA Today
Just checking the authors all of them
I've written for the UN MIT and Bill Gates
Exclusively
On devices in your home and spy on you
Smart toilet
Streetlights that watch and listen to you
Such a great example about how
Frustrating
Try and listen to Alex
Because nothing he says means anything on Smart toilet
Every step of what you just said there is almost impossible
To discuss
As it's being present
He asserts that there's a rollout of articles about Gates
This alone is unsubstantiated
Like what constitutes a roll
How is Alex establishing if there is a roll out of
Stories
Just based on a number of different Outlets the same press release
Or something like that
You know whenever you check the news
And you have like Washington Post and USA Today the New York Times and all of those
Did you notice that they only cover their news like they never cover the same story
Stand it
Proprietary information
It is there could be an instance where a bunch of different Outlets
Recovering the same
Reuters article on a PC
And then you have a bunch of different Outlets covering that because it's an interesting story and okay
It's like this
First Step that he has
You can't defend that there's a roll out cuz it doesn't mean any
What does it mean
That means there's a role that okay
People who wrote These articles about these Gates tattoos
For the US and
The right
Exclusively about household spying devices like toilets
This is kind of amazing because it's impressively
Which authors is he talking about
You haven't even specified in article
So this could be referring to anyone
Why would you possibly go about checking into the hour-and-a-half
There's no specific
I could just
I can't do it
Then go to USA Today
I did
Check every single author that has written for them
10 years
If you try to fact-check this claim you'll immediately run into the wall
That you have no Lawn Shop
You could maybe you don't find an article in USA Today that's about the right topic but how do you know it's the right one out
Alex's vaguely referring to
Why you being so vague Alex's essentially said he completely unfalsifiable lie
Because I could find a USA Today article about these like a tattoos my tattoo
And I can say like oh here's the author of it and it doesn't match anything
So I found an article about this very idea of XE tattoos and Scientific American
Which was written by Karen Weintraub
Very simple searched over by line shows that she doesn't write
Exclusively about appliances that are spying on you
Like the article
Are human body temperature
Like I said this means nothing
In terms of Alex's claim
He can easily just say this wasn't one of the Articles it's part of his alleged rollout research from that morning
We're right back to where we started
This is one of the ways that I was weaponizes Vegas
And refusal to provide specific details in order to create the perception that the things he's making up or based on something real
They're not
He's just talkingshit
What are you doing sneaking away
So makes no bulshit things he's
Almost impossible to the bus
I mean I did check several thousand other articles this morning and they all proved that he was correct
So I mean
So
Kind of suspicious evicted week
Can pull back from the
You know tweet that allegedly Alex got from Barnes that morning
Supposed to
This ship
Picture of alleged research
So that article was written by a woman named Lena zeldovich
Who absolutely doesn't write
Exclusively about spying appliances in toilet
Within the last month she's written articles on topics ranging from potential lung damage that could come from Saharan dust cloud
Devices spying on you other articles like why high-end hotels are uniquely positioned to rebound
From the Coronavirus
Nothing Alex says means anything
He's just making stuff up to create the feeling he's looking
Engendering is audien
In this case he wants
Listen to feel like there's a conspiracy of people in Media
So did you accomplish that he
Pretend
That he was up all morning researching author
And Heather now all pushing vaccine tattoos
It's a complete and pure fabrication
And I don't even believe Alex was up before 8
I just don't believe it
I buy it
5 I imagine he probably has some sort of apnea still that he's still got to deal with
Lately he's been saying
You can't
Fake having sleep apnea
You can fake having sleep apnea but that's unfair
It's mean I felt that I felt empathy for a second
C a b
Made me throw my computer cross the road because it's that that game that's being played.
Okay you want to make it so
I can't
Know what you're talkin about
And if I'm actively looking into the things you talk about
How much more abusive is that two people who passively listen
Don't even
Confirm thanks
I was up all morning
All these people just talk about spy toilet
All I need for corroboration is you saying you are up all morning
Like a lot of work
So Alex
Does this
I'm going to go to break and he comes back it was a goddamn baby in the studio
Sonny's
Take me to bigger than I am
But this guy is super handsome
Mess with anybody but
Calendar
Here is the Sun
Got this guy and I tell you
100-percent
Parsley and infomercial
Onesies available at infowarsstore.com Elsa
Infowars
Studio
Lookout
Like Blown Away by how surreal this
This this shift is
Pretty severe
Barnes texted me this thing you need to email everybody is it covid
Mediately after
You little baby right propaganda
Racism to new Justin Bieber
Matter is such a great slogan
Great thing that the world
Just great
This interview doesn't go well because the baby and the baby's father
Very uncomfortable
I know it's close to his bedtime but he is a sweetheart
He's such a good boy
Nope didn't completely healthy never been sick
It is you can really tell in their eyes we know when it is they just kind of look like something's missing
Most girls
Yeah I just know
Not happen over here
Just a little boy
Like I can tell you the boys
Well you commit the crime
Wow
Social worker
The right is really good comedy
Phyno
Crayola babies like this
I don't want
Children
Oh yeah
This is just a disaster ever
You bring this baby out
It's it's totally very weird
The transphobia completely unnecessary
I mean because he doesn't have much else to do with this baby isn't really a good scene partner
No we could use some Second City Improv
No Doubt
I find the Democrat babies
Every time that I've gotten into a Herald Democrat baby
Babe can sing
Do you know it's crazy though and here's what I ears or bothers me about baby
Are those b******* liberals they don't do anything Dan they're just like
Let's wait and see and let's hope somebody else
They're not leftist
Out in the street
Dan I don't want to I don't want to play this game
So Alex realizes
Maybe the best place for him and so he calls in Darren McMurray who's the baby's Grandpa
Has him take over the Segway
How God his grandfather
Yes he is
Oh my goodness
You want to say hi to Grandpa
You know that is what you want
Golden Grandpa
Where is Grandpa
Darren is not a butterfly
Hungry
That's my special boy
Extreme things
Turn off my grass.
It's
I really
Mostly playlist it's very weird but I mostly play this cuz like
You're going to happen throughout the rest of this episode
Please remember
Outside baby
Sacrament of the 28th
Capriciousness of just like
Get over here and you're going to host the segment for a while
Doesn't like being on it
He was referring pologize for believing people when they say
He was making a joke
About how the baby had butterflies
To be on air
That was a reference to a group
Basically an on-air host
You would be doing
Adidas
He is more like
I'm between person guys
Definitely do special reports
Very much
So now we get back tattoo
Narrative
Is weird
Text
Can pull that up
Microsoft.com in quote digital tattoos
So you can have
Prove you've had enough vaccine medical record all that
My point is I'm going to show you something Cardinals right now
This is all being announced
But remember
Just
A few months ago there is Microsoft
Smart tattoos
So
We come out and we expose what they're doing what they're up to
In January February March and April lay out exactly what they were going to do
Operation lockstep Rockefeller
10 years old
Exactly
Nope so specific cross reference
See if I can figure out what's going on
Start with the Microsoft
Alex just pulled up a page for smart tattoos on Microsoft research project website
It's nothing secret or nefarious it's actually interesting technology
We've been able to create topical temporary tattoos
Control that you can hook up to like you
Your phone through Bluetooth
Simple imagine what this technology looks like is to imagine
Things on your arm
When you touch the first one you can have it connected via Bluetooth to the lights in your living room so touching your arm could talk
The second button Scooby Channel up and down button
Install remote control your television
Like button remote
Control there's a number of other like application that you can imagine
Video game
Temporary
Yeah I'm sure it's actually
The project it at Microsoft is literally nothing like what Alex's rambling about his dystopian fever dream
Something
Even recent
There's an article on Microsoft like the page that Alex
Pulls up from
August 2018
And I was able to easily find an article on quartz about this from
August 26th
I'm sure now it would still consider this technology to work of the devil all the same but
Doing today
Also none of the authors involved in those articles about
This technology exclusively right about spying toilet
Quick question
He is referring of course to his coverage
In February and March whenever he laid out the
The plan and let us all
Is he still on the it's over for Humanity
You know what yes he is
Yes he is right so the plan at that time we are all going to die
Well
Reed will get a sentence
At that point yes that was going to kill everyone
Alex
Has an interesting
Death toll videos going to bring up later in this episode
No
7 million
Higher
Don't have the BBC article
And it's a little
Closer to italics
Kind of talking about
The headline of the piece is quotes will travel be safer by 2022
This is an article by the aforementioned Lena's zeldovich
Who doesn't write
Exclusively about buying toilets
This is a discussion about emerging technologies that could help facilitate travel in the near future
An industry that's been hit particularly hard by covid-19
She discusses a breakthrough in breathalyzer type technology that's been created by
Versiti in Israel
Apparently his breathalyzer showing a 92% accuracy rate so it may be fairly close to being up for consideration
Is it means to be able to control the spread of the virus while still allowing ce4less
Restricted travel
One of the other Technologies that's
Disgust is the vaccine record tattoos that have been
Research by Folks at
MIT
Technology has received funding from Bill and Melinda Gates at research
Nothing in this article says you'll need of exit
Can you tattoo in order to travel in the future
This article honestly is just
Zeldovich is perspective on what
Could be coming in terms of
Futurist kind of baby
Even the article says quote
Travelers present bee costumes officers with an entrance visa and a vaccination record
That could be a paper card or a tiny tattoo on their arm invisible
Infrared scanner
Even in her vision of what travel could look like in 2022 people would still rather have a paper record
Vaccination history
Or if they wanted to they could get their tattoo of a vaccine Wrecker
I'm going to go with let's do the Sci-Fi dystopia scenario and get them right behind our Earline.
Sounds great even so isn't this still the same
They're still saying that you need a vaccine to travel
As it turns out this is already the case in a lot of countries
Countries including Australia Travelers
Areas affected by yellow fever vaccination
The condition has a requirement for entry
It's sort of Public Health protocol already exist
Honestly the way would most likely be implemented in the case of covid-19
It's probably the same as the yellow fever situation
Countries will be able to set their own standards for barring entry depending on their Public Health situation requires
You can easily see that being the case of covid-19
Did we develop
Successful vaccine in the near future
Things return to somewhat normal
This vaccine tattoo record has never been used on life
Subject
And the Ulta
Golden would be to provide records for people quotes in the developing world where paper and electronic records are not always
The article goes on to say that quote
The goal is to try it on
Measles vaccine soon
But the tech may come in handy for other proofs of immunization
For example at the
Pinpoint
The article discusses innovation
Sounds like good smelling sanitizer is it
UV light technology
That sounds great but also to make little cages
This article is absolutely not with Alex's reporting it as
He's saying that it's proof positive that the mark of the beast is here and they're rolling out their plans
Could just be
Just as I was about a nefarious
Plan to fund
Lavender scented eco-friendly sanitizer
I think the global issue
Shoot a lot lower
Onsen
He's talking about that timeline of the denial in the confirmation
Import
To me frustrated me and almost baby throw my
Computer
At the beginning of the episode
Every publication
To the LA Times to wired
Come out and say
There are no digital tattoos
None of this is true
Even though they were already proposing
Marshalls
Digital passport or a
You just said you weren't doing that
They have not announced on the Microsoft website of the shuttles leave yours
Foundation
Directly
So no one is saying and has been saying that the invisible tattoo vaccine records are completely made up
Ready
Yes the research wasn't complete
Entire narrative
Oh you denying
That a month later there's a
This clip was so useful to me though because at the end of their Alex confirms BBC article
Written by the purse
He was saying
Yeah right about spying
Appliances
If you Google Lena Zelda Zelda
Bill Gates pops up
That you wrote back
2017 called
Toilet
This article was about her traveling to Madagascar to explore a company that was developing waterless toilets
Which is a very important sort of technology for the developing world
Where sanitation is a major concern in Water Resources might not be available to
Expend
That's huge
Involvement of Bill Gates
Year was it in 2011 is foundation ran a challenge
It's called the
Toilet
Square they solicited ideas about how people could create sustainable sanitation in the developing world
It was a grant contest
And this person Virginia Gardner
Cheap designed became a startup called
Which is what this article is about
That's some good
Right there
Waste is collected to be converted into usable biogas
Supposedly odor-free
Which is huge
The rest of this article involves more information about the history of toilets
Almost certainly Google
Found this article and he decided to write a little story about it it has nothing
Things to do with reality
From this article about a woman and water Gates Foundation Grant
Waterless toilets
Alex has reported that Lena zeldovich rights
An almost exclusively about spying appliances like toilet
It's a complete fabrication that came out of his imagination
I never would have been able to
Figure this out
Go bad if he hadn't specified toilets
In his rambling
This is why he needs to be as big as possible
Because a nice tree detail has the possibility of unraveling the flimsy ship is narratives are built on
Also to be perfectly sure that I wasn't misrepresenting things
Microsoft
Smart tattoo page
That you showed on screen is the same one that I found
It has stuff from
It's not and it's not a related story at all
It's about remote control you can have
Touchscreen on your hand
That's fantastic research
Great detective work
I'm still a little bitter at Gates
For rejecting my
Sebastian which was
Everybody s**** on the grass and we carry bags
I think it works for dogs
Doesn't work for dogs
I don't know if this is a good solution
Anyway
Intersection cut this article about toilets
That's great that really good research
You did a great job
Accidental
I mean you just like I get you
Well anyway
Much like these toilets
Other than turned into BIOS
I love it starts article
BBC
Zeldovich
Looks like the citizen scientist revising and Technology
Contessa
Globe-trot again
And she says my 2020
You'll get off an airplane a robot will scan
Odd in your mouth that other diseases
It's no big deal
And if you just go through how to buy and sell and live your life
The global medical ID and they said they're going to have all seven and a half billion people
Don't worry they'll give you money to get chip
Don't worry it's just a patch you put on your arm
You might have a rash
You're going to have nanotech
In your body
It is a long article
You do read this
For yourself
This should go without saying but almost everything you saying article
It isn't no way inaccurate or say or characterization of what zeldovich wrote and it
It's also not a very long article 1574 words
And to give you some sense of how much of it is about this potential technology vexing tattoos
Makes up only 245 of the words in the article
The article is about uv-light technologies that could be used
Clean playing between twice
We bulshit to scare his audience like there's
There's nothing going on here this is just embarrassing
Just feel like The Mark of the Beast should have like
Diminishing returns
The mark of the beast is that toilet since I've been alive
Every year there's been a new mark of the beast coming
I'm done with it Alex's also about Doctor Who
Hydroxychloroquine
The video getting taken down
No point does he mention some of her extracurricular activities about
Demon sex
And whatever he has any objections
You just treated as another totally right being shut down by the man
I don't really have a lot of time for this narrative so too much other stuff
Kind of a trivial matter in Alex's coverage
We're just going to
But much more
Yes the price of gold
Given the circumstances in the physical
Triangle be interested in
And raise the price of gold to
The point where it's at
And
Alex
It turns out
Nobody's trying
Anderson back in the game
Are you using
The cupboard crisis of excuse to shut down the economy
Before it collapses on its own
Consolidate power
Dollars an ounce
People ask why don't you have a gold sponsor
I know why
Show me overcharge people
More than 5% over on Boolean
Volume 15%
Keep the lights on
Market like Alex usurious
I'm working with some years ago
We are looking by next week to have a gold sponsor of everybody's everybody's to beat
Yorktown
So I'll keep you posted
Johnson
Kick down the wall like that like and just show up.
I mean I guess in suspension is probably over
But you wasn't barred for life from precious metal sales
Can go read those
Those Court filing
Yeah I mean honestly he could restart because he doesn't really need to have that much
Gold on hand the whole idea is that it's imaginary he was
Made to pay
Hundreds of thousands of dollars in restitution to customers that he
Defraud
So
Jim Baker bounce back
Imprisoned
I'll be very interested to see how this works
Dbd game
Gold Leaf commercial for CBDs
Everybody got
Genesis communication that gives out loans
Wonder Valex got one
Anyways
I'm looking forward to seeing if gold sales
Girls come back
Alex's
Chaves
To come back like I don't think Peter Schiff Show
I think a lot of the people who are the
Real gold salespeople Ron Paul libertarian
And I don't think a lot of them made the jump
To Trump
Writerly
Problem
But
Alex's
He's very funny
Some to wear a mask in public
Because he has a good new B
This just came in
Successfully
The Chinaman
Superman
Look at me
Oh yeah you're bad
Probably
A dog a b****
You know
No a sheep
Time shutdown
Miles and just walked away
Because they know their sheep
What's a fraud
So when you lasted Alex or saying he pulled realize how complicated it is
And how the conversation tree requires the other person
Yeah your comeback to make sense
You're right
Conscious participant
To do the feed is literally like he has to be like okay
Yes
What's up wow
Wear mask
You're looking at me
What are you doing staring at me
I think you should wear a mask
You don't be mean to animals I don't know I don't understand what does that mean
Alright well I will
Alex
Talks a little bit here about
The Eurostar
That are being used
To justify
Ambient background violence of the communist
Activated
The overthrow of local government
Surrounding of the White House and attempt to drive the Press
We supposed to be God
From family members they got high level and even
Charles property
Lawsuits against
When we got the documents
Just one front guy
Your system
Talk to John about thesaurus documents being absolute fake
Because he knows that if he told the truth his story sounds stupid
You did not get them from a family member exclusively
Is employee Harrison Smith found them on Fortune
I watch the episode where Harrison
Shows them to Alex
It was explicit
About the original Anonymous poster
Playing but he found them in his brothers possession
His story sucks and there's literally no way to prove their authenticity of this is how we
So he lies
He claims he got them through a much more legitimate sounding means
Because it also
Unless transparently fake
Also
The alleged organization in those documents had nothing to do with Alexander Soros
It was a political action committee that was run by Soros
But as we discussed the last time you contract
That's what collection committee didn't even exist at the time of those documents are supposed to be
Created
In 30 seconds Alex's lied about how he got these fake document
Getting them exclusively
Made up that they relate to Alexander Soros
They're all his legal trouble is actually just retribution because he exclusively cover these fake.
All of the lawsuit against Alex they aren't the result of his own monstrous actions it's serious damages he's caused another people
Journalist
Daring to take on Soros
I believe one of them
You can
See here how the details of the story seems to conveniently fit the version of the story that Alex's narcissistic Eagle require
Alex knows what the documents are fake story so there's no reason not to weaponize it against is Imagine
Can use it to Gaslight is audience the victim in lawsuits
These lies terrorized
So
Goodyear
Good
Yaga
Now these episode take a weird turn
Started with a baby got into spying toilets
Really
H and
Broadcast
Flow lyrics
He's a pirate
Vietnam
He's an author's one of the top
Homes and real survivalism you travel the entire world
Peopleready
Ctop survivalist expert for serious
Survivalism
Thank you for a long time but I
Pure offense mode trying to stop this
Tell you that I agree with his analysis Aetna long-term
We can just mitigated.
Try to make sure
Chile
I had a bunch going to be coming
In the
Fourth hour today I'll become a state
I've never been more certain of anything in my life
Newspaper
This is broker contact
Location
Bug out to try to sell this book
I'm positive it's so over-the-top like
Alex just feeding the ground
Looks like this would be a good place to go but you got to understand there's going to be spillover from the
Whatever here's what we do
All right all of us
Present-day agree
On the left
We are going to act like this is going down
It's the day
We're doing
The contract will be fulfilled
We're doing the whole thing it's over
For Humanity all they got to do all they can do all the right-wing conservatives all the right
All they can do is go to the hills and hide
And wait it out
And while they're there
We
Do everything right
Just leave them there
Little Hut
Go go in there in the forest
But
You have an interesting idea
I think it's a good idea to trick them all into the forest
That was in the book plans for this sort of countermeasure but
Alex like
Is making
Some money from this is it
Lili contradict
It's Alex
Things with Alex should know as fact
Well as you know and we talked
Before the show there is a satanic Connection in the entire deep state
Gordy's things are done by Revelation and guidance at
The highest level
Intermediate yes-man the stupid idiots that letting used to call them
Just one of those useful idiots to the
Conspiracy
I don't think so
He said he's a lightweight
Scales and is presenting
Useful
Said repeatedly
The gates is part of the Council of twelve Duplantis
Yeah I am
Furious
We have
Spending months
Engage being the architect behind this whole thing and then Alex
This is just a thousand
Considers Joel skousen
Totally different
Just one of those useful idiots to the
To this conspiracy
I don't think so he's a lightweight when you look at it mentally
Yeah this is not a heavier
But as big now
What about the Rothschild
So Alex agreed
Bulshit I just can't
No
No that is unacceptable
Unacceptable
I agree
Do you think about the Rothschild are we just going to storm Alex's other coverage
You should not only not agree with this
You should say
Actually Joel
I have information
He's one of the 12 people who rule the planet
There are twelve of them
Are you saying that there's a council of three above
The Council of twelve such a stupid
Joel skousen
Oh okay
I don't care about like the long passages of like you should of
But I don't care
I'm not I'm not particularly concerned with his geographical analysis of the United States
I want a lot of people think the Central and South America via great place to go but that's only because they
Don't plan the bug out based on current circumstances I think that's a smart idea
Joel
Plan for the future are you sure
Here's the thing
Joel skousen
Because I think
Like
She thinks
He's fighting a literal devil
You don't put a lot of people get concerned about who is at the actually really doesn't matter who's at the
That's right
That's the only reason that could be going for centuries I mean service. Back of the only reason
No single evil person could set this in motion and keep it in motion
Exactly
Yes
The only way we can explain a centuries-old
Centuries ago yeah behind it
You making all that up
Explain it actually accidentally very legitimate argument that he made
The only way that we can explain our b******* is if the literal devil is real and controlling it
If those two things are not true
Everything we believe is b*******
Earlier Alex
You know you like
Call people sheep who wear masks
I might have
Just saw when he came out and said where your Masters patriotic
Donald Trump
From the folks I saw
Sounds a lot like sheep because he is their Authority
Would you say
Come on man
I'm not going to go to bat for it that Batman
Like I said the rest of this episode is 2,000 telling you where not to go in there
Whatever
Plenty of
Any City
All of China
Should you go to all of nowhere near
Spell Japan going to take all of those
Playing the game
Recruitment is not safe
God dammit
Some normal Wilson
I have news from Federal
Unfolding in front of you don't need the intelligence
From higher level
I feel the same thing
Are we
With
Tpd sources
Shinso in
We're doing this
The every morning
Broadcast
What I'm going to say about this
You do that pre-show
This is going to be Paul Revere level stuff is this
Same over and over
It's almost turning into the rake infect I was kind of laughing
It's like
Funnier than is b b he does with masks
He doesn't actually wait
He does tells what the story is
But I can tell you what we already knew
But it's totally confirm now
Soros deep State Obama controlled Hillary control
Will be the decoys
Distraction
Systems
Real hit teams
The leadership
Pro human promerica movement
What are your personal academic
Finance
Your targeted for death
They may launch the attack
Week
The safety off the finger on the trigger
Squad
Tricom hit squad everybody
Everybody's everything
They're coming to kill you and your family
Be ready
Lock and Load ladies and gentlemen
Globulin
Get ready ladies and gentlemen
So it's confirmed MS-13 in Chinese government
Sponsored hit squad.
Cover from
Soros Hillary Obama funded
Antifa
Alright
I'm going to make this announcement
As the actual leader of all anti
We are doing
That's our plan tomorrow
Alex
All of the
Everyone
We're doing it tomorrow you got to get to your
Poker now go
Stay there for a year
Wonder who Alex consider a leader in the academic
Patriot community
Wonder who
Anyway
In terms of Alex's shorts
This is stupid it's obviously based on it is
Huge
Houses in Amarillo
Bucked up headspace
That it's like
He seems to be telling people to
Get ready to die
We're winning about the species
Individual
Your destruction will leave the tree of Liberty Tim power
We'll make that metaphysical connections
Falling from band of Zeus
Knocking on your back door
So great love you
Ladies and gentlemen we are broadcasting worldwide
Point of no return
There is a real feeling of that like
The people who paid
The price of the past
Destruction
You watch the Frontline now you're having to look at euphoric high off being attacked
Yeah
This really kind of like a
It made it pretty clear.
In the moron
And in the center of the
In the fulcrum
I know you are the fulcrum as well
That's why you're here
Why Your Word of Mouth
Is Kane
Your free will
Remember however you're watching her have your listening you
Amplify this transmission
And we will win
Will win one way or another but will win this round
What a much easier chance down the road to go through this AI challenging
More than
Now that sounds like a lot
Projector
The system
Asking earlier about the is it over for Humanity
We'll be lucky
I didn't want to step on Alex's estimate
What I was
The more I know I'm relevant
I'm so important
It has to be related to last night's
Look at all the attention
View it being channeled into this we're all going to die isn't it awesome Noble.
Common destroy the globalists
It's like Trump
Dakota briefings are getting great ratings
You know I love seeing all these millions of people are too and again to watch that's
That's great TV
And your leg
You're killing
You're a murder
How do you like
Does a little bit more dangerous about this
Making a little bit more explicit basically
The protest that you're seeing in in cities like Portland
Extract
You win stage riots long way to get there
By the break
I heard an interesting commercial
Now the UN do it it would stay dry at Sea would have armies of people wearing black cover your face
Akademiks
And then if you resisted all your bad
More rioting
With the Democrats to remove Trump and they're announcing that they're playing
Have we gotten them to come out of the open
Which concept On The Rise it's
Crucial that law-abiding citizens from criminals who are now becoming desperate
Learn exactly how with a newly updated hide your guns Emmanuel
Its newly updated
Bird extra 1.5 places to hide your
Be more places do not
Southern
I'm years ago with guns. Com
Sponsoring
Version of the book
Framing citizen protest
Un stage riots
Is really not good
Because
Alex has built up years and years of
Argument
About what you do
When you when troops
I said protest
Even though I look at
And I actually live there and I see the people and I know that person
It turns out they were hired by the UN
So I don't know if you realize that he's already
The story about MS-13 and Chinese hit teams coming to kill Patriot leaders
Does he continues trying to tease the story as if he hasn't already talked about
I have this from the APT I have the former State Police I have is from a governor's office
The people that are disgusted by the governor
Has been blackmailed
Totally turned on
Right now
This from
New York City
Cover at 6
It makes me physically sick to my stomach
To realize the situation
You already told the story you don't really have much else to add to it except for like maybe some
Fun details
Notes from New York
Plowshare in Chinese
Hit squads come on
Ruben Ramos
The only proof that he provides
It doesn't prove any
The things that he saying
A piece of paper where he is like
You type in a word doc basically
Austin Police sources told me they stopped the car with
I don't know
I don't care
Just escalated this and now it turns out what's going to happen
People right
Translate abs
Call Hayden
Indian teams
And they're going to
Blow up your house
The car bomb
You come out there going
Shoot you
I'm just going to tell you that right now
What's going on
They have teams of literal
Meth head drug addicts perverts child molesters
That's the lowest level
Black
Pissed off
People be white people but they can
Professors
Mmmm
Workers
Are planning
Judges houses
Governor's Mansions capitals
Media people
Police Seaside online
Going to come to your house
They got stolen trucks they're going to load them up with gas
And I just got up
Run your household
Come out they're going to shoot you
Capitals
Yeah so that's keep your item with a bet
Can you keep your eyes open for car bomb
Sands
Stage tooting
Operation against the party
Find ghost
I so weak that when they do this
Got plans
Go to conservative universities and
Dump
Sure
America's Best
But I don't think these idiots that are part of this
In this communist operation with Eliza
Their bosses
Target
My
That's nice of you
Thanks buddy
Okay
The story that he's already
Right
Leader of all
Tomorrow Alex
Go to your bunker now as far away from the rest of the human race as you can so I don't think Alex has any
He's basing the song that is what I would call realities
Misrepresenting has to sort of
A little bit of
A garnish to the story
They are escalating violent confrontation to set the precedent with everyone
Buildings down to shoot cops and they hadn't random citizen
City of Austin
Has the new budget
Calls for
Blowing up
To blow up
The police
Department
As a symbol of evil
To make police then
Inside other agencies under other bureaucrats control
So you can you can talk about this all day long Legends understand
This is the Takeover
This is a complete
Easily demonstrable
The real story here is that one of the Austin city council members Jimmy Flanagan
Forwarded
Florida proposal is part of the process of putting together the budget
Please start
Police Department in 25 restructure Department
Specific mission that leadership as opposed to it all being under one executive
Great technology in 911
Forensics and record-keeping
Investigations in traffic safety those three are all self-explanatory
Another Department of Professional Standards would handle
Internal affairs
As part of The Proposal which would see these responsibilities handled by more separate entities
There was an idea
Decentralize their offices
It's from the current building their house
One issue that I was ignoring here is very Twisted in The Proposal
The building that houses APD headquarters and formerly housed the Municipal Court as long
Beyond the end of its useful life
We should expedite the demolition of the LAPD headquarters
By directing the city manager to move all remaining APD staff
Existing headquarters building
Any other underutilized
City facility
It's an old building on very valuable real estate which could be better use
It's a city demolish the existing building and move the new police
East Apartments to existing city office space
Could be better used to serve the community
It's really a win-win although all around
Yeah that's great idea
But it's also
Recognize that this is all just still up
Proposal
Element of Alex's reporting
Why
He's claiming that this is officially the Austin city budget that they plan to blow up the police department or some kind of virtue
Signal
Figuratively a complete lie
Article in KVUE
Police Department budget
Yet Alex is Huron are saying it's official and certified by the mayor
Lies all the time
Is just making stuff up
Bummer
Yep
What an a******
He hasn't told his story about these hit teams coming to kill conservatives
Because he's still teasing
What's coming up next hour
Is the Paul Revere
Signal being fired up
This is it
Units
They're not just lazing targets
Going
The judges homes
Play Psalms
Talk show host Tom's members of Congress on
Preparing
The groups
Center going to go in and down those places than they're going to have actual
Professionals that kill the judges in place
Hanging out to dry
Course
I think that's great
These global
Have
Brilliant plans
Yep unfortunately even by our own measure those since none of them have
Actually work
I think the globalists are an ineffective in pointless organization
Alex
Portrays them bear the geopolitical mr. Magoo
Comical
Baby Ariel and the training baby l or maybe they mentioned both of them
Clip the training for Police Department
Surrounding
Either of their activities
Have woken up
Police Department
Because
The ADI was apparently trying to buy all the police chief's hookers
Or something
Now that's
Interesting
What's more interesting is that Alex starts rambling and talking about people who tried to buy him off
Over the course of his career
Police state plan
Military
Training
Did more than Alex Jones
Something about you
You're making this up
What the hell is this true we're not doing that
Educated and now there's another one enemy cuz I told you
The most group in the country is the police
Because they get taken to ATL and Southern Poverty Law Center events
And the captains
What are they saying
We got a business for you and it's actually Mafia
Has a criminal act
Resetting
And next to top sirloin
You're offering me a hook
Driver seat of my life
And almost all the cops
Refuse
So this is weird Alex is claiming that the splc tried to buy him off
Cuz I don't believe in any of that
Alex
Talkin about
How
He might have been approached by some Russian
With
Some money
Just like they had them in the Russia investigation
They couldn't get one American
Over 2,000 people including me
They couldn't get
One American
Money course it wasn't
So
I don't believe that this story is it all true
Truth-telling
He's
Approached and offered buddy
Yes
Now then
Let me let me toss this out
Did you report this to the FBI
So there is Alex's
Telling
Spit the Russians interfered with the election Dan or were attempting to Italy
So that whole Russia hoax Alex's accidentally got it all backwards
Because they were secretly
What okay fine then the globalist
Secretly
They'd still need somebody interfere with the election in trumps
Favorite setup
I hate living in this space
You saying is accurate I think he's just in a little bit of episode because
He had this adrenaline boost and all that juice from
I must be so right
Because people are attacking me feel so good
What's going on
Nowhere throat
Raccoons and it's not the Russians
You people
Laptops with epoxy
Because you spiritually Arbor
Why did you gave up your
Birthright
For nothing
Disgusting
You're like a rotting dead animal in the sun with Matt
You just want to force your way on us and rape us with your back scene
Toxic culture
Pedophilia and all of it and we're runs ejected
Do everything
Because when you're done
When you're out of breath
He said the only way we're settlers were both
Is relishing this like a
Ghost brake there any comes back
Prop
And the baby
There's baby the day before
Tune into rtvc right now you probably noticed that I've got
300 Win Mag semi-automatic
Sweetheart
Lapua
Semi-auto sweetheart
Brad nails Wendy's
Just want to set
Set the stage
What I'm going to cover next
Teleties right here
Eastern dish
New York
That
Antifa is
100%
Preparing Terror attacks
Shootings bombings firebombing
All over the US
Even organizing and preparing
And local police have informants in the group
Bars problem now
Thing at Busch
Senior
The clintons bush jr. then Obama
Fireworks for busting your buddy
Griselda manager
Marshalls
Too much enter to Gunn
By that I mean they're just
What are you talkin about
Basically so yeah yeah
He still seems to be
Acting like he thinks that he hasn't already told this story
He's talked about it quite a bit
I'm allowed to take those we come back on
Lightest horse vaccine World Government World by dinos
Layout
I just really mad at myself right
I just don't know how to describe this because it's so real
Understanding
Logical Warfare
So
I mean is the story that eventually gets to like
He's teasing he's teasing somebody's already talked about
As if
I really feel insane
You crazy
Still trying to
Is this
I think that he thinks that maybe people will think there's another story, but isn't
We have these shows they're in the middle of a zygote
Has the most insane ever
It's a form of
Laser welder
Shiting it's itchy
Incompetent
Front of me
Class A license already
Would give them the keys understanding all the other Shore
Alright because with
Is the
I am Alex Jones very serious political I speak in riddles
Remember When
Walter Cronkite would get on air and tell you some kind of a riddle
Cannot grasp
But looking at where I'm going is the fools
Good night good luck and weaknesses strengths
Sure.
So you want to talk about
He's gone
You don't need to
God God will help you break
Next song
50 caliber rifle
That's not my real power
Did you know with my bare hands
Actiontec any
Weapon
Read the will
I can break any man's neck
Okay
In the service of God
Cannot be resisted even destroyed
Need these
Haitian I have the spirit
Nuclear weapons
That's upsetting
Now
Somebody's had a mannequin
Claiming
Certain powers that may be Beyond you
Through Christ you can take nukes
I'm just going to throw this out
Okay now is our long-range
True that is the point of
Maybe I should stay away from the fence
Ya-Ya sisterhood
Much shorter
Reyes
Understanding why we have guns
Okay she doesn't need ammo you can break your neck
Stay away away from him
Got to help breaking up
So Alex continues to tease the story that he's already told
I'm not building suspense you're holding up covering this news
Well actually no
You're not
Drum rolls or
Another thing to do to build
Just because
That's a globalist
So much this
Info so much stuff going on
That
When you actually bring out the huge information
It just Fizzles out
Doesn't matter
That sounds like you
Yeah does
From Deep research
Credible sources
Experiencing it myself
Exactly what's going on I mean
I know more about this topic
Position of
Power Trip
You can probably imagine
Cuz you're making it all up
Anyway
Still building this
Your response
Roller like skylight
Alright Alex
Ali Baba's
I use these things like a spotlights in order to build up suspense
Sit here the Pelicans
When is next Cliff Alex is telling his audience to create kill list
If you pay attention to the types of people that might qualify for it
Could make sense
Saying is make a list of people who are out protesting
Because
They are essentially the UN troops
Slitter trying to overthrow the country
But if they want to kill us
The best thing to do
I don't want
I'm not going to
Okay
Everybody likes Santa Claus to take
While we're here
Think about the future
Did they take down your country they destroy your bank account
A bunch of patriot leaders
What are you going to do
Cuz you always talked about when the new world order came in and when the you ended this
You want to go out to shoot those two blue almond
Helmet
And once they get control your police
Those officers are program robots now
They'll follow orders for you
So anybody who I approached
In black or whatever is basically you and worker and a blue helmets
You should make a list
Who's really f****** dangerous
I wish that was in the Frontline documentary Alex is a f******
Like that is literal
I don't want to fight an offensive but I've created a fake one to fight a defensive War again
Created an artificial justification for all potential violence
And if you lose
Is any number it like hey if your 401k goes down because of I guess
Leftist mismanaging the covid issues
Which by the way
Happens to be everyone I disagree with but
I mean it is important
If we're going to play a clip like
We should probably play the follow up today
But the enemy is not
Loser
Method playing video games
That is told by the media given hundred dollars baby.
They're not the target you do not
Killing them
I don't want you to kill anybody right now
Right now
At what time 9
Free single globalist New World Order operative
An executive-level isn't anime combat
Humanity
Once they pull the trigger with their dick
Now's not the time
You'll know the time
And
This is the real world this isn't about
This is
Dark
Straight up
CBS does a report on Alex
Leftist
Really does because he's getting all this energy to go out
The Blaze of Glory all of these people paying attention to them look at me as I
Explode into the stratosphere doesn't want to report losing in court
Yeah yeah yeah
If more satisfying as a narrative story
Exactly so
That's somebody who yells all the time about how much he loves God
Interesting Lee Alex
At this point the episode starts talking about how I'm going to save this
Have to stop
Sitting back and letting other towers that could Our Lives
Shut up
Person
Comes down
Taurus
No
Everything we have
Motorboat
Got a job
Bank account that works
Someone lost her husband
Daddy didn't come home for that
Millions
Died
So what's interesting here is it Alex's
Just like
Pejoratively referring to God as a magic
Like a robot
Kind of
View things and then
If you really look at what he saying about like you on your motorboat there with you with your nice house
He's turning
Capitalists of the past yet into Christ they died for your ability to have this
Smoker pellets
62 million
I need nothing
God is the market
So Darkness
Think about it
Easy about Christ that is a Christian
Sacrifice sacrifice
For your sins
Course Alex's framing these people in the past who have fought two up
Hold this system
Capitalism
Christ figure think about all those men
Who got black
In order to save your bank account
They were in the
Dial
I just can't do it another day and then they think about Jeff bezo someday in the future making a billion dollars in a
And they're like
Goddess sacrifice
He died for his billions
Zach reversa
Jesus where it is one person
The entirety of the world as opposed to
Millions of people who sacrificed
Yeah you know it.
World's total inversion of the the Jesus sacrifice
Good
Pretty sure
Don't lose the lord's name in vain
Does not include calling him a magic dude in the sky
Seems it seems a little derisive
Tucker Carlson a year-and-a-half ago that people come to his house breakdown add or threatened to rape and kill his wife
I never told people laughing.
Things that are going on here
Until I learned what was happening other areas
Country
What's up
But now I'm going to lay it out
Abbott from New York City
New York okay
Los Angeles California
Federal Marshal
The FBI
And finally today
PD
Confirm
What I was told
But because I wasn't
Absolutely
I did not tell you
Have
Ridiculously name
Assault
Driving around in SUVs and trucks antifa
With two and four men
Groups
Pairing
Anyone that doesn't stop at a checkpoint
Including police
Will be killed
And that's just the surface
You're already talked about this base
Suspicious
Print it out
Statement from the Austin
It does
It's pointless
They're going to blow up the Austin
We have the
We have officially been announced
In the city council of Austin that they're going to blow up the police department
I showed you that last hour
Officially in the budget
This isn't some recommendations
Doesn't make sense
This isn't
Is here
So
You know
This is very weak that's are the Takeover is here
Right
They're there if they've already pulled the trigger
Yeah
And when they pull the trigger
Well that the hill said the time is right
You'll know
I mean I do know he said no he said it's you'll know
Legally Legally you know when the time is right
Luigi Luigi
Anyway
Here's the big news
I believe
Weiner
You said you were trying to build it off
Multinational corporations have
Found and funded Army of mentally ill drug head
White people mainly
Call themselves antifa
When they are Fascist
Call themselves black lives matter
Stop it
You're embarrassing all these little pathetic
Video game playing
That's who they are
Losers lose to go out and do all this
And now they got them going to people's houses marking targets
Long way down roads
So the police
Sounds right
Woodson only encourages
The idiot method
The carry out the next part of the operation and their orders
Halftime now
Who was Saul
Talk show host
Patriot law enforcement
Members of Congress members of State legislatures
Governors that don't roll over
They are so important
And Obama and Hillary
Houses
Police
Armed with weapons with
Amber's in Hatchet
What a what a waste of
Like structure of a show
You know what I mean like
He's
At the end of the episode exactly the same as saying an hour and a half early
Couldn't stop himself from getting into
He's like
Talking about these details
And scaring people to the point where you couldn't
Even hold off on the big reveal
Until the end
Surrounds
The
Good the narcissistic response that he has two other people outside of his media bubble
Paying attention he's irrelevant
Man
Every every single mom
At the front line in Portland
Has more courage
In their f******
Fingers
Alex f****** the entire Republican goddamn
Every single one
Disgusting
For you to say anything about
They've got an army of meth head
There's moms out there on the front
Bucking why
True
You don't know there's not like that song
Mom
Yeah that's true
Head argue that there is a connection there
I think there's something interesting in there like Alex on the 28th
Wasn't really all that
Concerned didn't even really mention
Frontline thing
Just did pay programming supposedly or what I would I be
Joel skousen
Just a bunch of nonsense
And then the day after
He's in a really f***** up headspace
Of of like really relishing and being euphoric about
This attack
She has suffered
Or whatever
And
He's built up this narrative where there's antifa MS-13 hit teams
That are going to kill all the
Fruit starting
I'm sure disturbing disturbing
And that would be where we at
4 Thursday morning
Trump tweeting
Responsibility
People are the ones who are Fascist and they're the ones who are fashion cuz it's a real fast
Just thing to do to not agree with the president whenever he says
Who claims to have great sources
Tomorrow's news today
Something about
The fact that drop tomorrow B between about the possibility
I mean who knows
Didn't didn't I get into that
Even bigger news has broken was here on the 30th
The news I'm about to announce
The biggest
And is Crescendo of incredible development
This morning
All the pieces put together
I will tell you this
Trumpets
Carry firearms at all time
The shotguns
Haven't even hand.
Because
Threat Level in this country
To what is known as the leadership
American resistance
Steakhouse
Is extremely serious
Big news at Alex's teasing and as a result of his news
He's going to be carrying a gun with
I think everybody did
Just assume you probably already were already
He might as well be a walking gun take any weapon
His entire personality
Yeah so this is about delaying the election
Intuit
Where's the giant piece of the puzzle that just went into completed
Universal mail-in voting
2020 will be the most
Embarrassment to the USA
The lady election until people can properly
Safeway
I totally agree with the president this year
Oh will beg
My father suddenly
Believe
He's not going to accept the results of the election
Because he's being advised by smart people
But you cannot allow
In over 25 State and over 800 weapons control settings
This is exactly the same ship
Like you was saying
Obama would try and is using
Some sort of a crisis they would cause
Some sort of a natural disaster with their weather control manipulation
Frozen fever
You know they be like hey we can't possibly have an election because there's been this natural disaster that
Excuse as to why they couldn't be an election
Right as opposed to what he's been saying for years and years and years and years
I saw all that stuff
This morning where it's like
Trump was just waiting. Out to distract from how the economy is the worst thing
And I'm just sitting here just being like
You idiots
You f****** moron
You better start having a plan
For when he does this
You should not have a plan for
I'm sure that the Supreme Court will stop at
The Supreme Court election in my lifetime
Play for it
Plan for it
I'm not as interested also in the
Distraction from ex wires
I'm also not
The camp of
He can
Unilaterally do this absolutely
But I
I agree with you that like
This is a line
That like you just can't
Can't you can't you can't
No there is there
Congress or whomever I don't know not taking
Suggestions like this seriously
Insect adherence
You're insane
He is going to try and steal this election
That is not a conversation
Do that because otherwise he's a terrorist
We're going to move back the election
You don't stop the mail-in ballots have to be declared fraudulent
Fraudulent made up
Mail-in ballots that are fake
Time results and throw Outlook is it good and they're staying even challenge
Frogs coming out everywhere
Stacked up in people's mailboxes
Florida
Texas
Michigan
They're going to say he's a terrorist
Anastasia bad guy
Does anybody realize the maximum alert they're making their move
You can see here how
Smooth transitions
Advocating for a
Completely Auntie democratic system of government
Because he has his fever fraudulent vote
Space mostly on memes and misrepresentations of headlines
He's positing that the only thing done to protect the country's to not have an election until all this is sorted out
What this accomplishes is basically allowing Alex and his
Define the terms of a quotient
Pharaohplex
Which is the standard that they will never reach
Democratic party should be outlawed
Do you think he'll ever say all right now it's safe to have
Never happen
Imagine this does go down
Trump somehow gets Congress to delay the election
Then what
When does the election get rescheduled
If the complaint is that the mail-in voting system is fraudulent wouldn't be until the covid-19 situation is worse
Which could be a while
So Trump going to be president
Until covid is over
Or does he still end his term
What do you do
Maybe since the problem is the mail-in voting system
Trump re-election
The only after a thorough investigation of May
Voting was done
Just that.
Systems in the country before
Agrees to an election
Isn't how this work
The president has to agree to an election
Everybody knows the democracies only work whenever the
Agrees to the elect
This is probably the scariest thing I've heard from Alex Jones
Yeah it's not even worth while to discuss how he constantly screamed his audience about spheres of Obama
Election of 2012
16 just the Highlight is apocracy
That does not even really matter right now because Alex
So transparently dangerous
But even engaging with it as something as something normal is wrong
It was generally very entertaining Alex's stupid ideas and trying to understand where they come from
A better understanding
Misinformation
Ecosystem
Sparta
In this case
F*** that
I was just cheerleading a direct assault on the idea of a democratically elect
The government in this country
And that's crossing a line that I cannot tolerate
Trump suggesting postponing the election is a Redline
Where people need to start taking this very seriously and considering what this could mean for the future
Alex endorsing it to tell you something
Sterno and that's what his political project
It's never been about the concert
Tatoosh in our love for America
Is always Christian nationalist
Dictatorship
And that's what he sees as being possible now
And he's going to fight like hell in order to
I try and install that
As well they are
Probably more than
More people
Would be comfortable imagine
So I don't know I mean
Obviously
I don't know what's going to
To become of this but like this is
This is this
Everything is bad
Protesters as un troops
Some stuff like that is bad
Trump
Muslims shouldn't come to the country
That's really bad
Stuff is really bad
This
Beauty sleep
Because
It's so Central
To the idea that this could never
Yeah you know like
With
Something like Muslims can come into this executive order
Is disqualifying in what we should see as a l 100
Assuming
The next Administration comes in
Try and mitigate
Hunan governmental organizations that can fight in court
Do duplex
Stop deportation total
You can have Charities that help displaced people
Focus on
In the Keys
A president of a
Nuclear-armed
Country
That is
Central
Functioning of the world
Exactly
The idea of becoming
Authoritarian position dictatorship
There is
Such a line
There
Is
I mean honestly I see that that very tweet
Should probably
Include the 25th Amendment
Like legitimately
It is time to get rid of that president
Right
Don't give a s***
If Obama even joked about that
We would not hear the end of it from anyone
Forever about Obama joking about being Superman
Comedies
About
Announces f****** documentary
You got it
To me this should be like a real
Crystallizing moment
Like
When people say
If these sorts of things are the Tendencies the Trump has
They weren't saying that for no reason
These are the Tendencies the Trump has
And allowed
Uncheck
To continue
Will lead
NeverEnding
Trump dictatorship
It's
Your timing is just
That is the
That's legitimately the line
When can you hit bottom
This is the bottom
Alex saying that it's okay to have a trump LED dictatorship
Is him reaching the bottom
Because I don't give a s*** what happens if yes
Like in instances where it's like
Abstract
Trump doesn't appear to be involved in Alex's fantasy
Trump making jokes about 60 more years
Mad
Nonsense
It's b*******
Need something
People should rightly point out be like a look at this
Trump
Making excuses about mail-in votes being also fraudulent in the election
Or possibly we should put off the election
Absolutely
It's unacceptable
You can you can buy the joke whenever he says 16 years
Because sounds
2insane
Extra 6 months
Text to 6 months
More to the point
Because
It is only an extra
That's when you know ocean
This is
This is never going to end
And this is basically Star Wars prequels
Essentially
Really is
There's no way you guys don't see the Republican Senate going along
The goddamn Merrick Garland
Argument of no we should wait until Bubba Bubba Bubba until the results of the election or f******
And then we needed the Supreme Court validated and says it because we can't be guaranteed on those
You're speculating a lot about how these steps would go but I understand why
Understand why
The president
That we've seen over the last number of years
Even the last 20 years
Inspiring
It hasn't been encouraging
To see the Supreme Court has ruled
Particularly this Senate has lost the election
It's not
No
Anything
Will be accepted by the Supreme Court
It does give you cause for Paws as you might say
If you wanted to rhyme
I don't know I don't want to deep down this road because I think that there is a certain amount of
They could be over reaction
But if there's anything that you should over react to
Yeah it's something like that
No there should be in over react
Yeah that is an overreaction is the correct
Many people will be hurt by
It's unconscionable to think about just because
The covid thing is not going to
Go away
And if he stays in there for any capacity it is going to get
Right
I mean that's only even one
But really the issue is MS-13 in Chinese
Speedmaster Excel
MS-13 Tricom team
Other groups ready to
Cooperation
Patriot
During all of this and then call a race war
Are going to have to themselves in the rightful Authority would George Washington do you know it's worth why she would do
If you're drowning in debt you can't afford
Alex wants
Toledo revolutionary war against
I guess things
Inside the country that are his enemies
Famous
For arguing that there should be asked to stay on in the executive branch
Passed his second term said no earlier
Washington
Killing people no but against the people he was killing where the Kings
Sorry the Democrats
So how it starts talking about what's going to need to happen if things get bad
It is essential
Killing us
It's essential that you do out of their leadership
Ladies and gentlemen that means a lot of other businessmen lot of uniform a military research people you might be 7 years old
You're going to have to get on that airplane
And you're going to have to go find these people on your mission
Shut up and stop
That we gone so far down this rathole now we're facing a communist uprising
Going in the Doomsday switches here ladies and gentlemen
What to do
Alex and saying like seventy-year-old ex-soldiers need to go on suicide missions
To take out his imagine l
He's essentially calling for suicide bombers
To go and commit missions
For him stop being
Howard's
What needs to be done
Talk about the Republican response to 9/11 as being when you look into the abyss the abyss look
Looks back at you
Like all we fought at all we hate terrorism fighting against it now
Best way to solve your problems with suicide
Everybody knows
That would be silly to think otherwise damn seventy-year-old ex-soldiers businessmen Garrix
Kill yourself by killing Soros
Yeah that's what is wrong with this guy
Execute Order 66
Weird feeling that I got when I would listen
I might be reading more into it then
That is necessarily there
There was a feeling that I got the where Alex is saying goodbye
In this
In this club
We can beat these people heart Bear Hands
When they go to restaurants
What
They're the ones
Long after I've gone to shovel in my grave
Understand that lady's and gentleman's it
On the real side starts
Now
Get up here until you
I think you already all know it anyways don't you
Where We Are
Altogether
Supreme
Call devil worshippers
Just like the Bible says
What is every culture
This also seems to imply that he has some believe sound like British is realism
Which is
Upsetting
Anything but it is
I think it's just for dramatic effect
The abyss is the end of the Republic so I love all of you you know I agree with you
Probably for dramatic effect effect that he wants to
Create is
We're on our kamikaze
Bucked up
But anyway there's no violence
What's my soulmate
I want to be completely clear about this no offensive violence
But once they start a physical
Operation is not
Jimmy the defensive
The best defense is offense
Once you enter a war
So once you add a reward any of this offense
Actually
In a war
Half an hour later
Nothing
I just want to
In the war
We are now in the war PlayStation
Has repeatedly is giving people looking
Condition where upon any kind of Silence Is by
Great Alex you need to pay better attention to the things you're saying
You're giving your audience
Permission to murder whoever
It just seems like just because you separated in
Time doesn't mean that you didn't still tell everybody to
Kill EPP
I don't I do not
At least from my perspective
The fact that it was a little bit later in the show
Can't be like all the closets
Basically a little bit earlier in the show he said if X-Men 1 and 1/2 hour later he said X repeatedly
That's
Logically tracks that conclusion is
Why but apparently logic is not allowed in the court
Logic isn't involved in Infowars world
Particularly
Considering
The guest
Stone is going to look at the election and Trump's response
Maryland fraud
He's going to be looking at the election with a Sim in
The cussing weather
Postpone the election until the fraud
Walk into the machine gun fire
Confrontation with them
Love you join the Trump tweeted after the accident need where they're going
So Rodger is going to come in to try and talk about
He's not in prison
You know the things
Sucks the most about fascist proper
Kiganda is that it
Exactly
You know there's no spin there's no like
You know like normal propaganda is there during a different era
You're just twisting it
Fascist propaganda it's just like
Hey
They're the one starting the war
It is a little bit less creative
Ring and then we move on
Does suffer from a little bit of a lack of like I said creativity
Exactly
You express your creativity and differ
Frontwave sometimes it's performance Fahrenheit
Is it planned about evolution
Wyclef dismantling
Communist
Kill somebody
Position
Which helps anyone
End
Christmas in July
Tell me that leftists are killing people for their dream managerial position
You know who left it there huge in the middle manager
Means like manager class within the communist
Sequoia Bureau or whatever
They're going to kill you
Their dreams aren't even that big dad
Express
Christmas in July sale
Late summer Christmas
So Alex is making a
Stop
Misrepresenting things around the protester in Austin
Shot
This is an invalidation of Alex's Second Amendment
Cuz he believes that Foster just holding a gun means that he was threatening
The person
And deserve
B shot
Shame on you from the position of
I think we should be allowed to grab
His guns from
Studio
Lies about this a little bit more
And
Touch on it cuz it hasn't really evolved much except for this
They have colds going around
Police headquarters
Last week
I got it blocked off
Turn himself in to police and was released
White
Leasing information
Any information has just
Determine that the guy who shot Foster must not be white
Why they haven't really suited there's a hundred other explanation
Transferwise
Be protected in this days
Wyoming a white hats
To make it there is no real reason to release his name at this point given
I don't know if it's suspect
Or what the exact terminology you're not looking for them because they already turned themselves
Appeared at the station so
Releasing the names of the public doesn't help you find
Going to charge them
So assuming that you do the investigation and find no wrong
Want
Say
Put their entire business on national news and make sure that every single person on the planet knows who they
Reasons to defend privacy in this instance
From the perspective of the police station by train
With no information because he
He's a huge racist
Has decided that he doesn't fit the narrative but it was a white person
You who it is
That sounds right
This is classic white supremacist white nationalist
So Alex
And this is really funny
Because Alex mentions
Something
And that is the Rodger was involved in the 2000 election
Brooks Brothers
Yeah but you mentioned it
And then immediately realizes he's not supposed to like
He was there in 2000
In the contested election in
Florida between Gore and
Of course bus you successfully helped get bush in so
Internet the rapper
Stone
Is Rodger Stone
Savor that
God
You know that you're talking to somebody that you're early and most of your careers based around like
He was involved in something that you thought was a coup
Overthrowing the public
In a certain sense you literally just blamed rogerstone for 911
My bad buddy
That's so
F****** stupid
I hate him so much
It just doesn't mean anything nothing means anything
Talking about
Result is going to be
That's clear to me
To reserve his ability to
Illegally
I believe the next election
The entire issue
Yeah what the president has done is really brilliant to find ways around a legitimate election
End the pretense of Define legitimate election
California and urban areas are going to be illegitimate
No matter what
So
In this next clip
Alex is like a rock
Why don't you tell
Trump something
You just say something on air
Trump
Aren't they supposed to be friends no no
Rodger Stone as a message to Donald Trump
What you say
Else you want to add to the offense
You take a big shot of espresso
Will you come back in 5 minutes
Rodger Stone Reese Trump on
When we come back and Rodger sellers you going to get to
President-trump
I don't understand how he expects anyone to not like he's listening to not think like Rodger could talk
To Trump
Send him a quick task
Oh no
Get on Infowars and Alex
Because of the gray
Listeners
This is
Childish
So anyway
Say a whole lot more of them
Love it is also just him trying to sell a shirt
Cuz he wants to appeal his case
I need the million dollars to appeal his case
Great that's a great group
That's still good
Is
Rodger Warren
Trump to not submit to a debate
Which is funny considering that all of these people keep yelling about how they left
Amazing
Schedule
Presidential
Commission on the base
Because it is
It is not a connection
Where and when
Is the presidential commission
When the moderator is in the chat
So you see
When Trump doesn't debate its
Strength when weak
Can I see it's fascist
Propaganda
Pinterest
You're not loud
Keyboard
Pops Pops out another guest
Millie Weaver
Because apparently there's developments with her Sunrise movement
Now he's very stupid
Alex
Asserting something
During this episode
Disclaim
Might be legally actionable and in no way does Alex
Back us up at all until
Courthouses in thousand
Illegal, to check point
We now have major leftist groups funded by Soros the Democrats
Sunrise movement
Please call me
Rogers Collegewood High School
Carry-out violent
These are all malice
Use 4 gauge you think your child's joining
And then I get programmed online
By the last two carryout sexual blackmail that's on video
Communist attacks
We have footage of this
Gordon inside the zoom meeting
And so they are
Activating your organization
Absolutely unsubstantiated
Alright
Children
Gather round we're going to talk about the high today
Does the idea that kids hit people with hammers
Alex
The only kid Racine hit people with hammers has been on it
Adult
Alex will bring that up over and over and over and over and over again
Dad about how this video is them telling people to hit people and conservatives with hammers
Payoff to that
Is amazing
It's so
Stupid
Before we get to that
Alex plays a little bit of the video
Cuz Millie Weaver Skype stops working
And so they play a little bit of Zoom call
That what it is is people talking about a plan
Demonstration
That was too
Keeps like Mitch McConnell up really late to his house and make a bunch of noise
Cuz like if we can't sleep like no justice no sleep right
Sleep troubles to be really scary
Well don't
Lead a genocide
So
If you if you listen to it it's very clear that's
The
Contacts
Around what they're talking
I'm about his car
Justice no sleep or Wide Awake
Protesters even showed up
I want to run your life
There is a perfect encapsulation of Alex's races
He sees this young woman
Generation
And for no other reason than the fact that she's not
Implies that she's not from America
He knows nothing about her than what he can tell visually and perhaps even the non-white person to something
You associate with them not being from here
With them not having the same rights to speak out or Advocate change
It's someone who looks like
Like himself.
This is very consistent and Alex's rhetoric
Use a ton of lip service to all the points that he has to hit like saying that we all have red blood
He's careful to not say racial slurs for the most part
Keep does not believe that people have the same right to be in this country
And to be treated as equals
Alex sees everyone as members of the groups that he can visually determine and treat differently
He sees women in her job is at the pool supply store at experiences at as as a sign
The Muslims are refusing
To assimilate
Eatzi's division on white woman discussion protest outside Mitch McConnell's house
And he experiences at as her being someone
The white people were nice enough to let into the country who's being ungrateful
This is not a small point
Do Alex Mike think that slip-up is kind of minor
It actually reveals a whole lot about how his mind operates subconsciously
He has an ingrained belief that non-white people don't belong in America
And the ones who are here should be thankful
That white people allowed them to be here
To go along with whatever circumstances they find themselves
Put simply on a deep level Alex doesn't believe in equal rights
In this country
He believes in a white nationalist state
It's clear I made just things like that are so I've just got nothing to say
The country you don't know anything about where she
He's from
You know anything about
It's not a dog whistle
The screen it is
100-percent
So Milly is talkin about the zoom call
From everything that they've provided is just people talking about a protest
Outside Mitch McConnell's house to keep him awake
Maybe even some other places but with the strategy
Can people off in order to
To take your
Your point seriously
Millie is so
Goddamn dumb
Interesting
Cremation of care
Is it
Call Dave
The Cremation of care ceremony historically has been held on the exact same
I don't know why
Always happens 100 days before they
When the planet
Yeah that that that's probably
The sunrise movement
Young women
Please
Cruise
Call Shanghai
Instagram
But now
Mark your house and go to Cleburne on you
This is
This is really
Depressing
Video plays
Are there they are with their hamburgers
It's like people with
Pots and pans
There is nothing video that says brick hammers to hit people it's all entirely based on
A couple of shots of people
Look actually like
Hammers
Look it look on one side we have the heroes the men decked out in military gear with
A r n e
They can identify them with their faces completely covered in only their eyes visible firing.
Non-lethal munizzi
Munitions
On one side and on the other you have these people with
A spoon in a pan damn
They are training your children to disagree with the guys who have all the guns
Terrible
Alarm injector position where Alex is talking about how like we're all going to die we're past the point
No return MS-13 kill teams are showing up
And you need to 70 year old veteran you need to sacrifice yourself in a suicide mission against
And then he's like yeah
Is people with noise
I got some Intel from the Austin Police Department
So Apple
A reports a timpani on the ground
Decent
Track record of people who
Or at least inspired partially by Infowars causing damage in society
This would be
The most hilarious self-parody I can imagine a name
The real-world ramifications of this stuff
Scary
Now Millie's interviewees
A
Dud
What
But you usually bring such good
Sexual blackmail
The
Hammerhead
Is that
The all seeing eye gif
Vettery posted on Instagram that is just a like a neon sign of an
Eye-opening
It's like not even the central focus of the gif
It's a bit of a
You know I already told across I want to come in tonight 7292 special commercial-free live show how they're going to do it I'm too tired
Xbox
The reason I'm so tired is
All this preparation
Why I know their plan and it's so hard I'm so tired cuz I prepared all of his stuff
I just he says it
As a point of pride
Over and over again he starts to get WIC
I just going to tease it because if I don't I don't know it's not making a big enough deal of it and then everytime it
I haven't done my job everything I know everything
I'm so smart and I have the all seeing eye I know all that's going on but
Didn't tell you anyways I forgot
Just do your job and boss boss I understand that you're mad
Only doing 5% of my job to come in from 7 to 9
I have a counter-offer
I'm really tired
Look I only did 5% of the news
Because
I had to spend all my show talk about how you're going to have to kill people you're going to have to kill people What is the news got to do with that right
So we won last year from the 30th
I mean
This is dumb but
Why not
But I was always close to it
A bunch of stuff
But now to be here in the side guy
I think Alex
May have just been heavily implying that his family was into the general
I think
Maybe
I might be working on his life Theory
That Alex had a weird relatives
Who may be terrified him as a child Satan or something
Avista
Is maybe unresolved
Unprocessed feelings that he has about being a young child in a scary distant relative or some
The devil
Or something some sort of some sort of dealt with trauma
Surrounding
I would have no reason to assume that
Some of his family members went to the devil if he hadn't just said that
We're getting this all wrong
Here's what we've here's what's going on Dan I finally figured it out
First.
Devil's ivy
Devil's obviously
Now
Here's the other
Alright Alex
Doesn't know
The reality that the rest of us live in
Because we haven't made a deal with the Devil
We don't have race memory we don't have these DNA memories
Do you know why Alex does because
Thousands of years ago in the American South whenever they were allowed to roam free his ancestor made
Deal with the devil to live
Forever in Pakistan from firstborn son to firstborn son
And that line is under his never ended and now we are here with Alex Jones who is the only person who can see all of this
Because he's the only one who's at
Actually made a deal with the devil Dan this is true
This guy
The original global
Wow this is serious
Alex's the devil
Is family
Go down that poor guy I mean
I'm glad to be able to provide.
There's there's
Interesting things
You can see here and that is the old episodes are distinct
Definitely
Violent in nature
Didn't like there is a there is a psycho roller coaster that Alex
Is going on
Fairly normal business as usual I'm going to pimp Joel skousen Book for a long time
They're still
Trouble around everything
Document
Another 29th Alex's high from his attention leads to
Embellishing exaggerate MS-13 Chinese
I'm just descends into a only five million people are going to survive this
And we're going downtown
Trump has given him all he needs to continue this
He continues that
Based off
Trump's insinuation that
Mask off entirely Alex's
Julian favor 100
August
He's been given the excuse
Dua to
Take on
That position as opposed to
What you would expect
From someone who pretends to have the principles that he does which would be
We now must fight
I want a dictator I just didn't want to be
Now I got one
Pretty simple
So what
7 to 9 this evening commercial-free
We are fighting I go to bed Jordan
Bail Fund in your area and
Join join the fight
Clark
Holding
Alex