Damn important I'm sweating
I have great respect with knowledge like I'm sick of them posing
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
It's around a little bit about Alex Jones
IMDb
Jordan Jordan
What's up
Potato chip
Later
Well you know I'm a
Do flavors like
Find a couple of new varieties
I bought two flavors York Pizza
Mostly out of fear
Smart is it thinner than the Chicago
It's a smaller bag
Nashville hot chicken flavor
Shockingly accurate
Read are you similar
It kind
Freaks me out
I don't like it
Utug
Like I did
I did it first and then I ate more
It's too much
Too much as a
But I still
Reconsider to Bryce because I admire the
Accuracy of the
The flavor and swing for it
Pizza one
But
Good job ladies
Mystics
Exactly like
And I never want to get another one for the rest of my life check it out the box
For me and my bright spot is I got to spend a little time with my family today and
We went to a place where it's like it's like
Target
Aurora
Hitting the ball with the with the
The other guy looks like frisbee golf but golf
So it's called
Weird really really terrible I hate
It was there was interesting parts of it they gamify day
Terrible game
And it's alright
They were there in the music was loud
A good time
Yeah
To talk about
July 31st and August
20/20 episodes
August 1st
If you'll recognize
Things I think
Cuz some pretty serious news to deliver
My brother able to figure out what was going on
Alright
Fatigue
Fut tigue
Are you very much sweetie
I'm a policy wonk
Articulate
Kimberly G
I'm a policy wonk
Text Kim
Thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
I have a lot of thoughts about your Manifesto
Saving for a party
Alright
PC2
You are now a technocrat
Alicia are thinking about
Money off at heroin
So good
Is freakishly large
Would be wondering
Take that
Generosity
Put it in a bin.
Walk on over to your nearest
Charity Outpost
Glacier over there drop that bindle and give people some Goodwill
I think that's a great great way to go I like it although I was distracted because
I can't think of a friend of mine from Missouri who described
Hozier
Bohemian types
Kindling official
No that's not bad
That is a great ride.
I like it
We're going to be getting into
Business Alex's declaring
Being on Sunday
Did not happen
But I thought
Do we do something we don't do very often
His follow-up on some other stories
But Alex has recently reported.
Completely Ross I like this
Are you looking might be some value in beginning this episode on past week or so
Completely unfounded assertions about
We just turned out to be complete nonsense okay
The first story I'm going to check in on
Was the Twitter hack
We're verified Elon Musk
I never used to run a Bitcoin
Scam
July 17th
Alex covered the story
And this is how he presented
Campbell just a cover
What's going on
It's
Patriots inside us intelligence agencies
On July 31st nbca out of Tampa reported on the arrest of a seventeen-year-old
Floridian dude named Graham Clark
Who is accused of masterminding the Hat
The charges he's facing include
Fraud
Fraud one count of fraudulent use of personal information with over $100,000 or 30 or more
Dumb
Fraudulent use of personal information
Access to computer
Or electronic device of that Authority
So what did he do wrong
Work was one of three suspected individuals in Mesquite
New year old named Nima fazeli AKA Rolex
Nineteen-year-old from the United Kingdom
Alright I'm on there
Team so far this article
A big deal of their aliases
Arrest affidavit clams
To get access to these Twitter account to a Twitter employee
Feel like there's a
Who committed the crime
Court used social engineering
Convince a Twitter employee
Access because
Customer service
Squirtle
From the appearances of the information
And it's come out
About this
Navigation so far it looks like an almost impressively simple
What's the think actually worked
There's no evidence to support Alex's fabricated coverage of the story
But honestly the other stories lied about is much worse
Okay
On July 25th
Protester Garrett Foster was shot and killed in
Alex's falsely reported on the story in order
Justify Foster
Killing
And that's awful
I think I want to focus on however is what Alex said on the July 30th show
About the identity of the person who shot Foster
They have armored vehicles going around
Stopping traffic in downtown Austin
Was shot dead
Last weekend we pulled a gun on
Amanda's car while I got it blocked
Anime
We still don't know the man's name
Turn himself in to police and was released
White
Doterra
Leasing information
Eastandard
Supremacist white nationalist commentator
Whenever there's a crime committed in the identity of the perpetrator is not an ounce
It's a default position for them
The perpetrator is
Person and that doesn't
The media wants to
This itself is a narrative
That these races to want to push
Namely that there's a cover-up of crimes being committed by minorities
Intentional plan to demonize white people
You see this all over the white identity
Never stop
Why would you
On July 31st the man who shot Garrett Foster identified him
His name is Daniel
He is an act
Duty sergeant
In the US Army stationed at Fort Hood
He claims that he shot Foster in self-defense and that Foster pointed his rifle
Alex has made this claim but the evidence that I've seen provided doesn't seem to support this Ark
Namely that he pointed his rifle
If that is the case he definitely shouldn't have done the argument of self-defense
Becomes a little bit murky
When prior to the alleged
You drove your
Car into crowd
People
It could easily be argued
It seems to me that if
Deadpoint is going to
The car that could be
Self-defense and defense
The people who
Could have been run over
I don't think this case is as cut-and-dry as to hinge on whether or not Foster pointed his gun at the car
Is it that determines whether it was okay to
Shoot them or not
That makes perfect
Even if
There were two
To be evidence
But he had his rifle raised
It justifies shooting him when
Once you already reached that point
You know if I was holding
And a car was barreling towards
Smith threw a bunch of other
I would probably throw the rifle away and
Apologized
I don't know
I think I was in a
There be some more information
And we'll see if that's
Prepare
Deschutes roster
Prepared to drive into a crowd of protest
I do I just
Or show is about Alex and his coverage
He's a 33 year old white dude in the army
The speculation was completely
It's just a product editorial position
It's based in racism and white identity
It was more important
Super Alex to push the nose
There's a cover-up
Then it was to deal with the story on its merits
It should be mentioned that Daniel Perry almost certainly only identified himself on Friday because
Certain protest communities online
Figured out who he was
His name
It wasn't
Terry tried to delete his social media but people are already taking screenshots
But things like a bond
Intuit
Trumpet put out saying
Any protestors anarchist
Meditators Lueders are Oklahoma
Please understand you will not be treated like you has been in New York Seattle Mini Apple
It will be a much different scene
Tweet Perry reply quote
To Texas will show them why we say don't mess
There's some pretty strong indications
Violet inclination
In-store protesters
Question
I'm driving
Into a March
The protesters
Information on this
Complete determination
But from the information I can find
It's hard to not feel like
This guy shouldn't be at least
Tried
For murder
Probably should
See the inside of a
Sound bad
Maybe he was just referencing
Litter
You know you was like as send all these protesters to Texas
Maybe
Nevermind
Pretend that the shooter was he non-white persons
When in reality
The shooter was a white army Sergeant who seems to share some of the political beliefs
Espouses regularly
How to say I'm shocked
So we start here on the 31st
Which is Friday
And
You know how like
P****
If you're a band
And you have one head
You better open your
Michelle with that hat
Or open close
Alex has the same thing man
By the way
Do you want to hear
Convenience
About how this Saturday
OverWatch snipers Oliver
But they're planning to shoot police
Citizens if anyone stops antifa major roads
So Alex at least got the story almost immediately after saying I'm having trouble getting
To be really into it
Here's the news
Secret documents to set up roadblocks
Some snipers in
And all this dick this weekend
As somebody who is here on Sunday I can tell you that on for
Fortunately Austin has
Been taking over
Antifa is not
Sing about now
You would never know if you just listen to the 31st
Short have to listen
But like dig into it
Forgo
What he's talking about
Couldn't tell
You wouldn't be able to tell just
Apparently this weekend
Plan
Is
It's going to take over
Six police station around the country
Border to border from seed
Driving sea-level is control Democrats planning this weekend
Moore City Police Department
Is this Von houses this now almost completely non-falsifiable
We can be here on Sunday
Are coming out here in
What a what a week
What a warrant
This this this whole thing
The trick is that it's a it's a
The Parlour trick
Your card is
Reporting on this kind of news where it's like
Police stations this weekend
Deep inside sources
Sing that most rotors Revolution
Is that
It's also an actor
Permission
Because
No matter what like the TV media that jerk-off to Violent protest that's what they want
Peaceful protest to the millions of
That happen all the time
Violent protests
Cats are there
Portraying protest
Violin
The Rake
Just propaganda is portraying and Eddie
Protesters are violent
Protesters don't have
But you get permission
Come up
So yeah there's that element to it
It's a trick
It isn't it isn't it
It's an absolute
There's nothing that can be done with the way Alex is reporting
Exactly
No matter what
What happens the next day at the end of the weekend he has a narrative that he can move forward with
Yep and that's
Just
The dumb game
Yeah
Okay nothing happens
I stopped yet
I told you
Completely honest
Related matters
Or
Going to Nuke a city
How is Chicago.
Secret documents
Very scared
Cabg
Route to know about this
Watch already with Andy
Apartments in
Balconies
Parking garages
Why is there Army Special Operations Command or something
Going to have music
Practicing
Checkpoint
And
Windows and pledge allegiance to antifa
Individuals who got shot
Start
Doing a second job driveshare
Food delivery
So the army Sergeant
Wow
Cactus on life
Lexus learn
Shooter was
Situation
Racist
Conspiracy to cover up
Crimes being done by non-white people
Racist rope that was really inappropriate turns out it was
Just self
Sure sure sure
That'll be the new narrative
Pizza
Defense argument cookies
White guy was in the Army and his right-wing beliefs
You know it's
To see Alex released
Supporting a member of the United States military murdering us
You know that wouldn't have done that I'm sure you would feel the same way
Right-wing beliefs
Probably
False
False flag event
Right now
Communist forces that
In the soros-funded Democrat Party
Assaults on
Police stations in federal buildings tonight
Across the United States
And when the Austin Police
Photos and video of this
To the mayor's office
I've seen the photos I've seen
This is happening
Sure
Didn't
Are you sure
Yep
I do like the image of this cop like walk
Going into the mayor's office
You stare down these are our communist
Really imagine of kicking
You sir
Pledge of Allegiance 12 taking off his badge
Setting it on the desk
Don't mess with tech
Exit
The nonsense
So I guess I'll stop.
Information
And apparently everyone else has got it to all the other media has gotten this
And the rest
Blown up in the official City Council
Budget
The controlled demolition
As a symbol of stopping police
So I mean is there probably saying blow the police station
What do you think's going on so there's going to be a back to Blue
Demonstration this Saturday in Savannah
Desiree yelling
I don't want to go it overshadow it because it's not my ass
I don't overshadow this by showing up in a tank could call Alex
Could call you dick
I do love you images
Presented like the city council
Decided
With a controller
Tastes like soda
Leatherman Style
Manor mushroom
Ovaries
Realizing
We talked about that
Episode
Me too I get to Deep
Can do that again
Alex explains the cities that are going to
Be targeted
5S antifa
Write all about
This is the time for all good men and women to come to the aid of their country
Are you around the country here in Milwaukee
Austin Texas
Phoenix Arizona
Or you are in Los Angeles California
In Miami
Phoenix
These are some of the towns
Police station
Saturday night
Behaviorism future baby
Past performance is the most indicative of future Behavior
I mean
If Alex wants of the standard
Past behavior is indicative of future
Performance
Sloppy
Pretty bad
Indicator of future
Station
He's burned down over the weekend
So that's actually kind of
This shows
How good Alex
Because like he not only stopped
The Takeover of Austin
Phoenix Countrywide Minneapolis
I think he probably meant
You stopped
All of the places from apprisen
I-41
Obviously
The communist
Soros / Gators
Influence in seven states
Embalming
Well done
Hibiscus is big
Big narrative
Forever
To figure out what
What he was talkin
About what
But
For now
Because on Friday was also an ounce
That's a lot of those deal and Maxwell documents we're going
How to be really nice
My big position on this that I want to really stress
Is that
I don't respect
Alex is coverage of the eps
16 story and I refuse to dignify it with
Any actual discussion
Because I find what he does is Sodus tasteful and disgusting
And I don't care
What is the dictionary
It will never be valid
And it will never be
Any kind of
Information
Betty actual source
Could not provide for you
I'm just
I don't care
B
Leave it there is something
Thing that comes up
That is
It's a big swing
Is he still going with
Yes
Yeah right
Alright whatever
Alright Tom Brady's wife
Comment on these FBI documents
Positivesingles Coronavirus
Obama running
All of it
Golf Course
Obscene heated know ghislaine Maxwell arrested
Oh did it fly when we go to war with China
You really don't want Trump wishing you well
Wishing you well
Didn't Trump wish you well
Yeah Trump wish Alex and Rodger Stone both well yeah
Consistent
I love the idea that he's now trying to build into the narrative
Because he was
Confidential
Grizzly original outside Jeffrey Epstein
Jeffrey Epstein
Everybody knows everybody knows it
Papers
To get a
Price
What else you want to claim that Trump
Why not just shoot
We never would have gone to the Moon if it weren't for
Trump when he was 18 years old
Forrest Gump
Every geopolitical thing right
Believe Steve on his b*******
Why not just believe the trumpet literally did everything
Comes into the studio
He's been working on
That is
Pressing
Stories.com
Salazar story
Camp Dimock CDC stats
Robert Kardashian
Haven
Get this information
Doctors Hospital
Found six months ago 5 months ago with true
They're counting on the flu deaths you name it in the same column
Problems here you have sensation to go over this
The Starchild Arizona with walk through this
So I walk through this to make some graphs
The show that flute
In a couple States
You sure these tracks
Flute
Covid death
Drawer
The Crux of this is that the grass appear to show that it's going down
We're going up
These graphs
Approve
Also there's one essential problem with them but Alex staunchly refuses to address drowning
Might as well
Issue is that
Destiny States all go down around the same time
And that's because the grass show the
The end of flu season
Presented honestly
Distributions from
Past years
We did end up revealing that the
Trajectory
Blue Datsun the 2019 2020 season is
Wheatley normal
You would expect to see flu deaths peeking around week 10 to 12-year
And then drop
From there which is what
You see in Alex's G
This is completely normal
Compared to past year are you saying that maybe the
Does cherry-picked information
Isn't that so
Pictures of wrong word
Misrepresented
Fraudulently presented drafts
Because that's the other
Big problem is there access
If you just take these grams to visually these lines might appear to match up
Really well
But when you look
The scale differences
Big problem comes
Take for instance there is a chart from Arizona
It appears to show they
Between weeks
12 + 6
Speed of 20
And because of the scale of these lines they appear to
To track almost identical
Whatever
The lines are being misrepresented
In that timeframe the flu that's went from about
15 whereas the covid-19 rose 29
I don't know what that Rose tonight
From because there's also a hole in the line on the grass
Covid deaths
Okay great another issue but the numbers are so far off from being explanatory
Manipulated
Make it look like
Like 121 like
Is it the same as the fall
Statistical game
Yeah
This problem runs through all of their grass
They do this really dicey kind of game with data Miss representation
And the fact that they don't mention the flu deaths are going down
Has flu season
And the fact that they don't
Autograph of New York
The highest number of covid-19 deaths
That's during flu season
He's all combined to create a lot of issues that Alex needs to address before any of this could be taken seriously
Can covet itself sue for defamation
Keep some respect on my name
Probably right
To remain anonymous
Doubting yourself is a person behind it
Way to clear
How willing you are to
Create bulshit graphs
For money
Roberts first edition
D give you another clue
Position
Grace
Great stuff
Another Studio
After this is Rob.
Incompetently presents this information
Holyshit
I mean we've heard it before he's been on in the past
Any he's not really
Nonsense
He
He's
Full of life
Alex
Basically
Like you can
Deal Alex
Becoming Envy
Invigorated
Welcome back I'm Alex Jones your house del bigtree is a very renowned award-winning
Journalist
I think it hurt you
So you got the four here you're on fire
We're so honored a an awesome thank you
Whether he's on fire
He's on he's on fire
The two of them are in a situation where they both have
Identical anti-vax narrative are just like.
It's hard to listen to
One thing they seem to disagree about
Gates Bill Gates position in all of this
Now he's been The Mastermind
The Council of twelve
Joel skousen came in the other day and said
You the middle manager
Kind of threw a little bit of a curveball for Alex
I don't think
It's like somebody got a gun
Pleiku what why are they doing this that's the case I don't know I don't know
I have Silicon Valley and I have the medical establishment
World
1 minutes going to kill us
So I
Guess
Childsup
Del bigtree about that
I don't I don't know anymore.
We got counsel at 12 we got middle manager and we got
Those are the Four Tops
Insofar
Okay gotcha
Who knows
B of A conversation
Anti-vax bulshit
And I don't even respect Alex's
Stuff about
I really don't respect
Olivia
Goliath
Bigger things we've already
Talked about a lot of narrative
I already in the past and it's just like
It's exhausting to go over it over and over again
There is one moment
But I think it's so illuminate
For the wrong reasons
In Bentonville big
Trees
You tell the story and I really think it sends
Wrong message
But I think
It sounds exactly
Like the message of the feeling I have
About people like him
What's a quick story
I would walk to school everyday with my my sister
T-shirt
Pliers
And he lives right next door to the school self
Call Tisa from him
Next day I like
I was homeschooled children
Share with somebody else thinks
In that story Dell thinks that he's telling a story about how he learned to stand up for his own
Which is why he won't back down from censorship
For his auntie back
Bulshit
However a closer examination of that story
Doesn't make
In the story he has a shirt that you like
Light switches
His friend tells him look
In response to this influence from his
A Dell decides to
Before going to school
When his mother finds out about this
She takes him out of school and put
Put cement homeschool like a responsible parent do this is not a story about Rising above
The influence of your peers
It's a story about running away from it
So you never have to
Front back
Countervailing Force
The good version of the story is an amp
Aesthetic mother telling Middle School
Decide
Back to school the next day with
Shirt on
And you know what
Liking the shirt
Something like that
That's how the narrative Arc of learning
Recumbent negative influence of others
Storytelling
Feel like ones up with no more wire
Singers like that's where we're at in this kind of situation
Here's how this story were
Do received some influence from appear
Which he succumbed
When his mother found out she
Changing his shirt
School thereby isolating Dell from having to regularly deal with the challenges of
Influences from his beard
Instead of helping her child recognize that his opinions and taste are valid
Regardless of whether or not people agree
Laterally remove Dell from the situation in
Artificial
Controlled environment
Where he won't have to
Make those tough choices anymore
Is Mother basically created
Bubbles
Instead of teaching him to validate his own feelings about the shirt
Even if not everyone agreed that it was cool shirt
On a certain level
This is actually a purple
Analogy for Wood Dale
Victory is done as a career
He's a
Text bulshit doesn't stand up to the scrutiny of actual science in the standards mainstream reporting
So he's metaphorically put himself in homeschool
Thanks to millions of dollars from anti-vax
Donors like
Bernard sales
An insulated bubble where is ideas
Compete with the influence
A metaphorical shirts sucks
He has his own safe space where he can wear his metaphorical shirt
In the privacy of his homeschool media operation
A company's vanquished
Risen above outside
When in reality all he's done is run away from it and hide
I love the idea that he's telling the story that he is
Completely
Send Skype message
Do what he does now as an adult
Know all of the all of the child true story
Stories tell like
Well that's one piece of the puzzle and how f*****-up you
Tapestry
Yeah I don't even
Desty I don't even hear from that
Story like granted I have no idea what his wife
Was like but like
I didn't hear that story hit mix
Expressing
He was distraught about his friend not liking his sure it seemed like it was
Is all his mom's response
I feel like
Better into that story is
He's taken away from his mom
I don't know I mean will be traumatic
I don't know
It's weird anyway
From social influences
Forever
Do you know you just got over it
I've decided
To believe that Andrew Wakefield is the best doctor in the world
You're just put myself in that bubble where that makes sense
I nobody
So
The rest of this is
Victory just like having a
Jolly time
First Alex does a 2-hour emergency report
Saturday August 1st 2020
So again
It's the same
Decide
Where am I
Show
Expecting something
Think big to happen
And it
It happened
I'm not sure he's expecting to happen during his show
It's more of like
Created a really intense narrative
And there's also a 10 date on when
I will have stopped that picture of that burning while it's an active
He starts this off with like almost
The 5-minute long clip from Road Warrior
Strange choice
Lord humongous
Do you want their children
If not
The city has announced they're going to blow up the PlayStation
Tonight tonight
Goodnight
Explosion
Tonight
Boston has changed the name of the police station 24
Sumpter
So then their plans plans
But there's other
Important information
And this is probably one of the most
Unimpeachable of the
Call
Wife
Tennis partner this morning
She was at Whole Foods in downtown Austin at 8
A.m.
150 antifa
We're out there with guns in the parking lot
So if there was 150 people this morning
The text came in at like 8
Ken
Can you imagine
What's going to be tonight cuz they pledge
We're going to take over the police station
City councilwoman but it involves defund the police
Courthouse
So
Hanging out at Whole Foods
Call the Prout
She's lazy or something but it's like I
To getting tear-gassed you can sleep till noon
How regularly Alex will have Intel from his wife
The various friends
Her tennis partner called me
By my wife's
Dubai information
I mean
Alex
Realistic Alex out of the equation
Anybody across any kind of
Respectable news
Spectrum
I have all the authority of my wife
It's embarrassing
Even if it's not Alex does he have any
Corroborating evidence
From his wife from his wife
Yes
Play trip
Play Triple J
150m
50 Triple T
Round robin
I like it we're playing three or four dimensional golf
Perfect
TNT
So I'm Alex's just rambling around about house
Everything and if you're white you need to be scared
You seen the footage in Utah
Colorado
New York
California
Or somebody
St.Louis
Are you for black lives matter yes but I believe all lies
Mama
Your dad
Because she was white
And because she didn't bow down to this racist ideology
Even remember any of the detail guys today
Years old he doesn't remember her name was
Jessica Whitaker
Never cared
St Louis McCloskey a couple pointing guns at protesters
Just all like trying to make white people
Scared details of everything that happened
Is even made up
So in this next clip
Sing about
Going to take over everything
And this is where I was able to sort of get in a little bit
Figure out here we go
Infowars.com Austin Police warn antifa BLM planning
Shooting downtown
We show you
A public document
My major
Manager company
CNBC
Apartments
They were told by
Is taking the roof with guns in their buildings and list
That's where they're going to be
This article and
Does two major pieces of information that Alex's basin
Astoria
And the first thing I want to point out is that Alex gave the wrong name to that man
Asthma company
It's Nazi ND
DC
It's hard to tell
If it be not because he can't read or because he's trying to make details harder to track down
CNBC and then
Who knows
This is the Guadalupe neighborhood development
Corporation has just posted
The screenshot of what appears to be a letter from the gndc to
Lieutenant
Asking them to report any suspicious activity because
People coming to Austin tomorrow may be armed and have plans to get on top
Buildings along the ice
Frontage Road
This weather
Steven Rios
There's no mention of antifa or anything else
Could be anything the only one group
People historical
Play who have the
The training
And the necessary to get on top of rooftops
Endoscope
So this brings us to the second piece of information that's in that article.
The other part of this
Really comes from a face
The Texas state gorillas militia
Which is supposedly a left-wing militia
Interesting Lee if you try to Google that name there's no search results
What's up other than message boards from like a day ago and
Trysting if you go look at the Facebook
DuPage it's pretty clear
This is not Alexa
Militia
At least one of the admins of this group has
Explicit Boogaloo iconography and
His profile picture
Includes at least two people pictured wearing skull mask
Switch is a look
It is regularly Associated that sort of community
The Facebook group is
Is private you can still tell certain things about it if you're not a member
It was created by the month
Which is a little bit weird
The other things you can tell
Private
Admin Pages aren't all private
You just created
It's really hard to determine how much of the stuff on their use
Like seriously
Is it the Facebook page
Pictures he chooses to post
Speaker to send to the guy
He's a big
Fan of guns
Pictures of him with guns
There's a weird picture that
Because white women are into black men because they have bigger dicks
Sounds historically like something I've heard
So okay
Is that okay
Just come up with that himself I'm sure there's no historical
Corollary for that exact
Narrative right
No
Memes in August
Igloo related me
Sure the second person to become an admin in this Texas State Gorillaz
Which is obviously a fake
Post
But almost related
It goes on and on like
It says you look at the members of the group
Profiles
This is not so much
Presented as much as it is a Boogaloo
The group
I have no idea has any validity
Which is what
The conjecture is
Because it's a private group
I'm not joining it and Alex doesn't have any proof
And we don't recommend people try
I wouldn't
Austin Police Department
Guadalupe neighborhood group
This ultimately could be a situation where there is an underlying
Storied namely that a subset of
The acceleration is the Boogaloo type
Current social climate
To trigger some violin
But
Even that
Substantiate
I'm not saying
Possibility
Even if that is the truth and story Alex's
We'd be misrepresenting it to be some kind of an antifa black lives matter
As opposed to being a group of
Absolutely
If Only They were a little bit more universally race
It's interesting to me because
He was presented The Story So vaguely
Take over police stations and others
I didn't see any evidence
To that
Maybe that's in the
Good Facebook group.
I can't see I don't
Don't know
And he's trying to present it as
Antifa Soros fund
It's like 100 people
What group
A cheat for Sora
You know that's
If you're paying that yet
Maybe
Max for 100 people
Facebook group
5 G
Thesaurus
Explodes
So Alex touches back on the story of the Doctor Who super into Hydrox
Who also believes that people are having sex with humans in their sleep and what have you
Imallexx
She's being attacked
Because she's a Christian
In the process
Kind
Is light as that people have sex with humans in their sleep
They keep my
Okay
2 + 2
Crazy Christian lady
Gee thanks
Solon made it with aliens
And so she's crazy at the very establishment believes that
Hold on
Are you going to read the Bible that says that
100% battery
Big thing that matters
Leaves
The Bible is about alien DNA
Some human cells have alien cells and that damn
The Bible says the Earth was
Preceded by viral RNA from
The directions
Miguel
What led
Too busy
Del bigtree
With stats
Yes we are commercial free on this August 1st
Saturday
Eversource
Bunch of lunch with Tom Clancy
Psychological operations State Department the CIA in a bunch of other Groves
Is Right Patriot always appreciated in size 10 most accurate smart people know
Now hear you're making a weird face
I think Alex is right
Okay
Okay I will compute that
Everyone else is wrong all the time
Steve's wrong all the time to entertain
Alicia Reeves
Briefings from Stratford
There's something
Rap status
Slip-up
In this interview
But I think our kind of telling
He's at the beginning
Steve
Start
Loses his train of thought
How to do a second
Take
This
Complains to me
Steve might be working off a little bit of a
19 is just a variation of a virus
That we've had for over 60 years
You cured me to fix a spike
It is a highly
19 is just a variation of a virus that we've had for over 60 years
It's a spider
It is a highly
Virus which can
Attack someone but
We had to do two takes there
Basically the exact
Austin's is train of thought
Everybody down here I just wanted to jump into correct myself a tiny bit here
After recording the episode I went back and I watch the video
Of this from Alex's show
And this is not actually an instance of Steve pieczenik saying this twice
Though it sounded
A lot like it if you were listening to it I went and watched
The video
And it is actually a weird editing
Nothing vet Infowars screwed up
I don't know how they did this it is not I've never seen it before
But they just
Played Steve saying this twice
I have no idea why
I apologize if that slipped passed me
Anyway I was wrong I made an assumption that Steve was reading the same thing twice when in reality was
Play never-before-seen of very weird
I think we're in Fort Worth played the same audio twice
No reason video plays twice
Just a tiny little
I've no idea who I can't explain it
Are we back to the show
Probably even leave that aside for a moment is it weren't for the other slip up
That happens
That I think he's being fed
Information
Remember that
He cured himself of copas
OK Google
There's a problem
So Trump has been 90
China virus
Happy quotes
Did the Chinese
Cuz Alex Isabel
Steve
Kind of completely
Fox Veterinary
Ironically didn't really come from
And fauci never understood it it really came out of Northern Italy
Tony has never understood the underlying dynamics of a vaccine
So apparently according to Steve
This came out of Northern Italy
Ruins everything
All right if that's true
If Steve is a lie
Right
Inaccurate people you could be talkin anyway possible
Everything Alex has built up about
Is wrong
Conspiracy
60 years old it's a variation
Tony fauci doesn't even understand pyrometer
He wasn't involved in
Bio weapon
Without
Why not you know Hillary visited Northern
Confident
Who's Steve the shape
The geopolitical landscape government
Putting l
Total every single
Certain person
In the world
I did with him at some
Itsfunneh
When
Steve
Accuses
Tony fauci
Of using hyperbole
Unfortunately I'm working Tony was my teacher
Medical doctor Cornell University Medical
What you see is what I said 425 months ago
He is Jesuit rain is narcissistic
He has hyperbole
Really made a medical mistake
You should never recommended
When you said what
Cornel Wilde
They probably would have overlap
Reese
Deserve
Cuz like this guy is a braggart
This guy is an a******
Also I
Self I was the first person to cure my also also
Anti
I'm Jack Ryan and
Every war of my lifetime
He helped kill the Italian Prime Minister
About that parts
Zoe
We get to talk in about like what's wrong with Trump
Because Alex is like
Wants to people who give him like really tough talk yes
This
It's not what I asked
Did you hear about
Policy but not with who he hires
Carlson told me privately
Just travel to his enemies
The fire somebody in front of them
He doesn't indirectly I see count responses like
And they can never confront somebody directly
How much are remind Steve at
Which phrase was
You're fired
Like in real life
Oru
Sure know if that's actually true or not
The narrative
Worked in the administration like
Not you're being fired indirectly or call me hearing on TV
Step down
Fun about Steve's
Is that it
Also recognition
Trump satire
Persona is fake
Is b*******
So wait are you telling me that his reality TV show
Donna was sold to us
Was as his actual person
Soda during the campaign
You think they were electing one
Where's the smart business leader
Like a big
Of course
So that's fun
Trumpcare Fire Pizza
Get the guy out of there
To the point of being ineffectual
Probably
Leader known bosses like that
And I think
Give them highly is that what you think they should be proud
End
I'm coming in
You know Biden
Is the other choice
And it turns out that Steve
Isn't big on voting
I need a stronger president than Trump
That's it
They will be no
Community
I'm saying what I mean
That's not funny
He is
Super enchi
Justin election
I'm telling the people in the
Community that a Biden president
Any kind of power
Perspective
And the position that he has
Deeply
Deeply authoritarian
To Blackmail the president
Into getting rid of Alexa
What you got to do
You got to get Larry Nichols and Larry flew too close to the Sun he's not welcome back
Doesn't seem
Because now would be a good time
A nickels
Yeah I don't know
I have it
I got my sources.
They gave me the pee tape
Ali choto paid my mailbox
Where's the guy bringing telling us that Reagan had a video of him getting paid
Where was
Yeah but he
I mean metaphor I like
That guy
And said that he had
Peg
It wasn't like they were trying to take down Reg
That was a no
Right
Completely unrelated conversation
I could use a non sequitur
The champ come
So Steve is one of these guys who
Since a lot of really bad
Things
A sort of casually like
Regardless
Black yeah yeah why you saying that
Soros
Surat
Knotweed
Does Melissa live
There's a lot of stuff that makes me think
You're a real big
And this is one of those instant
Is here
Georgetown
Goes into the Lincoln project another idiot Outpost
It makes Kia says the Trump is not
Narcissistic
We got one
Yeah I mean like why do you have to point out the Gorge
Conway
I mean you got to toss them in there
Most people who are half
I don't know
Anything other than whites how is it at all relevant
To any conversation as we all know
Send have never served
I mean that's just
Sorts of ticks are really out of
So
People
More telling
What needs
To be done
And
Because
He may have
The different view of America in a lot of people
What do we the people do the folks that do care about their family
What do we do
Into the street they protest and they say we want change and we want to get rid of our tongue
And we need to have
Financial
Program more than anything America
Is a business entity
More than anything else
We are business entity
Did you know 80s
Refreshing to hear it
Underlying
So much of this right-wing
The Richard like
The Constitution matters
Is a business proposition for that
It's refreshing
To hear somebody just come out and be like
I want to oppress away but I water quality
We talkin about
We the People
No
Business the people my friend
Crying about the blood is
Government source
Steve pieczenik
Business
Cookie with yours is equality and Liberty
Tell me about any kind of
Founding
For the United States of America even considers those things
I hate to do this to
Centro Bus
Because suggest
That
Is 2 week
To kill his opponent
Here's where there's another slip-up
Steve
Obviously
Mfu globalist ended up
Avocado accidents I'm not calling for this cuz you'll get called in federal court still alive
You know we're serious I'm doing myself I'm just saying
Revolution
George Washington
We'll just go after a few of these guys Abraham Lincoln wouldn't all be over
I mean
I guess the Pentagon is all too I may just actually go after a few people you took money for the Chinese and you're a traitor
Well you don't they take a dirt nap
If in a few of these people got trouble all the wrestler turn around there's a bunch of wimps but we have to hang out here under attack
We have to deal with all the physical threat
Which I'm happy to do and then no one else ever makes them pay as what I'm saying
Wilbur Ross
Here's what you have to do
Two men are who I do respect
Steve mnuchin who understands money
And distribution of money and Wilbur Ross
Steve
Is there with him
She's like Googling
Yeah that you should not have let her come on
Wilbur Ross
He needed her to feed the name but he's going to put into his next next paragraph
It's interesting
The business entity
Fine with being a
A traitor to a busy
This entity
Especially when the business
Exploit
Are we the shareholders of that business
If you're in Shaler
You get some sort of lip
Oh boy
Another time that Steve has slipped
Much like
Bring up that Steve Conway's half-filipino
Complaining about that
The Frontline saying about Alex
Why do they film conspiracy so much
Trump's bad Elizabeth piercings
That's how the real world
Listen to that show was so idiotic
First
What an amazing flaming individual but more importantly they said
He was a CIA intern
Really no kidding
I don't know
Number one
Steve can't talk about people who are not
White screen
Not be a big
Can't not do it
It's just impossible
And then I don't even remember Anderson Cooper being in
The documentary outside of archival footage of him
Like I think there's footage
Give him interviewing
One of the Sandy Hook
Parents
Okay prom like
Around that time
I don't remember him being a talking head in the documentary I don't under I don't know what
Existing at all
Very angry
Just in the documentary in the background
Hey Ivy was part of the CIA bums me out because they never get
They never get
Alright so if you were living in Steve pieczenik lily-white
World
Chisholm
Then he's just going to be a bigot towards
Oh yeah he's Italian he's going to do he's going to just be a
Bigger towards whomever
Confine
That's me
Exclusionary thinking
Is that you
You end up
With definition
Become
Smaller and smaller
If you end up with the white nationalist you'll end up then with a
The separatist
Community
Or whatever.
Puppy weasel
Just for being
Never realize on real reason
The reasons are forced
Artificial unmade
They can be forced artificially made up about any
Arbitrary distinction that you want to make
Because
Beans
You know moves towards exclusion are always
Make up for something else
Excuse for why the economy isn't
Could be why is there crime
Olivia
You want
To exclude people because it solves some other issues
It's not related
You have to understand that
Your way and then
Again another group of people
Yeah of course Steve will never be satisfied with whatever
It's joining its joining Stalin
Politburo
Like you got it
It's not going to you're not going to be in that pic
Picture later on
The issue for
Steve right now though
There's no leader
For his size
L
But according to Steve he installed Trump
The president's so
There's no l
But unfortunately you have f***** up then because you install
You're not going to
We haven't
Absence of leadership
Power
Country
The conservative movement
Which I think is
Justin American movement
Bactrim
What's supposed to be that leader but what you hear
I mean honestly I
Together
And bringing Melania to be your vice president
And you do
Calm down and start firing
Assistance
Another
To not know what we wanted the guy we saw 4 years ago
Does his wife know that Steve has a boner for Melania never heard him
Like
Without mentioning how Melania should be more important
That's that's not that's not
Number of times that he hasn't brought up
Melania's great
Vice president
I would say
Staff around me
Depressed of the National Security Council
Well
That's the point that's what I need I don't either in the front
I just needed a critical mass for her to implement what's required
And override a lot of what Trump is doing
Why is
Happening
It makes sense
Because we've met
Here's the deal
Alright
Clearly they believe Trump is a fake
And clearly Trump is absolutely not the thing that they believe
They made it all up
Shirley Malone
To feel better about
Obviously
And even they can
Can a boy.
Yeah pick a new person to make up s*** about
Play Muse right there and see wants to f***
Solovar
Oliver power fantasies on
It's weird
Consistent thing where you seems to want to
Install Melania in
I don't know I don't know how much I feel confident
About
This
You know in the same way you feel like you get these reveals the things that are going on while Steve's having an interview like his wife Google and stuff
The ruins of the side
America's like this
Insistent
Tissue slide
We need to make
Melania the shadow president
I'm not sure I trust you as
Like a crafty Mastermind either
I don't I don't know
I don't know if
Your plans are good
Is it like
Maybe
Okay maybe I'll throw this out
Alright let me toss this out
I think he's creating
An alternate universe
Clinton
Do you know what I mean
Like he's thinking Trump is your bill
So it makes sense that
FIFA boomiverse
President
I think I see
Think you're probably right that there's some of that projection
Entirely unconscious that's
Possible but it does have that
Feel of like
Either
Creating their own
We don't like they thought Obama was a dick
You know they thought Bill Clinton was his wife
So now they're saying that Melania should have that
Yeah
Maybe Alex
You know hey man
You're at your psychiatrist
Neuropsychology
Tell me
What's going on
I just remembered
You're not allowed to diagnose people
Opposed
Medical doctor
He's already there he was I I said it 6 months ago
Real quick
Being senile dementia
I don't
I don't belong to the APA quickly so where is he in a month
He's exactly where he is
Basically
I'm not knowing where he is
That's one of my favorite things because like
From Spotify
Resume
Ended because I diagnosed
Bush from afar
There is that I was at exactly
I bet have to alleviate
You stand up for your collection
Steve
We had some parting words
This is bad advice
Start going back to an ordinary life
And forget about the Coronavirus
If you got a problem go with your pharmacist a doctor
And I will handle it
The numbers for New York
Forget the TV
And go on with your lies and create a lot of local don't believe that
Steve's
Pretend this isn't real
This isn't happening
Like here's the
F***** up part
This is this is almost there
50 bucks down
Here's what
Almost certainly going to
It's going to double get worse
We're going to get a vaccine
The people who take the vaccine are going to be okay
The people who refuse to take the vaccine are large enough and number that when they start dying
They're going to claim that we're killing them
Because we
The vaccine that it wasn't real and that we're just killing them anyways
And because they're going to continue spreading it
It's entirely possible that
Mutate in the f****** backseat
Second
Tino come
You know you end up with a certain amount of folks are just
Going to have negative
Reactions to medications
People like Alex
Sewer anti-vax
Swell
Use those in
Instances of inevitable
Complications
They were right all along
I don't know I
Hypothetical
Vaccines
I don't I don't I don't know about that
Thresholds of how many
Vaccine would be
No problem
I don't know I can't I can't really speculate on that
Steve leaves
Gets back to his story about antifa that he's lying about
Information
It reveals that this is not a black lives matter
Antifa group
The Boogaloo group
I'm going to check these lights this is
Mine on Facebook it was real people
Intel Leroy Jenkins group known as Boogaloo
That's a fake cut out right way
ATL run
Advising about body armor and weapons the group
About 9
Farm people
Officer safety Bungalow safety Gutierrez
If we're at other people related devices
Another suspect advised have
Spray paint
Charges
Nfib
Was whatever that is
Whatever
Information is supposedly from
Police
Misinformation
Kitchen towels
Is that that Leroy
This Facebook group
And some of the other names that he read offer also the admins
Because he's reading this out
It's very clear that
Whatever is supposed
Then
It's still Alex so I have no idea of any of this information is even accurate
Assuming
Just told him that there is
Group that this is this Facebook
Book group
Betty's Boogaloo
Decent door inspired
And
Have some
Plants
And because Alex
Knows enough to know that word means something
He has to say that it's
The fake cut
It's 8.
Just running cover
Like there's no
He knows what he's doing
He is trying to make a
Get so no matter what
The Boogaloo move
What does doesn't come back on
Space here towards the end of the Saturday show where he's like man
Talk show host
Hard
I mean killing love with me so much easier to talk show
Play around me
It's so much easier to
Would it be not going to do that
But you keep starting your fights
Your
Dad
And the police know and the public knows and the military knows everyone sick of you
You won't back off you won't
You won't stop messing with constantly
You're going to make us
How's your eyeballs out
And you know it
Alright man
I honestly think
Alex's
Lazy enough
That if it were actually easier
He would
Oblique
Yeah
Could be easier than doing his show the way she doesn't
So sloppy and so bad
Devoid of
Crafts
You don't even need to be good at your job you spend the first 10 minutes of every show saying that you can't even
Watching some of the road warrior
Bruno Just
Hard it is to do his job
Please consider this is August
First
You know I said that the
Christmas in July within yesterday and it will end by tomorrow
Special yet
Double Patriot Point still available
He can't even do this
Christmas in July high in the first place
Definitely shouldn't
Yeah he's bad at everything
Do the same sale just make up a
Christmas in August
F****** just do it
Jesus in August sale
No way
Men's Day in August
That I'm glad didn't accidentally end up in any violence
The best of my knowledge
Who knows
Yeah I mean playing with fire the way he did this whole broadcast about
Tonight and tomorrow
Planning to blow up
These police stations all around
Country
All this death
That's really risking the possibility of someone hurting somebody based on that recording
And
Little bit further
You see the sources that he's relying on
And you see well what it is
Here's to be about is not all around the country
It appears to be one
Group
Is run by some
Who may or may not have
Been planning
Something
It's unclear
You know and he's taking the bath
Hispanic
Extent
Like that's really fun
Walking dangerous
Pretty scary
That's pretty scary
And then
They're coming for your town neck
B11 antifa there going to be
F****** bum
F*** Idaho any moment now
And what do you have
When you have like that
At the end there when you talk
You know killing people be so much easier than doing this talk show and you could
To do this
Restart to realize
You keep pushing us is fake stories
Really keep pushing you and I keep pushing you guys haven't actually murdered anybody yet
It becomes clear that this is almost like a self
Perpetuating cycle that he's trying to
Trying to antagonize and empty
I mean
It's hard not to say that he is I mean after you know he's covering for the Boogaloo movement movement
And he's
Actively
Encouraging his own audience
To essentially start the Boogaloo movement on their own
South
I think we know what
What kind of movement
Episode
I would have rather spent like two hours talking
About that story to tell
Revealing thing
Except
I'm actually not involved
APA stock
Protection Agency
Bradshaw for the WWF in 1999
Used to gamble with them backstage Bradshaw
Being Tucson I don't know
Back button
Also on Twitter
We are
World salon
And help out those doing God's work right now
Melania Trump
Shadow chief of staff
Thanks for holding
Alex