I have great respect for knowledge by now I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Dot-com
Fix it around a little bit
Jordan Jordan
What's up
The grocery store grocery store
Looking for some jalapeno
And I look what did my little eye spy
That sounds very
Very uncommon grocery stores
Some Carolina Reapers straight-up Carolina Reaper
Sauce or like
I got them a quiet side
Course what's Amana on a Pizza Hut
Pretty serious
Jim Bishop
I don't really like me
I'm putting a really hot
Casually in nolita
I I should know.
Very very hot
Do some experience
Afterwards
You know I'm not being gross
Torso
Weirdly tight or something going on inside me
So it's like one of those what are those stimpak
Machine stomach muscles
It was wild
But
Would you be
I drank the iced tea this week
Here last night or the other day
Had to charge it last night after eating a Carolina Reaper
Necessitate
Arnold Palmer emergency
The first thing I saw it when I opened the fridge and just
Some ridiculous
My brakes is a piece of information that I discovered in my preparation for
Imagine
Event of the century
Which is my debate with Rand Paul
Oh she is still tragically refusing to use
100 holiday
I am just going to bother his social media manager
Call Heather
Totally confirm 100% confirmed by the person who was kidnapped
This is
YouTube Jordan early
Other
Anti-Semitic
Secret society
He and a friend kidnapped a woman
Broken Door dorm room
Blindfold her up took her to a second location
Told her that she had to do bong hit
She had to
Nice you did
And then they just took her to a river and told her to pray to Aqua Buddha
And that's the end of the story
Right
That's an interesting story I don't know how this is going
To entice him to debate you okay
Navigate kidnapper e14
Responsible
Rihanna
Accept your challenge
Each other we may have
Third and fourth 2020
Fourth 2020
Is
A
F****** Trainwreck
Eagle guys asteron
Levels
From a Galaxy's out-of-control kind of perspective or anything like that
It is just a
Wolfman
Innocence
You're not doing the job anymore I like it
Yeah and I'm excited to get down to business
Starting to show
So first we got to Bonnie why are they
Dave
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks Michael H
Libi thank you so much
I do Levy thank you next
I'm a policy wonk
Who donated on elevated
The first of all Michael
Combined
And Andrew K thank you so much
You're now a technocrat
We got to go Full Tilt Boogie on this
What's the business
Heroin
Large
Andrew k
Jordan
Damn Jordan
Yeah or you could take that
Generosity
Terraria
Stop.
Today Show
I need a t-shirt
Play button for no.
Okay
Flash Forward
26 months from now Alex's cell
I feel like
He's going to be like I don't
Better
So we we start on the 3rd here on Monday
And Alex
In advance
In no way takes responsibility for stopping the antifa attacks that were alleged
Supposed to bring up that they didn't happen
That seems really important to at least Menchie's
Days building up a narrative about how it was going to take over police station
Exaggerations
From a blue Facebook group group worth getting
Yeah anyway that all
Google Dowden know Wheatley
He's going to remove
Computer chip from someone
No no you going to start
Akash
I thought about doing a podcast once a week for I don't speak
From my own analysis the world but where I only High
Highlight articles
That the podcast reading different sections of articles
Video clips
To do that I didn't want your podcast to
The show we know we know you intend to do that even tend to do that for
About the amount of time
What was
Audiobook of the news was that it
I'm going to do a show where I just read that
And that's
Different
Because it wouldn't have the parts where you scream
It wouldn't
It was
Undoubtedly
Just stop there
Only knows how to do one
In honor of this idea for this podcast that he has
I'm just going to read headlines for the rest of the second
A lot of things that are important to be done
Because their fastest of the show I've always wanted to do that I've never had the will to do
What's today
Relieved
5 minutes left
Headlight
He ends up making it I mean he does
Frequently interject with his own analysis
Outside like
Okay what have you proved
He can do it and you can just
Completely disjointed
Connected headlight yes
What do you need it for
Man it's bad it's really bad it is
You can tell the audio's a little bit we
Call Mandi background
Something something is not quite right disconnected
Because of the way Alex's mom
Connect to make sense
You can feel him having trouble just reading a bunch of headlines
Stories he hasn't read
Audio formats
Miserable
The impulse
To be like this is all about the same thing
So I found it Rob do incompetent deposition experts
Incompetent news director real weirdo
Drunk
C-pack
Do you have anything nice to say
Drunk at CPAC
He's hired
Idea of the
Going up windshield
Let's go down
Overhears condemning CDC stats show flu death drop
Increase
Number
Every state following NIH guidelines
Weather
Headline
I don't know what
To prove
It's it's interesting to me because I would have to either know that he's lying
Or he has to have been
Tricked by the scale manipulation the grass are presented in
The show
Glee identical Rises installed the same number of people there
It's all out of
Somehow I feel like it
You know like he knows you lying
But he's been tricked by the grass so it doesn't know what
Exactly
He's lying about
Eli
I think that's an interesting possibility and here's what I would say
Like because we can't be certain
It's either a lie or he's so hopeless
And lost
He's helpless
That's what I mean
Galatians of things like an image
Right you just doesn't even doesn't know where he's at either way
Rockin ignore it
So here's another story this is kind of one of the big headlines about the news
Of the day and
I believe that
He got this just from a Gateway pundit
Headline
It's really dumb
And gay or holding
Miles on how
Best to persuade
Nutbush
Quad Force
Covid-19 vaccine
Online thesaurus please and type in
Words for persuade
Force
There's a Gateway pundit article about States conducted by
What sort of messaging is most
Effective in terms of getting people to take vaccines
There are 12 different messages that they would give study participants and then they evaluate their willingness
Mystic
Yeah
The control group was given the message that was unrelated to vaccine
Just a quote
Pastor Johnny cost
And benefits
Bird feeding
There was the Baseline group straight message
Text regarding vaccine
Experimental in nature ranging from messages about personal freedom
Two messages about how embarrassing it would be to knock
Pocketbacs tomatoes
Is a pretty standard store to us or to study measuring the effectiveness of a particular type of message
Every advertising campaign does this as do politician
You're running for office
And I imagine
Probably
Any kind of public relations matter is benefited
From studying how the public generally responds to a particular sort of message
Not weird at all
Also as Alex's reporting
That this is a federal government there's no evidence
The federal government is involved in the study at all
The list of sponsors and collaborators is literally just Yale
I think what happened here is that Jim hoft over at Gateway pundit found this study on clinicaltrials.gov
And because of the. Gov website
He just decided to report that this is a federal government
And now Alex is just blindly repeating that assertion
It tells me that neither of them actually went to the study page which is very clearly says of the top
Quote the safety and scientific validity of this study
Is a responsibility to study sponsor and investigator
Listing of study does not mean that it has been evaluated by the US federal government
There's a link to a
Disclaimer that makes us even more explicit
Clinicaltrials.gov National Institutes of Health
US Federal
Not all listed studies are regulated and or reviewed by the US Food and Drug Administration or other governmental
Agencies
Information on clinicaltrials.gov is provided by study sponsors and investigators and they are responsible for ensuring
These studies follow all applicable
And regulations
MLM staff do not verify
Scientific
Of the submitted information limited quality control review
Preparing errors deficiencies and inconsistent
That's just
Nonsense the federal government
Probably probably
Assumption based on the disclaimer
Story
We just being completely misrepresented in order to make
Alex's audience that is addicted to being scared
A real problem
This is just Alex reporting on some new story he hasn't read whatever
Bulshit
Pundit now we're getting
Set it through
Does his own
Jazz
That really is is worrying
What was that Baseline
Personal freedom message
Is a
He's reading that Gateway pundit article about this study about messaging
Because he's just reading words and making up a story
He thinks that control message is a message about control
As opposed to it being the control group of the study
The same is true about the Baseline group
He sees these words and he's just reporting to his audience they mean something
Completely different than what they do
Like this
This is indicative of
Failure to recognize
Studies even on
This is an in-depth
Level of
Ignorance
Nowell if you understood how controls
And experiments
You'd be like
So you have to
Did not understand how it works in order to lie better about
About it you know what I'm saying
Like it's a pretty foolproof, do you know there
Controls
God I don't even want to address that this is embarrassing
Oh yeah it's terrifying
Even if you're somebody who loves Alex and thinks like he's great
You should know like if you've gone through High School
Control group
Are what make it
You know that's the thing that's in experiments that is in order
To test
Four variables
Like you should know that very
I'm just
He was busy fighting influences when he was in
It's staggering
It's bad but I am not
Listening to this
Reply
Just being like
He doesn't know what it can
True group and can understand
I guess I cuz they don't
Understand what
Control group
Maybe that most of these people
Don't actually understand what their talk
Like.
On a fundamental level
They don't
Lego like who's the who's the senator that just tested positive for covid
Debate me on that
Gobert
Itself gave me
You just don't understand
You got none
Alex gets
Of course my friend
My only friend
Beyond
My friends my only friends
Verilife
Plans the end
No safety
You're going to pay for submitting
So bad you better stop a bang but then you'll be so domesticated
Brains that you won't have any face but you go ahead and take the pill and kill yourself
That's where you're going and remember
Cut off cut off by the brake there
Certainly
Patriot leadership
I was thinking
At Valley Forge
George Washington
Together and he was like
Dino
Donovan's have any feet I get it
It's cold
And we're all going to die
We're all going to die
You are going to die
You're going to die
Pay for your crimes
Everyone here is going to die
Give up
Yeah we trying to fight the British to be begging for death eventually
I don't know
Sort of like
This consistent pattern.
Just keeps going
This this world like
There's a fatalism
Do it Thursday
We're already in the pesos
Yeah the globalist
Remnants
Not good
Kind of
Mid
Stage
This self-destructive Cult of Personality
He's at no point in time did he call it a divine wind it or ask
Play news
You should definitely not use
I'd like you to
On,
August seventy-year-old retired military people
Back to July
Actually I
Like I even have this quote at the ready
Alex has been talking about this
For a while
This is all been set up to make you obsolete to dehumanize you
To suck the life out of you to dumb you down
Protect your family away from you
I don't want to be part of it
Plan
About you and plan
We have
Talking about
What we're going to do
We can't just sit here
The leadership of the operation might be down the road.
Black
Is it going to start
It's been going on a much
Moreover
Certainly
In the last month
And so
I mean it doesn't
I'm thrilled about
I was just thinking about how Jesus said like how you treat the least
Diseases how you treat me
And
I feel like Alex wants to strap a bomb to the least of these
Do you know what I mean
I don't I don't
So
Sort of more
Palatable
Territory
I guess
Alex I think isn't Ancient Aliens
How old
Sumerian symbol of two snakes together
Poor
The metal
Creatures Came From Another Star
Now we work
British scientist all do this but they do to really get the knowledge in his excuse your mouth of drugs
Alien technology through Intergalactic space time
Keep going
Earth
Bring them in the Bible says in the end time
The Gates of Hell will open hell will open
Sure
Yelm
This is
Just Project Camelot stop lighter leadership
The California wildfires are a cover for
Wild
Cool Russell coming back
Coming back he was going to be in the galaxy
What's the most reliable sources and that's why I want to reach you from Erich von daniken
The Bible even says it
My next guest coming up
I think he's dead
Marion
Predate the Bible
And he's going off them
Actually meeting alien
Then that supersedes
The Bible
You know I'm saying shouldn't we be listening to the alien folks more than probably probably irrelevant
Flashbang I don't know
Okay smoked okay
And
I think just a little bit racist dance
What's going on here
Alex
Seems to have a lot of victimhood narrative has had
And leads to
The statement
Guy in the super rare event you're in some Town 2kkk that's something to you
Super rare
White person incredibly common
Credibly common event that a black person attacks you because your wife
Do statistics are then covered up
Part of the PowerPlay
Did the globalist Deep state
Plus billion people that aren't White
We convinced them to hate white people
Pull down the first world ended no one has a chance of getting out of any of this
So that's that's that's an interest
Perspective that is racist
Because they cover up any proof that you would have whatever it is that I'm
The KKK who even ever heard of them what are you talkin about
People all the time
Racist attack against the non-white person
It wasn't Clan
I believe
He is
100%
Trees are white
Yeah
Nancy Pelosi is talking about how people should get a stimulus
And
What is getting mad about
Badger
And then
Real non-sequitur on us
We need to stand up the American people
You talking about the American people by way of making sure people can
Eat
When they're paid agitator say
Snowboarders
So you are saying at all
So now Alex's implying
The Nancy Pelosi
Is funding all of the protests
Of people who largely are not fans of her
Philadelphia Police Department auction says the official budget
Telldunkin
They can blow up the police station
Going down all the statues
Money and give us their leftist organization their steezing
Fire
We'll have a new police department under our control he said it last week
Inter-Community wonderful
Didn't Somalia lady we saved you
Piston AR face go to hell
I didn't bug last hour I'm going to plug right now
Your financial support is obviously the total Zeitgeist we proven were in the center of the fight
Your financial support the spirit of the times
Weird
Yeah
Conversation
She set up the Somali and State
Isaiah child refugees
I like to imagine that
City council has like
Controlled demolition of
Derelict police station
Second nap
Also I checked into it
The preparation of this episode because earlier today Austin
Budget
Police Department
Unapproved
So Alex is talking about
Make sense
You might have
Jokes
Some people
Doesn't
Ouchie
I mean come on
I would come on
Jamaica mon
Serious an issue for me
Because their safety issues cuz you mean Bill Gates is coming accidentally vaccines that he says water doesn't kill us because we don't have a choice
Anyone coming to try to force me in oxalate you are take your job and I'll let you fly
Assaulting you
Prison for not taking her poison
So we are Crossing into an area where
The default does become violence
And the person we would talk about would be the frontman of this
Bill Gates
That's not my place
Attempts on their lives that turn them into victims affected probably going to Stage that
I don't wish any harm
Physically but their names
Should we destroy their own statements around corruption and onwards
Alex tries to be pretty
Like Trump in the military needs
Sure sure
Although it is
Fake attempt on their life
To get sympathy
You think everything is a weird conspiracy game
Garner sympathy for Fryeburg dr. fauci
You are preemptively
Choking so much
As a defense against
Dr. fauci
That is exactly what he would do seems
Some people Trump should probably do it and
I don't know he doesn't feel on
Today
Call Jacob calls
And this one caller
Hoo-boy
He's he's mad about snitches and then
Without further Ado and go to Mike in New York Newark State of New York City
Upstate New York thanks for taking my class beautiful area up there with your blush like
People are another rural areas
Go ahead
Valued well Alex you thinks okay let me let me tell you something about here people leave their doors unlocked
In their cars unlocked cuz they know everyone up here believes in the Second Amendment no one's going to go breaking in people's houses up
The small village of 5,000 people
Neighbors that I have turnto12 hi to everyday
Same ones who attorney in time and time again since I pulled up at 1:20
Snitches
Upstate New York
I should also tell you like you are from
I looked at this little bit and there's a number of places in Upstate New York that have pretty high burglary race
How old is what's his guy is saying really holds water
So it turns out you don't even need to bring your
Your gun to the burglar
You can just steal the gun that's already there
Building code violations
We put up a
Trump Flags
He's pretty mad about this
You have a retaliation
I don't know I think it reads way more hostile than he thinks it does
I'm here
Mike you speak on my son's beautiful friend
Your I will eat your ass
Beautiful
This is what this is on
You know like
Is it the thing is
Genderbent beautiful today
It was about Alex
Eating his neighbors
A player is Neighbors
Might be
We construe it as a threat
Man count to 5000
And you're the guy with the place next to this guy is my number was like
Eat my neighbor stuff over the fence
Yeah I feel like I
Call
The f****** know yours people yours
Maybe if you call the cops about me on this
Your double-stitched
And another speaker completely different
Imagine wasting your time
RadioShack
The angry caller who's like
All these damn snitches
Trivial
You got to fill the two
Nothing else
To really talk about
Disappointing
Rihanna somebody to work at MD Anderson
He had to stop working there because
Some of the surgeons
Ashley sexually aroused
They were injecting people with experimental stuff that they sign waiver forms would probably kill him
Off on killing people
Get off on like people missing their lower mandibles
Woodside on for Spirit stay alive
People like a zombie movie
How to get a Leslie hanging out drooling
Get off on it and then
Ugly jerk off in the bathroom after they went and saw it
Can you imagine
Masturbating
Two people missing their lower mandibles in their tongues hanging out
You realize that type of psycho scientist is in control you start turning things around
Tell you stories like this to shock you
Phone number to mistaken Jordan
This is a family show
For the kids
Can you imagine
Sometimes imagine about that
Another call from California
The Protector the children
March rally took place recently
Children
Get the Saturday with that
A lot of this might be similar to that Irish fascist to is holding a anti pedophilia
Might have been a little bit of
He has this person on and he accidentally gets tricked into promoting
Somebody that he shouldn't
I'm glad you're here so start over and I do know about your group tell us about who you are again
Send for you but more people must join you again
Natural operations to the AI isn't washing you till you do that
Other people to be the leader be the leader
Another leader jumps up and it's sooner they're fighting an army of leaders and they can't stop us
We're making is decentralized as possible so our our site is
Cam
Is Real Deal media website
Okay videos
Main video
Those are called The Real Deal reports
Show but one of those
Get the f*** out of here
Dammit
Set alarm
Holocaust denier
I looked at their about
Joining the real deal report is the heavily censored Victoria's libertas
Kristen Meghan
In the health Ranger Mike Adams goddamnit
Also we're not interested in Liberty anymore
Oh yeah
Between Mike Adams and Alex
Because of a disagreement that they have about masks
Not the Coronavirus
Is real Mike Adams is now taking his Direction
To the real deal media which is Alex's
I don't think that it is and honestly this is
Like Jim Fetzer
A real man
Oh you think you toxic
Yeah
Pretty fast
Lawsuit
Double jeopardy
I'm pretty sure that's a double jeopardy
Really really funny
That Alex pretends to know what this operation is
I'll let you know we got it we need more leaders
Core answer he's giving her a platform to promote her s***
You promoting somebody that he's supposed to be against because
He's getting sued over Sandy Hook stop
Jim Fetzer on his show
Right now
There's just no way for him to learn
He just called
Care
Just just careful
Just any kind of
Awareness
Just not a something so humble
About
Say I don't know or whatever
What is this
I don't have Universal awareness is literally everything
Open up vulnerable place
Nope ends up accidentally promoting Jim Fetzer in the year of Our Lord 2020
Supporting your little website
Another caller
Is a ramp psychonaut
Bloodline
I want to talk about a few things and it's
I believe that Consciousness oscillates at a frequency
And should be verified ever number similar to IQ
That being said
Ayahuasca ceremonies I've done all kinds of research myself one like mushrooms
Just everything like haha
What's going on in the world right now
Just like low conscience
Demons
Sure
Is the DMT and along with the rituals and with everything else
Naturally
I go and do it I can go do it through ayahuasca
Listen to Rogan bro
Abomination
With the power powder
You can't do this
You got to drink it through the Vine
Purge demons out
That's right
Straight help
Whatever evil snakes
Goddamn
Like drink
That's why they're addicted to it
Representative
And that he really did give them the
Response
Get help
Yeah that's
You don't want to be like not only that but
Immeasurable much like IQ
That be good now that I have used for my
Spotify
Take that as
Now we can move on to my next radio program
Like sending myself a newspaper in the mail
Option Xavier
So you can go
Non-Stop
Let him keep talking
Elites are
A squirrel
Probably
Sucked it was a waste of a shower
Things that happen
Call
There's that
A great effort
However
Heads and shoulders
About the force
August 4th open
Like this
Dead air
Okay
As a Shelgon
Autograph
It's art
That's true
He finally
46 that's 800-406-0046
Credit counseling services
5701 West Sunrise Boulevard
License
Marilyn dm14
Oregon.dmv 8090
I suspected Virginia state board
Serviceman
There's not Buzz Marketing on our part
Not alone
President Trump says he wants to help communities in rural areas
You spoke at the White House yesterday
This is the Genesis Communications
This is what they used
Play on Sunday
Should be like the first 5 minutes or whatever
For the first minutes there's some sort of
A connection
Problem
But he's having with
The Genesis
Radio station
Syndicated on
He doesn't get on the radio except through Genesis
Communication repair station
So
He's just not there
Maybe he's finally did have too much to do
Is to cover maybe couldn't open his show with it he had too much
News to even stay here too much news
About this
Delivery news person
For a little bit
And then Alex's intro music starts
Commercial
That is playing right before the
Victor Cruz
I've ever heard
Who now
It's wild
Great
Once I would start stalking
090crew patient's
Incredible election
Mushroom cloud
Killshot
This is tough this great
Is really great
I was I was always wondering
Disoriented
To Alex's before now we're at
Episode 400
50 something or whatever
Now we got to our new generation for a show
Going on here is there is like
Two different input
That are going to
Right is a rebroadcast
Some
Bulshit or whatever
King and trying to start it show
And then somebody fixes something
But they don't really fix
Anything because we just have to feed the valley
Text talking
Good news
That bad it was a sport
Pause
Ominous ominous
Explosion
Terrorist attack
Oh my God
Oscillator
Mine almost ocellated up a f****** window
Sister weird
Echo is
He said
No he's talking about thoughts and prayers
Best wishes are with everyone there
Squishies
That's my sound effect for fast-forwarding
20 minutes into the episode
Read through through
Vine
Today
My son
We're still struggling
From the Grand Canyon
No
Season Studio
This is a very complex issue
I just
Listen to this and obviously we can't play it on the show
Chunks of hair
It can't happen
It's just like
YouTube is fine
It isn't f*****-up hologram of Alex sitting at the other I wish there was that would have been
And
Trying to take the audio from that would have taken too long
For us to put out Tuesday's episode on Wednesday
I am so there's wasn't a way around that is like
Okay well eventually maybe he'll put it up on band.
Easier just to download from
But it was just it wasn't
Coming into the like
Unlistenable pile of s***
I would have thought that like
All right maybe he doesn't even know
At the same time I thought that was
Impossible because there was two different
Friend audio problem
Who was one problem
Feeds
Someone had to fix that and got it to the point where there were two
And then Alex just kind of freaks out
Summer start over next time
Skip.
Let's go ahead
Special Report
See what happens
I'm at the pushback other grasshopper
Covid-19
Land that plane buddy
And then after that we're alike
If you didn't know that this audio was coming out like this
Completely out of left field
Like I don't know why he's mad
Is going on
But if you know the Genesis feed would go out to radio stations
Like yeah makes sense our to be f****** pissed off right there
Start over
Wright-Patt
But I swear to you
That was a pro
That was a bet somebody made a bet
They were like okay
How long do you think it'll take before a he notices
MP he freaks out
And the moment he noticed and freaked out 37 minutes
Clinton with one button
37 minutes
Just
It was tough
50 bucks all right
And yes this idea that similar to Nichols
In his idea that whenever
The ship goes down if you're a senator
No you're a Duke
That's right
Extra
Don Jr would be a jack
And the cons
And a deck of cards
Yes to the sort of similar idea about like Whoever has the most
Inflated currency at the time when the ship goes down
I don't really care about this idea because he doesn't really spell it out very well exactly why I kept
Prescribed for
What month is over
Whoever ends up with
They're all doing it
Whoever ends up with the dominant Global turn
Who can flood the world with the most of their currency
Who can be on top when it all goes down we'll be in charge
Brentwood weather
And you can say it's a corrupt system you can stay
He's getting rid of our hegemonic power themselves completely
Being flushed down the toilet
Couldn't come up with a better reference
Alex is a
That's why I
That's just
Dooku just just letting
Sidious and Dooku
Not Emperor Palpatine
Not a problem
Darth Sidious and Dooku
He is definitely a prequel
Guy
Of course
Course he is he is the inversion of all that is good and right in the world
That's just reality
So Alex says this this map of
Narrative
What is a graph put a map
Look
We can talk all we want about Alex revealing that he doesn't know what
Control groups or Baseline groups are
In this next clip he seems to be presenting
As a person who doesn't know that
Flu Seasons exist
Let's go to the new numbers
May and June and
August
Numbers for Arizona
You can see
They just
Say there's no longer any influenza deaths there
Suddenlink
We don't know why worldwide flu
Just take the numbers
Do you read they admit
Doing
To the covid-19
They are
That big big
X-Wing flu season is just a
Colloquial
It's just the way we Cottage
Describe how we feel it sometime
Spring
I got nothing on this when he genuinely doesn't know what a fluke from mine
Trouble
That's really scary to me the idea
Either not
Or beware of it and be such a
Like a craven liar
Possibly be
Subject to those lies
And and not recognized
Yeah yeah that's not
Alex talks more about the
These graphs
Man is a bad presentation
California just like the last breath you saw out of Arizona
Influenza deaths
Completely
Covid deaths
Almost
Mattress
Yes I said we move
The numbers
Visual
Cheated the scope
Posey and the other
The scale of the
But also
Flu season
You safely
Is a government coup
Sing about
It's a government cover-up
Cool
Alex misrepresents this even more to the point where I feel like it should be legally ask
Like if someone
Alex Jones
Like I feel like he should be able to be sued for Direct
Misinformation that like
I don't know how this is okay
Love disease
Depopulation
The numbers all show that influenza deaths 12-week number
Goes down does almost zero
Skyrocket
Nations
Trouble Falls policy
I just don't know any other way to to put it then like someone should be able to sue in for the
Yeah you're using misrepresented data and
Argument
In order to try and presented like the perspective that this is a hoax and it's fake
Outbreak
And your
Doing so has a tendency towards
Leading people to
Make behavioral decisions that are bad for their health
I just
I don't know I see no way that that's not it
Exactly analogous to fire in a movie
What is a serious risk to people's house
That is perfectly analogous
I don't know why it's not or how it couldn't be
Yeah you know right
Totally
XYZ
This is so
Explicitly an indefensible
This is
Cheating grass
Very
Very Elementary
And
A misrepresentation of one of the most Elementary fact
About
Distribution of flu deaths over the course of
The year that I went back over actually there's a view
CDC website
Over every year ugly
Year-by-year coz
Different
It's a different strains of the flu
Right always has a very similar art
To them and
Very regularly are ending around this week
12 time. Alex is talking
Sometimes it's a little bit later but that's because there's variability
This is this this is just unacceptable
And like I don't
I don't
Yeah that's that's
.
Just now got
So Alex storm
Sure
Great
Is Edges a sort of routine
Now this setup
Roundup today
So ready for the show so ready to cover all this
Sun's up here to Anderson I'm trying to work with a guy
Easier decision
It's just
By the average person just turns out
The reason the most people to not politics is because
They can't handle having their son in the office and a shady gold dealer
I got so what
Wouldn't leave me alone back when I was
That's because so much of my time was precious metal dealers
Back to the Future
Oh my best friend is a disgraced nuclear physicist
Much like myself
Alex wants to run away to a cabin
Nature
We aren't doing it for different reasons
Myself I can't afford it
And I think it would be untenable
Just a complication
No I'm certainly not I don't think I think I've become a vegetarian
Lexi realizes and maybe
You know you just
I kill people instead
I want more
Little Cabin in the Woods
Deal with it
But you know what they're coming to your
Tabitha Woods
Not going to leave anybody alone I think
Everybody
Do something
Information
The minute they come
Unless you take this
And that is run by a guy that says he wants to depopulate
Take your calls
Depopulation agenda he represents what do we do about them because finally today
This morning
My psyche put into gear
About maybe I can fix this with information
Yes you are
Is it sad
So a war for violence
Now
Follow through the woods
Can we have a pool of the majority
The Republic
Yeah I'm just be trouble
Ramping up of the exact same Trend that we've seen
It's not where it's like
Kind of.
Very much
Keeping in Pace with
The transit you seen from heaven
Very scary
And the people to be aware of that
Because
Alex also refusing to learn
Some things that he's done in the past
He doesn't know
Said he's accidentally
Promoting Jim Fetzer again try
And he doesn't realize that in the
The past
When he's done
S*** like this
And talked about like
These evil evil demon people
And maybe you need to show up places sometimes people do
Jesus
Those the Tapatia
We need to not be violent offensive look at this point
We better be
Spiritually economically and culturally really aggressively right now
Physical assault
I don't mean Burning Down the police station
Beating up innocent people
Going into places without mass that means going into Parkside close
Aggressive
You better hope
It's someone
Who listens to your show doesn't show up at
The Clinton's house or soros's housing
Cause some problems
You better hope
That your listeners don't take you seriously
Does even have object
Permanence
Where are we on the ability to learn here
Because even if there are four ways to
To do it he's utilizing.
Not a single one
Seems to me that
Like once he gets into a certain headspace
He can't really even control himself
But you kind of talks about even
Like this right after this
Apologize accrue mileage radioactive today
Radioactive
Countdown
Think about this
Do this and I do that
Wargaming at all
But I know you're all doing the same thing
We just
Willie need
Got to fix this is basically impossible
Infowarsstore.com
Right away
This just makes me think of like right around the time when he got that DUI he was talking about how like he's addicted to
Rage
I need to take some
Some time off and like how you just
You know it feels good
But you can't like it's going to destroy
Like I can't hear him talk about like
You know I start sweating and people alike
Why can't you talk about the exact same thing
You just now talked yourself into thinking
It's not a problem because your experience
This great
True
Ratings
I don't know but
It's unhealthy
The things that seem to happen when he's in the states are the things that are the most
Destructive
The most dangerous to innocent people
II
Nobody around him at all
Has has
Man he needs a lot of
A lot a lot of
Right but it's impossible for that to happen
They're weak people like
I mean whoever works for m
2 time losers
Scam Fox
To compound the issue
You have
People calling in
I believe I've said this before
Coming to power of the Antichrist
Sure
When I'm getting my information from
I hope you don't mind me saying this
Golden State
People in the world
Alex
Port forward
Inspire
So you have people call again you are like the Antichrist is taking over and God has spoken to me it sounds
Exactly like you and therefore you're a prophet
You have people who are enabling you to that level would you ever consider that like what you're doing
Is damaging
You're lying to people about graphs
Why would you ever date
Responsibility for your actions
Basically a messenger of God you're infallible
Yeah like this is this is sick
Cold
S***
I would be interested to know what it
Looks like to exist in that Bubba
You know Aunt it to have that it to have your mind so War
Fat what he's doing and what you think he's saying and and whatever
Make sense to you be the caller
Anybody
You do like to exist in that bubble
It's just so reinforce that you're
There's just no outside information at all
Is just not
That's the only
Explanation for
And it's it's
Terrifying
But also
More fun
Like
Should I would I be happier if I was living in the bubble
Yes or no
No that's not the way it's her that I was hoping
See you talking about his new special and I think it sucks
Reopen America
Special
Especially
Which of the accounting in the math
We just can't find ourselves
When 20% off and the
Free shipping
Special
The same thing but worse
Uninspired even from a marketing
Perspective
To school
Specials in
AR
Very
Taste
A little bit
Pencils
I need school supplies he sells documentaries
Pills
Ridiculous
So
Whatever Alex is talking about
He always couches it with them the language of like
It's got to be defensive
And physically attacking us oh it's already
No matter what
Mark of the beast world government is here what are we going to do about it
Possibility for a
Exactly cuz
The giant cow
Grandpa
Year 3 of Alex not to be
Actually want to happen
So
All right here we go
Hours of the gas
Episode
Never end up really discussing
It's someone who I considered as like someone to do an episode about butt
I kind of don't
Yo
Good about it I felt like
There's a pretty decent chance
That he's had a stroke
Or something
I don't know
What's going on
Abilities don't appear to be all there
And seen him in this context
Text on Alex's assessment might have been wrong
Love the videos that I've said this is Jesse Lee Peterson
Videos that I've watched him
Debating people who are of the last
People like
Destiny or David
Jesse Lee Peterson the show and
People even started treating it like a fun goofy thing for you to people the low
To do
To be a little bit boring as a formula
Jessie
Appears to be almost
Unable to process the information that's going on
The context of seeing him on Alex's show
I think that's an
I think that might actually be employed
To frustrate or annoyed
Yes or no
When's your question
Seems like you stop beating your wife
If you say yes
It's not a
Interacted with the way people responded to questions and it made me worried about
How is cognitive
Ability
It's clearly like if he's just talking to somebody else
Then he's just a
F****** a******
He's just believes in white supremacy
Sure
Why not episode
Field that assessment of him was
I don't think I was wrong
To have the opinion that I had of like I don't feel comfortable
About
Him that I should take seriously
In the same way
Clearly been struggling the pts Beyond
By the way he puked processing information
And
Yeah I thought they'd like there's a neurological reason that this is going on
So
In his bio
In Jessie's biofit Alex gives a
Check out price
Elsa and Anna
Civil rights
Courageous
Outspoken
What does bran
Look civil rights leadership
Lot of them
Love need a lot of criticism sure
I'm with you he's criticizing
The foundation
Criticizing civil rights
Apologizes for Tech issues which
Alex apologizes
Yeah
Very special month
You got a lot to cover today
I just got bless you what do you want to cover
I want to say
Niod and happy man History Month
Is man history
Because
Men
Men and boys are most hated species on this side of Heaven
Brandy attention to that
So another thing of a troll
Trump
The Great White Hope
Okay alright
Piss people off
Pretty
But pretty sure
August is men's History Month
Very special
July was why should we started that
3 years ago
Because white people are the most hated
Species on this side of Heaven
We see that now
Whitney at acabar
The president
Donald Trump
The Great White Hope
We see that with the attack Americans today to be
Rob rape
Businesses are being destroyed and no one cares
No one says
Got to remind people of white shoes
Because if it wasn't for
America
Create it to greatest country on this side of Heaven
Not Mexican
Not Japanese not Chinese white people
Arrays
History
Create a
Alex has found his new best
Jesse Lee Peterson on the actual show
Alex says
With Owen
Which leads me to believe
Junior varsity cheer
The big league cup of coffee
Alex
Yes where is it where have you been my whole life
I have always wanted to say I have black friends and that wasn't true
Men are under attack
Right there buddy
Issue comes down to for Jesse Lee Peterson
Do you know there's going
Tubi
Concerta social app
It takes place in America
And then
Won't you think of the poor wife
Call
I have redone the police forces overran.
Exact same thing here
Afraid to speak up or
Sofia being called racist
We have these radical.
Command
We have them
Police Chiefs and BBC state-run Media
South Africa
Equal share of the landing
You don't you know it's like how they like how white people want
Other your Mexicans and other people to assimilate to American culture
You saw white people go down and leave by
Sable in South Africa
They submitted a simulated into the culture that's what they do right
I mean it
History is fun when you choose arbitrary start date
Whatever cockamamie arguments you want to make
Totally
Blacklivesmatter
1965 and later
So Jesse Peterson
Does not like black lives
I would say that he has an interesting
Complained
Might reveal
On this episode or maybe
Knows better than to be as outwardly homophobic as he actually is
But that's his problem
You got to realize that black lives matter
Liberal radical organization
Black
Angry radical lesbians
And I never
I just never imagined that one day
Christian Nation
That we received
Police officers grown men and women
That's my boy
I hate the
Family
He's angling for the slot right after Rush Limbaugh listen to The Rush Limbaugh
So they get to talkin about
The
You know how the party
Political party
T.i.
Democrat
Republican
I bet this
Super inside
Is 2 / 10
Party swap
Papa never happened
Well when
What happened
White people in South Africa
Fair enough
And the party the KKK is the party of Lincoln
Amanda
Accusing
Republican party of being white
Almost at the white part
Can we just talk
What is the white part
Tried to save the white party
Dwight tardy that's what it is all right
One thing that you should know about Jesse Lee Peterson is that grew up I believe
Who's in the south
Under the Jim Crow laws
What is it claims to fame
Very positively
About Jim Crow laws
A lot of people were better off
And for a return
Jim Crow laws
Alex was really ready
Best to spin the conversation
Affected
Human system
Strong
But no job
And they're just pissed off
Believe me
Is there
Whenever we want to visit
Maybe I don't know
You decided to block overcome
Leopardon Alex
Does Bart
December
Speaking about Jim Crow laws
I agree with you
Personally
If they were reintroduced
Especially Jesse Lee Peterson
Attempt was also kind of
Human
The human system and depression major stronger
No
What would what do you do with these degrees Dan
Trust in gym
Grow
I mean
I did get a real sense that Alex might not have been aware that Jesse went that far
If you don't
Hey Jim Crow was a better time
This a joke
Breaking the hold on one second
Takeoff
We're not doing blackface
Oh sing that song about how we're going to kill the giant days with the
I don't
I said I found this to be depressing
Never wanted
Thoroughly
Like I don't know I didn't
I want to see Jesse Lee Peterson on Alex's show
I just don't like it
I think it's a bad combination
Yeah
I feel like Jesse showing up your analysis shows a bad sign of things to come
I don't I don't like what they could possibly get into together I think it's a bad merge
Is this what we're doing he's about
Is Danny Glover
Alex is too old for this year
Is racist Lethal Weapon
Lethal Weapon was up by itself half races
A tough
Stretch
The third is kind of a really black
Show inspired
Then kind of lethargic and I don't know what the f*** is going on
The forest
Is
An unmitigated disaster
Stop talking about you stop
I don't cotton to that nonsense
It's a real disaster
I don't even know
I just
Feel like if you had anybody decent working there they wouldn't have allowed that to happen
Someone would have caught that problem
Anderson is in the station
Podcast Radio show that has million dollar Studio
Qan
We going to keep costs low overhead is
They can't even afford to give you free shipping
They definitely can't afford a competent sound
I don't know it was it was a bummer
It's just like
Now here's Jesse Lee Peter
It's such a positive
Message
You know other
Your family
Ramble about people walking around like zombies
Good
I think the most important thing
To really point out
In focus on here is that the Tramp
Towards
Self-sacrifice through like
Maybe violence
Is continued
You know there was that article and right wing watch
Watch that pointed out some of this
Some more attention being paid to it but
It's a trend and I don't expect it to cool down anytime soon
Think of anything this is only going to get more severe on Alex's part
And I hope
Small
And unaffected as I think they probably are
The thing I was thinking was like
You probably shouldn't have written about this
Feel it makes it look like
A story
The moment you write that
You're pretty much committing to like
And next week we follow up Alex
Still calling for follow-up for the next week
Alex Jones still calling
You can't just say that he said it
Because he's staying yet
Continue
It's going to ask
Yeah but still
Counteract
I'd like to make an ounce
And that is
On our next episode
I will be announcing
I have five
Just because of
Preparations
Is it needed to be made and
Slight bit of uncertainty
And everyone else this on the next episode
Very
Excited
Jordan
Rose on Twitter
We are in
To help out those doing
300ZX Clark
Alex
Birthstone colors