Damned important swetik
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
We are the bad guys
Money
Dot-com
Just a little bit about
Alex Jones
Jordan Jordan
What's up
About today
Black lives matter it's
Also I only work for like the four hours I'm outside of my apartment otherwise Mister Rogers sweater.
Out of the house is equivalent to the course of the week so
A baby announcement that I was going to declare my pet
Give this big reveal and I hope
Public
I'll be worth a lot more excited given me suggestion
When I said I was talking
Appreciate everybody
What ended up becoming
The plan
Is very much an offshoot of somebody suggestion
Can cockroaches hissing cockroaches
And it bounced around my head a bit
Absolutely
I don't want that cockroaches
I have a huge cockroaches there
Not interested
Not come on face your fears
I'm not afraid of dumb I just don't care for it
I've had it
And so I decided like
Praying mantis
Pretty cool
Fairly cool I like the idea of maybe having a mantis
I decided maybe that's
And then I thought of the
The pain name
This house phone
So I
Mantis yet but that is
Edible before coming and I will provide pictures
Of its cool terrarium
Bad
Whatever Whenever old
What's arthritis
Vibrate
Read my audiobook
I started reading it
And then I listen
To Somerville
Genuinely like so much
Voice is so wildly like it does all kinds of s***
Even though I've spent
Literally the past 15 years on a microphone talking back to that unlike
I don't know how to
Experience
All the sudden
All the fruits of that labor
Speedwell
Thursday of this week
Probably
I'll wait till the audiobook comes up
Stuff that requires any kind of focus
The show that I have barely any notes
Very little to debunk here
Enough stuff that
Meriden attention and Trent
Glitter continuing
Man
You need a booking at
Oh no
You know Nick Fuentes or Jesse Lee Peterson
Larry from down
Limerick
Jordyn Woods
Spartacus show
The first mattcave
Baseball players named Southern
Any baseball player
Single
Thank you, justice
Pui
Sorry
Next
Brian
Did Brian Boitano
Was he a diver the next one can be tough for you
Honestly I pick that one might be
Easier than Brian even though I can't think of anyone else
In the 1910s
Lawrence butts
Madonna elevator
Democrat
Heroin
Really large
Yes
We would preach
Ruby love
The episode proper business
Some business about a little bit of business
We just take care of business
Knowledge business
This was coming
In the not-too-distant future
The plant
They're probably be a real reason to official announcement
What is playing in September
And he would like to go on
As close
In person
Obviously the Coronavirus
Covid situation
But I do come up with some sort of a digital version
And I just wanted to make sure
Anybody still thought it might be happening in Chicago that is not that we're not doing the live show
We got to let this
But I mean
I don't know about that
Was clear and
And stated
Then
Jordan another Better Business
Jordans
We got a nice little letter
Barometer read
Jordan
Directions to classics
I specifically Philip K Dick's
As someone with a degree in literature or a Bradbury inspired imagine
My excitement when you guys start talking to
Anyway enough about me
Here are some sci-fi novels
Jordan
A copy of Rogers
One of my favorites
Geek store
Zelazny
Particular I think you will enjoy it
Plus the stone God
Probably my favorite
Tri blend sci-fi and fantasy
Teq self-discovery beautiful
Is the book mostly a lesbian romance novel
Syfy nonsense absolutely
For the show just because that title sounds like something I would say the accuser globalist and their eyeteeth
Attempted attempted
Via lame Boomers Spirit cooking
Performance
Thanks bro
Mason
PS here's a summary of David Foster Wallace's Infinite Jest
Has really good at being annexed not all Assassin's have
Using endnotes in a novel Isabel
Yeah that sounds about right
Thank you so much Mason with delightful note
And I can I cannot wait to read the
Not for me
Alright
Landed
Camp cave
What's this
Oh I need shirts
Sounds like Siri
Especially for you have blue one
It says spider leadership
Marigolds situation with a feline Contessa
Massillon
Black cat
The crown on top
Love it
Okay as soon as I
I think of what you would want
Ariana decided to send something homemade maybe next time
Max will be more inspired
Incredible
Yes hope the sizes are right
Which I'm very insulted by
Is it a large dog
Very exalted but correct
That was from Christy thank you so much
Awesome cool bed up on the wall
For sure it looks incredible
I would wear it off
Can I wear and tear would come in
You can't ruin your feline
Unreal
At the end of the bag
Exciting
Looking
So start here on August 5th
And Alex's
Decided he's going to jump in
Do the narrative about the Beirut
Oh and Dinos
No
Best present
You called this an attack
An accident
It seemed like it based on the explosion I met with
Some of our great generals
I just seem to feel that
It was just was not
A
Some kind of a
Menu
Explosion type of
This was a
Seems to be according to them they would know better than I would but they seemed to think it was a attack
It was a bomb of some
Comes out and tells you it's a bomb
Before
Intelligence
Declassify whatever he wants
Q-47
The president can
What we did we the people elect
Someone
Spade card play
Is that
Like the president doesn't have that power
President can do whatever he wants as long as we don't impeaching it's up to us
We the people's Congress believe what he's done is wrong
And we can prove it was
He represents We the People
Wait we wait wait
So Frost Nixon style momento
Unless he gets in
We There You Go that was
Well yeah but that weekend convicted Congressman decided
Appreciate him saying we the people that view of Civic
Authoritarian
Just honest
And Alex's he's got a really interesting position on this he's decided to spend it was probably Israel
Grill
He's basing that on comments netanyahu's made in the past about Hezbollah
Having like stations in missiles in Lebanon
Bind it with Trump talking
Can see it and now you started if you jump his declassifying that is real
I'm a huge fan of just making up things and then declassify responsible
It's it's irresponsible conjecture on Alex's
Is Bart hands
Kind of gross
Underground area super
So there's not a lot going on but I found compelling
Start rambling a little bit about
He's seen a video of someone getting stabbed
If I understand the video that he's talking about correctly it was
Trump supporter type stabbing a left-wing
Percent
Said that Lebanon
Israel
Video
Should stab people
All you got to do with it
Fox is everything
Everything is speed
Just like
That's what you do these to get off
Yeah quite a bit
Present quite a bit
You want to kill somebody you go straight for the gyro
I am jagras in a little bit
You pretty quick
But it was only when I was defending myself
Okay you know what I was younger I used to take karate
There were always the older guys in the locker room
Who are all these karate guys but in a white nationalist karate guys
Big Burly tattoos
Sure and they would always
Talk s*** about how best to
And your leg
That's what I hear from Alex because I was there and even as like a nine-year-old pitam like
You guys are full of s*** you know like that kind of
I don't understand why
Alex would do this sort of thing on a show
Like
Every now and again that you have to take
Step back and recognize that he tries to Pretend This is news
No I mean if you're covering a new story of someone getting stabbed protester something
I don't know why you would editorialize the best way to ship people
And like get their guts out leave you alone
Like I don't I don't know why
Filter report
Shooting isn't going to be like now
Just so you know the best what you're going to want to do is focus on hitting Center Mass
You think that the headshot is going to do the job quicker
You're going to miss the video game
80%
Outright
But instead
Is he put the outer core
That you better fucken hope
That his listeners don't respond to
We really should call
Recalled
Call Brittany
He's not living on the top
Thrown out of there
Cuz he's not
Globalist
Alex
Best way to write a check
End up going
2y where is the mayor of Austin
Send lives because they don't have a good track record of
Peaceful normal demonstration
Make a scene let's I mean let's say something does happen
I mean look
Quite honestly now
For him he should not be encouraging people to go to the home
Specific people
Bad
Break-ins at the first floor
And make a scene every Friday and Saturday night
Then we'll recall him I don't even think it's a great ideas for people who are trying to
Has like sodas are responsible
Protest
Places to be like
We go places and make a scene
I don't I don't know
Productive targeted action probably make
Yeah yeah
I don't know anyway I think it's a bad escalation
Refinement
Alex's
He's he's been talking a bit about Civil Disobedience lately in a way that I feel like he doesn't know what it mean
Yeah
Civil disobedience is that the one
Well
Okay well
Alex
Gibbster talking
About
There are people who have the opinion that there should be
Police defunding
And such
His position on it is that
They want to take over the
The police in order to create their own
Gestapo
And specifically he has this to say about ilhan Omar
Andy says the chief police in order to create around sodas
SS
Sure is obviously the conversation two people are having makes total sense
He can't have this point or make this
Position without
Getting
Very explicitly races
Ilhan Omar
Because that woman can't build a civilization
The minute
Flavors
Why does how does someone's brain work this way
Tobago
Complex
Tapestry of nonsense
I don't understand
What kind of racism you're really going
Civilization
That's fine if I'm incapable
Back there that I don't know what that means
I guess we'll be saying is that she's not capable or able to be in a leadership position
Mission of some sort because she's from Somalia
What are you saying is that everyone who's not
Pirate stock
I don't even I don't understand
Like Pirates
Yeah
Stock
Knowing nothing about her but the color of her skin and I am I
Refugee
Adventure pissing all over everybody
Trump supporter or something
How do you know what
Doc
Someone come
Just got that in the past
The cheese lighter-skinned that he would
Expect her to be be from Africa is also complex yet
Ugly
Hellboy
Alright
We're doing great we're at
Navigate to Greg
Directions
Dick
So
PS
I didn't really take off
It's just that
I'll go out the street
I'll just physically go out there
OK Google
Civilization
But really you watched
The public getting into their own enslavement
And all the lazy neurotic
People unable to get anything done
And it just makes me wonder man
God just kill us all
Willow
I should just leave
You suck
You are just turning into a
More of violent minded
Like
Doomsday preacher type
It's just like a bunch of people I don't give a s***
Cherry wine
Oh maybe I'll go out into the street myself disappears for me
Because you just like
Maybe I should just go out
Go to park
Springs without
Getting a test
Okay
Some sort of Civic civil disobedience
Vine
Whatever
I don't think it's a good idea you know you're doing what you do
But then he's like
Yeah hey Aaron I read these dumb headlines and I rant about the
I'm not doing business
I need more attention
Go to Barton Springs to break into something
I'm going to go to the W yellow
You're right they don't it's like yourself to the door
You can still get in the other would like the security guard is like I can take those off for you
Meanwhile come on you don't even know how to do it right you're just a nuisance like he gets into the creek
F****** fine just go
I don't know what the situation is Barton Springs
It's more of a local issue then I care about
But yeah I mean like if you wants to like I don't know changing self to the fence apart
Springdale for it some sort of Civil Disobedience some sort of a way to raise awareness that he wants to swim with
Never do it
Supposed to be so manly and strong and powerful and then you just keep whining about stuff you could literally
Do at the drop of a hat say I'm going to do this
Don't whine about something that you could
I mean we all know that when you say that you're going to do something you end up not doing it
Because your brain is Trick yourself into thinking
You've already know now Alex
He's already taken
This is just like I'm not getting enough attention I need to ask
Attention
And here's the thing I've been going through with this telescope
4 years ago
Say their name we hit the button
I'm going to stay there
Again we go through the second
And we are going to defeat this
This one thing
The part I hate is the connecting with
Hello
We're going to do this right now
I love Carlos is a longtime regular caller
Stop bitching to be a whiny ass
Joann
Go ahead
Carlos has got to feel good about that
And it's all because
Recognize
Explain the situation to all of the colors when they call in and get put on home
Here's another one
To do at 8
Everything is exactly as Alex says
She says the name
They don't hear their name
Or whatever
Jordan
How's it going what's going on with you
I didn't hear the
No I said Jordan
The character is waiting for the
Changes that could be made that are so
F****** simple that would solve this problem
Upgrade your phone system
So you're telling me
Not solving this problem
It's like somebody who is like
I don't know
With an easily I have a headache and you just complained for an entire day to take an aspirin
It's
This is comical to me
Hit it makes him so bad
So he's been on the he's been using this phone Sis
4 years
Conceivably guy
He has had this problem
4 years
And just now
On air
He's coming up with
The solution for
Right
And no point in time did we ever have a head backstage
Conversations lyrics
Sorry sorry that
BMO picture
What you see on Ayers what's going on
Okay
Apologize
There is
To his audience it is what he
He thinks his authenticity is
Like so deeply emotionally manipulative
Yeah
I think that there's a certain amount of the audience
Probably feels held captive by his like his outbursts
Sure
Sure it's like I mean it it's like having an alcoholic dad
You're you're on constant high alert like
Waiting for that
That little moment that's going to set him off
You're almost paralyzed until he does
Right
If you take
Those outbursts as being about something grander the devil or the global
To my ex
Wife is suing
Saying that my mouthwash is Magic if it's not
Sandy Hook I can't get that taste
Like if you
If you
Take those outbursts that are about like
At the consequences of Alex's actions that are eating at him use my phone system
Did you take those outbursts
Change them and Elevate them to being like
No
Alex is actually mad because the devil's out to get him
God
It's just
I don't know it's
Mysterious ways
But the devil only deals with bones
That is something
That's why you know
You lose service
If you're in the base
I just I just think it's
It's very wrong
The way Alex behaves himself
Better romanticizing
In order to avoid EX
Sleep dealing with him
You know it's just
It's easier to be like all it's the
The devil and it's easier for people to believe it
The devil because if he starts
What's the deal with real-world problems on the
The show that's a real bummer for everybody
It's not a conspiracy
It's literally you you're going to get
Olivia
No like that's less romantic
Coming to kill you
Exactly recognizes
Cell
If it does you need to buy water filtration system so I can pay my legal fees for things I like
Do you about in the past
I'm starting to use I feel statements at the advice of my therapist
I feel like you're going to need to buy this magic toothpaste otherwise I can't afford to pay my therapist
Right
Please
Like really ramping up
Alex does
Shouldn't be violin
People
So you know
We just gone too far
We've gone too far
Are saying
Kill kill
Weather tomorrow
Slowly
I guess it's not
Offensive violence ever
No I mean
Bill Gates
Is coming but a while
With a weapon
Yeah so
I don't understand how that could be anymore you'll know when the
Time is right
Constantly is doing that
And every
Zane insult part of my body is saying kill
Kill.
Repetition
Normalizing be sorts of feelings that someone listening might have just f***** up
Outlook
Tank
Alright a lot of people want to shake
You got to slap that's in the movie
Text to Carlos is a long time caller
Who sucks
Man's boring not going with Daddy that
Sharp instead we jump forward to caller who explain to Alex that
Finding Infowars was a Divine thing
What's on my mind first of all I just want to listen to know the reason why I started listening to you
A few years back
67 years ago
Was that
The Holy Ghost led me to you
And the message was when I was the first words that I have her come out your mouth
Was that of the golden life was a avatar
And this is what I always known all my life
I always try to
Understanding that the Holy Ghost through the rest of the work
So I just want to listen to the no
That's the reason why
Why I listen to
I'll let you buy the Holy Ghost so I know I'm in the right place
This is such
Zealotry or not good
Longest Yard
Is Big Tent Revival ISM if everybody's arm
I sort of touched on this earlier but like this is just a violin
Jim Bakker
Listening to these two episodes like I really experienced
Far more of like
This is
Like Loki transitioned
Complete religious zealotry tips
It's it's so much more that then
How do I
Another call
Maybe a little bit anti-technology
I'd like you to go ahead and throw away our still
We don't need him get our landlines
Go ahead
Get rid of
Computers we don't need those won't go back home
Isn't for you having your
Play some yoga classes to understand the more angry they make you
The more they control
You're all over the place
You spell yogurt
Disgusting
You think clear
Stress
When you realize
I agree with you but one reason we've been effect
You know I mean
The end is revealing too much
Is that he can't relax
Can't do anything like that because
Anger in the false
Performances
Of rage and all of it
Really makes him a
Attractive to anybody
His career the yelling rants
But you wouldn't be anywhere yellow Piers Morgan and you didn't see
I can just like this is what I call his career is Galveston and he knows that
It's like it's like a
It's so sad it's like a comic who's been doing it it's like a road a,
Been doing it for 20 years
Always wears the same
Because he opens
With a bit about the
Eunos palsy
A bit about it
I think the better version of this what you're saying is it's like
The comic 2
Can't stop drinking because they think the drinking is important to their stage persona
Cuz it's destructive anger and all this is destructive
And he
Feels like
Is no place
Without it
Comic they can usually I'm a lot of people
Find sobriety
Still be just as creative as they were
He's dead right
Not the guys wearing the shirt they don't have that car
That's probably start
Not at all he doesn't have an edge any other way like
It's not what's going to rely on their so dumb and pointless
Based on nothing
That they only make it based on performance
Attracted to anybody
It's like a badge
Joke that a good comic
I can sell because this just gets by on Katie Holmes
You take a step back and think about what the conversation
Justin if he's mad angry about something
Must be real
Cuz there's no way
Fired up
The manipulation comes into it
Edison Shores
Purple penguins or whatever the f***
Anyway
Leave your problems
Because
He has no reason to exist otherwise
So you get another car here
Man
This is fun
Do you remember episode back I was just talking to a guy named Larry gaiters
Did not seem
Maybe some
Topiary
So
He is not on this episode heard
Larry gaiters on another podcast
Ono Ono
Awesome
Go with the doctor
And he was talking about his nana
Everybody
That's going to be communicating with Wi-Fi Towers everything installed hydrogel
He was breaking down that hydrogel
Translated in Latin
Charlotte rampling
To Lucifer
DNA and turned into a luciferian
Outrageous
I don't even know where to begin or end
But that I love that scam still work
Backgrounds
That Groove still work work work work for like
You're as bad as a teen
Fine French sounds like this it doesn't matter too
It might be a little bit more difficult for people to
Google
Wow
Go to
If you go to the literally Translate
Elusive
Verdad
Actually he's right
We go to the 6
And trying to install Melania Trump as a
Liberty at
At all
But I think Melania is hot
Dark Shadow ruler
Alex might be getting in getting on board
Trump knows the answer
The fighting was satanic
All things are possible
Through Christ
Just want to leave
All things
So it is just because Melania said something vaguely religious
You're sounding in a speech
How is this not speak erotic sounding
Do you have no one else
She said not to bully people
I think she's good enough for me
I don't have
Drew
It's because of it cuz it was media's overlooking her
I don't I don't know I don't know I'm just mad
It's this Fantastical let's just let's just pick up to be honest I can explain
Some of this trees
Okay it's because
She comes from a communist country
And that's the reason that Steve pieczenik has built up his idea that she knows
What to do in the circle
Come stances and stuff
Is because we're facing a communist uprising
And she knows communism from the inside
There's some elements of that
Wow yeah
Wow
It's just a lot of
I would even argue
Million
The people
True
And anyway so any one of them are also qualified
Apparently
Alex
We were bringing pretty used to at this point I'm saying that the news is so big that he can't
Skip to it
August 6th episode do
This evolve
The news is so incredible so important so over-the-top
All of it today
Every single scrap of this info
He's over well right but the news is so big that now he has to go
Is on his own interesting evolution is almost like watching
It makes sense now because it's a nonsensical none of it
Does make sense to say I'm overwhelmed
Because there's so much
Do I have to get all of it
Is a coherent statement
Congratulate
Solo
Awesome
So honestly
Everybody was reeling from the news
Letitia James
The New York attorney general came out
Press conference on the 6th at 10:30 Central Time sure was a major
National Bank
That's a bear
The NRA
Wayne LaPierre until the other leadership
For self-dealing
I'm not entirely sure
As of yet
Allegations of mismanagement money that was
Supposedly charitable
There was some cheating going on let's see if she can prove it
Nobody's like
They're innocent of the charges they're just like I don't know if
F*** it up
Probably
Somehow or another
She has to respond to this cuz it just before you went on air
And I don't think his defense is good
We have Letitia James the woman under Cuomo's that ordered and threatened to arrest
Kwame resume current operators and managers
Not
Covid-19 positive patients who have
Other things like pneumonia
Monstrous woman
More than 10,000
What
He is now suing the NRA
Pierre had dinner event
Yeah that's bad
When the Democrats and its hole criminal group
Patterson
So his defense
Yeah well it doesn't have anything to do with what the NRA did or didn't do
Alex is super lucky because
Letitia James is not an unknown person on his show
She's the New York attorney general who sent a cease-and-desist letter to him and Jim Bakker
Weird silver product yeah about that for a couple months now
Thousands of people
Almost
Begging her
Suzuha
There is a sense that I get that he's almost disappointed that it's the NRA and not him
Well as defense of the NRA
Other people commit crimes
So I guess
Yeah whatever
I understand
Misrepresenting a little bit of the chief complaints about
Business management
Of money
Little bit my little cares
Their Twitter account was down for a short. Of time because
Pizza bulshit
Twitter suspends Trump
Almost
Covid-19
False positive
According to a July 30th report released by The American Academy of Pediatrics
6 using state-level data
330 1982 children a tested positive for covid-19
Approximately 8.8% of total
2669 of them required hospitalization and at that point 86 children
Been killed due to the virus
These numbers don't mean anything to Alex you can just say they were secretly all in car accidents
It is a lower rate of general population
That's just say that you're totally fine with these children dying
Being hospitalized
Who may be in higher-risk categories
Now Alex says no children died
And the only evidence
Massachusetts data
No what no children
So there's a zero there any keeps Massachusetts
Okay
What about Arizona
Arizona
Not zero they don't keep numbers
Is it
Report
Except for the ones in Massachusetts Pacific
Arizona
Dicey
This is some b*******
Campaign
Saying goodbye
Kids are basically immune
And so they lock the account
I mean I don't know I don't I don't see that as being
Some kind of a horrible
Abusive Twitter
Authorities are
Knauer's
Yep Alex says
What's up
I know that you are averse to Alex saying I've got a big juicy
Appreciate
No
Give me a little
Caviar caviar
Saban
It's a mistake
Weather going to cut it
Massive
Sabattus rod
Someone being like this
This isn't as good or as luxurious
One caveat
It's from Derek
So yeah I would say that the caviar caveat
Almost be like hey this sounds good
So in that sense Alex's correct
Oversight
Covid-19
Theoretically recovered and then died encountered it covid-19 mortality number
No one's entirely sure how many of these erroneous death so I could be in the pile but the estimates that I saw being thrown around appear to be
Around 1,000 to 4000
Which represents
Between 3 to 10% of the death toll
This is an important issue to iron out because the more precise and
Specific data is the more useful it is
For helping people making form
Decision
I saw this
Disgusted like this was a fine counting that they had initially
His pass
We are at a point where there's just an oversight
Statistics
It turns out that there's a big gap in it
Anyway this was
Miss you specifically Public Health England
Which reflected Edisto over-40 1749
How many Massachusetts
From an article about this in the Daily Mail
The office of national statistics
6 which is not effective
Has confirmed at least 50 1596 people have died in England and Wales
Up to July 24th
The office of national statistics
6 is far more reputable source
Tire number
I do not use the same faulty counted Methodist Public Health England
I was much of a big
For Alex
Also there's no reason to extrapolate this outside
Statistics released by public health in
Like this has no bearing on anything
Outside
Implicate
U.s. number
It doesn't implicate
Yeah it's it's an unfair bad faith
Absolutely
So
What's more complaints about Letitia James General and into some
What is going on
Coronavirus restrictions killing 10,000 children
Vermont
Millions more
That's okay
So she can do whatever she wants
That's why
Okay
Did we
Has it always been this way that the blood is
Like the heart J do like he says black is not
Black he said
Oh she's
Like it was like the black the blood
Is it a hard blow
I don't do it with Alex
Maybe you know there's a thing there and there's a subtext that really means
The 60s
I'd be tossing
Yeah yeah or is it later on today
You know the numbers of people who are entering start
Yes
Un
You know what they're putting that information out for
Courage
People to donate
To help people in these circumstances
Like Alex's solution
Everyone go back to work or whatever
Not her
It is Alex cares about this at all this is an acute problem
Be solved by
Everyone go back to work and things will work out
You need to be if you taking this seriously
Trying to
Solicit donations
Developing world food programs
You should be
You know
Resources the People Gas
Explore Egypt
Dumb two-faced bunny to the two people
He doesn't care
He in the right
Are obsessed with
Whining about problems
That they are actively
Trying to subvert
Solutions
Like that's what they want to do. Maybe I'll just go do this
Oh you thinking about that what about this well okay
How do you solve this if you want to worry about me
Favorite politician of all time wanted to get rid of all foreign aid
Released an ad about Joe Biden
Not even
There was a part there's a picture of him
Microphone
His face
There's also a
He's alone
Him sitting on the ground
And like a basement next to a chair out of the picture
That is cartoonish evil that is really funny
Most people
At that point
Just like CGI in some hair and be like see he's lying
I'm a gunsmith
Pointing out every time there are people trying to get elected
Never get anything done
It's probably about time for America
Decides
Just going to lie about
Now this lying app
Joe Biden
Social distancing
He said bigger rallies in that skill
Hiding
Yeah
Basically is Gary a lot of water in that way
Trump
Basically
Which is the picture of Biden in the basement
Is a living room
He's trying to complete that
The social distance rally where there weren't that many people there by.
Yeah it's so you just lying about it
It is amazing
Skip back to being racist about
Black women in electric
Position
What's matter
George Soros
He's not even an American
He's a dude rounded up his fellow Jews
Set them off to
That was the happiest time is life
Exhilarating
Cold
Probably
That on Fox News
Letitia James
All these all these crazy people
Lightfoot
Gordon
Why is it all black women
Soros is running
Cuz then you can't attack them
I feel like
Wow
You can't do the thing that I've spent the last
Hour-and-a-half
This is based on faulty premise
It's like a lot of people have
Pretty harsh criticism about Lori Lightfoot
Remember Jhene Aiko
Alex has this perception that invalidate
Any black person in leadership position
Because it's like
Soros installed
Meanwhile I think there's a lot of people were pretty
Solid living evidence
You can have
Complaints and criticisms about
Elected leaders regardless
Just that is race
List of Alex
And also silly
This is a silly show
This is a child is a racist f****** child just trying to get into a televangelist
Yeah
Nonsense
Incredibly violent
Scrap yeah
Because
I want to say that I
Google find common ground
On something
I would never work with him on any
Can find a point of agreement
Maybe
Explain everything is over
I was trying to go to bed early last night
Clock
Trouble sleeping
I should just stop there be like he and I can find, and bring you guys have trouble sleeping
Because I knew when I saw the headline what was her saying I read it and others
Roll out
Where they are now
We will wear mask
Home
Computers
Home assistant
They're going to watch you
Carbon dioxide
Movie
Made in the 90s or something in the future you are mastodons
Coronavirus
That doesn't really exist
Call Total mental illness
Talk about a recent episode
When he's talking about the tattoos
Elio
Trackable it's on
Verifiable right
Cuz it's stupid and meaningless
But I want to get this Olive Branch to Alex
I would say that if
Everybody
Regardless of political party
Wanted to make
Coding like an Amazon Alexa at your home
Or some sort of a robot
Yeah yeah
Is a book
It has that kind of thing and if any evil references
Is any party
Anython
Mandatory
Like a cell phone I understand
There's a lot of
Privacy issues that I told her pretty
Messed up
Have to have a cell phone
It makes things more convenient
To make a choice
The same thing is true about these household assistant
There are some concerns that they're listening advertisements
Because of it you make a choice whether or not you want to have
Your house right with the convenience that they offer
If it pivoted to
By law you have to have one of these in your house
I would I would say that vine
I will say there's only one thing that I would allow the government
Sweatpants should be out
Okay Publix
No I mean all sweatpants because we came out
The Temptation is too strong
I believe I believe in Liberty to the point where I believe that human should ever write
To choose whether or not
They can be trusted to wear sweats
Control yourself
Responsible sweatpants
20% of people don't even think of it is real
Ministration of sweatpants
But you know if you register your sweatpants are just going to leave the confiscation
True
Almost as an intellectual exercise.
To be like I should be super charitable to Alex and be like
Empty potential world where are Amazon Alexa's or
You know like
Such a household robot
Are you saying that this incredible infinite power might be abused
Yeah you have to go to in order to
Client agreed
So Alex is begging
4 coverage
Is that
He's just basically repeating things
The Jesse Lee Peterson said on the show when he was a guest
Rap about the leaders of black lives matter
He's calling them
Lesbian
Which is exactly what Jesse said
Mirroring
The previous day's gas
Negative articles about me please
Heard about your black women
Lesbian
Themselves and hate Men in Black
Please
Yeah no kidding
Use hear the music
To me that it's just desperate begging for attention is like
You can't even commit to being as homophobic
Is Jessie
Like Jesse Lee Peterson hates gay people stuff like
Hey
Is black lives matter is run by big fat black lesbian
He will follow that up with being like and they're going to hell yeah
To be like a social libertarian type or whatever whatever
Because I'm a very deep level Alex knows
Those position
Kids are not defensible
For himself
But he has
Do you hear that
Please write about me please I'll say offensive things
This is the problem now and the reason why
Wow I do think it is very newsworthy the trends analysis taken
Familiarizing his audience with the language
Boogaloo murder
No
Perhaps
Yeah
The self
Sacrifice of jowls
And stuff and also just
Violence is Worthy
Bring it up
It also has the effect
Reinforcing
Negative attention that Alex
And these platforms that have reach outside of
Niche market
Black lives matter leaders in La Kaldi's
All these black people
The power Just dare because Soros
Realizes that they can't be
Alright
I'm desperately trying to get someone to call you a racist
We are here for that we have.
And there's always
Leads to ask
Escalation there's no way
You know you you say the same s*** for long enough
You got to what's the next
Things that I can go yeah
It has to be an escalation
For something so far out of my neighbors
No one's going to resist
Chatterbait
Is self-destructive
This is self-destructive to
Parsley because what you're describing
Whenever
It's kind of like
Structuring a comedy show with your headliner first
Wrestling show in the first
Because then what is going to happen
You know and
If in the opening acts your
Murder
Is the only thing
Attention now
Is talk of murder in kamikaze.
Good luck with me
Headline his audience for 25 years in the
It's going to wind up with him
Flaming it out in auto-erotic
Asphyxiation
That's the only way this goes store
Call Ray story
It just makes it
Very clear that he does not care what you doing
Because he supports
D'Angelo
A was paid $5 a year he wasn't
They were flying around the country
You can
You got 10 people flying it's about the same price to get a little private jet commercial
Is it
Results
The second America
Justify the means
It's kind of more like that
Which is crazy
Which is crazy to me
Why because
Wouldn't you be serious
These people are giving God
Advocacy a bad man I would be
Curious not just not least of which because if I'm donating money to them to find out that it
It's not going to
Bring the Second Amendment and said going towards him having a lavish bulshit likes
Added him
The guy but you're
You f*****
Get the f*** out
Because then everybody
Held captive
By Griffin
And they like
Profitable
I know but Zachary bro
Walmer
So I think Alex is also taking this a little bit personal
Because so much of his identity is wrapped up in Gunstock
And then also
Kind of looks like a dick
Because he was against the NRA for a really long time
For the preservation of gun ownership
Like either real Outlets
It's some point you started to change because I get an RA is good now
Ted Nugent on the board and TED talks to me
Oliver North
Was it that
Obit
How to change
Pro-nra
When he could have just
I like the harder stuff
He went mainstream
He's sold out cuz he
He's friends with Ted Nugent
And now he's going to like having to be like
Career Alex is just like whatever it was that I said 10 years ago the opposite
That is true now and I have no reason
He's kind of like a guy who had a stock
That was doing s***
You sold it
Before would have a giant market place right now
Project this is this fantasy of these m************ everybody
For Trump you idiot
Voice
On the right but also like
Hey this is too much
Yeah
If you would have just
Like kept with the
F****** assholes
Got no no politician should ever be trusted yet left and right is a lie
He'd be cleaning up yet
In the any disaffect
Did community
It's the same thing that is easy
You're at the place now where you're like
Nothing
Other than she's the wife of trump but
Trump himself
You don't have it you're he's defenseless to this type of b*******
To be fair
Kind of getting the timeline a little out of order
Like brought to this
If you hadn't
Already
Normalized all of Trumps.
I'm just saying that it's part of the same magical thinking
Omnicef is just an escalation of the exact same thought process the escalation
Possibly only necessitated by
Kind of business to begin with
It requires that isolation
And if you never Escalade you just keep it in like Ron Paul could have saved us
Like
Great
Great what an idiot
Conspiracy about this
That is not good
10 million dollars
I almost defeated the globalist
Italian
We're going to lose everything if we don't start word-of-mouth
I am not rolling over
Like being an RA
Yeah
Say when they
My lawyers have said is okay
Operation
Notice when they did that
Brought
Little bloodthirsty monster Nazi collaborator
Minion
Collaborator
Vicious
First-time callers on this subject
Got the Gauls Alex's saying
Is that the NRA TV because they were trying to placate Letitia James
And I don't I don't
I know about this
Can we hold big dinners for people
Can we ride around on private James
How about the embezzlement
Transferring money from the charity to my personal account without
To get rid of Dana Loesch is show
Placate the globalist really wash
Nashotah Ono
It's all I hope you learn
So I just want
To get sued
Is he
Laundering money for the NRA TV
That's money from the NRA
What is the TV network
TV network
TV net worth
Google
They're Big Stan
DNC
Funded lawsuit
And investigations against. Including Letitia James
What am I going to talk about the embezzlement
The murderer
Cut off by the brake there
I just feel like that
I interpret that
Alex to talk about
And that's his
Accuse a lawyer of
Murder podcast
No I didn't do that
Save the New York attorney general
Josef Mengele
The people and directly make accusations of murder because reaction
That's what I hear anyway because all the stuff
Esoro
DMC back lawsuit
Bulshit
I feel like someone gave him some advice there was like
Coolatta
That's because this
This is where there's a line that you could actually get in trouble today
She know about the law like a you-know-what Soros
She's probably too busy
Doesn't want to get in the mud with you Letitia James
Has given you a seat
Desist letter about your IRA
There might be some kind of an action.
Could be taken against you
Yeah she has indicated
A willingness
The tangle
And I think Alex wants to
That sounds about
Because I think I was already
Take this ship National
Alex has some advice
The NRA
Run ads about
Letitia James
If they roll over
I need to go
Not going to do that I think they should do
Standard right-wing advice there is a conversation
About 6
So make the conversation about why
F****** address the things the conversation
No conversation
She has murdered basic human decency
By daring to attack literally NRA
She murdered everyone
So Alex at the end of this episode
For the third hour
The Gaston
Matt Bracken
Enemies
Takes over quick
Gaston for the 3rd hour
Can blew me away
What
I got my own money
You have a show
Boston Fish
I don't want to put
This is the big one
Give a f*** about you catching up with an old buddy
This isn't like Marin sitting in the the garage shooting the s*** with commentary
Haven't seen you in awhile just thought I'd put
You on TV
Alex
I kind of say this is embarrassing is not the big leagues anymore than
This is not the big league fight like
I got
Big Time cast
Old friend
Yeah
He's also a pastor
So Alex gets some calls
For getting to this a friend of his
Barrel shorthand
This caller seems to not understand what the issue is with the NRA situation
Make sense wouldn't get it
Charlie on business
How can I
Privately owned business
All your flying around on
Tax exempt
Political views and your gas Second Amendment
That's not the problem
Caller is
Expressing like
The
Probably
Privately owned company
Right now they don't have to pay taxes because they're too private
You might not understand the problem
I'm first of all educating his audience about the issues
About making them
Recognize when they don't understand something baby
You should look into it
Why
Is the New York attorney general
That's a question that I didn't
The answer is
Right right
Did the answer of like everything that attacks
Someone who believes the same stuff is us is false
Everything is false
Because that answer is so deeply embedded
I guess it doesn't matter
Everybody has every car block
Ignore
Everything
Has anybody on the right
Ever done it
No has anybody on the left
Is does this mean that whatever it is that the right does to the left
It is just
Defied
In order to stop them from doing the thing that doesn't work
So
John Rex
I don't know
It turns out I didn't know that
Rex
Is not a fan
Of Donald Trump
He got to go out and vote on November 4th
Post midterm post 2018
Right right quick from everything I understand I don't know when his birthday is
Before November
I don't know
Anyway
Despise Trump
How much does much is lapis do
Did this is me this is my coming-out story
To you about my opinions of trump
In 2016
I worship
The guy
I thought you was going to just come in and win Forest wall things he promised
I need to trade at son about 95
5% of things that he said
Biggest supporters always biggest
Everyone got him elected in 2016
Populist movement
That put him in office
Do you want those people just get smacked aside so we could be friends with the bigwigs
Stop getting
Right you're boring me
We got to give him one more chance
Option
Wow
What a Sad lesser of two evils argument that's not good
Develop political position
Adored Trump in the same way that you just
Kind of repeating alecsi stuff now
Maybe that's
What's going on I don't really respect this as a unique position
Do you know who
He sounds
Who's that
Owen Shroyer
He does not sound like Alex Jones
Have you got the same bolt pattern
His age I probably be more likely to watch
War room
I would hang out myself
Absolutely
I'm going to say that right now
Attorney General James
I'm going to stay out of it
Yeah
This is
Silly
First of all because
Who cares
Second because
Hey hey you're trying to sell
This guy is a complete
Broad
Betrayer
You betrayed all of our populace angron
Is everybody knows the first a ride on the theme parks
There in 2012
That election you know not super thrilled
A lot of VR
The unfulfilled Promises of Obama's first term
There were people at large block
Obama built a f****** chain restaurants in the swamps of evil
Eddie f****** lied to us and I don't like
I hate him about as much as I can party but we got of okay
Every
5% right there presentation
Extreme
This is the version of your youth pastor being like
Yeah man I killed five people I used to shoot heroin
Eyeballs
Maybe some people
You haven't done that
You don't you weren't betrayed you don't
I understand you're talking about
Feel any of this
You're just trying to make your dad proud
Shut the f****** your pastor who shot heroin into eyeball
You're telling me a fake f******
Story about
But all hey you're disillusioned with Trump you got to give him four more years
The fuc
The f*** out of here
That's so
Sad
I'm bored
Talking about this f****** Topman
Anyway
No
There's a little bit more Rec
It's making his ark
Lesser of two evils
Trump
Lied to us
He may have betrayed us on a lot of things
I think honestly in a second term
He can turn around
He doesn't have to listen
If he decides
What mr. popular
Consequence
Continued
The only way you
Fluids what he does his wife
Not voting
I know that
This guy outside the train with the
Cards on the table
Wilshire
Scam
Jet toner
Yes
He doesn't figure tourist he does it
Next round straight alright
As long as I say to him first
Excuse me sir can we play straight up Special Report
Lesser of two evils argument
Deweyville argument
Baby
Alex has his old buddy Daryl
Michelle for over 10 years 12 years or so
Manistee
I mean
Amazing
Shuffle men and women who have had
Positive impact on this come
Carpe donktum
Cernovich
Today
Satin match
Hammer only did a remote
Technically
Daryl got a great voice I can see why he's a pastor
God man I got to say
Like
I am
Deep in Infowars
SparkNotes
I understand
Like
Normal
Everyday person if you go up to them and you say Leo zagami
Celebrity
Unless you go to USA probably not
To me like those are names that ring out
Exactly there's other people even lesser gas
Darryl Ruckus
Has been around
I have no idea who the f***
This is prices right he's pulling somebody from the studio Auto
You
Hard-headed list of names
Michelle
Is Daryl rundas an old friend of Alex's for Life made of
That's a good question would not be able to
Confidently answer that question
Little boy
So Daryl run Doterra run
I think
I have a theory
Man
He's very excited
Mike down for this because
Darrell rundus
Is a return okay
Riverside character
With a short time that I have with you today
Bring a history lesson
The people in
Something
That I got from you last time I was on the show
So-called charity Crusher and if you would
Because of significant
All together to where we are today
He has Alex
He has Alex's old bullhorn original I don't know which one is which
Or anything
Is this is one that
That is the one that Alex
This guy bought
God dammit auctioning off
Right
I could I remember the Alex
Oxygen
Yeah
Is it it didn't work because it got
Piece of History
I mean unless there are multiple pressures that have been
Dammit
I don't know man do you think
70 Rainey crashes around
And if he wants to give them to the
Like if he's trying to date a woman he cuts the car and he's like
Tyranny Crusher one baby
I think there's two possibilities
Baked auctioning It Off
Possible and then gave it to his old
Barrel run this body
Darrell rundus has tyranny crush your money
He seems like the kind of guy who might have bought Tirico
And I turns out
Is a zealot
Olivia gold
I'd rather you be hot or cold
Call Jesus
Lazy Christian
Literally sick to his stomach
I'm here today
What kind of a cold action account
The challenge
Michaela
To get up and to get out and just
Freedom n okay
Covid-19
And we're asking all these other things
Hope you're really sound like
You should be hot statistically it's all alive put up against the rest of them
The world
So this guy
If you are
Every joke
About
Seventy-two virgins
Whatever you complained immediately following 9/11 of life
Take it all f****** backyard
Seventy-two virgins loving Christian b******* a******
F*** you it's okay to die
With God I mean if it's
If it's a personal decision
I don't know how much I'm going to
It's the same problem
That you had with like let's say a terrorist attack other people
Not an issue
You getting
Sure I can spread the disease but I personally don't want to wear a mask
So it's
It's cuz I'm right with God so if I even if I do die
Sure baby I'm spreading around to a few
It's fallacious
Because his argument is that the worst thing that can happen
Worst thing that can happen is hundreds of thousands of people could die
The worst thing that can happen as a result of you not consider yourself a part of an intricate
System of interconnect
Did people
Is that you end up through your negligence or your combative miss or whatever
You're like
Blase
You could kill people around you and you can you could be partially responsible for
The death of your loved one
Strangers
All sorts of things
There's so much worse than just
You dying
Yes
Like this is tunnelvisions stuff
It's predicated on
Just religious messaging and it have I couldn't scary
I don't understand how people don't get through this
Concept of like
Look I can't
Scroll
Other people
Possible
You know I can get the I can get the virus
I'm a human being I can wear a mask I can do all of this stuff but
Life is fucken unpredictable
The only problem though is
If I do know that
In fact
And I don't
Do and I don't
Quarantine and I don't do anything and
And I spread it
Directly to only one person or 100 people and one of them dies
I don't see any possible way that I'm not
Personally responsible
Do you know what I'm saying
Abilities very murky
Put it but I had one choice to to not go outside you know
The choice you have
A little bit of culpability
Going to be how you can live with that on your conscience
Yeah yeah
Doesn't care
Don't give a s***
And I want to say this
Who the f***
Is Darryl Ruckus
Bastard in America's Best Inn
Conversation
Well
There is one claim to saying that
But he has
Dot-com
We could stop
The Antichrist
That's what the Bible says
Okay Alex
He also said
Darrell rundus
Runs butterflyers
I was like what the f*** is this
Looked into this
What day is it
This is a compass
Right
And what they do
Okay they sell like
Write a birthday card for somebody
What's in the shape of butterfly
Enough. Here's where it gets bent
So it's
There's two parts of it that are connected by a little in the middle
Axel or whatever
There's a rubber band
Right until you spin it
You twisted
Alright
And then you give someone the book
Fly flies out
That's kind of fun yeah I mean I guess
I guess it I guess that's better than the peanut brittle
What's wrong terrible idea
His nihilistic murder lust is bad
Butterflies is not bad
Want to buy one I think someone gave me one and it flew out of a book
What is a novelty
Like it's a novelty product that you could easily see being sold
You know seasonal stores Vic
Business
All the time
Sure what the f*** ever
Can't imagine this is a billion dollar idea
I don't know look anyways I think it's great
Sure
Makes me wonder if maybe this is broker
Whether it is or not doesn't matter to me because
The content is atrocious
And if
Trump doesn't get elected
Emtime
This country
Is on
Tipping Point
If you won't get up wake up wise up rise up right now
It's just like it was
Belshazzar
When he called in Daniel
Benny asked him to interpret this riding that was on the wall
It was the hand of God writing on the wall scene
You
Sing for me
You taking all that your
Father
And all that he had done for me
And you squandered it
Do you not worship
Miles Inn
The enemies in your gay
He died
What's going to happen to this country
We do not get Donald Trump elected again
It's not
Who votes that counts
What
No
501 c 3
Silly never talked really about how stupid goddess
Like God isn't easy
That's not how you solve that problem conception of God
The Bible's conception is a dumb guy
If you're bringing that to the text
Administrator
Do you buy people Darrell regular
Outlook
I was listening to this first of all I was like this is pretty
F****** over and time s*** going on
This is just like a guy who couldn't get booked on Jim Bakker
But this is just a guy who isn't
Good enough to make the Major Leagues
Alex's
Apparently another platform
Cookie
End times people who make money off of weird products
Man go for a Lea
Just go for a lien
We look we can't deal with Kerry Cassidy anymore maybe we don't need to switch it up maybe Alex needs to switch it up
Some this is just
Straight up
Violent Jim Bakker
Listen to this s***
I think what's wrong with them
Christian or even American
Ready to meet their maker
Find Christian Life
People to do your soul on fire for God you love the Lord know the Buy
What's the secret
Read the Bible
Another believer
Babe I realized
Meeting your maker to all throughout scripture you see
Jesus gives about
For these days you don't have to be afraid you don't have
You guys talk about
A little too much
I don't know man
Really popular these days
Really popular we used to only have like a hundred people
Country
Yeah this this is this is scary
And it also gets scarier
Darrell
Rundus
I'm not sitting on the product product seems fine
As he reveals more of his
Flood
Band
Alex's talking about like a weird skull like a crocodile
Jungwirth guy
You need that studying on this in
Recently recently
Ago
The answer to the
I think you just watch a Jurassic Park
Yeah
Spencer Lee fine
Jurassic Park
So Alex
Here's this and he's like
Look
I don't want invalidated
I think you're saying but I also really
You don't want to
Commit to younger
I can't
Christian
Revising the universe
That our universe is held in power bi something 5
Stimulation
It's fake
Lucifer
Warriors
Discern
Do your research
So it was in the news
What just happened
Open the portal in the demons
Snoozapalooza Newsmax
A religion is boiled down to we can open a dimensional portal something evil comes out
Invalidate Hazel religion
You also have
Turtles are real
No I mean you're saying that they could create a portal there
Collider
Acolyte
How is it that science can open those if your f****** God is weak
Jordan I don't think you heard me
Summit
It was not in the news
Something something evil came out in
Subway Rogers like
Photo
What does various mean
Trump president
Wow
Flippant like totally portal
All right look
I can't do the younger of stuff
Yeah I've also
What Alex is saying
Suggest to me
Then if this is a simulation
His religion
Boobies transform into
Supporting the simulation
I feel like for someone who talks about the Matrix all the time
Okay so is the Bible
Dissimulation
So doesn't that make the
Bible meaning
Bye
I'm fun to say
Mostly because I like
Short
The contempt is drippy
Daryl run
Buddy
His perceived enemies who were also Alex's animes
Theodore Seaman
Straight
All the power
A politician the elitist
Power now
So therefore they stack
Those children that's why their pedophile
That's why
Empowered
The saddest YouTube bloodline
Isn't that what you
Him today though
Think about it
Very impersonal
Anyway
He believes that there the United States
The mystery of Babylon
Scripture
He kind of
Is a little bit of a
Pre-trib Rapture guy
Which should be a gigantic problem
Big 4
Yeah I'm sure he's basically the globe
Honestly
I believe it mystery Babylon
Is America
I believe that's what John saw it
Was revealing asteroid
I could be anything you live there
So to speak
Salvation
Will skate
Tribulation
But the rapper
The time is coming
One could argue
Nebraska
Tribulation
Turbos who died for
Lettering price
Linda.
Leaving world
What series is going to die
Jesus rules for 1000
When's the raft
Wait
Rivers will be spared whatever this awful thing
Is that what the tribulation is
Tribulation is a
Tribulation is like
It's more like administrative cleaning
Like they're they're downsizing
Right you know it's not the Wrath
It's not you it's me comes when
The dragons are outer what open
This dude just straight-up like apocalypse is here and diagonal
This is this is
Like even for Alex this is a bit this is Ludacris
A bit much
Call Will almost all of them eventually you're going to be
Escape
Most of those people
People get saved a lot of people are going to realize they missed the bus
Literally
7 years ago
Deal with it
Not being able to buy or sell without
Taking the market
Can have to barter
Stand firm to the end of we saved and then
Come back and set up
Things will be great again
Some reason
And he starts
Gemini
All the rest of those
Byron
Trailed off a little bit
East 1000 years but Dunlap in the mirror
How's the seven years of tribulation
Nobody visits
Okay
Going to start up
Alright so let's say I don't want to do this
The Antichrist imagine in this scenario
Brightwell
One last clip
Talking a little bit about his younger years here
I don't
Make this timeline make sense
Sanctum
No no
Christian but I was about I was about
Koala koala
Consciously
Evil
Or maybe me
Example
Nitpick
I don't understand
Exactly
Darrell rundas picker
Is that according to Alex has been aware of all of the
These evil plans
Globalist
At the young age because of his parents
Skip to this stuff and I
Conspiracy at 12
And it opened up his buying to how the globalists work
Plans
The men
Apparently he's a subconscious Satanist it's 17
Yeah it's just doesn't make sense his backstory
Too convoluted for for any of it to make sense
Because of just like these dumb
Stories of lichen
I had a big picture but then I saw everything
You can retcon whatever you want. Send
Bulshit
Susan Powter
Control
Fox up
Person
Got obsessed with ideas about the New World Order probably started dreaming about it thought it was a mission from God
At least his backstory
He's killing it
Is made up backstory
And his real backs
Alex is real backstory sucks just as much as made of
NOAA B picking is one thing
Maybe I'm taking it a little bit more personally than I need to go like nip picking is one thing
When I when I hear Alex tell these stories like
IPI did ascend
That you have unresolved issues that are maybe motivated
And it's kind
You as a human as opposed to a
Psychic who talks to God all the time like you want you live at
That's not
Assessing analyzing taking Alex's words in context
Nitpicking would be me saying hey Daryl
Really
People who were in the tribulation literally and metaphorically
The boat which means
There's a literal
Right
Newsmax
Yeah
Dick
Wild Christian
Zealot
Is apparently friends
Horn
And selling butterflies
Suck this noise
What is stupid
Yeah it's to be a real
Real weird
. of time
I think we have to
You know I feel I feel like
It's really a mess
And sometimes you know there's import
Sometimes
Yeah you would
It's hard to comprehend of an episode we do where it's like
Lebanon and Beirut
Right
Conspiracy
I'm going to make up that it was Israel
Specifically Massachusetts which I assume means of the world
And then also
Dumb dumb
F****** a******
Alright we're back button
Your area
Holding
Alex