I have great respect for knowledge but I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guy
Knowledge fight
Jordan
What's up
Wow
I have
I've been noticing a bit stagnation on Alex's
Is Bart
And I feel like
Because we are show the talks about Alex and
Do you know where we kind of have to just go along with whatever he does
A lot of the times it leads to our content Maybe
Feeling a little stake because
If if the source material is iffy
Right then I mean if it's a 8
Lead us into a situation where
And so I was trying to brainstorm and think about ways around isn't one of the things that I consider you know
Murder
You nailed it dammit no
I was thinking about the past maybe we could do it live
In that spirit
Did we always have a phone no I couldn't afford it any
Idaho
Sony on nip runaway no
We can get we can afford a phone last year and I couldn't afford it back then
Like to be able to do more of
Outside of
We are both
There are people who have other lived experiences I would love for their voice
Has to be able to
I'll be heard on the show
But at the same time he's not really room for guests so tough
And
Bringing anyone else in isn't fair or right
One of those shows
Anyway
Obviously they've never listen to the show
And everybody's like okay you're not caught up
That would be like
450 episodes
Sitting next to somebody and then being like what
Incorporate better but what
Call and leave voicemails
Here we go
Country code
773 Chicago area code
Words
I bet lots of anagram
I wish that I was a child because I found a phone number that was 77
3 up
Penis
I can't say no
I can't do it
It not me asking if I was a child
Perhaps
Cat guys
Now my answer is murder that's the situation
You'd like to leave a message
I can't promise it will play all of them on the show given that the other may be a bunch
I've no idea how many people call the police but you are welcome to do that
Is that
We got to go we got to listen to voicemail so then we
Voicemail
We're turning into maybe that maybe that'll be all I got is a phone number what's your
This is a situation
We got any of The Gift of the Magi Cirque
Do you have to have some sort of a gift for me that gets rid of a phone number
Taking away people's phones I ended electricity
The new album by washed out
Is
Really really good I have the chance
I think it came out last
The last Friday
And a chance to do a real deep
Listen today
Really great do you know what that is
No
It's like chillwave
Okay
Let me give you an idea of what it's
11-11-11
Keanu Reeves
Just had a bad situation happen in his life sure he's on a bus
Looking into the middle distance
Some watch that starts playing
Keanu Reeves
A Walk in the Clouds
Come out to the bridge and then the same song is playing but he's moved on with his life
Okay same song
Scraps
Jordan interesting stuff
Recovery
The period of August 7th to 9th 2020
Our login
The Weeknd
So we got to have that that business
Go over
Book to sign up and Reporting show the 1st
Hi Greg next
Lieb
Exhaust
Chris
Bob
I'm a policy wonk
Johnnie Taylor
What was that show crazy blank
Next
Yeah probably
Spell bureau
420 we would appreciate it take that to generosity lay it down on a pan
Marinara marinara
Delivery under 30 minutes
I never pay
Is that
Splinter Cell
I guess I could remember that was one of the times it's so funny
I believe there's at least three
I don't remember
Jordan
Further business
To go over
To take a little peek into the mailbag Z
This is from
W
And also say I'm scared
Because
Oh boy
3 water filter
Parentheses sap as though it's a stripper name
You don't you don't
Cork a tree and then get water out of it
Because that's not what comes out
Then maybe I don't know
I'm not a f****** Arboretum guy whatever
Arboretum
Narrow is the flavor which is a little terrifying I'm excited to give it a try
It smells pretty good I would have a taste
Myself here
That's not spicy
I'm not even positive I get an a habanero from that
I'm noticing something with shelters and the level to which there is great
Most of them
Really good
Very light
And then sort of mainstream Seltzer's Bill across the
Polar
Those are more busy
Those are everyday sounds
Some of the newer ones
I tried those sanzo
I got sent to us
And I got to say
Mind-blowing
Only in the sense that
Calamansi was one of the flavors the other two flavors are lychee and mango is there like I
Kind of headlights
The flavor is Sturgis
I know whatever
Ifucking mango is calamansi
Euro to dollar
I think I saw this on a cooking show title
I didn't look it up
Buddy's great 81 out of 100 from 2019
Damn
I'm going to give this a high score
I think this app is really good little while though I need to think on it
It takes pretty good though thank you so much Charles
Alright Jordans get down to business
This
Episode on the 7th
Sucks okay
August 11th is utter trash
Okay
Doesn't belong on the air
Most of it is just Alex rambling about how come out and said this might be the last
Time you see me
You keep saying that
The first half hour of his f****** show is about that
Do I have a lot of enemies
This may be the last
Time Yosemite
Lot of very very rich
But they are not happy with what I'm doing
But
We have one
To do what
No other president
Would do
A favored nation
Caribe
Dubai from Other Nation
Much less cost
Nobody
And there's a lot of unhappy people
And a very unhappy
We got one shot to save the country they may kill me
Conversion
Use the military awning
News article say what Alex says they do but
Is
Huge for our
Alex its most of his attention is on this
Yeah it alright I heard a really weird dude say something weird
I don't know why.
And I don't care
In order to escalate by something
It's not it's not organic in the beginnings of the on the 7th at least
Couple times about that
So the other things on Alex's mind is this New York attorney general of course who is
Pnra in Civic leadership of the NRA
Right Alex happens to be friends with the creepiest weirdo gross a****** monster
Ted Nugent
Answer yes Ted Nugent come on and talk about
From the NRA are the attack
Freedom
Freedom haters
They are
Is the time
Everybody you know
Because
Tribes
Haters
Daddy
Make them go crazy
200 by 100 pushups today
Savannah Nugent plugs his website where people can now
Forget that the problem here was that the NRA was taking people's money and then using it on themselves
So by doing this you're just essentially
Princess so the problem is financial malfeasance and I really think that the solution is flooded with cash
Another way to solve this problem
So Alex
Tattoo complaining about General
S*** about Trump
Like one of them the photo shoot
Yeah
Happy about that dude
He's complaining about these generals a little bit harsh pivot
Real weird
Week 4
Another start shooting off their mouths against El Presidente
That means they're signaling
10 million-dollar
Tell me when they leave office
They wanted
Domino's deals
Shot cam cuz their webs
Parade
Make it a little thing in the mail
General milley or whoever we know about your mistress
Jamal from your house we know about it to Buddy Boy
Turn down Oprah Winfrey politically
All right what you do to me
They want to eat spaghetti
Punch your butt.
Pedophile
Oprah Winfrey
Girls
12 13 14 15
Jeffrey Epstein
Anymore
But
From the generals into yelling about Oprah
Alex has been talking about Oprah a bit lately
Is that a thing we're still doing
It's been like over the last couple days before this he brought her up a couple times
I don't complain about her as much as I used to that kind of thing and I took notice of
But I was like
What is it why
You like I use complain about her a lot now I don't
You could randomly pick a date and criticize Whoopi Goldberg again because there are two things that
They have in common that he hates true yeah
Behar when it comes to the Alex claims The Joy Behar
Tried to have sex with him when he went on those two
I thought you just love
No
Call Johnny
Developments on forston occupation
Better now all out the oven
Food
I feel like we shouldn't he should be in jail for something about
Had Del bigtree on like a couple again
Just couple days before that
Clearly some sort of coordinated
Quite frankly I didn't
He has any association with it
Andrew Wakefield kind of promoting a new
Film
He's putting out
And so we work together on facts
They're related a mess
Do it
I just checked on IMDb I have no idea there's not even a
Documentaries
I do not have the time or respect for his opinions we've already talked about in the past
I need some not doing that again
Should not be
Allowed
Be on the radio
It's a mess
So we get to the eight
Saturday
Vincy broadcast
Things up
Going to be commercial free
For the next 2 hours going on our TV and radio satellites
But I know
Hundreds of houses
People tuning in
Right now
Alex Lee use an hour and a half into this special reports
Just a little bit of content
December
About child abuse
Additions coming up so if you're sensitive about those things
Please tread carefully
Alex has decided that he's going to do most of the Saturday show about Oprah Winfrey
And
A particular
What did you just say
And it's about a particular business
Representation that he's making that is monstrous
And
Religious
When I was reading about Oprah Winfrey
And all the reports that have come out over the years of her and not just being a lesbian
Weather for that
Sounds like one of the hidebehind
But her being underage girls will then you have her hanging out with Harvey Weinstein best friends with him ever hanging out with
Jeffrey Epstein
Hangout
With Bill Melinda Gates
Weinstein Jeffrey Epstein
And you have people digging into all the weird speeches she's given
Hold onto your horses here on play the moment
You get a car
Crocheting children enjoy being molested
Is
Representation of what she was saying
This is part of an interview
She did in September 2019
Kind of sexual
Sure and so they're at they're having this interview
And it's in the context of
The difficult
Believe that survivors of abuse have
Surrounding their memories about it
Sensations
Can feel good
Experience even though it's a victimization
To understand that at the time
And it's also a part of the conversation that she's having a
The the
The victimizer will make the person that they are victimizing
Feel good
Are designed in order to make you feel good
Which makes it very difficult as you get older to put things
To the proper context
As you grow in your heel
It's
Honestly monstrous like I have no words for how disgusting
Sing this is
For Alex
Is that Alex yells about
Like Hollywood
Abusers all the time
And this is Oprah giving a platform to people who have accused in Hollywood
Someone very powerful in Hollywood
So why is he
He just doesn't want to see the ground or something because everybody
But him and Trump being
Into abusing children
You can deny the
Or you can go headlong into it
And just
F****** a Tackett from The Fray
You know
Like of
Horse vets
But that's but she's
Victim
They're giving them to a platform but Alex
Doesn't f****** do at all
He's a monster
Something
You know
So you can either be like know she's faking it and doing all of this stuff and all that or you can just go straight
Just like
What makes it sound like
Encouraging
Do children or something
And it's just it's disgusting
It's a lot of this episode
The Saturdays
Makes me like really not want to cover it because
You know it's beyond the pale
This is about where it's at
Milo yiannopoulos literally said those things on Rogan's podcast
But he was on this
Year
That's cruel I hate this f****** hate
Cruel
So that makes it really shity when Alex's stuff like this because I mean it's just an outright lie
Destroy Oprah Winfrey that she deserves it
Starting pedophile supporter bare metal
And where to go out to everybody
I want to take the gloves off and my buddy said Roberts
Call Don
And then you need to put
What's brass knuckles
That's right
Where the point now where I'm not just going to sit here and fight you my bearfest
The brass knuckles on
That'd mean I'm an exaggerated Ally
But it may hit you I'm going to hit you to break your ribs
And break your jaw and not
Your eyes out of here
The butcher answer the ground
It doesn't mean you're going to exaggerate and lie but anything
You can't not exaggerating by
F******
Talk nonsense
Spa Q
What could you puff your chest up a little bit
4 minutes
The problem was
He's going to small
You know Alex
He's in this in the space where the globalist are making their move
They're about to take out all the Patriots
All that
It's kind of realizes if you listen to slip it's pretty clear that he realizes like I said this s*** 1000
Sometimes in the past
Why would anyone believe me
Every second I'm thinking what are we doing supposed to leave State could what are we doing to expose our operation what do we do to warn America that this
Just like the past attack
They're just probing and conditioning us to stand down
Outrageous stop this is a big attack
This is a big Tech
This is a Big Mo
Well the biggest
Waze alarm
The globalist are more afraid of this show
There any other
Carlson is
Riveting very populous
He doesn't amazing job
Money's unable to get into the really hardcore stuff that we are
He recognized
Yeah because
People just ignore you and he would get the advertisers would go away
I think Alex
Framing is is so stupid
Dislike
Hey you know I said it's a big one bunch of times but this is
And now the only thing that you can
Do
Promote my show because the globalists are so scared of it
You know how I know I've told you what a bunny
I give you one Outlet
Me
Yeah
Here's my problem
When we have nursery rhymes that correctly outline the problem and the solution
Adult should not fall
Do you know what I think I cried wolf
Tons of them how do adults not be like
Oh I remember the nursery story that I heard when I was
Decided that I will ignore that.
Alex is getting bitten by that snake
Right now
We know from past experience that
Pass
And then it didn't work and got mad at them thinks it's full of s***
Yeah man he sold a bumper sticker that said I am Cube and then
Threatened to expose the people who are doing Q at the beginning
And I never did any day from a week
Nothing happened
Arbitrary
I'm holding you hostage
I did not follow through it all because
You're a dumb
Liar but I forgot the return address so they don't really know
Contact us Oxo steel with it
I'm honestly
I told you I know who shut up
Chewing on a few years ago
One person us intelligence in a person
Their idea
Taken away from them they got pissed about it they told me that
Then it became his anti-israel thing
And and
But then it got taken away from those people
And became like a real movement against the pedophile ring
Months ago
About 3 months ago
Sticker out saying I was cute
Be careful to try to get you to do stuff
Make sure you know you're working with
Citizens getting involved in
Exposing conspiracy and rollers a good thing
About 3 months ago
It's becoming something positive
Started good
Because I looked at how I put outside of your children with you lady
All things that happen
They were positive towards me so I liked
How do we put out stuff about Spirit cooking
Devil worship
Child kidnapped
New World Order
Well we do it through 14 and 8
Alright whatever
Wayfair store in Alex
This is just so pathetic
And actually I honestly know exactly what's going on I knew immediately what was going on
Now it's gotten so huge and so Grassroots that I guess
The original creators of it thought it and fail
But then it got even more successful so I'm all for it
And the less said about it
But in your queue person
You should watch Arlington Road
And learn how
Spell trick YouTube
Sure Arlington Road
Now they'll use
You think you're with q
And make you think you're a secret agent to getting orders
Another thing
So what's going on here
F****** nonsensical now there's so many options
Different groups and a bunch of people are being kicked off social media
To the point where there's going to be rampant decentralisation to be able to snipe some of the audience
Try and create this narrative like I know who started it and now it's back on the right track and
How many how many Cuckoos have we dealt with at least at least two cute
Yeah
Intelligence people
By who
Give it away
On specific who those people are there without no matter
Is it squatter's rights
Send someone
Subway
Even is a fake story
And it's not real
Because I mean there's nothing ate mostly
Okay and I don't have time for it we don't care
Because one of his interns found that stupid clip from
Make it look like she
Supports child abuse
So good when your only job as a researcher
Just check blogs posted
I just find something on some sort of
Easy stuff
So we get in on the 9th
On Sunday
And
Alex is back
On the Trump said that you might
What's going on
Man
Is Oprah going to kill know Oprah is not really all that on the way
Headliner Gateway pundit
Lemurs swirling
President Trump's recent actions
Indicate something huge
Is about to happen
A while but
Detroit
Central and East Asia
Few hours
They tell you that you can put
Your money on it
I can tell you that
At least you're not rumors
Are Shoreline
Volcano
Machine gun
No Lie
Peaceful metaphors
I'd like to remind you the Gateway pundit
Alright he's nobody
Text Lee fact
That are swirling
Trump
Bat signal
Robin
Poison ivy
Confusing
Haha
Alex is telling me that there is swirly fixes his job to grab them from the air and put them in a bulleted list for
Information to
Besides that that made presented
Swirl
Swirl exact let those facts keeps world
Well we have nailed down and put on a bullet
Trump
Signal
Okay how about the phone
Alfred
Harlequin
He may not be
Around
Carlisle
Mr. freeze
His government having to go underground
During the attempt
That's a nice reference
Very very cryptic
People's attention
Are because
The talking point even in the local paper today
Thrown out of the house by the
We're not leaving office
Sounds right
So they can trick a group to run a military coup against
Before the election
He was planning
They're just normal eyes
Mom's going to get killed
Everywhere
People were talking about
Whether or not Trump is going to respect
Results of the election
Things that are completely against
It's the norm
Alexis
So yeah I mean like and it's not because of that stuff it's because they are trying to normalize this
Caution because they plan to cool him before the election
So great
Yeah this is this is one of those things where it's
Like I want to shout this
To everyone with
Animotica
Will power
You can use these people need to be treated like children
You cannot talk about
What we should do with our
Chrissy with these
But you need to be like
Here's what we're going to
You can sit down yes they're violent children but that's the only way to deal with it
Yu-Gi-Oh
Yeah I hear you and I understand the point I even have a trouble
Giving a prescriptive
Kind of answer that you are you're saying treat them like children
Woodwork
We'll see I don't I don't know
Associate of yours support
Like a supervillain
What kind of juice
You're you are putting together a nicer area visitor for a old old man that house bugs
You know what that is true I put together terrarium for old man's house phone and
Very much
You're welcome
I got some little a mini Easter Island because they think of that that is something that evokes Wonder
And I want to this mantis to have Natural Curiosity about its surroundings
Think about the
I gave supreme power
And I give you those things you never have to want for anything ever again then I come and consult you
Super advice I don't like this week
I want to be you like a
Advisor pet
What did I can put you in a cage we can put you to terrarium
If you work against you now
I guess if you're like cage or terrarium I'll pick Terraria
As your older than a good friend of yours and I will give you the choice of cage or Terraria
Great guy
And make sure this never have
So
This is where
Confused about
In the 90s
Hundreds of different
Last time I checked
300000 Acres
But just the Barton Creek Canyon area
The middle of Austin
West of Austin
Some areas
Hundreds of millions of dollars of US taxpayer money
Billion total now pay.
Aquaphor
Charge Zone
And it would always be free and open to the public
Something like that
You can't well now
They proposed charging you to go on there
Horses in America
What to do it
Covid-19
Literal
Club
A plan makes sense now
What's going on
You know there
Are you in all of us.
Tell my wife
What are you doing
Register
Allowed to be in there
Understand
The biggest
The Greenbelt
This is a great story by the way
Somebody every five
Some areas by deeper water weather
What are we doing is my grandma telling me this story
This show is so weird
Saturday
Yelling about Oprah Winfrey
Be suggesting the covid-19.
In order to charge people to go to Barton Springs based on the fact that his wife
I got turned away
There you go Dan it makes
Perfect
Sent this is such a good microcosm of Alex is taking personal issues and turning them into
Inconvenience temporarily at a park
This is all about the land Bible say about these in Austin
I knew it all along
Knew it all along and it just clicked when my wife was
Temporarily bother with her friends
Tennis partner
Listen to that
This is weird he has promoted you had like a video of himself going down there
Excited
Excited for that I was blown away I haven't laughed this hard it's Alex's done in
After
Yeah
This pathetic hilarious was a real palate cleanser
Is he doing like a a Redux of The Grotto
With nobody
In there what it what happens is
Giving too much away
Alex's wife got turned away or something.
Tu ik you tricked me into going to Parksville whatever
Alex goes back with a camera guy
I tries to provoke
Confrontation
With a tiny tiny
He has a tiny Bulldog enough
Looks really small and funny
Yells
A bunch
You can see them
Looking at their phones
Tiny bull horns that make your voice
Quieter
Do you know that
So Alex gets to talking about
Covid-19 death discrepancy
Maybe one of them
Important things that we could point out right now Alex is dancing around a really dangerous line
Actually Crossing it
Sort of casually
He better be really really careful
But all these regular people that died
You know all the rest
$60,000 US Post Office
Car wrecks
Gunshot wound
A seven-year-old boy.
He fell down in the shower
His head got a seizure in blood
And I get an Instagram
Existing condition
Existing until he hit his head and died
To create fear and all these gullible
Stupid
Sheeple
Weather
So Alex is lying about that seven year-old
This is a boy in Savannah Georgia
Utah State covid-19 numbers
I want to sing to the media claiming his death was covid related but in actuality fell in the shower and hit his head
Alex making that up
According to an August 8th article in the Atlanta Journal
Journal-Constitution
The child
Had a fever fueled seizure
While in the bathtub and brown
The article is
Pretty clear about the situation
The County coroner Bill wessinger quote cautioned that the full results of the Georgia Bureau of Investigation autopsy
You're still pending
And maybe a long time coming
But he said preliminary investigation suggests covid-19 gave the boy a fever which
Trigger to seizure
Bathing
How to investigate the circumstances surrounding a seven
Seven-year-old child's death
That's what I think is absolutely disgraceful there's no excuse for behaving that way
Also he might want to trade
Very carefully around the territory of quotes
Fake people being used to create the image of death
Why is that ever been an issue
That's very very close to crisis actors talk
If I'm being honest this is a really scary development
This covid -
His whole race specific bioweapon stuff was dumb
I'm either calling car crashes covid stuff is dangerous
Idiotic pursues this line
Conspiracy much further he's going to put thousands of people at risk
They're stupid but there's a distinct difference between conspiracies about covid deaths being mislabeled covid-19 and
Fake people being used to boost death numbers
Never be crossed without
Very good evidence
And specific information
You cross that line when it's just a matter of deaths being mislabeled
The villain is the nebulous global
It's the Fat Cats the elites the man
It's the people that the audience can shake their fists up and
Turn off
Triple M to direct your impotent outrage somewhere
Alex can take that directed the profit from their fears
Because it's real people dying real families grieving and then someone
Cheating the spread
Once you cross the line into the idea that it's fake people being used to boost death numbers
The victims and their families become possible villains
Which is super dangerous
It's what we saw was Sandy Hook and why the crisis actor a narrative
There were so destructive
If you believe that the victims were actors that you have to believe that the families were in on the whole thing
Probably
Alex suggesting they're fake people being used to boost covid-19 opening that door
And he better be super f****** careful because he could f*** around and courage of her ass
My campaign
It's almost unfathomably large
Vagueness here is one of the largest problem
If Alex's asserting that there are fake people in the covid death totals and doesn't speak very specifically about what names
He's talking about
He's introducing the idea to his audience that any of the names of victims they see could be fake people
Can you imagine a qanon type online community doing some research into covid death
7 dachshund people
People who they suspect of being fake covid
I couldn't imagine that a few years ago but
What Alex is doing here is the first step down that road
It doesn't mean that it necessarily will grow to that
That
This is the first step of
It's reprehensible
Especially considering
He's currently being sued for doing exactly this
As it relates
Sandy Hook
And yes he knows
You knows the effect that this kind of thing can have
He knows how he can read traumatize people
He has every reason to fully understand the consequences of his actions
And yet he refuses
To learn
Yeah
Yep you can't you can't do these these sorts of narrative
They're monstrous
Yeah I'm
We are at the space now where the the default though is to assume that there's nobody
The default is to assume that
It will
Continue to ask
I have a hard time believing that
Taking that first step doesn't mean take
Taking all of this
It's hard to say right now cuz I'm a recording this on the same day as this episode
I don't know what he's going to do
You test that water and
You know if there's no reason not to Why not start yelling about how there's all these fake death
And that's not even that's what so many people want to hear
So many people want to hear
They want to hear that
Even look this was a try this is awful
Call even if you don't
Or anything
That you still have to
Zaful
And you have to account for it
In what you do that's why you see Republican leaders being like
Reopen School some people
Account
Just put it in our f****** numbers
What people really want to hear it
There isn't even a problem
Well there isn't the problem isn't that people are dying the problem is that they're lying to us
I think I think if people would love that
I think it's unrealistic that anyone would ever
Ever really even accept that
What date
Can do
Is except
Anything that takes things down a degree
You know you take things down just a little bit
But it's less than you think
Take the ads
Soften the blow
I mean
It's pointless and it doesn't it doesn't get anywhere
Productive
And I only see trouble that could come
And I pray that it doesn't
Especially in the way that Alex has
Has been escalating is violence
Narrative
And the way he's been talkin about all the time
Take one for the team
If there are fake dead people
Are you not do not think that someone might put two and two together there
I'm thinking I should do maybe
You know
Sandy Hook victims families were harassed
Set verweij
Like it's not outside the realm of the behavior
Alex on this
Past behavior isn't the goodnight
Performance
So
I don't know
I mean the scale
Astana Dino Sandy Hook
There's there's a limited
There's like a relatively limited number of people that you
You can harass
But with this
I mean
How many people haven't been touched
Everyone's crazy
So Alex is mad at me cuz of course he is
And I've noticed that he's been complaining about
One thing kind of in
Particular
In the
In the past couple days
You got to think of
The vaccine
Is it true
To be able to get a
Pandemic
To no longer be a pandemic
But to be something that's well
Control
Well Control
Great rebuttal buddy
Left field
Great rebuttal
Defraud
He's been really obsessed with the patch
The first pitch
Well I mean it was good
It seems really reasonable
To play a clip of a guy saying don't worry about
I get what you're saying but
It's just a tool to get things under control
That's hard to argue with
Wow.
Are you not even manly enough to throw 85 down the pipe 60 ft 6 in
How can I trust you with this vaccine information
Like a seventy-year-old
Doctor
Head of Department I don't expect
The 12th
I don't
It's on my list of qualifications
They demand we should have
Test for Every Federal in
Employee
What kind of gun
I can tell you that
Troubles me to show people he's kind of obsessed with it but
Study is not scary
Say something that I always say every 6 months
As well
26 years
Early on
People send me letters
You're scared
My wife or you're scaring my brother or my father or my husband or my son
You know that there
Change it
And why are you trying to scare my fam
So you understand why qanon is a problem
Are dogs barking
At 2 a.m.
That the house Nexus bonfire
And I was like 10 years old I got a body up
Fear-mongering
When the dogs bark
Even though their house is on fire
Some electrical fire
People
Yeah
He just you know like
He does metaphor
Saved his neighbor's house
I don't care
He's using the story to illustrate how he sees himself in the world
He's this kid who hears the dog barking and wants his neighbors at their house is on fire thereby saving their house
Very simple thing
Fires
To the country
It seems like he's never not
The hero in his
That's a great story if the house is on fire
Must be on fire
The fire marshal is secretly told him
It has all the telltale signs of a neighbor's setting the fire themselves to scam insurance money
The only information he has to go on his dogs barking and the rest of the story is infantile mind
Writing
Weird narrative textual eyes the dog barking
In a way that fits the view of the world that he has
Which is basically just from movies
Is neighbor's house is on
Inspire
And he's like
It's all fire that much look at that other house over there that's not letting go talk to that
The first neighborhood
When you metaphorically hear a dog barking
You should not assume that your neighbor's house is on fire
Because there's a ton reasons
Princeton's by neighbors dog barks
Whenever I come home and my keys
When you metaphorically hear a dog barking you should check to see if the house is on fire
This is the stuff that's missing from Alex's process which is basically
You're what you're welcome to be worried that your neighbor's house is on fire
And then gather evidence
Other than a dog barking
How to hunt for doesn't work because in his work in his career as an anti New World Order propagandist
You've been able to find all
Wilmot instances of dogs barking but there's never really been a fire
Even so every time he hears a dog barking eats if you don't believe him
Forties in the fields
The fiery k9stud
His career is all bark no fire
And
Yeah
Covering up
Undoubtedly
So this is funny Alex
But when you swear to God
Blasphemy
What is my witness I've never consciously lied
Anybody
Politics and issues
Have a lot to a girlfriend I'm cheating on her side like that Elliot
What
Are we doing
What are we doing here what are we doing
What are the
Alex is 100% intentionally lied about
I would be more worried that was true it's all of the lies that we heard him tell has been just like
Unconscious for uncontrollable
Purposeful life
Yeah it would be like
Have a neurological
Because there's even just intention on this next to
This isn't
No it's not
I mean we can talk about what the implications of that are later but
He's rambling he starts talking about
If you're a random person
Pictures of LARPing the Susan
Fantasy world where you're playing video games all day
For you it is
America's first
He said all they're bunch of wimps
Intimidated
Yeah well
Roblox are you
Somebody
Shakira
Quadriplegic
F*** you man
Disgust
At the end there but also it's a lie
Alex says a video but he's played a bunch of times and someone interviewing Foster earlier
They were asking why you was carrying
Yeah he explained that they had some friends who have gotten arrested and so like their first amendment
Was being encroached exercise
And the guy asks him
Do you expect to have to use that
And he said if I run into any police
I won't need you to that would keep you I would be dead
Yeah and the people who want to f*** with us
Our pussies
Yeah basically
They're not going to start anything
He's not saying that he likes to intimidate people
This is Alex
I mean
That's an intentional
Or else
It's just
So subconscious for him
Making up reality as
He assumes it is as opposed to how he knows it to be
Bunch of times
He has every reason to know what the Foster actually said
Alex's version of reality experience
Is experience to him as of Jack
I think I have an experiment
That I really think my
BF might be a Luminator
I would really like
Too well that would
The Great
Exactly no
What if he had to like sit down and just
Transcribe
A video
Just like Plano
Here we're going to play this video
All you need to do is write down what
What they're saying
Choose to do it so I would like to see how he what what does he hear
Does he physically here in his brain cuz
Can't always be what people are saying
Must not be able to know how much
Depictions that he provides grocery store it's a month.
You just f****** around or do you actually.
I actually hear or experience is that like he takes this video of something
As Gary Foster saying these things
And he has turned it into I like to intimidate people
And it should be
Take all context away from it this is a guy who's at a black lives matter protest
It's a guy with a
Asserting the Second Amendment Alex should be 100% on board with this
Cuz he's against the cause of whatever he's like now
He hasn't gone he's trying to intimidate people
It's it's nonsensical
It's it's very worrying
Who's going to take care of your quadriplegic roast yourself
Piece of s***
That's the type of s*** that you only see in like a f******
Like that the level of psycho
Required
To say that s***
It's really
A person devoid of
Of apathy
Yeah
I'll be the other thing
Garrett Foster
His new Facebook group
We're going to put these terrorist attacks that never ended up happening
Until you combined those two
Eat like you single Foster was a
The part of that
There's no indication that that is the case
And so you should go f***
Scoop before we get into this really fun
Trip to the park
You got a big scoop
Yeah this is fun
This is the play
You know like we were
Look up the coach of the
Patriots
His party wouldn't
He persuaded the governors of Wisconsin and Michigan
President
Media
Military
Mega
Bigger
Just like an hour out of breath
New York Times article about some more games exercises
Working through scenarios that a bunch of people
Like a bunch of different stuff
And I came out like early August
The end of July was already an article about this in the Atlantic
This isn't some kind of weird secret thing
One of the scenarios they ended up laying out
Esta played Biden
And he does
Concede
There's a number of different scenarios
Is fixating on a being like that
Not that the one the one where Trump wins and everybody's fine he doesn't deal with that war games and wins and everybody
Doesn't deal with that WarGames the only thing that he can
Can fixate on it
The most dramatic
Almost
Cinematic
So
Now
Take you to bark
Alex Jones
Has been
Kicked out
Or something
Try to pull over near my house in Plaistow Hill alive
Quarter mile hill
I should go down in the email from there
He probably a 50
Sunday morning
Today
Johnny O yang
Greenvale
And a big beautiful crazy
Right now
Like Jonah
Good news
Opposed to
And they said we shouldn't have
College
Enforcing
And they shut them down
Dot-dot
F****** college kids a lesson
College kids
Then the world
So now Alex goes to a
Special report about his trip to Barton Springs
Worst is over
Like I know that we've talked to the Past like Wayback that have Bad John bowne
There's another guy he sucks even more
Austin city mayor
Steven Adler
Is attempting to see
Control
He has erected
Mixture
Registration booth at Park
And hired
Lifeguards
Who have lost their jobs
As a result of the covid shutdown
Vibing to this music
And register the names
Anyone who n
Going on all over the Nation Ford
The United Nations
+ 221
I'm not worried about it
Public landfill by Ivan
For their own private
Entrances
Have been set up
Like this by the Austin Parks.
It is unlawful
It is nothing more than the edict
A radical leftist mayor Adler
Who produced that
Who produced that music cuz they can't possibly fill royalty-free track
Some BJ Emporium
Not bad seriously I did not hear much of what he said I was just really like that
Maybe Leo zagami did it
The Parks Department
So this is unlawful and unconstitutional
Who's doing a gender
Be the president who's doing it
Through the lifeguards
Those f****** life
So Alex yelling
Of course with his tiny little ballora
At this point he just has the Boulevard in his hand
This is such a
So pathetic like you came down here specifically brought your bullhorn
Travis Boulevard
It's a really sad
Be one thing if you was going about his business that many at this interaction that happened organically
As it is
He's walking really fast like past these people who are set up outside the trail and Trey
Cool
And now you guys use your cousin
Charging
Started hot
Yeah already gone Adam
Illegal power grab
Of the people
Greenbelt
There's a small part of me that wonders if this is a joke
It's obviously not he's taking this very seriously really seriously
Nothing he's ever done absolutely
Few things that I would recommend people watch
Watch this for the tiny bulb it made me laugh really hard
I just here's what I keep my laundry Alex's like
Covered in sweat
I just I just keep picturing this evening The Sandlot where they're at
The pool and the girl lifeguard give them out to mouth and right before
Somebody with a bullet
Who are you this is
The grocers in Damascus
Mr. mask man
So this is where it gets personal about it everybody about how his wife was allowed
They aren't you
No crowd that you can see there is maybe one other person
People who are like sitting in beach chairs
Ridiculous
Okay
It sucks
Is a little much
Do Die Hard movies
Wow
Reservation
The free country
I'm using that at the next Chicago restaurant I go to Steakhouse
Good table move on with my life
Antonio shows up
I think it turned away thankfully Alex
While we were there a family from standings
Antonio arrive
Enjoy the day in the park
After an hour drive
The gentleman from San Antonio spoke to the Austin Police
And was told that there is no law
The police allow the family to enjoy the park
Has the law permits
Respect
There is no reason for a Boulevard
I can't stress that enough everyone could hear him
Krowd
Talkin people could hear him out doubted
Comical
So Alex is little bad breath cure
And
Certainly not but I realize like
I've successfully got the San Antonio family into the park
And now
A g stand for a crowd has nobody
I think Alex realized that this narrative doesn't work for what happened cuz the police site
Oh no it's the
I ever am I going with this
So often as a City Police Station
Have the police out here.
Something
Wait I like what you doing
How do I do this I'm going to blow up the lifeguard station
Alright
I just think that was
This is not going to
Good2Go
There's a few more people
Tries to get people to barbarash
Covid-19
Fieldpiece
Scuse me question
What I find really interesting about this is that
Very sad
A real bummer
Clearly like a
Personal gripe
What's that movie I can make a story out of it
Not good
Kind of
Narrative
Completion
Like
He started his career
A guy alone
And now he goes back to Barton Springs cuz his wife was asked if she had a reservation and
I don't want to share music
If I ever
Doesn't have the cash
She wants them to just like
So Alex
Comes back after this video
I guess a little bit wistful
About some of his memory
About this Trail
I know about that place
That's a good times there
Tell me what 20
29 years I'm old down there
College 20
9 years
Girls down
You told me this
I thought you were
Pretty sure you thought everyone was
Illustrate
Everything
Beer
Really great products
So yeah I didn't have time to get to some of these important news stories had to have a petty grievance with the
The creek
Man my wife she
Drove over a pothole bitloft a little bit
What was going on and I realize our destroying the roads on
Stardust Crusaders
He's going to go on a crusade
Yeah that way too f****** nowhere Noel
He hasn't brought it up since
Campaign against people not being let in parks
Is just about his own
Personal problem
This is all just
Such rank
Projection
Just because
Tempest
Fieldpiece
It made me laugh
So hard
Look horn is too small
For an adult at Alex's of stick adult so
Way too small for him
If it's a manifestation of like downsizing and like
Cutting expenses Infowars
Genital area
This couldn't Crush any kind of tyranny
The
Okay so I know you're all
On the first day of course now we have to practice what you would do if a large man with a tiny bullhorn
It's state
State-required now
That picture of Alex Jones up there we keep that
Just to remind us what exactly it looks like and who it is who will be
Greater Austin area
I wouldn't say the old
Certainly
The old man willing to use it the way it was meant to be yours
You know
And when you get a tardy Boulevard
Do you think that was a good purse
It makes me think
Betty has like
Like Rodger Federer with tennis racket like you've got them lined up and it's like
Oh this one is for the the high-tension the big bull horns
Newsradio
Nick Diaz
No I imagine
Here's what I imagine Cortana
What do you live at
You better their head everyday
You wanted me I like
Advisor the sun visor in the car
Opposed
Passenger door
Like 50 Cent all about the image that I have
It's like in the movies
You know where the guy's got the gun
You sitting behind the desk and underneath the desk Alex pulls at the buck
Fight back
Here's the scene
Okay
So it is like an office
Alex's place
Talking to Adam
Bring me charity Crusher
I'm in Rob's like to cut expenses around here
I got dragged at work with it is a title bar
Okay Alex
You can make it work
David Icke
Looks to the camera
Who is that a bigger Boulevard
I bet he's at every step
Cops
The office Andy's in Curb Your Enthusiasm all of the saved nothing of those shows is funny
Tumi
Then Alex with that tiny bullhorn
Tiny bullhorn
I don't understand.
I don't know I wish that he would stop imagining that is petty grievance
Outside
Himself
I just heard some Thunder
Home
I wish you the best with that
You need a ride
Call 1773
Pak-a-sak
Do do do that
Twitter
Write Rose itunes please find a local charity or bail Fund in your area to help out with
People doing God's work
I'm Alex's tiny bulb
Alex
Same color