I have great respect for snowledge B
Need money
Knowledge fight
Jordan Jordan
Question what's up
Interesting storm
Yesterday Monday as we're recording this
You know Chicago's really interesting place
You were a little bit south of me and you were telling me nothing
The debris all over the place
At all like you just saw a little bit of rain
I saw
The rain line
Yeah
So light it was a little ways away from a I could see you
Terrifying pouring rain
And I was completely drives banana
Meanwhile up at my place
Locked up
I'm very lucky compared to see some pictures of like
Treason
My lights were flickering and
Definitely been much more than you expected to do
Okay I can prop I'm from
Central Missouri
To do I can find someplace even if I
In a live on the top floor.
Nothing ended up happening and that everything was all right.
Wandering around my house
I know that
That
I haven't even mentioned
I knew I have been
Tons of plants
Ridiculously long process
Completely sucked it up because of
Just like
Got a little
Salt at the After the Storm
Nelson song After the Rain
Promise never to purple rainbow
The form of a tiny little thing of a Bonsai popping out
I like it I like it
I got the Bonsai, going to be a mess
Are you going to make fun of me because probably will this is Commerce related
But newly-minted Raptor Princess Emily
Has made us some new designs
The Earth
Defense for Aesthetics
Is really really cool human hitting a robot
It's so cool
Thank you so much
Are closer to the episode where Alex announced
The shirt is really awesome
It's never available public
Integrate
It's so good
Pretty cool so Jordan today to go over there will be interesting
Little bit of the storm gave me some trouble
Workflow
That's scared
By weather
I know and you know
Granteed's
I wasn't as worried as I had
Missouri
Weather sometimes
The uncertainty of it
For a good party afternoon
With just completely dark skies
When you're on the top floor
To me I was on the top floor
So that kind of and then afterwards
So like
Works out
About it that I had to take
Yesterday was a Washburn
August 11th
Alright
First gear
Journal probably why
Disappeared
Michael
Like Mike
80s
I'm a policy wonk Lego next
Thank you so much
Haikyuu Abner Doubleday
Next freaking sterf
Thank you
Perkins
Somebody donated on elevator
So Kevin Hart
Money off that heroin
Barge
Princess
The fake name
Butternut
Damn my chill thank you so much
Score after Prince
Four Star
It's over for Humanity
You're Beautiful song
They're coming for your balls
It's all over your God
Very few people
When they are
At juice
Eczema
If that's a real name you're going to feel really a bear
Pulled up into a paper airplane
Executed so far
The first matter
In front of us
Jordan I have here in front of me
It's a big book
Confessions of the Illuminati of
An aluminum
When is the diamond out of here
The name is the same color graphic design
2nd edition of confessions of an Illuminati
About the Illuminati and the new world order by Leo Lions origami
The f****** DJ are worthy of a memoir and this but maybe that's in there I'm really excited
As soon as we hit the record
I'm diving in
Definitely going to be talking about
Game with a little note
I wanted to send you this complete
Is a way of thanking you
I brought the great concept you put out over the years
Both of you enough for consistently excellent onset that's entertained during multiple
And learning how to paint miniatures
I think it's important for people to be introduced to right-wing.
Critical and well-thought-out
You're essentially inoculating people against these toxic etiology
I think the impact you both have had on
Thank you very much
The Greek
I'm totally measurable I'm not saying that
I'm just saying that you can absolutely
Anyway
Clearly policy wonk Brent speed
I'd love to make each of you a Warhammer Mini
If there's anything you know about
The setting do you have any preferences
Thanks I don't know somebody who has any experience in that that
Arena
Dungeons &
Play figurines
I would assume that I would have to be like a bard
Or some kind of scholar
And then you would be deserter type
How do you love your life is great
Some sort of a lure where used to be chaotic
Grounded
Brent I don't know
I don't know anything about this but I think that's an awesome I would love to have miniatures
Love you so much nonsense in terms of the show talked about whether it be like the project
Camelot.
Yeah there's so much
Potential for weird lure
I think you could let your mind go crazy
Something fun
You know
Some kind of
I'm a nerd
I get it
I want some sort of magician character you know what I was I was really really young
I was athletic and my friend was very much not athletic and in a reverse kind of role
A situation he would always plays the Barbarian strongman
And I would always play as the
And I've always irrelevant
There's a magic-user preferably
Violent temper
That works
Give it to me
Now Jordan last little thing for get to the episode
I meant to last episode
Medical courses
Received messages
So weird
Dear are some of the messages
First caller didn't know what to say
Call First is a great thing to say but unfortunately
Unfortunately
Hey where the second was the actual first
Second timer
There's nothing to do.
0 John
Thank you
Horizon zero Dawn I would say Enjoy your journey
Sometime enjoyed
Scenery
That's great
Get to the
The Cauldron
Early
You want to be able to turn all those machines that is true
Puzzle
Farming
Children's are a lot of fun
Yeah I found
The
Place that has like the special armor
Behind the big lock
You know what I never got that I found that
Almost immediately and became obsessed with it as like a quest
Kind of
Kurt Meyer
Yeah I did but never did
I took me forever but I did
Gator
You know because things you need in order to solve a court you can't do it. Parts
In the game getting really frustrated
You know don't get too bogged down in specific thing and just enjoy
It is a little bit like Assassin's Creed
Is you with that
FirstLight aspect that you need to get the super armor but then you have to wait like 10 full chapter
By breaking it.
The last one yeah yeah
Yeah
Cauldron
Override things
Interesting mechanic
I also take your time with the hunting grounds
Completely side
That's a fun thing
I'm just calling
Order some pie
Covid
Humanity
Anyways
It gets introduced as a problem with our phone number and is that is the people might be trying to order tattoo
Address
I think we could run into problems
Is there I did not think that
Through I would like to know if anybody called tap Bros
Is everybody going to get too smart of them on now future episodes
We got the phone
Jordan
On August 11th
Alex is getting
Pretty extreme about the coming election
They are now officially
Announcing a plan
When Joe Biden loses in a landslide
But they are going to have
I like this idea
I completely dividing this time
Military attack
Collapse
From within
The top story
So is he against secession now
10th Amendment
Assertion
Is suspended 2009
He was he was in favor of that when their work was talk of gun laws
Okay please the Texas is its own country
And so therefore it
Could do whatever the parking lot right right right
I think this is actually
Honestly if this plane was true I think this is a win for Alex Wright
What are you going to be mad that you guys aren't the ones who get to secede where's
Seating review
Essentially the same as use the seating for what
Alright
I don't want to play with you but I don't want you to not want to play with me
Probably
Just about what we talked about
Explored
Was the possibility of Biden not conceding re-election
You know like
It's basically the 2000 election but with a
The fight
Pretending is the official plan the primary
So that's where we're at think it's a great idea but we're just going to have to move Atlanta somewhere
It's my friend purple States
250 purple stuff
What song
Reversing that music video purple stuff
Her big mouth
Recipes Big Moe by the way he died
Cody, what purple stuff is very sad
Call T-Bird
Situation all over again
Video is amazing
Very weird unnecessary Willy Wonka
This next court
Alex said something that really got me excited
Because it's one of those
One of the indications to me that maybe he's going to try
You know
Very pops when I was like I'm going to prove something
And I thought that's what was coming here but
Sure if you followed through
Unbroken
All of which Infowars has discovered
Which
No one even knows about
What is it about the credit
But I want lister's understand
One of the stories would devastate
I got so pumped because like
3 Strikes
Thanks, somebody's going to devastate the code
Number one and then I can take care of that
I'm going to take care of
He doesn't he doesn't really specify what three stories are I'm not sure he got to all three of them
We could guess if the 3r
Various things that are covered along way
Explicit
No
For sure
This is one of the three giant stories but Alex about something
Actually allows me
To put into context something you talked about on a previous episode
There's hundreds of stories one everyday about all this lgbtq professor she died of Toby
Doesn't exist
Put out by Sia
Episode
Covid death numbers
Evolution
In terms of his rhetoric
10 things that you took
Most issue with was the lack of any specific details that would tell people what he was talking about
At least this time he's being a little bit
His story is about a Twitter
Larimer
It was run by an account called sciencing underscore by
The accountant
Reported to be in lgbtq indigenous
Professor at the Arizona State University
People who've looked into the details of the story of founded
To the person story don't match up with
Reality
Including claims of teaching
Classes were in session
And the fact that ASU had no faculty members died of covid
19 in the time. When this person
Send a text with.
Tuesday
Wow
Bethany
It's just a ways back
7 years ago
Sorry
As far as the construction was
Inappropriate reference
Is just
I don't know how many people
It's fine there's a great dad
A person's death was reported by Twitter account run by women
According to an article on heavy statement
I take full responsibility for my involvement
In creating the app sciencing underscore by Twitter
Excusable I apologize that reservation to all the people I hurt
It's really hard to say exactly what's going on with this situation or what people's motivations were
Twitter account
According to be an indigenous anthropology professor at ASU
And that time. She tricked a number of folks
Professor was a real person
And then she decided to pretend
She died of covid
This is what it looks like from the information that I can
This is why specifics are important
If you're a legend that there are fake people claiming to have died of covid-19 and this is the story you're talking about
We can engage with that response
And look at the
Details of the story
Is there is a Twitter
People do stuff like this all the time and it's one of the reasons why you're pretty careful with social media
There's absolutely no reason to pretend
Alex is claiming it
41 there's no reason to think this Twitter Persona is alleged death is being included in any way
That's a complete fabrication of
What is mine
The second thing is that there's no reason for Alex to suggest that this was a worker
Psyop specialist
Beyond just hurting an existing
What you end up doing when you act this way is that you really have muddying the waters
The Baseline story is about a really interesting and bizarre cases
Because of how Alex is speaking Sophie
It's easy for the audience to Come Away with the impression that things are very
Different
If you didn't look into it you might think of the underlying story in the mainstream media
Is it a professor at asq it officially died of covid-19
Didn't actually exist
Any one of these three stories
You can easily see how the conclusion you be left with would be different based on the two different versions of the story
And that confusion is Alex's goal
Dancing twisting of reality
Desire to
And that's why specific
Are so dangerous for him
Yeah when you first talked about it it was just
Suggest
But you're not giving me anything to go on sale
Bring in that it's an lgbtq professor
I can find out what this is and I can say
Story
Has nothing to do with what you're talkin about specifics
You know where it's like
Famous for
I need you to
Confirm
She pretended
To be an LG
Indigenous
I think so
That's the information I can find
But it appears that that is the case
And heavy
Does seem to indicate that
Confess to such
And in her apology
She wrote I apologize without Reza
Oh
Now did she parenthesize pun intended
Because
If you don't parenthesize that
Man your f****** with my head
Lawyers
This I think is one of Alex's three-story
No no
Stories
And it's um
Ue's he's taken an existing story in axios
He's pretending that he's gone to the bottom of a deeper reality
And then he just do some grocery
Islamophobia
Hospital Association
From the CDC
Children's Hospital Association
Almost all of them
24 years old
Gotham
Invaders islamists men
The children put them in school
In middle school with your daughters
Alexa
He's from Syria
Matchmaking your daughters
Pharmacist
Wow
Promise
Has is that
Deception ladies and gentlemen I thought your point was about an axios
Story
Digital this app
It's okay
So let's refer to the details of the story
Coronavirus covid-19
Exactly
Use
Being diagnosed with covid-19
So
Young women in
Sweden
We are meeting our Matchmaker
That'll be that's just disgusting
Trash but it's just say everyone
What started the Jim Crow era
Leaving now
Decide
About that axios
The reason there's some age
Confusion about the data in that report that is
What excuse
Reporting ostriches from the American Academy of Pediatrics
Is it the only thing that they can go on is state-level data
Each state is a different
Set smart
If you do go look at the data you can see this very clearly called out on page as one of the limitations
Of the dataset
Yet Alex is still lying
There's only one state that list people up to age 24 and that's Alabama
From the page about data limitation
Reported children as ages 0224 and is excluded from some
Figures
People compiling a report wreck
Recognize that this was outside the range of what they were talking
About Leslie throw things off
Tennessee and South Carolina included people from ages 02
20 but most States had to cut off of 7
1918 or 9
If you actually don't look
Charts where the
That are being reported or taken from
You'll see a little disclaimer saying Alabama and Texas
Excluded from figure
This is because the state-level data from Alabama was unreliable
And Texas was excluded because quote Texas recorded age distribution
For only 8% of all cases
Neither these states will be reliably sorted into this data set so they were
Excluded
What does actually means is that the real number of child cases of covid-19 is higher than what's being reported
Cuz there obviously some children in Alabama and Texas who've gotten sick did you say that
The age range was only
Reported for 8% in Texas
Yeah
Decision
Someone has that data but it's
Just not reported to the
I don't know
Oh man it is over
Survivor
Essentially what's going on is that Alex's misrepresenting something he doesn't understand about this
Report needs a misunderstanding exact opposite of the truth
You saying that these numbers are exaggerating
24 year olds
Thereby excluding also
The grocer number of people who are under
Christine Sixteen years of age
Who tested positive in Alabama and Texas
The study raised and dressed his
Concerned
Well before
Think about stuff in it
That's a large part of
To higher education
Now also Alex is racist xenophobic islamophobic
That's maybe more
Yeah that's fair
Since I've gotten to hear Alex and his natural
Yeah sometimes singing along to
Mayweather the highwomen
Places that he feels most at home
You know I mean you can go to a zoo
It's kind of depressing
Cuz you know
In a cage
That's where it belong
This is Alex
Kind of worried belongs
Saxophone is where I belong
So basically yes the highway.
You son of a
Body
There's something wrong with you
Future
Alex's natural environment
Letter
We didn't have that as Baba
Perfect like
The position of his like
God damn Eagles a saxophone
Nonsense
Manchester playing Dave Matthews
Let's move on with their life
I swear to God if he could do that for 3 hours
I mean
Is like General Patton
Seriously
Giving birth if you want Frank just gave a small like little mini mini you pieces
Just like
Distillation of insanity
Great he was like almost everyday
Censorship going on about conservatives giving away
Caramelo.
Sing anymore
It turns out that now
I can't use phone
Phone
When
Publican primary
How to use the telephone
Telephone service off
She's joining us today
To pay your bill
Sorry
Send text messages
That's a little
Infowars.com
Beer flags on the story entirely on a video
Laura Loomer recorded of herself
This mechanism would even work
Messages are most likely be delivered through third-party platforms like MailChimp for emails or
Anyway
River provides literally no evidence
Transfer clients in the video
Deceitful history I'm not going to
Take her word on any
If you know if utility is blocking somebody from using their service like a phone or internet based on political
Beliefs than I do
Yes I agree I just don't believe Laura Loomer the best
What's happening in this case
But look into this a little further
And take what I'm about to say with a grain of salt because I found this article on Breitbart
The article claimed that they had a statement from a Comcast spokesperson who said quote
We're reaching out to the campaign and has made a technical fix that will resolve this issue within 24 hours
We're continuously working to protect our customers for potential security
In this case our security platform which leverages widely used third-party threat intelligence services
Flags be texting provider used by Laura Loomer Scamp as a pet
Potential Threat
Anyone using this texting provider would have had the same experience
Not only with our service but with any security service using similar threat intelligence list
These security alert had nothing to do with the contents under
Any communication
Contact
Yeah I mean
Texting
They called Nazi. Great
Yeah it's just she's not related to lubbers camp
The mass texting company that might not be very legit
Free texting
The kind of makes sense I mean she has bad associate with absolutely Shady people
Adjust reputable company to handle
Even if this is the case
Has been responsive to the issue and is working to resolve it
This is at worst
Normal inconvenience someone might run into in their lives
Because people are invested in their identities
Whole thing becomes a
Plot against them because I'm so scared of their ideas
Luma releases a video playing the aggrieved
Conservative
People like Alex can report on that video
Unquestioningly accept
Because it also serves their purposes
It's their narratives
As is the case with so much of the stuff we see on Infowars
This is an instance of someone taking their own
Personal inconvenience
Broadcast
Conspiracies against
Laura's texting companies Shady's this ends up being reported its
Conservice will soon have no phone
Make a reservation at a park in this ends up being reported as an agenda 21 take over state parks
Hey it's all just narcissism run-amok that's all
From Comcast
Also said
We immediately flagged the text
Company called nikolaychuk text
That's alright that's alright
Well Cheska certainly more relevant than Manti Te'o so
Even though it's an older reference
That look
Haha
Bloop single over the third base
I think one of the problem
Like the difference between how you and I engage with me
That that's your goal after you laugh
Food challenge
And I can appreciate a Nikolai
Text you that I can appreciate that might not last.
I'm just probably not going to laugh at it
Nihilism
You're my dad all right that's what's happening
When I get a little laugh out of you I feel like it's an accomplishment that's why you can't
I feel like you can't give it to me on
I'll text you
That's
Headlines
I don't know
Baby
Why are the whl's fake to Panda
Years ago
In 25
Correspond
Coming from Tara
It's a lockdown drill
Bravo Winter Haven early something far worse
Tubi
Cotuit
Little Couple of important
Even though Alex Hughes
Accurately reading the headline
The first thing is a b article is from February 2010
Complaints about swine flu
The second thing is that Michael cemento the author
Credit on his byline
He's not listed as a scientist or researcher even a journalist
He's identified as a subscriber
No audience submitted op-ed published
Holding it up to be
How's the columnist
Pimento it's a dodgy history
He seems to have made a brand out of telling people to calm down about
All right like it be ladies hold on
Commenter b*******
Called the myth
Of heterosexual AIDS
So
So we've got a hero
El Cerrito climate change and Monsanto
Monsanto
Dude where he was employed
Any written positive things
Justice system has been bought and paid for by a large multinational
Like Chevron or
Monsanto
Answer your slip-up and not an instant
Someone writing positive articles about 9
Even indirectly funded them chairs totally broadsword
That sounds right I'll break of 2009
This op-ed in Forbes is in no way conclusive and has nothing to do with the topics that Alex's pretending
There's no mention of the Rockefeller Foundation or of dr. fauci
This is just another example
Story about what the article actually says
Articles and headlines are
Props for Alice
All the details are just things he's pulling out of thin air
Also just because it's funny
Michael cemento another article that he wrote is his
Calm down
Was about
Do vaxxers vaccines are great so I just
To love to engage with that article at some point
It seems like pretty much
Almost everything that I can
Can find of him
He's accusing everyone of being hysterical about topics
Play
Call Dad
Vandals
Does have a headline
That is saying that the World Health Organization
Sake Japan
Improve user-submitted on Forbes
This guy has
A decade-long track record of
Basically all of his work just be telling people
This medium post my dick back
Hysterical
What do we bother about slavery at the economy what are you doing it'll take care of itself
So what real long time Alex has been making
Claim
Cdc's on materials
That vase a
That's a lie called tester false positive
Glacier
Specifics about it
In this next clip
Alex Gibbs
Is an indication of where he's pulling that information
In from
And
Again
He has to not be specific because when he does
It reveals this stuff
CDC
Novel Coronavirus
Real-time are tprc diagnostic
VCR
Infection or co-infection with other viruses
This is one of the most
Damning instances
Of Alex
Playing game
So
This is just a straight line that he founded
The full sentences reading is quote
The 2019 novel coronavirus RNA is
Genetically detectable in upper and lower respiratory specimens during
Infection
Positive results are indicative
Active infection with two 2019-novel Coronavirus
But do not rule out bacterial
Infection with other viruses
The age of detected may not be the definite cause of disease
You can easily see the trick Alex
Is playing here
He starts the sentence at quotes
Do not rule out grammar of descent
When you start the sentence that way it appears to be a command telling people to do so
When in reality the second starts with positive results
Infection but do not rule out
We just saying that a positive result covid-19
But also that doesn't mean the patient may not be suffering from another condition
Also
It's a warning not to come
Exactly in proper context all this line is covid-19
Doesn't ultimately be more complicated
CDC says be thorough
Alex could not make this this representation without omitting
The beginning of that
So this is absolutely a case of him consciously lying about what the document says
Him repeating a report
It's someone else who's consciously lying
Without
Confirming it in anyway for himself
There's no
It's so specific the way the sentences been changed
To appear to be a command
I'm going to give this one to
Lower-level research
That kind
The strength second
Important to recognize
Starting
From it's absolutely conscious
Like because that makes perfect sense yeah
And it changes meaning when you started in the middle
Just unacceptable that
Should be
Super Bowl I don't know maybe not maybe
Motherfuker
Lawsuit
Recalls on the show but specifically about
No
Blue States this week
Open the phones up starting
Yesterday
Call Annabelle
You take your view
Secede
We're going to have our own operation and say
Is the present
The military will have to decide
So Alex has decided
Commiserate about this because
That'll be some fun violent talk prepared for the thing that we are accusing them of
While we are doing it
Quite a while
Because he has something else
Directions to me
What
The last hour
That was an accident
So there's a number of things that I desperately need a correction
The complete misrepresentation
The guidelines about PCR test
It's made by chopping off the beginning of that sin
Alright I'll give you that this representation of the axios article about children with covid-19
People who were 24
And consider children were explicitly excluded from
Miss representation
He's taking Laura Loomer at her word about her dumb campaign for congress being sent
There are others
Journalistic fuk up that he's made in less than an hour of his show
Expected one of these should definitely be the thing that he's apologizing for
No it's not
I'm sorry
0.32
He's talking about the Texas death rate
From
0 point
Preacher
Suck it up again
Sometimes worse than it is
It wasn't on purpose
0.32
0.03
So that's
Is Big correct
Correct somebody misread a number
I mean to do a correction but also
There's more substantiv Corrections you need to be Focus
Seems a little distant
Don't think I don't think he was real meaning that is a full-throated like pageant out of that
Topology
Dismissive
I'm very comfortable
I'm sure 032
Fuc yourself
So anyway
Cases are going up
Places like Texas
Going straight down like a lead balloon
Section rate is going
Because
I just showed you the cdc's on website
Infection
The flu
You were going to have
Cereal that we will also have even
19 this is just from that do not rule
He's pointing back to that that
It's a push it
Just talked about the
Concept of time
Haha
Alright
That somebody gets
Virus
What a two-week map 10-day
.
Virus
And when the symptoms start to really accelerate
So it suggests that
Hey straight was going
Then the death rate would
Follow
Later
Right and you can't really expect
Exact same trajectory as the first time cases were really getting out of control because we
You have more information than we had
Round
You expected
From
How it works
Timeworks yet
Expected
Goldust
You gets around to talking again
About this
Historian
He wants to really report on this
Figure this out
Is Tech Guy
Computer Fletcher's is really smart guy
He has his own show
Nobody's dying. One of them
Lgbtq
Going for broke why not
Million live
That's not
Not good specifics
In terms of these
Big people
The kids got even real
You had to be real f****** careful Alex.
And I'm not even talking about be careful because I think you'll get sued
Be careful because of the consequences
That these types of narrative
You hurt innocent people
You want you want to do something that molynes like George W bush
Like always
Try as best as you can to deal with reality on reality turn victimizes Georgia
W bush
You know Dubai
Things as best I can
I'm not worried about it as much
He's rich
Yes security
All that stuff
Individuals and private citizen
They can't be hurt by rhetoric
And narratives like this
Make it so much more
And you can't
You can't allow yourself to act
I think it's f***** up
Is that
My reactions
To that is
Like
In the context of Alex
I know he wanted to
Experience any guilt
The actual people
You know so
When talking about something like this
It's
It's so hard to remember to focus on like
He's not just going to get himself
He's going to hurt
You can't do stuff like that
You just can't
You can't do whatever you're doing
To Target
People
Not least of which
Because I would
Prefer to deal with the
Consequences of my own Acts
A second
Hands
So Alex gets into this paper
Actually really worried
These signs of like a delicious
This indicates to me like
Just completely
Falkreath
It it was really scary
Percent
Them
Yellow is 0214
Testing positive
Thunder 14
So there's absolutely no reason to suggest
Just because the state counts people who are ages 0217 as children
Must be 70 roll
Which is what
Suggesting
Yeah
Alex is not realize that only Alabama 24 in the definition
Explicitly says that Alabama data is excluded from
He'll he will die on
This is really weird to me because okay so there's like Florida
Considered
I meant over bunch of other states are 0270
0217 that actually means
In 217
And Florida is the only state that even counting 0214
That's what I thought you said
Text banana
Credibly scary because
That's either thinking that your audience
Will accept that which is terrifying
Just
Cognition and reasoning abilities that Alex has that's the conclusion that he's arrived at
Which is scary
Obviously
The only 7
Text help
0217 means 14270 because there's another option that 0214
These data sets
From each state or independent of each other
They're all colors on the map are to delineate which states
0244 literally examining my eyes
That's terrifying
You see we just ripping holes out of my eyes
And he's just making stuff up about this report
Again
The most danger
Just think what he's doing is throwing around these accusations about fake.
If you wants to genuinely talk about individual specific cases like that Twitter hoax
He has the right
Right to do so
But to take that specification then extrapolate that out to yell about fake deaths
Do children like you have been doing here
Is onyx
It's just completely unacceptable
And like
Only human
I don't expect this to ever happen or this message
To get across
Cease and desist
Whatever you're going to do Alex
But this is crossing a line
In the past
You should know is not good
I can just not accept
I'm making a citizen's put you in a little box
Everybody else's safe for me
Timeout yeah no kidding
Boomers on the show now
Towards the end of third hour
Really for that hour but I turned it off after Laura Loomer
I'm
I'm 36
Years old
Description begins with R 3060
Feel like
I don't have enough time that I can listen to Laura Loomer on Alex's show be like
Give me some more
We got 15 before the world
Alright
So Laura is
Can hear about
You know they're going to turn off
Your phone's if you're from there
Access to your internet service provider
Actually already
Garcetti
People
Social distance
Turn your water off
These are
You can already see here that Laura is moving the goalposts a little bit
The utility that pretty much everyone agrees that everyone should have access to his being online
More like having a phone
Your phone service
Yes that's not the same thing as being entitled to use every single service that is online or you can
If a particular company doesn't want to work with you due to your behavior being just tasteful or dangerous that's not the same thing as Comcast
Not allow you to be online
Where is blurring ventline on purpose
Because the reality of her situation is
The pretty weak grievance
And she really wants to be seen as the oppressed hero telling truth to power
I have so many people to look up on IMDb pan
Please keep in mind that less than a year ago she was the co-host
Where they went to Minnesota to try and prove the ilhan Omar was married to her brother
She's not a serious
And anytime
Is Justified
Answer the whole thing about LA mayor Garcetti threatening to shut off water and power to houses that are throwing parties
He wasn't talking about houses that actually have like their peoples home
These are big houses that are either vacant or used for short-term rentals that people are renting out to throw big parties in
Because nightclub
Close down
And this is Wade have your own little nightclub
Used to record according to the LA Times
The beginning Friday night is Los Angeles Police Department officers
Property evidence that such Behavior
The city shut off water and power services within 48 hours
These parties are pretty out of control
Even if you don't think about it just in terms of the pandemic
His Times article discusses a recent party on Mulholland Drive it caused a
Chart of neighbor complaint
Many cars that were illegally parked need to be towed and It ultimately culminated in a fatal shooting at 12:45 a.m.
People were shot
Resulting in one death
F****** Christ
Palmini, considerate
Regulate
It's just yeah
People like Laura and Alex
Shearwater because you're nuts
Submitting to their Authority
Real reality
Ice queen attempt to crack down on people using Airbnb mansions
Ginger is parties
You can agree or disagree with that tactic
Welcome
Make a pretty solid argument that's not the best way for the city to go about it
I think you can make an argument
Not a bad
Whatever
But
You do have an obligation
Resent the story as it actually exists
As opposed to some Twisted paranoid fantasy about Renegade
Communist
All this b*******
She doesn't get to do
If you don't advocate
For Universal broadband
Then you don't get to do that
Because you're saying that this Corporation
Can kick you off
Because you lost your job
You're saying this Corporation
Can kick you off because you don't have any generational
Sucking well
You're saying this Corporation can kick you off for any reason
Because you didn't pull yourself up enough by your f****** bootstrap
But you're saying that the corporation
You can't kick you off or any other
Like
That's fine
Yeah I don't know if I agree with you 100% I mean like
I think ideally I do in terms of like yes I would I do
You know that you shouldn't be able to
Being hypocritical
Under the current system that we live under
Is differin
Then being an a******
I mean
Operation can control what is ultimately what you describe as a human
Irregardless of
What their reasoning is
Well I think it should be
You can if you don't pay your bill during not dangerous for them to turn it on
Idealistically based on the system that exists as it does now
I don't
Don't think that it's being hypocritical to say
But it's different
To say you're a conservative or even like you're an Alex Jones type do you have a phone
I think
You haven't paid your phone bill your phone is turned off
It's different
I just feel like a little bit like we can go to accept
System
I mean maybe it is but like
It without changing the entire system there's no reason
Okay and now we're Where We Are
I'm coming at you with
R-Truth dad
Truth in you
No
Admirable
I meant look
If we could find a way to craft
Society where no one could be
Thrown off
Utilities
Because they can't afford
Yeah I think that's a better State of Affairs
Much preferable
But I do think
It stands now there's a massive difference
Between ideological and
In political denial-of-service
That I agree there is a difference
Between the two
Perfectly clear
We're talking about utilities not company
Yes.
Lights
Waters
That those can be turned off his
Bananas
But anyway
Jeffy
So
Basically
Strong arm talk
About how he needs to win
Lawlessness in this
Be safe
I said that 10 years ago
Taters and
Uno
Parentheses
Straight white
People and parentheses
How do I score a this is just a larious Laura is giving her sales pitch
For her Congressional run record
What are you doing
Is in the negative d.c. in
Breathing t.i. you've never made a promise ring
He played earlier
You know
Czerny Seymour
You sure
I love the idea of turning these until I
Positive
Joining Jake Harrison.
Dorsey by embarrassingly handcuffing myself to one around here
Embarrassingly
Undocumented
People
To Nancy Pelosi's house
Think she might be patterned perceive
It's incumbent upon you to
Technology
Take these embarrassment and turn them into
Success yeah I want to go back and see what actually happened with hurricane
He was just like you did not clean up that s*** at all that was Genesis
Job mr. Magoo antiquity
Story
Tradition Works call Mike got it
Golden Fleece in a thousand years I'm going to be real pissed
What we should do
I mean I studied homeric Greek
In college
Association with
Call Kelso
Worked with my
Greek professors
A oral tradition Journal
All the oral tradition journal and I've learned a lot about
Aldi DeSoto
Inside the Dead the world
I think we should start our own oral tradition
But around these people
Isaac
That we should do
Start telling
Mythological stories about the various characters
Jon rappoport
Okay we never write down
We all tell each other over and over again
With the hopes that when Society does inevitably Fall Apart
These will be the stories
Do you realize that six months out of every year
We
Get Summer
Because Laura Loomer turned to look back at that.
Absolutely stories
Will be telling around the campfire
2000 years from now
Maybe
Jordan
We're done here with this episode
I mean
Videos that
Strand of
Alex becoming a
Increasingly comfortable talking about the idea of
Steak deaths
Ryan the covid-19
And that's me think is really the most important
Something to keep an eye on
There's a lot of
Instances of just like
Like you slip
Like he uses these specific
You're able to be like okay
Is just total b*******
And that's just his game
It's normal
This introduction
Again
Into something that's
So highly about
Chanel and so important
Is really dangerous and really troubling
Think about the future
Yeah in retrospect
Like the idea that we
Considered
Because
We we considered
How bad does it have
To get before he
Switches up you know
How many deaths
How many
Cases what's the number
And what we should have been talking
About it
The real inevitability of it which is
How does one rationalize
Right that's the only way that he could really go you know it was just
This was where we were going
Episode
When we when we first started touching on this stuff
There's such a massive difference
Between
Clerical admin kind of cover-up stuff
Switching
Something
Interact
Fake people
Cooking the books on this isn't a felony this is a misdemeanor
Versus something that would require active participants
Cover up
It's it's such a different type conspiracy
It's so much more Danger
The difference I would look at it between like
Weed and heroin
It's like if you have a friend is smoking a lot of weed
Saigon
I don't know even the best
Example these days
Abused it
I do
Find the alcohol
You have a friend is drinking a lot.
Don't need to intervene immediately it's really out of control
You got someone you know doing heroin
Like this
Type of narrative is
Is heroin
This is the hard drug
But you're not going to escape kill you the first time you do it maybe won't kill you the second
3rd or 4th
But it will kill you
Yeah it's the 14
This can't like you just
It's unacceptable
I really really hope that it doesn't
In progress any further because I don't want to watch this happen again
The story of
I'm sick of watching this happen again
4:00 on
Twitter
Please find a local charity or belt
Bzx
Alex
In color