I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Vicks around your knowledge about Alex Jones
Jordan Jordan
I don't know who to give a thank you too I'm just
Is it did not come with a Sodastream machine
So I can make my own Seltzer's when it is going to happen someday
Target a number of times in the past and I walked
But I could never get my
Myself to make the
The jump
Waffle makers in the past
I couldn't commit to the idea of a purchase of a
And then I'll test it out in Clio
I wouldn't
Can you just like put anything in there and see what happens
Think you could
You turn into a zelter worried about those sorts of thoughts
Because they inevitably lead to like
Fizzy milk
And these sorts of things and dangerous
It's possible that's why we got you a soda
Inevitable
Please send me an email so I can give you a proper thank you very much
And I look forward to
Going crazy
Text electric shelter form
This is sad
You may feel like it's insignificant and small
But
I've rediscovered
My other Joy with
My partner is a peanut allergy
Peanut butter and now at this point in time she's like
If you're going to die without peanut butter
I can't live with you
Covid
Etc
And so here we are
Drastically altered by nausea
Ketchup
Months without ketchup
Lasso
Greece
There wasn't around
Was he missing some amino acid or something
You can't go further
Cookie butter
Another butter
Reviews okay alright
Just trying to figure out a way to help a domestic situation
Several hundred
Peanut butter and jelly sandwiches in the past week
What's that grocery store PB&J B
Seafood that I found
This was a little bit weird but it I really I found it
Enjoyable
It's a little bit of like a shells or 20 that's covered in like
Basically a dusting of peanut flour
And then strawberry jam on the inside
That's fantastic
Do you remember the uncrustable
What's up
We cut
And I went to the kitchen snacks
Accorded
Earlier
I'm sorry that wasn't crunchy
Fantastic
Alex Jones
Not
Time. Of August 12th
This is 20/20
Here is the part of the show where I will copy and paste
My lecture from the last time
Everybody that went around the couch
12 million
Timer
Number one
We're talkin about it on Mondays episode
Seems like it's a joke it has to maybe it was
Use the tiny Boulevard no right front of you that much craft involved
I feel like it's just like so
Goldie and not really what I feel like
Reduce as much to the conversation is like
You all love this
And I do too
It's very funny
The tiny bullhorn
You want to shame him for interested at the Barton Springs or the Green Bay
You will not shame him
The ultimate goal isn't going to end up being
A more productive use of people's time right now if you want to have that are getting
Thousands of retweets
Is making everyone aware that right now Alex is dancing around saying the covid deaths are fake
Something like that
That has implications
That is implications in terms of his life
Yetis dangerous
And
He's in the middle of a lawsuit with Sandy Hook for saying that
And all that
His ability to try and pretend that
He's learned his lesson
Cuz that's something he's going to have to
Wolfgang halbig
Diminishes
When you recognize
Without the influence of people like Jim Fetzer
You can do this all on his own and defend himself
From those sorts of things
It seems like honestly that's something that they could the families could add right now
To their to their deal is just really like hay as a as an other piece of evidence were tossing in this fact
Right now we haven't even gone to trial yet
So guess what
He's doing it now in 2020 I think
Showing
Any kind of
Remorse remorse
South Butler
It's it's
It's damning in terms of
Is is claims that like
Or whatever
Fault or whatever
I think that would be a more productive thing for everybody to be pushing out on social
Video that's
Exciting
It's a bit embarrassing
This is very unsatisfying but that's
Maybe the
Tagline of our show
I get white
And I'm not mad at anybody I'm not shaming anybody for
Asanti bullhorn Makarov
If people really want to dress the problem we need to get a little bit smarter about these things
Probably don't know
Doesn't matter it's not going to hurt him in any way
Not listen to our show.
That does not mean we are one step removed for patent
We are
Come on man
Different
Are there two types of responses that I have to like social
Like with this I get it I understand no no no sour
On anybody better ways to go about this
That people should know right now
The flipside of this is the accusations about Alex burning that homeless person
Mattress
That was bad
That is just like while you're you're giving him
You done f***** up
Is an unforced error
Is just
It's free promotion for in an opportunity
It is bright right
I think
Okay here's what we do
We we create our own Chinese firewall around Alex
Jones's entire operation
Any information that gets out through the rest
The world
Filtered through our prison
Another way to start actually tweeting things
How to resist
Primarily motivated
Attention Gathering
Perspective that I want people to take more seriously maybe that's something I should
Get over to I don't know
Does Alex
Supposed to sign up and recording the show
Do first mate bees want
I'm a policy wonk
Policy
Srk love
Is the best dog
Just wear diaper
She's fine
Text Michelle
Thanks Michelle
What's your name
Aardvark
Alex
Appreciate that very much
Rico CD
You are now a technocrat
Heroin
Is freakishly large
Frederico
Here we go
What you going to do with it then
It's fresh you want to suck out all the air
Frigerator
Metaphorical refrigerated semental refrigerator
Okay
You open it up and you give it to an organization or local was not good. Worse
I've done worse
That wasn't good
I was trying to help
You were going nowhere with it but
The song is good
The guys show proper we must
Voicemail
Hey guys
T-shirt
And
I really enjoy your friends
I work in a
April
Area
And a lot of
Our fans
Podcast
As needed
I am able to
Stroller
Cameron Dallas
Brother
Student
Which stuff
Thank you
Makes it easier
My job and
Also
Mantle
Headache
Earrings
From my students
And
Kathy McCauley
But I really appreciate the work that
That you guys do
And I just wanted to give you
Thank you
Attack.
Thank you for all that you
Very much like that
Which is awesome because that sounds
Becoming like us congratulating ourselves
Appreciate that message in particular
Perspective they're going to maybe we don't think about all that often than that is
Information can be helpful to people in other walks
Just like that
That's very much for sharing
Man quickly
Come Chile
I love you guys
Give me MetLife
Better
Take me to
Taking me out
Depression
When I'm Harry Iraq
What time are you always
Episode
Do I love you
So much
Thank you for everything
Previous
So if you play today
Eeyore
New Friday
It will be
Happy birthday
Absolutely the message there is not
Antidepressants
I hope that's not the case I'm helping us podcast I hope
I hope that it's just an expression of our podcast
Make me a bring some happiness
That's so awesome it's really great to hear from happy birthday
Much thank you very much
Really awesome
Looks like you guys
You guys did it you convinced me vaccines are bad
Is backfire
I didn't
I love your work
Lisa
Particles
Aeropostale
Sharon
But
Work there someday
Try the world
Even if it is
Mighty little one
Ensure yesler
A bunch of
Stone Fox
WhatsApp
Inroads
I knew it
So yes
Thank you so much Lisa
We will be watching your career with put in a good way
Used to show up after the comedy show and he would show up
For the dance party
Yoga class
We show up
60 year old man like nice guys
I know that Siri
Call Eric
I hate that guy's
This is Mack truck
I just got another
I would say something
I was looking the Fridays at
Avirex
Trump
Really sucks
But you have to give him
And what you did
Point out
Superhot
Is that why
You played
He said
We have to re-elect
Great
It says you got the day wrong
Election day is
November
Repeatedly screwed it up
I thought it was going to be
I'm saying like hey
Everyone go out
Trying to like
People dead
4 years ago
He is
Just missing
Lying about it
Anyway
A good work
You guys in
I hope you're having a good day
It's been so long since I've heard his voice
Congratulations
I do enjoy everyday life or whenever
Persona
Now with infant
Become the Knight master
First Day's Night Master two weeks later you're the Night Stalker
Reckzo
It was actually
Trump
4 years ago who said the wrong day of
Yep
Go vote for me on the wrong day
Okay and
This this episode
Something unintentionally hilarious have
I'm super glad
Kind of stupid does he slip on a banana
I feel like before the end
We have to see him slip on a banana peel
Peso de pie perhaps the flowers spiritually the equivalent
Banana peel
Not literally how
Courses that Trump is going to win
The election
There's going to be
And so Alex is picking up a narrative
How much fraud
There's about to be a giant landslide
Top professors
Political scientist
30 - 56 elections are all unanimous
Limbaugh
Talk show host
Iran
Kamala Harris she is absolutely reviled 1%
The woman has
In the belly of a 747
Nice
Set a timer for 8
Democrats are Center
Tracy Chapman
They know they're going to lose the strategy is to contested election have a woman they can claim as part black
Criticism harlequin
Star of Civil War
Prime
United
I've no idea who these top people Alex's referring to her all unanimously saying the Trump is going to win in a landslide
Satan
Simple look
2020 predictions I can't really find any reputable sources that even say the Trump is a likely winner
The Economist forecasts project is looking at an eighty-nine percent chance of Biden winning the Electoral College and a better than 98
8% chance he'll win the popular vote
Winning Florida
Some other predictions are closer but I can't really find anything that matches up with what Alex is saying
Now he's response to the announcement of Kamala Harris is entirely predict
She's a woman of color so is ankle is doing since that you was chosen as vice-president because now he criticized her you'll be called a race
This is super boring and is itself a racist position because it's very easy to see how Alex Wood
About any potential non-whites President Day
Cory Booker
Is Joyce exact same thing
And this works for any sort of bigotry
If I'm the chosen Elizabeth Warren Alex
You criticized
If you chosen people
Achieved by engaging in this kind of argumentation is to make the argument that
Are not on the ballot because of their qualifications
Because they earned it
They're just there to make
Criticized
There's a very passive and cowardly way of arguing the only people who look like you deserve to be in leadership
Positions
Also in a much more concrete weigh
Trying to preemptively excuse
He's going to be saying about calling
Possible to criticize her record and not be racist
For Alex to do that
Try saying that all criticisms of her be called racist
To dismiss valid complaint
His criticism
And those people in his sector are in track racing
Sister's house
Yeah
Irresponsible
Why do you people were criticizing
Harris
And are not being used because they're not doing
Oasis fashion
Sebastian if you are a race
Like that's one of the fundamental things they don't understand
The idea of somebody criticizing them
Without a racial component makes no sense to erase
It's because everything
Yeah you might you might be onto something
Harris is going to be the VP pick
The primaries
You can see the preparation I said
Cheer
That would be Kamala Harris
Jeff Zucker
Abby's house
Check
Course
They're just lying
Joe Biden
It's no longer om4 Wars
Exactly predicted
They were all admitting
Alex spent way more time talking about Bloomberg
Bloomberg eat something weird
PNP also like
Kamala Harris is going to be talking about Hillary was the shadow candidate Michelle Obama
Just about everything in the course of
Democratic debate
The primaries
Is top-tier of
Baby for a minute maybe maybe for a minute but that wasn't is consistently doesn't matter
Absolute
So now
NFL stupid Alex's
And why I like
Legitimately
If anybody takes Alex's show seriously
They need to wake up
Eclipse
I will find
We got a
Supporters and Outlaw Women on them down
Level on men destroy them in demolishing immediately
Dawn
Endorses actions because
He will feel those
No stone will be left Unturned
As we speak
Wow
In every corner this right now
This is a fake
From a satirical website called
Troll. Org reporting on it
Sure this is just embarrassing levels of sloppiness
But there's no chance
Ethereal quotes
Actively lying like he just doesn't care
How could you say those words
I think they were real quick
According to that websites about
Everything on this website is fiction
It's not a lie and it's not fake news because it's not real if you believe that it's real you should have your head
Examine
It seems that the mission of this website is to create big things
Conservative
Particularly scared old white men
Will believe these lies to be true
After they've accepted these fake stories it's been revealed that the
The stories are made up
At which point
These trick people will feel shame
Which is what they do right this is basically laid out in there about
And works pretty well
And we see working with Alex
Second part is
Flawed
There is no shame
There's no recognition of getting
Trick the response to something like this is
Denial and rationalization
The intentions of this site may be good but I don't think it's a side is going to have the effect that it wants and it Mayo
Part of the problem
The expectation that you would feel ashamed if it was revealed
You believe something that was fake doesn't translate the folks who have made a habit of accepting false information
Based on appeals to emotion
Mates accepting false information part of their core identity
In this case literal truth maybe the
Is fake as hell
But what's more
Powerful is it it feels true to the scared old white dudes
It resonates with them and it accurately what they're afraid of it must be real
Even if you reveal that it's from an explicitly satirical site don't just say that the word themselves maybe fake
But the sentiment behind them
Alright on it
You're not actually what Harris believes they're fake
What yeah
And the worst part is
I kind of wish that was actually what she
Now you know
That would be bad
So is just an outrageous
Alex
So sloppy
About King George
Lusive Stan
It's true you would have to have
Tightened in either direction
Yeah
Of Harris
Something
Something entirely different
Kamala Harris
Eclipse
Same as she will have executive action to take your semi-autos
Let's look at the center
By gunfire and sold by Amazon
Colleges in the United States
Would you forgive me for divorcing before lunch
Somalia.
To take it exactly back
That clip doesn't say what Alex said that it was going
But she was going
Going to take executive action
Yeah they're saying that she would be in favor of
Executive action
To ban Imports
Semi-automatic
It's almost like a nationalist
Protectionist enough idea for Alex to be like
American-made assault rifle well
America
The
You're at the clipping something completely different
And we're not going to dress
So
It's calls on the show
And
One of these calls
Is the funniest
Thing I've heard in a really long time
Probably the audio version of a tiny bullhorn
It's really good
But it doesn't come until later
Call this guy
Either part of
Alex does not know what it is
Robert and Florida Robert Curran the are welcome
Hello sir how are you doing is an honor
Alex Jones
Send them over here
Thing that is taking off like a wild
Fire in this area
Operation flag drop
Haha
Google
You're the guy operations
Do you know what that is
Alright me that is Alex
Pretty much it
Okay
Every Friday
People together
Can you do your love
Furtrap get out
Cat people
People on the ground ending
Everywhere everywhere
8 p.m. to show the poles Airline
For what it is
Sure
Bring people together in the community cuz
Promote your small business
This is that are coming out
Promote your local candidate
We all have
Rally for Trump and America everywhere
Juventus
Bush growing up in Central Missouri and Columbia my parents every week every Wednesday
After work
We go to the stadium in
That you are the biggest intersection in town and have like four piece against the Iraq War
They were a group of like liberal hippie types
I am have an anti-war demonstration
Every week
Catching like wildfire Iowa
Hippies in Colombia operation something pain
Military
She diculous alright
Here's what I've got
At 6
Now maybe 6:15 sometimes the 18 holes
Can I get off work at 3
Alright
Sometimes at 6:15 I'll get there at 6:15
P.m. and we are going to
Take it to
The goddamn
I don't know who were taking it to I guess the virus anyway
It's going to have to stop at 8
I have to pick up Mike
Kids from the afternoon some great ideas
Operation equal
So he all right
Paper
We write request
Representative
Give me like a letter-writing
Just discovered the most basic version
Let me tell you something about this change.org
Petition in their predicted for them to stop
.
Stealing this idea
Decides
Do an operation flag drop rally at the Capitol
Yeah I just filled everything
Country is under siege
Got to complain
The
Re-stuff
This nation is under siege
Today
Normalcy bias where we just
Play Danger
Broken broken
Expected to take care of
Landslide
Secede
Floyd
Do you for videos that came out
White people being executed just because they're white
Good
Don't
I will because we have to
Mom on murder of boy
Because he rode his bike
To the edge
Sisters
Father
Thought it was a joke
Sonic
It wasn't
0 coverage in the mainstream media
45 days ago only
Nothing I'm going to say here should be taken to imply that I think this story is anything less than a tragedy and a horrific crime
Instances like this we find ourselves in a position where we have to take the story that Alex is telling and I
Exaggerated or
Deceitful narrative
And when we push back against that it can sometimes feel like we're minimizing the reality of the underlying story
We're just not my intention
Ultimately it should never be ignored
That there is a child who died
And there is no reason but that
Needed to happen
There's no indication from the news that I can sign with his five-year-old child was killed because the child was white
This is Alex's editorial position
Racial motive
I know that Alex isn't saying
Explicitly that this child was executed because they were white
Heavily heavily heavily implying it's the only story that he gets to after the preface of
I have these people who were executed because there were
InStyle
Linguistically the link is there to make that connection
And there's nothing in the story that I can find at this point
That would support that reporting
Ikea movie for story on this says quote
No details about a possible motive for the shooting have been released WRAL the shooting wasn't Rand
Sessoms
The Shooter Jennings father
A neighbor said that the two men had dinner together Saturday night and that sessoms was at cannons father's home earlier
Sunday the day of the
Shooting
So there's something to this story
What has happened
The refrain of media's ignoring the story because the victim
This is a way of indirectly attempting to invalidate the stories
You do hear about violence perpetrated against non-white people
Would you must only be hearing about because the media's agenda to tell you those stories
Raymond history this way is a disservice to the public and further it's kind of insulting to the victim and his family
It's not clear what the situation
Is here
Seems kind of important
And in terms of what is different
Response to this
It's that
Good guy got arrested
It's a horrible murder
He is going to face consequences for it
Obviously
The ideal situation would be nobody is murdered
Seeing as we don't live in a perfect
The world
It would be good
If Justice was dealt
Appropriately
You have
Things like
The cases of Ahmad Arbury or Brianna Taylor
These cases are really resident for people
Because there is an action that's being taken
Against the people who committed
These crimes
Yes
And presumably you'd have a similar response
Carlos
Victim
This case with a child is horrifying
Because of the child
Require as much
Maybe outrage
From people because
The system is working as it's
Supposed to
The guy got arrested
We'll figure out what the details of the story are as
That information becomes available
I don't understand why that's so complicated
If you
Here's a here's what I was
Alright
If you say to me
That they're going to want to try and start a race war
Quote on the back of George Floyd
I'm going to swing
Like if we were in public and he said that out loud I would have taken the swing immediate
I almost took a swing
You
I feel like
Locked up
Or something
Because
Franklin
You mostly listen to it when I'm the only person within swing
Set reminder
Never hurt your plants by preciate that
My guy still very sensitive
Oh yeah I understand
That instinct
That that response
That you have to me
Just think it's a very tired game of misrepresenting cases
In order to be like the media isn't covering
Plenty of stories
Outlets
Going to go by call name
Mainstream media
Is there
Kill people
Needs to be
I mean not nothing
Social ill
Yeah that people
Galvanized around like
Cops shouldn't put their knees on people's necks
No-knock warrant
You shouldn't shoot somebody that you're chasing down because you suspect
Social issues that we can get involved with and have a conversation about the
Possibly lead to some good
If you want me to have a large conversation about don't
Shoot a child
Okay
Don't
Good conversation
We did it
Anyway I'm so grateful
Figure out what's really going on because at this point
Time I'm beyond bad faith argument
I'd say that's a tragedy you don't care
Let's move on
He's got to go fund me there
Given to him if he was black
Kamala Harris
What black folks shopping
Here's here's the two indications that you have
My cameraman actually donated to GoFundMe
A Man donated
Exactly
Knows about this there's that could give money to this GoFundMe
GoFundMe that I found
Was way over its
Obviously I think
Very difficult
Think about you
Trauma
There's no possibility of putting a monetary value on any of that
Nothing
Two things that I think
Are indicative of him not caring or one
He obviously didn't give any of his own money
Realizes
That's his that's his little out, I'm going to say this in a dramatic way no one will ever know
He doesn't know anybody
Whatever
Anyway I will try to pretend it is not racist
When he starts looking at like a picture of the traitor or the alleged perpetrator
Because he has gone to trial
He's just talking about how he looks
They can't even.
What they are
Demon problem folks not a racial problem
Some groups
Infestation
Are you doing
Very nice ass
Zoomer more susceptible to Demons
Look Hey listen
White people
Humans meme
Baby gets sunburned
Stay on bed so how do you say something like recognized
Your age
Identic bigger
How do you say something
More susceptible to
Some races
I think I think you're making a very good points that I believe everybody is wonderful
The system wherein I blame demons
All the races that I think are gross and scary
It's not my fault it's just that after studying all of these heavy until
Certain shape of your cranium is acceptable
Demon
Now it's just
Scraped
White people
Viral video
For now
And they
We have the full video
Are you talking about
Infowars
Dot-com and
. tiny bullhorn
Austin Greenbelt reopened
Contact tracers
See all the fake Rangers and all the police
The police
They called seven police cars on it
Media says ice cream the fam
Mean
To the
I think I don't I don't care about this at all but
Texas by
He's doing the normal game but it plays this
Contacts
No concerts
You got mad cuz your wife
What limited registration to go into the
Do you went back with a tiny bullhorn looking to cause a scene
Juice
Embarrassment the manager with
Tiny bullhorn little Boulevard
Course everyone's going to make fun of
Thing as Congressional next
Deanna Lorraine
Thanks for coming on what do you want to tackle first
I don't know you want to tackle the Australian cut when they pretend
Gavin gruesome
So I wonder
One thing that's really funny
Twitter handle is still Deanna for Congress
Stir fry buried
Yeah
Australian cut off there is that
Australian TV
An interview someone who believes it's a hoax
She was invited on and she's talking
About bunch of nonsense
Had this person
Heads up bankers get into a little bit of a like
Are we going to invite her back
No
Freezes
Becomes like
Spotty
She's going to complain to Alex about that
So
Australian invited me how kind of them I would be okay couple weeks ago
Once I found out that they were going on another lockdown
Okay except for maybe essential Services here and there
And they said they were having a wall of Steel
Police forces all the way outside the city of Melbourne
Boyfriend between defending
Their individual liberty saying hey this is like prison this is basically prison you do Australian
Fight for your Liberty
Hahaha
Let's go ahead and roll video on Australian television when they cut it off
11:11
Wow
Hilarious
Back
Is audio of someone slipping on a banana
Middle of complaining of Colorado
Mariah's
God dammit
Is everything this is idiot
Get her back on the line
Alex has no other choice
Two-player Co-op Tire on the Australia
Complete
I know that the United Nations
Come on Alex
Come on
Ye like I will say
You know this Miley Cyrus, but
He does
I think it was just your Skype
Howard Cosell
About Australia
For me I love it I love it
Anna back on so you have to go to call
This is
Oh oh
Talk to another caller
Let's go ahead and speak
Weather
Jacob in Georgia thanks for holding the head
Ono Ono Ono
Alright
We've been doing this
I have to I have to applaud Alex
He doesn't end up blowing up
Formal
Progress
At the end I was like oh no
Can you hear me
So he talks to this guy
I really didn't give a s*** what he has to say but this is like
Mike down for this because this was
So funny
He is complaining
He's complaining about
This college
Kennesaw State
In Georgia
You have to get like a
Temperature reading band or something like that
I don't know if this is true or not but whatever that might happen
This is very fun
I'll talk about that with RJ
What do you make the New Jersey governor
The temperature
College in Georgia
Bigger wife
Dijon
Deanna Lorraine is here
We're flying or Austin exit tell us
Don't think that was that guy's wife
Mom
I'm just I go through this chronologically
The show
Yeah you get off this like really weird self-contradicting interview with Deanna Lorraine
And then someone tells me something
Used to hear that a lot on a lot of the time
Made more sense cuz it was like
Late at night
Is your wife
This guy is like a freshman in college
It's not impossible context clues
One of them is that he said he's from Georgia to ks in Georgia
Presumably
Living with
You know that's in state situation
Yeah
I don't know
Damn I can't imagine so funny
At what about
Let's hope
So he does get Gianna back on and have a stupid interview that I don't think it's worth
Listening to
So are we get to the 13th here on Thursday
And Alex
Super excited
That the trending on Twitter has continued
And he continues just
To say that they're taking them out of con
Has been number one on Twitter
Most of the day
Video
10 minutes what doesn't make sense
You showed up at
And started
Yelling
Nothing wrong
That sucks right now that sounds right
Although innocent it is still read them because it's just
That his wife was
Yeah I mean I think I would replace random
Pointless
Workout
Evolution
Ally
There was a Rockefeller record
About
Various situations that could come up in the world
Technology
Scenarios
Of course the word door Ford scenarios
That they laid out and try to
Conceptualize challenges
In the world
Alex
You took this
A bunch of scenarios but in fact it's
Similar in some superficial
Cuz there's an outbreak in it and
Step one
First volley was ignoring
The context of a document
Second evolution of
To say that it was a
Plan
Lockstep was
The plan document
Now there's the third evolution of it
He's just making up quotes
Quote under the guise of
We will create a prison state
A planetary scale
He's not in there
David ickes website
Original content. David Icke website
Yeah that's someone else's editorial discussion document as opposed to be
Actually from it
This is just made up s***
This is this is
I wish more I wish more
Does simulations on what
Could happen just included like
Well obviously if this happens we're going
Integrated police state
This is underwhelming
Whenever you start off by saying
Where is going to be
Well-known
Sam Hyde
Popover
Do somebody who worked in comedy a bit
Upper echelon
You know wanted to do stand-up
Familiarize yourself with the topic
Certainly doing stand-up all the time you end up like I was on the festival circuit about her I went around
Metal lot of comics
Talk to famous people
Someone
By the name of Sam Hyde well let me put it to you this
Alright it took me a good seven years before I go
The bottom level of the food chain is where I was
And I think I knew just about everybody there
He wasn't even there
Vampire along the lines of sketching prank
His picture is used often on like 4chan
Do you the picture of him as like fake identifying
Of the shooter
He's like he's like
Facebook looking has become a meme that used to try and trick people into thinking
Scooter
So awesome
So that's how we got here
We're not going to listen I just thought it was funny
Me too
Analysis
Johnny Estrada
Kamala Harris
Natalia evil she is
That's really exciting
Not going to learn that from Alexander
To remind you that he was the third wheel
On the
Tricycle
Documentary where they tried to prove that I was married to her brother
It was a real embarrassment
But somehow Alexander's world
Move forward
I mean the pictures I'm going to pitch Laura Loomer
Alright
Everybody knows about
That's the trick
You got to get up
A good name you got to get some good Brandy
Call yourself The Luminaries
Done
That's not bad
1.what every election
Political party
Deanna Lorraine
Before Sunrise
For sunset
A big
I think he's done great work
Maybe I'm a little bit itchy on
I didn't Boyhood could have been better but I respect what he was trying to do
Coffee and cigarettes
Scanner Darkly
Sounds good
Unfortunately movies include Alex cameos
Is crazy guy with bullhorn
We got a
Glitter isn't working
Right now
Doing anyway I don't know what the f*** is a boy
Scope
You can do it you can totally do totally do it go in there
Director's cut only change
Slader
If You Don't Know About Us by request
Time Alex brings up linklater I always liked
To try in like it's worth
This
This created such an awesome mental picture
Rick linklater was at my office
Richtofen
Did you read what he said
Shut up
Rick Blackwell
Bringing some bangers
Today
It's not really me
What is Bluff and I love it
Later and now he's being that you know
Did you really into Zelda genocide
I kind of think he's accidentally like later just accurately
You know Alex is on this is an honest accurate representation of what happened
Just changing the tone
Because here's how it sounds to me
He says all that s*** to linklater
Yeah you know I've heard some of that stuff
I'm going to have to go
I shouldn't have kept you in my boobs leave now I thought you were a fun weirdo
Now you're a dick
So Alex is a free-speech absolutist
Medium
Alex is upset
About Bill Burr
Call sure
Scary thing
And when the people fairly.
On Netflix
She got into depopulation
We need to depopulate the Earth
I swear
Alex complains about comedians jokes
Use yells bad were apparently have to kill the first memory
Make a joke about getting an abortion
Alex wants her damn to
Sahel Bill Maher jokes about basically anything and the official Democratic Party
Platform reveal
And now I guess Bill Burr said something Alex doesn't like
I don't care
That is a fake Thomas Jefferson
I was going to say I already knew that
Monticello
Serious quote
They're often attributed to Jefferson but there's no evidence he ever said or wrote that
They concluded that this quote is actually from the 1914 debate against socialism delivered by John Basile Barnhill
That is attached to Jefferson as well as
Samuel Adams
I would assume
Because no one cares about.
They want this to sound
Yeah I don't
In Baltimore is that what happened
So then he would not like my Jordan
Jordan
Jordans
You said that I've been bringing bangers you have
Pretty good that I thought was going to be
Do you like
Really the most fun
And now I'm really self-conscious about it
This I think is incredibly funny
Promote his upcoming rally
And things
Fall Apart
Flag Old Glory
Texas flag
Tomorrow
When I went down there this Sunday
What song is this
Three quarters
Saturday
Quarter mile hill
Cutting a promo
Mother doing stuff I am Tennessee
For the next segment
Please print me the address
Because
See you on the screen
Sometimes
Miles show
Something I can't
I'm going to get that
And then we're just going to
Dennis Rodman
Also shooting promos
Cuz I I just
Refocus I need to get reset
I was going to say
I was going to do
Dominic bilderberg's
Alright
I mean
Not good at it
You buddy
It seems like it
You thought that the funny part was in couldn't remember what day you went to after the pill
No I knew that was fun
But that really added that snowball into something
Real grade
Yeah
Dude just f****** recorded
After your show is everything
Just doing this show to record
Yes promo
People to come to the rally on so he can double down on the time because someone didn't give him the
F****** address or whatever
Wait a half-hour of his show because this because he's got to use the next segment
Haven't you heard that old saying you got to miss two birds with one stone Dan Wild
Having so much of the show
This
FA Cup
I am talking about how everyone
Making a contact
And then he he
Coming back from break
And you get a different song that is really into
What is the whole song
Do Bonanza
I think your chattel
Come on you missed it
I want to go and you with her
Inoculation
And that
The UN world government must be number one on Twitter of the deception around
The family
Do your job
I love her
But I ran out of time to get to the news karaoke version of Rawhide
F***** up the promoter rally to do you have the address
Alicia Alicia
Baby that'll be next time when I do this Wonderland
I know be somewhere tomorrow no more time for news though cuz we got to get Allie Alexander
Actually I mean
This this guy
Who directed
Please use the director he was at least a third wheel
Goodnight documentary
Ann Woll
I can't stress this enough
Amazing never be able to recover some kind of embarrassment
Actually I think he's there
The danger to him
We ought to be really nervous and that's why I'm so passionate
15 Trump needs to collapse
The ticket on the other side
Tell the progressives and
Tell the weather
The truth
Mass incarceration war on drug
He's corporatist on the west
And we need the right and the left
Become together
Behind either a president Kanye West or present.
Infinity trillion Infinity agree with you
Xander is expressing here the real viable strategy Trump has to win
Service which everybody
Should be very worried.
You can just turn off the mail that's good
Not good
In order for Trump to increase his share of votes
To convince anyone
That's the best use of effort is to focus on making sure the other side has a
And as Alexander various
Progressive and further like contingents of the country
Democrat
Well it's a real issue that the Democratic ticket is going to have to face
And it would be an issue with or without any
Of course strategy that Alexander is laying out is to exacerbate those feelings of disenchantment or disappointment
In hopes of suppressing the vote enough to put Trump over the top
The real telling there's that he considers Kanye a serious candidate
I've been coming out about that whole farce of a campaign is starting to look
Real Shady
And even though I know if the talk about him beating with Kushner is overblown
You still kind of have to look at his idea of running as an attempt to f*** with the election
Be able to get on enough State ballots to actually win soviak
Redirecting some vote
Big huge publicity
Restart for Kanye on cell
Very smart series political commentators
They're f****** idiot
Which is a description of Ali Alexander
Jacob bloomer
They're either showing their cards
They're an idiot or they're showing their cards
Said they need some
I do want the
So take
Display
I just want the entertainment of Kanye West
Like that's the only way
Terms
You know the
Progressives on the left
That is a conversation that is valid on the left
It's not coming from the right because there is much worse
Yeah disenchant
With
The Democratic
The date
Is to suppress
The Democratic vote
Conversations about you know Harris's record o Biden's record on the left
I think you can have conversations about them. But if you want
Which you can hopefully
Who's closer to being
In line with
Social priority
Things that you have
And the policy priorities
Conversation
Democratic party going to have
In this election
Open Season
It's not something
No I agree with you that it's not insurmountable challenge presented from someone like Allie Alex
Because that is solely to be disrupted
And I think that there is a really important difference
Between those two because sometimes they can look similar
I think as
Electric gets closer people have to
Keep a pretty
Good sensor keep an eye on that
More than anything else to
Differentiate between people who are stirring and people who are having good faith
Conversation
And that's
That's due entirely to the Democratic party being s***
Like I'd entirely
That is it
They earned those conversations and they don't seem to be doing anyting
Do otherwise
So it's one of those it's one of those circumstances where
It is very easy
22 Jump in as a shitzu
Because you can just
You can walk in
What's that expression
Perfect is the enemy of good
The expectation
Being Framed from the right
Is the enemy of
Better than Trump
I hate I hate even having conversations about this because
I don't want to ever be a voice
It's saying
Like hey if you have
Concerns about XYZ
Don't agree with.
At the same time I think that
Realistically
There are only two possible winners
The next election
And one of them is nightmarish
And the other is
Not as good as we want
Ideally and hopefully
Someone who'll be receptive
Protest
It's complicated
I don't know
About the
You know
Repeat very difficult to differentiate
Petit pot stirrer
And people who are making good arguments
Say okay are you somebody who is stirring
Totally
Completely diss
Discount
Argument
Like if Mike cernovich has something
To say about the Democratic ticket
It's not coming from a place of concern
About keeping people on it
I'm trying to sew problems
And you know it
Vain
Alexander somebody who maybe you don't know who that guy is
Socks the White House all the time
There's one thing that's missing
Alexander
I'm not talking about the documentary
It turns out that Alexander didn't always go by that name
He was formerly known as Ali Akbar
According to an investigation conducted by Breitbart on cover
Hollywood Court convicted in 2007 of charges of credit card fraud
$20,000
Send
Where he began to blog
Get off the phone
He started an organization called license Victory group called The National bloggers
Club
According to a 2012 article in Yahoo news the national bloggers Club was started with seed money provided by right-wing
Foster Freeze
According to an article in the examiner from July 2012 National
501 c 3 status until this organization
Such status
Somebody to spec look
Super Shady
Hollywood be associated with
Egyptians claiming tax-exempt status
He was associated with the American Liberty Alliance
Who does a tea party website back 2008
Here's a little bit from an article about this in Crooks and Liars
Starting off as a LA's technology
Consultant
Donations
Yes despite claiming to be in the application process for 501 C 4 status
In August 2000
Yahweh eventually was embarrassed into posting the following caveat on their website
Do not On Their donation
American Liberty Alliance is not a 501 c 3 501 C 4 or political action committee
We are not registered as a non-profit and we do not respond to such
Yet they'll Incorporated under the name American Liberty Alliance a nonprofit corporation
Name
Circles of tea-party groups
Trump
Maybe he advises got from Robert Mercer
Brandy run up to D20
16 election
Also getting tons of money from the Mercers around this time was Milo yiannopoulos
Probably would still be on that scroll is Buzzfeed having
Indisposed
And that whole thing about his
Distasteful appearance on Joe Rogan
Star cast
My point is that I don't see much substance being a convicted felon whose crime involved
Defraud
Whose career
Republican political circles
Which seems exceedingly easy what are you just going to not look I feel like once you get
If you join the Republican party at a certain level of Fame
You know like
If you're if you're there if you do not grow manufacturing some kind of purse
Section of bars people will fall for it
Teach the graph I think
I think that
That seems to be
What the picture I've been able to gather
No I mean like if you're at is if you exist
In a place where like
You can hang out with Laura Loomer Jacob Wohl and Alex Jones and you don't worry about shooting your credibility of the foot
Credibility
Is not irrelevant concern for you
The bullet that
I'm a straight white male with a
Spell comedy
Nutella
After dark or whatever when you break
I should be grifting right now
Terrible idea
Continue some conspiracies here
Coherent nonsense
I was trying to make sense of it in the context that he was providing
And I just
This is just
Lunacy
I got to tell you you just can't help
Reconcile political Theory with the Bible
And come to these conclusions
Oh my gosh you know it really is a deep State oh my gosh
Clinton's
And the bushes have a relationship
Oh my gosh
Missing what is it
When Biden look like he was going to pick
Witmer equipment
The BLM Ryan starter
Biden and Kamala Harris
I got to tell you
It's not it's not lunacy
The point owl
Looks inevitable unless
We wake up
People
Do not be reactionary
Do not just save the oil
Opposite of a
Believe in something believe in order align yourself with God
And then fight
Because
People need to understand
Is it the Marxist
It's a spiritual thing for them
What
I sincerely don't really even understand
The goal or
Queen of that was
I mean
Conspiracies about stop
I guess the only thing that I can pull from the Bible that you might be talking about is
Obviously revelation
Right it has to be before it has to be
Christianity
Almost all revelation
They just don't understand that
Book of Revelation wasn't optional
You know like at no point in time was God in the Book of Revelation just been like
But if you guys work really hard to avoid this huh we're going to do it
Revelation right now
Wake people up
Need to worry about that hole
I guess that is an inherent
Said I weird
I don't understand I don't understand the point that he's trying to make outside
Across which is all these people are evil
Something to do with the Bible
Wright's dearest Dearest
Fritos this religious zealotry that's underlying is politics
Clearly
Which
I think
Is bad
Your religion involves saying don't look into it
I'm not cool
Well
Witches
We must ask for God's intervention we must walk blindly and faith
You said you wanted to wake people up
Think about this
Keeping in this from
Have we ever seen this many
Witch covens
Trey and cursing hexa gether no never seen
Sacrifices
You people are
Streaming
All these goddamn boys
Secret blood rituals might be close to the bloodline
It's definitely not lunacy specifically suggest
Oven
Generally speaking
Go to the forest under the full moon
And I drink blood
Play that's a definition
Also Ali says that he's been in this for 13 years which would be what to 2,000
Credit card fraud
Is the last year and people are just
Like it is
Wework soda
Sensitizer this
Just in a vacuum you be like this
Sensational
Outrageous political beliefs
Maybe yeah
Political beliefs
Designs
With
Our enemies are witches again jewels in the forest
We must call on God to Vanquish them
To take someone at
Ready
Eminem
Infiltrated even the good
Create
A contract
But that they must infiltrate us
Write in order to deceive our believers
Almost
Thank you so much
Very impressed
I was not you say something like
Have you ever seen this many witch covens around
And then somebody's like
Hey listen we got to have you back on to talk about the election
Listen
Those are some political opinions I want to
You kind of got out of pocket and I don't want to talk
We got over that just got embarrassing
I do I want
You fill that hole
1 800 wish I would have got
Wish I would have got that number
This was a bit more humorous than I expected
And there has been a little bit of stagnation with Alex
But I want
And let them know that we have present day stuff
But we have some
Some plans
For some really exciting stuff that's coming down
Pike
In terms of other
Substantiv more meaningful content than
Just laughing at Alex's dumbass
So excited
A moment
And that's what will be will be upon us
Pac-Man website
Let It Snow
Twitter
Please find
Doing God's work right now
I'm Ross
Person
Alex