Alexandra Thurston color
A couple dudes like sit around and drink novel
Montana's legendary soda in honor of
You know that ass whole body
Montana's legendary soda
Its soda is better than the feelings that I have about Montana to point
Let's see
I'm part of the rest
Estevan the ground
This is interesting
This is candy
This is gross
What is
What is groats
He's like
Have you ever put a lot of sugar after you
Put the Kool-Aid mix
That is exactly what this there are similarities
But move on Alex Jones
This is a podcast about Alex Jones
Is it
This is not just about Alex Jones
This is
Awareness
But Alex Jones
And relative to that
I know
You know only
The slimmest margin
At this point as many episodes
Done
As we've done
I know a whole lot more than I ever expected
This is a whole new level of
To get to today's episode but first I would like
To start things off with an out-of-context drop
From Alex
Because this is what they do
This is what they
Don't laugh
That's some solid work
I get there's no way that he can ever start
Don't laugh
It does not make me
I'd like to give a shout out to
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you for donating. Com
Sports
The show you can become a pilot
Today we are going into part
Of my
Investigation to what the fuc
Happened to Alex Jones
Brighton 2015
When when did it all go south
And why
Yeah I think I'm going to try and read between the lines as best I can figure out exactly what happened
How about just tell us why and then we'll save everybody several hours
More fun
Every Journey
Call
Investigation
We started the investigation
But
Coincidentally
The day after Trump announces
Some shooting happen
First investigation episode really became
About
The interview with Larry Nichols
Which I believe is the kickoff in earnest
Of Alex's hero's journey
This is going
To be a little bit more focused on the event
Navigation
That one we had to deal with
We're going to
To be covering the
The time span
Of June 9th
2015 up to July 5th
Ms episode
Hosted a bunch of
Alex
For like 4 days of it until David night was hosting
And we're not going to talk about
And then I'm going to my cousin Buckley's weather
We don't talk about that cuz we don't want to bore
And then on top of that June 29th
We're not going to be covering that at all cuz I have nothing to do
With presidential election
Entire episode about it
You can find in RI
If you'd like
Music off of
Listener yawn asked us to go back
Two when gay marriage got passed by this
Court episode ended up being
June 29th
Yes so that's why I won't be covering that but
Some variant
Interesting
To lay out for you and for our listeners
I'm excited to get to all of them we're going to begin here
Trump announced
Just kind of see on June 26th
Yes at the same time
He made those horrible
Disparaging comments about Mexico shipping us
A bunch of people
And they're not sending her back
What it means to be president
Absolutely
Before starting
On the 18th
Alex
Think about Donald Trump
He said nothing at all about
Not really
Hillary is evil
Did that like
Give me an election or anything
Just throwing a little vampire
Which
I'm beginning to love our regular
I will be
Completely cuz I've started to be really afraid of
Butts
Stevie Nicks
What's going on with it
I don't know man I just I don't want to f*** around
With a weird old southern
Is 70's on his Deathbed
Deals
Sanity
So much
It isn't real
Yeah so we're going to start with
We're out
Still
Wrestling a little bit with the Charleston shooting at this point he's still giving a lot of like if you believe this stuff
You're an idiot
You know all these race issues
Distract
Are you still on the false flag
Yeah
Drop-in Reverend child being like
Yeah and so the
Only thing I wanted to pull from this episodes is not really anything worthwhile is
We're outside
On his desk I don't like that at all
On his anchor.
Hostile work environment.
It's one of those giant
Rifles
Like one of those big sniper rifles that they would
By one of his bonds
I called face down ass up
Obvious thing to say but
Look at the logic of the people
At the end of the Civil War
That was racist the first gun laws were racist
Is again
Upside down it's a total fraud
I'm not even going to get into the history
Again
And the party the Ku Klux Klan
So
So at the end there
Civil rights himself said that we have lost
The South River
Never mention that because they are today
Wonderful it's a wonderful thing that everybody like
On the right for me on the right like always
Civil War the Democrats
Called
The GOP races
Give me the Democrat
Not a hunter
Because you accept
Did those people who left the temp Kratts
Like with open arms just love you
Please
That's an illusion you have in your head does a paranoid fear narrative
Or at least get our own guns
Shoguns off Alex Jones's death
We've established
Talked out the Pope
Pope said that people who sell
Weapons aren't Christian
And Joe Biggs
Special Report
Head down rifles is owned by Christians
This idea that the NRA was founded to Armed black people against the KKK
I believe that 100% sense to me
Please Dan go ahead and prove
Alex Jones was absolutely
Nope is based on a comment that a guy named Harry Alford made
Oh are you saying that his
Tire argument is based on what
So Harry offered was the president of the national Black Chamber of Commerce
Atlanta 2008
I want to thank the Lord for our constitution I also want to thank the NRA for its Legacy
The National Rifle Association was started founded
By religious leaders who wanted to protect freed slaves
From the Klu Klux Klan
Pre-made
It is been
Wild
Disclaim all kinds of stuff
Doesn't prove his claim it all Alex Jones
Speech by Ann Coulter
Which will get you in a second
But fast
We love
Dismay
Egyptian by their troops
Union veterans
Colonel William
Speed Church
In General George Wingate
Formed the National Rifle Association 1871
The primary
To quote promote and encourage rifle shooting on a scientist
Cific bases
So basically they were concerned
That they were losing too many bullets
Because they were going out to war if you will work good
Yeah that doesn't sound
It doesn't
Basically them being like
We don't train people well enough
And the roots of the was largely educational
Nearly as terrible as it is today
Promoting
Promoting guns
Shortly after
To the Civil War
Back then
I mean they were like
They might as well
Slingshots but that shoot farther you don't really have too much
Control over where their bullets
Yeah
The ball down in Monroe
Screw side barrels or whatever the hell they're called
Adjust that like
Hope for the best
So back to the NRA being sounded to
Help
Black people against the KKK
Ann Coulter speech
It was used
Alfred
You know
Proof
And she made an argument about the organization called the blackguard
Robert F Willie
Who was the Civil Rights Act
And if you look actually at the
Activities
Actually almost a bullseye
Williams after the NRA
We can state that when the NRA was created they were like
Innate
We're going to need to be
Yeah really interesting and actually works against
The
Robert Williams took over leadership of the local chapter of the National Association
Colored people
Close to the KKK
Williams filed for a charter with the NRA informed the blackguard
An armed group Committed to the protection of black
Mabel Williams
I said her husband the occupations of the members
When applying for the NRA Charter
That you quoted
I'm sure when we joined
And the years after then
Have they have known that we were a black group they would have revoked our Charter
She said of course
They basically just started it already chapter
Pretty solidly against the argument that the
Like like most times whenever White
People have decided to help
Yeah never willingly do it on their own
History of
Is Grimm
What are the big things that the Black Panthers
Do is
Watch
With a
Get ton of guns
Whenever I cop arrested
Like they would just go hang out like hey
If you didn't
That's fine
If you go beyond what it is you're supposed to go beyond
Guess what there's 10
Doing like renewal project
Yeah they would have armed guards
They're putting up a stop sign
Keep trying to put up
Stop sign
I am so finally they just send out arms
What else do you do like that's the situation that
All too often everybody found themselves in over the years
In the Civil Rights
F*** it
All the time
All of the America
People have found themselves
And pushed
Sooner or later what other things can you think of other than
If you're going to threaten US with guns
Which is a good why I'm in the place now I'm looking at all of our liberals
We should control guns and I'm more like
Gun control
They're starting to really talk to submit that there aren't armed liberals and liberals
Pentagon
More vocal
About it
This is an in-depth investigation
Can I get into the in-depth investigation
The Sacramento Bee papers to jostle
The real
Good enough
The rest of the episode on the 19th is just a bunch of like
Going back and forth on
Is this fake is this real
Benny other long interview with governor
Minnesota
He is in the middle of Being Suit
Over the crystal
The only the governor's over the body
Use in Predator 2 using a lot of stuff
Chris Kyle
American flag
In his book he wrote that he beat up Jessica kurai
Yeah
Famous book
But he beat up Jesse
Ventura in a bar fight
After Jesse mouth off about Murray
Stories
Unlock Injustice
Richmond
Slander
Right right right court trial
Didgeridoo
Couldn't come to a bird
And ended up ruling in Jesse's favorite 822
After 5 days
Goodnight
He's a state
Chris Kyle die
Spoiler alert
His estate
Pile of garbage called American
Don't recommend
Appeals
The Judgment the Ventura
+ 500000 of unjust enrichment
So it's 18 1.8 million dollars
The Judgment or is going to
The estate Appeals
And that's showing up on the show
When the appeal is pending
I need your audience
Help me out I need my legal defense
Respond
Because I need to
Tons of media organization
Are promoting
This appeal
He's trying to appeal to Alex's audience on the basis of life
Viacom
20th Century Fox Fox
ABC CBS New York time
They're all behind this
Because they want to be able to lie about people and make money
That the estate
Appeal
And Jessie and
What's a bummer
My relationship with Jesse Ventura
Like I kind of
Had some good ideas
He's in the same boat is Alex but not a proper
Cuz he has a lot of really dumbass ideas but it's same time he's really
Philosophically consistent about his support of legalizing weed
Maybe 10% more than Alex
Not an a******
Well now that is on the Alex Jones Show
I'm of the opinion that
He is a libertarian
Prominent Libertarians
I really
Yeah you're right you shouldn't go on his show
If you run for governor of Minnesota
Novel
Are making this argument and I read the court decision of his appeals case
Comes later
Down the road
The appeal
Because he makes this exact same argument
I need Court as well
You guys should
Vote for me
You guys should choose me
Rule in my favor
Because
They have an insurance policy
It's going to handle
Harpercollins has an insurance company
Think that's going
To pay the saddle
You're not screwing over the family
I've been slandered
Devoting my favorite
It turns out
That is very bad
Was that true though
Okay well that's a bad ARG
The appeals court found
They looked
Chris Kyle's contract with harpercollins
And the only thing they can find it
Is one line in it that says
They may have him
They may have
Insurance
Policy
He does exist
He brought it up
Open court and his lawyers made that argument
Unfairly biases
The jury again
Chris Kyle
Oh yeah of course
Screw over a a widow
No but at the same time if I knew that
I was going to screw over a corporation
The Faceless millions of dollars
Is
The traditional printed
We don't
We don't need to help
Twisting the Jesse's doing when he's on the show
Who cares
I really don't need
To hear that application
But at the same time
Alex is starting to play a little game
Jeffy
You should run for president
She's trying to pitch Jesse Ventura you need to get in the race
I'm Jesse's argument is
I want to wait till there's just two
I want people in it I have name recognition
I think I remember him having that conversation
Eddie keeps saying I've got this appeal to take care of
Then I'll probably join the race
And if I lose
That's it
Maybe that's what happened
There's no show on Saturday
You take Saturdays off
So we come
On the 21st
So the 21st is a Sunday
I started to notice that what Alex Jones does on Sundays
Is
So he uses it to end and
Start Naruto
And also to bury stories that he kind of Hope snowing really pay attention
Couple Sundays recently
To make the pizzagate apology
He's
Covered reporting on that
Another recent Sunday
Violated the terms of their eye
Settlement agreement of course
Just whenever narrative has run out of steam
Never wants to launch a new one
He doesn't on Sunday
So on this Sunday
He knows that the Charleston narrative is kind of going away
So he uses Sunday to like
So he has an interview with jhacari
Who's in Charles
And
It awesome
Oh it's actually really awesome
I love Jacari jacks
I don't know as we all know now he is
World
So
No clue
He's talking about how beautiful the church service but he went to at the Emanuel African Methodist
Episcopal Church
Was the night before he's talked about how there's a lot of unity and everybody in great
Spirits
And it's a beautiful thing to witness
And it's super fun
That there's a monument to a white supremacist a block away from the church
I don't understand how
It's free speech
And you know I don't want to encroach on people but it's real world
He's talking about how that night
There's going to be a march across this historic Bridge
Everyone's going to be holding hands and it's going to be this beautiful thing
And Jacari is he had the right idea about
For the most part
Meanwhile Alex keep being like
I think so are we seeing the beginning of the end of
Jakari Jackson
Alex wants to focus on the negative and rytary is really focus
Personally positive
And I think it's really cool is his literal come
The Jesus moment out of church
Possibly I don't know Whitney ends up quitting I don't know the story of that will find out more as if
This investigation goes
Sort of I believe
Basically the end
Charleston
He's got to be there
Courtship
It's time for the new narrative
Which is
An incredibly intense
Prolong
Argument that Financial collapse
Is coming this summer
Yeah it's right around the corner he has a bunch of people who are
Experts
He has Peter Schiff
Who is Ron Paul's economic advisor
He has
A bunch of people on
And it's all about how the dollar is about to collapse
And how we're all going to be
We're going to get to that
You know where this is going
Spoiler on it
Willie was the Y2K thing again biscuits why would you push this
Narrative well I guess I'm also selling
Apocalypse supplies
Little course you're going to push this
Narratives are what we already
Because you're a genius
You've already spoiled where that narrative it ends and why
Is probably worse than you
It's even more exploitative
What you're saying
In an hour and a half
Because
Jessica's boiler Alex Jones is out
To sell gold
You started this disaster
Collapse narrative talks
The town about it
Anything's really focused around
He's talking about the main story is that he's pushing are about how
Texas
From the reserves
I don't know
We don't trust
You guys holding our gold we want to hold it ourselves
That sort of
AutoZone like semiconductors
Electronics it does all kinds of
Amazing
It does 0 amazing things sitting in a vault somewhere
Yeah but
Much like colloidal silver colloidal gold
I did not know that
What is colloidal
Remember something to do with like
Floyd's
It has something to do with it being suspended in a solution
Anyway
It's all the gold narratives bad like
They're getting bars of tungsten covered in Gold like that
There is one
Like legitimate story of that but yeah
He's really pitching that
Hard
But on this Sunday show
He says something that I
Blank is involved in his abortion narrative
But I'm not sure
But I could not do this show without playing this clip
Cuz it's so weird
Listen to this argument
Everett just
Recognize
How f****** dumb he is
While he's trying to talk about how smart
This is amazing
I want to listen to
The psychological warfare
The manipulation
Billboard
In downtown Austin
Understand that billboard you understand everything
Chick-fil-A
As a window into guilt
Shut up little texas-based company
About Chick-fil-A
Set alarm for 9
See that's why
Little children
And I say ETS not this
And the cows
Look real but they also look humanoid
It's been downgraded
Just a yellow.
The yellow blob with two eyes
On your guilt of not wanting to hurt an animal
Adult
Come on your smart
You know what it is
Alder
Show me more than
That
Crazy
Isn't he
He's mad about it
Just thinks it's propaganda abortion somehow
Because you don't want animals go for the blob
Cuz the chicken
Nobody's not taking into account is the entire point of the app
Is the drawing the Billboards
The handwriting is really bad because
What do you think is going on there
Chick-fil-A
Chicken is really good
Actually read an article in
About the creation of this campaign.
The guy who started the campaign
Propaganda
Small advertising budget and they couldn't whenever they wanted to get outside of shopping malls
Just like a Sbarro or whatever
Directions in the mall
I've never had one
Cuz malls are the devil
But they weren't they were in malls and I wanted to get
Freestanding
Start advertising with a couldn't
With anybody
They had no budget
So they did
Is it looks like we can't get commercials
Not really going to work out
Billboards are
Comparative
So they started doing
Billboard advertisements
They wanted to get
Pretty interesting ideas but they were all kind of like
So they came up with one
Where it was
Three-quarters of the billboard is done
It's like a chicken sandwich
And it's like you know just a normal billboard
And then their last quarter of it
Is white
Like designing
Just had stopped
And it says boss
Got hungry be back later
On the the last part of the billboard
MMA have like a 3D
Going up to that
So people driving
Okay this is
Interesting concept but we can do better
And around this time
Simpsons were super cute
And Bart's catchphrase was don't have it
Call man
If we wanted to incorporate that somehow
Add wizard
We're coming up with it
Don't have a cow
Alright
Chicken
Hopefully started a couple
An amazing reenact
Can see it in your eyes right now you're sitting in that ad room right here I'm waiting
For you to describe the small boy
Maybe they've got some paper on the wall just write down ideas
Terrible what they came up with cuz I am going to Farhan too long on the
Don't have a cow who doesn't want you to have cows
And don't want to be right
A carousel
It's amazing
Family
Selling
Right
It's not about abortion
It's about Portia
How do you not see that problem
Find it right okay
You have cows
Because here's the truth of it
These cows are actually super intelligent
Good morning
Pretending to be these
It's not a real check
Working yet do you know what else is eggs
How do you get
So as we all know now
Chick-fil-A invented
Exact look all this b*******
You get this
You get everything
What was the beginning thing like it's a window into
Amanda looks like real
Isn't really feel guilty about the idea
I think that's necessarily A
I do
Well I know I mean from
As far as a worldview of
Ifyou humanized
You're much more likely to
You care about it
That you don't care
Right like the chickens were also anthropomorphize 2 on the billboard
And they were both like
Computing and drawing like Lego
Situation where it's
You know what
You're not on the same level here that's what makes people like me and Allie
Different from you
Well it's been fun is going out tonight
We're done
Ice cream
Abruptly as because I go
Full Alex
I believe that's the wrong quick but it's just like rocket I'm in
What was going on on the
Second
A lot of the rest of the stuff again is just laying out of the 21st
Beginning of the narrative about
Collapse
So we go into the 22nd that's Monday
Is virtual collapse of the financial
System
I got to get
This thing off my
Yeah that's all
Time to get in
Yep
Damn you out
Nipsey 22nd comes around at the Monday
You still on his b******* about the collapse
Peter Schiff
Who explains that
There's a bubble
Just Breathe
Sister now you can say that
Kind of
The didn't
The dollar still hold value
So they're really right
Misunderstood that the reason the collapse
Who's coming with because
Episode
Is stuff about how
Racism
Paul Joseph Watson
This is where he does his horrible parody character
Mangina
Paul Joseph Watson makes the argument
Clinton's running on feminist lies
All this s***
And all that stuff is kind of kind of stuff we touch down in past episodes
Earlier I did say
Truck
He is from Britain
I hope it gets
Hit by a lorry
Now we can move on or any of our listeners
Does we make Corrections amarok
Episode
He's really mad that people want to take down
Confederate flag
Or is he called it the Battle Flag
If you're calling it The battleflag you're just
Define why we wanted to be taken down
So he put an article that he brings up and
South Carolina Governor Nikki Haley
Who is now the Ambassador
I was one of the people
To say these were
Very weird
The Confederate flag out of the State Building
And so we end the show
With
Would she think
Is
On the reality of War
From Texas
Oh dammit
It was about who
Enjoy Western
On Southern
Southern president
SuperShuttle South had slaves
They were slaves transferred got here to pay for the layover
To explain Civil War
On their way over here and who were treated the worst
As well
Man the hammer drill rap
That's the point in the US Military
He didn't support slavery
Bulshit
Dress up in Gray uniforms at home
I don't dress up in blue uniforms at home
Quite frankly
Southern Civil War
Wait what
Pretty f*****-up
What are you supposed to been right there rednecks in the know the lo-down to me
I don't like that
I don't believe that's true
What would you be in the know about
That would cause YouTube
To Alex Jones
But no idea
Look
The plight of the app
Bright
Now admit it
I don't want to talk about
But
We killed em
Why don't why don't you don't dress up Grace
So a couple fun facts resolution of
Profession
From various States
If you go read the documents with their secession convention
Slavery or white
Supremacy in Mississippi
Slave or slavery
Attempt
Throughout the document never once mentioned the word tax or Terror
South Carolina's mention
Enslave 18 time
What's the fare
It's talking about
This argument little looking into this has nothing to do with
Actually it's it's pretty interesting history how everyone has
Two sides of issues
Interesting article by guy named Mark William Palin
Is a professor of history at the University of
It was breaking down visterra Fargo
Was explaining is the argument about parrot leading to the Civil War
Is based on a misunderstanding about the situation that existed
During the 1832 nullification
In crisis
That's
Got
Misunderstanding
With the 1860 1861
Secession of Southern States
That's basically what people 20 years off
They can fight those two things
So in 1860 the moral Tariff was passed
But
This is very interest
Precisely because southern states began seceding from December 1860 onwards
A number of Southern Senators had resigned
The could otherwise have voted against the terrorists
Have not resigned they would have had enough votes in the Senate
Congressional Passage
Because they
They didn't have a boat anymore
So this came before this moral tariff
Now what's interesting
Is the Confederacy wanted the British people
Recognized
Confederacy as a Sovereign Nation
Yes so what they did
Is they started to make the argument
Bit because of
The almost immediate
They what made the argument to the British
When that could not have possibly been the case
The closeness and time they created a ton of
Confusion
A group of people who hit seceded from the country over slavery
Considering the fact that they already abolish slavery
10:15
Beforehand
And so they basically
Pretended that
Sure sure
Pro Southern business interests
Internal it's not slavery
The better to win over people who might be appalled
The forces of abolition
On March 12th 1861
Just 10 days after the Morrill tariff
Become law
Editorial voice to the terrorist why
The newspaper pronounce that quote
Protection was quite as much a Cause
The disruption of the Union is slavery
And remarked upon how the moral tariff had quote much
Change the tone of public feeling in favor of this
Plies work
Milgard involved and started writing essays about houses
What they're saying
And had been
It's all about slavery
Hey
Who care
Who cares if it's
Who cares if it's 60/40
Slavery
Recite because of slavery there still f****** place
Being beholden
And being beholden to this narrative
Really indicates either he hasn't researched it as much as he think
Or he's been researching really dicey sources
He's inclined to just
The
Slavery apologist arkema
Commenting
Like I remember being in school
Small dump
Town with people pulling that Narrative of like
It was slavery but also say
Like they were telling that lie like they were his like that
Was
That was the same thing
Traverse City
Like teaching other surgery
Creative
Intelligent design or whatever dumb lies there
Some believe that
And we're not going
You can invent your own truth
Well
Starting to self on the show Independence
People
Confederate
Melts
Boggles my mind
Still don't
Put together like
He specifically
We pointed it out
Only 2% had
Slaves
Do you see what a big
Half
All of the wealth concentrated within a very small number of people
Can create the top 1%
Leedstone in humans eating
Free market
Flea market in everyone's up in that exact situation that were in
I mean if you want to look at
Stream is a free market there were people who sold themselves into
The slavery for black
Ain't back in Greece
Cuz that's one of things I studied about
Austin College
One of the big
Problems that led to almost
Premature collapse of Greece
Was the people sold themselves into slavery
They don't because they were so destitute
Sell themselves
And it got to a point where
That the government
Having to be like
Nah
Buck
There
You guys are all free
And that's what the North had to do
I mean we did actually
Save the United States
By getting rid of slavery
Alex's
An idiot
Through things
That are like
Glosses over
There's one at the end where he's like
A black person
How did the cotton gin
Who cares
I mean that's a good
That's probably true
I understand that the South
Sneaker
The South was bamboozled
The South was shut up
They were flipped the north was a victim received well
Did the South fight
Did the South win the first 23 years against the North
They absolutely dominated
The children of
Trautwein
That fart
On the side of the child I wonder why
The history you're given
Is not the real history that was going on slavery was a horrible Institution
Counties in Alabama
What was that
What
WhatsApp
But the weather
The North
The park
Start to abolish slavery
We're so proud of her
What is fighting
Sure
I guess
Be like if the
Spartans were the bad guy
The person but that's what 300
Well yeah but do you not remember the Spartans
War they fought against Athens that wound up destroying all I remember
And what if they kill their babies I'm not talk about abortion I'm saying weird had big leave them on a mountain
Good luck
Is that not what abortion is it's not quite remember protesting against an abortion doctor
Here one day and it
Is right next to a mountain
Shut up basically their own
Creole
Agrarian combine
That was going on a lot of people
George Washington Thomas Jefferson
2%
Ireland
Then what the media projection
Is not what's going on
No reflection
In reality
Then the biggest issue
Is that for the Civil War
Followers Sherman's model of reconstruction
By John Wilkes Booth
Northern Industrial
Ocean temperatures on record
And then when I had the boa constrictor
East Coast
222 basically cut off supplies
The British Supply
Watch shows like roots
They show a guy with a web beat the black guy
Slavery was already been phased out
It was
Whitney's cotton gin
Oh that was. Yeah there we go
No I'm sorry I only made slavery
Improve things at all
I need streamline the blow like cotton was dying as an industry slavery perhaps
Dude that was falling out of favor
Even more important is for slaves
It's so stupid
Kills me
When they're talking about
This is day
We all know who they is
Alex about slavery end
And like the
Horrible mistreat
Of slaves
The fact that you own
It's always like
Yes it was a bad
Like always
Xbox designs like why are you
Fury that it should be like the idea that owning slaves
Is just
Situation
Here's what it comes down to for me hold one opinion
So he can't
Really agree
Embody
Slavery was wrong
Sharecroppers had it bad to at the same time
He if he says
It's slavery with really bad
That in some ways invalidates the argument that sharecroppers had it bad
Mortgage did making
Because it offends
White people
Torque makes white victimhood narrative which we know
That was a super long I apologize
But I wanted to demonstrate first of all
That this is the kind of stuff he's wasting his time
Importantly we want
John Wilkes Booth was a false
Everything is offline
Everything
Trump has been running for president now for
What would it be
6 days
An eternity
And making a comment
About the Mexican
You still not mention him at all
Still not mention Trump
Barely mentioned the election
I'll wash it out of her mouth with a nice out-of-context drop
I'm so moral
It's disgusting
Alright Alex Gonzaga call baby
I love that
So bizarre
What is
What if
What are you
Talking about very weird
I don't even remember what contacts
What could
There's nothing more to say
He's so moral it is
Disgusting
Remove on illustrating perhaps
The great paradox
True morality
Once you reach a certain point
Evil USB
Is
Tuesday we're on a Tuesday show now
On that day is that they were talking about
TPP
Talk about giving Obama
The fast-track authority
Partnership
Evil nefarious thing
People don't ever take into account when
Bremen
What is that
Literally every president
Since Gerald Ford
With the exception of Bill Klein
Has been granted Fast Track
Yeah
Basically
Is there a notary normal Obama
Not share with them
Well I mean Bill Clinton didn't get it
Song
Obama
What leads up to
But to get this fast track
Sounds like something that's weird
Disgusting
Supernormal
If something happens with every president
I think one of the big reasons
Didn't get it
Was because of the Larry Nichols types
And all the propaganda
Any quotes
Conspiracy
That unfortunately is real
The Hillary complains about
It is very much
Citra seems like it will be making an appearance
On this episode here on the 23rd
Arvest Tuesday show
Because Alex Jones
Still bent out of shape about the TPP
He plays a couple of really long video
At one of them
Is Senator
On the
Giving a speech about how the
The partnership takes away the song
Of the country and the Congress
And this
Is the first instance
Of Alex
Being super complementary
Trump's cabinet
Part of Trumps campaign
Still not talked about Trump at all
So here Alex I said
I'll allow the
The powers of the United States
I don't want interrupt
Kimora
This is one of the main leaders
But
Starting to get a sense of Alex's political Hedgehog
Rand Paul is
Someone he always talks about Ron Paul comes on
Is Showbox
Partnership
Most likely
That's a big part
Is so
Because Alex Pacific partnership
As the final step
2 globalist
Enslavement
Our country eventually will the Asian Union and European Union
Trans-pacific partnership they're all going to be merged together
All right so that's basically where he's at
Barcodes
Total episodes
Months
Let's just put it this way
He probably believe the Civil War was about Tara
You almost certainly believe that
Either that
Never learned that
Keebler Elf
Yeah
That's a large part of this episode
He wants to talk about that
About it other than his
Beers
Narrative
He does explain that because of
And all these unions merge
The UN is going to take over Israel but Muslims will still be killing Christians all over the place
Transitions
Smoothly into him selling his gallbladder cleanse
Product
I wish it was a damn good
Splinter gallbladder I don't understand how
What
A gallbladder
Would be cleansed out
There's a plastic you end up taking in because of
Shut the globalist to put in your food
I may all collect in the gallbladder
So you take a bunch of his medicine
Is a supplement
And then you drink like rice wine vinegar or something like that apple cider vinegar
And then on the sixth day of the clamps you drink like a glass
Of olive oil
For a couple hours
Emma
He's not specific but I think he said you just s*** forever
It's got a clip of what one of the grossest things ever find the product
What other result of all of that
Could you tell me what apple cider vinegar for 6 days and a big old glass full of olive oil
Careers for 6 weeks
Now you pass a bunch
Plastic
Through your butt
Which is
No
The PowerPoint this episode we get a return visit for my old friend
Find Larry Nichols
Yes
On the last episode that he was on
He came on
And I believe
Kicked off Alex's lamp
Which was laying dormant
Idiot
His career
Is respected by Alex
Alex what you need to do. You're the only one who can save us
He articulated it I think
Is the route
About
Journey
So he comes back on in this episode
He's mostly just talking about a lot of murders
The clintons have committed
Talks about some guy who
I'll cut off his hands on his legs
Decapitated himself
I found no evidence
But this is a real thing that happened
But
What he really wants to talk about is
We need to build an army
He's enlisting Alex
His followers
Just stop
That's exactly what we need
I love it when people say let's turn into an arm
That has no negative connotation
Listen to it whatsoever
Describe
I'm here to give you a character
It's up to your audience
Play for me and Theo
He says there's 25
So you got to know who they are if you're going to stop them
Murders in also plays the last episode
So he talks about Hillary Clinton went to which church with the lady from Lee Vining women
I meant he drops this one on
Remember the time to show you what kind of woman this was
Two Secret Service agents in the White House
Gallery in bed
Court Bond
People
We call the clintons
Hillary f**** for Markie Post yes you played at the public defender
No Hillary if I had known this
Hillary
Markie Post
So you pulled up a chair and Hillary didn't like that he was watching
So he started throwing lights
That
The problem is
Pretty true
Also sounds like in terms of like
Like this is after House of Cards was 2015
Larry Nichols obsession with people from sitcoms super cool
Also like
He's going to do is come back every week
And have a standalone
Wreck-It Ralph
Except this
Designing Women which church
Is the scandals that you starting with x
Dude you got to do better cuz I don't care if
I'm pissed off you didn't invite me check Taylor
I don't care if she had sex with Markie Post she's a beautiful woman
And
I don't care pilkinton watched and I don't care if she threw an ashtray well here's the one thing that you don't know yet
Write the Scandal app
Hillary Clinton
Both
Telling bad jokes
Long panel wiring
Also she f*****
When she's like Telly Savalas
Put a lollipop
Alright
Buckethead
That's what Larry Nichols wants
I think the most important piece of it do
Cummins
You got me
Biking
Contribution
I think the most important part is that he's trying to enlist Alex's audience manipulative
Because he knows the millions of people listening
He's like
Just trying to
Get his agenda through and you nosey
The other stuff is just really funny
Really funny
Jump
2 Wednesday the 24th
If this
Is where I belong
Everything
The 24th
4th ID 2015
I have reason to believe
That this is where Alex
Began to lose his
Now
Have you ever read the case of
Charles Dexter Ward
HP Lovecraft
So
Part of it is
Does a running
Trend throughout it of
There's a guy named Charles Dexter Ward who at some point absolutely lost
Does mine different psychiatrist
They have like
Thought it was
AutoZone
He was later
I'm all of those psychiatrist it comes to Alex
Cuz I swear I think he lost his mind
This one is big
I'll just play the putting a lot more chips on this one
Well
There's two things that happened on this episode that I think are
Here's the first one
I just want you to take this
The future
You can say scientifically
Basically
Oh my God
And whether it was a dream or real
Weather app
It doesn't matter because
Without a shadow of a doubt
Whether it was at 9
Incredible
Movie
Smell-o-vision
How much would you pay for
From the brink of Destruction
So
Alex Jones
How to dream
Messiah
He had a prophetic dream
That's what he's
Sour cream
No no no
But
This legitimate
Is
Crazy
In my life
Just lucid dreaming for a little while
GameStop Mastery over the Dreamscape
What have you
When you apply
Concrete meaning to dream
A lot of the time you're really messing
You're doing something really bad
And I can think of no pasta
Historical
0 times where a man has said
Listen
The future
Do what I say
Yeah that's usually very verifiable thing
Really get to Indy
About the dream itself
Except to say that it was the next 20 years what the globalists are going
Follow the exact
Almost as if
He is a crazy person
Who is fixated
On this bizarre
False reality
That it has invaded
You know his nightmares obviously this thing that he thinks about all the time
So
That's not all
Like mine are just about
Slowly burning
Just money
Mariana
6 hours
6 hour
I was set Ablaze
Was it Hillary Clinton
There's only one
Naruto
Has not done
Talk about this
Everybody loves it when you help me
Absolutely horrible
Through their eyes
Adorable
Horrible
The future is going to be just hell on Earth people
Emma churches won't warn anybody
I have this dream that everything's going to be living here
Please give me money
Meanwhile making fun of the Prosperity Gospel
And the Prosperity Gospel people are f******
So I think that's perfect
To mock them
Like hey hey hey
Look at these idiots over here don't give them your
I thought you're going to make the argument that the asking for money with parody
Oh no
He would have to understand
That's true
To Alex's
I'm going to talk about the dream and then do a pitch for money
That he started to internalized the Savior myth
That Larry Nichols has brought to the show
Because that already
It exacerbates already had under the surface
But you probably wasn't able to really come out with them because
Even he knows that would be grandiose
How people be like
Nichols has brought it to him
It gives him much in the same way
Reverend Childress Racing the Charleston was fake
To say it's fake
Larry Nichols
Being like you are safe here
I believe
Are you making the ark
You meant that this
Is when his delusion
Out
Or are you making the argument
When he gives in
I think more the ladder
I think
The moments
At least where his mind
Becomes like
There is something
Talkin to me
Like these dreams
He described it as a vision of the next
20 years
And he's the only one
With your mother
Right
And you're going to need
If there's one thing I know about apakah
Uniden
10 more reporters
Exactly
The first thing that's super important
The other thing is the introduction of a new character in
The pantheon
Of Infowars
Not rainbows
She's just
All the characters who played big roles now aren't around
The Rodger Stone
He's not on any of these episodes
Almost every episode
Right
Necessarily usually just doing three hours
If you have to get
Some topics stuff like that
So a lot
Star cast of rotating
Rip David
Lee Ann McAdoo Jakari Jackson
Surround
Right
So far I've seen
No evidence of Rappaport existing back then
Although I'll keep you posted
I'm sure you still alive
Flipped into existence in 2016
He pulled him from
The first instance
That I can
Confine
But I may be wrong
But I know that it's the first time she has ever been on
And I believe it's the first time he's had a guest from Rebel me
Oh okay
Mike cernovich and rebel media at this point
Very low-key don't know what he's doing at this point probably
He's not he's not on his radar
Jack pasovic isn't a player at this point he's not even on the anyone's radar
Isn't
If he's involved but he's not on Alex's radar
He hasn't popped up on
Any shows
But
Alex does on the 24th
Lejeune have someone from Rebel media
On
As a guest
Alright
At this point she was a college
If you have a YouTube channel
And reports
Episode
She had just put out a video
That was making fun of the Walk
I'm assuming that she's doing it in a very sex-positive way and saying that there is no reason for women to be
Ashamed after they have
Wonderful night with somebody that they care about you
You might have the wrong angle on this
She's making fun of them for having sex in
Well if she turns it all ice
She turns it into a rape thing
And to be fair some of it was
Summerville
The protest was about
Oh absolutely
That is prevalent across many
Like a baler bulshit
I'm on board the Starship sex positivity to it and
So she goes out and it's all
I'm going to play 2 clip
From
When they play her report
They play a bit of
And I want to make you really mad
I need to hear Alex
I doubt it'll
I need you
Going to be right in my wheelhouse
I'm going to agree with her
I need you and the audience
To hear Alex
Mumbling in the background
While the video player
Because
It
Real it's worse than the report itself
You're the first one
This is
Voice will come in for a second
And then a lady on the street
We'll start to Sotto
Confront her about her position
I would describe this as Lauren not being good
Not thinking fast
Is it stopping rapes
When Dory
Police
Percent
Ask for help they seek medical attention
She thinks
Like the reporting to a women's clinic
Call recording
She's really moving goalposts around and then when Lauren is asked
She stammers through a couple numbers
Alex
Right now listening to this going
Lauren isn't doing the job
She's a woman
Listening to women talk to each other and he's not like that at all nothing and I was going
To each other that what
Yeah even if
Also you get the same
Even though he thinks that she's not doing the right job or doing it hard enough
Alright
I like what she's putting down
She's on the right
Side of it
Anti-feminist
The woman
Yeah that's why that's
Right there
Text pretty handle
Keep posting these Mark Dice videos where it doesn't show what
He thinks it shows
She posted on the rebel inside
Like know if you listen to what they're actually saying
No cheese
And you're like
Think about it is that she comes away from
Making that that was a win for
Like
The woman she's talking to very clearly goes away with that
Thinking I'm never going to get through
Somehow the people who know what's going on
Reflect reality
Who can see the issues
Losing
Whenever they're arguing with Liars
With people are just
Elderly and
Completely willing to
To obfuscate
Misunderstand
And then
Lie about the results
The world now
There's a really funny clip that I didn't cut out because it gets murky
By Alex
But there's one point in her to not use someone else
Haha
This person doesn't want you to use their footage can you take it out
She doesn't consent
Do you using footage
I bet you're not respecting her consent
Dislike
Like it's a sketch
So
So bizarre
But I so the next one
Is Lauren starts
At the March
A Judaism
A dude is talking
Is he is he
Dudeism
Coming on the show
Alex's
It's just a total b*******
Yeah
We don't break it
Golaurens
Lawrence
Rebel media bonafide
Canada
How did she get hooked up with Rebel media
I believe they found her
Goodwill jobs
I understand
I would have just cut this out and been like this isn't really relevant to The Narrative of
The Trump
Investigation that I'm on
But I believe it's relevant
Because this
I think
Is the point where Rebel media becomes
A factor in the Infowars verse
In the world of Alex Jones
He starts getting
Bespoke
Which leads
Him to bring in Gavin McGinnis of The Proud boys
Picture because of them
Are all of these
Disparate parts
They're coming together
Yeah I believe so and as best I can tell this is sort of the route of the year on June 24th
The day of Alex's vision
So that's
Really f*****
After this Alex leaves
The studio and ghost
The Buckley is winning
So he's gone from the 25th to the 28th
He is so I've no idea what happened
I don't care
On the 29th comes back and
Listen to that episode
There's one thing that we didn't talk about on that episode as much as I would have liked
Interview with a guy and they talk
The globalists are to blame for the destabilization of Ukraine
Sanctions
So much like
Went out started kissing his ass
The Russian sanctions part wasn't part of Trumps at that point
Yeah Alex
Cuz clearly already
Yeah
So
Alex Jones
Russia Annex
Crimea
Came before Trump
I don't think that he thinks that Russia is totally innocent
He thinks that it's the globalist fault and Russia's just trying to help out the people of Ukraine
And beyond that the UN forces
At the door
Is what he's more concerned about
Like without
Hearing it
I I just see him being like
But now that it's
Like if if he's seeing that as a
An opera
Opportunity for the
The UN to grab more power
Then now I can
See why he would take
Take that
More organically
Yeah it does the worldview of little bit
Because of the involvement of the UN
Because his imagined influence
The globalist
Yeah but at the same time it is
Pro-russia
Yeah which is very
I don't know
I don't have a whole lot of context but I hope to discover it as we move forward to the investigation
So now we get to June 30th
Studio
This episode
Is
A disaster
Alex
You know he's been on his vacation
He's still getting back into the groove
He does about a
40 minutes
With his cousin Buckley's wife
This is probably before he got remarried
When they first started yeah this is when the divorce
He doesn't 40-minute ads for brain Force
Yet with gucciardi
Who is a writer for Infowars and apparently some
Naturopathic
Of sorts
I don't know
Congealing from
Penicillin
Somebody's Baby
I don't think Anthony gucciardi still around
Episode
No. Not with the fold
And
He is
Incredibly silent
For a large
Part of the time he's on screen
Much like your car has regular
He knows with them
The fuk up
So long
It's
The Sunday show
40 minutes
I believe that's a Sunday
Fiore
Commercial
Tell this story
I believe he's trying to build
Credibility about himself
But I don't believe it
Eva
Not really but also
He does not get to these new
Dangerous
Terrifying
I can't believe he has rights to play Beatles
No
The ghost of Michael Jackson would never allow this
Exaggerating
Just overwhelmed then break your will show your level hasn't broken my will
But I just already know all this is coming
Opposed
And that's why they tell you what they're going to do
It's because humans are designed to adapt evolve overcome
Slavery
Do I say that all the time because it's very high-level globalist
Sickeningly
On a 3-hour flight to New York first class
What happened the other two hours
To it
Conversation that must
I am
His suit look perfect
I wouldn't even know how to look like that
And that he could just arrogantly laugh at me when I walked off the plane
Oh yeah you really talk to this person
There's a whole nother world out there
When you're a journalist
People know you live not breaking confidences
So you live in
Play
Do you live in Thai
So again our theory about Everytime You Lie to get some of the details all the details
That opens up
I'm not giving up confidential sources
The him giving away
Prescott system operation
But he literally says the people open up to you would rather
You having somebody
Seriously listen to what
Is about to say
That the
And I'll go
You're going to fail
It's like my head
15 years ago
Going from memory
Almost
Cuz I got a heartbreak
The guy said this is off the Record right
The he's just telling people that literally a demonstration of
Him not being
Clearly made of that was obviously
Here's what
The guy found out he wasn't from The New York Times he found out he was from Infowars instead
Cuz I'm
Uwell
We better get steroids
Hallmark
So they come back from break
Talks to the board operator
He's like
Hey you were here. Happened
You heard him say that just like you said
Cabela's also says
Look at the end there he said that you said this is off the Record
To make it like
Was that the name that's Alicia
The show goes on a little while
Interview with a lady
Actually let's talk
The whole bunch fairly reasonable and gives a lot of reasons
Alex doesn't talk at all and she's crazy
This is right before
The maximum amount of time they can
Can handle reasonability
I think Alex is getting his brain fourth notes in order while she was talking
Entire product plug for
And Anthony gucciardi is sitting there silently
Through this entire clip I'm about to play for you
That is
Bonkers
But I want to be clear
Alex thinks
Play into Anthony
East Hawkins
And Anthony's just going
Making no noise is just nodding his head like
Like that cuz they've only got one camera
Right there on the go
No I mean like there's a there only shooting the direct
Alex Jones
No there's multiple angles
The live feed
From one of the one
F*** what Alex is doing just stare at them throughout this whole this whole eyebrows go up and down
Just try and get inside the mine somebody Bliss
Yeah this is how he intros what is going to be a 40 minute ad for brain
Charlton Heston
Promo about becoming reality
Overton
But that's known by inside baseball
10 million dollars
The Second Amendment
He wasn't paid.
Closest money
Rolling out on TV
Basically his whole Fortune
Second Amendment
I feel like
Clint Eastwood in Charlton Heston are very similar
David gold tells are great
Spoiler alert
It was Earth the whole time he traveled through time
Everybody
Is racist
Margaret Sanger
And stuff like that
Because the
Yes so here is something from the NRA's website about Trump
There's a little bit of a biography
Control
Appearing on the ABCs
The bishop
This bill is no mystery
Let's be clear about it
Its purpose is simple and direct
It's not to deprive the Sportsman of his hunting gun
The Marksman of a Target gun
Irresponsible his constitutional right to own a firearm
It is to prevent the murder of Americans
Hesston opposed the Vietnam War and considered running for the US Senate as a Democrat
Affiliation
With his endorsement of a Republican
Ronald Reagan for
Delivering a fiery speech at the free Congress Foundation
Society persecuted
A year later he was elected the president of the NRA
So it looks like maybe he lost his mind around 1990s
That's not an uncommon
Trajectory
Like that
That's what happened
When do that
Entire generation like Fox News loving
Progenitors
Wind-up
Having that very
20 years ago my dad was
And a vicious
Obama's
Birth certificate
Until
Rodger Ailes and Rupert Murdoch
Droid the world Google
It will literally
Add
He doesn't care about Caitlyn Jenner
I don't care about the argument
It's about how
Some cop beat up a guy
That's. Right
That's it
He said that position with him supporting Arpaio and sporting Sheriff Clarke
It's like I agree with
The point but you're not logically consistent
Your question
You're thrilled the page
Text dropped Glendora
By MSNBC
So now
The month
We call them racist
With proof that's where
So with hours upon hours of listen
Yeah now June is over
June Gloom
The words of July
July 1st rolls around
And David Knight
Fox
I don't care
There might be I don't care
I could
They actually are a
Perfect news Outlet Deluxe Alex isn't there like we just have no idea
And your notice
Listen to like it is David Knight toasting all the time
Whatever he's gone because
People like Owen Shroyer
Millie Weaver is not around
From everything I've listened to so far so
There's not all that much of a mystery
So mysteriously absent gives
Like he's on he's on a Vision Quest 2
Yeah
Distilling withdrawals from Super male Vitality cuz his life.
Do dick too hard
So on this
July 2nd episode most of the narrative that he's pushing is about
How I
The
Juneau Airport
Basically are requiring people
I have a federal ID
Travel exist
Is the market
Oh well
Totally on board
No
Because he he believes
It's the federal ID
Do federal ID or still like an Illinois driver's license
Like a federal piece
States that
With the federal government
The mark of the beast
Mo ID laws for voting
So complicated
Look up
So in the first
What blind spots do
Pretty man like I'd like that
Like that
Like he has an ideology
Completely and utterly
Choosing what he's beholding to like do you like one thing that I think about alot
I'll just because
Is all natural
Like
I listen to that and I think
I am not
Some sort of
Superhuman
I hope that I have my own blind spot
Like that
What what are they
Like I'm trying to find someplace where I would not apply
Play My Philosophy
Those questions meme that
You'll figure it out
I'm incorrect
Yeah I think
You and I
Sea life especially
Philosophies and
Political beliefs
A sort of works
In progress
Start
In that circumstance
There are unalienable principles
Human dignity human rights
To constantly be
Shifting
Economic realities shifting political realities
Like you would be nearly as radical as you feel right now
Does motivate
Absolutely
It also
Those inconsistencies are those blind spots are best seen by other
Ratchet is often very difficult on yourself
But like in therapy or with your friends
Are the places
You can best
Define hosting
A whole lot of people who will
Dude what about that
Yeah even his lawyers bad
You're full of s*** what are you doing
I don't know
Bore the problem being
Cynthia is on those in a liter
Yeah like that that
You and I
It is bad
Anybody
Gets beat up by the cops
And we're always against
Is only against it
Whenever it is
Let's face it
Like like with our pay on all that's
How do you not apply that
Same
Rich badwan cups
He what he believes to be police not investigating sexual assault
It's done by
Immigrants who have come here
He's super mad about that
But never really stops
Joe Arpaio personally oversaw Department
That just ignored
Sexual assault complaint
And rape complaint
Because people were immigrants
Let's not get back into no but you understand that
F****** Kate
Consistency yeah I don't know I know I know there are blind spots that we have
I don't know if they are you guys
You guys can find any I'm open to hearing
We get to July 2nd
And this is a revolutionary moment
Cuz I'm July 2nd
What would that be
16 days
Donald Trump president
Alex Jones
Finally
Save Donald Trump's name on his show
Is the first
I'll let you see what's
What where you at
Running
Against
Trump and
Is the front-runner by giving them
Magnify
And then he will
And then we'll
Only in America
Fake political
Very reasonable announces that everybody was making at that time basically right more or less
So two things
If there was
Maybe that's the real world works very differently than Alex is fake
F****** narrative
Thought that that was what's going to happen
That's the first time he's meant
Whatever
He also makes this claim with Ron Paul
And he's bringing up Rand Paul
Is also running for president
It must be all your hard work
The only person out of a field of light
Eleven candidates
Call radical
Just because 50 years ago he be called middle-of-the-road he just promoting basics
I hope and pray.
He'll help educate people
The only person who standing up for Americana ideas
He is very much on the ramp
Super into it
So he has Ron Paul
Tiffany is there like
Is there like one moment where you
Switches tracks
This isn't this investigation is ongoing my friend
He gets into a little bit of a sales pitch
I'm just going to play it
I'm a very superstitious person
Superbad
I just love that like
Like I don't
Until the beginning of the show and we've talked about a bit along the way
The big narratives that he's been pushing along with all these sort of mini ones that we've been discussing
Yeah this stupid all these interviews with supposed
Experts like
Paul Craig Roberts
That was more about the Putin
But Peter shift
Max Keiser
He had these people on
I got on his own
And is just making the argument
That f****** the economy is about to collapse
Yeah everything and he does
Specifically the summer
He's talking about maybe the fall
Summer maybe the
We're already into July
So he's basically everything is coming down
He's also talking about gold
July 2nd
He has a little Gaston Studio
And
There will be an infomercial at the end
Modest resources
Sponsor for the show 19
This time slot
Well 17 years
Emerald
Financial meltdown
So
The globalists are headed towards the exit
Stronghold
Search
Anderson owns the Genesis communication Network
Vindicates Alex Jones Show
On all these mystery Affiliates that are apparently leaving
So
He is basically responsible for most of Alex Jones
He also owned
Oil company
I like the way
It started 17 years ago
As a reputable Gold and Silver Company
No longer reputable if you look online
Midas
I don't know enough to say I don't know
Along the way
Through the pass
Couple weeks
He has been saying a bunch
Just talk about how cold is going to be selling for $50,000 an ounce
Yeah he's been talkin about gold a lot
In the context of all this financial collapse stuff you see
A Ted he brings up at Ron Paul
Just was on the show
Right Alex make money if they sell gold
The mighty
It's a wonder One
You can't do this
He's fear-mongering
Greenlawn
And don't go am saying we're going to play an infomercial
What's the most unethical thing ever
Basically he just talks about how gold is
Skyrocket
This is Alex
Stomach nausea
What time
Set
Respectful
When it starts racing up I believe it will
And
If they can continue to suppress it I'll be surprised but regardless
So his argument is that the globalists are suppressing gold prices
Because they want to buy it all up and then
Paintball
You're an idiot
Yeah
Gold prices
Grown-up really
Substantially at all
It's right around there like $1,213 an ounce
Which still bananas for whatever
Quite a while and not really gone up or down
That could really make any money
With the amount than Alex Jones listen to cook by
Right
It's f****** stupid at all it does is sell Ted Anderson School
This is one of the most unethical things
I've ever seen
Because legitimately
Weeks leading up to this
He's spelling out this
Shift
The content of his show is leading up to this interview at 10 a.m.
He knows this interview is coming
That's The Prestige
The revelation
All of the other stuff is
And get them into a state of mind
Weather like
What
Talkin about
All of the stuff does predate him bringing this guy in he's bring this guy in to help us
Was actually a tooth
Yes
This entire thing was just one buildup
The Narrative I believe so
And then
At the end
He pulls out the
And here's the guys going to tell you all this gold is going to help you
A hundred percent
Deliver the solution to
Shifted off the Charleston narrative
Which is an out of character for him mr. collapses still within his
He shipped
Immediately
With predictions of the summer
Consistent
And it's so focused around goal
Yeah
That it
No way
Do you think he got a direct
Yeah
So in his bosses saying like I stole some more gold
Probably
For sure
Conspiratorial
Information that is is
No I mean
They need to sell more s***
Yeah they go to their advertising guys and say put together
Yeah
Put
F****** cows up on a bill
Alex Jones is the cows on a billboard for gold
What is 4 - 3
Which is what makes them different
Qualify
You're in ethical broadcaster
Even if
Your parent company owns
A gold Consortium
Or whatever
You it's your responsibility
Do whenever you bring up gold issues
That what our company is also owned by
Whenever you're talkin about these collapse narrative
Conflict event
Person wants to come on
You have to tell him you can't use my platform
And like
Go to if you go to a website and used
Sponsored
Content you have to
Hugo
This paper
You see they put it
As its sponsor
Yeah like it's not every time
You should bring up stitches
Sponsored content
So f****** evil
Same s*** that people do on in
Instagram like their models and
Just have products
In the background they make
Like it
Insidious advert
So f***** up
Prophetic dream was one of the ocean
For me
Terms of this investigation
Write this was another
It turns out that that prophetic
Dream was a
Email
Latite was about three lines long 6 hours to read in that email was
Goddamnit we need to sell some of your f****** off easy
Before bed
So
Warriors
Episode Alex Jones
Has another interview with Jesse Ventura
Brent comes back on in lies exactly the same way
Total
And this time
They take it a step
Further
In this in this time when he's on
Jesse's
Appeal of the cases
He thinks
Is it Hillary nose
Right
Jeb Bush is a wenis
That's his angle
Great but he probably
Couldn't win
You still whole hog in the rampart
Yeah
He's crying
Hard
To get Jesse to run
So he's not
Like I'd like I said
Yeah but he's not on
At all
16 m
16 days after
The Mexicans are rapists
Not on
It wasn't until the ground by the
That
Alex was like finally
Someone I can relate
No I don't know
Treats women as objects
Guarantee
He talked a lot of s*** about Billy bush
I'm sure he can't wait to get to that
Yeah I think one that's already
Full hog
Yeah
July 3rd
Is f****** hilarious
And we're not going to play it cuz I'm sick of playing Mark Dice Clips on the Shelf
On the previous day on the second video where he was going around asking people if they knew
On the 4th of July
Independence
From whom
I had a lot of them didn't know
Did he stay home
Correcting myself
Play that video on the 2nd
I've been on the 3rd
Alex plans Joe Biggs out to do the same B in Austin
Well goes great
Man on the street is so bad
It's not funny and it doesn't make a point
They do that
I'm playing this clip
Cuz it's the reverse of it sort of
This clip
Is Alex talking about what happens whenever he goes to
Like abortion rally
And stuff like that
I'm going to play the clip
I'm done
Explain what happened
After the clip
The Clippers hilarious
The truth is funny
Before Ma
Abortion clinic
Spontaneously
Crowded women in circle depression cement
Eurasian people always show up going I love Satan I want to kill people I want to kill black people
Eagle Raceway
Mckellips and Oliver UPS
We lost to this
4th of July
Declaration of Independence
Who's against satanists
Here's the first
Here's the thing
On a different episode
Remember which one it was
Play the video of it
Oh really people where's that but not the same way
The same way that we talk about this
People wanting to put up satanic things at State Building
You have your religion here we're just going to talk with you
Deer laugh
Reality
He hears them is like
Obviously they mean
Obviously they are real satanists
But that's
That does that does make
His world
Then so many other things
Then become
Wolf Lake
Every time
Because of how stupid
Globalist on the plane
Someone making conversation with him and then laughing at it
Also I will take
Insider information from colors and random people that he meets become parts of his narrative
Took
No ability to know what is real and what is not
And this clip
Completely demonstrates
And the way he integrate these people trolling him at an abortion rally he is
They're part of the
Satanic
Thing that worships abortion that's what Liberals are and that's fully informed
About liberals
It's crazy
How
What is it
She is
On that does iodine
Don't take his supplements
Pretty much not at all
Unbelief is a very important
Piece of my investigation
I think it does
Appreciate
Of what ends up
Getting him down the Trump
But I think there's
More to the story
Whenever it may be
Lexus plugin
And cut it open
Because on the last show he opened the floodgates talking about Donald Trump
Now
Alex
Has a couple things he wants
To say about Donald
The first one
That's what is
But
He doesn't just
Thank you
Does he have a high-level source that is
Confirm in this next clip
He implies knowledge of something about Donald Trump
This clip
Made me
Gas
At work when I was listening I was researching this episode
I guess
And then I had to walk around the room
And go outside and smoke a cigarette
I was freaked out when I heard this next
Like you saw three Muslim woman in the pool show
University
Palisades houses 4013
Is this Donald Trump
For some
And
They go in there
This is mind-blowing I don't know what to say anymore
Wow
So you know what he saying
That's mob
Consortium is on the East Coast
Does Bob
All this stuff that people are now
You know coming out in real research
Is that
Donald Trump
Alex knew about
That stuff
In 2015
Before he ever got on board
When he thought he was just there for publicity
Alex Jones
He knows something
I don't know exactly what he knows but the way he phrased that
So the problem with that is it does have the same ring of a lot of the lies that he told about
He thinks Donald the globalist
Perfectly within his
Worldview to be like
What just the same way
Jason Momoa
Demons
Either whatever
More specific stuff about Hillary
Donald Trump is nothing not rich
Yeah he's a front for some Consortium is on the East Coast
He's a piece of work
I don't even know what to
I know it does
It does match some of his life
Here's why I still think it's relevant even if
You're holding back
The reason is
Whenever
Whatever he does the
I'm not going to get into it
A lot of the time
He's not lying out of whole cloth
But he's going off of
Maybe rumor
Rat you going off of
Insinuation
Horse some piece of information that maybe he can't backup entirely
Something that he's heard
He knows to be true
Brianna reported
I think that this falls into that
No no matter what
Unity making something up
The thing that he's making up
Should preclude him from ever signing up
You would think
I don't know
Your you're
Your point is
Completely Valley
Here is my ticket
So far
From
What it is
We talked about
And how that leads
Based on
Can absolutely see
I can absolutely see
Headphone
Anderson
Meet like it work
Pretty pretty song
That we can
Can assume that
Master narrative
Was
Built to sell
One big a
Right so if we're seeing this at Alex Jones now
Then I can
Can absolutely
That
Send images
We are on the Trump
We're fans of trump
I don't I don't know
My application is ongoing
My conspiracy
These some of the enthusiasm
In your eyes diminished a little bit because you didn't see me explode
No
But
I'm just not willing to go that far yet I'm not willing to say that
Alex
I think that's absurd
I know that he's a liar
I'm at the premise of our show
But I am going to believe
It's not even that I believe
I'm putting myself into
Alex's hat
And for him to stay that uniquely our place
Nose
Necessarily
I'm saying he knows what he thinks he knows
And what do you think he knows
Is it Trump is the frontman for Consortium on the east
Coast
That is what he thinks he knows
Right
What is actually real
Who knows
Volume
And the fact that Alex says
Trump is a
Videos not wealthy at all
That to me is
Something this week
Define the fine line that you're ignoring I think
Is the times that he lies
About these things that you know
He believes those things that he's lying
Like
Okay what are you secret sources
They give him information instead
He thinks he has real information
If that's more important to my investigation
Then what the truth
Necessarily
I'm interested in why he changed
And write in order to know why he changed we have to know what the Baseline
We have a start point which is that he thinks Trump is global
Before that
With this Trump situation
His his
Very first.
He hasn't said that
No but he said that he's being set up
With
Jeb Bush
He's doing a job
Proclamation
He's he's not necessarily saying that Trump is
One of them or anything like that
He's freezing it the way he's freezing it
I'm very comfortable saying
Implying
Is some knowledge of trump
That is pretty comfy
Purple for me
I think
The weather or not he knows
I don't know if I make my point clear
He believes it
True or false
Is that Alex
That Trump is controlled by outside
Sandy's not really
Yes
It's all any TV show
What is
What is what was true
I don't many people
Necessarily
Around this time in 2015
Sing about Trump
I don't think a whole lot of sources
Flows through his Casino
Right mob people
Right which is all stuffy
Yeah
And bear out with the facts of our reality that we know now
It does lend some credence
Maybe Alex was right
Yeah
We are sort of that on July 3rd
Right now the 4th of July happened
He's also Fourth of July there's no show
And we come back on the 5th
Everybody's had some nice hot dogs
Already celebrated
The independence from country
Buckley's been married again
In the show open
On July 5th
With a johnbowne report
About
The comment
What's the Trump made about Mexican
19 days
So why bring it up now
Yeah it is interest
It is interesting I don't know
So
They get into it
There's a bunch of stuff about Greece
About the crisis in Greece
Most of the episode
It is about
How an immigrant murdered lady on a beach
Stop about that
Covering the Mexican
Can comment
His thing
But
Still
The number of his comment
Can't be squared
With
Like
That deeper reason
Yeah here's the first clip
What about Donald Trump
We did a report
Will get the dog from
What about
So he does support rhetoric
But you don't trust
Because he knows things about him
So that is where is headspace is at
A little bit later
Master
I don't trust Donald Trump
Papa Ella
Pretty much everything Donald Trump shares
Very accurate
The problem is
HomeSmart casinos
Republican votes away
For Hillary
Now what you think
Everyone was so wrong back then even Alex
Jones was wrong back then even Alex
Jones was like this is obvious
Everyone
Including Alex Jones back then
Obvious
We wouldn't live in the world we do now
Yeah but
Obviously
He believes everything the Trump says
Trumpet
Connected
Yeah
Alex
Seems to know that
Denigrates other p
A shady people
Yeah that he doesn't need to talk about
Because everybody knows
But the rhetoric can't be trusted this guy
Memes
Vb3 philosophically agrees
With the stuff
No that can't be enough
Navigation
Off the table
Now
You want to know who else isn't on the Trump bandwagon at this point
Rodger Stone
Paul Joseph Watson
What do you think about Trump
I love you
Run
All the candidates he might not be the number one but he's the most likely to have a chance
Defeating Hillary
Is that Reggie Saddler
Inherently corrupt
Everyone
Shift their position
At some point
Rodger Stone
If I brought it up earlier Rodger Stones not around he's exact
The turning point
That's when it happens
I'm Rodger Stone I don't know
Things start to change
If that
Leads into
I don't think Alex made a choice
You don't think so
I think someone
Maybe some of these mob ties
Discuss
I think someone might have something
On Alex
Now that might think you don't think it's just the opportunity
Just kind of
Using Alex
You like Alex
Very easily
Alex is a dumb
Someone with candy and promises he will get into
Your Russian band is much more likely but I like
To keep the suspense
Of the possibility
12C the only thing there is that
We already have plenty of
The story like
Rodger Stone
Like all of this all of this s*** is more than enough
The fact that it
But like it doesn't need
Trickle-down
Alex
The actual compromise
Stuff to a certain extent is irrelevant to my investigation
Like the Senate investigate
Talking Rodger Stone
Like that's their business
You don't you don't need to go after Alex
U8
It's I mean I mean for the Russian mob ties
Splatter
You don't need to compromise Alex
I don't know
Like I don't think I don't think so I think that Alex Jones
Having a career that's built on being anti
People being corrupt
Even though he's corrupt himself of his gold sales
I think
He were to stuff out
That people were trying to
Just wait him
In a corrupt
Backfire on people trying
You are a few are giving his abilities
Things out
High Praise
Pepperoni
I still hold up illness
Total brain that he's broke
I get that and I agree with you
But for the drama of the factories
Where do we spend our episodes episodes of his investigation
We got at least
Maybe we'll find proof
Compromise
Your version is way more likely
I can see exactly what your
I want to believe
Listen
I'm fine I'm just going okay
Set the timer
Look the reality is you're probably right you dumb
Invariant
Basically basically
Stories
Anderson for the 20 years of indoctrinating
Radicalized
But
It's super important
That he does say
That Trump has established
Right but he doesn't go as far as
That he's a globalist
That is important to me
Layton inasmuch as this investigation is about what happened
His whole
Journey and path with Trump
Like the fact that he's just like
It's not even the globe
8-bit
Cute f****** mobbed-up
Yeah that is weird
That's such a weird angle of attack for him
Conversation
Opportunistically to get
F****** promotion for his show
And he's not even a relevant thing
Here's here's who he's really on board with he says it on there
He makes it very clear
Bucks
Ted Cruz really liking
It's some bad stuff like support
So I mean
Crystal Clear is Rand Paul
Contradiction
With what he ends up doing
Walking out Ted Cruz so hard
He attacked him because Papa Jackson
Something we all say
He goes from this position
I like some
Stop I like bigotry
But I can't trust him because of these things that I know
He goes from
Trump is our savior
And how
Do you make that shift
He goes from not mentioning him for
16 days
After announcing his candidacy
He spends his time for Chick-fil-A
And s*** like it's nonsense for that 16 days
And when he finally starts talkin about Trump
It's with awareness
Dismissal and I don't trust
The journey from there
To where we end up
I think it's going to be one of the most
Bizarre
Things that every Bart
So join us next time
God damn you
Will be back
Monster
Of course of what's going on on the Alex Jones Show
On the background doing all this research
I had another installment shortly
Of the next week
And Alex Jones 2015
And we will see
What I can learn
I agree with you
Probably not as Sensational as I hope
But I have hope
I find something really f***** up
Here's my prediction
It's going to be
Like maybe
Maybe to throw you a bone on
Come on
Rodger Stone holding the stick
Problem
He's going to like
Because Trump
Like I think 8 is promises that were made
Hey
Get on board
Because
We are going to end
If you get some Patron.
He will come on your show and talk about how great you are
I think it's I think it's also Trump never planted
No Trump wanted to like the theory holds that Trump wanted to start Fox News
And that alley
Get a prominent
But even even if
Blackmail
If you don't
Then trumpsc
Going to come after you
I think it's going to come back
To being a money
Even play
Reputable gold and silver lyrics video
Look rich
You're going
Smart to fall for your trip
I don't know
I don't know what would you
What would you do if you were
Formerly reputable golden silver sales
The salesman
What do you tell
Alex
Like how what's your best angle to cells throughout
I honestly think that if you're smart
Senor Ted Anderson you want
Hillary to win
Everybody wanted Hillary to win I don't think it would be wise
If you're trying to scare people
The really support Trump
From the gun manufacturer
I've been selling at an all-time low
Because of course
You're not afraid that Obama
Your guns away
Everyone's best in
Trump to lose
Like
I think if you're a propaganda
Reno
Employees one
In order to sell his goal
He doesn't with a lot of other stuff too like
The all these conspiracy websites
Resources ads on them
If your
Network
Which include some other shows that are not
Nearly as popular
And you were dictating Alex's
Position
I think the smart thing to do
Is there
Look he's not going to win
But you stay on that ramp
Combination
You just make
Hey
Idaho you should have won the nomination
And f*** both of these
Right that's a smart move if you want to keep selling gold
Your smartest move of
Well yeah
Because then if you if you're going against both of
Look Trump
Is Justice Carrie is Hillary
Pinpoint to the picture
Pictures of them together you
You can do that
Angle on it
And that is a
Fear narrative
Your butt if you when you're sad
Risky gamble for propaganda
I think he would have a choice unless there was something else motive
He's built a business
Set up to 2015 with fairies accept
It's boiled
You still like you built an amazing thing
You can't do that if you're an idiot
You can't do that
You can't do that if you don't
Make some decent strategic
Choices
And I don't think he would be dumb enough
The shackle himself
With an inconsistent
Possibly mentally degrading candidate
The president
That he's going to have to
Keep with him yet he knows he's negative
Eddie knows that he can't trust
So I think that there has to be
I know I think they're how dare you
Cliffhanger like this
Cereal with happening now
Jesus Christ
To be fair we did try and get send an email to the cereal people
No response
The cereal
Do you guys want us to be on some sort of a f****** that works we can make some money
Gmail.com
Score fight
Cracked.com
I will have posted
I knew functionality on the web
Built a calendar
The ever-growing
In terms of
With the content that's on
But as it is now
I posted
From the month of June 2015
Each episode on that bass show
And I'm going to keep
Keep updating it
As we go along also building the current
If you just want information
Without listening the 3-hour episode about what was going on on this day
Right going to be information there about Meredith who's pitching
So we can
We all have memories
Fell
Keep banks on it
Exactly gold bag
To give you an idea of the Staggering level of work that Dan is doing
Just
Look at this website it's f******
Banana notebook
It's
Generally I don't do this but
Become a policy walk
Because
F******
This is insane
No
Terrified
Yeah I know so yeah
Please
Please help Dad
I'm about to listen donated
A lot
Let me rephrase that if we have 45 million dollars
Full-time job
Imagine what I could find
Golden Chick
Thank you so much
For those of you who have a policy wonk hours
Turned it off
Anyway you know what
A lot of tragedy in the world
What's up
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color