Airjordan.com
I have great respect for its knowledge by knowledge
Knowledge vype.com
I love you
What's up
Today is actually the form of a riddle
No it's not
You are a junior
If not giving an update on plants in a while
Peppers and I failed on quinoa
Brightspot Jordan
When is my cucumbers
That I'm growing
Begun to flower
Exciting things
I can't say enough
Wild it was
Come in here and look and see like
There's a yellow burst of flowers
The fruits
And here we are in the middle of apartment in Chicago just got a little yellow flower girl
Yeah 42 dude you're probably never going to have children
Wild I spent a long time the other night
Watching videos about the Cucumber
Can't f*** this up now
My shoulders. What needs to be done to make sure
I got the Cucumbers out of that makes
Great everything's going to be fantastic
Utter failure that we've not fully talk about
Flowers
Going great son
Recorded
I will
Memorial was yesterday
Woke up
And
Had like a really terrible feeling in my gut
The memorial
I couldn't remember what time the memorial
Transpose the numbers with a different
Appointment that I had it was I thought was not at 3 a.m. it's 11
So
It was later than it actually is
It was later than I thought it was
Maybe I will crawl
Maybe I heard you wrong
Are you recording this for
Reason
Live well we're going to talk about
A half hour late my dad managed to get them
Push it back so I could be there for the whole thing
Ahold
Not a chance so
It's a bracelet
It's Memorial
Sure
I mean like
American Memorial
But you being late
The audience when I say our hearts
In this trying time that you've been through the last couple weeks
You are able to take a nap
Ridiculous
You know erase their donations
But I can't
But I consider this group of microcosm
That allowed me to
Power through today
Where
Under other circumstances I might have
Thrown my headphones across the room and said
This is a Spirit Bomb situation
Came to you is as power that is what I would like to express
Mark-ass thank you so much
Not related
Next
Antichrist
Christ sold 25
I'm talking about an hour
Text John
Text Timothy Baker
Frank Sheeran
Unfortunately
She is awesome
Donated on elevated
Becca
Heroin
Why you pimp so good
Is freakishly large
How much Michael
Generosity
That when I feel like it
Urania tissues right now
Machine
And there was not a note
And I found out once again
A lot of people is not taking credit falsely for gift
Beck's
I'm not entirely sure Bex
I've known somebody name that way they say it was pronounced like an i
I'm not entirely sure
Amazing care package came right after with
Allsorts news
You are you are
Asura
You can add a space
Crazy
And a drink
There were there were some other items a an elderflower lemonade
Just Justin amazing care package
I got the best gift
I thought I saw a package iPod
Turn My Cry
Call Greg.
From Steven Universe
With all the original
Drawings and character prototypes
And cool interviews with everybody
It's an Incredible Gift
From back today and credible
Apartment
Later on to actually there is no right
I feel like that's the way fireplace
Any of us run across like never know
Listen side this bag is I got the nice selection of bravado hot sauce
You might booby prank trolling me with also
The bravados
Situation Barry I believe it
Yeah complex
The balance is pretty nice though
Burien
Much more challenging Mommy
Kind of like a miso
I don't know what the pepper is hot and also very
Variola Mommy
Yeah
You are like
Carolina Reaper
Garlic is mod
Across-the-board
Know about that
The episode
How are you doing
Big news over this weekend
In Ohio
That was policeman
Husband
Diesel truck video for rest started making the rounds on Friday and immediately started to have some
Responses
Is the bat signal
Well okay I better get a solid
Going on what's going on
God it's the worst he was arrested by Commissioner Gordon
It's f****** Millie Weaver and it's
Nonsensical
Anyway
One thing
Nooworks
So it's best not to take anything at face value
A lot of skepticism
There is a
Required for claims are being made by people like her
Steidl
There's only a suspicious
Additionally
Possible
It's tactically a weird thing to see if you was mine
A couple of important things to give him mine though are they million her husband are white and this is Diamond Ohio
Community in northeastern Ohio
Population
Responsibility
Angela Mia's
It seems like a lot of it seems weird
Probably not proof of anything or fake
Plus the rest itself
Pretty boring
The amp up the drama
Maybe get her tackle
Confirmation
She actually was arrested Sunday and
Go before a judge on Monday
The?
On the day of her arrest August 14th
Through an associate's YouTube channel she released
Expose
Billy purports this to be the most dangerous
Biggest whistleblowing event
Check that you would get arrested and then they would release the documentary
It's so perfect
Money could never buy
It gives the film appearance of authenticity
Create the Whirlwind
The Buzz
Looking at this rationally a couple of General possibilities
The first is that the globalists there whoever had Millie arrested because
They were worried about the documentary that she was making
This seems dumb from their standpoint because she's been talking about this documentary for awhile and any Global is worth their salt would know that a red
Trusting person makes an expose
I only ask
Explanation
Unless
Yeah considering that we do have a recent example of
In Edwards
You wanted to do Millie like they do Edward Snowden for releasing all this information
We would be in a very different
Certainly
I believe the Infowars is actually number of whistleblower types
I don't know
The second possibility is that Millie was arrested because of the documentary
Because something she did in the course of the creation of it
Could be an issue like she stole documents or something and that could be
When more information is available we can reassess this as possibility
The third possibility is this arrest has nothing to do with the documentary
I have no reason to believe that is the case but
I feel that way
Completed prior to the arrest
It was waiting to be released
What could have been done at any time
Millie does not seem all that surprised in the arrest
When the officer is there
Do you not happy about the situation video does not match
She's rainbow snatch
She's the reporter who go confront a face-to-face
It doesn't seem like
Passively accept
If anything in her documentary is to believe
Then she has to know the second she gets in that car
She's going to prison for a long time cuz we're just set up
We'll get two wires you would have to know that towards the end of this
Overalls Infowars reporter wood
Respond to an unexpected arrest about their reporting
Find
Like
If it were if it kind of seems like going through the motions
As as an imp
As a reporter I think what I would go for is a kind of
Resign Mannino
Officer
Can you put out both your piss
Right next to each other
I think I would go is like passive non-compliance
Sing like that
Show me inside
Boomer shirt
While she's getting arrested
As a whole
Or even large
She knew that there was a warrant out for her arrest
I'm just saying
It's weird the documentary was
Completely ready to go
It got posted online almost immediately afterwards
Surprise
There's someone else there to take care of her kids
I don't know it's just like
Like everything just happened organically
Release the documentary
Verbs with representatives from the Portage County Jail
Charges of robbery
Obstructing justice and domestic violence
They were arrested for and the fact that in order for a warrant to be issued
Approved by a grand jury
Really strong suspicion that this arrest
Entirely different from the documentary
Nothing to do with that I don't believe
The domestic violence charge in there's particular
The documentary
We need more information on this informed decision
Yours are f****** Infowars
She doesn't get the benefit of the doubt that she's an Intrepid reporter getting arrested for standing up to
The man I'm going to go to the big no on that one
Basically my feeling on this is balos
It looks like the arrest itself was real but
However it is super super clear that there is an attempt to use the arrest as a promotional tool
This documentary
The messaging is very
The rest was retribution
For making this expose
Is this documentary actually dangerous at all
Anybody arrest someone for me
The documentary art
That can't be a standard it only applies to Alex himself
Obviously this interesting
Galaxy
Talk about it as though
He wore himself arrest
Exactly I decided to watch this for myself
To see what was out there and it was easy enough to find on YouTube
Very easy
Another serious problem
Exactly wow
Another account
Your response does highlight another problem
In the past few months
From YouTube
All the doctors were telling truth about covid-19
People like David Icke
Alex has invested a lot of his energy into promoting the idea that censorship
Control process
Actually accidentally made the inverse argument
If it's the truth
U of L audit Bertinelli said to anything that doesn't get removed is apparently not true
This is a problem because Millie's video still up on YouTube
As of the channel to posted it which is run by one of the two main sources
Globalist went over to arrest Melly documentary
By arresting her and then doing literally
Play nothing to silence stop for being reported
It does seem a little odd
Problem
Sometimes you don't get the negative response you're hoping
Kind of looks like an invitation
Ezekiel's Bi-Rite
So I watch the stupid documentary
Stupid
I was not worried about that
Every single salacious thing that's in the film is just
Accepted as solid proof is one of those guys guy with telescope from Kerry Cassidy telescope
Motorcycle for Trump
Work when you start to ask yourself
Who are these people
Mount Jordan
I'm sorry about this
But we're about to go over Millie Weaver's new documentary shadowgate
Information such as
Impressively stupid documentaries
Sucks it really bad like I said without the spiritual energy
2 mi from our wonderful supporters
I hate
Every penny
A upper window
A week you're going to jump off your balcony
I think I went through
Sure
Dark Times
You listen to like 30 seconds of
There's so many things to look into it none of this is real
You get burnt out
I know you're lying I don't care yeah yeah I was going to say
You don't
Need to prove that she's full of s***
But in order for this to work you have to prove
It could have been just about everything
I could have said prove it
Very annoying
We have to do a show to
Play out the room and then
Oh no
Start off where Millie Weaver
I'm sorry
Please
Turn up the screen about everything
Beginning
What if I were to
Tell you
Small group
Government
Higher
Like government
Beneficial
To frame
Campaign
Shut up
Come up
For the Russia
Investigation
Provided
And
Services
To the Department
Justice
During the mule
What is it
Just so happen
Arby's
The steak new
Operate
Missions on social
And
So in this introduction
Either that
Or she's actually just curious
Something along the lines of like
You got to go
Have you considered
Because they're the rubric by which we are forced to judge it because what she said
A small group of government contractors were hired by the government to frame the Trump campaign
The Russian investigation was a setup carried out by the same contractor
Calls on Hillary's behalf
These contractors are
Social media
Influencer campaign same contractor
History of the United States
This is a whole lot for an hour and 20 minutes
Rainbow snakes the best because I'm from the future I already know that she doesn't prove
That's unfortunate
I think a lot of stuff she said two could fall under the normal category of invest
Navigation
Do they hired
To investigate him or to set you are as we're going to learn here maybe there are
Infrastructure company is
That have some overlap
Downtown
So anyway
Billy Gibson
That's just going to happen forever
I wish we could
Open gate
You need
To take a question
Or something
A class
About getting rid of gate
We'll call ourselves
Bill Gates Gates Foundation
Go get some fun day
Shadowgate my friend
Bad news
Covering up
What should
Turn out to be
Shadowgate
The Tactical and operational
The shadow government
Play
Behind the sea
Tearing out
President
Find the puppy
This document
Eastern people
Full of all
This is about
RealPlayer
Career
Part of the
The Beltway
Even app
But they are not
A government
Contract
Descent
Intelligence
Security +
And so on
Our
Mostly
Sis
Front face
Center compartment
Metalized
Grateful to work LOL
Or the fact that
Is outsourced
Contractors
AKA
The military
That way
Publix
Request
Investigation
Is as
As a
Why does
This is such a bunch of nonsense
You put it on for you regardless
Right off the bat
This is such b*******
About to say
It's impossible to prove that any of this ever happens or did happen because
Contractors
This is critical for Melly because
It's dumb
But it sounds just sensible enough for anyone except
Quiet
What's 3
Should be able to prove it
Here's what I
You would put in a foia request any
Oh I did search The Archives
Never once has anyone named Millie weaver or Millicent Weaver
Noah
There are no requests on file with the organization
Justification for not doing your job
Even if I wanted to so why would I
Right
If you are too gullible idiot if you would take two minutes to look at the house
Contractors are subject
For your request
Just like rain
Regular government employees
Contractor sounds like a big scary thing but in reality
Government entity on a contract basis
If you're a construction company and the government in the building erected for a contract
Graduation
Fredro
Yep
Panthers
Single bed situation
Spoiler request can be made about the recipients
Exceptions to the information that can be released
These are exceptions include involves protecting individual Privacy Information
Illegal to release
Trade Secrets because these are companies that are doing contract work
Also there's an entire exemption related to government information
Geographical information on Wells
If you go to foiaonline. Gov you'll be able to find all sorts of information about the government contractors
The contract and agreement
Sorting through all that stuff is really time-intensive in hard so it's easier for me to just make up
The contractors are covered
And use that as a bulshit excuse for why she canceled
How does she expect to quantify
Most of the work in government is done by contract
60%
Can't be measured
Expect more of that
Expect
Call numbers in trouble
Yeah
Like the course
The documentary that I trusted her own
I don't know if I want to double down on what you're saying even though I'm in a documentary
I don't know
Sure
Okay
Man-o-man
Rear window
Tori
Patrick Byrne
Who both work
Stencil
In the shadows
Have come
Revelation
That may be part of the
Whistleblowing
It's not
You might Toria Patrick bergey like a married couple
Very easy to find out who she is
Using some sort of a weird like
She has a f****** Radio Show online
There's an interview show where she liked interview Rodger Stone
Alright I had I waited awhile
Patrick is the first to start discussing
Situation
Show me tutorial little bit later
Patrick talking about
His involvement
How poisonous is the old coronavirus and covid-19
Call an internet simulated activity
Use their Spears
You stare
Anxiety
Found anything like endemic
Recognize
To help
We're flexible controller in
Target
Whoever it is
Greenfire elect
This is the main reason
Killing people
You never defend this implication that he's making because he doesn't have to Milly just allows them to save a pantechnicon real
Interviews
Does that sound familiar
Sears Melbourne getting out there and trying to tell people about that
Government contractor
Social media psychological warfare called a or Internet interactive internet
Liberties
2008-9 person contact Facebook didn't introduce the like button until February 2009
So that was when
Social media
In 2017 Berkeley released a memoir
Victim of the swamp
How the Deep State destroyed
The 40 year-old private
Invicta
The title is a reference to help listed in the armed services
Yeah we're not
The headline is quoted job
Now that's a headline right there
Vascular Associates Cardiology
Rudy claims that he was fired for country before company
His boss dr. Klein self and Air Force veteran
Zetterberg has stopped showing up for work shortly after he told client on October 3rd of his plan to join the military
1994 Uniformed Services employment employment Rights Act you cannot discriminate against
Andrew required to rehire returning enlisted persons after their active duty is over
That would have been a problem
However
Sweater
Comply with federal laws
Insubordinate
$3 charge
Call me companies phone
And was unresponsive to reports of computer problems at the clinic
Do you mean his job
It kind of seems like there is a documentation here that maybe his boss
Air Forces
He was also decided to enlist
Sabotaging thirty-nine-year-old
This was a strange decision.
This was 2005
Which was
The beginning of the Iraq War
You can kind of understand people getting swept up in the post 9/11 military
Patriotism
I guess even in 2003 when the Iraq invasion was be
The country
Propaganda campaign around
This was 2005
Wait 2005 no less
December 13th
So compelled to enlist as a thirty-nine-year-old civilian
And two young daughters just doesn't make sense to me based on her PO patriotism
It's pretty difficult to rationalize
Trees being served by the continuation of that war
Assertive person
Country over everything and also I really didn't like my wife
So that's that mean country
Like that Cardiology clinic
Another interview that Bergie dead
The truth
Some of the folks are treated like serious people on that ship
Another of Alex's favorites
Danbury bar
That sounds great
Night which is wild
Considering the time in between
The host of that show
Tries to play Aberdeen
And he says this
Which actually made me laugh quite a
Because obviously
At40
You got a lot more life
Experience
Mature brain
Thought process
And as you're seeing your physical
Might not
Match that
20 year old
You've got much more
Sophisticated thought process
Experience
In there at the age of 18 there's a
Psychological
A nation that goes
Military
It's necessary
Because someone
Take orders
You have that be there
Mental
Rather than
Themselves
Right is this
Should be done would you say that
That's fair
Well
Ex-Wives would probably
But yeah
I hear you on that
Oh yes such a freak
For the culture was engaged
I want to bring back
Water balloons that you fill with urine for this guy
I don't know if those everyone away I just threw up
Bernie Sanders
It's funny because his ex-wife
Ex-wives
Generally I have very little interest
Private
Can't not tell you this okay
Only Amazon page for his book
In the about the author section
Quote
He was divorced in 2010 following several years of deployments overseas and his personal struggle with combat-related PTSD
He was very briefly
!
This will ultimately end up
I do Wonder
Little crazy
But who knows
Who
Interesting
Just before deciding to him
In the 2004 election County Supervisor of Elections
Florida
An article about his campaign for the Tampa Bay Times
Very strange
Bernie seemed
Add appearing in public
The upcoming elections are on Tuesday
Sure
I was trying to demand
Equal time
Weird single
He was running a dude campaign
Miss Times article
What does Bergey's First Act
Getting into the race was the
Birdie didn't want anyone even considering election supervisor
You wanted to see the moral High Ground because he intended to slam Browning for his very public switched to the Republican
In 2002
In the eyes of many political Observers
Effectively shut the door on any hope
For organized support
We obviously had no
A political identity
Is almost universally pictured bikers for Trump vest
In order to appear
Because he's propaganda
He can't rely on the Party Machine in order to win
The article I read
All the money for a camper blowing from himself and a check for
From family members
Overly Fair
The bergey
Define distrust of the opposition
The election was held on November 2nd 2005 for Santa
Really good
That's surprising for someone we talked about
A run for office don't even make it to voting
3% is a good
Election for bergey
On June 9th 2005 in Florida elections commission filed
According to findings of fact
Designated
On April 18th 2050
And he didn't either
A little while
Very funny is
You joined the military to avoid a $200 by
Screw you
December 1st 2006 I can find evidence that he had not paid this for
$125 in pesos
You kind of get this answering this at the commission had a position of like okay fine whatever
Whatever they want to expend that much
Time and effort on
I'm just saying
That seems like
Okay
So much about going in
Incredibly fair but
This right here is the point where I started to get
Since the bergey was an a******
Still pretty early
But I like Dreamin
With the whizzer open
So he wrote this book which is all but have a deep State destroyed this Noble forty-year-old private
I'm not going to read this book
Mostly because it's
I'm sure it's a fine for not telling his treasurer's report outside
Imma pass
The hinges were Patrick bergey alleges is going on in the world is the term interactive internet activity
This is a term that can definitely go number directions
Depending on how you interpret it
According to bergey and his documentary the way you're supposed to understand he's in the world
Which are props
That is to say through meddling with the internet and social media
The activities they desire them to engage
Cigars elaborate
Hyper-specific data-mining that they do and then everything that happens in the world
Is due to their influence campaign
Interactive I mean we have Cambridge analytica
The terminal
One of them a memorandum for secretaries of military departments from June 8th 2007
Excited wave solidifying
Planes
Address down this memo
See the context it's used here
The use of a system accessible internet which allows for communication
UGA email blog
Chat rooms and inner a bulletin board
In a timely is not real time
As opposed to a system in which
Information flows only one way
In essence the term interactive internet
Activities
Action online
I supposed to do things like interviews
22 people
There's a conversation
Being taken
Being done by people from the Department
People are communicating differently online
You know any organizations are not code established
Recognizes
Only public
Strange
No that's got our own PR people to respond to emails and real-time
The other things
Recruitment
Military departments interactive internet
Organizing training
This makes sense
In terms of enlistment none of this
You go online you play some video games on Twitch
Everybody in electrical property
Quotes
Messages of materials protected by video and internet
Will comply with relevant intellectual property laws policies and Jackie
Civil based on what Patrick is saying and we'll go on to say I'm supposed to believe that this is a program
Government
They also specifically will not risk
Violating copyright
Which seems a little bit weird
You're in trouble I've had my internet shut off for torrenting, including one published on Army.
September 2009 public relations work under the.
Public relations
And psyops
Coronavirus in this sense
Taking on the responsibility that
Traditionally been associated with the state department
In terms of engaging in public diploma
Concerned
Claims in this film
Particularly about
This document is one of the
The first caveat is this is not applicable
The United States
Selected for an entity
The second is that they specifically say
Internet internet activities
You're trusting that may vary but if your document
They also have other places
Not supposed to
You know at the beginning of an email or correspondence to a representative
There are some Communications that are able
Attributed
But specifically this is only as authorized by the Secretary of State
Or
Named Operation in the war on terror
End the war on terror
Encompass
What patricksburg is going
Present or what
This is a document Personnel within the dod
Best practices
Every terrorist organization propaganda overseas
I'm not saying that it's a great
Recognize
Parentheses from what is being presented
One of the only things they fall back on is this document
And everything will become Central to write
To be clear I like none of the people that we are dealing with now
Like everybody everybody in this documentary I assume
Technology
So here's the layout
Is
This interactive internet activity
And it's
Basically
These demands globalist
Are tricking everybody into rioting and protesting for
Things that are deported
Straight white male
He was a contractor Elijah
Which was Ron
Buy these
Obama's former what was it
Remember who is Homeland Security
It's on run this company called dynology and they have government contract
Patrick bergey
Asserts
In creating a platform called
And also one called I Spy
Psy
Is it funny
Back in the past
Work
Proof that it's
Like a thing
Houston
He's in the world
No no that's not good
Sound like anything familiar to you dance
The unfolding of the George Floyd situation
This looks like shadow
One thing that I will say cuz I would rather
About these
Shadowgate is a better title than shadownet
Yeah yeah
SOI
I was reading over some of Patrick Bergey's writing haha
Credit for chuckle
B
So we get to talkin about this this shadow
This technology
So successful
They could
Do not use
I have the power
Affect
Collections at home
Commercial
Black market value
Technology
In Cal
This is
Motorcycle
I wish
Motorcycle with a sidecar
Okay
Lovett technology
Grammar algorithm or something
If the discussion here is about the creepy ability of social media advertisers
The target people with messaging that's worthwhile conversation
But it becomes an issue when it's flying around
I wanted some more information than the documentary was providing these website
Very consistent in his branding
Your post on there that was meant to lay out the relevant issues story
Apparently according to him
Here's Arcos
He was working for a company called dynology which is working on a social media psychological government
Contract
However
Developed with the name
We're in a serious like Mission Impossible scenario where a private Corporation
Feels that way probably not how I have some feelings
Well the contract with our government
A lot like my eyes were rolling
It's pretty hard to find information about Shadow and that's it doesn't come directly from Patrick Bergin
Shrug
From me
He posted screenshots from dynology website or what
Supposed to be done ologies website there's no link to this artist have to take his word for it that it's a real screenshots yeah but even if
It appears that the service that dynology was selling under the name shadownet was a service that allowed people in the Department of Defense
Safely use the internet
Secure computers
From the screenshot
I need DOD elements lack of proper tools to safely engage BB internet
VIP
Classified Internet Protocol router not working
That typically blocks access to Social Network
Working sites chat sites and other sites.
Information assurance perspective
Customized Security Solutions
Protect organizational assets and resources while working online
Our solution leverages virtualization technology from providers like VMware and Citrix
You safely separate intern internal corporate Networks
From the dangerous
Of the internet providing a safe sandbox
From which you can conduct your internet activity
So it's just like Chinese firewall
What kind of idea
Platform
Yeah
If a desktop is compromised potential damage will be isolated from your internal asset
Contain
It also allows them to wear their real IP address even though probably be bad for the dod networks IP address
I don't know where they are at all times
This is based on Patrick Bergey's presenting as
Pacifica security system
With a name that like catnip
The Conspiracy Theory
We got to deal with people and bad names
The other technology to dynology cells that birdie brings up here is called I Spy pssy
Clients to record and track their online interaction
It appears that this is related to recording things that an individual does
If I'm online interactions that I have
You know you could record that
Extended outside the interactions of your online cell
You were essentially based on what you're telling me
And what he's telling me
He is saying that
Every computer in
Everywhere is in
Affected with
This thing more less
Shadow
Useless the internet
Everything I can sell this is a
Where you can
Create
Perhaps
A fake
Persona
You can interact
Something online and then it will record
Your interaction
Continuity
Like some sort of
Oh no this is happening to me
Present
To secure the dod computers from any possible
I try to record all of the interaction
I don't know let's say you get sick
Someone else can take over at
And see what has been done in terms of
Technology at the same time
I don't see how it rises above the level of like
Something that makes sense from a law enforcement perspective
But the evil Shadow neck clams that are being mad
Dramatic version of screenshot
You know like
If you just took a screenshot of every interaction you had yeah put it in a
Email to somebody
That would be basically the same thing I don't know what it looks like
Description
Woody like a project
Right
It makes total sense
From that standpoint but
I don't know
It's about what they're not saying back on that pretty pretty solidly
Incredibles
I'm coming around
So I hear some
Load of nonsense
Think that you might not have much
Ovusense
Of what Edward Snowden
Sure
NSA data
Collect everything
What's called
Upstream
Forever
32 hours
However
They could private
Imagine
No
Brent
And
So claims that she works for John Brennan
And a project of like
Mirroring
Data that they captured upstream or something sure
Everything with their up screen monitoring which is definitely
That's a gross mischaracterization of the intelligence community
Questions about data collection and privacy issues and obviously there are issues a trust
And the intelligence community
You can just say whatever you want about this stuff
Rihanna say absolutely was not forthcoming collection in the past
Can't play that game
Them I don't trust
Facebook
I don't trust any of these motherfuker
And that's how I know they're stealing everyone's data and calling
Trust everything that's said about them
According to a 2011 report by the foreign intelligence surveillance
Court Clerk
Requires more than 250 million internet communications pursuant to section 702
Majority view Communications internet service providers and are not at issue here
Indeed nsa's UPS
Stream collection
Being acquired by NSA under 702
Really wants to present the image that
Upstream projects
Is actually literally every
Every call you make every text every website
What you talkin with his much smaller in scope
Are definitely legitimate issues surrounding the NSA and Upstream
The people who are actually fighting this or the ACLU
Would you never know any group
She's going to talk to somebody from the AC
How you write
And Tori that's a bad
That's a bad situation
So the main privacy concern that comes up
Upstream data collection of internet
Relate the possibility of an unrelated
This was because Downstream collected Communications
Person who was under surveillance
Collections involves Communications at work or about
I specifically Best Buy person
That last category is super hard to pull
Play Because targeted email address
And then you collect a message
Body of the email
You do that you could have inadvertently spied on a message
From and two persons who are involved in that prevalence at all
Search the NSA announced in April 2007
Teaneck Road
After considerable evaluation of Technology
Elgin surveillance activities
Will no longer include any Upstream internet communications that are solely about
A foreign intelligence targets
Instead
Is that a directly to or from an intelligence
Intelligent Target
Of course because you don't need any
Someone like me
You earned the
About it but I don't accept it as a
Conclusion
Absolute evil organization
No
World Xtreme collections
Did not collect everything that happened online they stop using it
If you work for John Brennan
Her copy the internet or something
It's a mess
I don't believe anything
Dispersants
Okay alright
Does she not take that next step
And realize
Were they to collect ever
They would need the infrastructure of
Thousands of P
People to even start
Trying to sort through a baby
You got my sister I don't know if it's cuz you're tired but that look on your face was verified
Play Kono
It is also I mean
It is one of the unfortunate
Appeal to some sort of a magical ability
Then if we're doing that whole thing
Programming the algorithm and what bias is it
I hate them so much already
She's going to talk about some work that John Brennan had her doing okay
Hard drive
Back in 2000
She claims
Wild
And
Tgin
Publicly
Beausoleil
What can you tell us about the
CGI Stanley
Brennan has a
When he wants to get some
So
I was at
Go by that office
Leave the cannoli
Drive
And then
M
I just
Kind of watch
What was happening
One person actually
Suicide or something
And the other shoe
Wow
You to follow up with another like
Question
Montgomery Style
That's fair
Claims because there's literally no way
Confirm anything this person saying
4 Milly
If you're going to do a documentary we are experts are real weirdos
Daisy things
Claims tour
Story just from the jump
Millie says Victoria claims to be the person who's behind of Hackettstown
2008 election passport information was accessed by unauthorized people
The breaches were traced to three individual incidents Incorporated subcontract
And the contractor for the analysis Corporation
Which are different
The problem is the CGI part
CGI had nothing to do with these data breaches
They bought in 2010
Has nothing to do with the story unless you're somebody who's trying to recreate it
Is going on here we'd pro quo my buddy so they
With the other company
But two years later so as not to make it
Look suspicious
They then purchased the other company making those p
Quid pro quo
I have no idea what he's talking about 32 miles turning up Dad or whatever but
Later
I think one of them committed suicide I'm not going to worry about you
I'm not sure
Don't 2000
They made it look like it was a
He wasn't really even hack it was
Contractors
Just access the information
Yeah it's kind of a cyst
Accident really
It was not an exit
So she goes in there
Information
In
Or something
Which
If it wasn't
Heck
Resume
In off of
Servers
So that
What would be the point
Hide
Well if I were
Big presumption again
Started yet
She said
Right now
Intuit
Wrong blues
So this this clip
Like it might have been
Deep into the documentary
This might be about where I lost my mind and I wanted to yell at the people who are
You're Sober
Better than you
So what is the relationship
Global strategy
Analysis
Are the Jacksonville
Except for the
That
Was actually
For All In
None of this
Prune anyway
A wholly-owned subsidiary of global strategy group
Do they all do the same thing
Material concrete connection
You would have to do research
I thought my pretty voice
Also Millie thinks Incorporated stands for Canadian Global Information
Which it actually doesn't
It's a French name which is called Sierra on guest
Which Loosely translates to management
Since grown into a
Global Information because the first line of their Wikipedia page
Which describes them as a Canadian
Incompetent
The next paragraph literally would have explained
The government and industries in order to preserve
I don't know what the connection is if there is any between
I do know however that just saying companies all
Have a lot of Divisions in them isn't strong enough of an argument
Didn't correct Milian
Pretty trouble
I'm noticing hahaha
Instead of the the screams I'm seeing in my mind's eye Millie Weaver
And a giant explosion of urine all over her
Sure
I wish I didn't say it like that
But
We
We all need visualization exercises
Sometimes
I'm so ugly
Battery charge
I don't know Gra
His son is listed in all the stuff that I was Finding
Possible that the father was also involved
Richard burgi apparently work for
The other villain is John Brennan
Former director of the CIA for short time
Rapid City area
The passport
Sure
Tori is going to say that she was that person or something
It's convoluted
Are we
Has been all over the world
40 years ago, he's not as I can tell
This person like the paper trail
Not true
John Brennan
Working
Network of Contracting
Such as Dan
Canadian
Information
And the analysis
Top 10
Senator Burr
Barack Obama
Get elect
Using
Internet info
Operation
March 5th
Brennan gets
STI
Director John Legend
Controversy
In the CIA in
Interrogation
This makes no sense
For 1 million saying Canadian Global Information again
Is not a real cop
Second-guessing about the sentence
Corporation
The hacker
Zero evidence to suggest
Just people accessing the data has been provided
It just hearsay of one person
Operation from 2005 to 2011 order to accept
Denomination
From Obama to be the deputy National Security advisor
I don't know if there's any connection between Stanley Incorporated
Outside
Early isn't
The thing that's stopping people from doing it is
It triggers a response
And you will get in trouble
In a New York Times article about the 2000s
Department spokesperson Sean McCormick
Discusses how Hillary Clinton
The previous summer
Context
Training exercise to pull up someone's file
Usually at least training circumstances family members name just for training Pope
The person that wanted man
Delray
It would immediately recognize they were immediately admonished
The undersecretary of State for management said the department had automatic control
Public Access
In the case of mr. Obama and Mr McInnes
We're open
Apparently super easy for the information to be accessed by people who we trust
Surprise
The contractors
Two different firm for able to access
It really just means that there were multiple people who didn't believe it when someone told them
If you click on that it will set off an alarm
Sitcom
It's your first day you're like how high is a joke
Blackstone labs
Lockdown
John Brennan is connected the analysis Corporation but not Stanley
Every story but until two years later
There's no reason for Millie to claim the debris has proven the brennity
CIA director
Salon games
The first is the Brennan specifically withdrew his name from consideration for the position of CIA director in Obama's first term
Brings up
He had supported Bush's enhanced interrogation
Knowing that he accepted the position of assistant to the president
Which doesn't require Senate confirmation
Also million
Public supporter of an advisor to then-senator Barack Obama
When was already on a short list of names to be nominated for positions like CIA director or
There's nothing that Millie is saying here
We can actually be proven or seems to mean anything
Yeah
Solo Dashie I thought
Thanks Billy
So anyway
A lot of familiarity with that story
Snowden
Created
Data Bridge
Anastasia
Private server
Intelligence
Contractor
AKA
Analysis
Corporation
Global stretch
Group
Global Entry
Twinning a stream
Set another come
Is copying all
Call
Messages
Emojis Instagram's.
Imagine
Uploaded
June 5th
Edward Snowden
Program
Prism
Revealing
NSA collect
Internet traffic
U.s. citizen
Major internet
And tell
Companies
Pfizer 7
You program
Snowden Act
Federal
Justification
Spine
End call
In the name
Preventing us
Classified
Or topsy
Being able to
This opened
The door for the
Clearfork
Switch review
Any information presented in this film
I'm not actually did she has no idea
Computer
Sounds like she didn't even watch Citizen.
Battery
Information still at the bank
There's no evidence
Tori is describing
Is happening
If she's just talkin about the Upstream collections that's very small percentage
17 persons under Fords
Surveillance
Would you describing something really scary though
Probably impossibly complicated
Literally everything everything online is collected in the 72-hour hold
Everybody
Horse problem
Switches
From actual internet service providers which is in contrast out stream collection works
The book and and
Watch the documentary through all of this
I realize I really thought that Snowden was going to send all this data to a non-existent company
Need to find out that it was confirmed by Millie Weaver that he saw it all
Analysis Corporation is a real
But that's the problem enough
Pools of reality that if you're not careful you can get yourself tricked into thinking like
This is real
And then you're like what's Canadian Global Information
Problem
I don't know if she started
Which is what clear for today
Eddie Bauer
Because I failed the multiple-choice
I got a little note in the mail that said that I didn't live the Eddie Bauer lifestyle
That's that's enough to cause a revolution hurt
Did Eddie Bauer in Uber
I feel like you should have been should have been the other way around
Sensitive
I have some check someplace I love the idea
That we are all the way
In a year that begins with a
The two
Snowden happened and then the government's like s*** screening people
Yeah we've been around for awhile
They later if that's thrown around like sheep
Call Thing 1 and Thing 2 and then we'll number of until we're done
One of them more
Troubling and difficult things
To look at
Into that
Documentary
Released by James Jones
Apparently Oregon
Contract
Government contract
Single DIN on
About a thing called the Congressional
Knowledge system
As I understand it from the things that I was able to find
Gather
Publicly-available represent
So it will have
Like meetings scheduled publicly-available
And then you can cross-reference that with like who was
I assume it has like a strong potential for like
For networking
Essentially all of the stuff that would be on it
You know you find this platform is stuff that you could find if you wanted to take forever to find
Create an algorithm
Database
I understand that
The sense that I get
From looking
Habitats a number of contracts for
Now Millie is found a website
Government contracts usaspending.gov
That is suspect
I didn't think that you was making something up because it is
Became an issue where I was like
And I wasted hours
Look on us
Receive Dino G
Was awarded
Congressional
However
1 Khan
Or dynology
Contract
Department of Defense
That includes
Mention
Congressional knowledge
Admin
For data
Primary
And
The North America
Street classic
Is data
Processing
Angela
Manufacture
Outside
States
State
Let It Snow
The desus
Documents
Congressional
Knowledge
Outsource
Private concert
Posted
Servers
This is Barry
It's very disturbing
I did pray sit down and
Apparently making stuff up okay
Call dollars
It appears to be for some kind of data processing hosting and related services
Primary places performing
There's other screwy things about this award but just don't
Operation cost 160 Grand
Yeah that's a problem
A couple hours
Looking for
Like details
I can explain this
Pretty clearly what does look f***** up
Sure
The first installment of it was paid in February 2018
526.
Then in January 16th
But on April 28th 2009
Return to the US government
Then
In January 2010
$92,586
It seems like an imitation better 2009
You failed to fulfill their end of the contract
Then work
Really hard to say exactly
Congressional calendar
Which is
Congressional knowledge services
I think that's a great way to you know I want the government run like a business
Something is up here
This page on usaspending.gov
Cmks
Hosting labor admin / cord
You can jump to conclusions if you want and report US Congress calendar data on
Server in Germany
All right here's my pic
Spying on Hitler who didn't die
Could be
Here's my attempt to clear this up I respect your
160g
I suspect sumption in
Siempre esta
She says that this contract
Of the Congressional
Posting labor slash
She's referring to okay
She's interpreting it as being the Professional Knowledge system which is
Calendar
Involve the Congressional service
This is the only contract
I went through about your phone
Abbreviated
Because I don't think that's what's DMT stand for
I think it stands for customer master key
Which are something that are used in cloud computing
The contract has been awarded
The awarding is
Contract
Explorer cmk
Is the office that's titled 0409
Cute
This is the only contract
And if you search for more information about it the office itself
You'll find a bunch of contracts per us regional office
In Bavaria
Contractors dynology been awarded early Shield of it and networks
Possibly were contracted by us stationed in Korea
To help with the customer master keys
And Billy saw the Abreva
Abbreviation cmks
And assume must be related to the Congressional knowledge system
Because three of the letters
Even if that's the case you completely f**** it up
She calls me Congressional Knowledge Management System which of these ckms not cmks
You'll notice that the contract for the German
Started
Prior to this in February 2000
Which is weird
Expired it doesn't appear to have been active at least since 2015
Everything I can tell there's no reason
This contract that was
Performed
Connection
The other contract
Exit
Or has anything to do
We can grab a congressional knowledge system
Millie just
Assume that based on that
Yeah
Sloppy
What you just explained right there
Is the nail in the coffin for when
If you made it this far into the documentary
You just turned it
You would never notice if you didn't look up recorded books were all these
Trucking contracts took forever
How did we get here
More work
Finding out the acronym
Then she did on the
Higher f****** documentary part of it
I really do.
Excited
Looking at that
React something we make sense
Why is it is one contract for Germany that's related to the Congressional
Knowledge system
The prefix
It's probably that the acronym wrong
Yeah
As an abbreviation in cloud computing
There's no reason to suspect
You're just making up
All around the world I wouldn't be surprised if
One of them Pizza.
Uncommon for
A bunch of different it companies
Perhaps provide
Fulfillment of the contract
Maybe they did it and didn't do a great job which is why as much
I don't know there's a hundred possibilities that are
Wheatley not nefarious
And you just jumps to the
Conclusion
Congressional
They have
Congress has information on this
I just
I'm just not going to buy 160g doing it
Spy on the Congress for only 100
Risk
Alone
30 million dollars even if you accept every misinterpretation the cheese-making is true
This contract ended payout
Yes so I don't know what the
We relation
Send a text to the present day
If you're spying on the government
Vertagear
And then they're like you did a bad job that you have to give back
Dollars
That's a red flag
Streams that are going sort of simultaneously
You have decided things right
Congress by the short and curlies
Guitar World
Because they do these I operations they face
Glade can
Make
And they do it on the cheap that's what you need
Then you have Tori
And she work for John Brennan through whatever
He has access to every computer
So you can do everything through the computers control the Congress
Completely
Fact whatsoever
They are doing a disservice
Spider-Man
Terrible documentary that doesn't prove anything
Computers
Compromise
Knowledge Management
My general
The abilities
Contract
The house
And the Sun
Staggering
Prove anything
Birdy
Comes back now
This technology I-5 because PSI like psychology
PS
PTI
Psy
You mean eyesight
Okay
Anyways
We end up with one of the
It's a pretty simple explanation for why they're wrong
What is your name
IPhone
Cipher
Real quick
They are absolutely
I know that I heard
Okay got you
Paradise.
You're alright
Then you need to be able to
Angela berate information
Provide
The leadership
Do
Provide
Asset
Journalist
News Oregon
An individual you
It could be anybody
Like that
Build them
Scratch
According
Birdy
The 2012
Open
What
For domestic is
Social me
Things Fall Apart
Some type of cancer
The fantasy world where
Operation so why would anyone take my word for it
Places that involve
In foreign countries which some propaganda
P2007 policy guideline on I-84 an exam
Terrorist propaganda
I feel like having the conversation about whether or not public relations messaging
The only reason that these people can argue
Social unrest
Comically sized conspiracy against them
Is because they believe that
Before he left office
Obama made legal
Government modernization Act of 2010
Is Millie references the back clip
This is literally all the result of one instance of bad reporting by the late Michael Hastings of BuzzFeed
Smith-mundt act never had anything to do with regulating the Pentagon reports in the Run
Perform
In January
What example included a report in the lake BuzzFeed reporter Michael Hastings
Modernization act propaganda of us audience
In fact
New circulated regarding
Besmirch the displeasure of Representative Republic
The sponsor of the smith-mundt modernization ACT
3 it's fascinating as a case study in how one blogger was pretty sloppy not understanding the issue and then except
Picked up by politico's Playbook
And you had one level of sloppiness on top of another
Thornbury told the cable last night
And want something Sensational gets out there and spreads like wildfire
Yeah that is fascinating
The smith-mundt modernization Act only applies to the broadcasting Board of Governors which contains things like Voice of America
News item items and programs that are available support
Spectre America Angela Banks
The modernization Act was prompted by to consideration
The first was that previously the products of the broadcasting Board of Governors was available in the United
You know that was when there was radio in
TV
Primary meme
Be increasingly
Possible to guarantee
Get radio stations from across the world
Like Chinese firewall around America really
Really really hard
Programming communities in the United States
For instance there's a large Somali American community in St Paul
United States
Meanwhile they would have access to other sources from smog
So that's one of the consideration
The important thing to take away from this is that the smith-mundt modernization ACT did not legalize using propaganda on America
Can citizens of the people like birdie likes
Pretend
Act like after that point the Pentagon and CIA were taking over every Newsroom in the country when in reality
Section of government
The programme was already being created
Carquest
Actress very clear on page 5 saying
No funds authorized appropriated to the Department of State or the broadcasting Board of Governors Chevy used
Wikipedia in the United States
It's a very standard talking points people on the extreme right
Conspiracy world
United States
Wanted to
If they want to complain about
A completely different conversation
So cool
So I
I don't quite understand
If you're if you're telling me
Obama legalize propaganda the United
And I took over newsrooms
Including podcast
Then
Why is it that they often reference those news organizations when they want to use them to prove
Who's their point
Literally literally everything propaganda
Because the time
Allow them to do
What I like
Alright
Okay so here's a magic
This is this is actually good for your conspiracy
Theory documentary
Right don't call it by
Okay
So that means
That if they're can
Controlling newsrooms and I sometimes use them to agree with
With myself
And I sometimes use them to disagree
The other people
Then the government
Is planting information
For both sides
All the time
Creating this
Great Divide in the United States
All there
Right
That's what you say
Sure
Difficult time processing
Killer Burger
Also a
I'm so
Frustrated by this documentary now
I realize this makes me angry
This product or not
Dunya
How is it we're not done yet
I'll be up all night
Hours for the rest of the night
IPhone
You know if they were created movies smartphone technology
Were they created in order for the military to run II operation
This
Is where I started at
Detect a trend
In mr. Burger
Smart device
Look it up
Modernism
Modified
To allow
Propaganda
Is that
What's the weather
Allowing it
And then what
With the Obama phone
Get the f*** out
Usually
Are you go
Yourself attitude
Yeah I might be a little bit
Nefarious
Because it was really sometime closed when its memo came out sure
Obama
They're not related
This is not well ordered thinking
Who's the person is actually making random connections between. So you can tell the story that he wants to
You do not get to just point the two things
Sure the memo and the release of the first iPhone 7
Like this for an example
Was in retaliation for the previous day's release of the movie Ratatouille
Glasgow
He's that movie
If they were connected
I'm close to the same time
Action is even more bizarre
Hutu things are absolutely
If it were broken and only picked up
Subtly racist ways this conspiracy theory starting to manifest
It's a pretty Stark example of birdies
I was wondering when we were going to get there was no way that we were
It had to
Also suggest
Dad
Play date
Control
Fostering
The Ferguson riot
Enable B outrageous. Connecting and living in a world devoid of standard 27
The unrest in Ferguson took place in August 2014 in
Connection by Michael Brown
The community was unhappy about the shooting and how is being handled come out of nowhere
There's a pattern
If you do that video of a woman talking about Obama phone from late 2012 and notices
Protesters in Ferguson
Oh boy
People who are interested in doing good job don't accept
Things like this as being anything other than an indication of someone not being a person
This response could go a long way toward explaining
The Patrick
Because that uses technology
To control people
This this this whole thing of
Him
What time
Milly responding
Humoring Lee
Or accepting Lehi
The Patrick bergey receipt
I think there's a pattern
It is life
Appropriately
What is website
He posted
Elevator version of story that reads
Here are some of the passages
Elevator pitch
She said passages suggest to me this is either a Long Island
God
No I know but that there exists more than one. So much
Shadownet is a social media project management tool
The Washington Post 2017 when I first work with a few others
My story after about a month of going back and forth
Rudy says to report on it looked into some of the things you would realize they were talking to
Conspiracy theorist weirdo
That kind of work before they accept information
And decide that it's worth
Reporting on
Quote actually spoke to me
Interview me in a private room for about 45 minutes but I never heard from them again
Burgundy you can easily see how this exchange is B of A
The only 15 minutes
Was they were having
A great
Exact
The House and Senate members I've submitted multiple memorandums of Records
Customers
I'm open to any other facts based argument
I've literally spoken to Matt gaetz and Lindsey Graham
Let me cricket
You can see how an accident on anyone parking easily to come prove it
They themselves are in on the future of unchecked delusional paranoia
The problem is the gauge of the world
Is proven correct
If you go tell Matt gaetz about this Stephanie takes it seriously you can work with that
He ignores you that he's
Probably secretly in on the conspiracy against you
If he speaks out
This information doesn't check
Conspiracy ship
If it's constructed in the matter what happens
This is like how Alex Warren
Has coverage
Stop the attack
Trust people who act that way
This last past
Is particularly dramatic
That's a little bit longer but I think it's worth
Patrick Bergey's Dan bongino show
On TV
And you like somebody cover it
But he thinks that has never full story
Not knowing who to trust I felt a strong almost calling if you will that I needed to meet Dan bongino
Some people suggest
Could have been further from the truth
Hoping you would help but I didn't know if you was a good guy or bad guy
Entrust Sarah
That's a person who
I think you might have been working for judge
Jeanine Pirro
I wasn't questioning bongino's honor
I was counting on him having
Patreon
Florida
Obviously this is a very long shot
My absolute surprising supporter
Is A-Rod
Along with airline tickets to join me!
I pick Susan up at the Tampa Airport Thursday morning and we drove straight to the event
That's another story for itself on another day
This elevator
I am no longer interested whatever floor I'm going to
I'm opening the doors
Update exhaust rolling through the tiniest hole that I can get that
I need to get out of this elevator
We got there and register
As we walked around
I needed to see for myself if he had honor and integrity was just another member of the DC swamp
And then
A few days later on Twitter
Metaphorical
Honor question
Describe what she saw when I first told Dan who I was
She felt afraid of something when he saw me and I felt the same thing
Having followed a couple years
Social media
And I like you respect someone with a gun
Little did I know he was a snowflake
Fox News contract
Again but I haven't heard any reasonable
Argument so far
There is a
Factbase
The getaway is a fact-based freaking people out
Leftover the reasonable arguments
Interactions
External perspective
Norbit
The close talker to
Suspect
I would probably ask
Exactly the same way
I am not a shadow net customer
Remember the last time
Yeah alright
Houston
Unsympathetic
Now it's time to go Hog Wild
Canario
Run from Ukraine
Can you do
Extension of a conversation about Obama phone
Just black people
We're calling them
Howie's
Starter
Riot
You had the
Data
So you can
Target
Pushing
Information
Tailoring
And when I
Michael brown rice
Traceroute
Stores
What I believe
No
Couple things
Programs through
Was like Obama song
His responses
That's a very suspicious response
Park
The second figure Jordan
More details.
In Ferguson in around the country prompted by what happened in Ferguson
CIA
An unnamed call traceroute
Burger spot with IRA
What does it mean
What is the thing you trace
I searched his website for Ferguson
Information
I'm absolutely no idea what he's talking about
Just ask any follow-up questions
I saw I strongly
Strongly suspected on sublevel whole thing falls apart
So
So what you're telling me
Is that the
The government the dod
Right
To get
Communities
Whenever they want
It right
Yeah I guess at the fair
Assessment of some of the activities
Because one way to get communities to Riot
Is to start a country based on enslaving an entire race of people
Alright then
When that slavery is over create different ways to continuance
Forever and then just start
Straight up murdering them over and over
I mean
Leaving aside the sort of grandeur picture that you're talking about the inciting event
Just dismissed entirely provided by
I think it's weird
Not just not maybe
A copper
I don't know
Next glucose I don't really give a s*** but
It was created by people who are all connected to this
Dirty.com
A John McCain was a customer
Really shocking Revelation little bit
But first we need to talk a little bit
About
Turns out
What's the first rodeo
The cheese had with million guy
I know that because I'm not an idiot I know
Millie's work
If you didn't
This
This next clip
Obama aipac
Correspond
Billion dollars
Scandal
The same aipac
Recital got a
Opposite
Yeah
Provide election
Action management
Sitel
Sartorius
For election
Regular
Electronics
Voting machine problems
You also
Tabulate
Salt
Clouds
In Europe
AKA
Servers outside
A whistleblower
Me in two
Internal
Sitel
Joe mettle
Particularly care about the connecting nonsense about this company because nothing that you think proves anything and I don't
Want to get lost in a week
Billy says the Jazz Source on her story about her beliefs of the Kentucky election 2019
Thesaurus
If you go and consult the Infowars article that Millie released about the subject it all traces back to One Source
Kentucky journalist
Tori
Spell tore which is how this woman in this
This is the same person who's the second interview subject in this documentary
The subject of the Kentucky election
Primary source
Happens to be the person who's the primary source on this story
Probably because
You f****** suspicious of s***
The sake
Is the real
I always look for a Lea
Butthole story about the
Kentucky election
Making an allegation
Another Republican
Her husband is not a citizen where is registered Democrats
In Kentucky
She insisted this was proof that the Democrats are failing the voter rolls of state election and Billy reported on the story and
Incessantly
Unfortunately propublica Kentucky registration form
Democrat when they registered to vote
In Fayette County in 2008
Her husband
Linda
That's a real last name
Why do the form carries a penalty of fines or jail time of up to 12 months
A couple records show have never removed themselves from the rolls or change their registration status until November 8th of
No
Do that difficult
For reporting on them
As it turns out this person Tori is a woman terpsichore Lindeman
Where is the great now
In 2018 she found herself under investigation by the North Dakota Attorney General
After a consumer protection division received a media inquiry about claims made by Chris Lindemann
Hyphenated
Charities
Indictment
North Dakota
Can you find the Griff
Yep you are there always there
Magic City Christmas
Which is required to solicit charitable donation
According to the attorney general's invest
Navigation
Affiliation
Chewy
The Bank of North Dakota and
In her solicitation
Without permission or even after being advised Bank of North Dakota
Could not be a sponsor
Wrestling in her websites
Magic City christmas.com
In her website and Facebook
Even after the city had repeatedly asked her to remove it
Brass Lindemann ignore
The contactor and as a result October 27th 2017
The issue a press release disclaiming any involvement with marasmus or a Magic City
Even after these concert was canceled for a Slenderman continue to sell items now claim
Proceeds
Denver homeless shelters
From what I can
Tell from the press release from the attorney general
It appears that Tori was
Investigation already has determined that morass Lindemann has engaged in prohibited
Questionable expenditures of donated funds received for a Magic City
Confirm the donations were deposited in October 2017 for purchases
QVC purchases
There is also evidence to suggest that when her personal bank account
Brass Lindemann made personal expenditures from the donated funds
Shady stop 160 G2 takedown
And to use the slogan
According to the election results
She did not make it to the ballot
I'm not sure if we're being on the resident created
North Dakota
Jason is being started because it's not that this individual is a concern for the well-being of our city people that reside within it
Yes 104
Due to harassment
Lying about City officials in claiming several
Including flower
Well I'm number of concerned citizens would like to shut down before any more damage
Can possibly be done
Several of us concerned citizens have contacted
Such things as
Personally attacked in such a pedophile
I've heard something like that
Hey
Sounds familiar.
AR
By myself little perplex
Princeton's in 2011 her name appears in the University of Kentucky's brochure
At the time she was an undergraduate biology she gave an oral presentation on
Acute spinal cord injury
Alright that sounds like b*******
Undergraduate research
What threw me for a loop that was her medium
Page
Uranium block
Jetta 2014
And it's really actually
Her first essay was titled USA language confidential
A nation built by immigrants
First generation
Healthcare private
Better Sports
Nationalist sentiments
United States of America was built by immigrants
Official language
Keep that in mind next time you think of blurting out this is America
With a redneck EX
This post
You can still edit
It's medium
2014 clandestine
Should have been people involved in all that by this point
Passport
But also in
She says quote
She's talking
2008 and I'm looking for work to help
Wework my way
Through Medical
School for a remote interpreter
So much of this doesn't make sense
In 2000
Super John
Passport hacks
Also she was a biology undergraduate in 2011 University of Kentucky
Maybe she meant pre-2008
Sure.
Scrub your page man
Her next to post on the same topic
Interpreters and their importance in the medical field
You make some decent points about the difficulties that are involved
Types of language
Appropriate language
Persons
August 2016 the entire Township
Previously the extent of the politics on here in a writing had to do with issues like language interpreters and her feelings about Greece's fight
Situation speaking as someone Recovery Care
On August 1st 2016 to posted an entry titled
There are only two options
You have to choose
This is a completely different writing style the comes off like an unhinged
Rant against Hillary Clinton
Whereas the previous post where
Accusations of things like Webster
Kabul secretly being Chelsea Clinton
Bother
Brother Larry
In the suggestion of inside knowledge
Another thing that's interesting about this post
Better use of language
Completely changed
Please remember that
By protecting emigrate
Terminology like a lesser English proficient
People speak a different primary language
Butcher now
In August
Is really difficult to hide a poppy Plantation to make heroin in the United States
From Canada and Mexico
Also it will help regulate immigration
I don't see why everyone has a problem with defining borders and ensuring know who's coming into our country
You have a fence around your house and how loud Your Land
You have a door to your house to control who comes the country
Is it a ploy by Trump's opponent to Pander to the Latino or shall I say Taco community
Yes taco bowl is how the Democrat the DNC refers to Latinos
Second-class citizens in their eyes that deserve no respect
Did Mexico pay for the wall
It's that simple
Okay so did it so either
She got
YouTube
And went down the algorithm and lost your mind
Or
She has all of her scam started failing so she would like
I'm clever enough to right-wing Griff
No
Yeah I'm not I'm not asking you I'm saying that these are the possibilities
It really shows
Apri log
Some of that
Trail and make of it what you will
Wild
This post is totally very different from her early writing which I find very suspicious
It's also divorced
She previously approached
The issue of medical
Renounce
Completely nonsensical
Papi from flooding in
From Mexico and Canada
The trick
Her previous post
Contained empathy towards
Two Face unique challenges
Now she's ranting about stuff like this
No
Capital no discussion on this
Shut our borders down completely kick out all the illegal alien
Keyword illegal meaning not legal under law breaking the law
How hard is the word illegal for someone to understand
Even though she probably
Complete range
Perspective
It's ugly it's mean required
Which I guess
I don't know
Okay
Dan Dan
August 4th
August 1st August
And then in 2017
She scammed people out of money
With an illegal charity
Dan
In the lead-up to the election to all sorts of conspiracy Yarns about Trump
In one post she says quote your vote counts
Remember we're voting dead people legal immigrants
Illegal immigrants and fictional people
We descended into that frame yeah
On November 7th 2017 she posted an entry titled year later
And this install but you've ears into religious ideology about Trump
Today Franklin Graham together and pray for our present
I firmly believe that he was elected because people pray
I don't care if you think prayers don't work
Eminem
Just posted
So then you do care
Caps are weird
Is all about
Impossible for an individual
Also in this post I think Tori is advocating for businesses to pay higher taxes
Businesses big or small must listen to their communities
He must take a position and putting their community's first
You can't ride the crest of the bugaboos without
The boogie board which is your contribution
Seems like I should be the most effective way to distribute
But maybe we should
What's missing from
Previous writing
Is any indication of her life path working in secret intelligence
Contract
Around the time when she's supposed
University of
Kentucky
Complaining
Not even the suggestion she has first-hand experience
I had to guess I would say
Probably cuz that stuff wasn't part of her narrative yet
Yeah
To be the writings of
Two different people
But neither of them claimed the backstory the Tory now
The first person you season educated person who cares passion
Immigrants receive inappropriately
The second is of Raven conspiracy Limited
There's probably a cautionary Tale
Lesson Port than the fact that her own writing seems to directly contradict
And definitely does not support her current claim
Billy didn't literally none of the work that is involved in looking into her sources before repeating their claims
Those about the Kentucky election
Care about our work
He's very bad at this stuff
She's even trying to obscure the fact
Tori also the person
That she based her story about the
Kentucky elections on
Because she knows that that's bad she's yeah
Wow
Complicated
Sort of
View that I guess
Looking at
Find about her
It's it's
It's tough because you know you're
Emotionally your instinct is to think
She's got f***** up by this information
Stream
Down
Terrible
That's certainly a possibility I don't know like that
Possibility
I also probably
But desire on our parts to have like an empathic
Reasonable explanation for whatever
Medium bloggers
Upsetting
At her
Right now
Not for all of the line when she's doing the documentary
But that she in the same way Billy doesn't have the
Or is just
Too lazy to do
The barest minimum of Journalism
Too lazy to do the barest minimum of scrubbing your internet history
Before you start
To become the source
Conspiracy theory
You know
But if it's basic
What's basic stuff
If you're going to create a mythology for yourself
Do it
I don't know
Into the past
Whatever
It's weird
Sloppy
100% not believe any of this
2008 you're in med school and you're trying to
Work as a language interpreter
Find it hard to believe that the University of Kentucky
Orange Virginia
Also I don't know
Change.org
Petition that was making a claim Is Stolen Valor and I don't know
There's a
Play
Where people can post
The times that they were in the service
And then try and find and connect with people that they serve
How much is that information is cell
Generated where I don't know
I did use that
2 cross reference
University of Kentucky
Is on her military
Meetup
How's thorough an in-depth your destruction of every part of her life is
I feel bad if
Like genesis
Like sincerely
And it is
Somebody who got
How much of that is misplaced
According to the North Dakota attorney general actively scamming charity
Being the centerpiece of bulshit propaganda documentaries
Yeah
It stopped and I think maybe some of the empathy is based on like me thinking that you
Early
You know you don't
Consider all that much it's not stuff
The needs that like people who
Google or not
Proficient
In specialized situation
Conversation
You know I don't know exactly how much attention
Yeah I know it's hard it's
It's always hard
I think regardless of
Any situation to see somebody
West
Very clear
Potential
2 South Emerald
No looking for you I would have a lot more empathy for Millie if I looked into her and I found in the past that she had
Crusaders
Yeah you know where
I am there but for the grace of God because I empathize with the earlier version of her
Possible for me to turn into the later version
Snapper I suppose
Soto's like kind of selfish
Get to talk in here this is just like about Robert store
Oh I Izzy
Is the Inspector General of the NSA
Millie makes a false claim because
Should a f****** attitude out that other documentary
Obama
Robert
Deputy IG
Time
Store
During the trash
.
From the Obama
Ministration
Stuart Pearce
You never have
Actually
Stration
How did the guy get
Confirm
Not one person asked
Nobody asked
Did you by any chance
From the president
It was all over the media
You're welcome
Set it up
Bill Taylor
That is odd
You should have added to that out
She's talking about overheard phone calls
The delivery makes it sound like she actually saying that she has supersonic hearing
And
That would be
Also
Does Millie mean when she says
Storch appears to have never been
Confirm by the Trump Administration
A mean bear
Lizard
Appears to never have been confirmed
Nautica Nautica
Weasel
Do not have been
Okay
Deputy inspector-general beginning in March 2015
At the end
June 2017 Donald Trump
Do that you could have nominated somebody else but Trump renominated the dude
If you go to nsa.gov super easy to find a press release dated December 20th
Director of the National Security
The president's nomination of
Is the Inspector General for the National Security Agency
What does Milli mean never confirm
From what I can tell
Here's To Me
To you because you Google
However where I'm not to Google
It appears that he is not been considered because I don't
See it then up here
This is where just like all right
Do they not know anything about Cambridge analytica to the Cambridge analytica used what bulshit they're saying
The other team is using
To get trouble
Haha
You're going to love that God damn it I hate them
They were supposed to sway
Give up the goods
Why why
Atwood
But that doesn't make
Distance from
Know that Jen
Darryl Jones
Is a Democrat
Don't like
Well
Cassandra
Russia was right
If you're keeping track
This is what the narrative is now
Cambridge analytica
Trump campaign
2 attack
Trump 63
They surreptitiously use nefarious me later
They're able to blame
Achieve the goal of making Trump not president
What you would only be because there's
The urine balloon dream is not doing it right now.
This is a long walk
Yeah so can you damage an elliptical
Except
So they're not really the problem
It's that they're not doing the shapeshifter well I mean obviously the Shaving should in the problem the other guy was like
Yeah that's what I would do except
According to this document
But it was
The globalist or whoever
Stay attached
The Cambridge
To Trump
To help Trump win
I meant Trump will be impeached
President worth
I don't know
Hertz
The brain
That has zero one hundred percent of the time
While
This is worth it get one
Was used to frame Trump
In this universe
Now
Has some implications that are difficult to get around
Mycampus
Analytic
.
That Russia
Operation
Help Trump
Election
Stonemanor
Davis
McCain John
I'm doing this
Decade
Personal fan
Priority
And I asked
Are you in
Did you work with
Knowledge
I didn't ask
You know about it
Stone
Trump
Early on
Suggestion
Appliances
What the f*** is happening
Apparently
Rodger Stone
Not
Hero now or something
About the pattern
From paper
Suspect today when he said Rodger
Or something
And in the process
And Rodger said what
Conversation
Associate
Does that not raise the question of what he was doing it Infowars
That be the next question the next
Take
You're if you're
This is unacceptable
We
Have reach stone for comments
By which I mean I walked
Down the hallway
And asking buddy and he refused to be a part of this documentary probably because
It's too good
Rodger isn't the same as another one
And this one is more of a character
Marvel Universe
In this section Rogers
Maybe probably not though
Good beans
Attached
People like Rodger and Paul manafort to Trump campaign
Or something
Fort
Beginning of this episode it's real bad
Sure
Through
Paul manafort
Submitted
Proposal
Rejected
I love that man
Boating
He's giving me on
Do that
Rejected Trump campaign
Trump must have sensed
Set the offer
Operation
Was a honey
Trap to set
What do you think that
Reason
Airport
Attached
Because they were true
Yes
Because they say
Ford
Whether or not
Roll
The Trump surrounded himself
Perfect
Backup your machinations to the evil globalist
Globalist
Inauguration in early January 2017
And reportedly met with General
Did Jules email group
Yeah
Overtures from Trump World group in 2016
Both represented themselves as members of Trumps Inner Circle
I don't know but it kind of
Bismarck Annex
Being installed
In the campaign order frame Trump
Inside group
I was talking about it straight b*******
You know damn yesterday at the memorial
The pastor
Who is doing the the service gave a real long
Awful
For the wages of sin is death kind of
Bible reading
It's the whole thing
So I've been thinking about the Bible and my relation to it for a while
Since then
And
Listening to this documentary
I was thinking
If Millie were there
Don't think
Jesus would have said he who is without sin May cast the first stone
I think you would've been like
This time next time we're going to do the turn the other cheek thing next time
You presented an interesting thought experiment
I would say
That is for you listening to this
Please
Please pity make I walk at this multiple.
You made me just
I will cast aspersions
Really
Interesting question for Tori here and that is
Alright
If you're if these operations operations were
Supposed to
Ensnare Trump
Why didn't they just run one
To get Hillary elected
And this is a dumb
Dumb answer
So why wouldn't they just
Mister Edwards
Opera
Good question
Censoring shadowban
Mitchell
Kingbird's I mean
Where we saw the real
I don't understand why the psychological operators would be deployed
Operations for comp
Letgo
Tall
Had one of them apparently telling me
With a straight face
She got straight face that she is she smiling is this documentary like a joke
That if you only listen to auditorily talk
As the British say taking the piss
Explain to me
Are you would have government agencies
The same government agency contractors
Working simultaneously against each other
Well it's the same people
Working against themselves
4 tons
Clear goals
Operate this way outside of a comic book
Yeah but
Patricksburg he comes into clear it up a little bit
I need some clarification
He seems to think of
Pence elected
Basically
What would be the
Good question
Because
He wasn't their choice
Is a jackass
So we're talking about
Dying
Which pencil
John McCain
Lindsey Graham
Rather have
Batman
We're totally irrational response to be mad at someone who gives out your cell phone on television
Yeah
Got that
Crazy I would say
Bass
Troll and nefarious dealings with are described
Simple solution would have been to run pants
And perform operations in order to support him winning the presidency
Or if you don't want pads
Grand KC
Run anybody
Having both ways
You can yes you can magical otherworldly control
Easy fix
So just chosen somebody else
More powerful than the iPad
Why didn't you do embed Cambridge analytica
Here's here's what this documentary accidentally proves
Trump
So
Everything he does
That in order to
At the very least make him appear
Competent
You have to go to Vizsla
Yes yes that is true that is what Trump is so people are
Killing their own brain trying to make him a good guy
Wow
Jamel
Get to the beginning
Some weird claims on Tori
Breeze Park
Don't say 3 hours in
Did we get to the beginning
Parts of the DNC server that got
Partisan
Still the same thing
They went with nothing
Females in song
When I had
Okay
Something all night which is not provider
I mean
You could even just
Take a picture of a random search better than just saying it
Cloud up
You can picture you can
Yeah
I don't I don't care for this I'm going to need more
Call Dan
Call me back
Told him about
I know why
Every one of these p
I have a hunch as to why people would not call you back
I wouldn't
There is
Sometimes
You know this goes beyond
A cigar is just
The cigar
I have a foot
Dealing with objects
Permanent
Not even the acknowledgement I hear this stuff about Bergie
Complaints about how people interact with
He seems to think he has the goods on everything and all of this
No one takes him seriously because he talks to them and they're like oh there's no credibility
Look into this for a minute now I got now. Doesn't check out
This is like me
Being like insisting that I have the best 3-point shot in the world
36 year old person
I keep going to talk to basketball teams in the NBA
And it's a conspiracy because they don't want me to take over the three-point
It wouldn't be good
You don't want me coming in there and Wrecking shop from downtown
Everytime I called like dude I called
Trucking
Utah Jazz
I called
Ages in the problem
Vince Carter played in till he's dead
Sounds that way to me okay
I did I get you
Because of
Turtles with twisting in your thinking
That's accurate
I'm seen
Have a 100%
Perception
And have you heard what some of these people say
Think that they're not there do inside
For you
I can't breathe very hard
Billy gets back to talking about
The DC passport
B I got some problems
Cgi's
The passport fee
The CGI involved
The Mueller investigation
See how contract
Ability to
Perform
And
Clean up there
We already discussed this but in case you forgot CGI was not involved in the passport issue back in 2008 that was Stan Lee in court
Has acquired by CDI to years later
Billy is trying to make a big deal out of their fingerprints being in two places but it was one of those places she's misreporting
Specific lines are being made about TGI's intersection with the Mueller
Navigation
But considering 3rd insanely Diversified company to brings in an annual revenue of over ten billion dollars
I bet it's not outside
It or systems consulting or something or some subsidiaries
Let's Millie could be more specific about what they did and why it's
Suspicious I'm not going on a wild-goose chase
At this point I should probably say I'm not going on another wild-goose Chase cuz my dude
Marquis last 48 hours
Ziggy's
Had a piece of the DNC server
Talking about
That came to be I would like to know that
I need it now
Southridge
He was at
Hey when is
Google image
You there for us
Florida
Jermaine
Copies
Fractions
So
Ancestors
Volume
Okay
She was watching the upload
DNC server
I don't believe any of this
Some some
Older guy behind a big desk
Eaton
Eating a hoagie for lunch
And he just looked at me like
Why don't you go download some of that DNC stuff
I'll see you guys later across the country story
Hanging out talking String Theory with her friends
String theory
They don't we wrote
Accepting extravagant claims without proof
Also if I understand
June 2016 so we can put this on Tori's timeline as being after her
Sure I can just prior to her trying to rip off people with the fake charity
And I don't see
Such a thing
People like her
Super smart
Around discussing String Theory like
An Algonquin Round Table
You know like Dorothy Parker
Show me literally one thing
Feelings about that
And when he saw that
Retroactive
Separate
Stories in the
Bernie Sanders
Elections
Stolen
The DNC
Armagnac
He came and cons
Decided
Okay
Don
Killed on July 11th
That's a lawsuit
Lucas had nothing to do with the actual process servers job was
Deliver papers
Deserve
For One Source process Incorporated company in DC
The video may have been celebrated by anti-clinton folks across the video wasn't involved in the actual
Much as they might have wanted to
On August 2nd Lucas passed away
This was naturally yet another Clinton murder case closed
In November the chief medical examiner Washington d.c. confirm that Lucas's death have been an accident and been the result of
Some drugs including Sentinel
Psycho Benz
Which is a muscle relaxer
Storytelling an intriguing Tale
It's kind of short on
Any of that
Summit entertainment
Boring annoying
You're not wrong about that
Trends that are just impossible to ignore like where it with Patrick Berg talk about how
Protests in Ferguson
Matter to Ukraine or something
Another accusation that he has about Ira operation
What you've seen
Riots
George Floyd's death
From your perspective
Does that look like
More stuff
Another social protest event is happening seeking to address issues that primarily affect non-white people and Patrick Bergin
Organic
Make sense got to be an elaborate plan to trick people into protesting
You notice that this kind of thinking doesn't get directed at certain
Other types of gas
Unite the right rally isn't being called IIA
Is social Gatherings and movements
Ideology
Because it makes sense that people will be motivated around something like that
Curry shoes that don't touch their lives personally
Contextualize those things
It's so silly
You're so stupid
For thinking that
A cop
Murdering a man
A black man
In Cold Blood
Isaiah
Yeah I'm tired
That's that I don't know
Probably IRA
But on the other hand if somebody might
Intimated that
Gun control is a good idea
Obviously
Disturbed me deeply
Quite literally
Movie still alive
Almost
I mean I guess that's the
If you actually
Was pointing out in
So
Will continue to for the foreseeable future
What's it called false Flags
Two more critical analysis
Sandy Hook
Really chew on
Add stop
About
I think what's more important is a terrifying it is the idea that
That Tori thinks the movies are making
In front of her
Programming
I don't know why but the framing of it is our making
Fun of us is like
A little sadder
Summer it's a little narcissistic to me
It makes me feel sad
About
6 years before the iammo
So
I don't know
Anyway who cares
None of that's important for it
Especially like you were talking about Alex
Has like
Alex's Volkswagen
Hold up
Your documentary
You know
Hacking reality
You'll see the reason that Millie
She thought
But you was being arrested
Documentary
She should never get in that car
If she had the opportunity to flee out the back of the house
Oaxaca
It's just
Software
Chorus
Schoology
All of them
Pick from all the people that will give you a guilty verdict
So there's no chance.
Anybody
Judges are corrupt.
The major
Your problem
For the justices
People are able to
Use that take
Selection
Predict
Who's going to
Throw their vote
Is anyone stopping
What's a major problem
Whilst
Rodger stone that I'm not sure if
Best
That's just insane
Ecology in order to
Jury pool
So basically all the underpinnings of every piece of our society are just
Under control
Possibly
To go
And get a trial for whatever these charges are
Even even get there
Every legal decision ever
Is up for grabs and probably
F****** fake to begin
Nothing's real
Magic show
I feel like she's making fun of me
Bikewagon the dog
Do deer Tori says something it's just absolutely not true about Trump
People new
Just how bad it is
Think about how
Think of all the money there
Stop the clearance
Never once you're out
Remember
Future General
Or all the future
Intelligent
Don't get to use your cleaner
Absolutely not true
What Trump did was a politically-motivated attack and pressed against political opponents
In August 2018 Trump revoke security clearance for John Brennan
Various people have been critical of his administration
Ettore in action
In nature
Historian
Is complete fiction
If it's not
What are the issues here is a misunderstanding of what
Security clearance
When is
If you have top-secret clearance that doesn't just mean that you're able to access whatever top-secret material you want
You would still need to be employed in a job where access to that material is required
Having security clearance is essential
Access to certain levels of classified material
Pre-approval TSA
Actually access said material you need a reason and authorization
People like million Tori operating this world grabbing top-secret clearances like James Bond having a license to Kill
Ears removed from being an any position in the government but because he have top-secret clearance
Texas Dall This Confidential
Do you know what do you know what this is
This reminds me exactly of the movie Red
Bruce Willis
Did you ever don't know if anybody ever saw
But at one point in the movie
They break into Langley or whatever because you know that's not
And then they get down into the super secret basement where there's a v
With the
I hear the second brother
But it's just as old dude who called The Record Keeper our share of everything
You can just walk in
Put it away
I don't even want to deal with it
You continue not watching it
Coming towards the end here beside some of this stuff
Established
Basically
These Contracting groups primarily
Ecology and
I guess
Theater
Advice
I'm not even worried about names anymore
Information
They're able to do everything
Based on misunderstandings of Upstream data collection
She's taking
Imaginations of weirdos
Now we're going to get into pivoting into robots
Future
It's going to involve
So worried
When the road was the biggest problem the road as well
Yeah it's not a report from Interpol
The biggest
And Bowl
Towards the Ulta
Surveillance state
Ever made
Micromanage
This technology
Artificial
Eponymous
Operate
The Shadow
Interpol
Publication
Official
Robotics
Enforcement review
40 there such as minority
Report and RoboCop
Technologies
Understanding how
Technology
Our Global community
Important
So I found
Because I was
Tired
Seriously
Literally from the Spurs
Paragraph
The forward
WYD
Clock out
This report has to do with a fundamental truth
Raiders
Collaborator
Is were recognizing at that is technology technology
Computer hacking or the black markets that are on the dark web
These things are naturally going to exist crimes are able to leverage technological advance
Is that true which I think it is law enforcement has a couple of options
The first is to be actively engaged with Technologies as strategy
State with change
X
The second district received the grounds of the criminal use of various emerging Technologies
Got a dumb
The report includes a lot of consideration
Participating
In those very evil evil actions
Your board includes a lot of consideration
So we'll end up coming up as a result of technological advances
For instance if we're to assume that robots are going to be used
Trolls and surveillance capabilities
As this occurs it will be necessary to address privacy concerns
Including issues such as permissible to use sensors
What are the main sections of this report covers house central Essex
Questions are in the conversation about
Nain 1/4
So yeah
Particularly in terms of the existing structures and up.
It's hard and automation is another area where these questions become super tough
Interpol report and read one sentence out of it while pretending that the report itself
Doesn't raise these serious ethical concern that's cheap
It's a lazy and it's dishonest
She is not pretending
You would have to have red
The thing
2 then pretend that it did not maintain this representing cheese right
Exactly
Pretty clear in this report about the challenging Terrain
Law enforcement also has the unique advantage
To be discussing these issues before the use of AI in robotics becomes a common feature in
If this opportunity is ignored and Ai and Robotics are used in law enforcement without
Accountability
Apparently and explainability then the law-enforcement community
Losing the confidence of the community
Citizens that is mandated to protect
Shut up
I understand you laughing
I understand you're laughing but
Nora
I saw a line of cops
Mashing their butt
Batons on there riot shields walking
Right then beating protest
I understand what you're saying
Buy land in the real world
Your perspective than you know
In terms of what we're looking at
With what Millie has reported
And what this documents
I find to be affirming the negative
I just clunk Ali pushed back on it I felt the need to respond you're doing great
Very tired we're on our 10
Little wild planet
Are you
Actually cover most of this
It's dumb
Misrepresented as being part of
All of this
Stop
International
Factor
Several features
Program
An iteration of shadow
Technology
This marks 27
Issued
And clear
Systems and methods
Veronica Limon
To determine
Being represented dishonestly
Employees and replaced it with human
In that weird voice
If you read the actual patente does
Network action
Which will also update with any alerts
From legal public
Supports for
Make you suspicious of your employees
A management relations
These matters are wholly unrelated
The conspiracy that Millie is trying to spend
Workers rights
Also is from 2017 is just an updating their existing Paden from 2015 titles
System and method for detecting
Chicken employee-related risk
Sochi even did a sloppy job on that
Good work
Define conclusions
Cool
Call Nelly
Which is behind
Define
Operation
The case can be made
Jones & Co
The police
Operation
Simply because they are in a position to Ben
Alternative solution
Is already in line
Find with the green
UD legenda
Black Ops
This
Completely
Baseless
An argument can be made
I am now going to throw a balloon filled with
That's her I know if that would work
Balloon material would have
I definitely think
If you are thinking it's coming out
Nowhere and the disarm the police
You're right
It's disconnected
Here is how
Documentary
Which is just
Incredibly unsatisfying
Very little sense
He just decides to
Rowan do you win
And throwing his movement
Technology
Behind
Abolition
Defending law enforcement
Replacing it
Differently how
Technology
Implemented
Is socialist Democrat
Sunrise
Abolition
This political movement
Who is Parker
Us into the ark
Artificial intelligence
Did she run out of
Tape
I guess he thought the point was made
She did
From the what if I were to tell you what the beginning I don't think that prove anything
Close off the thesis statement that we were working if I were her I would be so embarrassed that I
Put something out
Like is what CGI stand for
I would be so like
Like there has been a couple times
That's
I have made
Slight errors
On podcast realize like after I put out the episode
To be at like 4 in the morning like
Or even just like little tiny consideration like things are factually accurate
Maybe I said a name and I shouldn't set the name
Episode
Because it's
You make a f******
Like just
Basic
And pointless
Like CGI stands for Canadian Global Information
And you
That alone is like
Please call the other problems and just like really Subs
Sensitive misrepresentation
Factual
Inaccuracies
The thing is
Trashed
Convoluted
And contradictory backstories
Both of the people that she has
Experts
The contract contradiction the conflict-of-interest that exist with Tori as
Her unnamed source
But she does bring up the Kentucky
Unethical as hell
Derrius guice
Nothing worthwhile about this documentary
And I would further suggest that there's nothing in this documentary that could
Ever marry arrest
I don't think I see you until
Lying is well
Crimes against nature
It's like you know
Generous interpretation I guess someone would have
In the process of making
Dangerous ass documentary
She stole documents and that's what the burglary was right
There is nothing in this documentary that is stolen
And the only information that could be even like
Really generously interpreted that way
It's tough.
From
Bergey Tori
And neither of them got arrested
And they very easily could have been there known people
So
The possibility that there is any connection to her arrest
And what I'm going to do I did this on purpose
I wanted to
Yeah
Just be unwieldy
100%
So I haven't
Alex is coverage
Yeah
I don't know what he say
But I'm sure it's b*******
We will go over Alex's
Coverage point
Holding cell
Better do that
Apologies of people were expecting like Alex's response to the arrest
I don't know what it is
I don't care
I've watched this documentary too many times taken up too much of my time
How
Dare
Millie Weaver
Make Alex look like a good document
Or I would say I mean I don't want to sound sexist because
Greg Reese
Voiceover context
The documentary
Yeah it's not that her voice
Is terrible
The writing
And the delivery delivery is bad
Alex
The little more
It's not working
Careful with his subject matter
Yeah that's
Interview subjects
F****** spotlight
Yeah
Suffers from the same problem production values are much better on Alex's
The round was probably a really good editor
Yeah
Help values aw
And
Husband
Edited this I don't think it was very well done
Content standpoint I guess I would say
Yeah
What up
Couple giggle
This sucks
I'm sorry Jordan I apologize pieces beginning of this but
It was required that we do it now you can go home and take a nap
Our duty
Yep
Jordan
Will be back
Maybe not the one that doesn't
Stay tuned
If we do
Twitter
Israeli
If you can please find a local charity or bales onto specially if you're in Chicago right now
Help the people of doing God's work
Dzx Clark I Madero runda
Supersonic hearing and it's kind of weird