Damn important
I have great respect for knowledge right now as I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
A little bit about Alex Jones
Jordan Jordan
What up
Whatsyourprice
Office chair
The old ones that we had were little bit rickety but you were so kind as to provide us
New chairs Jordans
Good day my butt
Navigate to lower back more important
A sentence for someone who spends as much time as any office
This worker does
On a on a chair
Probably more
Yeah
It's very helpful to have a nice most don't have to live
Breezair job actually
No no
Yeah
I didn't really recognize how little support the other chairs had until I sat down in this one but if you want we had before
Actual
What does ergonomic mean
You specifically I feel like it might be that
Yeah so that's my brights
My bright spot is I just finish
Ghost of tsushima
Very very
We all know that
Beautiful you've already
Beautiful watch
Another thing everybody knows about I don't know about the
Samurai sets
During the Mongol invasion
Japan on the island of tsushima
And it's basically like a fall of
The Bushido code in the face of all this
It's
So lovingly rendered
Japanese island
Gorgeous
Open world situation
Love it you took my recommendation
Indeed
Jordan today we have an episode 2
What we got in front of us
Is a companion piece to our Monday episode
On Monday we went over The Tragically flawed
Documentary
Millie Weaver arrested
Dangerous
And arrested
Offense of
No I don't
I would say the most
People who got thrown at the Republic figures
Standard of actual malice
I mean it was so bad it's an arrestable
We discussed music rhyme against
Apologize for the listeners that it was that long
We we did that for Monday and it doing so we had to leave aside The Alex Jones
End
Infowars
We'll get to that in a little bit
She thought this
We will see over the course of what makes a
Very serious
It's important to
Let's see how Alex response to something
A close associate of his who's worked
Hi I don't know
Technically or not for years for them forever and she got arrested
Before
A reason
In the midst of that she is put out
Documentary
Quotes
He is caught on his
F****** back foot
It's this
Because he has to
He has a couple of choices one
He can go all in on the conspiracy
Not having to understand
Howard one option
I don't know what the f*** is going on I've never met this person before
This weekend's Alex Jones
Coverage
A little video we put out on Saturday
And then Sunday the 14th of August
I'm down this is August
Lego
Next to an hour
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very very much Jerry
Call Joe
Next Michael P
I'm a policy wonk
Animal
Next
I'm a policy wonk
Generosity
Okay
An aqueduct
System through a medieval town
Yes
Generosity
Slow down at aqueduct
Terraria
I don't know why I took it back from you
I took a swing and I tried
Issue a little correction I mispronounce
South
Monday episode
Instead of note North Dakota
Anyway
Episode
Chunky peanut butter
Spell other stores
The bad guy
We got a note here
I thought Jordan
In parentheses
Butters
I eat the light blue pack it all the time just vanilla almond butter
Only sweetened with Bates
Alright
And now
You must
Try
It will be.
We will see if you can put your
Let's see if you made this up to
Keep me quiet for the rest of the show as I like
This is
This good peanut butter is in the audio field I know that you can give to
Disgusting on a mic
But the only thing grocer is probably the idea of someone eating peanut butter
It's not like trying to get a horse to talk sets
No
I'll get you a paper towel
What you want me to say
What's all this
All this stuff running it doesn't terrible afternoon mix it up well enough
I didn't mix it up well I suppose that's probably that's why I
Look I'm not saying I'm blameless in the execution of immediate response to it was either right
You might like almond but I think you're being unfair
You've got a
Euro-Pro peanut bias and I don't approve
Dexter
It is nice I don't actually
Smooth peanut butter
People
We have some phone calls but those the end of the episode I decided we should move phone calls
The end of episode so as to not make a ridiculously long
Open Arrow
This isn't too long as long
Today Show
Shadowgate
The Gate of Olga
Not seeing it at all so he is going to dip his tailored Electric
Oh yeah
Call gate
Which games does it out
Bill okay
The Night's Alright
Star shirt
People posted about the old Nintendo game shadowgate
Play out dates that
Well that's to gate so it is
Amongst Shadows
Yep
So are we starting on the 14th
And haha
I got tickled by this because Alex
Playing the later
That he heard that Millie got arrested before the show started
So the show's starting like this seems really weird
He is Fancy free at all
Carolina
Trotline America wash
RFB
New World Order
Dystopia
Soho Friday show Alex Begins by whistling into the Andy Griffith theme song and then complaining that America is
Isn't like a fictional on anymore Billy is arrested by
This boy
Alex claims that she he knows or he heard that you was arrested before he got on air
Text ruhi decided
I don't care how to whistle along with Andy Griffith gives no indication that he is aware of
Millie's arrest until a little ways into the episode
So I don't actually think that he heard before the show
I don't remember exactly the
Time of her arrest
Or if you would like it's even possible if you knew before but he will say later on that he heard before
Retrospect
So I don't care about whether or not it could be true I just think it's funny to
Imagine that like
Right before getting on air he finds out that one of his
Quote-unquote employees maybe not
I got arrested in India
Oh she's in jail
Remember, pile like I was funny
So it's just a normal ass Alex show on Friday on the 14th
At the beginning and so like users yelling about black lives matter and what have you
Because their empathy has been taken out
Blacklivesmatter
Attacking emergency Children Hospital
Little kids are inside
Give us your money your house
How did everything
We're here we support crime
Good questions there's no bottom to it
Is that what
Zombie like Monsters
Zombie like Monsters you around your house and take it
I really am surprised
I almost missed you in the documentary because I forgot
Like that's
Terribly racist towards black lives matter
But at least they're not like spinning Yarns about how black people are going to break into your home and steal your shoes
And then slap them on your face you know sure sure
Is this is still more intense
Yeah much on this episode because
Does mostly get into like Millie related stuff
And other
Sundry issues but I just wanted to put that into remind
Until he clearly learned
Like half an hour into the show that got arrested
It's just a normal show he's just going through the motions as normal
And then
He finds out the Millie's been arrested
And it's very clear that out of the gate he wants
Use this for promotion
Okay so Millie Weaver and her husband Gavin
People affiliated with
Bumps in the White House
Kill your name
Interviewed former military officers
Whistleblowers
Individuals
And they were making us independent film
Titled
Shadowgate
Imma pull the trailer up
They were scheduled to come on yesterday
B
Millie said they were getting solid
The phone
Taking off their computers
Well they just got SWAT team
We saw the video trailer is
Upon
See the video of her being arrested
This is not Andy Griffith
Alex Alex
You've reported this site unseen Milly got SWAT team
Come on yesterday
It's important to keep the timeline straight immediately Alex the saying yesterday she was supposed to be on
Now on Friday
Not on
Arrested
In Ohio
I don't have it on yesterday
Do the jet-setter
This is the first point where Alex tries to cover his ass
She doesn't work here
So Millie and
Banana said she can't tell you what all this is real reason emails are
They're trying to rest her right now
We're not up for telling the other way.
Contact
Tear
This is Extreme dress
I don't want to see any of these.
Already know all this
Turn off
Know this stuff
No as a jerk
I don't want to see
I need blokable tonight abilities I will get rid of entirely by announcing that I knew
You do not work here
Any leads me to believe that Alex thinks that you might be mixed up in something like Alex might think that she's probably
You dealing with some shady Trucking characters
This is a situation all over again I don't I don't know what he's imagining
Other that
Have you seen the documentary you know that there's no reason to worry
But
I mean Trump
Needs to get involved
These two have got a f****** bill Barr
Hardin Valley league.org
What is that Susan B Anthony pardon was actually
Parentheses
Rainbow snatch
Please get involved
I think companies
Immediately
These are real people interviewed
And because of the way things are going I guess these folks told them so big safe
Believe me
Defense intelligence people there I mean
This is not this is a serious
Millie didn't get
Bucking Mike Flynn Jr to come to that Z-Pak
She's a social engineering know I brought Michael Flynn Jr
That's because Millie Weaver first social engineer The Minnow
Glenn Jr
No Ivan reichlin it been on Alex's show before the past
Flynn defense fund fundraiser stuff
Sure and he brought Michael Flynn Jr and you
And Alex did announce entirely what happened
And then Alex almost
Cried
While Michael Flynn Jr stood by
Very uncomfortably beautiful your dad was going to put the military-backed government
I hate that you're twisting
Todrick drunk before his head lyrics
Aren't the square Rob do had to close up
I tried to take the rain in the morning
Yeah it was not as full of
Defense intelligence
As much as Alex mites
Pretending
Elearn
Where's my shoe I have one shoe here
Wait to know nuts are bad apparently
Yet to get to mention Brianna Taylor at all but
Good to know that you reported that you got SWAT team based on
0 hearsay someone saying that
True
Good journalist against
So Alex goes back to the journalistic instinct
Probably because she had Hillary's email
I don't understand what's happening right now
All right so they're they're saying it's stolen.
Females all of it so
Reported
And the dust Apartments all scared
Reportedly it's
Emails
I think the only person reported
Yep
So as it turns out the issue
Now we know because the
The arrest indictment
I've come out with the family squabble
Lily and her mother
Who is coming to visit I have the article here
From cleveland.com
And I'll just read out the
The main thing
Here is
Their mom
Came from California to stay with the
Has Gail Road home earlier this year after North Hollywood
Due to the Coronavirus
McCarran told deputies that Millie Weaver was swearing at her being mean and calling her names on April 25th
And she was texting with a bishop at the Mormon church where she attended about it the report says
McCarron said she decided to record the behavior on her cell phone
And placed it in the back pocket of her jeans while she made a grilled cheese sandwich
Millie Weaver sat at the bar Charles Weaver that Millie's brother
Wash the dishes and wheat stood nearby their ports
The trio began picking on her including talk
Generally being me McCarran told deputies
Someone noticed the phone in their pocket
Suggested that you was recorded
The report says
McCarran says Winstrol Charles Weaver to grab her
Macaron set
Millie Weaver joined in and all three wrestled to the ground
McCarron said according through Park
McCarron said she tried to kick and punch them while they were on her
Cell phone fell out of her pocket
She ran to a neighbor's house
Dial 911
The report says
And returned almost immediately as McCarron was on the phone with deputies
McCann suspect Riverside was trying to get rid of her cell phone
Okay so he's he's at a traffic stop throwing
Alright
It's a
Her brother and
And they all gave
Different
Accounts of what happened now that's because their master
There was a bunch of contradictions like milia told the deputies that her mother had lost the cell phone
Nonsense like there's no
Parents to any of their stories
Surprising I really thought
These people would just really be a no
And if you read this article it also mentions that the bishop at the church
They took her mother was apparently texting with
Confirm
The stories
The correspondents
About this many of the details
That McCarron had realized that the report says husband and her brother all
I mean we knew that before probably before but now now we know that
Apparently that explains the burglar
Messing with evidence
Steps to getting rid of the phone
Your mother's all the charges make sense
Cuz of the stolen document
Right I mean that's probably
Yeah so after that if it is the investigation parently
The case was referred to the County prosecutor's office and eventually presented to a grand jury
Made its way through
I'm at now
Warren deserve
I mean look I think this all makes total sense
I don't know I don't have any reason to believe that there's anything fishy going on here other than
Yeah maybe some unfortunate family Dynamics and some people be in
Pretty Adeline
We'll see we'll see what happens
Things with the
Further
Information
I mean based on having watched the documentary having looked into all that stuff
I just
Millie Weaver
You probably
Mother who called the police on them
She came and talked to her
Maybe she didn't know that there was a warrant for her arrest but I would assume that you would I would
Notify
I have no idea on that though so I don't know
Anyway Alex at this point as nowhere to turn except the experts in that documentary
So he has Torreon
She's just a cat real
Real soft defense for Millie
Internet connection was extremely slow
Very difficult
Put it together
About to release this what what you think's going on
They know that we don't have possession of Hillary's emails
This is just them trying to get information
Burglary come on Alex
Why would one Burger
I asked you to Jordan
Because there was evidence
I don't know
Yeah it's not good okay
I think they might have talked in the past before because
Tori was the source
Spore the story
That was his much more forthright about them
Billy was a documentary
Just weird
But there's something really strange going on
And that is
The David Millie is arrested
It may end up releasing
The video
Patrick Bergin
The other expert from that documentary he's in Austin
This is very weird is weird
A Milli
A lot of crazy stuff going on
Patrick was in Austin the day before Alex's Milly was going to come on the day before
So there seems to be a timeline of something there
It's unclear
Like they were going to tag team
Human somewhere
You know
Yes it's hard sounds like that's the only sounds also like the guy who might
Hopper flights
What's really going on
Might be where my brain goes
I think you might be going it's busy for himself a little bit
If you have like a number chaotic element
And
Like all of them have it
Fibromyalgia of what's going on
And I don't know I don't know who the f*** is doing what
Looks like Millie's tight-knit family none of them have yet Millie is trying to get this.
And unfortunately the timing of it also coincides with her allegedly so
Assaulting her mother
Tori is
Out there
She's got some agenda of her up
Patrick burgy is another Rogue actor
Alex is confused but is also the central
Goodbye everybody he doesn't know what's going on
So old.
These planets come from
All four of them have slightly different interest but it
All around the same thing
Really confused I'm not even positive dipatri
We're going to be on the day prior I think it's entirely possible
The burgie came to Austin and wanted to get on Alex's show and Millie was trying to facilitate that
Somehow didn't work how the f*** wouldn't it work
What is happening on the show
I mean I guess maybe Burgers judge
Just really really annoying
I get that vibe
He goes to places where people are
150 dollars
I told her we had no water but he blocked me on Twitter
Zoe Millie was indeed
Alright
Intelligence operatives
You know what I saw
Millie Weaver husband working with
And some of the people I was like what
Carpetbagger
I don't know what's going on
I was crawling
Will bring my officers
You were f******
Three sheets to the wind
He does actually always credits
Franklin as a green berets
Look I love this angle
This angle of like Millie was indeed
Get into that kind of thing
All I do is report the news as of analysis the news
Smash cut to the hundred thousand times I wasn't like everybody
Stateless
The best of the best sources deep within the government the good guys and intelligent
Stuff is foia request
With publican
All of my foil request or under an assumed name
That's such a
I love when he's
Clearly trying to make up a narrative essay
He's going along
His tone of voice is
Completely different
To commit even about Billy being associated
I fell. I don't know nothing I've never even talked to
This has me on your feeling of that
I don't want
You are. Going to rub this on me
In Austin
Surprise of surprises
You still in Austin
Studio
Dear
Austin show
Not going to post
Shadow
Gate without watching it
Crime and their perspectives to watch it
But you see we're journalists so that's always been productive
Alex is being uncharacteristically cautious
This is Katie this is weird
He also seems very confused
Yeah
In the middle of being on air here's what I'm getting here's a vug
Holyshit I'm up what did she actually do something
Did she did she do journalism
That is kind of the feeling
I'm not supposed to deal with reality and Millie is making me deal with it not
Generous
Interpretation
Oh my God
One of these
Like Ding Dongs that works for me accidentally actually got
Secret
Clandestine document oh no I want no part of this
I don't want
That's one possibility another possibility that I considered is that like
Alex do such a bad job of like
Training or getting these people to understand how to do their jobs journalism
That like
He might think that she just
Broke into a place or something
I didn't get a secret document right
If she was doing it as an Infowars employee that could reflect poorly on
Obviously
She's a f****** contra
Yeah oh yeah
Nobody
They take a lot of money for Alex to pay
And
He doesn't plug
There ain't no money coming in
How did blog last hour
Reply yesterday
Almost
We won't be here
Insect monster that right I'm not bitching
Tell you hey the whole country may not be here if you want vitamins and minerals in high-quality supplements are books or t-shirts
We win this
Seems like there's there's two things
I don't understand which is the reality
If Infowars goes down so does the country
And then there's another part I don't care if I get destroyed as long as the country survives
And I don't know I don't
I don't know which
Is the
Like what he's actually trying to push
I want money
Yes
That is behind a lot of
Amusement
Because he has to pay benefits for these employees
Guanajuato
She is knocked
Exactly what you're doing
Your own stuff going on
Sponsor them
If he was proud of this he would be like
Not only is she an employee she is part owner of Mitchell
I'm not just that but he's going all-in on
You need to give us money so I can take care of her bail bonds in Wichita
He's not doing he's not doing
See if he cared about it
He barely is plugging the GoFundMe
I got set up set up
AI GoFundMe for Millie
People are not
Not your friend know Alex is not your friend Billy
Alex isn't your friend none of you are friend
That's the way I was behaving
Is very much like I want Millie to get out of prison I don't want her to be in prison but also
Anything to look bad for me so in case she did do something I want to be careful
And I just might be a f****** nonsense thing
Buckets
Metaphorical gunfire data piece
Alex
Basically is
Operating on Friday on the assumption that you got arrested for stealing documents
Pretty much
Where he's at
Social Security
Issue here is the trailer
Foreshadowed
Obviously a national security issue a
The feds arrest
The feds with the SWAT team conveniently outside
So Patrick bergey comes in
He has a bit of a version of the story
Complexity
She was talkin
Gavin wince
Just before
The arrest
He just told me that there was going to be a big interview on Monday
By somebody
Wasn't Trump
And somebody was going to ask
President Trump about shadowgate on Monday and I said
Until fate flown I said ain't no way in hell someone's going to let
That a
Ben Wright
Minutes of me saying that
The police were showing up
Gavin's
Milling
Them in the driveway
And she we saw the video right now so I don't know
Tell from the clear beginning or endpoint that video is
But I don't care as I can throw him so
Particularly care about this this
There is
Clip is too long to captain on the episode
But Patrick tells Alex that like
I was
Cautious about coming on your show
That's because your show is called Infowars
That's information War
Because I'm up against
Information Warfare
Are they have like this
Sort of interaction that like
You can tell that there's some Frosty tween them
This guy might believe
In some sort of Internet stuff
Yes harder than Alex and then maybe looks italics
With your imaginary
Bulshit
It is also
Includes a way to dismiss your imaginary motion
Believe that you're engaged in information Warfare
Sure
Yeah it's kind of defensive
But he is also like
Really
Really like the two things that he stressing on this episode
So strongly
Are there
And I don't do secrets yet
Meli watch out
That wheel
Wannabe
Gaston
Set us up a bunch
How to do secret stuff
I've never done a secret I've never had
Hey
Feel like I've heard him have
Top secret source
In every I think he might have a large number of lieutenant colonel's in every branch
I mean I guess everywhere
He says it like
The globalists are planning to overthrow the president they're trying to kill everyone
One with a specific date his best friend
He doesn't do secrets
Fredericksburg he's bitter about the various media entities that have snubbed him in the past
And so you can play a little bit about Dan bongino here
And then Alex betrays Dan bongino's confidence on air
Can't trust anybody in the media
They broke in his house yesterday up something will happen
They did a bunch of stuff to him and he's just watching him
I love the idea that Alex is like
Secret sources trust me because they know that I don't talk
Biagio scared
Trustworthy person in the world
Conversation
Gossiping in the in the foyer with a couple of friends I understand
Any kind of like public sort of thing
You do kind of have to train yourself a tiny bit
To get over the fact that a lot of people listen to a thing
Because if you really sat down and thought about
Implications of like
Every single ear that hears the word that you say you'll be so overwhelming
Very difficult to deal with extreme of that to the point
Arrington bongino's alleged
Dirty business is private s***
Like that's not cool
I don't know if I'd have a partial his
She didn't want anybody to know that but what am I
Piece of information
That
But I'm a good friend will swear and then be like cut that out
Well feel good stuff that's so gold it seems like if you're betraying a confidence
You would have to realize what a betrayal actually be
Turn off
Call Gino's
And all these people and media
Who are
Down
With helping out with Patrick bergey they're all just scared and blackmailed
I don't know what his justification might be yours
Box Elder
It wasn't guys are good people
He's totally
Only explanation
Prototype how to defeat them
Yeah
This is he really think she might have actually done it this time
Is at least one to cover his ass
He's really going hard
Yeah so
They have a disappointing end to the episode and actually because Alex
Ends up like
I guess not thinking that Millie being arrested and this documentary is what needs to be talked about for the rest of the show
Because he's like
Over the weekend he's going to go back to the test
He had a real boy bullhorn
Come to Saturday
Video on Saturday
Supposed to be an update
On the situation with Millie
Contractors
Gabon
They don't know
Other things
I got to say like there is a sort of sensibility
It's coming out of Alex
Because he thought he talks about how like the
The police
Seemed weird you know like the video it seems
Nothing I understand
Indicates
A little bit of the self-awareness
Even though I don't really believe in a good off the rails
I think that's a
Liquor of
Some sort of rationality that you rarely seeing him take a lawyer next to him to get him to
Where is Barnes neck
Just said the Shadows has mentioned talking to barzal a couple times
But he does not make an appearance
He gets out
Get to talkin about this and apparently
Friday show Alex said the documentary was supposed to come out on Thursday
Prior
So I would win the 13th
Now it turns out there's a different release date
It's that the film
Supposed to come out
Whistleblower
It was a free film
She's really in jail
I agree that they didn't stay now we have Thursday was supposed to come out
Call it's confusing and a guy that you
Didn't have on the show because you
Weren't
Sure who he was was already
Pre-scheduled 41
And it's it's strange because
Fredericksburg
And keep in mind
They weren't planning to upload the video
Yesterday they weren't going
I'm planning to be done with it
Monday
And so
Preemptive
Action
So in his video over the weekend about heading to Ohio.
Sure he says that the video wasn't even supposed to come out until the next Monday
We have three different release dates alright
Two different people
Provided
But
The difference in them is one is Future
The other has passed
I don't know I don't know what
I don't know what's real
Also don't care
Hair with real
I would like to know
I don't even want to know I'm more interested in the fact that there are these discrepancies
Resolve
That are just left dangling
Well I mean one of the reasons is everybody's full of s***
There is that
And you know what's interesting just like a compulsive liar they ain't none of them could tell you the real release date even if they
Wanted to
Probably not
But what's interesting is in this video that Bergie put out over the weekend
He is not so into Alex after the interview
He is turned on Alice
What I saw was
Alex Jones yesterday was pretty kind of disappointing one of his
Reporters one of his
Are subcontractors you know I don't know if you saw the same thing as I did but
Pretty much any cover-your-ass mode the whole time that's the last
I believe Alex
Listen
He's full of s*** I don't agree with him on anything 100%
Right before I saw the video
Watch
Show
I don't know Billy
Now
Just that I've never met the woman before
Sure
So Alex
Back to his Saturday report now
And Alex has a spin on this
This is probably as good as you're going to do
Do you want to go
Videotaping videos at doctor
Wheel NSA whistleblowers
Real
So
This is weird because Alex has been talked to someone who talked to
Confessed to him that they took the phone
I don't understand
Apparently the story now is it I mean because the information has come out that this is what the arrest.
Architectural
It's not terrible
Harold takes Nikki snapshot information percentage
And it's definitely not something she was being verbally abused
Question some very almost certainly raise the ship was said
Maybe and there we go
So Alex claims in this next clip
That was sort of
The reason
Which we know is not true
Unless Millie brought Ivan that doesn't make sense either cuz it's a show
Texas never met either
Do anybody
Used to fix
Yeah that's really
Coronavirus map
The deal with the real people multiple times
I'm hanging out with weirdos who are making s*** up
There's no other way to take that right there's no other way to read that
But I like to do is I like to hang out with me
Billy on the other hand
People who seemed more real at the red flag
Is Allen
I look I'll be honest with you I was not used to being around such scary people and it led to me being
That's why I passed out before my headlining speech
I would immediately be like
That's self-effacing probably not something you make it upright
I buy it I wouldn't believe it was true but I believe there was his experience of
He's not done
People that Billy is talking to
May be involved
John Brennan
Not true
Some of these people have been slacking
This is Patrick
100-percent Patrick
You can sort of tell that from his video that he also put out of the weekend
If you don't
Time in Helena
Alex Jones
The biggest
F****** conspiracy theorists
Planet
Doesn't see this is an issue
Please
F****** is dirty as I
Assured me that he was
He was a straight-up guy
We were concerned about people
Possibly around it
They said he was
Straight-up guy Infowars
Do the right thing with it
Clearly
Millie Alex
Clearly what's going on here is the Patrick Burger Express
Concerns about Alex 2 Milly Milly I guess the somehow got back
Alex probably through Millie and
Alex has taken
This to be
Either John Brennan Defector that she's talking to because it doesn't make sense
Because he's from the
Jim Jones of James Jones win
He was a contractor for dynology which is the other side of the conspiracy
Tori is the one who supposedly was working
No one can get your lies straight
Yes it's all convoluted but
I am
Freezer
Yes it was talking s*** about Alex
Alex
I don't think
Is thrilled
Wednesday or Thursday
Azhar solo
Yes
Percent
That Millie got arrested because of this video
You got
YouTube for now
It's like it by Saturday
Which terrified
Call somebody who said
She's into some real secrets
Suddenly put it on his website
The either you seen it there's some traffic you could get from it
He's watched it
And he's like hell yeah
That seems weird to me though because
Rodger Stone does take couple hits
But he's not mad about that on Saturday figure out what you're doing Alex
Or else he would be complaining about Rodger Stone
Get your s*** together everybody get your house in order
Anyway
Alex signs off on Saturday
It probably about the movie
Think about Millie Weaver she
That we all
The Deep state
I love that timing like that is
Probably amazing delivery
Expensive but I got to pray for Billy she's in jail
Kevin Nealon
Real good
Subway
So we get to Sundays
August 6th
Steve and on Saturday Alex also did protest
At the Greenbelt
And I will say
It was an okay turnout
Okay not
Huge
There were some people there
Did they take back
The Parker what was the
Did they all get in I think so I didn't watch
A ton of footage of it but I did see
Pictures of people swimming
I also want to show on Sunday
Any does scream we're coming back next week and I'll bring enough food truck so I think
I think Alex is going to spend this off into
Progesterone
Oh you better let us enter together
Well then we'll have a picnic I guess it seems like this could turn into a series of
Outdoor
Steam really quick
Does not Occupy Wall Street
Not all is well in paradise
Alex starts off the Sunday show given a little bit of an apology about that rally
Myself and others
I apologize to the people to collapse
Stop
Oh no
Oh God
But I'd like to apologize about the couple of
The few people
The group of people who
Just to let everybody know it wasn't my ideas
It was it was it was a good day everybody said that a great time it's not
Fault that people would have heat exhaustion
Responsibility to understand
It is
Very funny to hear Alex we like this event was a success
Now I apologies that some of you passed out from heat exhaustion
Ta things
That is the thing that you say after
Successful bake sale that went on too long in front of the Walmart
And you lost
Very strange
So Alex now a days
Do you think your responsibility to have
Who are the facts of the story correctly
I think he might have
But you also has some of the facts wrong about Millie's arrest
Bicycle shop
Millie Weaver
Husband and an end
Gavin her husband's brother
In Ohio
It's not Gavin's brother
Melly's brother
Factual inaccuracies
And he says it's a couple times
I don't think there's any of you like purpose or malice
I don't I don't see any reason why I would be like a cover-up
The story
Is very close to him
You would think
You know that
Yeah
Kind of really gives you a picture of a guy who's just like I do
Total Care
Pages
We're moving.
Went
2 Barton Springs
I went to the Greenbelt we drank some beers
Next week
I don't care
Billy's into some secret s***. Going to get in the way of
My block party
The week after that we're going to be
Fucktrump
I love to party
Legendary
Is Alex
No more politics
Here's how we're going to beat the Globus
Where is starter fraternities
Coming up is it exemplifying the turn of ourselves
Bring it up Andrew w.k.
And after him by our next guest is going to be this dude to get a keg stand for like
4 minutes down Barton Springs he is so cool
Moose look I don't know what the guys name is
Until you take that put up with him for a little bit
Show the drag for a bit
God damn it I would love it
Infowars info party
Party Wars
Have you better show
So at this point
On the 16th
I think Alex is punting
I'm afraid that you might have actually done no
I think she's beat up my mom
So
Use the
Not in so many words but on Sunday
Was she arrested for anything to do
The film
Shadow
The answer is probably not
But that
What is going to end up always being thought about this because the timing of the twin sitters if so
No s***
I also the Alex is still on the angle of it being a little bit like
There's possibly a conspiracy
Trumping up an existing charge
Still like some angles
But he is
Definitely kind of
I think he's mad at Birdy
First of all that might be coloring
And he's just like
I don't know it's like anybody arrested
I don't I don't have the energy so personally betrayed
Milanese made more elaborate
Conspiracy
Conspiracies out of less
And stuck to them in the face of overwhelming evidence
And you can't even come up with that half-assed
Bulshit for Billy you're just like
I don't know I mean it just out of it
I feel like
It's got to feel shity
Because it's the same thing with like promoting her GoFundMe
Yeah because the premise of the GoFundMe
Was Jesus rested she's a journalist
And the games you're playing our that you was arrested because of some Intrepid journalism
If she was arrested because of a domestic
Violence incident the chief and two other people enacted upon her mother it becomes thing works like
Wait I thought I was supporting independent journalism I just paid $100 to help out someone who beat up their mom
Yeah like that feels bad and for Alex I think
Like
You don't have any need to do this and there's no money in it for him
Documentary
I think he realizes also like
Hey
When project Veritas puts out something it's all over Twitter trends like crazy
This didn't move the needle that much or not that upset
Do witches like the ultimate
Remove the needle kind of freedom I think a lot of people
Serta got a sense of like
Probably reason
This said this raft happen
So you look bad
Documentaries good we still on it's the Gate of all gay
No I don't think we owe
Arabic
Good
Now
Black beans
Patrick Bergey's Phyllis
Operate
Rodger cupcake me a call this morning
Evike
That General
Jones
Paul manafort net worth of them over 20 plus years he's my friend
Rodger Stone sentence
Going on
You did already know
Yeah we know
But like you said during the breaks
Representation
Apparently Rodger called in that morning
And with
So now Alex has another pair you share this documentary
Has to pull off now which is like
Documentary
About the media being
Controlled by the globalist forces
I like that
Like that
I don't want to be against that
But this guy
Like I don't like him
And he's talking to about my guy Rodger
Personal and professional lives are coming together in a way that is so
Usual for me so I'm going to say
Is it dark batteries good
But
This guy they talked
Is it
Functionally half of the documents
Because he's the guy who claims that he invented the technology
In terms of people who hat like
Both him and Tori are Central figures in the
Even more so about
I think you either of them you can get rid of whatever they're bringing to the table
Closer to a keystone
And they're both
Nonsense but
It's so crazy
It's pretty wild for me to hear Alex be like
Yes
The central focus of this documentary is a lying piece of s***
Talks very seriously and earnestly it agrees with everything that
Giant piece of s*** says
I don't worry about that my apparently independent
It was all of this she thinks he's great
Alex
Seems like he got
Yeah he doesn't like that
Rarely
I don't know if I can think of the last time I've sent this vibe from him was like
People fuk to me
We just bring it and say hey
Alex
Thanks a lot
Level
What happens
In this whole tumors is
Trump jacket
But
That is a distraction can't wait
Out of
He is mad
Is reference
Where's all the time
The leather vest that is Trump's bikers
He's not thrilled about that bass
So yeah he's decided that to Bergey's just like qanon
He doesn't like me I don't like
Alex has Rodger on
Because Rodger called him mad that morning
And because brother dies and Rodger knew him
Cuz you gone through a lot Rodger Trump gone through a lot
Amore has been you
I guess that bridge got killed so I guess he paid more there's been a lot of people paying
Interesting Alex
Interesting
That's a weird
Undercutting
Nobody's paid as much as you I mean silver
I know that Alex
Microsoft
Pedaling
Words back into separate
But I've not heard him fully commit and selected this is kind of interesting to because now
That indicates to me that the editorial position just over
Passively
Hillary
Right right
So that's interesting
Great
You don't say
They would
Actually
Fair enough
A convenience
So
Patrick Bergin
Slight against the movie
Friday
Senior film called Shadow gay
They do their own you are absolutely
And at worst Windows know about until she's been arrested
Charged with Family Violence
Looks like
Last thing she said is this guy wants to be on
He comes in
Has Rodger Stone
Rodger Stone
I like Rodger Beasley
When General Joe's
So
In the film
When you're in a film
Rodger Stone
Rodger
Running
Shadownet
It's a small part of it
It's not
I mean the actual rogerstone part is small essential credibility
Of one of the main
Repeat this is why Alex Jones is really weird
Because I can see what his thought process is
Okay yes this Patrick
Lie lie lie
About my friend Rodger Stone
I'm possibly in charge of this gigantic conspiracy
That's a lie
The rest of the stuff he's saying it's probably
The in-person Rock
Doesn't realize that it's still the Council of twelve
Yeah Bill Gates's
Yeah Alex doesn't see people like a it's it's almost like looking at every single thing
Completely unattached to other things
Like Deedee lying about Rodger doesn't implicate the truth or credibility
You should approach other statements with his lies are all a cart
Patrick
I guess so
I got annoyed every time he does that I know I'm like
Denial that like
Bababababa I'm not trying to distance
You are because you just said you not I'm not bragging but
I'm so annoyed that better
What are the things that I think is pretty interesting isn't notice
Rodger doesn't seem to be trying to solicit donations
On this episode which is
Interesting because that Sunday Monday Rodger dropped his appeal.
It doesn't come up also
Why would have never happened
No but I'm previous episodes
Indy shadowgate documentary
It discussed tell Rodger stones
PO is going to be the thing that brings down the Deep State I've Salinas Rodger was so
Clearly
And so
Obviously wrongly tried
It would be the easiest thing in the world for them to appeal this case it was going to go through was going to expose ever
Everybody
Hell or high water
Nothing was going to stop Rodger now and I'm sure that the
Dropping of the appeal had nothing to do with what happened on Tuesday when the Senate Intel report was released which game
So many more instances of Rodger Stone in contact with the
Russian
Apparatchiks
If you will
The appeal would have done it short
Today there's a lot more evidence even further against today
Descendants
I didn't see this today
And it's kind of to the point where the evidence looks
Is though
If you wanted to
You might be able to bring a new charge account
I'm going to drop that a piano
Suspicious
Barry Easter egg
If I were Alex
Sure I would be so conflicted right now cuz I'm the one hand I got this Millie's at
Screwed
Documentary is trying to try to use me
He's making me feel kind of policeman and I can't just get rid of them because he's attached to me
Yeah I can't completely without attacking the documentary
Get my employee was not my employee out of prison
Never met her before
This is complicated now at the same time is going to be
Needs to commuted sentence because he's totally guilty and I don't want him in prison because he's effective
But because he was wrongly
Prison
He doesn't to Pardon him he just needs to commute the sentence so he doesn't die in prison
Of course now the appeals drop
What the f*** like
Just because
Set on all sides by people he previously trusted to be competent
Incorrect
Millie's whole thing would be totally fine
That's not a competency
Crying issue this is like a heist movie where Alex is playing the the ocean part and then
Millie is one of the bumbling idiot ew in the middle of of a heist
You know what I say
Think they need was
Number that song
Shadowgate
Hiring better people
Touch with somebody who can help him out with that
Human Resources problem
Couple bad hires
Seriously
If I were him I would be pretty f****** pissed off at just about everybody
Check out
Begin right
Let's throw a party
Eastpointe on Sunday
Alex has to
Kind of figure out a way to thread the needle because he's like okay
She didn't get arrested because of anything in the documentary but you did get arrested
Patrick bergey was in Austin which is
F****** weird
He showed up
Dick
Way
Hi
You know what
I think this is a psyop against
Me
Friday
She gets arrested in Ohio
The police are very unprofessional
Lego hey
Wow at my door
I guess if you know what's going on with you want
Rodger stone is the Kingpin
So
Something make me think
This is done
Millie's a good person a good mom
Okay
You got two children they win
CVS
At 11 a.m.
Over an argument with her mom and broken cell phone
Three months ago where Mom admits that so I don't know why
They're grabbing Emma doing this other than
They may have been conned by the Deep state
Will show you the pill
Microphone
Police Department
Pipe it up
Maybe it's a coincidence okay
Now Alex is presenting
We were going to release the film until bergey was there because it's
The setup
For him to be like it's all about Rodger huh
I just can't believe that this
Come back to
Being entirely about him
You're wrong
I understand why you would think that because it does sound that way
It's not all about Alex
Mostly about Rodger
But that's also about Alex also
I do like the idea that Alex is like
Ifucking got screwed on this probably about I got screwed
It's a really interesting
Character
Style
Is confused on how to play the victim
Because there's that there's some pride involved
There's some confusion
I think Alex is totally fine
Trump said about me
Your reputation is amazing I will not let you or your audience down
He was,
Because of Rodger Stone
We have the president endorsements
But we're not trustworthy according to the internet operation
Messages Keith
Which swing state
Continually
Wake up and we're the Bad Guys
I've been totally Trump
I mean I really think about that
Whoever ran this
Did you do all this and get her arrested
What was Operation was happening
Full push
You buddy they really don't like you
Talking to Rodger
This is interesting to see how this sort of rationalization happens on the
The fly you know I don't like him understanding
I don't like
He's getting punched by so many people all the time
But it's
It's he's calling himself
Of course this is cuz it's elaborate it's not just you hang out with
F****** Desi weirdos
You have no standard of who you trust as experts
Employees or contractors
Emphasis what happens
Sometimes
Yet end up with some Rogue actors
Slipping through
Somebody like Millie is dumb enough to listen to one of these people nice okay awesome.
Understand
No it's a secret globalist
It's a circle
She was better if her job she would have known not to listen to these people
Red flag gone up when she realized she couldn't
Verify that the documentary that you
Sponsored and gave them free editorial control over
Cuz you were the sponsor of it you wanted to make sure it was up to your standard
Or you don't have any
Drop it on the floor
Who gives a s***
So Alex really has to clarify
Interesting
Clarification
And that is again
Cuz one of the people in this documentary is an a******
It doesn't mean it's not all
Your house Alex Jones
The fact that I was a rock
Earlier
Criticizing one of the people in the
That Millie Weaver
Was somebody in the Fillmore District
Film
Shadow game
Dad she got arrested with her husband and her husband's brother in Ohio
Believer
It was original complaint
There are they
Again he's got the brother thing wrong
I don't understand how you can be like
The information flow documentary
Is a dick
A liar someone I don't trust it all
Was good
I don't understand that.
I think if somebody were to
Watch one of Alex's
And pick out a talking head
You know I think if you know it that's just one thing I'm sure he still thinks the documentary
I don't know
Also
From what I've seen
The thing that he's talking about with Millie's mom coming out and saying that you wanted the charges dropped
Apparently somebody
Who had meli's mom as a screen
Who left like a YouTube comment
It said that
There's no verification that it was actually her mom
It is that fast how the internet works
Baie
Confirmed or any from her
Except YouTube comments
Taking that as like fully confirm gospel
Also not good
If it were me
I would
Play my handle
Would not be
Ownership of
Parent Parenthood towards the person that just pizza
The s*** out of it
I think if I were Alex
I would probably have cut bait
Like I think the
You've already said that you don't need
I mean like
Once you're already embarking down the road
She's just a contractor she does work I pay or sometimes
Like why even muddy the waters
Why you try to salvage something here
You know like I put eight years into the truth
1/8 years he's he's got his Bilter up his parts
I guess I think that she probably
Might have
Some embarrassing things to say
The NBA
Is strong with contract
Allegedly
Devon lights
So I'll accept the process information
Is there's only one conclusion you can come too
No he's a great person
But I think there's a psyop
Teaser
Here
Is a brain teaser
Is she
I don't know if I don't know I'm looking for
She got released on her own recognizance
The show on Monday
The documentary put me a bit behind
And I was laughing too hard let's get you Friday
Saturday and Sunday
David buddy
So at this point on Sunday Alex's Torreon
The Whirlwind of a weekend
Anyways recharge my batteries about Alex
Show my batteries
Already well
But I really enjoy
Now your life
Apparently Billy beat up her mom
Weirdo to his Studio Diaries play me
What song
So he have Tori in studio or on the phone excuse me now and
We've already heard
From Alex
That the documentary was supposed to come out
On Thursday
And we've heard from Pat
Bergita
Supposed to come out
Future Funk
1-day yes she has another story
Film
The film gets released their arrested
I do to my office saying rogerstone masterminds everything with no proof
I can't even begin to figure this out
Is very bizarre here's what's even more bizarre
So I spoke
On the telephone
July 20th July 20th
The grand jury returned in July
Original release date
Alright
Wow
Who I need a little bit like Alex is struggling to figure out what they think
Is going on a completely new element to this is going to make it very easy
Thanks
I think Alex is still struggling because
Did the content of the documentary and the singer John Brennan and
Little bean like
Oh yeah all the media is all lies
All that is so good
For him and he likes it
We also
Fucken hates
Patrick bergey
Tori is a lady that has the show with Millie Weaver who was arrested she was releasing a
Online doctor
Okay
Here's here's my pitched
Everybody has gone wrong
They think lawyers and s*** like that are going to keep them in line
Do you know what you should have done do you know what you do your trick out
Do you want to avoid him doing the Sandy Hooks
Guess what
To do you find somebody who's there
Conspiracy theorist
You pay them to be Petty and annoying Alex perfect he'll be like
That Sandy Hook
Make it make it personal so he takes a
You can pick you could manipulate her maybe but doing whatever you want but I think this is actually ever
Evidence to the contrary cuz he still stays
Maybe maybe not maybe they wouldn't work at all
Maybe he has such a
F****** stupid
So Alec suggest that
The film was released after the arrest intentionally
True
No that's that's not what's going on
Amazon for a while they were just
Weather
The arrest finally got it
Yeah I would say that maybe the film was done for a while and then this was the best opportune moment for them to
To suggest that it was because of his arrest
They must have been
A little bit of them
This is an opportunity
Totally a whole lot of coincidences going on because I find it hard to believe that without any evidence that I had to
Time they would know
Like the date that they were going
Macomb execution warrant because Patrick bergey being in Austin
If you imagine that that was part of a setup
Yeah that is too much for me to believe
A clear opportunism General Vibe on this
Iida I think Alex
He's probably telling the truth in this case because he has no idea
The same time supporting them
He's in a weird like
Tell the truth I don't know what's happening
And so it would make sense to me that they had finished it
And they were just taking rad
Which I think that's generous I think it was
Sucks
Editing
Maybe I don't know
Arrested in somebody a few hours and then like
A few hours later they like
This is the best possible time to do this
So drop it
Sartori
Giochinos has been arrests
And so we got to deal with that turns out you can get arrested for
Anybody
Anyone arrested
One person's words to Alex if I want to I can go down to my local police
This all the time
Fighting our cell phone broke
3 months ago
It wasn't even a fight
It was the second time they caught her
Recording
Documents and serial numbers in computers and logs
What I love about that
I love two things about that the first is Alex's just like the responses hilarious
And the second thing is
You got the response to Tori saying something that he himself said that video he put out on Saturday
That's weird that's very weird
So Tori as a new detail about the Iraq
Wasn't in the video at all but apparently
The power was cut from the house
I was I was riding
Where it's at on the network
Spanish
60%
10 minutes later
They were rested their power was
Power Wheel
So there's a lot more power was cut
So this isn't about just arresting people
And I know there's going to be a cop for me tonight
They cut the power that's huge
Interior
What's their evidence for the power bank
I'm not sure
Tories side it stopped
Uploading
Because she got the stopped uploading
I don't know but it is to convince Alex or something
Now this is my favorite thing from Tori's.
The two of them she's able to smooth over Alex a little bit on the Rodger Stone stuff
I love Rodger Gray
I am at she's trying to explain to Alex that that's like
His whole version of it like
Birdie says that Rogers masterminding everything show
It's not what he said of a documentary Alex
It's a confusing back-and-forth between them
But she's able to make everything fine by being like the best
Article
Alright
Unfortunately date falls apart a little bit
When
Restart
Explain her feelings
About Edward Snowden
Oh no
Alex
Doesn't quite like what she has to
To say this is really a
We can disagree on that Julian Assange is not in the same boat
Caused
Creative
Windstream
Over-the-year up-to-date
The only reason he bristled blue is because he realized he was
As the song pure
Get immunity
Exactly
Okay because
Those opposed receive Communications from people that are
Do you think about snow
The thing is maybe we can
Fingers cuz he was registered
Snowden
Whistleblower protection
She does
Their payroll
Snowden has been good
Perfume
Glorified
Reinforces
Every single piece of data
Pictures whatever you want
How's it going to say is shipped
Let's be clear on what he did
Verizon
He controlled all architecture to put everything overseas
Don't ask you to Quest architectural
So don't do this
Brennan did that in 2003 with Saudis
Sandburg
I don't know I don't know
Did you see him there
So now we have discredited
The other voice other documents
Elsa
Still great documentary documentary I have some serious problems with both
Of the people that buy non-employee talk to but
Jerry
Why would they do you say that
I don't understand why anyone would act that way the problem with that is that means
What is capable
Oh yeah
All the other interactions videos suspect
Least a little bit and and I rarely see pushback
And the fact that I was pushing back
Is not a good sign for these folks
Highly doubt it
You know
It's a really interesting position to be in because you know I watch
Shadowgate
I looked into these folks
I found them to not
Certain tests
But I have
Credibility they didn't seem like people I would take their word on stuff
And it's really interesting that Alex and I are on the same page
Very rare it really is
Both of you
Exactly
Is pretty good
You are conclusions slightly different
Possibly bricks
Baby
Take it personally
No it's
You know by the end of Sunday's show you get the sense that he doesn't
One of them for sure
The other
Subtly signals
Will this last quick cure and the show ends of Alex distancing himself
Even further
Against himself and Rochester
Here's all I know
He says get something later contractors people iSpa
Whether it's
Paul Joseph Watson or weather
It's Millie Weaver weather
Weather in Hawaii
Content creator
Sports
Here is some support
I really thought about the mission
Film
Never saw it
I saw the trailer I wanted the film I wanted to promote it
She's arrested right when it's coming out
Do the tenants at my door
Rocket scientist
Well
I love God I love Jasmine I love you but I'm not running
Adora Dater
I just say something's going on
What it is
Who's good and who's bad
The bottom of it
For me whatever I find outs going on with us
I just got cute art stuff written all over it
I'm going to give you that information
I solved it
But I got a good idea what's going on
Brennan is just trying to sabotage our movement
No
Freedom and justice
David overall home
Shonettas mixtape
Just so you know everybody
Solve this mystery surround yourself with s*******
This is so much listening to
Two people on Project Camelot go
I think the grades are behind this
No no
I think the rapper
Exactly the same level of like
Fine fight it out amongst yourselves in the star
Neither of your answers will end up being correct
Tell Jordan there's something interesting that happened
Over the course of this weekend was the andaz Monday Tuesday rolled around
I noticed
Monday
Alex
Had his Saturday report
Where you talked about Melly
A video on his Alex Jones
He also had his Sunday broadcast
Now
And his Sunday show
Gone
They're gone from Bayside radio.
They are not in the
Thread
I'm looking at it right here
They have a video of Rodger Stone
Talking about Trump's brother tonight's celebrate in the
Nba.com
In the spring
He has a show from Friday August 14th
It goes to the the park
Boston nights at the park
Rodger Stone eulogizing
Some video about Maxine Waters
And then
August 17th
Monday
There's no Sunday show on here
It's it's been taken down
Interesting
They don't do that he doesn't retract
You know they don't do that I don't see that happening
Regularly with Alex's show
Where things are just gone
And I think it's
Probably because this isn't fair
Maybe a little baby a little bit of baby a little bit of
Yeah
I understand it sucks
You get
You chopped I think Alex is going to put a
Horse's head
Saturno
Obviously somebody will refuse
I want to say that I wish him well
No I want to say I wish you more and utter confusion for forever
Yeah it was pretty fun
Watch
About shadowgate helps understand
It makes it more enjoyable for us to see him
Competently
Alex
I mean look I I feel like my advice would be like hire better people but as soon as it comes out of my mouth
The path of the career
Has led to a point where you can't get anyone good to work for you
Give these people to work for you
Sure
Billy's going to be able to get some great footage of yelling at protesters
Pretty regularly you'll be able to get that it'll be great
But
Whenever he gets a shoes
You might end up with something like this cuz she has no instincts
And be like this guy is the greatest expert ever
You should have run the other way and blocked him on Twitter like Dan bongino
Pennywise
What's on
It never occurred to me
If this guy is
It's telling me
Even people that I
It's like even people that are in my unit
Refuse to talk to
Maybe I should
And said she was like
This is a scoop
For me this is a scoop that's too dangerous for everyone else to touch
Yep
Jordan
I felt like it's always difficult to figure out exactly how to end
Offended
Doesn't feel all that gratifying to have a wrap-up of
So my point is Alex is dumb
There's a little bit
Hi I'm calling this
Do you understand
New knowledge
Phone number
Call Dad
Because
You said that
Phone number
Why not
So I think
Think what I've decided my call was going to be
Couple months ago
You guys are
Twitter
Instead
Qanon anonymous
Crossover
When
And
You both
Very nice
Twitter
He's known for
I realized later the whole reason
I found your show
Embarrassing
So I didn't
Online
You guys have a great shell behind
We appreciate that
That's a good impulse to feel ashamed honestly
The fact that he
Went out of his way to call us and call him cell phone
I respect him more
Yes perfect point and that is that I don't know how to make a custom echo.and
Message so it is just a weird voice
That doesn't say knowledge fight or anything so I noticed a trend of a lot of people's messages
Start with
No it's right
Every time
I say hello they don't know that it's me
Toledo message
Call
Boys
What a what a voice
Deep f****** voice that coming from me
30 bullhorn with a big head
Hydrobike
Heights
I am a non-binary
Furry
And I've been about
A little while now and I'm going
Catching up
I really appreciate the
The show
It really is
Something I enjoy listening to at work
My day a lot
Appreciate you guys
Peeps
Sky
So hard
Jordan 1
Can you start jiggle
I lose it
You start laughing
How does a little I feel like
Because
The episode
It about
And
Call Amrita
About it
Tell a joke
And the first
Brine
Alex
I know you guys
And the
God
It is really
Thank you Ashley
Sandy Boulevard
She just giggled and I was like
This is the happiest I've ever felt much better than you
That might just be because of familiarity with you
Exhausted
What's the right word white noise
Ringing Sanam
Number to Goodwin
This tiny bull horns really made some waves
I think it I think my next tattoo
What is a bullhorn
And then next to it like a giant quarter
You know look for scale
Recorder
Bethel conceptual that way I have to go to pull off with the tattoo right away
A scaled-down
Walmart baby with little measurements
I feel like I don't know this
Recommend
No that was my idea she actually didn't say that
Let's get this next
Lawrence calling from
Sunny New Mexico
Nothing like hell I reach
The knowledge spider
Brian Auger the British
Sort of boy
Inspire confidence
Harrah's I was just wondering
If you guys could do like
I'm going to
Jordan
Origin app
Like growing up in a cult
I know
Highway
Michelle keep up the great work
We have great news
Episode
The website
Can find episodes
And also to point out that we have a lot of
Call ziv ComEd
It's a real B also recording
Securities in the future
Their questions that kind of require
Maybe some props for larger conversation
And so I feel like they would be more appropriate in an isolated like sort of special setting as opposed to
As part of our episodes question being able to play the clip of
Personal info
Jordan
Is on there.
One last call here
Ancient Egyptian artifact
I was working
How old
Think this guy was looking for 773
Guys I don't
I don't know
Mommy's we got it all
All right well this is the phone mailbag
Oh boy
Until then
We Are the World
If you could please find a bail fund or local charity in your area
To help out with
Until then
Darrell rundus
I'm also distrustful of
The people in that documentary
Alex