Air Jordan X swetik
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Knowledge fight
Nick.com
Jordan Jordan
What's up
I can't stop
Is it worth
Right now
Switch to the nature and you know the only way I can really satisfied
It within my middle of
Chicago existence
Car having too much access to like
The wild
No
Address
I'm experiencing a little bit of nature vicariously
I know I brought it up of the flowers on the Cucumber couple episodes
More flowers
All I want to do is Garden
Very weird turn in my life shake that is now
Let's get a car
Cantaloupe
Download by the way
Outback
Whatever you want
Is the way to go
I just want to sit around going to talk about
Are you I want you to grow something
So good
Help you with joy
Phone number
No I'm not a good person I've never been
Pumpkins
To eat it later
Record
If you cut it up how would you know because it's something beautiful
Find
Whatsyourprice
Focus on the show.
The new album by glass animals
Okay
Fantastic
Specifically the song
Really good
You're turning into a huge program
Two things are great give me a little high-pitched falsetto voice
Sure
Okay give it a look
Got to give it give it a listen I've not heard that this time
17th through 19th 2020
August
This is a COO
I guess so.
Millie Weaver
We started the week
Wednesday we talked about Alex's immediate response
Who are the people who
It is weird
Images
Beginning middle and end if yeah it's very satisfying
Doesn't seem like there's more trouble trouble coming for sure
So to be done with it
Dead and buried with Alex's embarrassment
Burgits so much
It turned out
That's Alex
Terminated his working relationship
Well she was never employed
I don't know if
But I would assume it's true
Benzema a real reason to make that up
Then to challenge Alex
Steal a $10,000 bet weather
Then Caitlin another Infowars non-employee started
Good s*** on Melody that got into a fight
And Millie tweeted where we go 1
Berrington Levy
A bad week I do like her immediate
Spring crafts
That's the smartest thing I've ever seen her do
Tori and
Maybe even Burg Dark UFO
So I can quit her experts
But she's been hanging out with to make this film
Shadowgate
I think that they might have
Help him steer her I think she's been aware we all go but we can always choose been working in forward
Her contract
Possibilities for the future
17th was Monday at May 19th is Wednesday
That. Of time where
Milly got out of jail
On Monday
Gender hearing for the judge
And then on
She had been let go
Infowars
Galaxy
I was surprised
Go to signed up and are starting to show
Thomas thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Text Wallace
Thank you Brian
I'm a policy wonk
Next
Not as a lot of contract terminated
I don't know I guess I don't forget started one
One just one more difference between me and my rainbow snatch
So much your nail polish a rock
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you Whitney
What
Augusta Whitney
It could be next nikkei's
I'm a policy wonk
Negative
Text Sarah
Sarah Sarah
Are you very much Texas red
I just nuts
If you would like that
You can take that generosity
Make a documentary
Talk to a couple lose your contract
With your
Primary in Florida
I don't know just
That one way out the rail.
My brain just like
Delightful
So when start hero I should make one direction
One of the charges was burglary
I was just using the term because that's how the
Conversation was framed by
Charged with robbery
Much more fun word
Break-ins
Second-story man
Descend from somewhere
Slippers language that
So on the 17th
Princess drop
Most people do not crap in the pool
Unless they're baby unless they're
We've learned
From Alex
This is not a social contract
Where there's a neighborhood pool
Everyone
Take a dump
That is a phenomenon
Oh-so
It is
Play music
I guess you can open
I give it to myself
Episode
It's just treading water just
Rambling about Satan
Under the wings of absolutely
You're missing the embryonic level
The big guy right there
I want
Shellbug
Explanation of the
The devil
Never seen those those movies about Catholic iconography
Are the order
Here's what the problem with it
He knows where evolved too far beyond him out wearing an embryonic stage
That's what
That's what Calabrese Peach preached from the pulpit
Do you say masks
It's always what he say
That's true
Yeah so the devil is jealous of human because we can build things of the devil
Citric acid to building is stopped
The Shakedown.
This is
Show about the dangers
Right
Is wonderful.
It is it's so much of this stuff
What's happening with Millie you as a real house on fire kind of issue on Monday
Didn't get to the situation until maybe a half hour into the show
And not that great
Let's get into the Millie Weaver situation
Vonage
Avomance
The tag place
I just go with what I really believe the true test
Now that implies
Wow did do that
That is basically what he say
Blindsided on Friday
Because
Elliott said she was right in front of the film
Saturday understand film hit behind
That's great
Your freelance
No
But I had one lady that's in the Philemon
Then it was put away
Coming into the show
This story is well told
Nelly Furtado
In the film
He's in Austin
Let me know when
Show me some clips of the film
We'll set you up and Studio
Well nothing happened on that Wednesday Thursday and then she calls me in the morning
I don't answer
And I called Aria
The producer
What's going on with this
Flowers
Millie Weaver arrested we're getting
What the hell
Ohio
SWAT team
Call Jesus Watson
Am I okay
Victor's for the film
In the film
Free
Millie doesn't own saying I don't get that I'm not distancing myself in the film
Don't know what's in it
Promoting
Trusting my guess I'll just nice guy
I had nothing to do with you
Okay okay
So
Why is he telling me this story like if he's old
When
No one is in trouble for anyting
But in Infowars that's that's fine have fun with that you don't fire somebody just repeating up their mom and info
Universe
Seem like it seems like
It seems like Millie was fired specifically for opportunist
Yeah
What is the you can't do that
Totally transparent
She got fired because Rodger Stones name was in that documentary
That's what happened
Rodger Stone said get rid of
Kylie Jenner
There's nothing else like this
Kinds of
Shady shenanigans on people it would not matter at all
He had
Temerity
2.2 finger towards Rodger Stone and that means you are out
Infowars
That seemed right up
But this this telling of the story I think is
Sounds fairly accurate
Because it's convoluted
Is boring
Incredibly boring
If it makes
Little sense
But it's kind of kind of how are you
Flyers
They're on my payroll.
Hey you know what this one went sideways
Easy when there are no consequences in any direction
I think the consequences are
Rodger looks bad
Does he
I don't know
So Alex is clear that he does not think of his arrest was in any way related
But
Really suspicious
Was to
Stop cuz it didn't stop the film
567 days before
Type something up
People thought something
Supposedly just going to release the film
How the guys here in town waiting to come on my show and then I'm never sent the film
No technical problems will get a copy to you
Aamir Khan YouTube
And then to find out
Rogers
You know
Oh my God
Eleaf Vape
The internet to do research these folks themselves
Figure out what they think
Paul Watson
Or Millie weaver or
Very little feedback
As long as her putting material out and buy the new world order
And we get great content to fight the new world
Alarm people
As it happened here
It's an inch
Like if he was there if we were bar and he said you know
If somebody makes claims about you without any evidence that kind of makes
You feel bad
Lincolnton instant reaction of just like
Dare you
You said that you son of a
Think
About Arthur.
If you feel this way
Oh great apply that to other human be
No no cuz they're all global
Decided that
And
This is Monday
He's very clearly being like
Millie's f****** Shawn
People becoming famous and people
Interfacing nnnnn people
Has come in and they try to sabotage by try to do all this stuff you know it's like I want to embrace
I told you you're going to get it for the child kidnapping ring
100 plus thousand dollars a year I'm just a horrible person
Rodger Stone
I don't I don't know
John Monday
Two more days apparently
Call Buy HR representative father
Real familiar
Ha go away
Yep that's not good that's bad
Very funny
Rude pretty funny so funny
Pretty I just love how
Millie could never have imagined that
This was how it was going to
I think that's what I enjoy most
Probably should have no clue she had no clue that this was even a possibility
Surprising enough for a front
It really it really goes
The show some
But I think
Alex like
Billy was
The property for him you know if you're a team to the franchise player
The Infowars
Umbrella cuz you have people who are like
Who are there who are
Famous like Paul Joseph Watson
He's too famous
His face is recognizable
How many people like Savannah Hernandez Harrison Smith
No one really knows what they look like they could blend into a crowd pretend that there
You know not with Infowars
But those people aren't really all that
Good
Not good at getting attention
Conversely Paul Joseph Watson
Talking with people
Someone like Kaitlin Bennett
Israeli people
She also gets gallon everyone yells gun girl
Diaper protest
Yeah you're not going to be
They have those like
Problems with their ability to go out
Where's Millie had like almost like a real Center
Of that
She had
Her own
Popularity
Her fans
Over
Exposed as someone like Kaitlin Bennett
Did she could get away with
Doing some
What kinds of
No one knows that she should her pants
Before it shows up
She was somebody who had
I mean not a lot of talent potential
Usefulness
She was young 229 documentarian
She's somebody who Alex
Could have really been
And it seems like was very invested
Like brake is happening
Over what just appears to be
It shows me something it just
There is
Glaring
Imagine if if Alex
Just been like
Woohoo
I knew Russia
And then he's dead
Look it's that easy
Texas fired
Obviously I've never met Alex before
Decided to terminate our relationship
Juvenile
I don't know if it's as simple as just like she touch it on Rodger and Magic
I don't know it's very confusing
Here's the
I feel like in a normal environment
If you were working at a company as an on-air
And you
Beat up your mom I got arrested
I think it would be
Retired but that's a regular thing
It we're just Jada it was wearing the Infowars universe
For sure
And here's another thing
If you fund it a documentary
You probably get final Kyle there's that
No
When you fund a documentary you get a burlap bag
Some guy who's in it who you've never met
Largely Alex's phone
Mismanagement
Stop
Haha
Oh yeah
Better training of his people
Maybe maybe that's part of the problem
Liberty
That you're
End up having Hands-On time with Windows
Like I don't want to go to war with her already
I get the sense from listening to this episode
Is that she got setup
By Patrick Bergin
Bertie cetera
I got rushed out
Just felt weird
Agree
I think Millie is a good person
That's what you say before you find somebody for sure
Just imagine being 29 year-old mom
On YouTube
And she's beautiful and she smart
And there's always people that come around
How people
The other with the wrong crowd dancers I know what those people have told
Ignore the secret weapon
Check my business
Then something blows up
Assault
Fuqua.
Has Rodger Stone
Filmed
Stupid over all the films good though
I'll just go with it
What is a hat why
Alright
So is the general Vibe of what
Hillary smells like evidence
That she is a demon can we say that you call that's gossip
Which he's calling her gossip calling her demon with Avenue
Sources
Out of nowhere kind of assumed
Politically
Connected person influence events
Perhaps even global-scale
Consider colluding with a
It's
It's an it's interesting
It is
I mean like
Obviously I have no f****** idea what's going on
With any of this
I'm going to take Alex's right
Millie
Tried to do her own thing
She relied on really
Dodgy a sources
It created something that runs
Counter to one of the main
Pillars of it
For five years
Donuts infallible
Right
I don't
I think I think he's right
I look at it differently
Of what appears to have happened
Is correct
Alex is about
Documentary arguing that stone is the Kingpin of stuff
Which makes sense
It's the way that you create the strawman
That you need for the argument of this is offensive
Reality
It's no big deal
I'd like to imagine
In a better world
She would have been fired
Just because it was so bad
Good buddy thanks for the program
Which is not
And then
Get to talkin a little bit more about Melly
I took away from this the implication that
Billy stabbed him in the back
But you have no water
Single Reed
Lockstep Rockefeller Foundation
Prison
Global police.
Industrialized world
Population collapse
You know what that means
Sitting here
Telling you this is going on you can verify it
Is change the subject to infighting
Just like the race rioting
And the divide and conquer their empire
Is divided and
Conquer people
Accident 1
Classically
That done. Over and over again by people we think are French people that weave
And finances at everything and good
It just makes
Myself
I wonder how are we turning out so many
Twisted screwed-up people
Or Justice or Freedom all they know is betrayal and lies he's obviously
Oh yeah well I think he's also including all of the Joshua
Yeah
He has to think that publicly
Do we keep getting
These types of people at Infowars
It's a mystery there's so many of those it almost appears that there is
Mynced
Crucial problem because business is rough
Alex gets off the topic of millionaire documentary and he's talking about how like
Hey man
I8
Generally hold
Back
From calling out
The globalist by name
But God told me to stop that
I know the most effective thing I do
Calling different globalist out by name and putting messages directly out to them
Conscious level
Payback
That's the one time you can really piss them off and then go ahead
Read legally
Suicidal things
Suicide
But needed Willie
Holy Spirit has told me to go ahead and attack
Literally the whole East
Skills
Put everybody on notice
Alright
My Wells.
Hellboy
That sounds right
Wow
That's a bummer
I did not realize that
This was sandbag
I didn't know the 25 years
I know that
Screaming at the top of my
About to die
Baby
Ridiculous I just can't I find that offensive
He says that he's got like
Call Lefty's globalist
Couple days
Is he using his enhanced oratory skills after
No
Almost the same if not worse okay
The next level
And about trying to hold back
It's just not going to flow so
Can probably have some starts but I'm just going to let him have it
And
You know that Ms a bomb detonate starting to build
Enforce
Because the whole thing's going next level
Animes going next level
And so I've been holding back
Ananda
It's like a storm that I'm not there yet you see it blowing across the water
Nature Sheila pretty start moving at once actually there
When does a break-in it's like
Now I know what
I think that Alex fired his lawyer or something maybe
What it what do you do stuff like
Right to fear getting people hurt all I think of is all the times for getting people
And what he says he's going to stop holding back
I want to start f****** behaving like I always
Like a complete
For hurting private citizens and
I don't know what else he could be talkin about
Start naming
Cool globalist sewer behind everything
Should come get even sloppy order
Just doesn't think about things that could get me in legal trouble
Got to go Full Speed Ahead
Are going to bankrupt me
Literally have nothing to lose by acting like I have something to lose
Borrowed time
Financial standpoint
Moving money around
Actually I've never met Millie Weaver
But
I think now is a good time to remember that next level
We've been holding back
Yeah
Next level
Talking more s***
I think next level would just include it
Picking on more obscure people like
All kinds of people
A freeway going on
That's what's going to happen
So
It's going to take is not great
It terms of him talking about
Situation
Into the 18th
Parking take the day off
It's on days like these that tell you really
Understand how transitory in
Short life is
T-Bone
The other guys dog that is okay
Good to be here when you today
Concussion
I think it was the wrong lesson from the movie whip
Cut that one
Man
Like
Just don't don't come in
It could be dangerous
Go to the doctor
Mild concussion
Not something you say on are you starting a broadcast like
Due to the T-bone
I heard that
T-Bone
Probably
So the night before Rodger withdrew his his his appeal
Nothing to do with it
Immediately released
Certainly.
Despite be possible minor concussion
You got to
For everything
Alright I got up
This morning. Slept last night
He just texted me at like 6 a.m.
The article that has stone cold tryst.com it's also at infowars.com
Why I decided to withdraw the appeal of my unjust conviction in the
Mueller Witch Hunt
Now we all know
But he could never get a fair hearing
The article he stayed up all night to write
You said lengthy which means you didn't read it
Add forgotten what they've done
What they've done to Stone
Call Ben
You didn't forget anything
And it's just a really boring interview
Basically just like I'm dropping this because
Hey my appeal won't be fair either that's good
That's good
I like that you know a lot of a lot of Freedom Fighters are really I really recognize
Guides for in the face of
Defeatable
Yes
They were like
Not worth it to much efforts I'm just so you know
Ships are rigged
And no I'm not giving refunds
Nelson Mandela
It's the garage or like really a brazen
Funny as hell these people
This hard with no consequences
Pretty remarkable
Once you find your Niche man you can really ride it out
I know that
I don't think I want to make a big deal out of it cuz it could just be saying we're like Rogers
Tired
But he seems
Not interested
At all
There is a very weird vibe
Between him and Alex
Frosty
It's not a good vibe
Final Cut
Give your employees
Hundreds of thousands of dollars you idiots are you put my name in the streets like that
I know he's not happy about that
Separated from Millie's
Rogers to be happy about that
Yeah I don't know I like I said I don't want to make a bigger deal out of it then
Then.
Disappearance
Not a good interview
It almost like there were a couple points where I was like
Rodger
Eden is he trying to flip it on Alex
I don't know I think it's just in my head
We got a lot of issues going on right now but post office sure love people are pretty
Concerned about Trump very clear overtures towards
And Alex has a
Way to spin this
Maybe
Play the next hour I'm not kidding
Trump stealing mailboxes
The mailboxes in the mail-in ballot
As a secret weapon there their hyping up the post office
We'll go out and get the balance and fill in granny
This is really all about
Not protecting the very vital service
This country to operate
Weather radar
Sleep or hail or
Is it bad junk
Mail delivery
I mean like
Anna Auto really basic level
The notion of
How much
Widespread damage
It would be done by
Like a capable post office
Like
Exxon it
Astonishing
Even think about
That is so Essential Medical
One gigantic
It is
It's
It requires prosecution
But the fact that Alex is trying to put a break
Post office
Dismantle mailboxes
Whatever Alex haddish
Call
Call Santa
Is a theory about Alex's car accident from that morning
The calls are received in California
Thank you Alex I wanted to mention to you that there are parallels between the two thousand
16 into 2000
Election
Namely the fact
That you were T-Pain this morning and at
Rodger Stone was T-boned
That election but he didn't mention it this morning
And you know I know you mentioned about
A Gatorade but there's nothing that you could have done to prevent yourself from being T-boned
Real quick is the Gatorade is a Alex
Because he looked down and grabbed his
Is Gatorade
This morning and the fact
Choose look down actually
Saved your life because you would have
Pinhead on the driver
And you should call on Yahweh
And ask him in the name of Yeshua hamashiach to put
The ring around you and your family because you don't know how much
Danger you're in because
The shadow gay film
Well sir I know this mini rex
Like yep
I don't I don't I don't think that's
Because of this
Sorry a guy I hate that I'm firing up my non-employee over
Spell that's why
Highway buddy
Body call upon Yahweh
So Alex has
He has a guest
Dr. Mercola
Wacky dude
Big girl big supplement guy to G-Eazy
Disaster
Nihilism
And stuff
But I do want to give
Mercola props
This dude
Is
Really good
The pro in
Promotion
Information
Read it
Read the message to individuals like the churches
Members of Black station
I know next month
Million views at minimum
Tell Heather perspective that is a little more because of my position
Only reason.
Congratulations
Jojo
Now there's that
Kind of nuts
We'll see if Alex's
Augusta tomorrow I wouldn't be too surprised by that but I was very surprised
If he ends up promoting
Someone else
Very very surprised
Listen I'm going to take my time
To make someone else
Money doesn't sound
No probably not
Yeah that's like
You get booked on a show and your friends are like
Give me on that show I don't book that John 100%
Also dr. Marco maybe a little bit
Not up-to-date on Alex's
Shadowgate situation
Congratulations on 190 what are you reporters put together surveillance gate that was a really brilliant
Yama color
Toothache
No you didn't call Chad not surveillance
If you had you would know
We're angry at each other
Didn't go didn't go great for me Mercola got caught in a lie
DD Rambles for a bit after response that
Boring interview dr. Mercola
Snooze
So we come in on the 19th all right
On the previous night on Tuesday was that Laura Loomer won her
Primary
The good news is there's a mass Awakening happening resistance is intensifying not just trim around the world and Laura Loomer
More votes basically than the other two candidates combined
Unbelievable
Great going Laura
Laura Loomer quite a bit on this podcast
And
America
I think that my feelings
Should be pretty clear
Oh yeah
I think that it's an embarrassment any political party that she could make it through a primary system
Primary
I think it's a real indictment of the state of politics
She's a guaranteed win in the
The first
In the in the general election
I think that Frankie has a pretty good chance
Of winning
Election
I think the
With the right messaging
It would be tremendously easy you would help
You would hope
I bet if it might if I was in like a debate
And I was just like
Mike Kennedy wants to
Kill all Muslims
To genocide I want no genocide I feel like a rational
People pick me
Record of her doing incredibly embarrassing thing
Infowars
Good for you
Lesbian office probably
I think I think
Any competent
General election strategy
I will be effective
Against what she has to bring which is right
Publicity stunts
Bigotry
They certainly have
Approach
I don't think so I mean
Really bad at 4
But I I don't
Erwin primary as like he's going to win this isn't General
Exandria winning the
It's not the same thing
Is at least a competitive Alexa
Yeah yeah
Who in the general app
Everything's that I know about Laura Loomer
I just don't think it's going to work
20% for Steve Bannon
Yes
Patience for his appeal but is now dropped
Millie was raising funds after she got arrested
Assumption
Something to do with her dangerous documentary 170,000 dollars donated to the
Right
Steve Bannon
Fraud committed fraud all the time
A really simple
Look at this person
She used to date a guy named Baked Alaska
Anyway
Celebration party was
No I wish you could have been there
The witness that because we truly did
Cancel culture
Everybody who has been cancelled from
By myself
Milo yiannopoulos Rodger Stone
And even Faith Goldy they were all there
On stage
Really it was just a big middle finger to the
Silicon Valley
Haha
That's fun I mean if that's your definition of conservative
You think less of conservatives than I do
Here's my ears my ad
I'm running against Laura
Safe gold
At the celebration party
DC
See look at it
Just be in front of it
The board to keep in mind
Laura Loomer has no interest in governing
She has no interest in being in politics for the sake of
She doesn't want to read bills and like points like minutiae
Within the halls of Congress
She doesn't want to do this just give a f*** about those things they're going to put her on the appropriation
He committed to have real power
This is really what this is all about
Single-handedly
As the Republican nominee for Florida 21st
Presented
Do the doj
Prosecute
Mark Zuckerberg
For committing perjury because now
They are actually guilty of committing election interference because they are
Dragonsong District
Florida 21
You and I both know
They are not
Center political
First of all that statement was from
The past
This is this is basically what the game
Spycakes
Essentially on subway to get back on Twitter
AMC
Her getting into the the race and winning the primary she gets
Grandstand and make this whole
This is a criminal action that use
Press conservative
It's just a facilitation and continuation
Of the online culture War nonsense.
Handcuffing herself
The doors
Specific
Pics of a farming build
She really wants to make sure the people know
What zone is
Available in the
Districts in Florida she is going to go to bat for her constituents of which she knows
Get the f*** out
Alex has no social media
Give me
Just
Oh my God it's
Beautiful
It's beautiful outside
Now that is actually in the general there will be a lot of those
Nefarious
Rodger
Floating around
Because of the potential that they can have to use her as a condom
Great piece on her and The New Yorker
Embedded with her for a while and
Cool boy that's who I want representing me and Congress
Corazon forbidden Alex
Full speed
Aurora train
Which takes up most of the rest of the show just like
I just don't care
Oh f*** off
Coming up
Graphic novel
Believable
Really graphic novel I don't understand what it is
Apparently there's like a book
But the pages have videos or something
I don't know maybe could Digital Book I don't understand love it I don't care Alex
Really fully explain it all that well
I don't know I don't care
Things to say
Business
He's not a psycho
You said he was a psychic
But he's not like
He has is from reading all right
You know I'm not like
John the Revelator
Atmos having a vision
The godson angel now
I know I'm
Reading
Applications
Put out by the John Birch Society and others
So you are
I didn't believe so I went
Helmut Schmidt the German Chancellor
Flint
And I went and got the book
Where they admitted all of it
Said man this is horrible
Here's Alex admitting that he has not read Carroll Quigley
Infowarsstore.com in the tragedy and Howe
That's an 11:00 Pages or so
Rossion William gaspers
Bookshelf on Skype
Watching us on TV
Where the Georgetown political science Professor Bill Clinton
Louis centeno
Admits they control liberalism can
Conservatism fascism
And the trilateral commission and all of it is meant to bring in World corporate government
And it's only meant to look like there's the illusion of choice
In politics I'm paraphrasing quotes
This book and I've actually read almost the whole thing
I said I probably read 800 pages of it over the years
Doesn't mean I skip over some of the Mortal factoid
Inside baseball stuff
So Alex didn't get this
All these books
Maybe he just sort of skimmed of those books and read the
Society materials and then
Knows that you sound
Like a lunatic
If you're a John Bircher in 2020
Protect
John Bircher
All kinds of Christian identity non-central then you end up with Alec
I think the libraries
Kenwood EX
You do not like a wholly
Grounded is up
Interesting experiment
Ban Alex from libraries
And see if he cares
Do you love me from things
Don't tell him he's
Do you have to tell him cuz he has to fight against it
Tell him
Alright
And see if he find out
Cuz if he finds out naturally can go crazy
Here's an interesting way to do this I don't know how we would logistically
We could tell Alex
It's that we've got a bunch of witches
Kids together cast a spell that makes him unable to read
Came to prove us wrong you would have to read
This might be
The best reverse psychology we can do
Alex is not ready because
He hasn't
Yeah I just think he said it was lengthy
It's not like
I'm not
Begrudging Alex for not reading tragedy and hope that is his choice
You want it and not reading it
Is my complaint kind of
Phoenicia
Control
I have to take my videos down
Is trying to figure out
But but but they don't have any other knowledge
Yeah
Kentucky shark
And he has been there
Coast to Coast
You talking about the original Hanna-Barbera cuz it's a very bizarre reference if you're talkin about
Coast to coast is also a bizarre reference no matter what
And it doesn't land
That's not good
31 last clip year in cuz I don't care about listening to David Icke talk about his
Yuval is a possession
Says this
About to BBC there
Satan things when I was younger
Dislike really Disturbed
Did you ever see what I've seen I do it on TV but I saw some growing up in Dallas
When will say this when they make that
Phases or the
Pacers made by Arc or the faces made by the Hillary
Call Sharkey now
Newsom
Obscene
Strange things
That's a great save
Can do
Because
Stupid question
I'm not going to get it
Alex is just trying to rationalize why he can call whoever you want to be
The face that only demons can make humans can't copy it
4 Bonanza
Who is also a vampire hunter
And he's like I kill all these vampires how do you know
A joke
Monica
I've seen a lot of faces on a lot of people
Trying to think of other like classic
People who had like soda
The motivations Coronavirus
Robin Williams died
The demon
Yeah there's a lot a lot of folks
Features
There's some voices but only demon
Yelp
Humans cannot die there a verb
Just drove right into the white papers
Episode has a lot going on for it
We've entered back
Into info
Yeah
By this
Like the weekend was f****** exciting as hell
MN
It just fell apart
Alex decided to reject
What was going on with Nelly
Behind-the-scenes clearly must have been communicating with her at all and the working relationship
Wednesday
He's not bringing it up on the show and pretend like Shadow gate doesn't exist
Like Tuesday and Wednesday showed Rodger defense
For his like a boil
It's important
To drop stupid interview with Mercola
It just feels like
I find I found that to be disappointing I found it to be an insult
You are a really cooking with gas when you were
Being mad about what I'm saying
I'm really disappointed on his decision.
I think he has to
Getting into the mud with these people is not a good idea
Yeah he's making the right
I'm disappointed because
My life would be infinitely better if he was like
This is where we die
Hill is what's going down
Millie Weaver
Tooth and Claw either bergey goes down arrivals
To get a deal play more with a tie
Exact
Most of these other people look at Matt gaetz
This f******
Good dude
Is
No good this is going to be a mess
I don't want to be involved
I just gave you and I think I'm going to do a dime
That's what I look at you think
You're going to if I talk to you you don't get the game War place
Exactly
You can play. It's like Michael Madsen in
For the High Senior a psychopath wildcard
And I don't want nothing
Do with Utah panniers off
That's what that's not even helped us steel chip what's going to happen is you are going to
I don't know your game
Here's here's what I would say
You got to know when to drop your appeal
And it's the day before it's revealed that you did even worse
And she doesn't appeal
He's going to think know we actually can win this
Probably doesn't want
To be involved with
Ideologue
Yeah or like people who are like
Really deeply committed
He's running scams
These people are running like propaganda Grit
And there are some things that you can feel passionate about
Got to come first
For people like him
Someone like patricksburg clearly
A zealot for his own
Pet conspiracy
He's a danger to the primary
Grease videos
Get like and I think that's even more I think the Rodger thing is probably more
Cover for that
Documentary
Isn't damning
I mean
The extent of it they could be taken as bad as like
Rodger didn't realize that his association with the Trump campaign will be used against the Trump
Crimes that could possibly imagine
I mean
I'm just bored
Standard interviews of David Icke
Come on you started the week like this
Shadowgate use
The Gate of all gay
What happened
I don't like the mean but life comes at you fast I'm kind of goddamn sometimes it works
The span of a couple days from shadowgate is the Gate of all gays
I don't know about it I'm going back to Treading Water talking about the devil and covid
It's it's weird
But it does also go to show
Can revert
To this normalcy
This should have been dragged out for months
Beautiful pro wrestling Bookers
Tease this out a little bit
Something else entirely
We'll see what happens
Episode
People
Eboys
Former Minnesota Governor Jesse Ventura
I just wanted to call and say that
I know you've been giving my friend Alan
Looks a bit of a heart
Uberall I think
Doing a really good job
As you know I'm a big
Say Edna
Interpreting
Looking like real.
So then listen to Dan
Just break down the reality
The documents
Situation
Sister real
Free
Treat to hear
I'd sometimes I find
Alex
Go back
Stewart's Root soap
Posing
Skookum
Conspiracy
Trees that are out
Bear
Show Monster
Relying
Been a phobia
But unfortunately people
Well
I just want to say again damn
Jordan
You've been doing a really great job
Thanks a lot
Again
Jesse Ventura
Approved knowledge
Wow
Remind
Billie eilish
Because that wasn't
I like the Jesse Venture in French
Because there's a team for it is the arrow
Like the way he says
Just like that that's how you get into a Gorilla Monsoon
That does help
Jordans
On your way
Episode
Oral
Thought
It's kind of what you been doing
For last few years
You were
So much are they
Evidence
The factory
Fishing right Olive
Leo zagami
Lionel
Dino that are not
You have to have
To the hungry
Cursive H
What is a nice graduation guys
And hopefully working General
Is awesome
Go to church Dad such a good person
Perspective
No that's it that's very insightful
The only thing that's different about this then like
Classic oral tradition
Is that like
In a classical
Oral tradition
Has to do with the same Stories being told over and over again
Preserve that
Will to preserve them and then they change organically over the over the telling of it
Telephone
Yeah it's
If we were telling the same story about Leos
But I guess that's the kind of
Yeah yeah I guess so I mean he committed 911
He's an important historical
With no other help
Fighting in Jordan
Mary Hardin you don't have like a
Message
Brandon Boyd
Right
Anyway
I'm calling about your show because
Study Island
You guys naked really powerful
The reason I'm calling
My name is Ricky
And I thought that Jordan being a
Futon mattress
Baseball fan
Aaron's like baseball
I hope to go someday
Got it
Oh yeah
Score
Shameless
You guys were talking about Andrew Wakefield
A couple days ago
And
I run and
Instagram account
At
Mystic academic shrimp
Anybody want
More
About that
Check me out there
I love the show
So much
Thank you
Go to Wrigley Field and
To Wrigley Field but never sober
I've never recommended anyone go so I don't know how much I would have enjoyed it if I was sober
Bud
You just don't understand the beauty of
The field
The grass I guess I was sober when I came in
But I also was like
And
I was making
Because the
The Cubs song sucks
Stupid
Who are the playoff game
Remember what year
Yeah really really drunk
By the end of it I was
Singing now you understand
That is how everyone watches
I got really drunk and evict
Caught up in the feeling of like being a
Krowd
An experienced at Wrigley in a way that I haven't really experienced
Sporting event
Powerful is one of the most powerful experiences that you can experience
Big people are really into it
A long time
Are the attic on
Stop.
Got me in
Your podcast
It is Alex
Describing him
Tirana Liberty
Gnashing his teeth
Do do more out of
That's a good point I need to rededicate myself to the other contacts dropped
I think Alex used to say more out of context funny
Liberty National
Stop
Seattle
Hey Darren Jordan this is Emily
Just calling to say that I love you
Longtime listener first-time caller
Couple quick things
Thank you plugged
Cher merchandise
Enough
Just want to let you know
Stanton Optical
I cut it up into little strip
I put those strips
Send a pill 5
Everyday
Tell you that I
Stronger
In a good way
Anthem
I'm sleeping between 4 to 12 hours a night at
I can't recommend
Enough
Antenna
Secondly I have another really important
Question
Have you listen to Taylor Swift
New album and what do you think
Alright that's it
Have a great day guys I really appreciate the show
I don't know I have not listened to the new Taylor Swift
Taylor Swift is
Sort of blindspot
For me in terms of like a
Pop I don't know why I don't just like her at all I certainly
Like there was there was a stretch where Blank Space
Yeah blood was pretty good like I liked a couple of those singles
But for some reason I never ended up listening to the album's in the same way that like
Like cash Carly Rae Jepsen
I got me
No
I don't have anything against
The problem was I was introduced her as a but as the
Punch line to a joke
And I hate when the Kanye
Oh no I guess that is where I was introduced
Well
I guess I was on Kanye's side so wrong
No I was totally right
I was right Beyonce deserve that
You can you can agree that maybe Beyonce should have one and still not be on his side for
Musical about people treating each other with respect get that he's a real
For me for you
If I was having any kind of story
Songs early on
Country Tianjin
But I remembered enjoying stuff like
She wears short skirts I wear
And then I
Why don't want to turn into the guy was like
Actually Taylor Swift
Any good I don't want
I bet there's a lot of really good stuff
A catalog that I've just
Missed because of like
I don't know I don't know why I must
No whenever I don't have to have a take on it
Twenty years from now I'm sure I'll love it
Sure
Hey this is
Ashley Moore
My wife has a big
Info Warriors tattoo on Earth
Call me back
You shouldn't have gotten number
Well I mean where we don't know anything about that
Apologize for any confusion
Stop
Subtle sardonic phone call
Could please find
To help out people doing God's work
Dzx Clark
Darryl Ruckus
I'm the piranha of
Liberty
Holding
Alex
I love you