Air Jordan
Dot-com
I have great respect for knowledge B
We are the bad guys
MoneyGram
Alex
Joe
Jordan
Question
Required
Text okay
The motherfuker prosecutor there's no bright
Laundry room
Temperature
I looked around and what do I see
On top of
I'm light fixture like it you know
Laundry rooms are in basement
As bird's nest
Some baby bird cute little baby birthday
Like sort of personify
Things you can see in animals
These birds were making a racket
Until I looked at them and then they were looking at me like what
As soon as I had any kind of attention
Yeah they're trying to look at it from Human motivations way
Appreciate
MetalBeard
Mom I have a cat
You know you never know about
Next time I do laundry
For now
Call DCFS
You keep on doing what you doing
Of the only other sport I care about tennis
All three of them
Decision entirely under the hell out of it
It's amazing
Credible love Amnesia Tennessee
Do you know why
Cuz you made the smart decision not to
Fly to America for any reason
US Open title
Damn bud
There's always
French Open
Irresponsible
Responsible
That's fair
That's all.
IWatch
NXT NXT XXX on Saturday
The middle
No because it was bad or anything but I just did
I thought I was
I don't know what it was
I don't know
How do you say I have no patience I don't know
Will see SummerSlam on a delay
Recording is on Sunday at SummerSlam is going on
So I'll probably watch this evening after I at the episode
I'll probably be bored
Is there
It's time
Didn't seal.
Got with the Weaver shadowgate
Yeah right
I needed a sense of closure to it because it wasn't addressing it on his show
Done
A little bit
He brings up
Whether or not
Closure for this breakup
Essentially
Obviously
As intensely as anybody else involved
I'm involved in this
For a long time
Nevada
The first Jeffrey M
Journal about what you want
Ice Matthew
Charlotte
Andrew
X-Men
Astro robot
Freakishly large
Industrial robot
Animals
Probably always giving me trouble
Weather
Alright there was a couple things
Special kind of adorable
A very very cute names and I'm like
I know what that is
I'm not saying it I don't know how to say it I've only ever
Appreciate it
Might be all artificial confidence it's just momentum
Generosity
Put it in a bowl with Cheerios
You know what you you made it through and that's looking for
Before the episode
This is a little something that is from Purple Penguin
Jordan look at that look at that piece of art
Obviously an audio medium but this is a painting
Attire Illuminati
Bishop
And the Vatican has finally accepted that I am that Messiah
Because I showed them the codes that were inside the Vatican
That only the real Jesus would have
Don't ever forget that
Don't betray me
I love this painting so much Matt thank you so much
Not just the best
I love you maybe
Most of the fan art will be Leo zagami related
I do like that your podcast
Anyone can find
Literally in a possibility
Anyone could find a flyer for like is
80s radio
Okay, I will pay even more than that
No
I got to get a permit
Yeah man
Florida
Bear
You know I've never thought about
You realize
So keep going
Bees RV Millie
The second reason was there's a lot of nonsense happening first of all
Before the 20th
The night before
We had the reporter asks Trump about qanon
And that was weird
They love me I've never heard about there.
Slowly
So I felt like there was a lot of potential for
Takes
Started
Alex started the show
No it was not the Andy Griffith Show
The show starts with Alex
Of the reporter
Talking or asking Trump
About qanon
It's missing from this
You are secretly saving the world from
Titanic
Pedophiles in cannibal does that sound like something you are
Find
Haven't heard that.
If I can help
I'm willing to put myself out there
We're saving the world from a radical left
Philosophy
It will destroy this country
Fisgon
The rest of the world would follow
Every time that Alex plays number
The beginning where she's asking about you and I
S*** on this because he also says that Trump is fighting a Caballo
Cannibalistic
Pedophiles
Network
Nick should on that he has stated position the qanon debunked assholes
Do you have to take the Optics of this
I'm just remove the part where the questions about you and
Perfect sense
From his
Nice
Trump is fighting demons
I've never met Millie Weaver
Interesting Lee Alex does
Start the show
And I thought that he was going to get into it because he says he's not going to get into it
Credit impeachable
It was true
The medium is the issue
They said everybody up to
Copper something
But it wasn't
That was happening
Clever
Bees
You know I recently
Certain people
Evil
Coming out
Bowing to the
You're going to have
So
And
Whatever he says I can't today or not
The central point of my curiosity
What was going to happen
Coming out the gate
Touching on these topics that I want to hear about
It's pretty interesting
Stephen Manning was arrested
Southern district of New York
Border wall
The millions of dollars
Thousand-piece
Even interesting taste
What what
I can't see Bethel now I just can't embezzle she ate that on some level that Alex's position on it
Seems like we haven't had a real
Stop people from stealing
And then of course the old standard the fail-safes at the end there is the
Whatever
They're one of his videos or one of his co-workers like well of course they expect you to steal that's why they pay you so low
No
Stealing is wrong all the time
Route
This is
Evolves
A little bit okay and now talks about it a little bit more
Baby
There's something up with the Stanton arrest
Obama speech right before Biden
Credible
Scandal
Bannon is so slippery in
That he might be in on this
Wichita
Asinine
This is a false flag
He committed fraud
Got away with it for a long time
What was you thinking like what took you guys so long like now
From the jump in order to get this arrest eventually
Someone just you know
Like when you put your head down and you just wave your arms around and watch it's the windmill
Yeah
Fighting Spirit College spirit and Alex
Impotent
So I guess the sex clip we find out
In his
Fear of
Love the future obviously you've talked about preparing his bunker
And maybe somewhere outside
Austin or something
You certainly don't allow disease
Food people
The new pinnacle
Prescription
In the medicine cabinet
Little Things
Antibiotics
Okay
Yeah
Yeah sure look toward antibiotic I don't know what to do with that I don't either Will Smith
Very real
Yeah I mean I don't know
I feel like you could probably end up causing more harm
Then then good expired antibiotics or if you don't have enough for a full
Cycle giving yourself a drug-resistant form of something
You could end up like that outside of doctor's supervision
Taking medications is usually
Antibiotics is one of them
His Back-up Plan
For when the operation with his supplements goes down
Talking expired antibiotics in the Apocalypse
Overdue but
Where you going to get better to do
Slidell
So Alex really trying to cover this to a non question those opposed
Trump without really
Having to own the fact that it was about qanon
Allstate Insurance
The question was about the human
He don't like Alex doesn't like completely
Deny
Mention
To cover everything surrounding
Much longer in the show
Yeah he's almost trying to discredit
The Conspiracy Theory with
Conspiracy theory
About how there isn't a conspiracy theory
But there is a conspiracy
Something like that
So Alex plays this clip from MSNBC
About
And
This is interesting of one of my favorite things about
This show
Alex's show
Is the various ways in which Tech goes wrong
Phone call Problem by problem
Just says
Hello yeah certain times with people can't find things that Alex needs
This is a new
Into this is from
More well-suited
Police
Terranean way down underworld
Around
How do you say
He has
Congratulated a right-wing
He is
Go commit now
Fringilla
I don't see how
That they're willing to roll the dice
Jason Brooks
Willis information
Bookstore
Music
That was not going out to break
That was just middle of this Sacred Music
Is work
For us that's the only thing that makes it would just start playing music
Or something like that
Accidentally was on a radio station or something
I just
Today's eclipse
It's remarkable that you've been new sign up your professionalism presentation
I'm waiting
Somebody has to throw a pie
That's what needs to happen
That's what I bet the close your eyes preferably another publicity side with
Should be Millie Weaver absolutely
Disgustingly
California
Mom
Come here and want to be us no no no
Yes you do
You not in Brisa
Reminder
When he's talking about normal
He's not having a conversation that specifically about people
With extreme ideology
Of whatever orientation
Yeah he's talking about just an average Muslim
Stop trying to pretend
Stop trying to pretend that you're having a different conversation
You just generally hate other groups of people no matter what no one has any in
Interest in assimilating into into American culture at Large
Their culture upon other people because he
Pull up and force his ideas upon everyone else speaking of people blow things up
Particularly
Government
If you believe
Alex
Is going to be on today
Call Auntie Mary
It is
It's already out there
Dentist
Why did the Senate committee
Intelligence
Said that.
Stone
Need
Show trial in
Rodger stone with judge
Jackson
Trial
Trial he claimed the opposite Nordic Jam Rodger up
Surprise
Unfortunately the Senate intelligence committee's report was released last week and you can sell page 241
Call discussing Wikileaks on a songs with stone both before and after taking over as the chief exec
Trump campaign on August 13th 2016
We called the prior to joining the campaign
Inside information about WikiLeaks
After the role of campaign ceo-7 repeated to him that he had a relationship with Assange and said that
Wikileaks additional materials
That would be bad for the Trump campaign
That sure sounds like a
Crime
Alex's promises false Rogers
He's banking on his audience without taking the time to learn what the Senate report says
Which is a safe
It's very long very long
So Steve
Amazon
For the sake of clarity
So Steve comes
And
When he swings
He swings for the goddamn Spencer's
Lili when's it was without
Anybody who's really going for it
You know I hate people in a girl monsters and they all have nefarious agenda
Taken as read
Classes of criminal here
And there's people who are like just really
Embarrassing
Give the ship Millie Weaver's terrible
Troyer's terrible
Dismissible
Steve is another class of criminals
I think part of it comes down to brazenness
Steve doesn't give a s*** f****** s*** does not care until your mother
That is Steve just like
You don't like it I don't
From the perspective of someone who has to listen to these ding dong talk all the time
Sort of entertainment
And particularly when he comes in
And this is his complaint about Bana
What is your take on this
I was show couple months ago
And I said that
Steve Bannon
Complete
And his delusions
Conviction and prison
Or
The reason is
Free sample
Shannon is what we call a self
Automotive
A nicer term
Oh really oh really
That's why he should be in prison
Now coming from the guy who's called from it solves every geopolitical problem because ever happen
Coronavirus yeah
There's something so Universal about mentality of like whatever they're accusing us of
And I think that everybody has a little degree in this Infowars world
But
Steve f******
Relishes swallows
Save it
Tom Clancy base Jack Ryan
It's just
It's just delicious. Projection is amazing he's covered in someone's blood that he just murdered
And he's like
I don't like Steve Bannon
It's amazing
Terminator time with Stampy
Well by his logic
Steve months ago
Yeah well I mean that was a safe bet that might down for this but I want you to follow how excited Alex gets when he thinks that this was
Based on inside information
And how disappointing it is
When is the size of talkingshit
The arrest
How do you do the say that I should have started
Rumblings of this
No
You and I
Intuitively
Sure
So that was great
I don't know where in over his head
I didn't like him I don't
Yep
So a little bit about Obama and
Playing this is just as a way to point out that Alex is back
Pretty deeply in the
Calling Michelle Mike
That's a pretty disgusting
CIA
Homosexual
Complete farce
You know delivers Michelle Obama a total nobody
Already
French
TJ
Asexual
Individual
America
This is just such a stupid game but Alex is getting deep into it again and over and over again
And it's really not worth getting riled up about
Ugly and you know
He is just trolling
He's really just trying to get a reaction out of people
Because we like we've seen this happen in Cycles before we're totally
And then whenever there's too much heat about it
He'll be like we were just joking you know obviously
This isn't something that we're serious about
Play it very seriously like I absolutely mean this is attention-seeking
Absolutely
I I was I would leave it alone entirely except for its becoming
Pretty frequent
And so I just
Wanted to say
So idea that you know
What's going to happen is that
Going to happen
And then Trump going to win but then Pelosi and
Democrat
Or surgeon and they're going to secede
100%
Every one of the Punisher
Jones
Does Senator Schumer
Normalizing it we're going to secede
.
Claim
What
No s***
Shut up let me start off by saying that your premise is ridiculous
Abigail
You're still a big dumb dumb Alex let me begin
Working for the last month
Stupid
Never happened it's nonsensical does not need to be afraid of that
I love whatever he's so dismissive
Just take an Alex point of view just go
Stop it get out
Blue in the background
Alex Azar
I mean that would be disrespect
Certainly
Disrespectful
Like whatever Alex
Talks about his ideas and his Notions about America and
Freedom
Usually there's a presentation of romanticizing ideal
When Steve comes on
If it comes
Pretty queer
He doesn't share the same ideas
About America
And the reason for that is
Business people to understand
And one simple religion
Cereal
Angel
Steve believes that the only religion the only thing that this country is based on
Capitalism
When was that
Right I mean boy
Loverboy
We are sick
I'm not being cereal capitalist
Away with you
Different view of America that
A different view of it
And the way he sees things
I think that he's done it already his audience of the series be serviced by you selling them
Romantic notion
Why even talk to me about the
The Constitution or the Bill of Rights or the Declarations are all
Don't you just don't bother with
Yeah
That's it it's not in there
Just you just say to me you don't give a s*** about them
It meant protecting Kappa
Is
Certain
So are we from Steve's interview
Seems like a really big brag
And I don't think it's accurate
But it might be less far off then we want it
Jonestown
And we have to leave United States
And that's where the Democratic
Party is going there in the process
Involved in Johnstown
He was Jim Jones third in command
A meeting for way
You are your ancestors
Timeline of the undersecretary assistant secretary
State Department for management
Right I could see him being aware of
Situation in Georgetown
I don't know if you had any major role to play in it
Something along those
And whenever I expect that briefing to my Superior
Obviously I didn't lose things and change the course of human events
Yeah I could see him in that role is like Deputy assistant secretary
Something about what was going on and then learning
Steve
Either one
And I we get our visit from Deanna Lorraine
I'm like really ambitious bull
Dickhole what is real is not real what's real is
What's not real
Deanna Lorraine
This is such a shift in tone
Antabuse
So much
Like this dude
Amen
And then we go to this
Yesterday I'm not a nice hotel this isn't like a cheap hotel
Another world
It's a good one but it's a nice hotel
And Stan
I just went to the restaurant I want to ask
Ask the hostess a question
I said you know the restaurant know what time does the restaurant close
And naturally as I'm
I just pulled my math down a little bit to talk to her because otherwise that's so muscle
I said
You could just say Hi how are you are you could be nice about it
But you don't have to scream at me
And again as I'm saying you don't have to scream at me about it in a nice way
She screams at me again put your mask over your nose put your mask over nose
I can't do this anymore
At least during this pandemic
I'm already wearing my mask it's already too humanizing
You can at least be nice what happened to customer service
During the pandemic
Alright you and Alex and then I
Could really help myself I did flip her off
As I'm walking away
And I said I'm going to file a complaint about you
I can't
Yeah you should
Jasmine
Just wow customer service wow
John
You know
I do like the glow but I like the globe-trotting
I do I like the idea of Steve pieczenik be everywhere the Forrest Gump all.
And his swing
She's like what happened to basic
Beeson place that's it's minuscule it's very personal
A boring story
It's shooting on people who are
Having to go to work in an ideal conditions
It's it's Anna is unable to take of you outside herself at all
To what these people might be going
Through and it's just
It's not it's not worthwhile
It's
Even if the stories 100% true she sounds like an a******
Nothing about this is
Heady
Culture War type nonsense it doesn't rise to the level of being interesting
This servant that his risking her life for minimum wage is not treating me
I would appreciate
I am going to scream at her and flip the bird
Yeah maybe
So anyway from the 20th
About how she was on the TV in Australia
Which we know about yes we were there
Oh a scalar attack
I was on the Australian News Today Show
As soon as I started getting into the real death numbers and
Zoomdekho no yeah they cut me off and they said it was a bad
I'd be the president
Samples
Dressing a goat
Testing a paw paw
You can't make this stuff up but you can they're making it up and yet the siop continue
You know what it's really funny how
First Skype
I don't think they caught her. I think it's her Skype
Now and then now she's in the studio and Alex is helping her pretend that they cut her
IPhone
I don't think she'll listen to the rest
Galaxy
God
I was saying a bunch of nonsense and then my Skype which I prove never happened
My Skype feed cut out with you Alex the person I'm talking to right now obviously it's supposed to tip
Dangerous
An in-your-face terrible
Alex Jones
Now I'm in studio
Years ago
He's ruler shelter
So we get to the 21st
And Alex Wilkinson show and just like
This is this is where we're at
Show the new ads
PrimeWay
Playing Trump produced
Trump produced as
Yeah
No charge
I would assume so
I don't know I don't I don't complain if you're not being paid
Probably because like nothing, I don't know I don't know how I feel like
I don't know if it's wrong
It puts you in a box
Because Alex gets a new Call of Duty commercial
Or why not
Cold war game that's coming out
Soviet KGB Defector
And Alex's pretending
At the storyline of the game is reality and it's very weird
Expect that come back I want you to video games are also
Predictive programming
Predictive programing alright that's a real surprise
I'm going to leave that aside cuz it's not really all that important but I do predict that it'll come back
Anyway
Rodger comes at now
Bridgestone is also to talk about
Rodger
I got these guys are Pros him and Steve are Pros
This is just the shittiest
Taking the high road stuff ever heard
Predicted
That's just like such a such a cool like
Hey look I'm not happy just make
M
How do you think you can get away with that
Rhetorically
Every single time that Rodger was on
Did you read that report those just do 20 he says
He does touch on that anyway
Interesting Rogers be really mad that you didn't know during his trial
Was under investigation because Bannon was a witness against him
The government obligation
Was under federal investigation
Show me
Classy classics
Clock doesn't inviolate
You should probably be lit on fire Ave you seen wicker man that was pretty good
Sacrificing now I wish him the best of luck in the yard
I would say my response.
This investigation is not essential to each character
What what are you what are you talk about if you couldn't have done any prior
I don't know if he's going to help
You can't bring up all this together
When
We were talking about the immediate reaction that Alex had to shadowgate
So it was a yes
First immediate reaction
Then I was just reacting with I don't know s*** about this
I don't get involved with secret stuff
It wasn't even the Gate of AJ
Call Alex.
Is take
Publicly available information
Now
Yes groveling lines
There's no honor among Thieves
Secret sources
Embarrass Trump
It's just not fair it's just not fair
You know you get through it through it every now and again it still hits you it's just like this is just not fair
I mean
Outside with it most of the time but when he says that it's just
Yuri
Slap me in the face with a glove and was like snow I never hate you
I never hit you at least give me something
Right right
Next
Navigation
Chinese
Rodger is very careful not to say the person's name because that dude
Sued Rodger for 100 million dollars
That was Miles Kwok
God Rodger I heard about 8
Never even talked about it
Millie Weaver I've been hearing a lot about must insist
This person's name
Because it only gets sued again
Interesting
Pretty interesting Alex always
In interviews is like 25 more minutes always like me back when I used to drink
And Alex is like
In almost every interview and almost every time
People are like
Yeah let's let's go ahead and do a little more
Rodger
Fuel factoid
Cyborg
Busy
Rogers Gattaca
Talked about how Bannon suck
But then also been like I've also spread
Just enough suspicion about
Manning intersecting with my trial to buy a very definite connection
White and Shifty
Alex Costa bright
Comes back
And
Really was weird
I got worried
Times when I go where the township is so dramatic
What's going to happen
He's going to happen
Let me just get rid of this right now
You sound unhappy
When I say I'm going to be honest with you just means that
What
I'm so scared
Terrified
Because I can't be honest when I tell you that I got to be honest
What are you doing
Worried me and doesn't get to the point
Keeps going down we were roads like
Racist
But
Vietnamese wedding and in certain ways are losing
Trouble
Real issues
New World Order
Mothership is killing everybody
People
I'm so fucken scared
Make this make sense
This is what happened right after Alex's
Exasperated
Hey you know why because I'm white
Sport me
And I can lead into that and be more outwardly racist and that's super profitable only for a little while
What is he his career
Is that what he did he just some up like since he joined Trump is like well you know
That works really well for a little while but then
It all caught up to me on account of I'm being sued by everybody for all the things that I did for
Doesn't
This is sort of a stray thought that he's rambling around like he's clearly dealing with something
It is
Because he just keeps going and he's
Valley View
Stop
Smart
Before the show and just
6 hours
Read and talk about the first time
Devil worshiper
What are you talkin about trout
You should stop doing any research
What are you doing
Hire somebody else to do all of the research for him and then read and analyze those articles that he'll
Like to talk about directly to him and then he can just react
Tonight
I think he thinks that the writers are doing that for him now
There are no
That's fair
I look like I'm tempted to stop work
You don't work now
What does he think he's doing I don't know
Eat sandwich while you're swimming
So I was listening to this and I was troubled
I didn't know what the
And then even more than that
I was confused
Because he was not being specific at all about what he's talkin about her
Admitting this next trip I kind of got a sense of what this might be
Call Barta
Modesto
This morning
So there's some Children's Program
Thomas the Tank Engine is gone
I mean I had a sense this was about those Netflix
Posters
For that show or a movie
French movie cuties
Something down because people are pissed off
Hyper-sexualization
The prism of like sexualized
Aim
I I had a sense that maybe it was something like that but even so this was in the movie for kids
Children
Okay well it has kittens for kids I don't know
It's um it's interesting
Children's programming
Philippine specific I just I didn't know what was going on
He wants to kill people
Henley people mad
I didn't know what you was talkin about
Context Clues on infowars.com
And there was an article from National flyovers reposted on Infowars
Clearly what he's talking about
It was for a show a Netflix show from last year
RuPaul
From last year
Yeah
Call AJ and the Queen
Okay it was about a drag performer who befriends a ten-year-old
Trailer
Alex
Screw up a stairway
A bit of an overreaction it's a trailer I also don't think children
I don't I don't necessarily think that was a children
I don't know anymore.
Yeah it has children supposed to be for children until the trailer
That's what he's talking about that's what the article
They pick matches up to
Certainly drives into water kill
Just make Angels in the Outfield every every year
It's wholesome
Is it worth
Also
If you watch Angels in the Outfield you don't have to take on the pain
These trailers like this gives him great pain
You're supposed to take on the plane
Look at
One little piece
Convey to
You know what we all started
Okay
Alright
You know when you only saw one set of footprints
I think this is a little bit of
AJ and the Queen
I actually wrote that
Inspiration for Tom Clancy's
Is AJ and the queen true I heard that on Alex's
Calm down
Yeah
Trailer shouldn't make
People
Angry
No and I honestly while I was watching that sounded two rings very full
Be very fake yeah outrage
Weather where
That
There were these quote-unquote save the children marches playing for the weekend
You know you certainly likes you in on stuff even if
Cast and make it like a more
Front facing passionate presentation
In anticipation of that becoming
Something that he covers more children
Murder because of a trailer
Okay
What are other reasons that I feel like is very false
Very performative does this whole segment
The place
Meandering
Rambling nonsensical
He doesn't entire segment about how you going to go down to Barton Springs
With a food truck
Just left the City of Austin has declared Parks and Recreation
Calling
Emergency
We went down last weekend
People
Jump in Barton Creek
Multiple times on this episode Alex mentions people passing out
Emergency
Zoom versus me that Europe
Not taking care of any of the people come to your rally
Sometimes cause and effects needs to escape
You know
But sometimes there's very clear causes and effects
Review are hurting people with your dumb s***
People are going to be like
Alex talks
About how great
What makes it really funny is that we end up in this
Very familiar territory
Let me do this
Gestalt
Because it's
Operation
I'm talking about how we're going to go swimming is going to be great and then
The news I got to get that in order
In order to do a protracted plug
Pissed
Everything is so petty
Everything is so petty of their grievances are so stupid and pathetic
Steve is the elevated level of international espionage
Ryan Daniel not real and not true
Bigger
Then
I'm going swimming
It's going to be a great weekend
I want Melania to be queen of Earth
What is the thing is that you noticed that this like
Swimming at Barton Springs protest has certainly.
I'm going to save everyone who's been wrongly convicted of DUI
You don't have to go to the police office nobody nobody asks you questions
Effort for someone else's behalf
Really sucky
Remember a product name
Jesus
He's trying to sell some fusion
Gone
Discontinued
Incredible
Family Show
Fusion
Doesn't exist anymore
You are his own secret
Maybe he's been doing too much I would describe how this plug and Alex
Sad
Essential specials
They got usual
Trying to remember the name of our
Parasite
Drive me insane
Gut punching
What is that
Johnny Depp powerstack is not
What is the name of that Prada
So I know
You need a boss like Alex needs somebody to write
I understand
Do you have a certain
Set of skills you can ramble about things people find it funny
You're putting on a show you can't do a minute of not remembering something
Putting it in your earpiece the type of place that should take
What don't you
Take this and then kill them off
It's fine
You do it all the time
Product but he does remember
You went to a smartro
Conference in 1996
Smart growth conference in Austin
Abusing people
We are
Convenience
About a film
Mm mm
How
Movies really dramatic moments in
Sure
What are the one of the things I want to really stress answer the listeners don't
Make it there Habit to listen to Alex
You show on the regular
What is a
Really frustrating about it show is
Most of it is
Extemporaneous bulshit a lot of research
Know a lot of relying on fake research that he's done
The long stretches of time sometimes someone will pull up something on
On the screen.
Every now and then I'll really try to get to the news and when he does
Reading headlines
No contacts
Go project Littleton
A little like
A little clip a little later
And this is a story about American Airlines
They're going to trim
Some cities service to some City
And this is basically
Buddy
His analysis of it is
Nonexistent pretending
Which I don't know how he's justifying
8 they're not
But would they
Why would they celebrate celebrate
That's fair that's fair
We got to be more cautious with our punctuated an article about it if they weren't so
Celebrating
The assertion that CNN is celebrating this is completely unfounded and it's just in order to make
Sienna and look like a Cheerio a that are
Is there an expectation
Issues
The Imp impact that all those are probably all in that story with that headline you didn't read it
You know
I read some headlines
Garbage
Nervous
Earlier
The name of that
Free shipping on it and it's
Turn off
Living defense
Okay what happened earlier
I'm just saying
I just don't understand why he calls them sex when you could just
Call them your eight
Pac power sack every time
Be selling
He's not going to make it
He doesn't come back
And get into his covid stats
Instead
He does what I've needed him to do
This whole time
Getting to the Middle Ages
Something here that I
Lemur
Yesterday
Because of the
Good to know
Adjust still happen to occur
Simultaneously with the release of the bilge alligate
I mean I think he's trying to say he does end up slicing out
Content of the movie
She's hanging out with weirdo
The office
Brought up
What if I don't talk about it
I was I heard that has like
Listen to our episodes
Who around here
Kaitlin Bennett
Former friend
Millie Weaver excuse me now
Apparently she's dug up some dirt on Harrisburg
Starkweather
Might be about us
Alex doesn't like
Oh
Okay
Okay if you send him a Punisher logo that he goes further that's a rule that's a hard and fast rule
Used to be on Twitter
Message the info gif
A gray white
I know a couple times early on
Very seldom
And no response
Rent-A-Wreck
No but I think it's really interesting to see you
Alex's is expressing that like
I'm going to now
Dory
Nitric birdie coming for you
Heading back so I'm excited to see if
Because Alex
Kind of like
I'm going to say my piece and then I'm done with
Five bucks
This morning
Kaitlin Bennett
We found
Trampoline
Or getting arrested
What's the film came out
But this is what attack
She did well we ever total freedom
So Alex is just basically being like Millie got to a certain point of
Same
Craigslist
And realize the sort of delicate nature of the Griff we're on here
Alex
I'm sitting here like I hate that I have to be composite
This is actually a smart move for me
This this is the lowest level of self-preservation
Yeah yeah this is
Like legit
I don't know what they're going to do they're going to blow up our spot
Do if we are associated too closely with them you don't know what they're going to do
You can't do this
So yeah honestly
Golden State's Alex confirm
My assertion
Beating the s*** out of your mom and getting arrested for it is not what will get you fired from Infowars
That's what that's what I thought
So in this
Peter farewell
This is
Goodbye Melly
On Monday
Because it's my side
Operation
Is the film
Stop
The truth
You're working with triple treat you real good
Air Jordan
This is really fascinating because
This this is history
Millie Weaver is officially the first person to be banned from Band video
Alex
My God
Alex, are you saying that because
Your website is a private Enterprise
You have the ability to remove anyone who you do not particularly like
You know obviously that's her right
Technology down to remove this from
Millie
I don't Delight in her downfall at all but I'll tell you right now I knew this was coming from
That she was behaving earlier and I think she deserves what she's going to get out of it
Now
This is trouble for Alex because they've been promoting
For the last month she has the sunrise movement
Anything that you said
Shadowgate
Millie Weaver getting fired
Just what a week
What are we
College
I should have used the Alex Jones
Great grasp of History
Volume
We'll get back to this here in a second I love the idea that he has volumes about the occult
At 11
And then was a Satanist
About that makes
Timeline screwed
Was it
Different ideas are weird
You're being popped
How would you know
Don't you didn't
So I mean
Everyone's really stupid cuz they go to college when they could just read encyclopedias as a child
I understand that kind of thought
Higher education
Right
You think you can find that you know people are self-taught many people
Amazing things yourself.
Alex Jones
You cannot learn none of those people were like sometime life now I'm done
Self teaching
Think that
College is mandatory
I don't think that there are a lot of incredibly intelligent
High-functioning
Brilliant people
I will never
Hear somebody like Alex
Who didn't go to college
Say things like
Teacher that ideas are weird
Higher education essential for for everybody and
One thing I feel like he has no concept
Is the fundamental flaw and if your education consists of your parents buying you any book you want
There is an issue there
Many of the things that I learned a lot from where books that I did not want
Do not want those horses rules
You read that
Self-selecting for your own
In college
That I learn
Exactly
Not going to read this b*******
Somebody music yeah and I'm looking at it and I'm reading the first two chapters just
How can we escape this book
Exactly
I haven't read a book
Hundreds and hundreds a year
Most nicest
You only finish 800 up
Straight up lie
Set this image of the burn the Midnight Oil
Such a narcissistic just like
Not only have I read a lot of books I've read more books than you can comprehend
Hundreds of books
A day I'm Wilt Chamberlain
Books that's what happened you know how many potential universes there are
How many books I read today
21st
Is Deanna Lorraine again it looks like
Maybe
She's doing a job interview
To replace milk
If she were on Skype
How do you think this interview
But using Studio
Who cares I don't really care
Little story
A.m.
He's driving me jogging
Ryan
Weird neurotic
Like this thing that I just imagining Alex
Can't lie
And he's not making things up before
Navigate to the show
This morning really early see the trailer for something rose up in the stairwell.
For half an hour on the floor and then goes jogging
You still got to get your exercise in maintaining your but his body
Is the temple.
Certainly has
I find this difficult to believe on this long hike or people with masks
Coming up the stairwell
Has Leo zagami committed
A well he is
That is not bulshit
Closer here
At least it is much as like now we know that Alex
Appreciate that
Shadowgate
We talked about the actual movie talked about Alex's
Do use it
And then on Friday or show on Friday we talked about the weird
What why are you talkin about this at all
Yeah you know like none of this is a movie
No sense
Nope it's stupid
Their relationship
As ridiculous as that as it was his only less ridiculous
Relationship
Close
Probably not
But we're done with it
I don't know
Time travel in the past for Wednesday we have
Dumbness
Yeah chapter has opened up in
I feel like
Obviously we can't we can't leave the present day alone cuz
Coming up to intellectual
She's getting
So I feel like
Something that I made
Is
One of the things
Over the course of the shows that whenever we set out to do investigation
And time travel and stuff
We've been
Because we have a question
Answer
For the answer to that question and I think that's a bad way to go about it
So I'm thinking maybe we time travel
Just see what happened maybe we just pick a random day
But I think that maybe we go around when something
Pink or like
When did Alex
Josiah disappear trailer
Sure
Here is a time in history right let's see what happens
I don't want to let you control
Mario
Focus on the present it really is just at his whim
Women boring
It hurts me personally
So I'm not going to stand for it anymore
I'm going to start my Independence
It's a go f*** yourself Alex you can
Stairwell
Take a hike I don't give a s*** I like
Yeah this is built like a very Complete Saga
The only thing that I regret is I wish I could have been contained
I feel like there's an asymmetry to that that I don't like
I do feel like the story has been told
Documentary
Fallout from documentary Millie is now fired
The other thing is really motivating me to feel like
Alright
Whatever Alex getting arrested
Intelligence report coming out
Rodger
Handle
Secrets
Rogers appeal is going to completely change the Ballgame and exposed
Because you can never get a fair trial
That's never done anybody any good
So we'll see where I
Take a little time to people
Hey Danny
All siwa
Just wanted to reach
Unironically
Here we are now
It's a remark
While watching you
Hope you great
Thanks Carl.
Sucks
Get Reserve there
They're intense playing out Major League
Like there is almost like they're trying to lose as much as possible in order to sell the team
And move it out of Boston for some reason cavero
Are the Red Sox over there
We'll call it the French monster that's all we'll do a throw-in might be this one
But they were going to the second
Best player in baseball
He got hurt
Yeah well
That's terrible I really sucks
Yourself up too much about there like an hour to newer younger
Animatronic outdoor. Not necessarily believing everything but I didn't have the same critical
When I was younger
Let Yourself Go
No Tech game
My philia
Yes I was
Meteor Man
This one is Wednesday
You know what though I miss
More than Project Camelot is I miss Project Camelot being innocent
Yeah yeah in a sense being just fun
Goofy nonsense the first time we meet captain
I'm you can really meet captain my preacher you know
You mad is a murderer
That's fair
There was such a there was an appealing purity
The theory is about space and aliens
Yeah you can stop for a second
These are just space we
Yeah you know there people who were people there just face and that's great
Munster does like
I would like to find something else in scratches that is
But I do miss it as well hopefully we'll find something
Dan and Jordan
This is
Asthma
Alabama
About two years
I've been listening to yourself
Gratitude
College
And I have
Research
And a couple of my undergrad
And I am moving
Auntie
Doctorate in
Sociology
I really hope
Y'all
Research
The other two
My
Medical sociology
Degree
Haven't started
Where can
Conspiracy theories
Like that
Really a great
Michelle Ellis
Just about every
Everyday
My mom turn me on
Are you guys at
She's also a Polish block
And she'll be happy
I'm your message
Thanks for everything
And you are appreciated here in
So much
Shout out to Alabama Tide
For sure
Obviously it definitely wouldn't be this bike that I've heard that from a number that's really cool
I mean I guess
Lot of my ideas about how parents are people who are very put off by obscenity
This feels like it's in impossibilities
You know I listen to your podcast
Very clear.
For a tiny bit
This isn't the first yell this wasn't this isn't for me
Post
100%
Using research
I used one of yours
Jokes
Not a bad impression
French stuff
Like that
I try to err on the side of my messages that are
Strictly just like
Thank you you're awesome break brings up a couple of really
Yeah good thing I point out and one is that still awesome
The escalation
Possible
Poor people
Really humbled
That really is
Probably the best
Dealing with people who are going down
Is it an assumption
Productive
Cooling the temperature a little bit
Event also I wanted to allow
Shout out for the rest
I don't know whole lot about the Discord I know that some people running and they have a good time chatting and stuff
I don't know where it is
How about it
I got it I got it I don't understand
Conversations about stuff
We are very lucky to have a
A group of people who
Find each other
You know like
Everything that I hear from people who listen to the show about our groups is like
These are the nicest people that had like we're lucky
Yeah it's it's I don't know if we rate good people
Not all inside
Coronavirus
Deanna Lorraine
Fashion
To pronounce the
Melbourne
Melon
Or if you
And you got some nerve
Purple peacock
Coming
Forget my voice
That was a bad line
Trace of an Australian accent pronunciation
Watch for the call
Ever read it and then somebody's like you stupid
Three times a week
Different
For that nice offer
And if you'd like to send something that I just send an email gmail.com
And we can set that up
But thank you for the calls everybody
Will be back
On Wednesday
Independent
Yep World on Twitter
So there's a review and all that stuff
And if you could please find a local charity or bail Fund in your area to help out with people
Fight
Dzx Clark
I'm Daryl runda the Gate of gate
Alex