Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for its knowledge B
Sick of them posing as if through the good guy
Need
Knowledge fight
I love you
Little bit about
Joe Wendy
What's up today
Got a couple of really nice things first of all other another
People responded so amazingly to the picture of the painting that Matt sent of Leo's
Twitter address
So so much positivity
The best
Also another thing here in the mailbox
I'm addicted to ZF does Kwikset
Got
Package
From his greatness
Damn
Over in the UK
This package
Candies
Chocolate
Stuff like Curly wurlys yes I'm looking at one right now
Marmite
That's not candy that's a spread it is
For some reason Werther's Originals
Not sure why
I can get those here too and
Not British one
That's very maybe even tried to
It's really cool
Real milk chocolate in there worth Petersburg
It's really cool and I really appreciate it and say that if anybody out there listening
Foreign countries and you have various candies that you have there that you can get the United States
Don't don't don't stop yourself
It's something really from my youth
Religious studies professor
And every year he would go to the fbl conference the Society of biblical literature
And that would often be in foreign countries
Scores and so he would go to be always really exciting when you come back because you have a bag
Candies from
Yeah yeah
Find
Maybe it's a selection
Way better
Stop with better
Ingredients in
Because they don't allow us to they don't allow people to get away with
Interesting calling American
I don't think you're wrong
I appreciate that
That's very
Seems It's
A very trivial
Siri trivia
It is is getting very long cuz I have not gotten a haircut
You know what's going on
I don't want you to
I was getting my hair
Starting to YouTube
It was amazing then realized that I never even considered
For it is because where I grew up
It was always so associated with with only women
And I examined myself when I see that I'm still carrying those gender bias is even now
God dammit
Congratulate you on your progress
That's great
Ponytail
Longer
Especially since you're taking care of it
Summer break
Active option
That's what I hear
Jordan
And it is as promised present-day Alex Jones hell yeah
Episode
Tried to look at
Honor YouTube channel
Naturally sourced
The person
It was a real disaster
And also I tried to go back to the gym
But unfortunately I stay because Jim Bakker
Had a stroke
And since he's come back
I don't
It really is it's kind of hard to watch
He's not 100% yet
Certainly even if I'm not making
King fun of
But his health issues
It's still just doesn't it doesn't feel right to be like
You're talking about the end times and then
Been out here
To figure out what
What to do for a suggestion
For a date
Indeed and you came through
When you choose random
You have the unfortunate possibility we've already gone over
After 22
Was June 6th
2016 indeed 66
Was not random
I got to say
Maybe
This is this is a lot of Coke
Who cares
Episode
Was a lot of fun
It was revitalizing
Alex Jones
Used to do as bad a job
Liar and racist
He used to at least have a little
Hey are here for a reason yeah
Start the show about 20/20 hour now
Certain obligation to cover his dumbass in the present
A lot of the time
Just complete
Lack of creativity Beyond Reason
You know
2016 episode
In June 2016
But
It's not
The same as now
He's not just sitting around yelling about the tickle
Almost not at all talking about how
Absolutely not at all
Well they didn't in 2016 Dan
Russian
Figured this would be like all right
This there was a
Every time you forget that he used to try
A little
Well the president used to dry
And so I really appreciate that
A lot of really
Stupid s***
Yes
That is surprising
And then what
Surprise Cameo appearance
That
Wow
Jaw-dropping
Jaja
I think I'm normal
Pretty shocked
Okay
Show up before we get down to business on that Jordan let's give a shout out
So
Max
Alex
We got 343
Thanks Rowan
I can't deal with this one
Text Alexi Jonas
That's Alexa
Thank you Alexa
One Man Riot
Text Sean Cavin
Policy wonk
Hellboy
I'm a policy wonk
If you're out there listening music
Sports sports
Or you take that generosity and right
You're going to head on down to the what's it called
Aquarium Aquarium
You're going to
X-ray to the charity that is the fishes
Is this a metaphor
This is this is really exciting
Come on soon
Yeah yeah
Chili's
Doug globe-trotting across the world
Indiana Jones
The Archives
So we start the episode off and I got really I got really excited because Alex
Has
Is getting ambitious
It doesn't it doesn't go Gray
We have several
Very informative
Robbed in Deutschland
Meeting
Every four years
Since its Inception
Every 4th year Meats
States on the East Coast
The first time
They are meeting
In Europe
On the fourth year and that's obviously because you're up
Crisis
Tottering on the edge of
What great news
Alex
Alex is correct about the 2016
It didn't start until June 9th but
He doesn't the location corrects of good for him
Past that the rest of the stuff you saying is
Pure b*******
I want to search that they hold the meeting in the United States every four years but because you're a busy in a crisis of world government
Decided to forego their four-year cycle tradition
For the first time he said that that makes no sense what is this the f******
Olympics how get the s*** out of here what are you talk
This this is where it becomes just way too clear that even close to an expert
Papa guy on because there is no for your cycle and Bilderberg location history
For years prior I'm 2012 Bilderberg did meet the United States in Chantilly Virginia
4 years before that
In 2008 they were in the United States as well
The problem is the two data points don't prove a consistent pattern
Princeton's four years before this in 2004 Bilderberg wasn't stress Italy
You continue out the four-year cycle
Here's where they met in the next year's when if Alex was right they should have all been in the United States
In 2000
In 1996 there were in King City Ontario Canada sister cities with an American Social
Play Silly United States in 1992 they were in a van
In France in 1988
In 88 Austria was an American state
In 1984 it was Sweden in Germany in 1976
Do you have to go back to 1964 to find an exterior metal Edge
For your cycle we're building
Were they actually met in the United States there we go out
Navigate Lovett
Love it
I love that kind of nonsense here are the years the Bilderberg has had their meeting in the United States
1978 1985
Foresthill 1990 1997
2008-12
When do we have the 2017
Alex is reporting to his audience if there's something weird about this 2016 meeting being held in Germany because based on his
Fictional expertise
He should be in the United States
But naturally must mean that the globalists are in a panic because of Europe which is just another narrative element that out
There is no for your cycle when the Bilderberg Group meets in the United States
Alex just thinks that because he's a dumb dumb and he makes a lot of assumptions
They were in the United States in 2008
Therefore it must be the case that they were regular for your cycle so it's weird they're not here in 2016
This is only relevant for one reason and that's because it reveals that Alex doesn't know anything about the Bilderberg Group
Because if he had any kind of deep familiarity with the subject
You would know this was a pattern and where they meet isn't
Real someone like a big Jim Tucker or Daniel estulin
Makeup a lot of bulshit
But they wouldn't make a mistake like that easily like wait here's where they were
It doesn't even give a s*** about like anything
I love the swing UCF Ice and you're like well obviously if it was if it was 4 years
That's almost
The pattern of the scientific method
Forever is how that's how long that's been
Interest in covering Bilderberg meetings in 2000
Maybe he just started
I don't
That can't possibly be true cuz Bilderberg was a name that rang out
SeaWorld before
And what was that it doesn't care about
You don't need to remember before Obama was President
For they weren't to the United States
It would be impossible for him
The guy who I'm sure would have been there if it
Very weird
Xenophobic
He's rambling here a little bit about
In foreign countries
Most
And take your children
Articles
1 Telegraph Avenue
Not even really from the UK they hardly even
Speak English
The police
Sweden
Germany and France
And in the UK
Also
Muslim
Speak English they weren't even born
In the UK
There now you're in
Disappointed
Most
Of the sea
Security
Airport
Charles de Gaulle Airport
Muslim
Hardcore
Kissing Muslims
Women
And they're running security
And then upload
This this line of thinking is consistent
Without
What is an alarming number of Muslims
Everywhere for alley
Police chases
Farming for him
He's alarm fire by Muslim women in the pool supply shop
Muslim cop would be alarming to him so I don't I don't trust your Calculus here
Yeah yeah
No matter what you know what I'm saying
Way
Last of Us
Stupid chore compared to the present
It must be pointed out in stress
I'm not saying
I wish I think it's something that we should very much take with us as a reminder
Republicans are acting right now
Oh this is something brand-new right now
Republican Party
Just like Alex it was f****** b****
Yeah yeah I think you could get into interesting argument about like
How much of it is
Always been there in
Allowed to
Become public and how much is it was
Maybe something
Denver racism because of
The the ways the Trump
Frames things that Trump
I wonder if Alex doesn't interesting thoughts about this episode
We'll see you later
Interesting at this point in 2016
Alex
Honestly this hasn't changed
Alex believes
Cover news about Infowars
Course whatever Infowars in the news
You don't want to make the story about your
Present today and turns out he also says that
In 2016 when he's getting ready to cover news about himself
Started about a week ago
And I never even covered it
Infowars
Real blinds
That we are the
Because I
Want to just be a Gonzo journalist
Myself
That's a good belly laugh right now that feels good
Present-day Alex
On and on about his own personal truck love it love it
By the southern district of New York
Resolve
Certainly
Except for the ways in which it is a Rosetta Stone
Turns out
So it turns out
Show you how insane 2016
Incycle was
I didn't remember this happening
Something that should have been disqualified on its face
Coming up at the bottom of the hour I will see
A few minutes on this whole
Klamath Falls
Southern Oregon Northern California
Contour
With headlines
The news
The last week
McDonald's
He has been
Caught red-handed
Using Infowars material
That there is a
That were built
Why what
Farmers in Northern
California
Southern
And
You could
Julian Tire
College education
On medium
Medium
Deception
Gustoff
He couldn't
So Alex is mad about an article that came out on June 4th in salon
Infowars as a source at a campaign rally in Fresno California
Full disclosure my dad's family is from Fresno
No offense to the good people that happen to live there
But suck at City
At the rally Trump denied there was actually a drought
In California
The only reason the water was because there was an EPA rule that required
Some of this water
Flushed back into the San Francisco Bay to maintain ecosystem there
This is true
Water park
But the scale of this water flushing out of clothes
In a drought
According to the salon article the use of water in this way can take up to 800,000
Acre-feet of water per year
Which sounds like a
California water system
Managers over 40 million acre-feet of water a year
Perspective
Nah that's almost like what point 5%
Percentage water
And it's not just flushed out to the Bay for no reason
Part of it is to protect endangered species
Nobody cares but also preserving the waterways around the coast
Is really important
Because a large part of those cities their economies involved
Yeah around that it's a balancing system resource management
Cycle System that exists
Ecology
Right and so like you can do this whole grandstanding about like this
Small amount of water is being rerouted used for Farms that are in need
These ecosystems collapse than these Fisheries die
Obama Crosby's Fisheries
Alex posted an article on Infowars that was abroad attack on the EPA that oversimplify the issue
Water was a large difference in terms of drought conditions the California was facing
And that it was done just because the Looney left wanted to protect a little fish
This is because the story was never about
It was about
Pain of the drought being used to fuel the machine that the right-wing needed to attack government regulation
It's unclear if I actually got this news from Infowars
The article is just Alex
Riposte
Did something
Second article
Psycho-Pass release papers
But it's probably safe
A Dorito
Points
So you can make your own conclusion about where you think you might have
Messed up thing that happened everybody knew everybody
Everybody f****** new guys we are
Because of us
Oh man
Brutal episode
Immediately undercut
He's complaining about how the family is under attack
Family never exist
Father
It never really
Existed
There are you coming out
And I was always really a village
Which is true
That was your other
What
Watching your kids can't be under front yard or backyard
Two seats they kill the village
Artificial
System
And then they tell us the state
Good save good save
It's more than just a nucleus
Okay
Are the new Village
And then they tell you it's not good to hit your kids
Yeah
That's a great that's a great trait
They say you can't let your neighbors watch your kids and then they're like don't hit him
What how do you say what everybody knows that the progression
Little little bit
I like those moments a lot Alex's brains
Alex
Is it I would say that the beginning of this episode is largely
Centered around Aslam
There are two driving things that
Make this up
The Varsity narrative
Of this episode this is not one of the
This is sort of
A garnish at the beginning
Then Germany
Alright for now we're still dwelling in the space where Alex's
Wdi text me because they're scared
Donald Trump's house
Hey hey
You're so scared of what we cover
They're so freaked out
Dlg
Sofrito
Beautiful he's not saying the Deep state
Bednar meme hasn't really taken
Because it back then it was still the regular government
Yeah the government sucking up
She didn't have to create a 28 government
So
Alex
And like the hard-hitting news that he covers
You know
Great I appreciate the pets
How he has to experience
When is take a step back and you considered
The stories that you're promoted
What are the things that you're taking your time to cover
Just doesn't make sure it doesn't make sense
Stories
We also have another
Dot-com right now
Video
Obese woman
EBT card
That's
That's the story you're pushing
Because apparently the local news wherever that was enough
People on site on site
What is they needed the assist
Flabbergasted and up next
Cat learns how to ride a skateboard
I don't
Know if that's an important story
To cover it unless all you're trying to do is demonized
People who are dependent on
Program
Just a very idea of social welfare
What June sometimes y
16 nothing else was going on
I'm pretty sure that nobody was even talking about this
Supreme Court for Auntie
Hey Jordan
Not know if it was
Would not know
You know that I was mad about Solange
Route to use in Germany
Amanda here
Is the big hairy p****
So exciting
Rodger Stone did not
Tell me
To the
VP choice
Donald Trump is
Ford
Vice president
But
He did
Concur with
My per
Prediction
It will be
At this point
When the shortlist
Stone and
It doesn't talk bad about
TV in battle
The campaign
It really is just
Trailmanor
Right now
Butler
He goes on television says that he's heading up
That is not the
They brought in former
Comp lawyers
Background check
And research on who Trump
So this is really interesting
Teasing out
Like there's a big scoop here possibly about Trump's VP pick
Because we're in the present
Are the future from this episode
And I was really fascinated
To know
Does he think it's going to be
Yeah
F*** yes this is this is I can't wait to see what the discussion was all about
Essentially telling them telling Alex that the actual camp
Campaign manager for Trump is just a booking guy is still running
Different
Yeah alright one is the disappointment I'm about to show
He understands Showmanship
Like he's teasing this
Latency s***
About specific
Until the end
Get you interested by this thing may or may not have
Just rambling about it immediately
Are you telling me that you're teasing this information
You're not just going to hear the next five minutes being him talking all about it
And then the five minutes after that beating him teasing as if he pretends like
He didn't talk about it he doesn't say a name you didn't say anything that would give you any
Location of like it's time to pay it off
This is like Bass
Security light
How old
School
Wrestling would be
You guys fighting each other you keep them away from each other
You don't give away the fight for free
And I was just giving it away until until
Well done
Well done the second thing is really interesting to
Deceive that Alex Corey Lewandowski
Because he hates
All of the people who he perceives to be the media
People keep in trouble way from him
They're the people that should really like me
Pizza bread Pascal
It's because they're the people act like you can project
He is a reject
Want to talk to him
You can be like oh it's
It's f****** Lewandowski
Innocence though maybe in 2016 before Trump actually wins
They probably did have to like keep him away
You know like that
They probably were like
No do you have to talk to Alex and Rogers over here in his ear like
Workout Alex
Galaxy
You'll love it
It'll be great I'll get you a job there
Yeah I would say it
Probably more likely that they have to do more of it
For sure
So Alex has
Three names
But
Corey Lewandowski
Rochester
And then
No but
Rodger had a pretty severe reaction
Rodger
And Stone
Galt
Such a character
You just said well you should have made it
Visibly
And was concerned
Oh my God
Sir Rodger Gault
Switches
Did you just say that I might have a pair of Threes go
Rodger Dupree severe reaction to Alex aiono
Radu's in Germany but it turns out he's not alone
We got robbed
Josh Owens
What's left
For the next 10 days
Bilderberg kicks off on
On Thursday
Is there
Really interesting cuz Josh Owens is the guy who is
Left Infowars
And an article for the New York Times magazine about how you regrets working there
Regret getting that sweet ass vacation to Germany for 10 f****** days
That's not bad as having a great time
Yeah it doesn't seem like it would be working text to
Every now and again
Part of your job is to
To say things that aren't true don't even do the job and that's something
He even has brought up about how they manufactured
Situations in order to
Create Optics
He is there I I just think like
This will be one of those times where I actually maybe would want to talk to an Infowars but like oh yeah
So then I realized
Still probably couldn't trust that I would ever
Call Debbie Whitlock.
It's 10 days
3 hours
6 hours of b-roll
And there
For 10 days
What else do you have to
Not on location in Drive
Sometime
He talks about how he's got this
Video with Rodger coming up later where they talk about the VP
This is pre-recorded
Alex talks about recording
These segments
Kiko's way out of his way to talk about some personal ship with Rodger
That makes me fairly uncomfortable
And I honestly think
Is maybe an intentional
To try and humanize somebody
Is a f****** scummy weirdo a******
I was here
Saturday
Different segments
Saturday Sunday
And then today
On big topic
The real reason he came to town
Was
To discuss baseball
And fill me on a lot of things off
On the record
Temporary
6 months ago
A few months ago and came back
Boston Texas
Obviously that I got and I can't talk about it
We were
Talking about
You got a call from his wife
And it's nice re-roll mother
Had to come home from hospital
And I just
It looks you going to die any day now but she
Excruciating pain lung cancer
We're going to
Give her morphine
She wants it
And
You should have seen a minute or two
And Heat
Got the phone
My mother while she's all there
Morphine
Superhot
Probably.
Next 48 hours
I'm going to go finish the prompt
Speech on Sunday
I'm going to leave early.
McCloud Sunday morning
Afternoon
He pulled himself up
Pulling self up
We came in earshot
Shagman
I went out to lunch
Talk about his mother
Am I right ladies
Why are like this is weird that is weird I would feel because I will Rodger just as a person
Hey man
Don't talk about my personal s*** like that on your shoe
Yeah
Talk about
Private I think we've talked about
Hey like without you bring it up first I was going to know.
It's not it's not appropriate this is someone else's business right
I'm not a psychopath who doesn't
Experience emotion
Seems like other human beings
Man way to tell a good story
That makes me look
Very good thank you for not sharing the
Can I reach through my phone
And pull the plug on
I don't want to speculate about like him being that kind of a crass or like a cold dick but like
It's
So
And I don't
Comfortable about that
It's not appropriate
So anyway
It turns out that they discontinued
And
Text me about 3:15 last night my mom just died
Thanks pal frog
About time
Woken up
Hunter classic
What is the guy
This is a real story about their interaction
No it is just difficult
Like I don't have any problem with the
Story and I I appreciate people
Supporting each other have a problem
There's no indication
Rogers go ahead and tell my business business on the street
He was actually his source for this
Alex's
Bagger keeping other people's personal business office shows good
So sjws are a concern
Jordan 16
Interview listen to this clip he's talking about a viral video
They did come out a couple months
Breyer
And you'll see how sjw social justice Warrior is really a proxy for Alex
Text to talk about race
Justice
Warrior model is going
San Francisco
Few months ago there at the college
Young
Freshman
Hazard
All the fake
Culture soup
How's my home
Hollywood even
With a
Polyps
Pull up
City dialect
If you're going down
And the video
Just says it all
It's just an excuse
Enas
Ashley evil
Mean Thug
That was white water rafting
Just be like
Alright I know that's a big
That's a big rock
Valkyrie
Trendy alright got around that rock
There's a viral video 2016 this year college student
Francisco's State arguing with
And the woman felt that this was cultural appropriation
This is what 100% not a story that needs to be covered by a national Outlet
Learn how to skateboard
There was a tiny bit of physicality between them but it's
Genre of people blocking each other not even close to violence or fighting like Alex's describing
Beat them up
This is the kind of discussion that should be allowed to be had
Vulnerability
And hopefully they can both Come Away with a better understanding of
Other people's perspective
This is one of the very important things that college environments
Facilitate
Is people from
Tons of different culture
Pictures of backgrounds
Come together
In one place to learn
That should be an intense
Broad
And unfortunately that's a process
It's not always free of hiccups
I misunderstand
And hopefully if in a healthy environment
You can facilitate those sorts
Clashes
If you want to call it
They can lead to growth they can lead to
Something better that's the thing that
Most
White conservatives are afraid of
I left from
Homogeneous place
And was suddenly thrust into cultures from everywhere that I've never experienced
And then whatever Anderson
And my parents alike
I realize this is what I'm talking about
22in extent
Beef environment where people can
Assess
Their reactions to things that confuse them
4 into them
It is a growing
And this sort of a conversation between someone with dreadlocks
This is cultural appropriation
Is a is a really great example of a conversation that the two of them could have
You'd hope
Conflict isn't inherently bad
So I watched the video and I cannot possibly imagine hosting a new show and picking this was something that I should cover
Let alone again months later
Alex
Especially couching is language
There's a proxy for him to talk about that
Adopted all the fake culture superimpose by Hollywood
Do they meet up
Social justice Warrior inner-city
Black women
Pork chicken
Who are looking for excuses to be quote
Nasty evil meme songs
It's pretty broad stop when you really get down to it
Play another video
And that is that I was just reporting on a fake version of what happened
According to an article of the Golden Gate Express Wichita long before this episode was recorded So Alex has every reason to be aware of
Scared at all
This video did not include the entire exchange between the guy with dreadlocks
Woman in the video who I will leave Anonymous out of courtesy claim
Watch Pastor while she was handing out flyers
She made a passing joke about his dreadlocks to her friend then the dreadlocks guy called
All of which was not included in the video
This sequence of events is verified by multiple other students who were there and saw the entire incident
Captured the second half of their Exchange
This woman
Is it on her way
Because garbage
Garbage
Everywhere was recorded by another student who posted online
Control black student
Attacking a white guy for having dreadlocks
I was reporting on this shoddy framing of this video because that's the story he wants to tell
The stories that centers around the whites
Innocent
Possibly misled by culture victim
In the black student does an out-of-control Thug west of browbeat the white student submission
It's a fake
Story
Alex
Because how they feel when they see someone getting
Trouble for saying the n-word
Or they see people's
Suggesting the Confederate flags
That feeling is real to them and the edited version of this video provides the story that they need
Do you need to hear that
His feelings they have two pics reality reality isn't going to justify my feelings
I will make reality Justified
Months before April
Actually March the video came out by April
The write-ups about
Circumstances capture everything
I mean
Here we are in June
Story doesn't rise to the level of Alex
If something's there
Campus Folk
Who are in positions of
Maybe
Facilitated conversation between the two of them in a safe environment
You don't need
F****** racist
Ding dong
Right-wing talk show host
Turning this into some kind of important
Staging ground of a culture War share that Rush Limbaugh needs to be involved in any and all
Disagreements on most college campuses I don't think so
Choose interactions between white students in
Black students it's strange that it snowed only those
Situations but I guess
They are uniquely qualified to mediate those right then
Coming from the other direction
What is a left-wing version of Alex
The story is
Yeah look at this this woman yelling at this guy's house
A nationally syndicated
To be taking on as an issue there's only one thing to say
Which is
Come on guys what
EXO
So I needed to get worse
Spears Alex talking about her friend
You are both
Weather
Supremacist
I don't care
Weather in Salida bring it up
Call Black
Getting in the
That white kid
That white nerd
Maybe
20%
African
Yikes
What race is people when they're not sure of what words they can or cannot say
And so they're like well I'm going to go out of my way to
Almost always are then like
I don't even know if these people are black
Yeah I see that they are not races
Is diet
They don't look like to me did you just hold on what you're saying that these people
20% African
So they're not black enough
What percent
Dwight do you think those nerd
How do you define 98%
Let's get into your definition I didn't say black because I'm not a racist
I just said that 20% of a person is
Interesting relationship with racism at this point
Is career
Because there's
Still kind of a balancing act that he's trying to put on
Bucky really wet
Tea Party
A very racist
Pretend that that's not
He has a real vested interest
Appearing
He says
Play Frasier
Aries
Is though he's like proud of himself for navigating the choppy Waters of race
Look at how great I am
Here's another attempt
The media has Party Movement
That's racist
Anyone promoting free market
Wherever You Are
Aldi control
Global of programming
They're telling you your role
Telling you who you are
You're a woman so you support Gloria Steinem
Your black
Hispanic
Because Trump pointed out that
Mexico's completely
Remote control border
It says it wants to conquer the Southwest
A bunch of people
They're racist
Absolutely
What
Look
Nobody
You're just being told there's no other
There's no way for you to guess
Only 10% what are you going to do leave a party cuz
10% of them are Nazis come on come on that's what happened with Hitler and now
Weird
Defense
Sigi's engaging in
I am not
Sure
I like I like the idea you could confess to a crime but if you just say it like you're not confessing the cops will be like
You got it
Yeah
I didn't kill him though
About 10%
Racism
Very high
Very high seems to high positions that you know maybe if those 10% were in positions of power right now
We could assume that that
That you know they're totally fine with 10% racism
As long as it was also a group that was willing to
To discuss
That the sort of unexamined parts of their belief system that includes
If there was a willingness to hear other viewpoints
I think everybody given ourselves we just are not aware of that needs
He brought to our attention
It's something very
Sort of a part of Modern Life
There's a race politics
Texas being played
It has to do with
Using minority somehow
Try before but with white
It did not work out
So Alex talked about this a little bit
These are people that use rice baseball
In the fifties and six
Trying to do it
Because you're the majority
How to make an acceleration to gender on that
Because whites on average will still be
Per capita
The wealthiest group
Because they
Had the brainchild of
They were taught
Save money
Now they'll have
By the political
They will go into a hardened defense mode
And a new
Shut up
Over everyone else
Interesting theories also they were taught to save money as an interesting way to say they were allowed to participate
Writing
To save money the other people weren't allowed to have
So they had a lot more money to save you could like
There might heal your money fake
Facebook and put it in the bank for you generational wealth in a way
Yourself
I think undergirds
So much more of this than than what people are really talking
So many of these people
On the right
Are genuinely I think in favor of of that kind of
Thunderbird
Because
They think
If they were in black people's
They would obviously already have killed everyone in the country
Because they would never allow themselves to be treated so Tara
So they assumed they black people
Given the opportunity to put their bootheel on top of them would treat them the exact same way that wifey
They think they have it coming
And that's why they're fighting against
Yeah I think I think that there's something to that mentality so conscious or consciousness
Alarming number of touches on maybe not explicitly
At that seem does run through something
Is is conversation about
You know about the ways in which
If white people become minority they'll be oppressed it does sound a lot
Like well you're reflecting what
Minority experience in this country
Do you
That's abuse
That's that is
System is coming
Right
This is interest
This is really interesting the way Alex frames this
Progression
In 26
Then down the road
Will be shot
Down in the Hole
If you're not signing up
Newsletter
Infowars
Dot-com newsletter you really need sister
Sounds does add pivots to his newsletter
At this point which is fun
Great Notion that he also he also sells his supplements but it is
Who played very weird to hear that
But what he's saying is apartheid system becomes into place and then that will collapse
Apps or that'll ABS Ackley
Societal collapse
Societal collapse is coming
And we haven't had that apartheid system
So
Societal collapse
Can come from any direction really seems like
Use ability to assess what the global is to do in might be faulty
Hey because we're all just making this up
They skipped a step
What's up what did you need
You skip the clip before
I want to try
Alex talks about he's got robbed
Josh Owens in German
The field
We got robbed
In
Germany
So I listen to that cliff
I thought it was really
Interesting cuz he's got four people who are on location
Used to be able to afford to send people all over the world
Call Dad
Josh Owens is come out and written
An article in the New York
New York Times magazine about how
He regrets working for Infowars she's disappeared
Yeah yeah silence doesn't
Me indicates like
She still looks back fondly
Position is
Gee's Bend
Very much gone
Joe Biggs
I mean he's still
Sure you still
In this world but Alex had to let him go
Three out of the four people
He has on location are
Gone
And that just proves
Rob do is the best employee
Robbie's got blackmail or something
For you
Guess what I've got robbed
I don't know what it is but he is yes
Power
There
So Alex has a bare-bones staff
I am so he wants to really talk about
Like really
Supporting
Screw
I appreciate it
Look at it it's great
All these gifts
I think about
Reporters whoever
Somebody on the crew
And just tell them we know what you think about it
We love you you can
And hear from us
We care about you
Alex you want me to adopt somebody understaffing
Is the Grapevine
You suck
You're terrible at everything you do your time as the Nightly News
Couldn't even keep a Nightly News show going at Infowars
Great deposition
Be a great help with that position as a corporate representative
Maybe one of the worst never say embarrassing to the end
Degree
I don't know probably
The decent father
Yeah but I don't know come on how else do you stick around for this log
I think you've got black marijuana or something
Tech Automotive
I don't know I don't know but I think he's terrible at his job
USD
To say we really
Think about
I just adopted a highway
The Highwayman
So Alex
Talking about Trump
But at the same time
He's not
As I don't know
No certainly not he's into drop indefinitely
Terminal A
The Trump hat
Most powerful weapon
Donald Trump has it
Correct
His Allegiance speaks
Just pushing basic common sense
It's that
I've seen the raw footage
Cam
It's got to be
Percent of the people going in the door
Hispanic
And
It's got to be
10-20-30
Center Bar
Because
Is racism narrative
The thousandth degree
Quite frankly
Common sense
People that have it
Hey I'm scared
Which I would call racism is just called normal tribal
That's weird
Weird
Trump has his disposal
I don't know if those numbers are good
I think he was arguing that almost
50% of trump rallies were non-white no more because
60 to 60%
It was a menorah T of white people
Footage that I've seen
Beers like it's a lot of weight
I've seen a sea of white but I don't know
I don't know
I don't know Cal State jerseys you busy taking every individual in rallies and determining
Whether or not their minority enough for him
People who are not glow on glow racist maybe they're saying some things that are like
Normal tribalism
Spots to be scared of other types of people
Now here is where we get a little bit
The ideas of trump
Kind of
A lot of the narratives that
Ford
And
Things in that media ecosystem
A lot of those things
Probably
Went out of their way to incite
Some racism exist
They got pushed further over that Alex talks about that he's actually pretty clear do you understand
Compensated racism as a political
Tool
Really
People that have it
Hey I'm scared
Which I wouldn't call racism is just called normal tribalism
Put a little bit of
Pushing them on their side
I'm not even defending I think you went too far
Amazing
In June 2016
Did Trump intentionally push some buttons to Insight
Tribal racist ideas and it's fine because the last does that to fuel
What Trump
May have gone
Kuffar
Alex according to Alex Paragon of non racism
Sure let me know we're not going to go so far as to call him anti
2020 Alex be like Trump is never said anything even close to racist
Yeah I know
What is what is
Spend
Years say to me that the left doesn't have any men
Remember things
Cardan
This is a guy who thinks
The Trump is going to lose the reason that I think that is
Because the way this is going
It doesn't feel committed
It doesn't feel like Alex is talking about this
In in the terms of like
I hope that my career is connected to the
He saying he probably push buttons too hard
Yeah he did
He's clearly saying that
The man cynically
As an electric
As an election strategy
Said very racy
Things in order to incite
Braces
To vote for him
That's not okay under any circumstance
Apparently it is
Oh okay nevermind then
So
You texted me earlier when you were talking about suggestions for the daisy episode
Nixon was a great president who didn't use any racist
But it didn't work
Can white people do
That was weird that was a really strange text to give the
And you mentioned John the Revelator
Artex 16
Yes answer here's where
Comes up
Depeche Mode has the song making fun of
He's gone
From the Muslim
Sure
The Muslims didn't
Hundred
And hundreds and hundreds and hundreds and hundreds and hundreds and hundreds and hundreds
Of years
Think I was 302
John the Revelator
It's just
I love it
Couldn't even hardly walk
Bugs that
Like
In the same way that talkin about this viral video from San Francisco State has no place on a series shows
I would rather listen to Alex struggle with like I love this
Disagree with the message
Talk about that more
Don't you
Where do you see the law to suck at that all the sudden
You just realize this song is a lie
Blaspheming John the Revelator
Straight
But that is a struggle video I would like to hear Alex talk about
A revelatory for him
Hardly use the word
So we get to
The point when Alex is going to Nail Talk
To Rob do location
In Dresden Germany
Reflecting on how cool it is
He can be at his studio and Austin and talking to somebody is Buddy in Germany
And bacon broadcast that on the radio and cool really cool realized
The future looks really cool
He's talking about that video because this is the second banana peel
100 years ago 1000 years ago
8 / radio show
Infowars
Radiou
That have the technology
Does ubiquitous
And we can meet in Dresden Germany
Nationalist
Rally
Where is she
Supremacist
Lp1
Your Country Wide Open
People coming in
Women telling you got to
Submit to them I don't see any
Kenny Knox
So that
Going on flag
I don't know that's a naughty
Associated
I've never seen Millie Weaver
Somebody told me in the past
Lowe's Bowman
Skylar Grey
That's Westwood joke of the Alex Jones Show would be
He has sent
He's reported to a nationalist rally in Germany and clearly his vested interest in showing
And it's not
Alright
Just the tone 280
Cuz you know what he is worried
He's mad at Rob
Is that a josh
Don't you hear it
Except for the skull in Bones flag
Yeah I think I think you're probably right that is a Optics issue
Also might be just
A sense of like
But I don't have either a bunch of those skull Flags
Okay
The presentation is that this isn't some kind of a f*****-up rally
So now we see this flag that could be Nazi
We have to preemptively explain
Bobby the FED there to discredit them
There's one of those
Flags there
Shutdown
Probably just
Who's there
So Alex is being a little bit
Dishonest
When he talks about this rally
According to Joshua well just two days prior to this episode being recorded large Nazi
Rally in Dortmund
In the Germany
Those groups many of them explicitly neo-nazis
Which was met by approximately 5,000 counter.
Strader's
Little violence
My current crisis that was happening around this time was in
Inspiring a real surgeon and closely related sensibilities in Europe
Which were being white washed and sanitized by being called National
It's hard to say what this rally that Rob is at is actually
At this point
This is on Monday and that's Saturday there was a cheetah
Which is an extreme right-wing group that is a
Aggressively anti-islam
An anti-immigrant in character
Paquita is based in Dresden so it seems like
Probably another one of their Gathering
Which would mean that it's not some cool rally about people who just loved Germany
It seems possible that they would hold rallies as frequently as this because the guardian reported in 2050
Poquito work against what
As the islamist islamization
Of Europe
It's hard to say for sure at this point but it will be confirmed later
Go to Germany to whitewash
Explicit xenophobic fashion
Yeah that does sound right
We're we're in a real molyneux
Kind of situation
Yeah just change the country
So Alex's
Did seen this video all around the world
Together it's a create a One World Government
Alex is this video going on Skype
It turns out
Another thing that's been consistent
Describe don't work
Walter Scott
Before I go any further though
Obviously
Expensive to have
Joshua
Who's about to be there
In Germany
Alex's Tech issues are consistent but you see a very different response.
He's not angry
He's not freaking out
You look all we got Skype issue we lost the connection
I'll go to a plug
What time to tell you how much
Expensive disease
And you should buy our product
That seems like a real irrational
Normal person hosting a
Play a report I'm leaving
Sometimes
The Skype is
It's not like
Sometimes the Skype
Just goes down
Nobody Cuts you off
Yeah nobody turns off your
Sad Rabon
You talked about house that morning they've been in another city in Germany
They'd interviewed migrant
Individual
And to just be
Where the hell's about
Glad
Exactly
That's
Alex's
You know when I suspect that this is a Poquito rally
You act like that's going to
Probably
I'm just going to go out on a limb and say that name might be a little too long
You know as far as I'll leave goes
Sometimes you want to shorten it down
You notice it in there
You don't want to go with illegal Invader immigrants from
Play 9 hours Pace, Florida
Yeah
I think Alex is a little bit
By the fact that there was this flag
So he really needs to insist that these people are not
I know
Is it good if they are fascists
The great so you got
People state flag
How tall woman
Just calling crossbones
That could be fast
Isis related
Furthermore
What's the weather
Why would you say I'm looking for
Alex is a sneaking suspicion it's just a party
Talking about
This is alien there's one over there
So there's a counter-demonstration
And
Rob's talking about a little bit
But you could see me
They got the
Billy Gunn
Future down the river
Show more attention to that blonde police office
Get out of here
Alex is a little harder
The kids say Alex's little horny on Main
Fire
I saw this and I was like that
Alex my man that is
Real like that's what I expect from this guy
Get a little bit closer it's not appropriate
Really fired
Really horny
Feel free to ask
See what she say
This is like
I'm laughing because this is so outrageous
Beyond Paradise like you can't imagine
Alex is trying to play this game or haha just kidding
You should be fired
This is a fireable offense
Crippling problems of the show he has no boss
Yeah I can't stop laughing because this is
As if it's not even
This is just such disgusting Behavior
Yeah so disgusting as Beyond
Does get worse
Of course because bra bands of talking
Speaks English
Detox
He's actually a pretty sensible interview
Problem
The huge problem so also I do appreciate this person because
They do end up confirming
Are there two counter-protest of Poquito Valley
So my suspicion is
Confirmed by this clip
English
Alright
Wisconsin
Why are you here
Cheetah is
Teresa
So
They suffocated a rally rally
We're protesting.
We've seen this happen a number of times in the past
End
This phenomenon that happens when good enough job
Conversation with this guy
Obviously leading
But
Alex is not satisfied
He wants him to hit it with
Gotcha
Talking over this interview
What's the weather
Amira
Oh yes
Great
So why ask
Good question when you can just tell them how he's supposed to
Idiots
So it's the guy has
Responses that don't fit into the Infowars
Which is supposed to be
A trap
Geisinger
There are other cultures that
Support violence spousal violence
Proprietary
And it's not
And that's bad
Because
You don't want to run away from this interview because he can handle your question
And at the same time
You don't have any other
Bro
Discount beginner job later over people that work
Bring up the blonde police officer in Pursuit
I'm still horny for that cop
All right now I'm graduating
From just straight
Misogyny
And just
F******
Patriarchal shoving his behavior
I'm going to wrap
That up
And islamophobic bigotry buddy
Talk to that tell that
Cops
But she's going to be in Islamic
It's interesting because Alex is trying to deflect from this interview not going well
The same time he's sort of shaming Robbin
Illustrating like
These are the thoughts that I would have
You're not as good as me
Yeah and yeah
Like very alpha alpha
Boy mentioned earlier there's a surprise
Appearance
And here's where that happened
This almost
Knocked me out of my chair
That blonde reporter right behind
What is the f****** wrong in fashion
Stop today I was expecting
Today I told you before we started
Recorded that I was listening to everything just kept getting weirder
A blizzard
Lauren Southern
All right guys
He starts interviewing or I don't think he was relevant
Start having conversation
And it gets
Really clear really quick
First of all that Lauren
Is aggressively islamist
Feel so left out
We're having a conversation
Studio
Anti-immigrant Islam Club Points back and forth and Alex's juicer the Ghost Inside
Kind of sad
Understanding Islam
Religion
Do not erase
And it's the details.
Animal
I don't know about that
Nordstrom
It's just the really
Quiet the adults are talking
Really weird because you know doesn't have an earpiece so she can't keep
He's it's like
He's a toddler like jumping up and grabbing robbed has arm sleeve
Tell her to be racing
Yeah yeah
Maybe at might have to just be gassy
Same here but
It partially I'm going to go ahead and decide to report on air
Them
EXO
Much like a person who's at the party who goes and sits in the corner to talk to Joshua
I always busted his butt
And he's gone shehadi there he's got
Joking were joking
Ask you questions when you been in German 24 hours already
What do you want to impart
What have you picked up
In day one
Weather 10-day
Operation
Infowars
Yesterday
So I don't care about his perspective
Micro-cap particularly because
He has written an article about how it is time
Infowars vase
Stories
Incites animus towards
Muslim so
Probably this is
Go fuc yourself
Do the interview wraps up
Alex has a bit of a story
Infowars
I don't know how to explain this because
It doesn't really make sense
At this time there's a lot of talk about the wall
And so they found
In Germany that they're calling a medieval Trump wall
What's going on
Upon
Infowars.com medieval
Wall found in German
Muslim
That's what they do
It's definitely a religion
Conquest
This is so it's
Listen to his mom with workout
Yes and just like a base
This level 90
Frills nothing like yeah not hiding behind anything
Just
That's what
They'd
Just wild
But not surprised
It's almost strange to hear it's so targeted now
In the context
2020 it seems like all racism is Now shotgun blasting @alex a10e
I like f****** non-white
Just do the other matter you know but near its focus
Austin targeted on just
Soo
Play existence of women
I'm just like
This is a dick
I think what it is is that Alex talks about all of these various things
Trees in different story
Yeah supposed to 1
Hayden Summerall
So Alex is Varsity the big one is
Talk about Trump's VP
Yes and now that we've gotten robbed in Germany out-of-the-way
Alex starts
Teasing
Gyros
Never going to premiere
Trump VP pick
But you know when I
Figure something out for myself I figure it out
Show and it's not 104
Stone
Liberty shed
95%
Little birdies
I love me and 95
Percent serious
He's doing it right he's teasing
He's doing his job
He's giving you a nice little
Look
I know
Everybody
Lauren Southern was
Be out of nowhere
Cameo there was a guest that was surprising
Guest
That is surprising
Tucker Carlson
What the f***
Yeah
Episode
Yeah earlier times
Had some
Almost adversarial
Hostel
Mainstream conservative
DeBrands at the time
I know that I
I don't know if the dates on them but I've seen Tucker
With Alex
2016 it seems like
Too late that's shouldn't
Tucker would have wanted
To stay away
Cuz he has
Some sense about him about like
Optics in
Association she is it just me or is it is
Is being on Infowars not just as easy disqualifying now but it wasn't then
It should have been
2016 first
It turns out that there are some people who flew under the radar
Tucker I think people just didn't notice
Yeah
It was just kind of like a what
Compile this is where I
Episode
Are running into Lauren Southern on the streets
Crystal racist but
Far
Tucker Carlson showing up this is weird
Maybe it's just back then
Stuff used to happen
I don't think so this is
Excite
This is the Fast and Furious of Infowars episode
Starpower listening to other eras of his show
This is not how the show used to be all the time
This is a good episode that ended up randomly getting picked
It is still like a
Sweetly different show
Buried
So the reason
Tucker is on
Is because
He had gone to a conference or Summit of some sort that involved
People from
From Facebook
Glenn Beck was there
And it turns out
Going back
Wasn't
Cool or something
Just been kicked off something
Baby serious
It seems like a great time for the two of them to have a conversation
And so because he was at the summit with Mark Zuckerberg
Mark Zuckerberg
Photos
He does look like
Actually
Play Nas
Huarache without in Prosthetics
He didn't
Wolf
I think it was a fake life that's hilarious
Is charming enough to
Alex wants to be funny
I know
So they get to talk about Glenn Beck and Mike down for this club cuz this is
Sowa Mesa
I got to say I mean like
Tucker Carlson is a smart guy
I think he knows the way the wind blows
He's able to with some
Competent
Prophetic present himself in Waze
But he's not an idiot
East Phoenix
Like three times
Right like he's Crossfire Hotel guide
Come back enough times to know
Even in those times
Herrera
Now
Fashion era
You just a shitbag the whole time not somebody who is it is like
Very clearly much more adept
He's there because
I think that Tucker makes a lot of good boy
Honest
Can you make so we're not going to get into too much
Is
He's not saying Facebook
Twitter and all these companies need to be destroyed
But there are concerns that we should talk about about the ways in which they engaged
With foreign government
Sure
Laws
Better counter to American laws these companies to operate in foreign countries
They followed the foreign countries
He's not saying
That we need to stop all of it across the board
Vic that's not an invalid conversation
This point that he makes
When talking about Glenn Beck
A great
Great point
And it follows
Alex
Making not-so-great a point about why he thinks Glenn back is out to get her
One time I was there too
Do on others
Socks
High-level produce
Has their own show on Fox
Also produces stuff
Steak with me at lunch
And I sat there I love you
And he looks right up
Climbing the wall
You're about to be
Last year
What is he carrying us look
He runs the whole place
Kicked out
You crazy
But
What was your taking one back
Talented man
But when
Play is on radio career
With some sort of religious
Understand it
Mystikal
Hey Tucker I got bad news about the guy you're talking to
Isn't that interesting though
It's not
It's not it's
Interest know it's interesting but it's
Interesting in that cake
The tweet for everything kind of yeah yeah
Interesting words like
You know that they know
Beyond out now
No absolute tomorrow
I love your Evangelical Outreach
He had Tucker on his show is defended
Alright I get what you're saying here too dumb argument
Based on your brand you would need to protect Alex
It's it that's really interests
Tucker's is coming from places
Of humility
Humbleness
Modesty this like he's much more talented than I am radios very hard but
It's nuts
When you take your
Radio thing and make it a religion
He's just
And Alex says
Colton
Yeah Alex is responses so obvious
Of course he was mascot to the present-day Alex saying that
The literal Christian Satan
The opposition
Drop
I forgot
We have not heard this is the 6660
Nobody has claimed that the devil is running anything out of mention of the devil
Optimus point of anything 666
Or something I don't cut out any mention of isn't it funny the date
One of the reasons this was really refreshing and
Fun to listen to
Funning Petty quotes
Comparatively to the present day is he's not just yelling about the literal Christian devil
He's not yelling but pedophiles all the time your blood
It's not that
Tucker's right
A pink
Do get out of control and completely
Icon will be once you enter that level of things
Ostensibly political show become some sort of a religious mission
Everything you're saying stops making sense yet
Alex's show is
Probably in some ways motivate
Is that extremists religion
But it's not as forward facing at this point the actual product
Has like
Here's a story. Maybe
It's about a dumb viral video
San Francisco
But at least
It's something
Happened right you know it's not dry
The devil wants to get you in a basement so we can scare you and drink your children's blood
They're living in the world that ostensibly they've always said they wanted and it turns out it s***
And so you can either
Try and defend your monster president or you can say that the
The devil is killing him and everybody else's
So evil they are eating children you can order please
You can only give a value judgment
Your guy by decreasing the value of your enemies
Which is evidence of how shity your diet
You know the person who pulled the gun
Yeah
Tupac
Take this from another level
Everything gets out of control way too f****** fast
Spends all his time
With the stakes
Being this sort of
Spiritual
Dichotomy
The Trump
Comes
There's nowhere to escalate it from his after they want
To kill all of your children to drink their blood
Because it's a sacrament to Satan
There isn't another level about that
Until Trump actually sacrifices that kid to Satan and then they have to find a new way to make the left even worse
Where's the mat
I guess like you can make history altogether how bad a Republican
Governance is by how evil they have to make the left
It's a very simple correlate
The more the Republicans go out of their way to
Escalade how terrible the left
If you look at the Republican National Converse
Convention now you know how terrible
Trump is
Compared to
Just f****** but
Just as Bush wasn't like
If you don't vote for me
The world will
Yeah
None Shall walk
The Earth
That's how bad this comparison made
Pointed out that tracks
Chickens are out of power it's the talkies
Always fiscal responsibility and the budget
Through the concrete things and numbers and all these arguments and then as soon as they get into Power every
Becomes culture-war bulshit
It seems like that is
That tracks
What I
Be live experience
Yeah in my life I can't really claim to be an expert
Just tell me about the deficit Walmart
No deficit
Devil
So here's Alex and Tucker talking more about how creepy it is
Stop it
He has the only answer
And that and that
Cruz is Anointed one
And that the children of their Dupree
And if we don't do what they say we're going to hell
That is Jim Jones
We're trying to solve
Hereafter
We're trying to do this
Reason
Shooting
More significant
Support
For me
If my guy is
Messiah or I'm the Messiah
And you disagree with him or me don't do it
You don't do it
Looking at
Don't do it stop it
The person you're competing
Stop it
Is outside
How f******
Dario about the guy who's talking to
He who is not a right
The first stone
You make a lot of sense to give it to you
Is exactly what your president
Tucker
We'll see you in 4 years
So we get back to this VP thing
Alex wants to tease it by Tucker
Thanks
BP pet mean obviously
We just actions will always be my
My first choice because I think he's the smartest
On immigration and trade
Rodger Stone
But I tell you okay
To try to overthink
Play He Who you never heard of
Clinton for the CC
Up to women
No Organics
Session
Tucker W session
So Alex goes out to break
Tucker interview
Pimping
This interview with Rodger about the vice president
Rodger Stone
K102 BP is get ready
Find out in 3 min
Professional-grade he knows what he's doing
That's good stuff we want
To keep people around
Haircuts
Scream
Stop
At your stoplight
I'm sure that
Within a couple weeks of this episode either in the past or in the future.
But this is a good job
Because he does about job all the time doesn't mean we can't celebrate he has it within him
At this point
To do something
Presentation stand
Is
So goddamn
Foreign to me
Going to be nice
Just say I think it's acts like
You you texted me multiple times
There's no way this is not the same Joe it's not the same
It's so different
Like it's it's not like it's a cut-and-dry black-and-white there except
It became
Like what he is now which way
I don't even I don't even know be honest though the last 4 years of broken
Everyone
And it allows us to
Weathering the storm look at them
Exactly where is the to everybody's broke
Rolfe
Hello it's gray
So Alex comes back from break
And instead of going straight to the report talks a little bit
To setup the report
What's f****** cool
Too busy
And I got hung out
Everything
Because he just really
Funny really smart and fun to hang out with
If I were Rodger and I heard that
The sky
I could do whatever I can take over his business in Ocean's 11
Step two of the play at his complete confidence man is like I have achieved confidence
Amanda
Dirty rotten
Scoundrels
Bum me out
Special report again
And Alex.
Michael Caine this is really interesting because Alex is talking to Rodger but at the same time
Set up working four tens
To Rodger
Preston
Hard who is
Is the VP pick
I'm not going to tell you
What I think or what I know
We will
And I said okay well
I have no
That woman
Whatever
But he is on
Fox last Sunday all over
That's weird cuz he's talking to Rodger he's telling the story
Using him yeah he did this
Very strange
I got to say I don't like Corey Lewandowski
Everyone City pushed over this woman
Reality just shoved
Hii
I defended this guy when he committed a violent act against a woman now
Your measurement of you
Your loyalty to this guy is you protect
Him
The worst thing
That he's done but I don't like to be and mad that he doesn't hang out with you
We talked to drop and I don't like to be goes and does interviews where he says that he's involved in choosing the VP
Women over all day are we not going to talk him into the groundwater
Alex and Rodger had dinner
And
We get back to this
Go / gas
That Rodger had at Alex's
Half staff
To come up with
Last night dinner
But yeah
You've got
People really want to know
Obviously
CIA
Shooting range
Oh boy
Just an interesting Wrinkle in history
So
Will reveal
You I don't
Think that I've done anything to indicate
What name gets Trump
Not at all we know because
Spring 2020
They could have guessed my
They could have guessed somebody else
Didn't guess Mike I would like for you to come up with a list of
Three names that you think they are going to you too if possible
On the spot
Go from most likely to least likely
Alright
These guys world I'm going to go with number one pick
Ted Cruz
Okay
Alright
Number to pick
Number three pick I'm going to go with
Judge Napolitano
Supreme Court
You know that
Interesting
Try some pics I know that Rodger
It said some positive things about Napolitano in the past
I don't think I like Joanne
That was at Saint Joe, Missouri
I'm going to say that your first pick
Is flawed
Because you forget that this is during that period where they hated was was the Zodiac Killer
I forgot about that
Forgot
This is during that weird. Cuz Alex Ted Cruz before his tea party
Best well-spoken
Kinfolks and then
Afterwards after he submitted to Trump
He became good again. Especially during the primary and
Into the beginning of the
The General
Not like Ted Cruz Ted Cruz was the Glenn Beck
Canada in Craven until the ends of their
That's right every person should be followed around
People being
Ted Cruz's be like you're the zodiac
Every single day of his life somebody
We should scream that into a
His face
Okay
I think Buy
By process of elimination
I like myself
Would-be Senator Jeff
Jeff sessions
Session
Back to the Alabama Young
Republicans in the
80s
It's all Jeff sessions
Tucker Watson to be the candidate
Really excited
Greed without
Yeah it was hard to read because he was like
I'm making this s*** up
That I'm making this s*** up is behind reaction to Tucker's
Do you have any more concrete than I do
Which easily be like
Oh s*** I was going to say
That's how I read it
Exactly
I don't feel bad
Call session
Wow
Rogers
Start stalking other name
That he thinks
Might be in the mix
Mothers
Am I saying Trump has chosen set
Directions no
I think Johny
The senator
From Iowa
Under consideration
Miriam
And Sheldon
Very aggressively
Advocated Newt Gingrich
I like
I personally
Are some drawbacks
Consideration
Kind of drawbacks
I think the short list isn't involved
Doesn't matter if this has any basis is reality
We got to get 10 minutes
Done this is an evolving situation that in hindsight
The name that does
Become the VP
Is not meant
Around
Sure
So Alex
It's talking to Rodger here and
Yeah man
Session
It's got to be session cuz I studied body language
Body language
Literal
The body language expert Alex
They're just like simpatico
And then they have the same ideas about immigration
Going to be session
Is not session
And
Sessions
Becomes available later
Because he recused himself from Russia
Stop pain
Like that
I'm too weak for the Maga crowd
Turned on him
Primary
To get back into the Congress
They all knew
Everybody knew
And they still convinced themselves that they could
Pull it off
You know it's
At every part of this reminds me so much of
Reading about Stalin
Closest
Group of friends
And watching them disappear like
You guys all knew that he was disappearing people
Disappeared
Murder of equation
Look at it
Like 30,000 ft closer
You have
Like this
Glimpse of this 2016
Rodger that
Sessions is going to be
The VP pick
Shame
Out of the Maga community
They're complaining about Corey Lewandowski
Not involved at all
He's alive
Do you have that like
Trump's fear these people talk about that
Palace Intrigue about them that's so important
Completely irrelevant
You take it into a sharper Focus
You looking forward
And there's all these people who were there and now are gone
Greased or or heat Alex now
Just mysteriously berrykins
None of this stays
Yeah
I'm not I'm not saying that like
Every staff has to say
Completely
What is a high level of folks that are all gone
Really
And I think they I think at least the banana
Republicans
Flourish
Under a Centrist president that they can
That is where they grow their they become suck their butt
They blossom in the beautiful flowers of who gives a s*** about the
Deficit
Angry but they all get
And then
Then the gift
Power and they
Realize I was shity they are and they're like
Well it's obviously not
Spell literally
Yeah cuz I
I don't agree with
Arguments
Possibly productive people can at least like engaging reality because there's like
You're actually finally saying
800 billion let's atleast tell me about
795 or 850
Something you could look at and discuss if you like
Let's talk about our priorities
Right
Cataclysmic
Devil deep state
Centrist president a massive Pentagon budget
F****** love so much you get corporate bailouts left and right like you f****** love so much
Oh you have to deal with is a little bit of extra Healthcare
And that's not even hard
You want to make that so toothless it doesn't even bother people usually allows you to fundraise really well
Serta Progressive policies and
Progress made
Is enough
You can
Fundraise off it effectively
With your your audience
When they get power they like obviously we were right it's just sort of a larger version.
He works
Almost
Only in an adversarial role
Interdesign
Or
Just have it I don't know I would not be a competent person to speak on this but like
Reason for whatever reason
It seems to only work adversary
Yeah they do not
Seem to work
Actively when they're in charge
What do you mean for what but it seems like
A bit more competent in terms of capable of
Right
Borderline is not a great driver the others ham
Yeah
So we have one last
The wrong side of the road in Britain
So we are one last clip and it's
Alex has this pre-recorded
David Knight is hosting the fourth album
Answer when it comes in
He's boring as hell but he gives us exactly what we need
3 hours into this episode
Jones Show on this
Monday
I just mentioned that Alex Jones he says
A lot of news this week
Pentagram
Demarco
Play Five Points around
La climbing at Forsyth
Already had been.
Do that
Good job David
Thank you David
Little put the button on the back
Episode
It was pretty imprinting interesting to me that immediately address the elephant in the room
66 and apparently Alex had no idea
Clarity about Satanism as but it doesn't seem too important
Something like something
Distressed
As this episode comes to a wrap
I would say first of all I know that it was accidental and completely random
If you can see you at
Like the reasons that was such a
Interesting tie
To look over in
YouTube
To prepare an episode about I just
I feel recital unconscious mind
Yeah and it's amazing
Based on your thinking about the death
Knights devil is Farm
Cheeky and fun than Alex
Is dapple a boring devil
So much
More palatable
Despite the awesome
What's up
Much
Much better 4 years ago 100
Things that I've already learned cuz obviously I've listened to his shows
In the past
Is it ufer
Forget you forget that like
This show was
It's very different
Yats
I appreciate
Getting to experience that
And
F****** weird
You said
What do I
Tucker Carlson
Cousin be there
Of course it did
Rodger Stone
God what an amazing display of s*** head
Except except
It is it is one of those things where it's like
You just
Can't experience change over time
And uh
Suggest a road so slowly and you think today is still just as normal as it was yesterday
And then reminded
Time does.
Christ
I'm listening to
Episode 26
Back when I used to go to the gym all the time
Always say
Pink Floyd
Getting into shape
Something like you have to look at something from 3 months ago to recognize difference
Alex is erosion
It's become so normalized to us
Especially in 2020 like
In the present day
With
You notice many diversions is when used
To do
But I think we can
Forget
Like that that is not
Yeah he's always
Has been
I just wish that I could only talk about
Cuz honestly I hate him I hate him
This is a this is a simulation and simulation where we talked about
Descent into madness
We didn't get stuck in the simulation where Alex Jones switches gears
Hates Trump
We turn
That'd be a wild future anybody who's booking that guess what
The problem with our evil twins in this universe is I guess they would have no face
We're both bearded gentleman mustache
Mustache just mustache problem
I feel like if those are the two options and I would choose this
So Jordan
The past for providing this so this is this
Interesting
Longtime listener
Caller
Think that
Steven robbed
Shannon Robb
Nice
That's worthwhile song
Has like 20 kids
I don't know about
In the past and so I would assume
Is hypo also there was that whole time
When Alex was selling super male vitality
I robbed you
Boners too hard
Uncomfortable
I kind of see rub do is
Like in the movies the the mob assassin
The Hitman who just he's just a hitman
You know that's
Tuesday job
And then he comes home and he's a perfect family man he's completely divorces
His professional life in
His personal life
I could see Rob do being an amazing
Family discount
To work never would have
And it's still working
And did that stupid deposition
Never do that
IPad guy
I got to be on
I'm waiting outside
Help me find
Ready for
Shity shity remote
Hellyeah Massachusetts
All I got too many people have been like I use yours over learning and all that
Really mentally prepare yourself for
For s*** to come with
No I mean it's tough in college right now.
For them
I don't know ticular Lee like if
I understand if you're like just
Entering College this is very weird
No idea how you handle that
But if you are a couple years into college
The shift
I just
I have no idea
My heart goes out to people who are having to deal with it
That's
Situation
My dad's a professor and so he's talked to me about some of the issues of
Of the remote teaching and
And stuffing
I don't I don't know if he's
Experiences Universal by tell the teachers
Resume arriving to deal with
I keep telling my partner
Convince everybody
Toyota strike
There's just no
Functional way to do
Everybody's being set up for failure
And then they're going to blame them when they fail disgusting psycho that there
Being forced to play into
We see these new stories that are coming out about like schools opening and then
Closing
It's disheartening
I imagine there are also schools that have open
That have no case
About that possible
I'm about to make a headline
So
Possible
Obviously not Universal that their outbreaks
Falcon challenge it's incredibly hard
I was at the hardware store the other day
I need
Plant lights
To the guy there
Love these dudes at the hardware store they're the best
I swear I
Bilal
In Lakewood
But I was talking to the guy and we really connected
Boats
I don't know
What's going on
I tried to listen
To folks
Perfectly happy to wear mask
I feel like rudderless
Everybody has a certain amount of places where it's definitely the most
In higher education
Even just
Primary education
I can't I look if I'm a 36 year old dude
Who's self-employed
And I feel directionless
And like there's no leadership given a clear message
Can't imagine what it must be like for people
The responsibility to
Teach
A mentor
The next turn
To it it's a
It's a scramble
No one has any idea what they're going to teach
Nobody from the top who is supposed to be giving them like guidance is doing anything other than being like
Hey you guys have known
You know how to teach
Just dude you just do one of those
Just do one of the teachers
Have you ever teach them before then just do the teaching
Even though nobody is ever
Existed in this situation
That's okay
Absolute
F******
Disaster and a tragedy and it is going to explode
In everybody's f****** faces
So
Colorado did not say your name
I would say I like the look
Nice Dan does that call
Jordan
Stephen Amell
Good
Heard that was
Restarting the
I had
Or more
If we get rid of Jake
Still going to
My idea
We cut the gate
The water
Yeah it's
Time
Trump getting caught
Embrasure water
We'll figure it out
I leave that to you guys you're the
You are the tack
Alright
Get back to
Water
And it doesn't have to just
Political
Still
Do all the others
Deflate water
Not bad at all
Anyways
Get back to me
I like this because it's nonsensical
Eat twice said get back
I feel like I've got to respond
And I was saying let's do it
I'm for it
A better than gate
The water water
Shadow
All right here's another one
Wife from
Prison protest
Struggling everyday
Very much
Laugh
Family members
Overall
Take care
Enjoy the Sodastream
Yeah
Yes thank you very much
Is really important
Appreciate
You know there
Missouri is a state that is s*** on and look down on in the same way a lot of States particularly in the south
Are look down just a bunch of dumb dumb pumpkin
And I think it's very unfair I think it's a mentality that people need to train themselves out of
That's where the Columbia is at
The town
That is obviously the college
Call so very Missouri Town
It's very nice to hear like I still
A good
Activist
When I used to live there
Protest we talked about this
Every Wednesday I'll go out
Back then it was just the peace Nook
Bunch of hippies
Fruit leather in a basement
Yeah
Hazleton Patchouli oil change
Some books
Organized
These protests
Is very small and it's
It's nice to hear
I'll bet a lot of that sort of spirit
Definitely as
Iraq War
Continued
The movement got bigger
More people
Amore protest
But you know that a lot of that is still alive
In Columbia
That's one of the things that makes me think of
How important it is to like following
Support local journalist in Seattle
Like that because
The national news is not going to cover
A protest
In Columbia Missouri
Unless they burnt out
You wouldn't know
So many different places are holding daily protein
George Floyd
I know so many different places
Unless you were connected with it you know like
I follow a bunch of
I follow journalist on Twitter who are just deposit like a gray still Becky
She's doing incredible work in Chicago like that's the kind of stuff
You're not going to see on 2nd
National news so follow people around your area
Takes an investment it's hard to get
Define voices you can
Entrust
But that is a part that's kind of like
Where this advice falls apart a little
That is that like
It's easy to stereotype
Places
Like a like
Is right off
All of it
R2
The people in
I mean like totally
Exposure to bat spend a lot of time in various cities around
Even spikes
Springfield is a very
Conservative
City butcher
I'm in the same way that I feel bad that I say f*** Fresno cuz my
And there's a ton of people who are
Springfield Missouri who live in Springfield
Service to a lot of regions
Is that the country
Bye-bye
By painting with such a broad brush
That's alright
That call for
Hell yeah
Last call
It is Echo from
Georgia
Bartaco
We just finished listening to the most recent episode following up on
Alex
Great
Ridiculous
Heinie bullhorn
May I gently suggest
That
Tattoo of the
Tiny bullhorn and
A quarter for comparison
Just have it labeled on the bottom
Actual size
Like they do on like
Medication label
I don't
Wanted to throw out my
Suggestion for what
Could end up looking like
We really welcome
Shout out to all my siblings
Listening right now and thank you so much for keeping us company during quarantine
Hope you guys have a nice day
Thank you Echo that's a good
Mary
Them
Suggestion on the the tattoo
I will say that
Actually
That was straight talk
Next tattoo tattoos
That guys talk
My next tattoo has to be there's another tattoo my brother design
He designed the life is very fragile one
And he also has
Comic strip that used to draw Batman
Sure there's a panel from if it's really funny
It's called the all-nighter
Is a panel of a comic strip version of me
Smoking a cigarette
Staring at
Hungry Hungry Hippos board
Is if I'm studying it for like
Trying to figure out what's going on and it's just so funny is my next tattoo
You for sure because
I love that and I love
The art my brother does
And then I think
My next tattoo after that is going to be I don't know how exactly it is or the design of it
But there's something that really resonates with me about a banyan
Some version of that on my arm
Is
Something that I like my for I'm going to finish more birds
I'm going to finish my whole sleeve
The way up to my shoulder
He said top on your bicep
Yeah it is very connected
Is on your way
Can shoulder there's a bunch of different
Some things that I've kind of put together and I want to finally do a full like sleeves sleeves
So I'm working with a couple of people
Get a full f****** forearm sleeve
I feel like the real seal breaking for me
I feel like there's two hands
Yeah there's a weird social taboo that I think that I still have
Inside me some
Hand tattoos
I can have that has a little swirl that little spiral on her hand
Anti spiral
8 in the palm and even that I'm still like well you went ham
I don't know if we can do
Better it's less visible
Where are you I will obviously be putting some
Transmutation
My buddy Nick Kroll
He has running gags
Or like
Just anytime anybody said anything that was 8 letters tattoo
Is obsessed with turning pigs into knuckle tattoos
I like it
If you also have like Sonic
It's funny to think of better things
At my old apartment I got this piece of mail and the person
What was the funniest name
Culturally insensitive but also local job is an amazing man
That's eight letters
As a knuckle tattoo
You could live with yourself
Because at least six months for that I would have to
To hear you be like
Really regret this Pogo jump Scout project
That's what that holds me back
Appreciate that was a lot of fun
Of course
We'll see you back next time
Random episode from the past to do it again
Vacation for us feel like a next Monday
We can talk
The guilt Water of Life
It's it's it's
It's difficult
Like the responsibility to pay attention to the present going on
Drought says thoughts
I don't want to lose track of her
Goddamn was this enjoyable
So
Until then
Weave website
Jesus real local charity bail Fund in your area
How about the people doing
Dzx
I am vice-president Jeff session
Holding
Alex
Person coloring