Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for knowledge fight
We are the bad guy
Need money
I love you
Which is your
Yerba mate
Which I didn't even know what it was
I was responding to you making that faces I didn't recognize the
And I made a face at you
Oh well the theme song is always
And you still didn't run the song
And the only Interruption was mean
Yerba mate
Hi
What's up
I feel lately have been a lot of plant self-conscious
Stop.
But I
Perceivable future
Since you were last year
Installed
And I've installed a makeshift ladder
Vines
Bean plant
Something
Call Lon
Trouble
That's true
This up
And I like it so much
That I've decided
Like it's the season
Recovery
Walls that I can
Why not why not it's garden plants not I can create basically a
I will
And we really seem to weigh that it's grown and how quickly it has like
Photography Empire State Building
More involved
Community stuff forward
Once I once was more able to
Please find a community garden
Get involved and try and donate
Whatever is grown to food insecurity
That's not the worst thing ever
I'm still in the experimental phase
Seedlings coming up
Mentioned before cucumbers have flowers on them
Female flowers on
Peppercinis that much but I randomly
Sunflowers coming in
Crazy and having a good time
My bright spot then I'm going to have to go with us
Cobra Kai
She's about to go back to school and she's freaking out
Teaching
Is there anybody cuz nobody has any idea what's going on
Everybody scrambling around so she's staying up till 5 a.m. every night
Last night
This morning
Call Cobra Kai
And to this day
Ralph Macchio is the least imposing and graceful
Martial artist screen before
Martial artist I've ever seen
What is the wind speed supposed to be exactly
Who owns the dealership
Right
What is this
Talking about watching The Karate Kid
40 years after the events of The Karate Kid I did not know that
Kicking ass and then we all learn who's the bad guy
It's really good
I know you are really good
Is confrontational very tired
Herbalife
Episode
Frazzle
The. Of time from August 24th to August 26th
And I think there's a lot of stuff
Going on during the time. That especially
V the world
And
The timeframe of
The day after
Jacob Lake
Was shot by the police Kenosha
The shooting happened
Also in Kenosha
So take a look at that
Time.
I think there's a lot of stuff that's been going around
About
Social media
Inspiring
The shooter
I saw a few references to Infowars
Until interested in that and I wanted to pay
A particular Focus to it
Difficult
You coming in really fast
Responsible
And simultaneously didn't feel like I had it in me to do episode about something else and not talk about
What's happening
I just couldn't imagine feeling and saying anything and anyway appropriate
Just anything would be inappropriate even though
Sometimes it's more important that we ourselves and up
Listening to that I was in
We'll get through this episode
Policy wonk next up
Next
Then I'll probably want
The same time
That I keep saying
Christian Scott
Next Rihanna
Juliana
Money off at heroin
Barge
Thank you so much Jason
Take that generosity
Everytime I'm going to throw up
I was going to do it every time
See how long it took you to notice myself
Hey I'm trying to force you into this season
Well as asthma make you accept a reality for our
Bring told me if you are sitting down you are always right
So what you're going to do
Is it going to take that generosity to put it in a paper bag
You're going to head to the park with a few of your friends are going to drink whatever is generosity
To a urine donation center
Of your donation that they need
Good idea
The first time I went to a park
Drink my friends are so stupid they had a bottle of red wine peppermint schnapps
What are we
I realized
The brightness before we go
I was wondering when we were coming back
Forgot that it was forgotten
And I want to see the one of the things that happened
I wasn't drinking as much South
Is there a little bit
Depressed about Seltzer check
I tried to find a couple Jelly Belly
Has aligned himself
What songs
I don't know. Like there's a number of things that I
Found tried to order the mini can't
Something
Jelly Belly made 100 those and everybody was like
Jelly Belly sell Crystal Pepsi
With the
And it's 226
Pretty good schedule
Cuz you're going to get into the doldrums of Summer
What you got the strength
I think that
Viable
Couple highlights
San Pellegrino at a diamond
Addition
Box
Like it's a bottle of f****** $10
Just like 50
It was
Playing fizzy water
And then the other thing I wanted to bring up
Definitely deserves a call out cuz I have been very
Anti grapefruit
I think grapefruit sucks
However I tried the Limitless
Hibiscus
Very good 76 out of honors
Island
Another flavor
Conwell
Yeah I think so that's like
Fresco works
I don't know
Anyway
South Jordan
Discuss
I think it's pretty self-explanatory
The show why we didn't have an episode
Release Alyssa possibilities isn't very long
But I want to explain exactly what's up here
I texted you about this on Thursday morning lost some respect
Really tell what direction was
Many things that were happening
Not necessarily surprising
Process anything
In a manner that would make it possible for me to commented on it in a responsible way
Kenosha police shooting of Jacob
Call me Sunday August 23rd
There's the unrest
Stabroek outside
Turn on Tuesday
What is 2017 year-olds militia
Fascist jock
Killed multiple
Protesters
Kenosha
He lived in Illinois
Wednesday August 26th
Homicide suspect
Which Samba stuck as a police shooting
Trust is there with
Publix
Trust them when they say they didn't shoot
This person
In a move that I absolutely resent
The police released security camera footage
I watched it on Twitter which
F****** alphabet
Then on Thursday there was the landfall of hurricane Flora which was looking for ticket
Has a storm
When it arrives in Louisiana it was tied with the hurricane from 106
Before years ago for the title of strongest to ever arrive in state
Wrecker
That are being broken
Earlier in soccer formation
Tropical storms and hurricanes
When it came time to record an episode for Friday I realize that productive thing to add to this conversation
Listen and try and gain some sense of
Perspective
There's a difficulty for me professionally and that I had to do a seventeen-year-old shooter in Kenosha
And how there was a media talk
Encouraging sign of violence in the days leading up to
To the attack
Very quickly there were tweets talking about how Infowars had an article up promoting the militia that was in Kenosha
It involved with the shooting
Ernest a dude forget to point out that this wasn't posted elsewhere that
Just reposted on Infowars
Still bad
Screenshots were posted that militia trying to legitimize themselves by
And then on August 28th Media Matters released an article with the headline
Vigilante violence in the days before a gunman killed Kenosha
The protest
This article is fine pain analysis but it also isn't
Circle
In a couple of posts on Infowars
Which misses the reality
Extremist killing protesters probably believe in
Is the ultimate conclusion
This is where things get really complicated for me
Because there's still a lot that's unclear
To make a strong claim as I would like
At the point listen to Alex Jones
Alex directly contributed to this tragedy
I struggled with that because this was one of the points are my ability to retain perspective was really being
It feels like Alex helped Inspire this terrorist
My immediate reaction was sort of alternate
Pretty predictable eventuality
And how disheartening it is to realize that Alex was far from the only Outlet
From which the shooter has been getting the messages he was getting
I can't say with certainty if this guy was an Alex fan but I want to lay out to your house
It won't surprise me at all
Which is a lot of contact like he was missing from the Articles and Outlets like Media Matters
For months now
Against left-leaning protest
Hurting ramble about how Vengeance belongs to God
The answer
To that riddle
Which I didn't realize was a riddle
Is that you one of Alex's listeners
Might be men
To be the instrument of God's vengeance
Impact
Vengeance is
God has inched
That's always the twist
The riddle
Terroriser
You got strung up when you're done
We're going to terrorize you
From last April
Close attention to Alex
You'll know this is a theme but it brings up on a pretty regular basis
Princeton Sears him discussing how his listeners could be a tool that God uses to bring vengeance
Is June 30th 2020 episode
Scott
How does God deliver
God delivers
Real careful that you're at
Following God's plan
And you'll know when it's time
Possibility
Tell you what
Which could be better understood as Alex
Essential things very difficult
People to wrap their heads around as it shows like Alex Azar
Are Fascist cult religious
Programming
Where is the host
For running the Democratic Party
And everything
This is critical to understand because it's not
There's been a religious undertone
Current state it's just basically authoritarian brainwashing
Authoritarian
Alex wants a dictatorship
Is better than me literal Christian tab
So we should all go with the white identity
Most of the rest of his shows
Idiot
The heightening to religious terms also justifies whatever actions you listeners B
If you're up against a literal Christian devil
Really is it
So bad
What if you're able to convince yourself that the person you're killing is an agent
The same literal Christian
To kill them
I mean
God might even tell you to do it
I believe in you
They're going to figure out ways to take Act
There is no more law
Did I just speak
I believe.
An essential piece of the project
You need to be doing
When you're out
You're playing this game
Is the dehumanization of people you want violence to be carried out again
This takes many forms
Because there are many aspects
Stew how you see someone as a person
Each of us has different forms of
Butterfly the different aspects of Our Lives
What element is the rights that you have is this
Like how an identified agents work
This is completely unacceptable
If it's being done to a group you wanted Beach
You need to justify
July
Are these men
Federal Marshals but most of them are u.s. military
Bracketing
Why you're getting grass
And then you're getting interrogated
Because you work for a foreign power
You work with
Literally trying to burn the country down
Destroy the stock market
Bankruptcy economy
You're a military operation
List attention in kidnapping
Alex
Imagine that
It's because you don't have
The people enjoy this country
What is an effect of arguing
Test result UCR of a separate class of people
Disney humanization has another level to it
Tom's
Temperature
Equating protesters to quote
Obstacles to Freedom
Considered enemies of freedom
But
To me that psychological
Approach because
I don't sit here and see them as my
Freedom I think if you ask them they wanted
I'll be free to just like anybody else
Become
Unwittingly is
Obstacle
Become
Nicole's a Frida
When is American
In math
Willingham
Fight for their freedom
It's a trap
You know an optical
You're going to get run over
Use the cars running people over in the streets as a
The physical example
The opposition is not personal
Freedom
Obstacles
Coincide
On the road
This is pretty consistent as a mentality
People who have passionate political beliefs that are counter to Hughes
Idiot to the globalist
Tricked into a person has perfect ideology
This is at its core a convenient and cowardly
Without having to release
Explain his problem
He does this primarily because you can't argue for his positions and if you try
Really fast
Along with dehumanization another tactic
Secret important
Encourage violence against
It's a massively exaggerated mischaracterize your opposition
Whitney apartments on in Seattle with setup
Alex engagement
Freeway system, cold behavior in this
When he discussed Seattle
Raz Simone
A self-described
Warren
Videos of him running around
When was YouTube Channel show
Running around beating
People
Calling himself in his armed goons the police
Area affected by the autonomous zone is
In the State of Affairs has misrepresented to being with the areas under the
African Warlord
Obviously meant to paint a particular sort of picture of the audio
Does mine
Helps them just
Responding to test
Is there a protest in your city
That's a possible outcome if you let these leftist type their way
At the end of July Alex engaged his behavior
Piccalilli flamboyant
Claims
Themes for being sent out
To get all the conservatives
But it's totally confirm now
Soros deep state
Obama controlled Hillary control
Will be the decoys
Distraction
The leadership
The
Pro human pro-america movement
In finance
Government in the military
Your targeted for death
They may launch the attack
The safety off
Finger on the trigger
13 hit squad
Tricom hit squad everybody
Everything
I'm coming to kill you and your fam
Becoming
Business nonsensical claim
Total confirmed
Conservative
Languages L being targeted
Ultimately he ends up by saying they're going to come kill you and your family
This is the personalization of the exaggerated threat
Which is meant to make the audience feel too sensitive
Another example of this outrageous and embarrassing style of exaggerating your perceived
The weekend of July 31st
August 2nd
You took some erroneous and bogus information
Down police stations around the country that weekend
Because this is the time for all good men and women
So wherever you are on the country but if you're in Milwaukee
Austin Texas
Arizona
You are in Los Angeles California
In Miami
These are some of the towns
FIFA says
Saturday night
Country so you should probably take them
Behaviorism
Performance
Ridiculous
Information
The idea of a coordinated attack on police stations around the country is very sick
What kind of organizational centralization
It's less important whether or not
Coordinate attacks on police stations around the country
Because if they accept that
They have to accept the other side
Basically an army
Uncoordinated marching
Together
Backflip also highlights another important aspect of inciting violence against Target
Responsible
To do something
You created the feeling of impending doom
I need to act
Now it's being expressed that it's your responsibility
Do something
Alex is directly calling for people in those cities that do something to stand up to this
In their City
Stop these left-wing protesters
It also is a problem for Alex
Might not be legal
This is actually something Alex explicitly recognized
Themselves
So when we was sign responsibility
To do this thing
It's not that the thing you're saying you know you're suggesting is a right
Sing to do
It's that inaction is itself a wrong thing to do
There's something that must be done
Responsibility
Suggest
Really f***** up
Instant there was the July 28th episode of Alex
Kill list
Protester
The best thing to do
Quickly as possible
Again
I'm not going to pay
Everybody likes Santa Claus
Name
While we're here
Some days off
And just think about the future
Do they take down your country they destroy your bank account
A bunch of patriot leaders
What are you going to do
Cuz you always talked about when the new world order came in and when the you ended this
You want to go out to shoot those two blue Elmer's
I don't wear blue helmets
They show up in black uniforms and burn down your local courthouse
Run your life
Maurice speaks for itself
Because he believes them
It's pretty outrageous
Restart
Possibly someone
To sacrifice themselves
To take out globalist
Versed
Plan
About you in plan
What we're going to do
We can't just sit here
The leadership of the global
Stop
It's not something
Suicide attack
Takeout
Expose its Global Leadership
Protesters
He wants the audience to essentially
The same thing
Without having to
Constantly talk about killing
The average sick
Obviously can
Which is
In order for someone to really consider the idea
Supposed
Political
There needs to be religious significance
There needs to be some kind of
Way in which this is your fault dear listener that we're even in this situation
Which is something a Tilex actually does
Express
You better get
You better
Engineer
If it works and it's your fault
Minions or something
Most people are not comfortable
Generally most people are violent confrontation of verse mostly because adults realize that we don't want
Violence
So unless it's necessary or in response to other
It's wrong for us
Even Alex recognizes this
He acknowledges that offensive violence is wrong
Russell redefines any violence
We've gone too far
Politically
Offensive
Gene
Are saying
Kill kill
Bill Gates is coming with a y
To kill us slowly
These things that Alex is doing he's engaging with his audience designs
Says vengeance is mine but hey you might be a
Violence against protesters is wrong but it's fine cuz they're actually enemy combatant
If you don't fight them your city's going to Africa
Therefore it's your responsibility to fight back
May not be illegal
You have to create killas to protesters and someone might have to take one for the team sacrifice themselves to take out the globalist leaders
Severe
It is
Severe because we've sinned against God so we deserve to be fighting group
Wanamaker
Which is basically the same thing as killing everyone really think about it
We actually deserve it
Application for committing violent protest
Position
If you're a person listening
Do not surprise me at all
Protesters in America
In order to save the cont
Operates
Violence against
It has to do with what happened
When Jared Foster the protester in Austin was shot and killed
In order to make it a simple self-defense situation
Police headquarters
Rashad
We still don't know the man's name
Turn himself in to police and was released
White
Measure
Shooting
These clips
The more recent
Part of them wants to be like
Gyros
And then the other part of them wants to be like
What we didn't have anything to do
That so the easier thing for him to do is trying
FineLine that's yeah
Yeah
He feels he has the optic
6 that are necessary because there are protests
Audience are scared
That he can
You know play the self-defense card a lot more than
In other situations with a right-wing terrorist
Like when he spent
Mute store
That my son was going to visit my parents
Kick their ass
Unbelievable
IMovie
These acts
Are celebrated and rationalized
In a way that
I refuse to believe his axle
Whether it's
Subconscious or conscience conscious
The pattern that he operates in
It's consistently accident and justify acts of violence against people
It doesn't feel inaccurate for me to save it to the way yet
If they take what you saying
And one of the reasons that I
Just can't accept that he doesn't know what he's
He's doing is because Alex is disgusting
Very behavior in the past
What he was talking about film saying things about
Bratz
On television
Alex described as essentially being stochastic terrorism
Mudwing on TV
Will kill this guy
The CIA will
Kill this guy
Government
That was done
Telegraph
Confidence to their
Works
Embedded in the government
People
Create false whistleblower report
The leaked information to Media
Finally
Somebody else the muster up
The president
Kill the president
I hope somebody else does
From that Cliff we know beyond a shadow of a doubt
To do something
Then the field mode was doing that
But what's the accusation
If you're aware of this tendency or this
Strategy someone could use
Greater responsibility for your actions
I want to do a
Excuse
If he's aware that someone saying things like
The other responsibilities messages in more careful and safe
If you refuses to do so
Strongly implies to me that the ultimate result of violence against
The desired outcome for him
Either that or despite
How to literally incapable of stopping yourself
That would make that more like
If that's the case
He's just as condemned for not removing himself from the airway
None of this is to say that the shooter in Kenosha definitely listen to Alex's show and was inspired
I don't know that
Might not be the case
It might be the case
I've no idea
I can't prove it either way
But
I'm not positive it's even the most
Important point
Alex is part of a media ecosystem that operates in the same way he does
Some independent qanon weirdos incites violence
More than him
Some giant names like chocolate Carlson engage in slightly stealthier incitement
Define Act of terrorism
That's said I'm not sure if there's anyone who's been Alex who's as explicit
Terrorism tendencies
Whether or not the shooter was a fan of Alex
What happened to Kenosha is exactly the effect
Expect to see from the way Alex
Behaves
And I'd be very surprised
If we don't
Oxymoron
I see it as a possibility
I don't know I'm sorry
I'm sorry about that
Apologize
I have a dick
The apology was that you had to sit there
I could have gone to the bathroom
What about employment Optical sight
I really
Had to sit with this for quite a while
To really
Figure out
It's all there
Talk around
Alex
So much of this was about like Alex
Posted this article about the militia in Kenosha and like
Yeah
He reposted someone else's article
There's a chance that article. Repost
I don't know
This is probably
Not exist
Had no idea
No
It's really hard to trace a direct
Between anything and I think some people are trying to
Yeah I see some Twitter account
Trying to make that argument
Are you understand I get it
I understand why
I just think
I know I know it's all this
Yes this is what I look at all the time
I just think of it
Mi 4
More of a
It doesn't matter
If Alex had any
Legitimate Direct
Connection with this individual executor
Looking
He's doing
Is
Behavior predicates something like this
I am struggling
Is
Just the massive
Forest for the trees situation that we're dealing with here which is that
I don't care if it was Alex
Text Jones
Posted
Suggested everybody go to
What is what we're in
Is
Media system
Popularize and propagate
I created an entirely false reality
40%
So whether or not
Alex
F****** zerohedge or its
They're all part of this thing
That is cultivating fear and using it to create chaos
And that chaos is going to make the order of fascism
Seymour
News 8
All of these people
Social media influencer
It's a little bit like a
Childhood develop
It's like the parents
Impact
Bill Peters do the media like Fox News and that stuff is a lot of it
And what's more effective is going to be those Twitter campaigns those
Those Facebook
The names and all that it's really easy to internalize information
From social media without checking any of it
Completely distort your understanding
I don't know
I don't have a solution
Kill who's killed more cops in the past 10 years
How is it that
Cops themselves
So
This time span from the day after Jacob Lake shooting
The day after when Alex is
Knows about
The shooting of the protesters
Cuz I was interested to see
If there was
A compelling argument to be made
His work
Over those days that he was doing something
Insights
To leave Illinois
Post-modernism
He posted this article
He said a couple of things
We'll see what the
Conclusion we come to is
I think kind of fundamental misunderstanding of Alex's
Ideas here
He doesn't
Care if one person goes to
The whole idea is a shotgun approach
Every protest should have one of those people who
He doesn't care about Kenosha or know wherever
I'm trying to inspire somebody somewhere
But based on the fact
Brakes of
Being sort of a moth to the flame
Attracted attention
Is that at
Does not come up
It doesn't the water of waters is out
Restart to on August 24th
Red Alert Red Alert Red Alert 70 days after me Alexa
Overshadow the Republican National Convention
Has launched even more intense
Policeman shot at
Car dealerships
Black lives matter sign
Porch
This is the globalist
Program of total Destruction
The people are waiting up for the truth
So I buy starting a show with a red alert
That sounds right
Obviously Alex has no idea
Open this episode.
Is where protest
He further doesn't seem to be
The protest
Instance of convenience cigarettes on his part
What's interesting is how I take a picture of complete
I'm using it for his purposes when in reality
To decide how it should be used
If you punch me in the face and I immediately forgive you and we're able to grow who that experience
No third-party really has the right
To use you hitting me for their own app
You hit me
Experience
To get past it
McGee Florida
Is it someone might think about you
You would think
Is car dealership
Was Bernadette that's fair enough
Abc12 in Wisconsin reported that virus cause damage
I can't blame people for being angry
We have some damaged windows will be okay
As for the actual car dealership
The owners of that might not have been too worried about the
According to a tweet posted by BBC he spoke to the owner
But if it actually gets justice of Sherburne 20 times
I can't find
Professional journalists reporting firsthand conversation
Set a really wild things
Embellish
It seems like that kind of misreporting
Yeah that would be
Collect
I would prefer Justice they're like
This mentality
Personally
Victims
More important than money or things
Finger bikes with stupid particular
Car dealership
August 24th
Reporting Center in the media's coverage
Tester broken out
Images of the cars burning with the central Focus
To drive up to the rampaging mob
So kind of makes sense if that's the centerpiece of the coverage it's relevant
Social unrest
Ben is easy to report
Yeah I don't think people emotionally aggravated by a picture
Of the burnt-out
Car dealership
With the owner standing in front of it given to big thumbs up like
The owner burned-out building says
Also this is a small point but this car dealership
Announces audience
It shows that these people are just out to destroy cars
Pictures of the fire that were posted on
If you look at
Dealership sign
It's a marquee for the Bradford Community Unitarian Universalist Church which isn't
Nextdoor
Whether or not a business had a sign on it bring this up to highlight that Alex
Doesn't do any work
Because
Even care
No one cares
It's hard to care
And it's easier to live in
Dystopia
So for the first six minutes of every hour generally a special
Corey doesn't do that cuz it's not on most radio station
Traffic
I usually skip
Skip pasta cuz it's usually someone of the terrible voice over
I stuck around
Stussy
Who are well on their way
Contingent
Larger
Throwing a
I never want to go back
I'm telling you what I will destroy this country
A million people like me
Hours of August
Come down
Protesters in Kenosha
In that report
Bound plays audio the veteran
Zapata
California
Zapatos pokuty Shasta
The County Board of Supervisors closest violence
Jessie is about to supporting
He was pissed about covid-19 restrictions
Here's a little section of his weird phone notification sound effect
But I wanted to point it out
Is the little
And I'm telling you right now
That right now would be
And you better be happy
Southern people
Nautica
Goodfellas
Real concern
And nobody else is going
Apply the only person that has
Building
But you won't stop
My boy I hope you open your year
Actually listen
This is a warning
What's coming
It's going to be people with smaller
It's going to be raw honey
Sunday speeches Saturday
30 Whelen
Flags
It's a real
When you see the things that I see
I went to war for
I've seen
Ugliest dirtiest partyman
I've been in combat
I never want to go back
But I'm telling you what I will say
It has to be gas or Oil City
It will happen
Million people like
Unhinged
Combat
I've seen the ugliest of humanity and I was like
Phuc yea
Terrifying when you look at it
First
How to show on August 19th
Just faded into the background noise
Beginning
And honestly it's become hard for me to tell when something has me sounding like a broken record
Walking up bring up things that I talked about a ton unless there is an evolutionary shift in the narrative
To be fair
19th
Hey there everybody listen to The Show Must like read the news about Alex
Guys
He has been screaming about how we should be good killing everybody every single day for four months what do you do
He posted an article on Friday we've been doing this for years now
Protesters
In a very close proximity to Alex postic an article that endorse has this militia that was there
That is
That's not good
With this video of
Meeting
Completely misrepresents the bottles words
This Ranch at the supervisors meeting at nothing
You specifically
Because of covid-19
What he says that his fellow citizens
That was a threat about
County didn't reopen
Businesses
Recognized
Threatening
Those really good for the optic surrounding police brutality protest
So we took his comments and apply them to
Different situation
Jordan
Good reporting
Dan
There we go
It's so insane
But that's what I'm talking about
System has created reality
This guy is
I paid the government that I support that I love so much as absolutely destroyed the economy in every possible way
As they're pulling people off the streets and
And do you know who I'm mad at
You know like that's a must being say You must drive yourself mad
You know you have to losing
Like trying to control
Cognitive dissonance experiencing
You think you would
Maybe not
Comfortability
Eventually
Just like I didn't stay too long
Alex spends a lot of the beginning of this show really just
Painting app
Dystopian
Picture
Of what looks like in the ground around Wisconsin
Wisconsin
Where
Again scene
Third world collapse or Civil War
World Warrior isn't even
Strong enough
Describe it
Police getting shot at
Police being stopped by black lives matter, too checkpoints
Warehouses
Churches burned down
Treatment
In the back of the head with
Brick
Total loss
How to control
American flags being
Watch
Rolling guillotine
French Revolution 2.0
Alright Supply
What's
Head of the flag
Probably the Stars
Discusses
Apparently the video of
Long-haired hippie
Running up with his assault rifle
Menacing and
Ordering the police
And the police are so paralyzed and they do anything that they'll all be given the death
Ideal right there is huge
Because it's a central theme justification for the shooting
Police refuse to restore justice of course I'm 17 year old from another state that Justice
Authorities
Charge of the sea
Refuse
Accelerate
To murder
17 year old
Decided
Tucker's words
The five
The shooter did
Either he should
To take these protesters out and stop being so afraid of getting in trouble
Or he's saying that the system is setup is such that the police
His audience understand what you say
Yeah I'm trying really hard
Very hard to remain called that needs cream because I'm
VyStar
It's just not going to stop intro
Launch really just the way it's slowing me down
Receptively
We didn't actually cancel Friday's episode because you were too busy yelling
Very very
The process things in different ways
Memes
Meddling with plants
So Alex these these these demonstrations on the street is property damage and
Realizes that hey I remember project Veritas videos mentioned that
Amber what the Democrats videos
A year ago
Burn the cities ahead of the election
Election
Alex has project Veritas videos straight
He's referring to his original use by veritas
If Bernie doesn't win
I guess I could go for that
It's a bit of a stretch to just rewrite this piece of propaganda
Players in these narratives because he knows they don't mean anything
Truth to preserve in what
Veritas
Alex that if someone is stupid enough
Project Veritas videos
Probably stupid enough to believe that the Bernie Sanders Democratic Party
Organizations behind each other to make sure that if no cost would anything good happen to him
Episode
A car dealership
It's got a boring so trying to find
Some points for things could
Get tired of interesting
Nothing to talk about
Just listen to it
The criminals have censured
Everything USA at all
Has killed millions of 1.4 million died
Just last year
TBH
Block people stopping
1.4 billion people did not die last year for million people
TBH
Were the Rus bowl like what is it happened the biggest story
Probably way bigger than covid-19 10TV
Approximately
States
Numbers
84304 people got
What's going on is it Alex's actually fairly close to the accurate number of how many people died in the end
Tire world
From tuberculosis last year
Almost all cases are in Africa and Southeast Asia
3 particularly high in developing countries were ax
Vista Medical Care maybe properly
Which leads to many of the Dead
There is a vaccine that can be given but its efficacy
Princeton's people living with HIV cannot use it
Create a lifelong immunity
Still progress
Alex wants to use the statistic of 1.4 million people dying of teach
You lying and saying it's
Just coming in and infect everyone
That's essentially nazi-style propaganda
Statistic as Ally
Somebody saying
Immigrants and foreigners
Bringing in disease is some sort of Nazi
Next thing you know he'll be saying that his enemies
Statistic is there a lot of people
MTV and there's a lot of things so we can do
If we prioritize the proper
Creating cheaper high-quality tests particularly ones that can be used on infants
You differ
And that's something that the government could easily help subsidize regulations on the test manufacturers
Prices down
More money could be directed to research and breakthroughs in a better TV vaccines
Or less complicated drug regimen
How to care about the 1 million people dying
He only wants to use that number as a prop
The demonizes imaginary enemies
He's a piece of s***
Yeah yeah
It's the only thing
Everything is wrong
We have no solution
You should kill people that's Solutions
Make some difference
Tell me a joke
We are actively tried to kill all of this solution
With God
So Alex possessed with the idea of
Better
Noticing there's a lot of videos of people trying to run over protesters
Is just trying to get out of Kik
Alex has an interesting way of looking
This made me laugh out loud
I'm driving down the road
Forest fires
Police.
They're looking at
I'm going to
Compliant
Checkpoint
Well you're not going to like what
Your
But respectful
Hey man if I saw some cops do their job
Because I know Alex's career
In 1999 recalled police state 2000
In approximately 15 of the first 25 minutes of it is Alex gay
Here's some fun clips of Alex really respecting these cops were trying to do their job
Exposed
Hopefully
React
Their conscience
We are entering the eye of the check
Is it that loving children
Actually kind of hurts
I'm kind of a random
Capricious
Calling them Nazis
Pretty sad now it's his career before 9/11
Did he tell me
If I'm driving
And there's a forest fire in front of me and I see some
Set this checkpoint
If they're stopped checkpoint
Running a fire
That is a possible interpretation of what he said yes that is one reason of it
Cops beating of that
Top surgery
Checkpoints for your safety
In the middle of a city
Even take a step further backed up
Amatis there
Why
Do they have this checkpoint at a forest fire where the cops at the continent
Are slaves in California
Deschutes
The fire I don't know how to deal with that
I guess plan options
So are we back
Stuff Yer and Alex's
Tom Soros terrorist
Ordering the police.
And the policeman told by their leftist controllers
Supervisors
The Methodist so here's the fun
Here you see Alex heightening and
These are powerless to stop
What's happening in Kenosha
Include group
Documentation of things like
There's a video of the police in Kenosha
Protesters
It goes along with the argument
Situation
Even
That means it's open season for vigilantism
I recognize and realize that some people
Prince between one side saying
And the other side saying
The police and the state or not
Protesting
The property probably going to get damaged
So
He his name
Problem with t
Gentleman Square
Was that the guy wouldn't get out of the way
You know
Pocopson
California China didn't have a leftist government run the real problem was that the cops
Didn't
You know they'll let it get to that point the cops were powerless
We're doing great
I'll take some calls on this episode
Kind of fun
I don't know if
I was desperate
Looking for anything
He's talkin this caller
Trying to make an anti-vax argument
Love it and it's really this this
This is really interesting to me but this is also in that state where I was like
I might
Complete
Anybody
Discusses the Nuremberg code
The precursor
Convention
You cannot test
Is on people
How much you have in for
Because of what Joseph
Angela
And the Nazis
So what you're saying is incredibly important
This is in response to like I said to call a rambling but
Because the Nuremberg code says he can't force
Experimental things on TV
Nonsense for 100 reasons
Should definitely be opposed to the Geneva Convention
First National
18/64
Before the Nuremberg trials
Invention that took place in 1949 after World War II
He should hate them
Geneva rules are based on
To Any Nation sovereignty
The rules to including the provision of taking hostages
Help
Forcing people into armed services tonight
And they're bound to these rules by international law
That's globalism s*** that's pretty much what Muslim
And you should absolutely hated because he's cheering for the cops to violate those same Geneva
Interesting
Enforceable universally which is to say it doesn't matter where the crime was committed
And you know it
Where are the crimes committed
You got any knighted states Security Council
The UN Security Council
International criminal Tribunal
I recognized
Ineffective
Define discussion for another day
My only interest right now is this
Based on his fetish for nationalism
Each nation's responsibility
Tether
You can be a dance
Countries taking hostages
Torture dance
Absolutely 100%
If he's serious about his beliefs
While we're at it
You should be super upset about the nerve
Just got here
Local government keeps him awake but for some reason
Well I guess I'm glad
Support the Geneva Convention
But I'm still not going to give
To make is it Alex Jones is not a serious person
Don't know what is allegedly because he hasn't actually sat down and bought them out
He perfectly happy to yell but nationalism all day when it's a mask that you can use to hide his white identity police and opposition
The social justice
Weirdly
Nationalism
Obviously unpopular
Like opposing the international
Nationalism
Book
Ignorant piece of s***
It's just it's just a socialism is wrong
Fixed-income Social Security taken care of
Just shut up
Spell cloud
You realize that like
Alex
Just some
Dumb f***
All of that
F****** freaked out on weird
Conspiracies for a while and now you yell about the devil
You didn't know what your beliefs entail if he was up here talking about how I get
Good
And given a trial in Germany
They committed crimes in Germany in the German government
He doesn't do that because he knows how f******
It's not
There's two things
They're all held
To this weird subconscious standard
Progress
Becomes accepted
Like
Jeff sessions
I mean his ideology is
Do you know what I mean I mean
Doesn't matter if they're not trying to make you
They're just trying to make you
It doesn't matter if what you're afraid of is really doesn't matter of
Carlson is actually telling you the truth about how
F****** kenosha's on
Flame is that you think it is it's
Is what's going to lead to situations where some assholes
The time
At the same time
Specifically
What I'm complaining about
Is that Alex has ended because it makes sense
It makes more sense
Next clip
No doctors
Lowest
Span
Sure why not
Doctors live less Long Live
Then combat
So you can find an article in the Scientific American from
1850s that refutes Alex's claims and you can find a stud
National
6 in the UK
Definitely also contradict
Speaking physician Turner
Top of most
Some of the reasons are usually offered to explain this
Because of their profession
Live jobs
Physical activity walking
Tyra not to be discount
The job satisfaction and position within Society
Almost everything I can find on the subject
Feels like Transportation where you might get exposed
Bachelor life
Second season Doctor
Portland
Issaquah
Let's fucken hope so
Action cycle
Bob Marshall who's running through the primary
Virginia Senate seats
He's also a huge, so
Boston House of delegates
It's in Virginia
The game
Tracey Thorn beglin
District judge
Marvel Justified is opposition
You could preside as a district judge for a marriage of two guys if you wanted to
In violation of the law
Moreover if you have a barroom fight between homosexual and heterosexual
Wow
His actions Marshall pointed to a 1997 study
Decrease life expectancy between 8 and bisexual
From 1987 to 1992
Study of come out and said that these numbers are no longer relevant
And they really like the HIV aids crisis
Is still an issue but it's not nearly as bad
Southpoint
For some context
The CDC reported 36.3 deaths per 100,000 people
Compared to 2.7
For 100,000
In 2010
How do you make improvements on understanding
These will become even smaller
There's a sharp decrease in hiv-aids which was the main driver of increased life expectancy in the gay bisexual
1997 study by Bob Marshall
The Defense Force out right now
Jumpy got heat from the Press about it and he stood his ground
Members of the right-wing
All you got to do
Confirm
Is a district judge
Dumb dumb
Bob Marshall
Years that Alex counselor just makes up his research
Strickland reality
Or some picketed right-wing talking points
Kind of remembers hearing at some point
Nothing means anything
Single-sex
Add an
I just don't have the heart
Energy
I hate them all
Alex
I really excited
Virtual
Cold
20 ft 4
And I wear this
Sleeping around
It's really great and awesome
In unrelated news ABC reported on Friday that at least
Support staff
Speech in Jacksonville Florida but actually had to cancel that
Actually I lied
Originally planned
According to an MP
June 11th
President Trump formally accept the nomination as a Republican president in Jacksonville Florida
Instead of Charlotte North Carolina in late August
North Carolina governor Roy Cooper
Coronavirus
He was supposed to give his speech and Spa in Charlotte
The governor
Baby Buddha speech to Jacksonville Florida
Fire
I can't put this more simple
Just just
I don't want anybody died but you need to be in the hospital with the right
Time do you know what I mean like let's get him in the hospital when they
Do anything about it
Just keep them away
Play keep away
Sitting down
Realizing of Trump's RNC plans
It's in the middle of a pandemic
I felt
Really intensely embarrassed
When Bush was president
I Was An American in Europe
Bush was president
Almost there cuz that was
What like our third week
Do in the shower and
The very first words I said we're just like
I'm American
I'm sorry
Just sorry
Guys Auto
End times
Your self
Myself one time
Do every morning
Lawsuit
Googling yourself is how you find out you've been so good
Mail it to you first
Ulcer
OK Google
Get the f*** out of here
Starting your show with a red alert Red Alert Red Alert
It's searching like I don't understand those people get off I'm just like constantly
Scrolling through to see what terrible things people are saying it is not good
And
Boot socks
Alex it is solute
Total
Lawless
Is it going to rain
The fam is now that he is
He got some of the videos
They've been circulating
And it's
It's obvious
Is marxist
Agendas are now beginning to
In our real-world
When I showed up last night
Garbage truck
Just lined up
Fire
And then out of nowhere there's this
Police Squad Show
Matter militant
Sarms
Police officers
Leasing
Shadow
Policing the streets
Worried about the hour 40 mark of the program
I realize that Alex hasn't even mentioned
Plenty of discussion WBLS
You were listening to this
Test
Is episodes from August 24th
Jacob
Who shot in the back
Multiple times by Kenosha police officer while the children were in the car
Thankfully Blake survived but according to his father he's paralyzed below the waist and it's unclear if he'll ever walk
Again
I'm not really interested in litigating the arguments about whether or not Blake has a great person or whether or not it matters if someone has a knife
To justify this justify the police officer
They're shooting someone like that
There's a reason that people were protesting and some
Which broke out
Another on our black man
The officer was shot
Put on administrative leave later
But it's clear the people weren't accepting that is an appropriate response
Cop fired seven bullets
Set this guy there's no reason to think that that wasn't something
Or at least
Incredibly negligee
Denton in weapons
Whether this was a cop trying to kill person or copies in Compton enough to shoot a person like this
That's not someone you really want on the streets with a gun and a badge
Kenosha's not my city so I have no right to say or should not demand their officials and enforcement
I don't think I'd be satisfied with administrative leave as a response
I think you could
Probably go by the Geneva conventions and do a better job then
Hasn't talked about that at all
I just surprised it seems like it would
No that's a big piece of context
Kind of pretending to protest it's probably a
Flashmob organic response
Straight up
Sucks I believe the matter is a y
I seen a black
Cohoes the YouTube show called lives matter
Basically ologist videos
I just had a visceral right there videos just look like clickbait ass titles
Are basically just be anti left-wing content your
Everything it seems Progressive
Supervisor program
And to pull down webcast
These guys are real s*** head makes me sad
He posted a video from Breitbart
You can hear the remind me
What's the date
Is August 30th so that
Run away from accepted
But I heard a rumor that situation
People demanding
I'm scared
For his life
Videos for
There's a video purporting to be people trying to torture house and it's just a firework
Number videos that are supposedly
Violence in the streets that are just fireworks like this
Yeah it's
It's hard not to shake with rage whenever you see
Twin
Nightmares of the far-right
Them
Being the out-and-out
Aggressors
Nightmarish fascists with their boots
On everybody's f****** throat
And at the same time
Them being afraid for their lives they're terrified they're the victims of his awesome
Illinois
Trailer for Dinesh D'Souza
Dinesh D'Souza redpilled me in 2016
2020 is now your turn
Even for you
On the lighter side
From the night of August 20th
He's either in Minneapolis Minnesota
Flights from
Correction Wisconsin
Annapolis
Minnesota
Amazing level of incompetence
Completely accept
Goodbye right-wing propaganda
Celebrating ionized
Tucker
Yeah that's a good
You're going to get what you want and if you don't ask questions
Bring me stop my research into
I know people I've decided to play the game where they take people were shot and going to something that they may have done in the past makes him somehow.
Deserve
Doodle on the other hand is a sociopathic monster
August 27th
Rosenbaum was arguing with someone
Technically mr. Rosenbaum gave consent to be shot by militia
Cool
I understand about the shooting of
Wildlife Refuge standoff
I bet we mentioned that he kept yelling
You're going to have to shoot
And that might have been
But someone might see that is just text
I feel like a difference
Reaching into his jacket
Find a loaded semi-automatic
Like also the footage
About
Like it's from earlier
It's not connected to the shooting itself
That's that's the type of ship just like I
You are given up on
There's no point
You're gone
You're you I have no interest in talking
Do you or existing at all
Street
It's going to be cover
Gregory Cinema
Does insane
Play last night
Crazy by the way when I tell you food
Quality
Are we back to food
Starbucks food
Is really annoying
I would say
Patterns
Very
No they rub me the wrong way here's an example
My message
Just hoping that Donald Trump
Or just hoping that you know like guys like myself or Alex Jones or Savannah
How old are you
Do so much
We can only stay
We can only cover so much
It's the everyday American
And do something and say so
Bled
This moment
Alex
For this moment
Because whenever freedom is on the line sacrifices have to be made and that's where we are
I mean this with all the disrespect of my words imply
Don't listen to what's more we enter the breach
On this
Saint crispin's day
We're going to do it guys
You saying how old are you is really
Appropriate
I just took you sounds like a child why what are you doing
Ends up getting
Just take over the country
Honestly I don't think
He gets that most of the right-wing media personas job to incite anger
Any idea what do you stalk
Size lollipop
The cigar
So
Savannah
Time she had important
Let me tell you
Did you go to record store
No
So there's a real twist
Was
Like a civil war out there and you know Alex you always use the word arranged when you're talking about these leftist and I was talking
Do we see that they're deranged their demonic
Was exactly that
The people there are demonic
They're evil
This is tough because
There was a shooting in Portland on Saturday night
Unacceptable
Violence
The made of
Involved into protest
If it was a right-wing person who pulled the trigger arrested
I hope they get arrested too
Killing people is not cool.
Generalized opposition to killing people I have no idea what the circumstances
Thesaurus
Comedone much more
I do want to just save it Savannah gofucker
Portland to report on anything
Hangout
The other thing I want to say is that this episode is deeply and
Hayirli about stoke
And heightened tensions around me street protest
Alex
Ignored the shooting of Jacob Lake
Black supremacist group
Interview does very clearly intended
Protesters in Kenosha
Potential Threat not just to some building
The very existence of America
City of Savannah
It's weird and I'm almost certain it's not intentional
Singularly focused episodes
There's some random instances
Getting lost in the woods
You're talking about TV your nurses
In terms of content he's actually dedicated time to
Entirely
List of the biggest threat in the world
It's pretty bad in hindsight
Probably
I think one fundamental things
It drives me insane about these people
Is just like
All the left-wing protester
Foaming at the mouth are demonic
One side
The line
Has medics
And the other one doesn't one side
Cares enough about people to have met
And I would guarantee
Through f****** clenched
Teeth
If one of those Patriot pay
Beating assistant
They would f****** get it
True as well
I don't know if it's right
Ringside
Of things doesn't have
I don't want to say that for sure
Savannah
Those are secret antifa
Corsair secret K-pop
What is the framing of these people is like
Is
They also have to like
What I have to wrestle with the idea
Involved in protest
Yeah how do you do that
People don't know is that the people in those neighborhoods are
Actually encouraging
Thank you for everything that you do
And that's what made me realize that
Exactly
Going to Kentucky
In Charlotte
Communities understand
Issues
Sport
Send a text
The rest of the country Portland has a Democrat
Essentially condoning violence against protesters
I do not seem like something that they would
Alright that's true
Broad swing
Are like better organized organized
Nice
But it's not a well-organized
Melissa.
They have vehicle convoys have people on mopeds they have their own press
Can I see know exactly what they're doing they're coming to your neighborhood
Every single day bcnu City being burned down
Literally
It's one of these degenerate child molesters the most of them
Cool
Really man
I wonder what Jesus would have done is Facebook
Let's hold on with the violetear guys but I mean
Confirmation
Spectrum
Because they're friends with the proud boys
And then he brings up something that
Took me in a flight of fancy
Avanza bugging me forever
Chicago
And I just asked her why not
We just asked
Perhaps
So we can meet
Portland
U-Pick Portland because you asked
Not good
As a reporter
Resent
View
How the proud boys are the best people on the planet
And I really had no interest in anything else
They like me
Obvious answer like I was more surprised he said that
Kind of ghost
Chicago come on Savannah
Absolutely
I don't know
I don't know.
Assumption
Listen to ameliorate
The flight of fancy
Me running into them and then just
Talking about 2000's
Kman
Because roads
Charter Charter
Slide your way through
Come on
I wouldn't even pretend to even bring it up I still think Infowars is what wasn't
Oh yeah yeah yeah
I want to talk about
Port
I wonder how they respond
Complete
Was completely forgot I totally understand
In this next clip
This is where my mind got blown listening to this
On the scene
Monumental
Weather report
Broke his finger
Selectively Obama victim
Very wealthy
Antifa
A lot of the people in those videos that have
Thomas and
So this supposed
Too close to each other
On August 22nd
Hand
Roberts
Antifa
Obviously he's opposed to fascism
Someone who's hurt
Even if he supports one side
There's a press hat he's literally
Figuratively wearing
What's interesting to me though is that is actually there
If that's true how's that any different
Great reset
She's there with
He's explicitly and definitively there is
If anyone takes
She's not very good at don't
Doing it so it's okay that we are doing I also I reached out to
To say he wasn't there for.
How do you respond to the accusations
I'm not working right
That's fun
The thing about
So well no wise they have to have
There has to be independent press on the ground
They know everybody knows why
Cuz you can't f****** trust
Announce
You can't trust the national news media Source because that's not what they're for
A lot of people
Fila calling
Towards certain
Total
It's just you can't rely on the information and you just can't allow info
If I can control the narrative
Interesting
Is Savannah goes on to talk about
Brick broken finger
It's
She's clearly only talkin about him
And then gets into how there's
Fake press
How's this fake
Breast settings
And then presented as if it's something that's happening
Certainly implies that
Savannah
Real dumb
She's really bad at this job
Basically it allows us to have any cities
Because he's forcing people
To say okay we need your help
If you follow what you're saying and then
He is describing what Alex's said is the globalist plan for the last 20 years
Call back Galion dialect
Or the problem reaction solution
Cedar Creek
Which will elicit a reaction
From the public
Then magically the globalist will be ready with their solution which was their plan all along
One example of this thinking and Alex
Coronavirus
Outbreak
He believes that the globalist
Created this virus and or heists
Which is the problem
Is problem reaction begging the government
Vaccine microchip
What is the solution
From the jump
Except
Who created a solution
This is exactly the pattern that Savannah's describing words
If you take what you saying
Is Trump allowing these protests
To get out of control
To come in and put down
Solution will be an unconstitutional authoritarian
These people are f****** stupid stupid world
Anyone who listens to the show
Hold on
Compass intentionally allow me protest to escalate the situation
That probably means that he's wanted to do something he could
Out of control
Any half-decent conspiracy theorist
Goddamn
Well I mean it's when you all when you don't have any creativity whatsoever
Your enemies can only be doing your ideas
And since your ideas are on creative
You're just by telling me what your enemies are doing you're just saying what you
You are only capable of Imagine
She's not
You're not supposed to
Define your enemies
The same way is your hero
Reaction solution
Explicitly
Globalist
It is well
Purposefully killing off your citizen it's not something that's like
Bomb trick me into eating my vegetables
That's not the hegelian dialectic
If Trump is doing this than you are just telling me that Trump is murdering
So
We get to Savannah
Really weird
This is a very important election probably
Comfortable
Because Donald Trump has been in office
The last defense
President Donald Trump in office
Our country
Love she's talking about
Comfortable
Regardless
No one is happy
Isn't the entire premise of Alex's show supposed to be
The public is suffering because of the globalist
It simultaneously soros-funded militant
No it's almost like
And yet
Just can't admit it such
Bulshit
Anyway goddamnit
So comfortable
These are the most comfortable years
That's why we're having the most important election
Because we're so comfy
So Alex Goes to Kohl's while Savannah and Gregory sarsfield
This caller
Interesting
It starts off
Alex
Speed dating guy
Message to get out the trunk
I think one of the major things he needs to do
Is go
Open fortnite
Show us the gold
Show America
They're going listening
2009 Mariners
We're not doing this anymore
I don't care
I just don't care man
Now that's a protest that I if the right-wing was just walking around show us
Gold Lulu
Show it March on Knox
We can have
Cuba Gooding jr. Ramen and yellow show us
Jerry Maguire Style
You had me
Recorded a video
The night before they got really popular super excited
This is
Thank you for taking my call I actually was on
Teen in Kenosha shortly after Jacob Lake
I was shot and I took
There is no other conversation
He wants to talk about this guy's video
So that's cool
Show us how
God's name
Can you possibly hear those two things
And be like
Honestly be surprised
He didn't even register or what
She's complaining about protesters being bailed
I'm stuff
Bright
The ACLU legal observers dare
Animal organizations
What's antifa
See who got arrested
Building
There's also the national lawyers Guild
Your number on antifa members
Does the power structure is behind them in this complete
Evolution
Alright
I dug.
Okay
Okay alright
So these people
One legal Observers
Communist
Are are watching
Protesters
Take him to a holding cell
Held are for hours upon hours
And they are saying that is because
The power structure is behind them
So
To break
The 24
Where is all the money and all the power
All the doll Hollywood
Are the rebels
You're not the rebel
Quenching George the third is on your side you're not
What are the rebels
And we're going to win
But the tree
Devil worshiping Phil
Person you're amazing give your info the producer please
What do you want to guess
Has really sucked up
Police stand against
Tubi
Expression
The kill you
Protesters
Keppra pick your the rebels
So that was really bad
That was bad
Until we jump to the 25th
The show off
Existential Danger
Are you going to let him win
We have the truth
Something
Is Vape
Alex's
Continuing to
To play drum pads promotional
Trump campaign
So I noticed this was continuing
Kind of pinky mice
Breaking federal election
The problem
According to the SEC rules
You might be in trouble because of disclaimer
There's no disclaimer at the end of the Avid Alex Blazek
Clearly says
Which is a requirement
Political action committee
And if it's not there needs to be a just claim it indicates who's responsible for a vet advertisement
Like if there's another political action committee that produce the address
Pretty clear that the exemptions for political ads are pretty Limited
Show me cases that disclaimers aren't necessary or instances where they wouldn't be feasible like in the case of promotional pens or Skyrim
I bet the ad does have a disclaimer in the visual
On the radio
I'm not sure
Cuz anything to worry about even if anyone took this
I need to be a lot of stuff
It was next cool if we get
Disclaimer
No Alex
You told me to really kicks.
FIFA
Decoy
Remember who did
If you're in a war
Your laughter
But from time to time he will tell his listeners not to go after
She gets hot
Annotation Focus On high-priority Target
I don't find this compelling or expelled
Cotorrito because he also says
Because their enemy combat
Self-contradictory
Music
You spent about his violent fantasies regarding what he wants to do to let through
Is metaphor also doesn't make any sense
In war
You absolutely go after privates
Less time than generous
Congressional research service release numbers about military casualties in up to July 2020
2349 active service
First persons killed
The embarrassing renamed operation enduring
Freedom
These approximately 10%
We're officers
Approximately 50%
C134 and in the army
Private first class
Special
Before our price
Rex
This makes sense because typically in a person ever going to be able to fight
I understand but I would says he's warped sneaking into soros's secret underground compound and taking them out with
And now you understand the far-right
Alex is not getting fire to perform targeted assassination
Everybody knows, the only effect
And the only people for them to fight realistically our other private
Does not have access to metaphorical General
Send it
Higher likelihood of metaphorical privates
I just fine I find even these caveat stupid.
Caviar caviar
Hellboy
For some reason Alex is fine
Bringing up Jacob
The individual that started all the latest
Dieting
Wisconsin
Just got in today
Jacob Lake
His mother called him on him he's he's got a sex assault charges
Charges dropped all these drug charges in a rap sheet
Long
I guess Alex is finally decided to talk about
I said earlier
Bearing on whether or not
Games a transparent attempt
Which is what Alex has to
The only thing I want to point out is that I was lying about Blake's criminal record
He was charged with sexual assault against an adult in July
According to their research
Other cases in Wisconsin court records include a traffic violation and custody disputes
Sexually assaulted
Look meme
What someone like had was 3rd degree sexual assault
Definition of third degree sexual assault
In Wisconsin that's not specifically a crime
Committed against an underage person
It is
It wasn't intentionally misleading mean
He doesn't know work
If you can say to someone having a traffic violation and custody disputes is a rap sheet 80 ft long
I guess Alex has a rap sheet 80 ft long
Because
Coming up for that DUI
Alex Wood
Justify his own police
He's been
He's been sued by the southern district of New York
Yes
Sandy Hook families
Cups
According to Alex is only could shoot him at any time
And he'd be fine
I just imagine how it's reporting on that
I think you may be right
Whether he was
I guess he
God I hate everybody
In Kenosha
It's
Seems to me like
I'm read the article that's up on it
Demolition tries to stop looters and rioters
Bored.com
Borden
I said huh
Weird
Hanger with his new friends this is where I
For one second I have to like stop
To avoid
Becoming the conspiracy theory of my own
Isn't it suspicious that
It's it's conspicuous in its absence is
Took a second to get over but there was a
Confusion is going on
Kind of weird
Completely oblivious
Read his own articles
Because she wants to hang out with his new friend Boris really got a new class
Entering the circle
Deanna Lorraine
Congratulations on that hire
The bad news
Weirdo
Real independent contractor situation
Fire Doral
Who we saw come up on a recent episode
I'm just really trying to think of
20 years on the internet
Such a Justified shoe
Shooting in Miami
So
The last thing they ever wanted to do
What
Jacob Lake
For Infowars is somebody with
The same patterns is Owen Shroyer
But somehow and annoying are more annoying
On the road but
The last thing they wanted to do the problem is that it's not the last thing they want to do
A lot of other things that they want to do
Justified shooting
Alex discusses a little piece
Putting out a fire in the dumpster
Guy with fire extinguisher
Chaka of course
Alluded
For sure
Shoot them with a riot
Shotgun
Okay
Seriously
Defend your businesses
Shotgun
South
CertiFit Matic
But there're other ways
To handle console
It never occurs to
Gun
There's one other way
That's not good
Here's a
This is what keeps me up
These people exist
Thinking
People still
Continue to exist
Continue to be ministers to society
So
Is Roundup
Wow
50 million at least that were rounding up and putting
Bizarro world
Appearance because you have
Rebuilding his entire career
Hazel guess to say all these left
We can't be a menace to society
Do not recognize that like
Pretty clear
This
And I don't care
Problem
Really starting to feel like it's not
There was a problem
Problem
They're working with the Devil
Aggressive
At the mall
So they're coming for Maxine Waters that I was talking about was from June 2018
If I was trying to take a, but she made over 2 years ago
Pacific connection
Does he require to prove causality
A frightening recent cases
I don't think that either left types are really the whole into represented Waters
Very rarely hear my left-wing friends talk about
Right-wing Dum Dums
Yeah
Not responding to till I got
Alexa
With 80% of the vote
Trump's going to win
Going to try to steal
What they're going to try to secede
What's happening in the economy
Bali food
Alex wants
To talk to Q
Because
It ends poorly
Start stalking
Really confused
Black
Church Someone shows up 10 minutes late and then sit
Investigate things
Diligent
Massive
Campaign is working on that
Is abrupt
Is a word
I don't understand
Analogy
Is racist
Somehow
I guess it's like that
Sing that all black people
I thought it was
It was along the lines of
Black churches are well-intentioned people who don't want to do the due diligence and research
Describe. What do you think he just said that they was said in front of the pool after 10 minutes
To the cute are you coming late to the black church so you don't understand what
He came to the cube
So he doesn't understand all that's going on
With the intricacies of
Song you're still you're still
Prime's for the goods
Whatsoever
Special Report
To the crew
Mom's mad
Jesus
Special Report
Thank God
Explain that metaphor
10 minutes late
Front pew
Vicious media
He's like hey
If you have something good you're still going to have these infiltrators
Educating liberals
Dylan wheeler
Is a
Freemason
In a satanic
Close enough
Information
What is entropy
Trump is a demon
A wake-up call
This isn't just some person who turns out there with her or something
Cuz they did such a
Good betting know it's that's not based on any kind of research
It's just people on the internet
Also clearly like
I initially misunderstood that black church comment
My initial assessment
Clear Lake
I think he's trying to say that
Church
And
There are the old-school conspiracy theorist
You know about the Bilderberg Group and all that and whatever
People turning into cute people to show up late and sit in the front row and
Understand
Or something I'm not entirely sure it's a weird metaphor that doesn't really attract think it's not as bad as I
Initially thought might not
Here's what I hear you know what here's what I think we got stuck too too far in the weeds
Here's my problem
This guy's just never been to a black church
So that's all that's my problem before we even get into the meaning of duplicity
He is never been
Yeah
So this episode Mal descendants
Submit the cues
I hate them
Don't mind I don't care at all
McHugh people to his Revenue stream cell
I don't care
Alright
Watch a show
Successful
Country and western
Music music
Multi-talented
Country music
Comedian
Channels weird
Here's a joke
Dakota
South Dakota
Campaign for Texas governor basically entirely on his
Supposition
Also second side note South Dakota is basically a rectangle
If you wanted to make a rectangle
And save itself
Dakota
Do that
Also maybe these other states don't make all these dumb s*** shaped like their state cuz they're not painfully insecure
Also
Texas waffle maker isn't Maiden America
I've seen that joke
Kill two men
Watching the future
Murder on the line like that just wondering what am I doing with my life
Is talking is the guy who I mean obviously
Comedian so I don't know
Exactly how much
Commentary to take literally like some of it being f****** around
No
Everything's literal
That's the way I'm going to take funny funny can be pretty subjective there's a lot of things I think are funny but I can handle
Look at
I get
Did this is an attempt
To be funny and maybe some of the different sense of humor
To track sometimes now I don't know
So anyway Chad
Peter strzok
The FBI agent
How to take the flight
That's the effect of an anti-bullying campaign
The stand
Playground I can tell you that
Call me a bully
They're about out of them anymore
True patriot
My boys right now
Mission
To stand up for yourself and take
Them
Winit
It's a debate when you're talking about
Bullying in
Throughout history
Have the funniest people
They have not been the comedians that everybody
Then why A2 from the 25th
Yeah
Remember when I video on around me that chicken place when I was younger people
He makes a start
Confession
I just completely casually
Autumn the third time doing it
GameStop
Down the article
An idiot
That's not even technically
Alex is a murderer
The Austin Statesman
Apparently they should have said that Alex was a murderer
Confirm
Alex
Some people said that
It's almost like this is what happened
Bullied enough when they're growing up you know what I'm saying I'm sick of these anti-bullying campaign
To keep bullies from being bullied
Give me 5 minutes on Spotify
Probably now we get to the 26
Night
Shooter killed two people
I was pretty
Again I am your house talent show
Well in a few minutes we'll play you the clip Hillary Clinton
Has come out
Politico interview
Anna videos linkedin.com
Under any circumstances.
Let It Go interview
He doesn't do any work
Hillary said the Bible should not concede under any circumstances
It's a recognition that because of the way this election is
Clearly going to be a mess
Be ready for the possible legal challenges that could arise like back in 2000
Is there like
There must be a
Clinton signal
You know like like you know it's like this news I don't want to deal with somebody hit the
Clinton signal guess what Hillary Clinton sheet we can talk about something else going on today
That's not important
Local news
Hillary Clinton is a National City
Internal speaker
Numbers go
Things are going
They're damn
Demoralizing
That does not mean 168 long days
The longtime the short time
Raconteur
Blockstarplanet
Star War
Release a new more deadly virus
Resubmission
I sincerely don't think Alex's where the fact there was a
The shooting night before in Kenosha at the beginning of the show
He's opening the program rambling about secret internal Trump
More diseases to throw it off
In the early morning hours for shot in Kenosha
The shooter was a seventeen-year-old in town from Illinois
And there was some kind of Duty
You didn't leave
Protect businesses he had no connection to
Enter process
Kill two people
You left town was only arrested back in Illinois the next day
It's really really suspicious that I wasn't talking about this right away cuz it should be his tops
And yet there isn't a hint of
Very weird
But Alex has other things on his mind
May not work on social media
Live coverage
Tonight
They don't want that
The way you do it
He's with this new URL
URL
Censored by Jack
Come
I mean this is the whack-a-mole game
Earnest of the sites
Another URL
Eventually people like Alex's new site
It's a little bit like antivirus soft
You're always going to be losing cuz they have the initiative
They're always creating a
Motivation to
When texting people
And being able for his links
To be spread around despite him being kicked
Into the show
This is when the first
Mention
Shooting comes up
That's all just about self
Defense
The Earth shaking
I'm holding on
Kenosha Wisconsin
Response by the media
And the fact that
Young man
Auntie
And then he shot and killed two people
F*** you
With a weapon
Better man had a pistol in his hand
Lowe's
Mobile
Imagine someone chasing you down the street with a pistol
You turn around and shoot
Governors calling for his arrest
The police
Running down the street in the shooting
First Skywalker
From really any relevant conversation
About
Stop being scared skateboard
Because the preceding incident of someone dying
Super Morelos
Honestly 250 patients are the arguments like this
To me this situation
Elementary level
Some people got shot
So the first question is who shot
He was a seventeen-year-old.
The next question is why
These people
So question
Weekend
Why did you
It's obvious because
That's just the focus on the initial incident
From everything we can tell
Is that the victim
Which logical Quest
I don't know
Unfortunately
To ask him branch
Send the first one is why was the shooter there
That's a tough question
He clenches there to protect businesses
But he's not from Kenosha is from Antioch Illinois
Antioch is in Northern Illinois
Centrum personal connection
In between the two businesses
It appears that the answer to that question why he was there
Across state lines
Cano properties
Just seems weird
I would say that it sounds unbelievable but
Next question
How did he have a gun
In order to legally possess purchase or carry a gun in Illinois where the shooters from you have to have it
Card or a firearm owner's identification card
In order to get when we start the person has to be 21 or over or have any
Possessing acquire firearm
That tells us that it's hypothetically possible for him to have a gun
Did not have a permit to begin with
So it appears that him just
Having a gun is illegal
You couldn't have like he couldn't receive the permit to carry weapon in Wisconsin
This is why in addition to first-degree murder he's charged with possession of a dangerous weapon under the age of 18
If you trace out the causality Chamber of the first shooting there immediately at least two very serious reasons why the shooters
Position
Be carrying out
Shooting
You have no reason to be in Kenosha other than a desire to build
And he had no legal right to be carrying an arc
For me these two aspects of the story make arguments about self-defense you a little bit Halo
And how did you that you know we don't know what happened
Before the first video picks up where the shooter is being chased by the first
I don't know if there was an inciting incident to that
Who might have been an instigator of
Whatever happened
So I don't know I don't
Care about this I don't care about is the
The arguments that
Attempt to Center
Victims
For the cross
It's an uphill battle if you're trying to make that argument see the evidence
It would be required to just
It's like one of those things
I know they're saying they're saying it all over
It's in
Homes
10 garages
And it's on f****** TV
It's not a garage
I get it
I just
No one will say it to my face
Do you know what I mean
Like they're all saying
Alex is saying this s***
Alex would not sit down across for me and say that s*** to my face
You know you just what
Coward
Static
And it drives me insane
On the 24 Alex was about
Lisa being policed by the protesters and stopping the police
We're unable to do stuff and this continues after
Because
Those barriers existed to justify this preemptively
And now that it's happened
The payoff to
The man
Go to the police with his hands up
Trying to get
They won't
When the police Stand Down
Thousands of people going through neighborhood
Burning down houses and businesses
Robin
You're going to have the vacuum filled
With citizens and you're going to ask
Stop
Anyway
Alright let's just do this one real quick
Were there
Full f****** body armor
Carrying automatic weapons
And they're they're just being
Handcuffs
Bye
People wearing
Improvise
Protecting soros's beer
This is
This is pathetic
Is filled with nothing but
Edit f****** disgusting
Can't tell me that
It's alright alpha males and then
Cry all the time when they won't let us kill them where they were
The cops aren't need to be protector
F*** you.
F*** you know what's really interesting now like
Ida wants to talk more
About
How he has a new URL
Galaxy more focused on
Whatever
Tolerance of the
Criminal
Has conjured a nightmare
Legend learning yesterday
Any video from Bandit video
Build platform millions of Musa day you're sharing it
He's just doing
These new URL that are able to
Talking about shooting
Sexy
Yeah
Advertisement
Propaganda videos to be able to get on social media
Is easy
Existential
His need to just
Justify the shooting
Contrast that to somebody who's
F******
Businesses
20 or 30 more time
You know
Types of people pleaser good guys
The focus almost entirely on
Shooter and what he is
Experian
I thought they already shooting hunting chasing him with guns
Fungi
With a gun in his hand
Because he was physically
Walling off part
Forearm
It's just
Poor guy is getting me messages
It's no concern or care about
For Dad
If you want to entertain this
I will give you this
The seventeen-year-old
Did not do this in a bag
Vacuum
This wasn't something that he would just self-generated this idea
Of course
He is
Just as much a gun as the guns
He was fired by all of these people
If you want him
You're still the bad guy
So
How does an interesting relationship
That is an interesting
They're they're always be
Stablish
Order police by the ACLU much like
Justice
The protesters in Portland
Something like this
I have to justify that
Round circular
The police never arrested
Virtue signal by arresting him for
Noblesville
Whatever
Good news
He killed reportedly two white people so it's not going to be as bad
My God the whole country Woodburn
F*** you
Race
Is the sentence f****** Psychopaths
That is
F******
Beyond
That's crazy
Alex
How
Talking about how you know
Urine Wisconsin
Jacob Lake your black
Keebler way more likely to be shot if they're white
Police officers
The trigger the slightest thing
They said all the police in Wisconsin long history of
Statistics showing
In Wisconsin you're more than double likely
Statistically
Timmy shot
Like the black
Thousand
Are more than twice as likely
BS
He's completely made up
JustFab
You can find some 26 about demographics
Come shooting
If you look at
Wisconsin in 2018 for white
6 out of 100,000 are killed in a shooting
A black people that number
Is 25.5
Maybe I was just talking about Elise related shooting
Associated Press reported killed in police shootings in Wisconsin
Three were black
To work
That sounds like a situation where
This is not adjusted
Population
According to the 2018 census numbers Wisconsin population is 87%
80%
Means that population is 87% of 68%
Police shooting
Which is disproportionate to population
Distribution
The number for police shootings
Not match population
6% of the population
Population sees the same percent of the population represents approximately 12
Percent of police shooting
Shut up
Nothing to back up the both of you throwing around it's just pathetic attempt to argue that you shouldn't have to care about police brutality Direct
The groups who are white
So very boring at this point
If I don't
Like the reality I will just say it
Make some calls
The gun store
To buy guns
Makes
And that is the if you want to buy gun
You have an obligation
2 train
You're going to have a really hard time finding that in a lot of Market
Good stuff
Stop
Coming in
Ammunition going to be back until probably about
Book about February or March
A lot of preparedness
Forgetting ammunition info
Maybe be able to train and use it
Seriously
Scared of gun
Sound sound
Thank you probably minimizes that a little bit
I think is really weird is it like Alex should be
Yelling about how there's no
Well he doesn't have a permit
You don't have a concealed carry for sure
Oh that's
Kristen brand
People fear
About
So why is it like now
Get a guy's
This makes no sense that is
That is weird
I guess cuz he doesn't sell guns
But in the same way baby
Big guns are flying off the shelves
I'm doing my job because celebrate
Olivia is on the right
I don't know
Episode
No no
Interesting guy
Ali Alexander
You bet
Really think Alex is trying to hire him
Catholics believe in
Church on Sunday the Sabbath
Ackerman
Keith ape
About the restrainer
Do it
Yeah
Number of churches across like all sorts of denominations
Temple Run
Close
I know this is a social Gathering we are doing the potluck later but let's not forget the reason for the season to make sure that
The hell to say
I know
This train has been Unbroken
Nobody's had to take a smoke break and forgot
Left the door unlocked nobody is f***** up one time
0 engine
Nuclear weapons
It's very it's very weird
Complaining
Sephora
This is just like you guys are
They're f****** assholes
I don't want to get super religious
Now he is Satan and now he is
Alright okay
Alright
I'm fine with this show
Here's how I allow info
They are allowed to sit
And talk the same way that they normally are
However they are both
Thanks
So when they say something stupid like that everybody gets together in a throwaway f****** but a lot of
Every fathers trans rights
Bipoc causes and it has to be
Alex's.
I mean I would say
I resent that
Episode
Because
Don't call them both elves okay there's multiple races of elves come on now. You got the jharkhand
Elves you got the elf on the circumstances of the world
Operating Within
I mean
There are obviously things happened since
Responding more Sense Media Matters
When people talk about
Dance Connection
Into
So I assumed
Blow up
In the future,
If you look at just
This section of
Time
It's really interesting to me because
When I asked myself
Do I think
There is a
Like an actual connection
I don't know I don't think so
Like I don't
I think Alex is that interested in it
The events that are happening in Kenosha
Side of what he does all the time
Yeah
Feel like
He behaved in any way differently
Then he does
All the time
Yeah at the same time
Who's showing the 24
Intensely
Answer things that he says
To be able to get involved
And
Makeup buttering out to break
Are there a lot of things like that.
I think
Things are things that you could make a solid argument
Maybe the shooter
Yeah I don't know I think that case is thin
That being said
They don't know
A sentence beginning
That's really all that important
I think his behavior
Is disgraceful
And it it fits the larger pattern beginning
He's those behaviors
More likely to create outcomes like that
Right right
I just see that
We have
Allowed and sat by while the most
Profitable media Enterprises in
The world are
Stochastic Terror
That's why
So
To me it's just like
Who you want to blame it on
You know
As it is for the
To agree posted that
Militia article
If this happened two weeks from now
Then maybe
Carlsen would have posted
It has nothing to do with individually these people are absorbed
Information from
Because they're all getting it
Picture of the
Ecosystem is far more important than the Chicago plant
And because I mean there was a time
Be far more confident in tracing
Prince
That's not really the case
So much
It's like
Dick could have got me directly from the goddamn
If you want to deal with stochastic terrorist believe it on Truck 2
And the thing that I think
But I keep coming back to on
Is that these articles in the people who were trying to make
I get it
I don't think they're wrong
I think it's in
Complete and I think
I think that's a better conversation to have
Ecosystem
Secondarily
Alex
Don't
Talk about
Like
Hey in the days before
Before the shootings died of a
He has an MO
Babies operating
In search
Of things like this happen
It does happen
Predictable
Defying it
Self-defense
Was going to happen
Cuz it and it did because
So I don't have any phone calls I didn't have time to
Cerenia before the show
Time crunch
So where will the next track
We are on Facebook if you'd like to download something but if you could please more importantly find a local
Bail Fund in your area
Yes
Same color