Air Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge
MoneyGram
Jordan
What did I see
But
Italian dressing from Olive Garden
I don't think it's
There's just something about that
No it's not I never want to help
Fazoli's
Free breadsticks
Sometimes
Music
I was listening to music
Once more I was listening to the cigarettes
I remember when I was 18
I went and saw them at the Chicago theater
Incredible greatest
It's my brakes right because as you know
I don't like to deal with my memories too much I like to keep a nice memory
My memory
More Valley
And
Interesting situation going on here
So I went to project
Because I'm constantly
I think it might not be working
That word on a tree
Is a sign that maybe the next time
Super sure actually today
Little bit of a
Project
Is a show called unexplained Howard Hughes
What happened
I was going through
Okay
Real real cool
There's some people like Joe
But I found one
Episode that I thought like
I've never listened to this guy I don't know what product I don't know anything about this
Abyss
If we're going to do a trial balloon episode
This will be the one
He is not able to
Call F
Next
Thank you very much Freeze Frame
Niccu
Next
Robert
I can't remember his name
No it's not Robert Scottish god dammit
Three goddamn secretly
12:00
Soccer.com
Robert Burns meldish
If you are
Feeling generous and don't want to start
Area of a subwoofer cable ND
Virtual
We wouldn't allow you to buy South Bay
Facebook
Mediately
I have tried a number of that
I think that's better than I would have
Hair candy
Do you think they'd be sweet
Really not
No it's it's strange
It's pretty subtle
Excited to try something force you to buy like you kids by mangle
We are
Feel like vanilla
But
Got a nice little thing in Austin sent over some other
Seltzer's as well
Okay
This brand
Alright from this company normal size
Call boy
I don't know I want
If you see this assured it is a
Really does seem like it's a guy blowing an armadillo
Yeah
I like the shirts that I will never wear
Thank you Paul
Unzip
Sure Jordan I don't know anything
Howard Hughes
I was trying to come into this with no idea what I'm looking at
For us
I think this guy is incredibly Charming right
Okay
Dress up nice
Across the UK Across America and around the world on the internet
Greetings from Springtime in London as I said those were the best of sunshine came through my window which is up
What is a rarity these days
For the last 2 weeks
What fun
Narrative Arc of life
The 4th doctor
Was he became a radio host for a while I would buy it
I like it so far
See why I chose this
Captain Randy Cramer
Remember to get it together but we've
On this Edition
Planes
But he is part of a secret Falls
You hear the whole story here
Misconception
Episode
First episode
Captain Randy Cramer
This is going to be
If you want us to cover your product on our show
Wendy of courses the guy who was fighting aliens on Mars
And
So
Mars base
So how it starts out the show for the interview
This guy is Charming
He's forty miles from popokatepetl time
Email from Elizabeth
I'm 50 miles from the time at Redbox
He said the reason I mentioned to you
24 years ago
Many people say they're being sightings of alien ships at these places are being told of them
And I haven't seen any sightings
Disposable that aliens exist
Visit popokatepetl a Great Pyramid
But it likes go you said
Old account info Lisa Meat Market
It look like scream of the garden section
Navigate
I scream on Alpha Centauri
Is BBC 4 how to show where they're just like
I don't feel like at this point
Editorial decision response
Joe
That's not saying must be coming there cuz they like ice cream
Editorial decision
When are you going to stay somewhere where does the Boston
What is he doesn't hate
What do even do how do you spell unicorn
Is this space
Listeners
Like a meat market
Jonathan in Mississauga Ontario
You're so in love with him from Canada
Iceland's in Canada like Yellowknife
Mississauga
One of these days I want to come to Canada
Yeah you and I are at the same conversation about a luggage
This is Lord forward
I just love the way certain names are pronounced
This is this this is fantastic
So you've done the business up top couple of emails
Captain Kramer
The red planet
This is a place that we are actively making plans to visit
Companies doing
Vero
X by Masa and others to
Explore the red planet Mall
And maybe to Paris
Environment
To be able to turn the right.
Into something that you grow things on
Science fiction anymore
Anatolian the pipeline
It's stuff that we dreamt about
When we were kids
Emmaus
We coming for real
We're actually
A lot of us going to live to see this
There's another perspective on the listless
What if I told you that there are people who say that I we have bean Tomatoes we're actively involved in Mars
That we have
People who are
Explorers of
I'd say you were full of s***
He claims to have spent 17 years on Mars
He is
I'm a secret space Fleet
Expiration
So he claims.
Yeah and in the editorial position is still on established
You can see a bit of life
Like what I wrote wrote something
Someone
President
Grammar on Project
A blue block by Stripes breaking up in
That this guy is the best everything that he's ever said even though
British man
Apparently at this point
Doesn't seem to be pushing
Yeah for this person to be credible or correct
Totally free uncommon press
This is the first episode
Have like 400 episodes
Story
Call Randy
Brandy's just fine
Very much for coming on
Wow well I guess
My military back
Literally
Play born out of a
Projects
Was
Drum
The mid-60s
Tuaca
Augment and work
Create from scratch
Genetically augmented
So he was in the military before he was even born
I think this is cuz we're America
But when he said can I call you Captain Randy or just random
I want to say that was a really deep insult right there
Can I call you Captain Randy cuz it's not can I call you, captain
It can I call you Captain Randy such as to say that I'm kind of treating you as a as a
Can I call you cuz no one else will
It's a
Two military people realize
Desert iguana
Alien technology right
You've got to do it with babies or something
Soldier
Cracking
A number of
Roxanne
Tables
Information for Mexico
Suppress
That was giving us
Jumps ahead of
Civilian Tech
Acknowledging civilian research and develop
EXO
The ability for the military to stay
Start doing genetic
Experiment two-headed what anything in the civilian were
YouTube
Advance
Technology infused
Programs that gave us to LEAP ahead
Alright
Technology p
People wanted to figure out how to use it
So the first thing to do was
Find figure out how to
Who you already got
You realize that it was minimally
That you really just
Do what some of the
Did you do or working
Coming down work
King in our labs
Ground on Trussville
To advise us now you really want
To do this right you got to start
From the ground
We got a bill.
Start from the beginning
And don't
So you can hear
Couldn't use it with existing soldiers
Sort of genetically alter and create people who could use this text
Or whatever
At least make sense
Your stomach
We had this alien technology so they were like
Let's just use it on the guys we have
That was their first stop
Duplicate
Geneva Convention
So if we've got this program
These these these
User being created before birth
To be able to use this tack
Sure hey you know it raises the question
Where did you come up with who
Well none of that is the answer
I come in all days Iowa
One of the first genetic
I created soldiers from
That project I was
Built-in app
3 days from the ground up
Late night
19 midnight
1869 and I was born in nineteen
I hear what you say when you talk to me
How can we be sure that
Show you
2 radio channel
Already out of the gate
Mildly
Described by surprise
Bees bees
Are you talking about
2:30 proof
Radio
This is what Randy comes up with veggies best
Proof that he actually is a super soldier
Proof that
I have to throw out to people
Is that
I live
Envy most militarized Nation
In the world
We have had no sense
Humor
People who impersonate
Officers
Interesting
Ever not true
Impersonating a
An officer next
They're absolutely steps
To be taken by the FBI
Marine Corps to discuss with
About my fraudulent doing so and how I needed to cease and desist and do that
Randy
The space called they would Closing Time fun
I'm saying is
But if I were doing that fragile
The process that
They would follow
Decision decision
Show proof
And I would say great
I love hearing into Jago
Officer in my lawyer
Assured me that
Probably never going to hear
Because they never want
Me a hearing
I have my first problem
His best evidence
You thought you had you thought you could catch let me tell you something
One hand not slapping me
While silence
So
Gibson
Because
Do you see saying that like I've talked to my lawyer about what would happen if I was
And why would you ask his lawyer any of these questions
Beatrice
Like this one
Because you're telling the truth
But if you were telling the truth wouldn't that be a reason to close you down
Call ghost
The Command Staff
Map of United States
Or special sec
Decide
Person to act
Just a public relations officer
And apparently there was a short
List of which my name was
Put on and then when they
Through that
That list eventually a
My Brigadier General
Me very politely
If I wanted to be the public
Expressing guy
Not really
But he convinced me
And I said hi
And so yeah
At my commanders have
Absolutely authorized Mutua number of
Legal parameters
Exist in the United States Marine Corps special section
Conduct
Go beyond
Giving me
Permission
Outside of security
Are answers actually illegal
Mandy
To do what I'm doing
He legally has to come
All right now
Either type
Do you understand
Images about the potential consequences of being a
You got a lawyer
Navigate convoluted
It's so
Is that it is largely might be
You might want to ask something because
Your guest
Howard
Another topic
It's this one is really where
Serious red flags
Coming to understand
That he was a super soldier
Your you're
Living
Call my wife
You wake up everyday and
When you perceive that you are going
Normally and then
When they decide to
Go take you away for
For training.
I or educational
Congratulations
End up being
You know a number of
Years
Restraining
Your father
Who are they
Was run by Unite
Marine Corps special sex
Call Project Moonshadow
Project Moonshadow
He's got this this whole situation
Night sometimes
And at the same time he's saying he was created as a superset
This is kind of getting
Theological Paris
I'm who
Contributed to you
How involved were they in this they must have been totally involved
This is a real sticking point
Artificial insemination
Secret
Disappeared at night when you were really young
Sure do parodies ever woken up
There's never happen this becomes an issue for him
Wait your parents didn't know about this
Well I always
Wake up
With
You just wait
Disassociate
I'm thinking well that was the strangest
Longest dream ever
Even though
I know you had a
Dream that seemed to last days or we
Weeks at a time
Stream to be buried
Consistent
And not have
Weird dreams
Qualities to it
And have a very solid
Linear timeline to it other than that
You know you wake up
And they're sort of this
Are you talking about
Brainwave app
Conscious brain wave Activity Works when you move from
A data.
Delta Theta
Asleep
Optimist Club your Alpha
A bridge into your beta state
You often
And disassociate
What's happening in
Because primarily what
You're being trained in
Is in a lower
Brainwave Consciousness state
Which is actually
Better for
Hi babe estate
Falcor
Sort of
Consciousness
Kind of shaking
Why that was
Weird long dream even though
Nothing
You were to sit down
3 man was dead
That agent talked
Would really into
Having a dream
Go wild
Is the weirdest experience
I never heard that you do
Don't trust your emails
You just ate
And I learned
A few conversation
My parents like
Right now waking up
Sitting at The Breakfast Table insane
Why I had this weird dream last night
Let me tell you about
And getting those
Disconcerted
Good looks from your parents to know I should
That makes them work
Okay there's a lot going on here sounds like
Super-Soldiers.
It's a lot of what I think is true is real bummer sounds like
And maybe some kind of an inability to connect
Leads to creating
Alternative explanations for why they're having
What I
Experience as a child
You know I got an A+
I got an A+ I need to see the counselor
Like that's what I'm here
Concrete
Issues
Like
Question
If
Your
F****** Mars super soldier
Face person
How's your parents not notice really important
So when did the Foster created you to search
Intervene and stop getting involved in your life as a kid when did they start training you
Earliest
Memories of training or
Probably really somewhere
3 1/2 in
4 years old
Okay and you will be
Taken away from your parents
Portraying
And they didn't know anything about
Has anybody taking me away from my mom and dad they be hearing from my dad pretty damn quick
Right
Bright
I don't know if it's
They must have been
If you were disappearing four. Going to get rain
And you want with the
Presumably
Some of this doesn't I have to say some of this is difficult to take in
Which is that
We're talking about
Programs that are using
Reversed
And or handed down
Technology from extra
Variability
To do things like
Hover over your house
For the spaceship
You are and
Projector wormhole
Into your bedroom and pick you up
And or take you to a location
For training
And
Used
Time travel
About to take you back so that your ex
Is really hard to read that's really hard to read
Ono Ono
Oh okay this is how this fits into the narrative
It's hard because I don't know anything about I might be
He's a really funny response
Like I couldn't get over the the like
Some of this is really hard to swallow
Deadpan face while he isn't even like the hint of a smile
Music
Mystery
Unravel
Earth-based solution
I want that one thing
It's really important
My mother is
A very
Metaphysically psionic
Sensitive person
She is
As always had in some
And is one of those p
People that I think she was
What's going on
And it was one of the reasons why she was always
I had horrible insomnia and was always terrified
Anchor children
New about this on some level
On an intuitive level
Did Anna created a lot of
The panic and anxiety she had her
Run sleep issues and around
Broken into it
There was no
That was happening but
I think she was
Barry panic
So I would say there are super soldier
Warriors
Way of being
These paranoia
Sort of projected onto her child
Has this preoccupation way to explain
Susan anxiety not
Kind of makes sense I'm not saying that is the case I know psychiatrist or psychologist
Any Dream analyst wood
Completely disagree with you I feel like I have all the information that I
To say
I don't think you were on Mars
Just keep you this with all of his guests as he kind of like snow I don't like it
I feel like he's loading him into the sense of like
Accidentally sent her of all the problem
And Howard is just going to like allowed to exist in the space
Style
What is 2/2
For no reason if you ask
Questions and make a responsible choice
About what's being said
All right this doesn't make sense
Where is the bike project
Is in such an unquestioning is questioning its quest to take
And that is irresponsible cuz you just you give your audience a full sense of credibility about everything
I see that
Very cautiously like I said I haven't listened to any other episodes
You guys look
I'm waiting to hear him say a hard J always in
Thomas episode
Gears of War
He's approaching this audience to make a decision about
I think that you can tell that some of them
You got from you alright texts and tweets not all of you buying into this necessarily Randy you must get a lot of office
Position from people who simply dumb
Believe it
I mean they're certainly
The
I stay away from them
Phone number of
Unranked Seville
Want to have there
Opinion about it
When it comes to my interactions with
My local
Politicians elected representatives
Local law enforcement
Auto professional person
Military personnel
NASA engineers
Holistic
Bear grey Payne
Professional produce
Show people edits never even a question
About an eyelash
Neither
Babe they all talked
Miraie profession
Play a very interested in what I've done
And what I'm doing
Okay
Whatever
Your list is too long
Hell
He cartoon space Explorer
Created by this Chucky on radio the real
Creator God gold Kenny Everett
I must we could just to say this is more
Captain Crab
Send Captain Kramer
But some I love you
I like that
Tonight's comet
And you are more of a joke than the joke
You understand that
How old is another interesting question
Kid
Someone's trying to
What how was that experience
What is you being taken away by
Various crops
Some various mean
If I was being taken away
Against
Unify
If I didn't realize why was old being dumb
I would say please don't take me away
Sure
As a kid
You're certainly given
Childlike
When Nations
For what you're doing and where you're going
What trainings for
And so
Basically
You know
An adult standing
Denair
You know you want to shoe
Raygun
Susan fight space
Don't you and you're like yeah
It's an easy motivation
Aliens
As a child
Correct
Broad
I just
I don't know
I can't imagine the government
Secrets
Super soldier program successfully kidnapped
Extreme
Slightly
0 government watchdog
Who are like
Hey guys at least cut it off
Accuracy
Best child kidnapper we have it though
Lazerism
Doesn't matter
Say yes
Enter this by saying hey little man
You want to play with a ray gun like you seen in the movies on the TV
But genetically
Engineered and
Engineered
Built to fit
That this is a
So it wasn't something
Thing that I would have
Resisted anyway
Because I was Jeanette
Ethically engineered
So
You said all this
We are talking about kidnapping children
That's a good point
Remember how we told you
You tell the Brigham's and that's what we do
But you genetically engineered to say that is a great idea
Superpowers
Describe two superpowers
It's so perfect as to never be provable
Capabilities that maybe I and my colleagues season like that have
Be a little smarter
Little faster little stronger
More than everybody else
When you say you were little stronger what can you do that we come
It really
My physical strain
Physical fight
And the best way to
Plane that is if
I get jump
3 Guys
My physical body
He will respond as if I'm
I'm getting jumped
20 guys
My body will respond
Funny guy so
Output
On the input attack
So
The more people who attacked me
The stronger and
Leather
Earlier
He's in complete control
It is a skill that is completely
Controlling in
Completely in my grasp
Has its own safety
Call Austin
You know keep me from you know killing innocent people and Sophie
Forest
Sorry to
Very badly
Find me I've never lost a fight
You are
I like that
Very easy
It keeps me from hurting anyone
Suddenly show
Most highly trained martial arts Professionals in the world
Don't kill them but if you can beat up
Chinese government authorization Brigadier General
Call come on
Play
360 easy to cash
I mean the smarter perfectly quantify that
Race
Cursive anymore
Versus
Spotify
Is first
Dawn from Spotify
Literally on Spotify
Have a freak out about that
Superpowers
It turns out you can also run
Really fast
Tall buildings in a single bound book
But yeah like I
Situation
Responsive
The faster I need
The faster or run the higher end
Need to jump
The actual limitation
As far as like
Inches in feet or classify
Play Space 50
So we're not really sure what
What the top of the scales are some
Because we haven't necessarily seen pops
Perfect
Way to test this
We have to create
A scenario where there's a park or contact
High-level professional parkour version
Whoever loses will be executed
Now that you have to make up for it against the law for the government
This is an asset
No
Furthermore what this implies is that the government has done a lot of testing
Regularly increasing threats
You find a lion
And then tomorrow they like
Perceived by the body as an adrenaline response
Causing him to respond to
We know from listening to Randy on Project
Regressed
Perfect clone
The age
Consciousness was transferred into
Because I formation
You spent all those long periods but
Because
Variable vaco
Back engineered technology presumably that allows them to compress time
You are not
Like sixty or seventy years of age and I wish you would have to
Wfu cycling
Here's
Funny part
Right is
Because
Acholic age-reversing
But it's not real
Age reversal
At the end of
Your 20-year tour they take
LLC which
Operations Command
And they say okay we're going to do you know
Wipe out your memory
Secure things that you don't want to remember anyway
And
And we're going to
Send you back
Can a young do
Musically
Hatch you out a new
Clone body
That's the same age
You away and they
And I know this is going to sound
Sound weird
People again
Hide
Advanced alien technology
As ensign
To understand
That the human soul
Is a quantum
Fluid
The body put into another
Handheld Andor
Another vessel
Another body
Through a mechanism
I was not conscious
You know now how it works
Other than
Are able to remove the soul from
That body
Put it into this
Younger clone body the same age
Cresol
Memories
And then put
To backhand you ascent
Wake up
You know
You left from a 20-year tour
Juice
Sing on stage
And he just said that and then just
Deposit I would have stood up
And slow Clapton
If I were the interviewer that exact same situation I would stand up and walk away
Deserves
Due south may use it to power spacecraft who knows
Are you not curious
You can't tell me anything about the process
Say that about it
Do the words
Quantum and fluid mean anything when they are putting a
Next to each other
You might be on the half of the audience
Some of them
Love it
And some of them say
He was not sure about this
I was polite
Into this hour and you missed the first half hour if you see what I'm saying
Captain Randy Koehler is a man it was bread
Commissions tomorrow
Amazing members the constant
Trash garbage
Responsible
Clearly a bunch of people saying he's full of s***
Question
Exact same stories
Very important points on people will get on my bike if I didn't put this point to you
People on board then which she will have
We're all of those people and why are they speaking to
Well some of the
Do that
How sure some of
Their memories
Protocol either badly
Clearwell
And so sometimes there
Brains in Dubai
More Swiss cheese
Oatmeal
And it's hard
Werdum
Bring memories to
Cohesive state
I talk to people all the time
Gordon the process of
Unfold
Memory experiences
Enter constantly asking me for advice on
How to remember things
Get their Memories Back In how to
You know deal with
Tom and so forth until
I will just be honest and
Most of them
Have no desire
Trivia
McPherson they don't
Targeted they do not
I want to be
I'll get any hassle from anybody
Cuz most of them have
The main person
Authorized you say to be doing the speaking about
Contact with them here on Earth
I'm one of two
Jess
That if we take
There's a government program
Make super soldiers current
Anyone can sign
For twenty years or whatever takes the soul juice
Remember
For them
Because he hired you as RPI
Gave us PRL
Scrambling people's brains baby on purpose
Well
Scrambled brains
You are describing something really really horrifying
What why
Weird
Explanation for that
Yeah they're too
People actually
Well let me let me
Put it in
Answer that in the air
Anna Moore
Broadway
Be more specific
To get where you're going out with that
Have you ever seen me with a mustache
Naval space command
Once
For the planet
Divided into
Two fleets in the same
That here in America we have opposite
Separate
In our ships
Vanguard fortitude if
Coastal ports
Until we got up space and down space
Policing
The solar
Easier to started
Divided in imaginary line
Down the middle of it and have
Of course it is on the one side
Starfleet on the other side
Solar Warden
And radio
Gardy
Now each Fleet
Decided
I need to have a stroke
And that they would pick us up
Guardian Brothers
Spokesperson for solar Warden is a gentleman
He is
The both American guys space
Need smokes
Is good a better spokesman lately
What's interesting to me is bit like this look at this from an Institutional perspective
Solar Warden
Okay this guide
Or west
So your garden does things differently from solar
Wow
Like what is achieved
Questions
Sure there is nothing to answer questions there's a recorded story
So this is this is
If people are Fielding questions in order to make the company
Spokesman in Blackson
If this is some like crazy elaborate secret program
Bears
They want you to think they're so stupid
Finally, Brillion
Kramer
How does this work
Policing the solar system
Who is policing the solar system
Well
Earth Defense
Forest Naval space
Command in this other sort of
Loose
International Group
Military person
Chart of conglomerate
Either to make up the fleet
Countries have officers
Pilots and so forth
Contribute to the larger
People are distributed
Throughout the fleet
Various
Missions a
If you want to get real
Mummy get on nerdy
Be about it starts
The federation's mission
Was very diplomatic
And peaceful
Was non-military
We definitely have a military Mission Beach
Because we consider the military
Protection of the solar system
Come to be
Absolutely necessary given the Tangie
Do we have to deal with what you again
So horrible
Deal with them but there is a list
Intangible
And yet
Brain fried after work
Well I don't support
Listen as your PR guy I want to just let everybody know
This would be way better if it was Star Trek
In actuality this is the worst
Star Trek
Who is a scientist
And is a regular contributor to the show says
Prolonged exposure to 17 years of whatever of Martian gravity would cause massive bone
Deterioration
How did you avoid that
Well
Was used on a
All the time
Because
We were in the field
Engagement
Combat
And I've had my
Arms in my leg
Blown off so many times
I can't even count
And
Holographic
Regenerating
Knology
Projected Hollow
Cellular level
Convince your body
We grow
And damn
And ripped off
Traffic degenerative it doesn't sound like he believes him
Sounds incredibly polite
If he's had his arms and legs off
Lakes
Does he lose any Soul juice
Soldiers in the army
There is even a little bit of soldiers
Are you your arm is the philosophical question
If you replace every part of your body are your clone with your soldiers
I'm sorry
Hologram
It has a resolution at the cellular level
Projective
Perfect Image
Your body
Bad
Restores damaged
Tissue and
Endure at the end of
Of a severed limb
Will fool
Bat cellular tissue
Keep going
Cuz the only thing
Doctor tissue from growing when
Reborn off of limousine
It reaches out there's
How to keep going to
Buttafuco
Convince it
By having a holler
Cellular level
But it goes all I can
Just keep going
You essentially
Full your body that I can just keep growing and you
You can regrow an entire limb
The template of you
Somewhere
So you said you're
Genetics
Basically it's just
DNA map
Projectile
I have nothing further to say than that
Biology classes in college
Maybe
Baby works
Anyway
That I think is very important
Terry if you can if Soul juice exist
Fluid
Can you
Artificially created like in like a Collider
Can you create soldiers
If you are telling me that the soul is a physical
Your job
Dealer job is as an in
Independent field
United States
Main course specials
Reminder that
Judy series of Duties is
Three main
Right now that I have to
To deal with witches
Criminal investigation
Research and develop
Correlation
So
Yes I am
Have a cup
Very
I'm just going to call them strain
File
Chase's
I've been given
For me to deal with
Involved
Activity of a very
Unusual nature
Which I'm really because it's a no
Anything more about it but
Those are probably
You're the pr guy
Why would they have the sleepers with Fox Mulder and
Good look
I would say that he does have
Quit
Would have all of those
Joseph
This job
I don't get one
That's why I'm
Field command
I'm responsible
Gopher
Dealing with all
Of my own
Resources
How do you earn
Your accommodation
There's
Who has
Wonderful and how
Peaches
Tax class
And every once in awhile when I do one of those
Marginal fee for teacher
Republic
Get some really wonder
For people who have
Disliking said
We want to help you
If you know taking care of
So just people
You should maybe
Children but they don't even
Slave investigator that's what he said
Quit
You didn't say that for sure
Situation
Where is a soldier
The payment
Payment for his shity life
He has a job in an office
Really great Trucking
Really make it look beautiful
I know it's not cold out the stock quote
That is actually
More complicated
Been activated
Independence
Closet
I actually have a
Greater legal authority to do the things that I need
I need to do as an independent
Commander not
Need a paycheck then I would get in a page
Which would actually the limit
Legal discussion of
It emits a very
Specific
Legal parameters
On being independent
Being
Give you the pain.
Do you want them
Ask the question I just asked
Ask you about the how do you pay for
I am not a ton
I mean everyone
He doesn't seem to be getting gas be regular question very often
I guess what he's trying to hearken to
Farm
Like outside
An organization that has no problem genetically creating children
Secretly implanting them into host
Then stealing them when they are for
I don't understand why there are real hung up on the payment part
Play variety
Any radio station that explanation for why you shouldn't be
Because they're all going to be using
Silver Lords would love
To treat me like that
You're doing PR work
You're a detective for paranormal s*** I'm a good one
Do you have a contract questions
You can read like a piece of paper
Release
Show yummy
Somewhere in a
Fault
My records
Exist and then there is a
Going through a process to try and
But I don't expect
That happened soon either
I'm trying to get my legal documents
Cinebox
To talk about
What's it like to be on the surface of Mars
Well the gravity is
Less than half
It's a
About 20
So
You know it
It's much lighter
That's for sure
Presumably
I mean
Where
Therein
A
A notch
Power
Body armor
Environment suit so
Not only
Do you have the ability to sort of jump
Empire and throw things further
You're in a power
Body armor
So you can even
Jump higher in
Farther and throw things
So it's a little
A little crazy
Also throwing things
I think I think this is indicative of
Everyone who's in the space weirdo like interviewing
Community
Whether consciously or instinctively
Knows what questions not to ask
Because he's really thrown off by a lot of these very very simple question
You can hear him when he's like
If I had been on Mars USB what's it like on Mars such an open question
Gravity
Chicago
Immediate
Satisfy
Undoubtedly
My favorite question power Dax
While I was on the Nautilus I was
Very very very
Kerry Ford
On a number of
Missions to the intergalactic
Attic space station.
Happy International
Galactic
PlayStation
Jupiter
Which is a meeting place
From number of species from all over
The place we meet there other
M to f
Really fascinating
Discussions
Mostly diplomatic arrangement
Contract negotiation
Treaty negotiated
And on a number of occasions
I was
Tagalog
As one of the only officers fight off
A hand-to-hand
Combat experience I was a jest
Even though there was never a Justin
But they wanted one guy
Stab somebody that way
So I got the
Many different tables
Across from many different
Species Wild
Senior officers were having
Many different
Discussions
Initial negotiations
Contract negotiator
Appreciation
First Contact meeting
It was one of the most
Amazing
And isn't that
Who your favorites
Yeah that's a great question
I haven't listened to enough episodes
You're not taking this very seriously anymore
Yeah I went to I went to this Intergalactic Space Station
Seriously
Really worried about contract lawyer
Is there must be must be
Universal government
Correct must already be
Okay
Contract
Do we get blown up
I mean
Overseas contract
We have a question
He doesn't realize that's an actual question
But it is
Your favorite
You know who are the most interesting
Would you like
As a person
Who has always
Been very sore
Like science motivate
I mean I wasn't
Nerdy science
You know from the ghetto
Do info
I was
Always fascinated in
Interested no matter what no matter what
What they look like no matter where they were from no matter
What their behavior was I was always fascinated and interested to understand
What no
World
It was like
There's another issue that comes up here and I think this is another really important point that
Call Lisa decent interviewer a task that never comes up
In other places
You're doing all this s*** on Mars
We just had a
Virgos are
Pictures of Mars
That's problem
Pictures back from Mars from NASA
Federal orange-tinted and it looks like Rebel up there
The biggest Barry Sullivan
Play Trouble
Mostly
Nothing
In particular
Really great picture that
It came off the JPL
Rodent
Tucked between
2 Rockwell
Supposedly
The rodent on the
Ground I mean it look
A giant rat
Squirrel their necks
Store Rocketman
Wayless
Buzzing Wireless question
Alright
Yeah alright there was okay
Then why don't you ever talk about how big the road
Narrative
Chile
Don't worry about all the technology that I said was there
That's true very excited
So
Captain Randy Cramer I have a million more questions are no time to ask you thank you very much and please text me
I think this is real
As we come to the end
Don't think this is a good option for Wacky Wednesday at the future
He does
Talk to
Right
He's making fun of
Me too
I don't think this is necessarily a good option for us
He asked
This guy
The audience can make up their mind
That is all I ask
That's how you like this response
If someone's being too offensive you probably at the interview
Just like you can talk to people
Irresponsible
It was polite
And that you're kidding it does seem like his questions become less serious because I think
I don't want to be
That's not the brand
Even greater question just because if you
Taking that into just terrestrial at can you imagine a journalist
Talking to somebody at a diplomat that f****** you and being like
Who's your favorite
You like that you like Germany would who's your favorite just give me a just give me some of your face
Cuz he doesn't get that no
I think it's fun to listen to
We will have to probably keep looking
For a new
Juice and see what comes up
Listen to voicemails
Hijack guy
Small town
August
Thank you for
Shane
Also in working
Should I get a tattoo
Orchard of mines
Candy character
Or just one
Kimball Avenue
You know I didn't know
Fortunate
Little bit
Anyway
Have a good day
I feel like that's question for you
It's more of your vein
Portrait
I just think the representation of a face is so
Iffy unless the face itself is December
But I mean even then
Spaces are tough to tattoo
D&D character is Nixon you know where to put it
Alright please survive
Hi guys
Long time
Turn color because
The podcast
Ashanti
Light on
The way
That
Propagate
Really
Is important as far as
People
How do you
Angry Birds
Can you have a
Propagate
Alex
Oh I remember watch
The world
Grove
Episode
Alex
Ghost
Union Grove
Recorder
Alright
Do you have
Alex's.
Secret rules of the world
Also on
And
Remarkable 2
Ronson
Alex's
Tell Alex
That would be a fun whacking
Wednesday thing for y'all to do
Adam I don't know
Whatever you
Y'all have a good one
Stay safe
Much
Alexandra Bronson
Vici
That would be redundant to the Wacky Wednesday
Do like the suggestion on the last and thank you for
Damn Jordan
Coalinga California
Jordan keeps saying he has an Andrew Jack
Drew
I was just wondering
Super curious now to know what it is
I'm sure it was a few other people who are equally
Chicago
You know I always I'm not sure if Jordan will be performing at night
To Wong
Or if I
Jordan is not
Opposed to it
Could we hear that pic
You do the BET
Stand up
Pretty sure it's on one of them
No I won't do that
Indiana Jordans
I'm really glad that you
Because I didn't
Sweet as hell
Like
A water
Fixated on it
Sign up for him
Globalist
All the time
I'm convinced
First of all
Exactly
Scatological returned to repeatedly
Yeah it's hard to say
Form of like
Female politicians
Correct
A lot
Listen to
Frequent personal brings up people
There's a family show
Some sort of dominance thing
So
I don't know
Escalated to actual water sports
Going on there I Can Only Imagine
I don't know
Betty White
Long time
I'm really only doing this
My friend
And I don't like you guys appreciate
Set alarm
How many podcast now
Great work
Encourage
We don't negotiate with terrorists
Frustrated by a message
Hey Danny Jordan
I was wondering
He's with a plan
If I've ever heard of the game stardew Valley
If not it isn't
Compusport
First games
Posting screenshot of the game because I named all my animals
There's a screenshot
It is very relaxing
It's just interesting enough
Cuz there isn't a good story
So
You should give her a shot
Consider consider
Coordinate
Chicago
Lee
Go
You have
Narrative
That didn't happen
Run the show
I'm going to
Honor your request for an apology
I'm sorry about that
Situation where Alex
Very consistent and very repetitively
You're being very blunt and direct
As the person listening to
Recreate that
On the show
For sure I appreciate call out on this
Except that criticism
Ourself to buy into that a little more than we should do
But there is also a decent chance that he wasn't terrible Financial Straits
Something
To fix that
Assistant about
Predictions are almost always predicts
Something
Mnnr faces I don't know how much
I certainly wasn't guaranteeing this
That possibility
Like
Like look like behind the scenes
Prediction would have come true situation
Granted
Did not end up
They ended up costing him like four quarters of a million dollars
Happening
Kind of around the same time and
You know
I think that I've learned
And do a better job
Like not letting myself get caught up in what if this happen
This isn't to say that like I probably did
Get a little bit more into like
But at the same time
Recognizing that excitement
Hangouts is bankruptcy
Appreciate appreciate that
We are called out
Find a local area and the best I can
Alex
Same color
I love your work