Respect
College B
MoneyGram
Sit around
What's up
I had a little bit of time
Do laundry earlier
And so I was listening to another podcast
Gas while I was
Doing my laundry and I was thrilled to find
That my dear friend
Old friend
I'm over selling this a little bit I've met him a couple times but the new episode of the doughboys
Brightspot
Costco's Saxbys delightful
He said
Nick and Mitch
And I brought up
He doesn't eat anything out of the sea and this is a position that I've had for a long time
I felt I felt like I had
Making disposition publicly in
I appreciate that
In 2 hours
Eating anything out of the ocean
I bought that
I'll get it out of here
Not like specifically saltwater
Okay I think you might have a harder line than I do cuz I think like
Like seaweed might be okay
Seaweeds okay
I still think I can find common calls on this
What are you surprised
You gave me the cantaloupe and your apartment
Trying my best to grow it
I recently
Stopped
F****** with it
And it's doing a lot better
I'm not good with plants yeah it's tough not good with you don't want to micromanage
Is this better
Let me give you an idea of how bad I am
Planets
One day I realized
Set the plant that my friend has given me
I haven't watered it in Forever
And I was like this is a whole new Leaf for me I'm really not upon absolutely.
Send it right
I'm going to take care of this plan a lot better
And then when I went to water at the next day I remember that this was a fake plan
At least 2 years
I was thinking that the story was going to be that it's a succulent and like you killed it by water again
You killed it but it was never even alive in the
I haven't having plants and I'm working on them as is its exercise and taking care
And also the same time learning Wayne
You've got to let it be
I'm enjoying that part of the process of
I could I could talk over these plants and like
Just be really worried about every single leaf
Or I could you know
Every day or so and
You know
Some of the steps
I'm balancing act
Watering it in
In the morning making sure that
I'm doing good I'm doing good I'm pretty proud of myself so
Listening out there if there's a little bit of a
Slightly different sound apologize for that
Beginning of this episode so
Hopefully be able to figure out what the deal is
Jordans
As much as possible Thursday's episode
Something's going on
Trying to figure out what
Alright
Books inside
That's great idea
Is actually this interesting person sent me an e-mail
You get a shout-out
For donating to charity
Yes
Thank you so much you are now probably walk
Hey thanks geological next
Are Jason Joseph
IU Joseph
Text Eric Seebeck
Thank you Eric
Exam
Next Kurt are they
You could take that generous
You could put that
In a
Little
All right next to cantaloupe
Going to take a little bit of
Time to germinate
Take care of it but
Same time you want to leave it alone
The focus more on the generosity
See that generosity
Spring from the dirt
Take that
Do your logo
Call Charity
That sounds like
Compliance
Alternate route
This is very exciting
Is starting to come together a little bit very well reviewed
Painting decoration
Cross stitch
Time to pray next week guns shooting roses out of them
Percent
D'accord
It is looking nice there's the beginnings of
You have stages of your life
You got the brand new
Plantain you got the
Gifts on either side
Illuminati cards
Exactly so that's awesome I really appreciate
More like Christmas
Santhome
I also like to take Sarah
Got to have some packages of treats
All over the world I think one box is just polish
I'm in the other one is a scattershot from all over the world
I appreciate that I actually got a chance to try any of those yet but
Pretty cool
Yeah and also
We are now to 240 South 3rd
Yes and I have to say there's no chance
We would ever be making
As I do right now if it weren't for the people out there listening
For this to continue on
Jelly Belly flavors
And orange sherbet is the leader in the clubhouse
It was the best that came in at 8
Britt broken 70 mark
Which is a pretty impressive
Pina colada not a surprise
No not a surprise
You love a what all goes into a pina colada
I don't know
Coconut
Play there was a grapefruit flavor and I thought I was actually really well done taste pretty good
Not good love
Jordans
This at this episode
Strange to me because there's going on throughout it
And it's
Exactly what we called ourselves out about at the end of the last episode
Which was Alex
Is definitely going to get into a little bit of a murky
Story where I'm going to play the role the same
That just made me I love this
This is great
Libertarian
Fiscally
Nothing I ever did
Wow
I mean yeah
If that's the case
Everyone who's ever heard of libertarianism is like
The terrible idea sooner or later sure that everybody's been wrong about
Be able to Copper to them but
So much of Alex is like
Foundation of what his whole operation was about was based on a libertarian
Ron Paul the only person
Being a Libertarian was the stupidest thing I've ever done
Go fuc yourself you a******
If you do think that
Why should we trust Iran now is any better
Cuz
Behavior is the best predictor of future
Alex
Pretty severe situation
Trump is under siege was basically what's going on
The prop
Negotiate to the shot, and others
Admin position for
Loyal forces
NWI
On the field
Poor people in that
Rash with the things he's going through
President
Rodger Stone
Exactly Rodger
I always love
I'm just kidding
Insecure about it because yes of course I can hear us
The real
Sensitive like
This could this election could go either way and Alex
But at the same time
All the time it's
Not close
The only way it's closes because of
It's a f****** close
Anybody who tells you that it's not close
Is a Deceiver
I'm telling you that this isn't
Erica wolf
That we are an incredible trouble.
We dominated enslave you and break you financially
Control
And then you got
What's the plan
Go to sleep
That's not true relation John
I'm out here fighting
The General
So you are
Regardless
We're going to do about that
Alex himself talks about her
How is just mad at you cuz all the preoccupation with like
Focus on the plan everything is according to plan
Which is really funny because you know just hired Deanna Lorraine who
Is there a person who promoted KB in that in the past up
That's really what are you going to do
Where to find anybody
Like popular on the right-wing grift seeing right now
Johnson keep share resources respect
The biggest gaming
It certainly safer to get on that hustle for a while
I mean like Alex
Jerome corsi
I think before it really got as ugly as it is now
And is comical as it is now so had a lot more
Play around McHugh sandbox
Certainly
What are the most
Convincing things Alex's ever look into
And then definitely stop talkin about
Nope
So this is where things start to go into a real tailspin for the episode
About what
Is
Going through
Leave that out
But I mean
Reinforcements
Very serious
He's going to get into it
Quite extensively
He's not good
A very
Long
Consistent diatribe about his troubles
He also had some news items to hit
The first one
Democrats
Runners will begin forcibly arresting you
Contact Tracer which is former Clinton Global initiative or
Honda Accord
Solu
Cast
Or if you say you have a sore throat will let me forcibly
Taken
Jail cell
So
Sounds sound like a true story to you
Barry Obama was in control the FEMA that's why they had the FEMA camps in Clinton
Oh that's right those clear
Mechanism
There's a surge of cases happening in Ohio right now
Places where people who's been exposed
If they're unable to do so at their own home
There's nothing about this squads of Obama Corps members runaground
To give you some sense of how weakness reporting is how Alex is covering this news
Now here is a selection from Paul Joseph Watson
Article on Infowars
The basis for a liqueur
It is not
People suspected to have been exposed to covid
Denise
Although numerous respondents to the directive
Expressed this concern on Twitter it's a long way
Make up some b*******
People making up really bad
There's Something Like lyrics.
Might have gotten exposed to somebody through work or something
Hotel Impossible
State being able to set up places where people can safely
Self-quarantine for a certain amount of time
Makes total sense and I think is a great service
For folks to be able to prise themselves up
He's reporting
Obama goods are going to
And if you look at the underlying reporting on Infowars it goes back to
Some people say weird s*** on Twitter
To just kidnap
Houses for
Yeah cuz it's Obama Court
Trouble trouble
Tweet saying that word
They were busy beavers
Houses of 80 + people that
Covid lockdown
The cdc's
Are false positive
Since last weekend but that fail
Alex's understanding denialism reporting
The big news of the government percent of cases were false positive
That's wild
In reality woodhouse's misrepresenting is at the CDC announced that only 6% of people and their statistics who died from covid-19
Had no other contributing factor
Taking that number and not attempted to better understand what it shows is basically what people like to do
Surprising that is comprehension skills of eroded so severely
He's reporting this to his audience as proof it over 90% of the test or false positive
The fact that 6% of the deaths were from covid-19 alone not really surprising
Part of the reason for this is that there were a number of these deaths that were due to
Conditions that were precipitated by covid-19
Which would be listed as it gets from covid-19 and ammonia for example
There are other cases where covid-19 exacerbated existing condition
A chronic condition
In those cases you do you have multiple cases of causes of death
Very strong
Covid-19
A further issue
Is that a lot of things that would be considered morbidities are super,
Conditions like hypertension or diabetes
As causes
Covid-19
If you just write off all those deaths
Then you can handle the deaths of approximately 45% of the adult population of the United States
Which is the number cited by the CDC has people who have
These shoes really well understood here you know exactly this phenomenon as it relates to
The other condition
Like answer
It just being intentionally misrepresented
Making money off putting people's lives at risk
The scary part to me is how Alex doesn't even seem to grasp the
The talkingpoi
It kind of feels like he's
Yeah he doesn't even read memes because their two legs
6%
Positives another settings
Players positivism false positive
Let's do it
94% fake
Why not
What is somebody going to hold me accountable for this July
I mean this hot this couldn't possibly be connected but apparently
Alex is having some consequences
It is why
And here is where this
We have seven major suppliers
Smaller suppliers
A high-quality organic
Copper line stop
Compliments that we get
For the medication
Herbivores
34 months ago a lot of more late
Stop
We are going to come by
The seven
Fox6
Analogous
The money you put as a down payment on that
When we just
Nothing's coming in
Distribution Center
There aren't any more
I just got a couch
I don't know
You got it from Wayfair.
Fox and nobody was happy about
Got to replace
I took forever
Situation
Come down and he can't get the products in anymore
So yeah
He's a face of like
I'm screwed
I don't have anything to sell nothing to do with it
I will
The next day
I'm going to resist
The siren song
He probably
I don't know I mean it seems like he needs money
Can say with some certainty
And maybe it's that he needs money because
PCS
That is suppliers are resupplying
I will have nothing to say
I can have somebody to keep going
For a while
You come
There will be no money coming in
So what are you doing
Supply cost
Disappeared
So there was no cost
Yeah
So I bring this up with who wasn't like
Really consistent on this especially in the first hour of the show
Alex seems like he is just like
There will be a pain.
Horrible signs
Maybe if Trump gets elected
Stop Landing
It's not right
It is Hell on Earth
There are
Suicide today
The media
Pedophilia all over it
Uno
That
People are in for a rude awakening show
You need to get your storable food infowarsstore.com
Little telerin
Everybody's going to die
When the rapture
Yeah
The numbers are a little bit awesome
Some of this
Obviously real problems like people who are dying
Numbers are a little high
No
Steve doesn't count like you know it's like
It's a b b a
Nothing
In the Box
The worst possible picture in order to then transition
He keeps talking
About this product
60 + items like
Complex formula
We got it
This is bad
I find this pretty remarkable cuz like if you take a little bit of a step back
Makes no sense
If you take Alex that is that the supply chain is broken down
It's the cell you anymore
Has not prepared for a situation like the one we're in
That's okay internet itself
Most of us weren't
The only thing that makes this really funny
When you realize it's so much of Alex's survivalism
Scenario
Bug out bags and Seed vault
Entire industry survival food water filtration
Collapses
For years he sold gold on the expectation that you would need it after the imminent collapse of the dollar when paper money would happen
Just hilarious to see that Alex himself as a businessman seems to have done nothing
To prepare this business to run into difficulties
Supply chain disruptions
Biblical real survivors might have expected this possibility had a plan
It turns out the supplier
Took my advice
Bugged out so
It turns out I should have had a bug out the book and got freaked out
Should have taken my own advice but I insisted on going to Idaho
I'm out
Even though he has product
Don't don't think that Alex feel sorry
Sorry for himself
I think voting for Infowars
What about now
No I feel sorry for the children of this country in the world thanks
Poison vaccine
Fluoride
All right. Get more obvious
If somebody does that you're just like f*** you I'm more worried about the children
You're not children
Call won't somebody please think
Children children
Spending almost
In my entire show yelling about how
I can't get my product anymore and you need to buy stuff for the children
I'm just talkin about me because I don't care about the chilled
I don't need to use it
Falsified concerns that I have children
Helps me
So we get to another appearance
For this
Person quotes
Positive
They censored all that
What is the limit
No that's not a Jefferson quote that's Frederick Douglass
It's interesting Alex's using it
Distributing at we're going into slavery when Frederick Douglass
Who was talking about
He was specific
In order to accept the
Punishment
The thing that
Actual guy
Yeah
That's really white really white
I can't even acknowledge Frederick Douglass
Existence
So Alex
Comes back from break
And he's got
A meme
Up on the board
Sure
This meme
Is a bigger role in this segment than I expected
If you've seen a hundred of these meme picture of a damn and then
The late the water behind
The town below is labeled
Of course this is the dam is Infowars the water on top of Communism event below
Look at this traffic I've got run over here I'm going to walk over here
Hoover Dam
Gallons of water
Unless it's unleashing improper way it'll destroy
Thousands of people
Communism is held back by info
And you're down here
The one thing
Types of dams that are used
Like they don't
Just hold back water
Water energy
Hold It Back
Summer able to create energy
The water goes down
This water is great but if it destroys
Suggest
Right
Perhaps explain it that way you could just literally put
Anything over the water
And described it as
If there's too much of it it will kill the townspeople below bees
Anything it's a stupid me
Explained
Yeah yeah
100 billion gallons of I understand the water and if you don't have a damn it
People incredibly profile
The Damned
Infowars
Trump
Holding back communism
They're coming for you
Just like Donald
Are you
And this is real
Tell you again because the Straits
If you want to get the supplements or the books are the t-shirts of the films
Supplements won't be there in the future
The food is therefore Now 1 to 2 weeks delivery
You need to get your orders at not just for you
How long will be able
The continued operating
This system and self-funding
They Takin are they taking everything away
So I guess we're in a position or Alex
Spending almost his entire show
On this be
Wow and
And obviously I don't believe the problems as severe
Maybe he's making it up
The sound
A real lot to make you sick
It isn't as bad as it's ever been
Vicious and 9
They got people out
With
Contracts out to kill
There are assassins assassins just wandering around
Turn on Alex's light
I don't think it would be a professional assassin
No worries going to be
We've seen I know that he has security and stuff
Universal echoes
Just going up to it isn't a good idea
In the past
Is such that does not seem very careful
Holding weekly swim session
Here's my pitch
Alright
If I'm an assassin
I'm going to use Nova
That's what I'm going to do
So Alex dies of that poison
What can kill Alex Alex do this time
Show up drunk at restaurants in yellow
Situations
It doesn't seem
If he had a heart
No coroner is looking too far into it
Probably not
I don't even call it a day the only reason any of this
Borders on like
Acceptable conversations because
That the globalists of put out assassination team
Trying to find out
So dumb I'm only using James Bond style
Asinine
And I'm as much as this is trying me my result
I refuse to believe you have almost
Exact same thing
I don't trust
Classic situation
Not doing it man
End
Alex says
I'm part of the reason for that is it he is meddling
In the globalist plant
And he knows that
Because they keep telling him so
Is you continue to be the epicenter
You need to stop right now
And they're very very serious
They are moving now
It's okay
Go to info
Northshore.com
Cauliflower
I am
Just
Over and over again
No matter how many plans they make they can never pre-plan for Alex
Needs to eat too much of a wild card doesn't matter what your
It gets even funnier when you start to realize
The devil's plant
The oldest
Personally says god dammit Alex
Spoiled
Something that Beelzebub did not play
Is a weirdo drunk paranoiac in in Texas
The hubris of
I am the only person
Who's fooling
The literal Devil's centuries-old
Play in motion
Fruition now and if I weren't here they'd all these open smooth
Alright man
Delusion of grandeur is like kind of hilarious because it's Alex
Do you really believe that he believed everything you said
That's scary
I like to imagine that Daniel got that profit
Just like
Nah there's no that are you telling me part of God's plan is a weird fat drunk
As the only bulwark against Satan himself and God
How thick is a vector
You telling me to stop it
Food truck out at Barton Springs
Are you kidding me what does that even mean
What's Texas
What's up Joe question me he got his ass beat Daniel huh
20000 Alex Jones
Ridiculous
The Alex Oxmoor me just won't stop talking about these difficult
With what we've gotten our coffee
With only enough to operate if I sold
Both my house
I've got the mortgage
This place
Operator
Okay so yeah houses Anthony if he sells
So
Kind of
Baby empty
Not really all that potent
Okay
You do that for
Be able to keep garlic
Why me you better fucken
Make a difference
Dance party to save the f****** Rec Center
You better be regretting every time you've done these Marathon
Because diminishing returns
Yeah
I mean who knows his Visa total liar and I'm not going to get
I'm trying to make progress I'm not going to get I'm not getting it
Not going to do it cuz I going to get caught up in speculating about like okay
Seems like
Terrible situation financially if I sell both my houses we could go about that
In that both in a few and I'll be able to right the ship so you wouldn't sell those houses
Thing to do unless you had some belief it in that month
Busted
Little way to your house
It doesn't make sense is the Destroyer
Sure you can do that
Scrub home
Podcast
Something like that it's fair
Defeat the Devil you got to have at least 82 Philly
That's what they say about David and Goliath
Slingshot
And
Come on
But what I'm saying is is it
Have the gasoline
To go to the future with the things they're pulling in the things they're doing
Yes I get a big chunk of money
Infowars.com live show feed today
It says emergency
Broadcast
Public planning
Massive world
Windsor losses
There's a link
Infowarsstore.com and the donate
Backpage
Where you can sign up for recurring donations
Or you can sign up for one-time donation
Would simply
Go there and make
A major donation
There's also a p.o. box on there I know people got money out there
Subscribestar it didn't really work out
Any meaningful black and that's why you don't hear talk
Nyra
What is
Oh man why isn't he on
Maybe he should advertise on Facebook
I needed that hatreon
I think it went well
So Alex has other
You need to do this
Support our local
Radio station
Become a sponsor thank the
Ty's local radio station
This show and I'm not saying we're good life
Motivating people to cry
Been a little fake
Country Club
Donate your local
Radio station
Give them your word-of-mouth go and eat at the restaurant
You know what
Normal radio show
Well that would help
What model is here for
So they don't end up broadcasting something else that sells ads better it's literally like
And
It's it it's kind of
You know it's a radio show.
Practice
Like it you basically saying
You guys need to give money to the stations in lieu of
Eniac
Maybe the my pillow guy
To be a sponsor
For nothing in return
I don't want
And I don't want
Anything just give me money
Quietly
You do get something
Rescue in for save yourself
Save the world
We're in this together
Communism
Save yourself
By giving money and potential
That's such a
You know when you make the full switch cuz now he's a you know he's not telling as he does really do much
Politically really it's it's almost a full-time televangelist infomercial
Pills
Show all the time
A lot of the time it is always amazing how like
0 shame there is like that for somebody with millions of dollars
To be like you guys
It's got to save yourselves
I getting me a joke
There's only one way
Behavior
I think it's not as extreme with Alex like I don't think he's trying to buy a jet
Easter something going on Sonos what it is
This episode
Lots of it
It's a lot
Over and over
And over again
Hibbetts doing bees like extreme
Anybody kind of things
3 hour money
Yeah basically
I think the
Save Infowars save the world is not
Going to go as well as save the Cheerleader Save the World season W of Heroes
The bit more than
Whatever season this is
Infowars car wash
You just got to do it
Tires
Emigrate
What can you say
Hell,
Cowgirl
Don't stick your fingers
Creamer on the other side
Scotland
Acute
You understand though
At that size
Doesn't really matter if
Cleaver.
Molasses
Killed hundreds of people
I mean
I don't know slowed
Fair
And then there's a hole in the wall
I would be as words
Cuz it's baby
It's going to take forever yours look it up but we gotta move in a week
So Alex
Meme
Like Easy Love lyrics
Then comes back
Any plays this parody video by Brian stelter
It's not matter
Say something troubling
Request
Request from the number one Fox News shows
Literal require
Repeat
Will you make another Brian stelter
You got it
I don't know if that's true but that seems like a problem
Sad-sad might be a legal issue 2
Look at the White House is like
Requesting
Create propaganda against media Networks
I wouldn't be surprised if some ass I Stephen Miller
They sent an email is like
Memo parody videos really funny you should make another
I mean leave it at all
That sounds like it's not legal
Really effective
Make me pissed kitty parody video y'all go viral on the things that you're not allowed on
Because he wants to cover the story about all the false positive
And the staff
Maybe
Cuz
Headline
Bishop
This one
Last week
Covid test
False positive
Broadcast
Covid-19
Okay I guess
Whatever
Different thing that that story was about but
Is a video that is episode
It says whatever you wanted to say
So I don't know I didn't even try to find this
Justice Dallas
Yep put a date on it
Whatever
Exactly
So there's been some talk about ready fairly soon
Not sure exactly
I don't know
How
That's too rushed
What who knows
I don't know
I don't have a strong opinion on it
Alex believes it's coming soon
Theoretically
Memes
Proof
But they've had the vaccine all along
In a month they say
That's magic thing we don't have it for you
They've already developed
Years ago years ago
Again
What ride again
The right again
Doesn't prove anything
It's at that's all just nonsense
Or if you're I don't know someone like
You
Bei hater I'm not a hater
I strongly disagree
Understand is that Alex Jones
When he does
Is individual research
He creates can't even find his own headline
He creates a research
Product
It's based on
He's on
In depth
Analysis navigate his own website no one else does this time
Heater
ER word-of-mouth we need yours transmission
Original research
What's going on
Intuit
We the high quality of very low price
It just keeps going
The more you think about we don't laugh about the devil too much cuz that's
You know we just ignore it but the more you realize what
The devil being in play
Vietnamese got their best brains working
A million years old
And incomprehensible to humans
Yeah
Autosmart
Smarter than the devil
Hubris
Okay also I love the idea research
Headlines on drugs
And now it's just reposting articles from WorldNetDaily and like
Gateway pundit
I listen to my
The base
So Alex gets into talking about
After Trump win
Okay it's pretty dark
There's that you and I are going to a camp
In this political we have to live without the Democrats
Global sports that don't believe the country
Destroyer
Destroy them
They started it
So we have to have the outlaw the Democratic Party
Rooting out and rounding up all the Democrats
Locked up
This kind of conversation just being like
Add casual
Is
Unacceptable
And it's fine we're going to need some sort of secret
I guess research
They wouldn't even bother researching your behavior
Fog attic asks like a cool Trump password
Hey you know why it's super funny to talk about
Champs now
In the present that we're dealing
Is that it
Because it's so
Because America has never taken the Aged
You know you never seen that kind of behavior from America
Now with the climate that were in the sky
Because Alex is entirely career was predicated on the idea
Full circle
There's a lot of like really not good
Role models
In the world of professional wrestling
Water monsters
There's one who's probably the biggest
Because
Famous
And also
Complete Freddy perhaps now
Alex lifeson
But I got to say
Watch WrestleMania
Andre the Giant weigh like 50
Hulk Hogan
The show
Years ago
Florida affiliate
What is shock Alex likes Hulk Hogan
Man
Hey Brother
Hey brother brother
Did you just start
I think Alex would do
Particular line of work
This group of friends
Alex's just into it because you recently came out
Said there's like a neighbor got a valid and its dog's name or something
My God
Great
But he's he's recently
Also Alex because he's the leader of the new new new world order
Earlier
90s the leader of the New World Order
But that's what he was doing he was secretly revealing the globalist
It was brilliant on his
Globalist
Was to allow group
Is it true
Entire company
World War
Gaston from Australia turns out to be Syrian girl
Okay talked about a bit
Exposition of like
Hey I don't like a side but also I'll spend all my time talking about how the enemies of a solder
All this s***
Although I'm not sure if there's much are between her
And this out apology
Talk about how shity interested
Interesting things like
Yeah
Old
Was choked
Under Obama
Years old
She was
SO2
Is a complete and utter
Nordstrom
No one's trying to sell that
We're actively trying to keep you from using that as a way to miss frames
But also hey got beat under Georgia
Right
Also I've bad news for Syrian girl about that old man
Alex's decided and reported
And so he deserve to be pushed over by the police
Soap and girl don't see eye-to-eye on that exactly
I think they do
So I
I do voice on Alex's show of at least some kind of
Service
Towards what
Protester about
Syrian girl is coming in with a little bit of that
I think
A little
And I think it might be in service of the wrong
But superficially it has at least some
Like
Appearances of
Something close to rationality dealing with
But I mean
You can't allow that
Because if you actually talk about the problem
So I'm surprised that she has good but
A window or some
Get the f*** out of here
So Alex is trying to also interview rationalize the police shooting people
Glad
It's just
Streaming to shooting sticks
And it's just
Shooting save cops lives
What do you expect
The world
Perfect
Absolutely
Man
Time does anybody
Just like
Think of a solution
Maybe we should also find a way to keep cops from getting shot at as much
Like the problem is cops are getting shot at
The answer is like
We have zero creativity Society zero creativity
Maybe there's a different way other than let's have cops shoot people
Alex Jones say like yes
Because the world's not perfect
B2B say
About would never be his position
Prior
So
I mean
Reposition
Been a little wild episode since we've heard something like this
Force.com he orders in now plus uni Portal 2
Over and over and over again throughout the episode just
Hammering at home
September 3rd August 6th
Top of the month bills
I don't know I don't know
I don't know what it is
I can't pretend to understand exactly what it is but there's
Like the whole game that I was going to try and play
Beginning of episode is B
Like in denial of making everything up
If you look at their somehow extended
It is on this episode
There's something nothing is real something requires money he said he needs a lot of money
Probably a lump-sum maybe a lawyer's fee or something whatever it is it something
Like I can't pretend
Manifesting this
I don't believe you would act like this if you just like
I don't want to get a second car I'm going to f*** with people
In this kind of way
In order just to get a little bit of fun money
Yeah your money for the possibility
Because it's so psychopathic
But now that I know it's a possibility
He might want another car
It seems unlikely
Syrian girl is gone
Have you can't go anywhere else
And actually speak the truth without getting censored or banned
I dare you to make shadowgate
Speaking the truth
Doodles
Can speak the truth and I believe in you and so I will continue to speak you in on things on the show I'm sure that I will be allowed
How to speak the
Probably not
Probably get your 6 month contract in the contract and you never worked at the begin with
Send an email to Millie or a
You don't even Twitter
DM like a what's it like to work for Alex Jones
Nope nope
Hey you know I can come in and say whatever I want speak
What is the kind of Truth you want to say beautiful before and then
Feminism happened Martian sir
Really it's a cancer I mean look at what it does it infect
Text all these women and it has them disown their greatest power which is their femininity
Is boring-ass online talking points from the other Proto alright gamergate nonsense from
Be angry at the other stuff to do. I feel like the right wing
I mean obviously there's always
Amongst
In terms of like when that was really their Central like a big thing they put
That was like when Milo yiannopoulos and Sargon of akkad we're kind of like
Who are these
New faces feel like she's a little bit late on this anti-feminism Kik
It's a little stale it's a little bit
Disney movie
The needle probably what is it with these women burning their bras 50 years ago right
Good luck
You're probably going to get fired
Really get a good lawyer
Get a good lawyer Barnes
Yeah even doesn't work anymore
Alex said bring about
From time to time
This is this is our look at September 3rd
He needs money
I mean I want to take a look
What was going on in the present day
But I also wanted to skip a couple days and get us
Up to the present
Because I was pretty concerned go back it's going to be a lot of
Denial justification
We've already talked about that on Mondays episode
I don't want to I don't want to wallow in
Haven't gotten better information is only gotten
Liar
The present is present as we can September 3rd and it's just
In your face
Food
Cellfood I buy my supplements
Suppliers okay
Man
Tell me you got to get a new gold guy
Well maybe it's his old guy
If you're tired
You can't get back in the game
Situation if I ever saw
20 this year
Gould
Is attack issues and stuff but I apologize about that but
Happy birthday
I'll try.
Go to
Leo
Supply chain
Alex
In color