I'm sweating
Respectful
I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Knowledge fight
Prepare for the question question
This one should have been prepared for this question in the past
I don't like the generally by video game
As soon as they come out because
Experience playing a game
2 years later and say generally very late to the party
Almost all the time
Exception because I had to give Tony Hawk 1 and 2
Out of the game first came out
I was unable to
Structure of a
Snow fun
Pretty self-contained
Enormous
And sprawling
A lesson about asking for what you think you want
Rendering
These areas
It's just great
Just Machinery itself
Maybe the parallel
And every
Nope that's the challenge
I got all of them as I started
The new remaster version
I noticed
Trying to do that
I might
State around
Yeah yeah
U.s. open
Tennis in ever
Today
What playing the game the world's number-one player perhaps the best tennis player of all time or at least maybe the most perfectly constructed
Accidentally
Hit one of the line judges
In the throat
So he's disqualified
So he played one set and then he accidentally hit the lines
U.s. open
He's an accident
Exactly
For the first time in like 10 years somebody under the age of 20
Probably going to win a major
Perhaps
Incapable
Sports 2020
Hrrr Friday episode
Was such a disgraceful I need money
Stop
See where his head's at
Panda
See what happened how
Are you very much Thomas
You could absolutely take that generosity
X much like a tennis ball toss it up
Hit a nice serve directly into your local charity or bail fund and that is
Love you
I got to say to the confusing look at the mailbox okay
Knox
Purse not so confusing
Imagine
Epsom salts
Yes
EBay
Shut up
Scratch
Computer
Happy birthday
Could be
A day would be great
Inside
Is back
Going on here
Potatoes in this
Bach
I open up the bag potatoes
Directions
Yes
Potatoes
Because I
Furious
You can buy a bag of potatoes
I didn't know that that's not something that I'm
Actually I already got it
Message person who sent that
Yes
I do need to share this with you
Whatever you do
Do not drizzle butter
Alright
Message to me
Appreciate more
Or the confused
Is it a message
You know
Did not know what's going on
No I want
Sorry
Switched it up
What happens in the election
Trump won
Secretly or publicly where
Democrat
The economy hostage
War
Criminal scumbag
These this is going
Be the most contested election
Pearlridge
Anything that I would say the same about mail-in ballots was true he probably would be
Materials that are needed to create
No matter what
Yeah and whether or not the mail-in ballots thing is true they're going to say it
Doesn't matter yet
Is going to be like week afterwards
We predicted this
Predictive literally every single day
Advice
That is
Or Biden win for Trump actually want to take out the right
I don't know
I think that we could have
Starting to give me hope now
Is that I'm starting to see the right
Pitch
Trump is the single greatest there
There's little bits of like
We know Trump is going to kill everybody
And it's like I've heard that kind of argument before
People who are not
Come back around
Relationship
Between local and you work
Co-equal between the feds
Bashar
Separation of power
Understatement
So you and you come in and take over the cities
The governors in August
Antonio
Remove the board
Separation of powers
This is weird
Control local government
There is a
Constitution doesn't need
YouTube
Nothing is extremely constitutional
It's just in there
Very
Degrees
Deserve
Joe Biden
Thomas
Edison was black
He said eight million.
Wisconsin audience
Edison's design suffer from a particular issue
According to CNN
His longest lasting light bulb could only last for about 15 hours
For the filament burned out
Which was essential
The best of electric light for people to actually use
So technically
Diversion
True
Thomas Edison just invented
Going to ignore that be
Alright
The great resource
Now we're a lot of children
Growing up
You should graduate pastor
That's like me saying that I still apply for book it
He sees this as
Sjw
People everywhere
Lewis Latimer
Everything by Gresham
The mental illness of the left
Making movies
Real Street
What
Work there
Marc Anthony
It doesn't come from a study history
Overwhelming amount of scholarship you can find
Diversity in ancient empires
Is raw
Coming up
On the Verizon
There's going to be a new strain
Covid-19
That is reason for deciding is what they're going to do is
Familiar
Murray State Police
Covid-19
They have this whole war game
It's going to be Wicked
People be pissed
MN news
Pneumonia
Superman
Vitamin C
Zinc in your blood
You make me
Cannot
Careful.
Just don't like a real Super Evil plan of the enemy is going to do
And I know they're going to do about it
I know in that situation if you're in their situation
What I would do instead is improve other people
Weasley I'm as evil as they are and their situation
Yuck LOL
William Barr rambling
About mail-in vote fraud
Bad clip
Show
Every subject
Remember just like a couple weeks ago
Just went off on bar for all of the ways that he was betraying Trump
I just like
Just like that I disagree
Guess who's a trailer
I wish people would
Listen to this and be like
Like I really like you and then you just
He might about that
So
Upsetting but also
Because the Alex
Yeah you know he's he's wearing his
Is familiar
Metaphysically piss on people that have done this.
We go down this road
Survival
But the enemy
This will be like
It'll be alright
Because
So illogical purging
Great
Okay
It's just a little weird
People
I just think if you knew that this was going to happen you would provide a better plan then
I just Barrel forward
Real strong aversion to it that I did
Infowars is about being
Gateways to then
Brought out the enemy so we know their real numbers
Instinctive job
Is the pawn sacrifice
I will tell you
More to do
Before we reset
Victory or death
Eternity
The other side
You can decide what you're going to do
Becomes
That's the sacrifice itself
Can survive
This is the true nature of
Real leadership
Okay
If you had somebody who's describing like the
Before suicide attack
I didn't want to say that kind of thing you should become suicide attacker
What we are is the Vanguard
I don't think he understands how Chatsworth
No
In order to
Great
Where is Ray Lewis
Really even think that much of it except for
The Talk
Is come up a couple
Sacrifice the seventy-five-year-old
These ideas are not straight
Sprouts
The kind of affixation more than anything else
Constantly talking about it
Yeah
You should become you should Pawn sacrifice in order to become a king which doesn't happen
Jasmine
Yeah isn't troubling it's troubling
So Alex
Images
You did
Being directive
Suspiciously like
Police officers
Department of China
Hello Hollywood honest
Malaysia
Hong Kong
Should be discussing this
China has thrown a little Hollywood
Mission of that
New York
Military training
Chop area
This isn't something fake autonomous Zone
Footage of
Humanity that Barrel forward through all the time
Like in the middle of talking about a thing
You f****** the exact
Is an expert
You should know that
60s guy is
College classes in Burien
Eloquently
You know Greek history mythology
2%
Clever Beach
You're awesome
Single ever go to
Yes
Give me a super obese black woman
Iceman
Eusebia crazy
Chinese agent
Young woman
Nope
Taking tokenism to a new level personally
A giant list
Haley Peterson
Black lives matter
Characterization of all the black women
Involved in protest picking up herself is
It's always like this
I don't know it's like Zoom
So Alex Goes to call
Color not great
Is war
Virginia
Hello welcome
Are you welcome hi Alex I'm a first-time caller my son adores you so I just want to let you know
Is Martha Collison
Israel cancer
Dlm Denise
Crazy.
Cinema way
They should take all of them over to the
Make sure they have no way of coming back
That way you don't have to worry about him anymore
That's so dumb
Just for logistical Reasons from
Supporting
As a system of government
If I were a reality TV show
The show called
Where
Medical treatment
Fun
So it's alright
People more capable
Exile exile
All right now
You know you're on the team of right
Caller is wrong
About
How to behave
So great
Your 141 out
Disappeared sooner or later
You know the people who facilitated authoritarian rise of the first one
I'll be taken out by those
Seems like a
In present day
Himself locked up in his own prison
Satan walk to the prison
Estate
Is building for us
Hell is the prison
That was for children
Wife
Rothschild
Inhale
Stupid greedy
Nobody
What's the weather
The losers
Call Zell
People I don't like
They're talkin about that
Capricious
Yeah doesn't seem to be paying all that much attention
Certainly
Yeah
Take some out and he's like what am I doing
Back here I've read the book
Alex and kicking my ass
I just
Sharp focus on the
Because Alex
Pretend to be a news show
Number one
You're not established Doctrine approved
Beyonce
You say
David Rockefeller and the Rothschild
DoubleTree
Correspondence
What is real bad out here
Color outdoor
Before I go
Trump's October surprise might have something to do with Joseph
Gregory Hallett
Good BBs
Some things that concern me about it
He is basically climbing
King of England
Put in papers going back to January
Good morning
British economy
They bought the right
King George the Fifth
It's just like
He didn't sign the Star Wars prequels
Space wizard
Grounding
Green over here
I just don't understand it
What's going on
Altered reality
Alex and supplements are
Accidentally
Interesting
Portrait
He's just
I guess he doesn't realize
Cuz they're not coming
No you don't generally progressed from like harder drugs more
Like
From time to time
Quickly all the time
Talk about the f****** rightful King
Governor Greg Abbott of Texas
Are there full
Not really
Don't have to play hardball
Certain business groups, San Antonio
Years ago
You know
Shut up
Stupid
After shadow
To listen to him
Secret blackmail information
And not juxtapose that with
Listen to talk about
Do the open-source Journal
Governor Abbott
If you do not do what I say I will reveal the secret that you have a mistress right now in the
Blackmail
So
There's no reason for this back thing it's being rushed your videos
The doctor
About the
Submerging the back pain
2.0 everybody needs
To see that
Trump is undercurrent
Emerge
Kim dami
Protocol
Permission
Is wild
Charge and the Beast
Different back then I don't know what part
To the world they're in
You can find in the military to trust to carry out his
Executive order but go into the
Going to be
At least on the hard drive can't find the inventory
Evacuate human live and blow it off
The freaking
Wow
Wow that's very smart
Blow up
What is Lakewood
Okay ask me tomorrow
Really scary
Alright
States
Sure
Because you will have to go to war with a welder
Economy
That's all I'm saying is I'm
What
I'm not a warmonger either
The power to make a move now we're also
Back on
No matter what
You have to do a preemptive or otherwise you'll get 911
Foreign policy
You know your letter from Alex
How many times do you have to
Warmonger
As opposed to like just reward app
Irrigating
It's quite small.
Duchenne dad
Okay enjoy a little bit year
Humiliated
What
You say
Center
Christian
Child molesters I just want you to know
Show think of anyone sounding more like a Satanist little clip right there
AOL
Through something really true
Skip back 20
His response
Class action
Give up before you begin
Judges are scared
All the time
Mafia II
There's some good ones but what's really going on
And so many people
Because
Ground
Asura's Wrath
Frivolous lawsuit you never end up
Cowardly judge
Warriors
Judge in his own courtroom
Play the score
That's so dumb
In dealing with
And have all these fees legal
I stay in the Endor or now
Give me the names and then
Not good what else should we do after we ran over again
What else
Cuz I'm already loving the blow-up all the vaccines power graduation
Murderers Row great ideas
Callers
Guys we got a pitch meeting
For the new ad campaign
What do you got
Alright I am
Impressive
Talk to a bunch of
Here's what happened
So if your show wraps up
Not good idea but people Wars Army a little bit literally
Every man that I've talked
In this area
Is
Same way
We can't help it because
Under attack
My idea that I wanted to put
To you is
That you have
Connection
You have the inside knowledge that
Average civilian doesn't have
We will we will come together
Whatever we need to
What are those
If you call us up to active duty
Yeah
General revolutionaries
Has plans they're the same as the globalist
Accidentally discovered
Protest
Biscuit
Search for now
You all can hear me right now
We have to get behind
General Alex Jones
K thanks bye
Awesome
Power numbers
How many
Do we have to gather in math
Maybe once a month
We have to gather and show them what they're really up
The globalist have all this
Is their main opposition
More than that
So you want you want to run
Do you listen to my Ibotta food truck
Getting together for a rally that's
Not as big as it used to be
Zester
Queer
If they want the produce
No I mean the right-wing is done pork
Forever which is 2
Centra store
Somebody in the protest movement
Just enough
To get them to break away and then they don't have the same power
Not doing it right now because I accidentally elected
You just can't give up a little bit so it's not hard
A little bit and you go back to normal
A winning formula
Worst
I'm not even going to dignify
That we're fine with metal
Before we go
Wholesale Auto
Really love
Definitely
Uncle Bacala
Walker
So I from an Australian
Australian accent
Disgraceful understated
Just say like I'll see you I'll see you on the street
That's great
Can't you accept
Never bothered without one
Like I've always had to do voices in order to get by there
Oh s*** now I got to find it
So everything
You know everything's minimized
You know he's one of those guys like
Sight words
Going back to you
Studying
I already
Frantically to eat something
Lovely
Positive to where you need to be right
Hey
Really hope this is knowledge
I am a
Joe
I really want to talk
Primarily
Talk to him about
Matrix
The Matrix
When are in the Earth
Only form of a Chorkie
Messages
Available
Was America
Came in a little red pill
So
I need to talk to Alex
For providing
Sharky
Transpo
Either way though
Super Show
Hope you're having a great time
Have a good one
That's very
It's probably
Protocol
Call absolute
Early in the morning
I can do it
In your basement
I was wondering if
And I also
Swallow
Anime
I had
Alright
Yorkie
Update
Take me to another
Birds
Be ready to
To move along
More
There
Update
Samantha
To be perfectly honest
Premature
Plant stuff right now
House decor
Sure you need to have a house
This is my emotional
Take care of
Really clear on
Refuse
You know like
For it you know it
More difficult
Alright
Situation
You know
Even if it's just
Yeah
So I'm just covering the bases
Understandable
I'm looking at the MUA
Girl
I need to be able to melt plastic
S***
Did you call him back
Now for sale
$40
Parcel number to take today
I should have got a different phone number
Charity or bail Fund in your area to help out people
Alex