Damn important
I have great respect for knowledge
Imposing
Fight
MoneyGram
Alex
Knowledge fight
What's up
Dan is
I started smoking a little bit
Cigarettes
Oh yeah
Dress and I finally quit again
Without any cigarettes at also
That's my bright spot so finally
That's great
No I'm sorry I'm sorry
The scenic route
This is the perfect weird how the world works like that
Whenever you need to be tempted
Even know you're not going to be late
Portrayed
We get by
Flower and plant
Shop
Walk-around
My people
Which is the plant shop employees and also plants
Inspiration
Songs there is anything
Around the walls
And I realized
Flower
Treated myself
Pedal with the Yellowstone
My childhood
10 bucks
And get one to put on my desk
What was the alien flower
From a seed.
Pepsi
Looks
Maybe you need a clipping
Maybe you know you need a clipping and then you put that in the thing I've heard clipping before I have no idea
I don't understand corporate leadership don't ask me
I'd like to
Podcast
To go over but
Ridiculous
According to Cheryl
First Tennessee
Teddy Teddy needs
PIRA
Sponge brush
We got to go.
Heroin
Tim
You can take that generous
Spirit and you could
Put it in an empty bag
Cigarette pack grab that
Decide never to buy another cigarette pack again
So instead you take that generosity
Cigarette disposal store
Recycling center
Michigan Iowa
You don't end something like that self-consciously
Miss
Now I struck out man
Sure
Black Box
Zia
On top of this black box
What appears to be
Clippings from
Hours of entertainment
Useful insight munition for
I can guarantee
Yet
So that's just to err on the side of caution
This is a gift from
The flatulence Royal subject
Alright we open it up here
Are we on
Subjects of his horn
Can't get the bullhorn
This is another
You see I'm a fan of this voice how can I ruin that part of the show
Both of them screeching annoying
Yeah this is just got an image
Disturbia
The nice rainbow hand
You don't lose the time
The noise comes out
A small Society SPS
And then there's a little ass
Ryan
That is
How do you
I'm going to
Shrub
And you know what I say
Jordan
Embark on this adventure
Contacts dropped
I have a very
Time and time again
Rivertown
Arthur Dan we average a lot
Shoes
They are really doing it are you getting out
And by largest
Respect
Copyrights or whatever to
If you sell something to take that
Even if it would be fair use I'm still going to respect that
All you needed to hear business baby
Is an interview
Kerry Cassidy over project
Did the podcast for the month
Listen to Alex Jones
How we had it set up
One of them
Something silly silly
Even though the times are much worse'n
Severe right now
We are wax
No idea who this guy is
No interest in looking at the mall
Nope
The muscles from Brussels
Yeah this this is this is an interesting interview the covers as Alex with a covers the waterfront
Okay there's a lot of a lot of territory
Okay alright
Terry doesn't respond
Alexa
I'm guessing she loves
Show a lot of it has to do
With
Covid-19
Televangelism the devil's wheelchair
The news
Who is related to
So I talked about maybe turning Chinese
These people into vampires
Houses are boarded up
Confirmation silence is deafening
You can't talk
Virus
Of course
Frequencies and do other things
Gaylord
Weather
Targeting ended
Scalar weapon
Really
Right
Hi Carrie
It wasn't for us to
I deprived you of opportunity
I think I cut out
Scalar attack
No
Really Otero.
Taking things
Brighton
Reddit covid
The common cold percentage should I try
On this to give you an indication of how little she gives a s***
What is all about
Understanding
How doctor
Go anywhere
Fever
Lou likes
Skin
To radiation
So we even had a doctor
In York
Turn off machine
And it may be that he was innocent
Sure
Frenemy
But she was quite
Traveling around March I think it was
And he came forward
Innocently near doctor in
I think it was
Dealing with emergency
And she was
Same.
Trouble breathing that it was much more of a kind of a
Radiation sickness or high altitude
Sickness
Symptoms
And the TV
Ventilator
So this is a
Very important
Tails there
She sounds exactly like my Bob tried to remember
Okay 1000 sometimes people are asleep
And then I slept
More inside their sleep
Stop codon
He's always wearing a mask
Sometimes
He was an expert at something doctor guide
Cameron kyle-sidell
Yeah I remember this is not making up some pictures lying about everything around
Revelations remember his name
Story
Maybe corn
In April Kyle's Adele posted a YouTube video
Presented with acute respiratory distress syndrome
Which is treated with the ventilator
What Kyle Citadel was pointing out was at the muscles of typical ards patient
Or malfunctioning
Program
Same pressure traditional
Sure that would be concerned
Did you see if he is been threatened in the face of the Earth
No I can't tell that to
Is video with covered by
Find articles
Gabe
There wasn't the cover-up
Going on
Settings
Covid-19
Inmates
News 12
Personalized approach
Haitian
Which is why she conveniently can't remember details about this guy
Reminding listener of how about that story made them
To actually engage with the story itself is dangerous
It's just the doctor kyle-sidell disappeared
No reason to suggest that
He hasn't posted any more videos on his YouTube channel
Before that videos that doesn't seem too weird
Twitter account
Okay
So
So much of right-wing anger
Boiled down to
Just like I don't understand your words
I think they mean why do you talk
Difference
Speaking English
You might ask yourself scalar weapons
Or whatever
He's targeting of cities
Wow
There's one
Cleopatra
Target population Center
From a distance
And this gets into Tesla and his wardenclyffe
Power
There we go
I talked about
Augusta
And how he
He was aiming for I believe it
I think was a
And it actually
Something like 2,000
Then I get into the fact that it was
Show that they knew what she was doing and in the process
Houston.
Different
In tomorrow
No s***
Tesla
What's the cause of the temperature
I did not know that
You haven't read all of the files in the Assassin's Creed games
No s*** I know that much
Address of the villains of her story are using Tesla technology to direct remote attacks its please
This is the Tesla accidentally shot Sunbeam
I love it
This is great
It doesn't work
Gotcha
Redirection
Place was a really exciting place around
Matters because it's just a cover-up version of the story
Going out of business sale
The government right
Secret
We're going to find out where this comes from later and I
Is it literally says
Who created
No
I didn't ask you what
The kind of person who would read everything in a game
I could never have done that
Become an adult
So
Deep
Denialism medicine tonight
Call
Urology
As Judy
Never isolated any
Virus associated with
So what does that tell you that tells you that
Working on that
Contagion
Right away season questions I mean it just sounds
Questioning
Premise
What is virology
Have they been able to buy
Isolate antivirus
And if so
How did they do that at
They've never done that for any virus
There's also
This germ Theory
The whole thing he's thrown out get rid of it.
Little germ Theory get it out of here
Disease
And creating certified moral character 2:30 a.m.
Quite a bit
Really feel like
You know how you get
Free samples
The grocery store or 100 days or whatever
Here's what we do
Vaccines also have
Station
Polio and the Cure
So you get polio
This is really bad
It was a good idea to make
Conditions that you need to be vaccinated for
That's a that's a situation
Solution
Marriott
Syringe
No
You just a quick rebuttal
She's wrong
I'm not going to throw away
Isolated the virus
Never isolated
Textbooks
Little drawings of sucking viruses in
Why do you have tons and tons of studies about I mean anything to her
Does any Nobel Prize actually
Secret Wars
Go get it out of here
There's another guy
Okay
This is who carries it
Alright
Germ Theory
The whole thing thrown out
Your
There was another another sign
I discovered
Substantial way of looking at
Human health and what what's going on
The bottom line is that
Comes from within
So that we generate
Except around our cell
Which is like
What is expelling poison
Coronavirus
Difficult
Telford cell
And this is where that comes in
And it's all about
Poisons that are cell
Poisonous
Poisonous environment
Who is the other guy
Who is this guy
Who just took up more you know like Broadview
The details
Was that you
To tell you
Psychic
So I got psychic download
They were installing
Using
So
From there I I kind of
And then also
Certain person
Referred me
Get a tremendous amount of research around
Around
Tesla
And
And he cites all his
Documentation
Tell deception like The Story of Us
How to use Tesla check.
Mirror
Basically
Power and what happened
And do it in this country
Where do you find objectionable
Alright
Do Tesla's stuff and I read books
Cliff Towers
Bien
This is what you entertain as
Possible and even you know like a reasonable
The first person who got it
I mean if this is something that comes from inside of
No.
It's the Coronas that comes from inside of you and your cells are expelling poison
Obelisks and Towers wardenclyffe
Or whatever
Store evildoers and her whatever parlanti uses
They are the ones who were shooting
Shore Towers
Want to say that
Physically and physically but functionally germ Theory
No that's
So how was it
Spreading
It doesn't not from person
Yes
He was drawn to
Tesla ideas
Or something
Just in the sidebar
Historical Tesla
Don't comes in what stock
Yeah Nikola Tesla
Evereve
Hey edit don't even get me started on
To start this this storefront
Discovery about Tesla's
Boy
Instantaneous
Virtually
When
He's going to
So there's no down
And the other thing is that
At least 20 investigated
Is that
The Tesla
Exact words as a scientist
I was riding down when he was
Doing his experiments
And his his exact time
Is wardenclyffe Tower
Amy
Where he thought was a nun
Populated area of
Antarctica
Ended up to be
Going
Ended up in Siberia and cost
Directions REI
He's doing ab invesca happened is exhausting
At the moment
Yes sir
This is from
I think I think there's a very serious question
Corrected
Is it possible to shoot a laser that
Accounts for the
Curvature of the earth and still land
I don't know
Do you know is those journals a plot device
Have you ever
Cuz it's true
To keep the Constitution
This is all from a 2006 Thriller novel called ghost dancer
Buy case
Isn't a person
It's a pendant husband and wife
Cheat code
Thriller novels
Tesla's Journal
Villain in that novel science
Treating them like historical document
We transfer
How do you how what better way to hide the real journals than in a fiction novel.
Perfect
If you take the first letters of each page you'll find where they're located
Confirmation from another weirdo
This is a completely independent
Situation
Brown remote viewer guide
I've consulted with Carrie about some Fusco
So just do happen
Take that
And what they found was
Italy
The remote URC to agree that there was actually an alien
Thekeyplay
In the area of Augusta
When
They don't
Weather
Okay so they are not aware of that link up
Tesla
So I
Interesting is a tween
Tesla was in touch
I got to go
Are you
The remote
Confirm
Seriously the alien battle
They didn't know
Tesla blowing up
Yeah the alien battle was ended by directing Tesla's
Course
It was God's plan.
Thrillers
Injustice 2
Although it appears to be much like Alex
Carrie is taking pieces of picture
Weaving them into a Fantastical narrative about
All of this is
In my world document
And backed up
Doing a lot of work on that.
But for the general populace
No nothing
Do these episodes condescending attitude
Tesla blew up
Accident
And the real people don't even want to know these things
Probably at this point it's fun it's fun
These ideas
Can't handle
YouTube norlien
You can read this 2006
Thriller novel
Pikik download
It's condescending
You don't even know the aliens are
Dumb for not knowing that aliens had a battle and I really don't like it I don't like that mentality at all
It's hurtful
He's right
I'm scared
Trump
Timer
Sunny's Carryout
How old is
America
First general
Government
So according to Jean-Claude you folks are old generals who got fired
To overthrow the government
Doesn't sound good at all
That's the one
Joseph
Destroying Tesla way to give you a call
Either
Discussing how their purges often times and reader
Worship positions when there is a turnover of administration
You put your team
Extend
It's generally known that whenever
Got rid of
General
I think that goes on a lot whenever
President
Takeoff
Presence definition
There's a Changing of the Guard if you might say even in the Angelika
That I've been told kind of cheese
Secretly
That
And people don't realize
New president come on
L Avenue
And maybe they make
But they kill a lot of the CIA agents that are non
Why
Why would you ever do that
Why would
Why would anyone work for the CIA
So I started and then the next day they said if the president changes I die
Yeah that sounds like a recipe for a toxic environment
The real Megan and Morgan is coming up
You're aware in with the agency for a while
You can either accept your new president
Love you
Kilgrave
Lover he's my favorite you know how a grated into work under regimes where if you
Make them angry
We just pretend to like
Current president I think you would like every president
Equally
Bia2
You know what that's like regulatory capture
The SEC has offices inside the same building
You don't want your CIA Hunter guys
Just the recipe for disaster
Are there cell phone
Do like the idea behind the scenes there's evidence
Maybe it sounds ludicrous
Maybe there's accident
How many need a lot of sources on this
Knows about
What is it
They killed the CIA plane for about this stuff
Lady who's afraid of
Somehow I can't get hurt
Jesus conception
Superpowers
22 idiotic antipasto
Jean-Claude
There is some credence
Scary
Go back to
John F Kennedy
He was president
Incorruptible or something realized
Get hung up on that I'm going to pull up
Interrupting
That's the nature of these episodes
Uncorrectable
Don't worry about it
At the time he realized he couldn't Trust
People with me like intelligence Services operation
Where he was getting people recording stuff
Tahir Moore
Secret
As far as
It doesn't look as though the Kennedy
Family
Getting murdered
No Doubt
So at some point
And yes
Someone's got to read the writing on the wall
You're going to be at Target
Special
Crainer
Joe Kennedy
Literally just ran for Senate in the House of Representatives
When rsk was killed in 1968
Death in 2000
Half a century
Global most of the other
Incorruptible William Robert
Right
I don't know about the Camelot connection
In between the Project Camelot
I don't know I don't know
JFK jr. realized
You know he's going to be
Probably
Plane crash
Decades
Do with all this s***
Get more internet
Here's my here's my fantasy conspiracy theory president
Love it come on man
He didn't even get to finish out his first three months
You got her you why did he die
Right everybody's like
Rashad you know this dude didn't even make it he's either you could have been polonium poisoning or their Warren G Harding
James Garfield had a beard
Look me in the face
Do you do I
I'd say you didn't have beards
2q stuff a little bit later but
Interesting about
He's working with these good folks
Tesla raised used
Spread covid in what have you
Obelisk
Ukraine
Hunter Biden and Joe Biden
Anniston
And everyone who's involved in Ukraine
They're involved
In action
CRST
And the real truth by the way
Not even about Russia it's about something in Ukraine
And I am
Sort of online
The devil in
Andy Frain
You talked about on other
Update
There's more here than meets the eye
This case will not go under cell
Board this Ukraine situation
Baby it's
Mountain
What's a fun party Hardy Boys way of looking at life
Mountain where the devil makes his residence
And that leads you to ask yourself
Who wins in a fight a lot
Look I would say
Stupid
Geopolitical truck ever been
One side Russia resource issues
Play Store
Incredibly, the fact that there's trouble
Horoscope
I was in Greece
Back in 2007
One ring of course
We took a little trip
We went to some Island
Amazon Knoxville
Scooters around
And weave
I don't know
I might be mixing up memories
He wasn't there
That was Jesus born
We we take a step back
Geopolitical issues
Because I love hearing about Double Mountain
Nonsense
Mike down for this because
She tried to put videos up somewhere else
Although by the way
How do you say the band video I will call over there and they haven't even accepted
Fanvideo not sure
His videos are being banned in whose are okay right now
Battery capacity has banned from banned. Video
Alex Jones is censoring
Kerry Cassidy
Why would you allow her free
You coward
You hypocritical coward how dare you the truth out videos about Ukrainian devil mount
How different is
Now Barry Moore
Exactly
Great
Gino
Okay
So we have DNA
Would you say that your DNA is
That's a loaded question
Right
Kaiser
It's kind of a trick question
Because you're human
Made a profit of 12 or more
Haven't
Actually if you want to look at it
At least 12:30 races meaning
Planet
Some of which have also said
An inner inner earth and inside
Civilization 6
Did come from
Off-world initially but how
I have been here for millennia
Living inside the planet flat-earthers carries a hollow Earth
Love it
Okay so then humans were
Constructed
Where we were built
Yeah I want to call
I'd like a slave race
Sumerian text
You were created as like
Remaining race because they needed
Something from Earth
White gold
Evolve
Is
I don't know I haven't heard her
You know.
Going to be down there
I'm interested because I always do the HALO Series more than I like
XB
Because he allowed
There's promise there's promise with you can find something in there there's a place
All kinds of animals running around I can see everything
Isn't another
Does it work
Play the video game
Map
That would be what happens if you
Or whatever
Science fiction writers
Always have a hollow Earth
Somewhere along the line
The worst science fiction writers have the Flat Earth because it's just a
It's a measure of your explore invitation
I'm glad we're in agreement
Just talk more about that
Trump jr.
John F Kennedy Jr and Trump
Many many years ago before
So this is where you guess
Unity
Qanon
At least inspired by John F Kennedy Junior
She may be running it as the top
Yeah but I don't know
Pecking order hierarchy
Qanon but I can definitely say very involved are in it and it has it actually smash
Kennedy Junior Style
Poor grammar
Yes weird
Predictions
That must suck to be believed in the qanon
You have to defer to the
Right
She can't just be like
I know this about cute because then people be like
I think you can kind of play games
Bad
Specific as long as you don't do it
Screwed over by aliens
Time
In our history
Diesel
Asian
I don't know if there's any history at all
Species. Then
Intermarried intermingle
And word you know
Interfere
Especially
Is there a murati
Species that go from planet
Planet and that is what they do
Justin Bieber
On the planet
And they
Omastar geneticist
Do they wrap their own genetics
Into
When they interfere the way they enter
Interfering influence
Through
Genetics
So no difference
Was Bill Gates and his whole genome program
Typical reptilian
To help
I would suggest
Siri racist
It's hard to say
Is a lot of places it's hard to say
If we imagine
The reptilians
To be this marauding
Horse Across the Universe
Easier to take over its resources
Is it Ben
Total waste of resources
Whatever they could possibly get from this planet
There can't be something that they couldn't find it somewhere else is it on Iraq War
It's just locked in an endless conflict
Nobody has
Meijer like that
That's just a misunderstanding of typical reptilian
Misunderstanding I don't know man I just think
Weather live
Thousands of years
Right I mean
How many have died in the process
Somewhere else
Do they have a memorial on their home planet
Even like
Wild animals
Sure will.
Many animals
If they get to a point where
Whatever they're trying to get
From attacking you
In some way things can do a basic cost benefit analysis
Operating
We're getting what they need takes more
Yeah and I don't know I don't know how
Is it there first
Give me the first. What is this their first goal
The bigger problem is
The easiest Target
And everywhere else is so much harder than us and they're just like
It's like the first black
Constantly
There's two low-level
Durham
It doesn't make sense
You are asking about
Typical
This is getting a little bit
This is my issue though and I don't know if you want to talk about this
They don't want
Okay
Can't help
Themself
Because they
And this is true of the majority of
Humanity that has
Stgnews
Shimla
No have a related Gmail even to the Mantis by the way
Even because
No Simon parkes was their Emissary to say that they're trying to change their ways and
Align themselves
Emissary from the
And they're saying the same thing that used to eat us
But then they decided
Future and sauce
Ourselves
Manatee
So now they're there
Branson are helping us behind the scenes
The reason I try to explain is that
There is a mixture of races
From all different
Sort of shades
And most of them have an agenda
They're not just here
No for our well-being in
Cuz you know they want
Jason light
Insurance
Not really
It's not really like that all that much
I don't I don't know
I don't know I don't know how much
Play the centrally from a different genome are lesser groups of people
And the ones that are 7 impact
Character
Like that
Your morality or your ability to control yourself
Evil
Stop yourself from being evil
Timmy is a real problem
Is an idea that I rejected
Yeah it seems like once we got DNA phrenology just got smarter
I just got more smarter
Technically complex I suppose
Keto acids instead of your
Because it's like
Look like lizards
Compositive alien DNA
And if you have that reptilian
Who has that reptilian
You give into that kind of territory
Dan White
Right you get you your start
How does a supply realistically
SMS in humans
Become problem pretty
Probably
So f*** you carry
Anyway
This next
Is talking about how she may have manifested
Says the name of the person
I don't even care no no no no
They didn't really
Person per se
In anyone
Particular individual
Call Rudy
Many many months
Stration
As we get closer
Selection
And I even put out
Lee I don't know if it had any effect but it seems to
There seems to be a manifestation
The weather
I was helpful in bringing out
All I know is that
Yo I did some block
Video blog
We need to see your win
We need some evidence of your win
It's not enough
We just talked about it we need to see some you know some
So I think what they've done
Certain individuals
The week
Now those individuals
Because he was
Intuitively
Number one
He's like a master neurologist
Mary Kate. And then I guess also interpreting the two material
They noticed him and they made overtures to him basically saying
We don't have a leak so how do you know this
As he says I'm I show
And so she became one
Repository
Information Valley
Yesterday or whatever
Listen to
Master numerologist Charlie freak
You got a master's in numerology
Charlie freak might be in the running
Numerology
Charlie freak
Picture of musically if i q i of electric Charlie
Is Charlie freak a player in the game how high is the freak
Freakaleak
Delete delete Pablo was in on it
He's in the mafia
No no
North Carolina
That doesn't sound like me
Damn this is not an issue for
Charlie freak
My mind is blown
That's why they
I think I believe you have now
I talk to myself oh my God
Yeah I do care
Charlie Charlie
Has another source named Charlie that
I don't think she
But
He is in direct communication with
Information
You want to know about financial
Now in this interview
Charlie Ward is saying
Cuz he has an inside track
That he's been told
It started in August
It's going to manifest
September 4th
Today
Supposedly today
Okay
Now I guess seeing is believing how it's going to manifest you know they're calling
Financial system
So do we have a quantum
Fluid
September
Haha
No manifestation no root no reset
Surprise appearance from Jeff session
Play makeup
And he becomes the vice
Interesting
Because I already knew that John F Kennedy Junior and I'd already
That
In my
So
And then since then of course there's so many other people
Anchovies and Jennifer Mack kind of
Lay's that out very nicely in a very
Brand new
To this idea
Why
Pescado is now Hemet
Carolina
Material
Bottom line
In end of July but for some reason
Timeline change
Extraneous
Circumstances
Actually
It didn't happen
And then Charlie freak. It would happen early August
Ecology at he was following that he's hot mic
Dodging
Lately the latest is now
October
Sometime during
That's my under
Is
JFK jr. is going to be the vice president
Was wrong about numerology
Call Jessica Alba.
PhD in neurology okay
First two letters
I think that would be my break
For all of life
I think it's suddenly JFK Junior
Reveals to Earth that he faked his death
And then just becomes vice president like he faked his death
To become
I think at that point
No
He declares that he faked his death
Immediately arrested
I really do
There's no point if this is real there's no point
About
Man
Play a mountain crash
1 Westcliff
Bioskop Terminator
This purpose show here
Conversation
Energy
Please turn off
Champs.com
CIA Church my principals
I listen to it
How did it go
I can't tell you
It was actually released on YouTube on her side of the stream I don't know why
Actually didn't listen.
Interested
Theoretically
What is the property they made themselves
They have respect
Guy who faked his own death
Just just the back
Just the best.
I'm glad you're back on YouTube
Because
It is
It's much funnier
Condescend
Cuz he killed
Trees
I don't know
Born
Through the boulevard
Hey there
About
I understand
You have
Work
Baseball
LOL
Baseball league
Sick or hurt
Community
SAU Jordan I think I read something about
More I'm like
We have
Twenty-four hours a day
Set up
Yeah yeah
At least I think so
Check it out
Or maybe.
Hello Dan
I always
AR
Tiny white
Thank you
Barrel run
Pavers
Thomas
Overwhelming
You are
So inspiring
My friends
Really
It's just
Challenging situation
You know you have been immunocompromised
Social issues
Situation has become so much more difficult
Goes out
So much
Now I can't imagine the the
Alteration of
Just like
Perceiving people as knowing now like
Getting too close to somebody as a threat you know like that's a whole different
View
Yeah
Just like
Shaking hands
F****** yeah
Yeah it's scary
Thank
Thank you so much for the message
Yeah
Please
Recognized
We gave tools to help you talk to people
Different ways
In those different ways
The Courage the wherewithal to interact with people
Make believe different things
God using whatever dumb information we can come up with
In a productive way
Dan and Jordan This is
Triangle
Pendejo
F****** cancel cancel
Our way through
From Perth to Melbourne
About how he loves
Chinese like
Yeah I get it but in Vietnam they're not like it's pronounced meatball sub
Bye
No I appreciate it
Australia
Enjoyable
Capguard
I hope
I've been playing
Horizon zero Dawn
Rex robot
Airblaster
On the show
Redfin
Stuff
Supernatural
So sorry
Torero's
Back
Hard enough to remove the backplate pateros
Electricity arrows to take out the
Raiders logo
The stuff you can use your fire arrows
To get rid of The Blaze
Canisters
Everyone tonight
Alright
At 100% tax guys rule for sure
I wanted to thank
Dannon done for
Shelter
Last night I was
Supermarket
Store brands
My heart
Is Jager re-evolved
And I noticed they had wanted the IHOP
Coffee
2 1/2 x 4 price
Terramycin
Sastre
Damn
You were right
The damn phone
Yet another victory for the year of
Man
Results
Yeah
Really
To Seltzer's more than helping
Wynne Arkansas
Wig
It was a watermelon mint
Watermelon mint Taylor
This is amazing
That is amazing
Jordan I do have to tell you
That
I've been putting off
Drinking party pics
I can't do it
So we're going to have to try it right now
Leopold's that bees these big Swig Seltzer's from Austin
Yeah you are
Key lime pie
Yeah
Reviews were mixed
A chicken
Except without the smell
If you like this that will blow my mind
I have to say
You know what it is it's understated
It's totally not that is
Terrible it's so loud and
Yes that is a pickle drink
I think I I think
How do they get that much pickle
The angel question
Man I just
Smell it
I have my own here
You don't even
I may be biased because I have I like pickles
I keep going back
I guess reviews are mixed up but you know what I can't
This might f*** around and be less than 250
3 * I don't think it's merely that low for me
It would be like spit out
Yeah it's definitely a reminder
As far as like
I thought it was going to be more aggressive than was cuz people who built it up.
Going to be a Slave
I would say
I could see how someone might enjoy that
New guy
Jordan
I hope so
But
Before that
Ukraine
I know what mountain is
Twitter is that knowledge
We are visiting McDonald's
Please find in your area to help out people
Alex
Person coloring