Alexandra Thurston color
We're couple dudes
And talk about the light
The good hobo Alex Jones
Hopefully
Swift return
Shephard's Resort
This is a non-alcoholic
Sparkling sangria
Dreading
Yeah this cannot be
Ur10
Your first step and we have
It's not good
Arizona surprise
Look terrible
Undrinkable
Okay
It's Pleasant is what I would say
Things that are Pleasant
Lucky
Stewart
Awful I think it's
Neutral
Nutrislice
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you for donating
Computer the show if you're listening cuz your first time I welcome
Davis
Absolutely we're going to get to our episode for today but before
I'm going to
Two are out of context.
So we're going to be going over today which is
Two things
Are indirect
Opposition
On the May 31st episode
Over today
Alex Jones is about to do an interview with Megyn Kelly
She's a pretty girl
He is cold her horrible names
Considerate
She said about her and parents mostly better.
Do ugly for a fox
Her friend said
He probably tells
So yeah Alex Jones has long thing for months
I'm not doing any more interviews unless their lives
Unless I have control over the edit
I'm at now you sitting down with Rodger Stone on this episode today and he's like
I know whatever they want but
I'm going to do it
Look National TV is not bad man
It is if you claim that your principles or against
Being all people shows for no reason
And if you argue that hey
They're dying media I reach 50 million people a week
Hey Annie press
Is hypocritical press
The meaning of that
May 31st
Yes that is the Wednesday
Here this week we're back in the present after we have been embarking on our investigation last couple episodes
Hope you guys have enjoyed that would
But now we're back in the present
If you recall
The end of last week on Thursday
Alex Jones drop
The Jerome corsi
His friend
Sorry sorry
You survived the weekend
And the reason for that
Is surprising
Some people is it on Thursday Alex
Found information
That was bigger than Watergate
I probably would get him killed
So
Must be just a
Bombshell
No plug is there a reason I didn't read about
What is bigger than Watergate
Play Scandal on Twitter
Alright Twitter
CNN
What is the
All right if this
Just us
Just you being my
Alright please just punch yourself
Tuesday comes around on Monday Memorial Day
Actually what they did do something I've never seen them do before
Alex put together like an 8-hour best of
No
Which
Yeah kind of gives me the strength
Best of what
I don't even I don't even I didn't watch it I just thought I'd existed
I wasn't going to watch that I don't know
Possibly it's
The same still that you tweeted out for 8 hours
Portland
Hexagon picture
Back to Rapaport
It never will
Tuesday comes around like
Holy Ship
About
The find out what corcino
Died over the show starts at 11
And whatever work I listen to it live
Because it's really funny
How Alex Jones comes in commercial singing
They cut that out of the rebroadcast
And I enjoy it
So I listen live
Hyundai TuneIn at 11
Jordan started
It streaming live
If the show is streaming but there is no show
There's nobody there it's just commercial
Nobody's even talk
It's just commercial
Special Report
And then every now and again the announcer voice
Become interview like
He's standing up for the
Your house
Alex Jones
Another commercial
Okay well he went 34 minutes
With nothing
What the f*** is going on
To the point where I was pretty sure I'll expect a Zonda
Great
King story that that was what
Find out later
Alex
Insinuating
On the Wednesday show
There on Tuesday he was in court
And he wants some big victory about his cut
There's no.
Because it was so good for him but no one wants to report it
34 minutes in Rodger Stone
I'd like a substitute teacher
You just played videos
Tire time
It's just like
Nice report
Let's go to it
So you're telling me
That Alex Jones apparently was in
Court
Apparently
No one knew about
Nothing
No
They were just all sitting at Rob do is sitting behind the ones into the hot pile
And court is not something that
Jumps out at you know about it ahead of time so why would I
Planet video of Jerome corsi's information on the nose
It's such b*******
It's wonderful it's so fake
Cuz it basically puts it takes him off the hook
He was even there right but that's part of the information he did show up
Course you did
ATI no new information
Seth rich
I have the other two Bombshells that Alex promised
It was nothing
It was absolutely nothing
Rodger Stone interview
Exam
The craziest thing in the world
For a good half-hour of the show
Which is mind you
Supposed to be the one that you're going to Michelle's
Rodger Stone interview
Derringer
Rock and roll
Do you know who that is
What he wrote the theme song now what
What
She wrote audiobook
Hulk Hogan around
He pays Derringer to follow behind it with a guitar that Rick Derringer is
Very bitter but it's Hulk Hogan
Theme song
Deserves
Fact
Most famous were pro wrestlers theme song
Very bitter
Very better
Here's why
Okay
Rick Derringer believe the Earth is flat or some s*** like that
I wish I would be more interested
Rick Derringer claims
That Barack Obama
A newspaper
This is the part 1
This is
His source
Yeah okay
An imaginary will remember when Barack Obama and Donald Trump had a meeting
Won the election is very Bittersweet for all
Rick Derringer says
Part of the meeting
Was Barack Obama's ass Donald Trump using the real American song
Because Barack Obama felt some sort of acclaim
Because he used it on a campaign before
I don't know if this happened
I don't care to look into
Also
All the presidents
Teddy
Why would it go that direction
I have no idea
Trump with dancing Obama about using that song
Years ago
Probably
Rick Derringer hears this news
It gets worse
Rick Dicker
Snooze
How do you like
I cannot let this stand
Barack Obama is so malleable
So he decides to do in his mouth
She's going to write a new version
A real American
Just for Trump
Time Trump meets with Barack Obama he can be like I got my own version
Derringer
Correct answer to that
Licensing fees
Yeah like they play the music video for his new version
And it starts with him and some other guy in a car
Talking about birth
So
You know that's where we're starting
So they play the song
Play Play the song
Rodger Stone to talk about greatest song it is
And I
I was freaking out
Felt like like
Is this an alternate
Really thought it might be like
Is this an episode from like
Six months ago they're just
Replaying
Like I can't be
The big bombshell episode
When people believe the big boot
Devastating
So
Rick Derringer starts talking about how he cried when he wrote that song
Wow this is great
Rick brought
A producer friend with him
Who directed of documentary
Alex Jones
Language
To dream in that language
So you brought a producer friend along
And this guy made a documentary about how if you really look at the Bible it predicted Trump
Yeah
Working after watch that documentary
Documentary
One the Bible predicted a lot of
And the ones that come in a lot of their
That mirror Trump's rise art
Knock their dark
They're very dark
So not to be outdone by these two
Very
Ghetto
Soft interview
Right
Rodger Stone goes on to
Interview Rick Derringer
Who is Olsen
And I have a clip from that
Rookie back
It's an interview
With Rick derringers wife
Rick derringers wife in her own right I'm not entirely sure what her deal is but anyway listen to this
In the studio
The real American
Very proud
What is so I told Rick and from them
He said it's too late then I came up with the idea of having Space Odyssey
Come in first before
The song and it did come in just ride and our drummer said yes that sounds really good this way and
It also exits with that
Songs that I find
Once you listen to it once
Kill me I keep thinking about it
It's got that kind of catchy
Rick to it
Rick derringers wife is claiming that she is the reason
Spake zarathustra
Is very 8280
Now it's
Exactly the right amount of 11
What time Uganda now
Keeping your boot
Oh
Second Amendment
From my feet so the Tuesday show was a completely bizarre
Who is Lucinda jenney
Yes
Because
What happened is
Last week
I forgot his name for a sec
Jerome corsi came on the show
He wanted a new man
In order to fight the fall
The quote false Russian mirror
But he called them as well
From their perspective
So the first propaganda game
But they played
What's this
Jerome corsi
Is going to get killed this weekend
Big news
Ben Alex isn't even in studio
They do this horseshit on the Tuesday show
Pretend
That they never said
The stuff that they said on Thursday
They just rely on people forgetting
They pretended Jerome corsi life wasn't
The Never
That's why you can't have Alex in there cuz if Alex talks
Jerome corsi
Eventually Alex
Because of course he has
I'm going to guess if that's the case
What everything I can tell the stories that we
Speculated were what he was talking about it appears that those are
What is
News world
Those are stories that are picking up on like
The
Right wing
Sikeston read itself
Did not
The 31st
I want to find
Well now
Prison in Concord
S*** but it's
Really not
We get to Wednesday 8
Alex
Decided
To ignore
Thursday
Ignore the entire course
Plotline that they were trying to go with
I'm starting entirely
As it were
Or Tuesday
And talk to Shay
Shut the bed
And then
Does he come back
He's not on this app
Not on Wednesday
No
On this episode on Wednesday we got Owen Shroyer sitting in for a little bit
We won't have to listen to him
Goodbye we got the big baby
Mike cernovich Plays very heavily into this episode
Decided
Did they have a new narrative going to go off on and they think it's
Like this
Lightning in a bottle
And it's worth
Ignoring the idea that Jerome corsi literally had information that would blow up
Gamewright that is like
He had a new storylines so amazing that it could get them all killed
No no
Otter bulshit
Jerome corsi the way they presented
He had the information that would be the culmination of Alex Jones
His 20-year career
This would be what blows the lid off the globalist they can't deny it
So we're going to have to kill Jerome corsi
They have ignored that in
Hireling
Holy
And it's not like he wasn't there
You could have said whatever he wanted
He had clearance on Tuesday to give out all the information
Course I'm going with him there
So here's what they do on Wednesday and it's a pivot
Hard pivot
Now
Siri
The globalist
No
The Godfather
Right
Nintendo switch
Exactly
Nothing's going to be beat that on Wednesday
Literally have the show starts
1984 is 1776
Alex Jones Show
American worldwide
I don't care I don't care
So
I can't begin to describe how hard I don't care about Kathy Griffin holding up
A severed Trump head
I don't give a
I could care less
I hope I don't care
I don't know why people are talking about
Who cares
No one care Griffith
What why am I seeing why am I seeing people if with liberals like on
All the site that's like
Liberals condemn this act
How about I don't care
No it's
From the people that I listen
And I respect
Who gives a f***
But not like
Kathy Griffin
She's Irrelevant in a shocking thing for attention
Obvious
Everyone
Who's ever been on that side
That's
Ridiculous
No one has been like
Yeah alright
Operator
Now you're a man
Exactly
Is operating with a couple of flawed premises
The first of the Kathy Griffin is super relevant
Which is not true
I love I love Kathy Griffin's career it's been amazing she's been able to get to this like level of Fame where
Enough people recognized early years ago she had a show called my life on the d-list
New Year's New Year's Eve with Ryan Seacrest
Not anymore
Step into the Joan Rivers roll
Something she
Here's the second flawed premise that Alex is operating under
Anyone is going to defend Kathy Griffin
But this is going to be
The biggest beetle in the world
Little does he know by the time he starts broadcasting
She had already been fire
Vietnam head already fired over New Year's Eve
Of course you can't do s*** like that
It's it's bad
For the brand
Yeah you're the reason that O'Reilly's
Another reason why I don't care about what
Undead yes it is
So anyway
Going a very interesting Journey with this this episode
And if it was just
Like I'm mad about Kathy Griffin
I would be like
Not do this at the
Yeah I wouldn't be into that
It would be very boring because I would just go on a lot of rain
Explaining how I don't care
But
It's important
Because
The weight
This is
The neck
Distraction mean
This is
Jerome corsi branded
Take attention away from Russia
They Sorry boss I blew it
I get it I'm bored and go hang out with crnkovich I guess I get it
So here is a Alex
Next
This is the problem
But the globalist
And the liberal
Also privately talked about about it
Friends and family
The whole Russia narrative the whole Trump
Push poles
Trump is going up in scientific poll
With everything there.
They have committed so many
Just absolutely
Massive distortions and lies
Massive
That they are now discredited
I've been committed so much illegal leak
So about the Russian stuff
Call me is going to testify next week
Yeah the reason why he
Said he couldn't testify in open court
Legal protect
Do you have to get clearance
2 in order
To say the things that he's going to say
From all sources that
Disgusted
He's going
To discuss the obstruction
You can't talk about the ongoing
Best vacation stop
His investigation
He got the green light
Just yesterday
From you
Okay keep the two
That's what's been holding it up
And that's why he was supposed to go into like June
Before he would be able to testify
So by next week is supposed to be in front of the house intelligence
You got the green light
I just don't trust anything
Yeah
It's stupid
To get excited about anything in
What will be will be
Then we'll see
But
The idea that Trump is surging in the polls is insane
Right now 4.8 disapproval rating all of the
Combined average
39.1 approval rating
4.8 disapproval
The only pull that he's going up in is the calls for him
Repeat
Say he's at like 43% now
Up from 38 last week
The 5% jump
In a week
People who want
Impeachment to begin
You should be gone
Yep
Yeah we still doing this
I don't know
Guys
Let's stop torturing ourselves
Pull up just come on get rid of them
You'll feel better if you have
So anyway
I think you'd be easy.
Lame duck president that's a new thing
We would be able to use it if Hillary Clinton was in office
Problem that Alex's
Describing the globalist Abba
Migraines all of the pillars of
The problem he's describing are not true
Is a solution
Because
Yeah
But here's
The solution
Griffin comes out
Kind of failed comedian
Feels like a store mannequin
And she comes out
Videographer
Image of the president with his head cut off
With blood pouring out
Across his face
Most you've already seen the image
The top story in the world since it came out yesterday because it's so iconic The Girl Next Door
Looks like an elementary school teacher
Had on President Trump
I go to sleep liquor
Elizabeth
Kathy Griffin picture
And that's going to be the solution for all of these the Russian narrative is falling apart
Trump is going up in the polls
What do you do
If you get a failed comedian
Career
She has had a
It's Against All Odds amazing career
My career for hers very quickly
Very much so
What is a quorum
Trumped
Trumps
Severed head
That's alright and then I would have a lot of people
Jerk off onto a skull and encrusted
Absolutely exact
And
He's going to develop his narrative throughout the course of the episode
Explain what
You mean
By Kathy Griffin beat the answer
Global
Problems
Yes
I can't
Kathy Griffin
Is the answer to the globalist problem
Globalist
Really bad at this
Barrett
It's probably cuz I don't
What
He's going to explain
Like his what he thinks is going on his analysis and all this
But along the way
He is doing
So much
Projection
Like
Whenever he talks about the mainstream media you kind of get the sense he's talking about him
Cuz last week
He was talking about how he was losing tons
Now marked all his product down
Even further than their Memorial Day sale
Extended the Memorial Day sales and chopped off like 10% from other things
And
You now saying I don't know if it's always been the case but never said it
If you get on auto-ship
Right you get your
His pills
Whatever price you get it at
You lock in that price
Know if you get like
Knockout now
Is like 60% off
Did you get it on auto-ship
You can sit
2% off price
As long as you get it
That he's taking a bath on the supplement
At this point
Is broke yeah
Holy crap
Was not that good
Also plays into what's going to end
Which is
Delightful
I love me some hobo Johnson
Talking about how much celebrities
As part of the establishment
Because they understand that all these attacks all these calls for violence on Trump
Backfiring on them in a big big way
High Praise for the
I have a video clip that I'm going to play here
Snoop Dogg
All two of them
It's all of the ones that he always goes
It's just
Video of Madonna saying
She thought about blowing up the White House
Write convenient that at the end
She says
But I don't but I wouldn't never do that
Just eclipse
Snoop Dogg with a gun
Atrophic Trump
If I don't I don't know if they even kept in the part where I put the bang flag out comic move
Now here's what I would do
If I were putting together the
This video
Video
I would underlay YG
Geez f*** Donald
Perfect family show
It'll be perfect
Projector
This is really is talk about himself
Initiative
Terroristic
Chaga
Rock bottom
Assault on Trump
Classics
Trying to reorganize and decide what new lies they need to push and put out
Wow that's that is
Eerily similar
He's doing really feels like
Cuz I mean what is he doing
Taking a respite taking a big Brethren talk about anything that matters
Firefighter
Dogpile on Kathy Griffin
Then no one cares
I love I love that
Bullying
So much
Yeah
Eristic bullying
Awful
People bully
Yeah
I hate it when people bully
You should believe those bullies
VH1
Is the show where people that get their bullies
Amanda MMA fighter with lights
You think you're tough
Beat up this kid
What about me
I'm in the Bollywood train
Okay
I want to
Reboot that show with Kathy Griffin is the host
Please get out your brother
The bullies hat
Alex Jones
Totally
Totally I'm sorry
I can't think of anything other than that now like I can't
Think of anything but the meeting
Where somebody was like
This
Is the best show we've ever thought up we wanted to be on
MTV and VH1 really lost it
For a couple years
My mom
Alright I'm onboard parental control that was a show
Parents got to
Amistad
Will you go on a date with a girl's mom and then if she liked you got to date the daughter
That's throwing anything out there
Everything else
Comic
Courvoisier
Decide
About
Financing stop killing Riot civil unrest
Resume
Personality
Expose the MSM
Now I know you have to do
Give us
All of your money
Of course you have to pay to be in the contest I know you love the animation contests and so what I heard
Contest
I was like
Specific in a little bit
It's the biggest shark
In the world
But
I have this Vision now of
The globalist
Is sitting around this giant like dr. Strangelove table
Just walking in there being
When should we have
The riot there's debate
Play Summer
Not too hot that's what I imagine it's like whenever the globalist
Stupid
To see the leaves change color
R-Truth that should organize
Yeah right
Understand
What do you think is going to lead the March
What you doing is 100% like in that cliff
Literally doing everything
A fascist propagandist would do
He's trying to invalidate the Press
He's trying to attack
Depressed
At the same time
He's a labeling
Legitimate protest as riots
That's
If you were an authoritarian leader there's a little more that you would want out of a mouth
It's almost like bullying
I can think of a few like
Lycra
Some examples of that exact
From
Turkey
Sure
I don't know
Soon-to-be
Soon-to-be us
Is pretty short but I think it's
Really telling
About what else
Think matters
And it's super f***** up
I don't I don't know how to set it up
Just listen to it
Chicago Tribune
Properties on the soft targets again value of them today
These people are at war with us
Why the f*** do I care what trumps
Houses are valued at
I don't give a s***
Read the article that he's talking about
I did mention
MSNBC
Counterterrorism expert
That Isis shoot bomb Trump filled
That was Malcolm
From there I watched everything that you put out
Watch the clipping
That
Obviously would want
To Target is building
He saying that the
If you had to predict
Those would be the first Target
Course they were
Idiot not to think that really
It doesn't seem like it would be hard for Isis to really get one in the in the Trump Tower
Because there's a lot of protection there and what have you but go to one of the other one
The perfect snakes blow up a golf
Two bag
Bob and I told you
Falling into a giant pit
Isis
Donate to the shelter
Aw that one back whenever what matters it
Steve's doors
Now you're not
Is Trump
Property
That is important to him and he thinks the people who
Would act against that
Are at war with
I know I don't understand
That's it.
Like that's really where he goes
The property value of
His houses of his property
Obviously
Their value
I think that
Alex
Alex's house is not worth as much as
Responsible
Possible there's no about it
Bella's house
We Are Young
Crazy high right now
Court on Tuesday
Yeah that's it
Anyway
Awesome
And then Alex
Consulta Mickey Rourke
And then
Alex Jones
Not understand Pro-Line
It's really at it
Really fascinating
What he thinks he's doing
Just let this play and then you can ask your
Look at this poor guy he looks like a Catwoman had some plastic surgery
It's big right after bombed out of the brain totally insane
Hollywood
Mickey Rourke
Like a clown
You look like
Really overweight rain
How do you know you guys look like
Club Paradise
With so like I know
I know
It's so bizarre
It's just like
I'm trolling the media
But what part of it is trolling
What is it that you're saying that word
Is that the part that strolling
Is it
Understand understand
There's a reason that word is a
Them
He means I think
I think he
Thinks that
When the MSM reports on
Unless they're going to take
Take that out of
And be like
Here's Alex Jones
Transgender
Buddy is
Exactly
He doesn't understand that by the very name
Nature of him
Throwing off those things
Using the investigation
Yeah I don't think you understand when people
Ask not to be called the n-word or the t-word
They're not doing it because they want you to be nice to them
They're doing it because those words have been used
People
Throughout
Time
Right
Insults
Towards people
It's not like it is
If something was used as a pejorative
Stop bullying me
Bracebridge Second Amendment
Second Amendment
So
A free speech right
More importantly
Hell yeah McKee Road
Can suck my f****** dick you are goddamn right
Are you going to do
So it is next clip
Because does not see
Exactly the same
Jones love
So much
Like
Exactly that
Yeah
Suddenly being like
Let me tell you something
Because you're in
That's why I like
F*** you you should be
If you're out Jones just be like you know what
I disagree with you
What are you talking about
The wording
Every part of that
Exactly what Alex Jones I think you Adam Schiff I think that Alex Jones was drunker and less
Creative than exhausted
I don't know I have no idea
Big ants
How could he not how could he not at least respect
Has a vested interest in not
You know yes
Right but they
We can Punk move I know but
Jones is a b****
We're coming
I don't like using
We're coming to the
From a rational perspective
That's a problem
Cuz he lives in a rational world
But he has to hold up
You going to hold up that line
Are we going
There's a lot of things that we could give up on
I we don't have to defend
Like we're liberal-minded people but we don't give a f*** about Kathy Griffin
Flexible about thing
Cuz we're not hearing
And you can
That I
Is the people on the right
Arby's
That whole thing
Then you have people who are like
What are you f******
King talking about they net
Big dude
A burden pictures of people
Burning Obama has done
Either way
You're just sitting there
One of those
Is
Intentional
Yeah
The Griffin does not actually want to
A lot of
It was not a symbolic was making an artistic statement but at the same time it was aggressive and vile
And like
I'm not going to let her off the hook
If you're just trying to save it like
One person
Hanging
Obama
Is equivalent or is is worse
Because it's racially-charged
Intention
Maybe
I don't know if that's fair though I don't I don't
Think it's fair to say that those people who
Expressed themselves
Through lynching a fake Obama I don't know what they want
I did express yourself through lynching a fake Obama
He said he's well with whatever whatever you're following argument is going to be
I'm just going to go right back to the express
Themselves
I'm not thrilled with that came out of my now the argument of making is I don't think that they would necessarily hang
In the same way that I obviously
Kathy Griffin wouldn't
Behead Donald Trump
Like I think that there is
Would you just for a joke
Never going to get everybody's wrong
I don't either
But I wish Alex hadn't brought it up
So I could continue to live in my world where I don't
Just ignore it
But you know you can't ignore
Alex Jones
Has a nuke on
Now we're going to get to it
It is also
Infowars.com Mike cernovich
Historic
How do you not already know what info
Idea
What is Kathy
Griffin story
He said you know how you did your Bill Clinton's a rapist
Contacts
And out
You have a rally
They tried to change the subject
Bill Clinton at chateau
And Wild
All the child
Also when I'm nuts
Others work to get
Bill Clinton
And I work will you the listeners
I promise we're about
To get to the actual account
This is just
Himself off by what
He's talking about how he
He's got the most successful
No action disorder
And I agree
So I
We're about to get to the x
And to make it more fun everybody that
Get the shirt for more than 5 seconds or so
You get $1,000 if you do it
Are a bunch of terroristic bullies
I don't care
Do the ball drops
All the company
And defendants were going to sell it t-shirt
You also get $1,000
If you're wearing the T-shirt
Your local news
2500 until it hits $200,000
Mossad is
It's not a conic it's already
Snooze
Different story
The morning of
This broadcast
G2000
Have more gigs with Sienna and she really was just there ball drop with Ryan Seacrest lady
Maybe fell through a little how to say probably a few of them are actually in the South I assume you got to take a little break maybe go to
Vegas for a bit
Workout
Yeah
Like the thing is
Alex think like we're good we talked about
Nothing but Kathy Griffin
6 months
I mean the rest of his phone
He's making everybody knows that
It's based on like Shepard Fairey
Style
With her holding a severed Trump head
And it says terrorists
3 mm
CNN terrorist
Onnit
Backfires
So fast she's already fired and the shirts are a week away
Emoji bats
Why do you want to put that image out
I don't know
That's
Yeah we want to remind everybody about how
Pretty much everybody feels most
Because they think
This is the jump the shark moment
For Trump
When it's not
It's not at all
Something off
On some weird Side Road that most people aren't going to
It's somewhere over there we're all ignoring it
Moving forward to the actual investigations the facts of my life
She is going to take a
F****** hudalla on this
I don't I don't remember all the clips that I have put
He says that he ordered 10 varieties is they all have to do with the Kathy Griffin picture
Call man
Broadcast pretty-much
60% of the time
That picture was on the big screen behind him at the news desk
It's like
Take a bath on
He thinks this is going to save him as the new meme
But it's not it's not going to work
It's terrible
He's not going to do well
But the flip side of it is he has enough rabid fans
Want those shirts
I don't think he'll even sell that many of those
I think
It'll be okay
I don't think you'll hit $200,000 give him out
Bye
Yeah
The bigger issue
Is that this is
Trying to get
Pictures of bats
Right
Opportunity
Monopoly McDonald's
That's what it is
Yep
Levi t-shirts so you might win
How many people have access to getting on
The news necessarily of the people who are going to buy these shirts
You get on the local news and asked to go viral for it to pay off
And
In order for it to pay off
You have to say infowars.com
While you're on the thing
Oh really there even more catches
Yeah
You seen on TV
With one of those shirts or assign
It says that
You get $2,500
If you have one of those on TV
And you say infowars.com
Repeat
Bumfights
Open chat
So
It's all it's all clear in this neck
But
And I got to buy
The shirts are being produced
Contest
Operation
Real Alex Jones
You can make your own any of the login password
Make your own t-shirt
What you doing
However you do it just get it on the news that CNN is a terrorist organization
There's two pieces to that the first
The shirts will be here in a week but don't worry
Buy them now
And then he said make your own shirt
Do your own s***
Because he knows that even if people do their own stuff it's still advertise
It's still absolute free advertise
So
Like that is trolling
That's what that is trying to get on CNN's putting that but I also know
Anybody who's watching
To be like I forgot we'll check out
It's it's trolling
To the news to stomachs
Put on a greater excited strolling his audio
Right
If you buy these shirts
Play into this you're the rude
You're the one who's beautimarq
If you listen to Infowars you're already
You're already past that point
You might as well go Whole Hog
So in this next clip Alex admits that what Kathy Griffin did was totally legal
It was of course it was
But then he gets to be failed predict
Kathy Griffin should be ashamed
Noxious
Putting the idea of violence and this whole atmosphere of the riots
Ukraine
The pub
It's just people are so
I said they hiring
What is our next tactic going to be false flag
If you guys
Oh yeah they would make themselves a f****** victim
Some kind of right-wing terrorist you f****** murdering people yeah they would make the
There's already enough right
Murder ink
The most dangerous
F****** people
In this country right now
Are old white
F****** X2
Well that situation to you if you think that
You guys are doing more than
F****** enough
Well the further thing that I agree with you but also if you're listening to our investigation back into
The 2015
You'll recognize some of this language
Because Alex Jones
In 2015 about how it was going to
To be the summer of Rage
Yeah that never came to be
He always does
He always predict
Basically almost every summer
That's it's going to
Jump office hours
The summer of 69
And he's always known some
First real six string
Guitar
But you know what
What your knife for good news
What's a good
Alex Jones a smart man
He's figured everything out
He's figured out exactly what the globalist threw up to
And he's going to lay out his plan
I'm pretty sure he's figured out what the globalist
Have been up
Two for 20 years and none of it has come true. All of this but it doesn't
Okay you're waving it away
Fair enough
Vic news in the past let it die let it
Be buried the past
Alright you can't live in pasty white 2K
Come on man
Okay
You come up with things like this also I believe that this
Is pretty strong evidence that Alex Jones
Episode
This is such an exciting
Because I've been waiting for other contact
I've been saying any contest for free speech legal in Laughlin
Bill Clinton Joker
Obama Joker stuff we've done
But I've been waiting for the right moment
Can be destroyed by that they've gone too far people are fed up she did this right at the right moment
About to reject
The numbers show that
Where they've now or throwing her overboard
Preparing riots the summer they want to reply
Start the crying
A month out from before they trigger
We're almost exactly a month out from the July 3rd riots
Stop.
False flags on Patriot
Yeah what you think about that
He figured it out
I mean
Justin
Let's just
No I'm not I'm saying
The mainstream media
For Alex Jones
Has developed a very poor plan
Alex Jones
And that's what he think
I'll give you the reality
There's a bunch of people who were very pissed off about the way the Trump is
Comporting himself
I'm so they planned marches
To peacefully organize a protest
Isaias the right of
Citizens
Secondarily
Is a nut job
Picture that was
On the right or the left
Class
I'm not into that
No thank you no thank you
The collective response
What's the Kathy Griffin
Nothing
Promptly certainly more promptly then Fox News has ever fired anybody
Fake news
So it's all resolved already
A result
There's nothing left
But Alex thinks
It's going to be the big
Let's have our own
Okay
If you find somebody wearing one of those shirt
And you email us a pic
Give me hog
We will give you an honorary policy
If you see one of those f****** shirts in the wild
I've only ever seen one Infowars shirt in Pueblo
Yeah ever
Marty
Do a show in the middle of Indy party dress
Yeah I had a show in the middle of Indiana
Umaga
I like we are in the middle of Indiana
Bruiser still one guy
Right
Akbar one dude
I want to see
It was like a unicorn I want to know I want to know how many of those shirts
I want an exact
I can't imagine
It's not many I mean the only cost five bucks
He sells a hundred of those at
It's free shipping in the month
Please try to give a s*** away
He's having trouble
Sincerely believe that all of this is just indication
The chit is falling
Park
Of course that also would explain his manic episode
Also I don't think he was in court on Tuesday I think it was probably having
In a bender
But
Jerome corsi news didn't
No password
I was jumped at.
Anyway
At this point in the episode Mike cernovich
It's in the mix
He says some of the dumbest
He is
About this
This contest
He's super into it
Because it was his idea
Which is a which is a fantastic little trick of like
I have this idea but it's really your idea so you know it's a
Good idea
Is the Golden Boy
It doesn't work
It's going to be home
What I think is
The funniest is that this is how cernovich starts
Eight tries to
Maybe be a little bit grandiose about the purpose of this contest
And it's pretty funny
Ways to help
But also
If you want to get into the media game
I remember I remember Ted Koppel
Such a n
And was
Edward armero had a con
You remember that
These face on it
Mediterra
Despair
I apologize
I got that mixed up with
Prince sir
That is
The craziest thing I've ever heard the contest
To help Young Guns who want to get into the media game
Yeah you're
You know that most things don't work like Rebel media
You know most things don't work like Lauren Southern
40 G
Tired
It wasn't great but you got moxie
You're very cute women Uranus
It's like they think it's
Team Ford
New York whatever like
And
A doctor Roebuck Billy Bathgate where everybody
Little kids wandering down the cobblestone streets like
Hey Richard
You work for the
You're a maid a boy
It's also it also has the smell of like
It would be the equivalent of getting a job
Howard Stern radio
By going on someone else's show and yelling Baba Booey
You know
All you're doing is disrupting people and giving Alex Free Press
You are not doing anything for your own brand
You're not helping yourself at all but because they know that people are
Stupid listen to their stuff
Your foot in the door
Is there a real
I think if you're charismatic enough
When you're on Are You The UPS Store
You're right you are part
Like like that f****** nuts
That's really good stuff
Yeah
I mean it's just not
But it's even worse
The next group is even worse
Listen to this
Cars
Build a civilization
People
There's
This is how you do it there's so delusional delusional basic doing a contest where you can win at the
Thousand dollars to troll
That's creating prosperity
Is it is a stimulus package
Yeah
As much as
Sure
I think of randomly maybe putting out
Roughly 50 Grand at
Most is really going to jump start
Think of all the things
You could buy with $1,000
Not that much
You could buy a
Medium-level TV
Maybe yes sir
Least
At least
10000 Big Mac
1 2/3 months rent
Amarillo
Salat if you're a child
Like a fifteen-year-old if your fifteen-year-old do you want to go out there and put on one of those shirts
Which I think is irresponsible to go out there and put on one of those
You need to have a
Conversation
Alex Jones better give someone $5,000 to put it on a onesie
That would be amazing
F****** lunatic is it to be like
This is creating prosperity
To me this doesn't sound like their usual lying like
I think they're cool on deluge
This day or really believing
This b**** your episodes
I got this great idea
This was going to bring us out of that f****** hole that we've been in
I haven't slept for 3
You just listen to one bucket
Maybe we wouldn't be in this situation huh
Maybe it's we're losing a lot of it.
It t-shirts already
Who killed even bigger story
Would be an even bigger story than corsi's bombshell information
Dead course
If there was a corpse e
Delusions of grandeur
But like
I think that Alex is having a manic episode and I think crnkovich my
I don't know
Easter bread
3/3 mm inches
Daughter
Eating Easter brunch with
Lonely
Childless Ally
Alex Jones
Oh do they have
They have a new baby
Gross
Poor bastard that babies going to be wearing a dick head that baby is due
Doing great
Thrilled for that baby
But yeah you're right
Going to wind up next
Do the Super Bowl loser
Their t-shirts
There's no way that like
Entirely
Elizabeth thought I was trying to get you is that this isn't the normal line
But it's still the normal desperation absolutely this is a desperate man
Trying to come up with a PR stunt
Because everything is going down the tubes
You need attention
Because also he's not selling s***
That's why everything has all the prices cut
That's why he needs to move product
It is bullshiting everybody
Like he's saying that he's building a new studio like a million-dollar Studio
You're not
There's no way you're doing that
You shouldn't be building a million-dollar Studio
Andrew the $200,000 contest
It's not a $200,000
Is a contest with a limit of $200,000
But all this is bulshit
Huge distraction
Crushing it
Or
He would be the least lucky man is like it would be
200 people
The only 200 people who bought shirts
Who all somehow
See now that's how you jump-start the
Over and over again
Now they got a limit one per person
I don't know about that let me look on the website
Let me see I know they absolutely do not
Absolutely.
Sweet
Then we are buying one of those shirts I am not
Just listen Good Morning America wall that you can all like
Oh yeah
I am punching a lot of people out and scream it in Fort Worth
Again
This is
We want award as many prizes as possible
Even if you don't quite make it on TV
Post your pictures to Twitter and social media
Take your pictures
@real Alex Jones
Is Isis
It's just being an Isis
Isis's
So ridiculously really got to get a better social
Listen to us
Send this next clip
Mike cernovich
Explain what this is
About
It's not about something else
Getting back in their face
Break mix
Property
We want to try and get people to do this for us cuz we're not going to do it
People to do this
Yeah
Also too late
She's already she's already fired
CNN
Come out
And
Denounce terrorism
They do
I think they support
Isis
Love's
Pale redhead
Totally
And then of course
Why won't scan and come out and renounce terrorism
They fired
They fired her
Yeah
I was just like come on Kathy
Yeah come on
Well that's the problem they didn't
Should be in jail
Brilliant
I mean dogs
This is a terrible at
Is this is this the same as corsi pitching about how he's going to die last week
No no cuz this I think people might actually do that one was
Just straight b*******
Alex
They really should have
Because then the next week you don't have to reveal the information that's Bumpass
Navigate to the bottom what the information was the course he died for
You could do months of that
You still in there to cover it up
No just don't take over for like a month
While you're on assignment to figure out
What'd corsentino
You could do you could stay home drunk
And just do reports from the road like
I got to leave I talk to this legislator
Infowars.com hunting Bigfoot
Really f***** up
Like there was of unfortunately
You could have just made it look like a heart attack
He's already old
Walking Dead as well just push cliff
Ready to hear certain which is dumb idea
Will do a million dollars
Exactly
510 shirts
Walking billboard
Play right now
There's not a chance people
Play the homeless intrendys love violin
Well
If not like they
Bright like
8-day absolutely hate violin
They hate
Giant gun
Silicone tape
They're making making cotton murdered by this picture
Hate
You got to buy one
It's a collector's series forever I do
Those frosted glass
Suggest rethinking
Be homeless billboard strategy
A couple reasons
That's one thing another thing is it's really insulting
To think of the homeless at thing
Using
Walking billboards
So that's better
What sort of problematic
Beyond that
I don't Clear Channel actually owns all the homeowner
Channel locks donate to page to Jack FM
You've never gone up to a homeless person and seeing their shirt and been like
I got to check this out
8 Buzz Marketing
It's at its underground the more touches the Moors in the public
That's so dumb
The dumbest idea
I love his excitement when he's like
I just thought of actually
Terrible
Also
Please do that
Homeless people shirts
Everybody could use more clothes out on the street stuff out there
I know plenty of homeless people who would still deny those
Inside out
Baby
Yeah you are not a smart business
Cernovich breaks down some big news that he's gotten
There's about the murders in Portland
On the train
It's about the big news out about this
And I'll just let him break it for you
Was trying to
12 year old punk
Arrested Development
Guess what you're going to prison
Bellflower
So Mike cernovich a lot of his sources end up being like doctored photos that he finds on 4chan
Right whenever he has something like this
Set my public service
It is true
Support Bernie Sanders
Initially but I don't think that has anything to do with that anything in let's not belabor it
Discussing
Do you like Bernie irrelevant I don't care
He's a monster horrible bigot
Is bigotry and bigot
I love I love that he's like
I love that yet
Schedule Daddy
It was definitely isn't because he
Ifucking murdered two people
The pile of garbage
I know that Alex thinks you being severe with his language but he's like
Now you're going to prison for twenty years dumbass
It's almost like he's critiquing
You didn't do that right
Weird mentally ill person
It's and it's not even any recognition of the tragic nature of what happened
You can't even connect with that
He's talking about
The people that were killed
A veteran
And
What was the other twenty-three-year-old
The guy who just graduated from college
Do not f****** pronounce though I've tried
He murdered those two
Two people
Because they were
Defending must
Will not
Like the only
The only thing that he wants
To do there
Get into this
This whole thing about how
There
That's what he wants
Stupid also liberal false flag
Yeah but he wants
Discover cuz what he really wants to do
Is pulled the same
It's at that like
Polite
People sign say
You're all on it we're all insane
Right
He wants it to be
He wanted to
Subway
You can't allow that white p
Would actually defend these
The people that he's so afraid of
Muslim women are on the way out
I'm out and you don't understand people would defend them
Gyros
He doesn't understand how his rhetoric in his beliefs that he espoused
But I feel is really laggy
I don't feel like I've seen
Fair enough
The coverage that I've heard
Was something I was struck by
At the realization that these
These two poor girls
Are going to have to live the rest of their lives
They know that people died for them
They shouldn't feel bad about
It's not their fault
Or anything like that
But it's impossible as a human not to feel
At least somehow it's going to take a lot of therapy to be okay with the situation that happened
I already
Had the thought
The thoughts
Why wasn't
Just that that survivor's guilt
It should have been
Especially in the like
You know the youth
It's processing
Promotions
Be very difficult
No matter what
There's there's nothing really
Nothing good
No good feelings except for about that guy who survived
There's a pretty nice feelings about that
Cuz at least
One person
Start to finish
I will say I don't like this
The guy who survived
Slam Poet
I can say that that's one thing
All the horrible things that I have said that is the worst thing that's been said on this phone
I'm being facetious.
Slam poetry and I fell in
Insensitive
Mike cernovich leave the show
He is done
His shift
Any of the last clips that I have here
I'm stuff
Here is how he comes back from break
Boy
It's a lot of
Loteria Nacional
Points against
Boulder still Rising
Most dumbest
Stat on trendy's arm
Worship
She's legitimately calling Terrace losers
Because that makes people did not do do it you call him dangerous and powerful word
Aldi's
All the same
BFDI has profiles
Hidalgo blow-up little
Call Amor
I don't know kill everybody's f***
Looking family
Drone strikes out of
F****** Noah
Why would you become a terrorist
Because you're a loser fighting back against something
Evil empire that murdered everyone you know isn't it so Alex Jones
To think like the answer to terrorism
Bullying
You're afraid for the women don't want to have sex
With you is killing people so caught up in his masculine narrative so caught up in his
Trappings he doesn't
You can't be anything else
All he can see things through his
The prism of white victimhood
And masculine fears
With all he's got
Everything goes through that prism
And it's so sad
It's so sad that that is
That is a deeply ingrained piece of him we speed in 2015 we see it now
Yeah
Attic
It's a little like
If you've ever
You have
The dog park
Cat guy
Very very defensive about it
I like at many high-profile men
Like cats
Go ahead
I know you like dogs don't have fun
What is it what is it like
Like to see the world through
Zeiss
You know like
They can't
Color blind or whatever
Just their vision
Is different from
How is it that day
Yeah
Of course
But I don't know why I chose.
It's okay
Attitude
Know that like
It must
It must be
Weird
Fascinating
To try and
Steve the world
True Alex Jones
Because
It's it's so
And it's so divorced from reality you halfway expect
Like if you saw through his eyes for one second you halfway expect
Toosii
There are two suns in the sky and one of them is purple
To be this weird
Funhaus
Mirror's Edge
Situation you almost wonder if he has a tumor or something like
Like that
It's not though it's just cultural cultural conditioning
Such like
I mean we've solved the mystery about his psyche
The minute we found that clip about his mom
That is
Where's a lot of this comes from not a racial stuff I'm not entirely sure
Maybe there's some parental situation
Is that wound up
I've been using the n-word
I don't know I don't want to put that on his parents I don't know that for sure
Maybe an uncle
Uzbek klip
Jordan
Bookmarks clip Alex
You want to tell me what's really
You know what
You don't have it I really threw me off with
The cat say
Turn myself off I misspoke
Cernovich is still around
He was held over when Rodger Stone shows up
And the three of them are are there
There's brownout
This the next clip is Mike cernovich
Certifix
Explaining
What are the Kathy Griffin picture
It was all about
Cuz I don't I don't
Transparent
And obviously I don't think that you like really are able
The Dakota
Wasn't that difficult
Well I don't know if you came to this conclusion
There's a big
Apogee
Did you come up with that analysis
Get that one
That one
You're right
Damn right I was I thought it was a very simple and direct message and apparently
It was a secret communicate
Expressing love for Islip
Cuz you had too much fluoride
Deep Earth iodine
So this is more about the
Action with ISIS
It's unfortunate he doesn't know that has already fired her while they're recording the
Wichita
You're totally right
Of course but again
They've already fired
But they
It took them
A few hours
I did not few hours
They signaled
For sure
For sure turn off those beacons
Before now it's
Almost
So I'm an expert we got way more projector
Lotaburger
But you might as well
I work at a movie theater
Because
They know Prosperity is out competing their authoritarian model
Energetic
Feel it being lifted bad but now it's what to do
Our forces that are makes more money
American System
It's so much better
So the sexiest of America
And the return
Everything I realized incredible
How to fight that in the first place
Well they're word like things
Came out about Mike
Modern Art
And stuff like that there were CIA operations that had to do with like trying to
Injec
Random
Weird things to see if they can get them to be popular
Do not know about that
I don't know enough to speak about it but I read an article about it a while back there
There is
There is that but the
Rosebud variance
They were still trying to figure out what they were doing
Extrapolate that we're going on
You out so trying to sell ugly things
Deep Earth iodine is that at the beginning of a clip
He's talked about how I
I have felt their will
And it's
Yeah exactly
You
Wait for him to experience his feelings like
Through the prism of somebody else
Speedball negative feelings must be ascribed to the global
Figure that one out
I don't actually know if that's true I was just listen to
A bunch of
Episode
No that's it that's a really fascinating thing I don't know if that's accurate
But it would be it would be interesting to go back in
Seattle on my investigation
Keep note
Yeah but like
Whenever there are negative things it must be something
Globalist
As opposed to
Part of the randomness of life
The consequence consequence of some good thing
Write classic
Symptom of MRSA
Personality
Or just illusion
I can imagine
Really did he is
All of these signs
What is manic depressive
Even still have manic episodes
And it could be caused by
Long Bender
Followed by some cocaine
I will snort the super male vitality
Or Superman vitality
Play
Coke with super
Female vitality
It's a liquid
We'll see that's
What you doing
Take a couple of take a couple bumps of Coke
Super male Vitality up there
And you get none of the negative effects
Mexico
Sometimes
Superman
Rob Dyrdek's wife can agree
Cocaine and then the email is the numbers
Pitman arm
Declassified
We've come to our last clip here and it is towards the end of the show accidentally finds out
The Kathy Griffin has already been filed
You about that in your back pocket the whole time well it's the end of what's interesting about the show
So
I mean
I knew if you knew
Can we bring Alex to figure this out cuz
His whole thing is is f*****
His whole point
Flick no
There's no point now he's going to have to really try and aggressive
Sibley post to story
To get
Deals with the news
In-stride
Okay also
Joan
Iran our New Year's Eve program out she'll be back
If we blow up Trump Tower
Isis
Humble
Make a shirt
We need funding
Million-dollar contest
I mean like
A boy
Sade
The last hour and a half two hours I've been screaming about how we're going to ruin her
Are there any
To like what about this guy on NBC or MSNBC
Is Malcolm Nance
That's not what he saying
So they better
He better so I can you cancel this contest
I think we all should get shirt
The cleaners
What about
Does that count
That would be great
Pictures of Dan we're going to perform at the Laugh Factory again
So smoothly into an ad
It's not even an ad so much as it is like we need money
It does like selling products and what have you been
Clearly is leading with
Give us money it's less about you need the product
Morwenna sucked money
We need money through this whole thing
He saw this Kathy Griffin you misread it real hard
I thought it was going to be the biggest scandal in the world
F****** episode talk to crnkovich about it they came up with this
Amazing plan
I8
A0
God
Man I hope he loses
He's a freelancer freelancer
His ability to shop on
Yeah
Cuz he does do the 4th h a
Oh yeah
Since our last episode from Rebel media
Probably because of the macron league
Because he followed by his report.
He's too truthful I also it's come to my attention that Lauren Southern is gone
We discussed.
Not sure if she's up to but still probably
The rabble-rousing
Yeah also what was the other one I could do
Extended Hiatus from
Does baby
No
Okay
How dare you
You're just mad at the idea
Average
I'm not that guy I'm not that guy
But I do believe that you single
Okay
We wouldn't get along
I would say that my hypothetical relationship with Leon McAdoo would go better
Then this Kathy Griffin
I'm pretty certain of that
Awesome
Good luck Alex I don't think
That you're going to be able to distract people from the Russia investigation
Isaac
Distracting your listeners from the fact that you did not pay off the course
I don't think that anyone is
Anymore
Cuz no one else is listening critically
I went to their subreddit I went to the
Infowars subreddits and people weren't talking about it
Not at all
Is there followers
New cycle is so fast now who knows who might be dead
Could be anybody
Yesterday its course
Tomorrow is Alex Jones
The day after that Alex Jones kills Kursi
Anything Could Happen
The thing I was of course he dies now there's no game
Yeah I know
Cuz it's already expiration date
You know a bunch of nonsense
Yeah
Like
I don't know what to do
Do
This is so stupid
Like not the show
The last couple days on Infowars
Has been like
What is you doing
B like Rick Derringer interviews and s*** like that
He was kind of hard but at the same time
You're supposed
To be a hard-hitting
I meant today with this
Like I don't know
Like we we've cut into your regular MSN be brought MSNBC broadcast to bring you
HR puffin
You know like it's
That
Absurd
This f******
Weird Telethon move the T-shirt contest
This isn't like
I want him
Same thing
Disprove
We disprove this shirt is a good idea
We've certainly indicated the likelihood that is
Undisprovable
CNN is Isis is not even a claim that's worth disproving cuz they're not
Pretty simple
Let me ask you a question how much research
Did you have to do
Before you came to the
Conclusion
None
I think that's why you're really unhappy you don't have
You're just like god dammit I want to research the dumb s*** you say well it's fun for me when I can come to the episodes and be like
You're busted
That is not why the NRA started things are really fun
Dumbass
I don't have to tiptoe
6 of a cup that giving t-shirts to the homeless as walking Billboards is a bad business strategy I just assumed that it is
Because I wouldn't buy anything it's advertised on a human
I don't I don't does not like
Well here's here's what
I'm a little bit
Is the more this goes on
The less we are
Combating right way
Wing propaganda
And the more we're laughing at
Mentally ill person
Yeah that is true
I mean he'll be back off this manic episode
Certainly before too long
Usually
Couple weeks boy
Yeah boy
So who knows for the next couple weeks
Sick of it says we might be doing
I want to save this
If you go to knowledge fight.com
On the homepage there are now Three Links
On the actual page
Direct link
Do the by autobiographical pieces Welch
The LIE files
The new calendar
Break
Episodes
Please go check those out
It's it's
It's interesting
I think
Comprehensive
Like me
Yeah it's interesting
But yet
The girl that falls
Twitter
Underscore
We're on iTunes
Knowledge fight
Please leave us a review
Gmail.com
No
So he's a lot like a certain
Friendly no
Let someone go in a while
I wonder where he's hungry
Royal tomorrow is Thursday might have a shift
Rosa Parks
Thanks for holding
Alexandra first in color with huge fan I love your work