Air Jordan
That great respect with knowledge like
Everybody I talked to Ben work
If you just
Yeah quite know where to put your mouth
He's got
He brings to the marketplace
It is interesting it's a niche
It is a niche
Master bullhorn
You know
Hey everybody got to go out
Abdullah
Jordan
?
I'm just loud
Andy
Related Brightspot
Number of various stages of progress
Brock are not broccoli cucumbers
In particular
I'm really really like and right now that I'm feeling just so great about
Is the fact that I finally got some quinoa to grow
I had killed
At least three rounds of trying to grow seedlings
This time
Plants that are pretty well established
Up there
You got to make everything about you all the time
Shurfine
Maybe the seeds were not work out or something
Keep doing it over and over again
Progress
I had the opportunity
To tell my partner about
Saint crispin's day
Never heard
She didn't know anything about it so I was trying to get her inspired to go to work
And make it through the day
The saint crispin's day speech is the only speech
That will make you run through a f****** brick wall even though you don't understand a word of what
Is incredible it is the original f******
Clear Eyes Full Hearts can't lose
In drama
Play I played her the signal Laurence Olivier B
And she lost her mind she's like I don't even like this but I want to run through a brick wall
Hard Times promo
If it weren't for the saint crispin's day speech tan
Time travel
Randy Cramer
It'll give me a chance to talk about my favorite conspiracy theory mature been we've been asked before like
Are there any conspiracy theories you believe or what's your favorite
Conspiracy theory
And I've always left
This one out because I forgot about it but
My favorite
Conspiracy theory is the Shakespeare is a woman
Conspiracy theater everybody knows
100 that trailer with him
But that's my favorite one to entertain them like
How many people have to
He was writing like that and they couldn't
Amazing
The theory that Shakespeare was a bunch of different people
Are you sure actually Shakespeare
It wasn't it wasn't what's his
Francis Bacon
Shakespeare was not a spy what's your love
He wasn't
Conspiracy
Is it right now
Difficult storical Shakespeare was a much more open question but
I will grant
Never looked into it in the history of olives
Literature and you think people would just let that be an open question
Probably true
We were little bit of
We forgot to mention
And thank God
We were on there
There are there podcast
As always
Just that I just rambled about that early various
Self-conscious because I am who I am
C3 podcast
I have notes on now
Promoted promoted
About our own Joe
I'm the worst
Talking about the period of September 9th
Sort of plan to do a little bit more longer
The beginning of the week
Everything is
We both put our fingers
Is too much as possible
And see how Alex is dealing with the the fires on the West Coast
How can I learn about
Trump
Tapes
Got the PJs
The first
Very much Mel
Terraria
Thank you Cheryl
Some guy or one word
I apologize
Heroin
It says Sports show or
Indeed your relative
I think about who is involved
The characters necessary
Take all of that
Creative Energy turn it into generosity
To the world or more specifically a local bear fund or charity
This is what happens when record marathon
Here on the 9th
Talking about like red state-blue state issues
What you mean
When he says Red State
And what do you mean
In Blue City
The red and blue
Yes
Human blue blood is blue
Is a blue state
Arrow are there smaller
Brialee breakdown
State-by-state ordination by Nation
Yeah it's it's
He's just
I would like him to have
Video from the Animaniacs where he's singing the the country song I would like
It's right next to that juxtaposed with just
Red blue
Everyone hates humans
Covid-19
Secretly about taking over the world
This is
Pneumonia
Smog check
Exist
What's your impression of it
That condescending suck
Tone
Hate that so much
Yeah it's at
Yeah that's very annoying deserve
Idiot
Coronavirus
It's essentially an argument against Republicans
What country did I support
The first important point is that we did not do nothing
Princeton Gatherings of more than 50 people
Restricted bar service the restaurant
Was not nearly enough
Really bear that out
Article on the BBC
What day is it
Population size in Europe
CBS News articles from July point
When the data is adjusted for population
The strategy
The ultimate goal
The presumptive goals were to return Community which has not been done and to protect the economy which also is not
Necessarily happen
As one might have designed it to
See how bad ideas ideas of people who started this their entire lives
Don't work out it's like
Not nearly as bad as it could be is that the population
Charges
Voluntarily accept
Protective measures
Jamaican house with guns being like
Right
No are they a blue state or red
Probably blue
What will you be saying
So Alex is paranoia
Sure and I'll tell you that
Mark Zuckerberg may or may not
He's in charge
Telling us what's going to happen apparently or something
It'll be days or even weeks
Weeks Avenue
President
Becomes depressed
The 40
President
I know
Hillary
Michelle
It just makes those noises
Currently being the speaker of the house but there's no guarantee that you will still be speaker of the house after the November election
Election against guitar on November 3rd
It's not like Fatar would just automatically become the speaker though
No you dethroned the person
Whoever's in California's 12th District just gets to be speaker
I feel weird representative who would be chosen
Going to be speaker but that's also on certain
Choose the speaker
No there's
There's two choices and it's all
Nightmares
Hillary president
This is just about the most unlikely turn of events
So this is what he always chooses
Portray is the globalist evil plan cuz it works
Pisses off the audience
Revolted Hillary became president
If that is Nancy Pelosi was like
It's Hillary
WCW Wrestling ticket
In terms of
Alaska
I don't know I don't know how this
I'm going to fly
Interactive stories
Skimming some headlines
As he does
This is what Alex calls like covering the news
Report
North Carolina
Good
It
Coverage of the news
Gnome says it's b*******
All right next door
Here we go
What's your news
Okay
Nextdoor
I don't know
All right did we do it
I don't know if anybody has any better understanding of those stories are or anything now
You like we just wasted
Couple minutes
Great you would have known about Rick Perry being invited to join a Ukrainian oil company
Did that actually happen
I don't know
Redbook
That was brought up on Alex's show and I don't even know what those stories were affair
There's a patient's of Alex leading in this episode
It's all just about like how
You can't be saying it's some eventually
Martial law
Petition
Operational
Operation
Miles an hour
Okay
So you'll know when the time is right
There's a train coming to town.
The plan is operational
Like later then
I guess
Okay how many trains do you have
To get hit by before it's
In terms of nuclear warfare
Metaphorical trains
You understand
The disjointed almost self-contradictory
It leaves the audience in a state of
Completely
If you listen to this
You could make a pretty solid argument from Alex's words
Drive to
These are the conditions that we know and when these conditions happen
You have to go kill people and then you stopped there that you'll know when it's time and then on Tuesday you say
The operation has started they're coming to kill with a 100 miles an hour
Split infinitive still saying now is the time
Just cuz you're waiting a day in between it doesn't count
No it's it's really really bad to do that two to the audience
Alex
I am probably one of the biggest stories of the week
The last week
10 days
Joe Rogan what's Spotify my moms
Favorite
So far
This year
Certain episodes
We're not
Included
Spotify
Hello
Dave Seaman
It kind of makeup
Total
And if you're Joe Rogan
Spotify is like 100 million assholes
Yes
They were trying to censor you I would hope that no matter what level of money you received
You would fight back
Fight against
Is there censoring your Alex Jones episode
You like I like a hundred million dollars
Sneaky Snake
He did no hook star talk about
Gross
River
That's what's going on
The Joe got a really really good deal
For the rest of his career
Take that money you're a weirdo comedy
Oh sorry
Or wherever
People meals
In the future
Not like not talked
Alex ever
I told you
Going on
Whatever the most controversial views are
Commercial
So there was some proof
Censorship
Shojin control so it's
The minute
I've heard that so very conversation, has been banned from Michelle
Like
They're going to get me
Controversial glass
Sometimes
5 m
R62 why I haven't been
This is this is Alex realizing
You been let down easy buddy
You been let down easy
Auto Brite
He is obviously right on the street
It is weird it is
It's not that weird of a rental
Commercially available
You know
Might see JoJo when he comes
Maybe I could see that
YouTube
Grogan to have Alex on
Really
Interview with Alex ism
Seas of the Spotify deal but
I would guess episode
Did not make the migration
Issue
Amazon
There's there's Black Tuesday and then there's the day Alex's allowed on Spotify
It's going to be in a studio and it's not going to be
Experian
For a while
And he starts ranting about what it's going to be like when the death of a dollar comes
You are
Will Annandale
Prophet
We're talkin
Pressing button.
Speak of the devil
Watching
Boris and the Republic
Save yourself
Okay
Speaking of the devil
I got it
So we can fight the literal devil
Everything is going to be
Now
Your money immediately
Rambo
Episode
Future and as is
I'll just tell you
Falling apart
Real war
T-shirt
Overtime Super Bowl
Future everybody
Things are going on
100 mile
50 MI
There's a lot of things I can do
Support we just got
Boss baby
No and I'm not I'm definitely not dealing with a barrage of similes like that ever again master of
Metaphor
He knows how to really just
The word picture
It's like
I got to go 100 miles
I only have one donut hole so you guys got to give me more donut holes otherwise
My stomach is going to be update
I wonder why
Bad
Yeah I didn't feels almost exactly
Exactly
Because I heard that kind of ship before December
Escalate to like new levels of
Support
Or if possible
That was
IND accurate
I don't know but
Okay I'm not taking the bait is going on again
Happening again
Overwhelming
What do you listen to the if you listen to his episode is like wow this is over and over and over again
So a little bit of etymology here
We know that a lot of his guests don't know how words work
No that's definitely true
Doesn't understand
Pecos Hank
Powerful you are
Moses
Lily in the mud
That's not true
Just such a
Just like any object has a
Do you know where the word pain comes
It comes from the Sumerian for pain
Cool
Stretch
How about it loves board game
Jesus come from
Different
Between being like it you're just as valid as anybody write to the New York Times where the person
Like you
That's why you should arrest an FBI agent if you don't like them
Yeah there's different preposition
You know
A handcuff you can arrest me
Because a functional plan
Open the movie rapper
Impressive
15 seconds
Dolese on McCormick Tony Montana
The good people
Who do The Killing
We're on the ground
We see what's really going on
Queen
Busy
Stop with killing Joshua
You're creeping me out
I just doesn't seem described as
Wheel of killing wheeler
General
We're the ones are doing The Killing
That's fine
Because the other side
Ain't got no soul baby
This is slave doing this
These are pathetic
I'm so spiritless
No got it
Nothing no connection
Is all synthetic.
First people on earth
What is the symbol of energy
50% off 40
That was impressive. Really was impressed
There is craft
That I don't know
Somebody definition
Rihanna
I could see that being a ruse that was just
Going on too long and that he hurt himself save money and he's like
Money's my albino
Did Mark Zuckerberg
Remember that okay
Cuz he knows what is weird
So
This gets back from break
Talking about some culture issues
And
This dude to get mad about anything
The biggest video game
Video games
Quarterback in the NFL
What
What are we doing
I'm leaving the race
Race racism
Man I can't imagine how angry
You know what NBA used to be about the rating
Drilled three
Absolutely
No
Let me see him do one crossover money cycling
A boy
Here's what here's what Alex is missing
What he needs to do is stop complaining about adding people to game
And start inviting them to add more people to different types
Mortal Kombat
Why isn't Bill Clinton a playable character
I don't know
And
Let me go ahead and respond to this by saying
I don't
Statement of our values
Write as a country
Can do a video game
Is Alex
Kat Kerr
I just can't care I remembered
Is embarrass it is a problem it is a problem
Listen to my show where I complain about
Quarterbacks
This is the racing
Alex video game
Yikes
Zuckerberg
He appears to be rich
Like Alex is already touchdown anywhere
Yes money naturally
Overlord
Destroy democracy
Ask for permission
Zuckerberg
Cold
How big is
How many houses
K
Table
In the 12
Menu
Zuckerberg
What's up
So
Jeff Zuckerberg
Fezzo's
Zuckerberg he does that a lot
It's really sloppy
Zuckerberg is told how many houses you can buy by his financial advisor
Who is Ella Mai
Still don't care
Do you have more than one house
I'd still don't
I still don't care
Sort of
Schrodinger's Bill Gates
Situation where he's a member of the
Council leaders of the world
Gia Edward Griffin is on the show and he thinks
Middleman
And now Bill Gates is in some kind of limbo where he was a middleman but
Now he's finally got a seat at the table but even then we don't know if the table is the 12
We might have gotten rid of the 12
I don't know
Still mad about Cabernet
Closest Network
Wow what
Did I just hear it
Colin Kaepernick a guy who is blackballed for kneeling during the anthem
Is actually a Nazi
Because he was blackballed for kneeling during the anthem
Closest black celebrity
Kind of arguing that there's an equilibrium of black celebrity kids
The other is closest to Jesus
Alright
He'll like those
Aren't they
In response the idea altogether
I just present the brain work
So a new story There's an actual story and spout loading
Better off
Directions using
1000 Georgian
States June 9th primary
Party cheats
Yours
Yeah I'm going to go with yours
Interesting something going on here
What is voter fraud narratives about the presidential election
He has to believe that because Trump says that and he's not
That's not a follower
This is the Georgia story is a problem
Institute
Conspiracies about mail-in vote
History also highlights
Caught
What do you mean
Well the situation here is very unclear because the investigation is still ongoing
Fear that aren't good
Brought
One possibility of the people sent an absentee ballot
Which is
The second possibility is brought up in an article in the Atlanta Journal-Constitution
Quote Motors are allowed to cancel their absentee ballots and then
Yet been received
By election official
It's unclear whether the voters under investigation at
Tempted to do so
!
Poor communication about the process
But not Criminal Intent
Yeah I do
Been on Yahoo answers
If you feel like you voted wrong go to the
The go to the polling place and vote for the other guy to cancel it out
Well
North Carolina last week
Now you're assured
Tropos explicit
The very thing
Democrats and Republicans
I don't know
Happens in the Democratic primary
Even eat each other
Cuz blue states don't have
And also I'm going to have to
To save it or iguana is a blue State as well
Understand exactly what the
Point here is I don't really know what all the details are
And I think more information will be known eventually
Too fragile
Whatley phone as much as people didn't know what
The deal was
Selection cycle you would expect to see
Increase incidences of
Totally just completely screwed up voting system
People who don't understand
You know
Absentee ballots not knowing the process exactly
And the fact
They're able to catch
What's this
Memes
This type of
Mail-in fraud ballots or whatever it is
If you want to deal with that type of fraud
If you made Election Day a holiday
Make sure that everybody had the education on how to vote
Got paper ballots only in standardized across the entire country
We wouldn't be in this kind of situation
Nah
Fair enough
I'm bored
Episode
Hour of this episode
Shane Steiner elk parade
About it
This Saturday
A show that HD footage say weather
So yes
So he's not that's he's burying the lead on that wood right
In his in his bike
That was the most fun I've ever had
People that it was not the most fun I've ever had cuz they were inside the water under
Broke
Man says that
Gaslighting is
Where is now
Something different than your being told is going on
The whole day was
Articles
7 bulbs
It was going down
I still don't think you understand
Difficult
Approach
The coverage of the event
Did largely focus on the fact
What makes it newsworthy is
Welcome Center
None of us really scared
This
Is the weirdest tower
It has nothing to do with anything important
Adventure in Lake Travis
It mostly has to do with how great
I don't care I don't care
Psych commercial around
I believe that
The Drone flying around actually arrest
He did
Amazon
Aren't you glad Star Wars
Franchisee
I mean it
Yeah it's kind of
Star Wars franchise has brought in approximately six billion dollars at the box office
Force awakens number for highest grossing film of all time
With their opposition to divorce cast
So this is like a guy would like
Champs Diner
Moorage
2012 Ikea
Battle course makes Alex turn into
I'll roll over and let you scratch my belly
Emperor Palpatine
I just think it's a great
Newark, Delaware
Bankruptcy
Star Wars
It's the size of a small economy
Star Wars movies that came out
Of course they are
It's kind of a big deal a lot of people
Helicopter talk
Alright
Well we are you going to have to get rid of my new phone number idea what 800 helicopter talk
That's too many letters
I mean
Trump
Trump did Trump said something about
Some sort of
Like Global disease I think
I'm pretty sure he said that it was a giant hug
And that no one should pay attention to
He was recorded saying it CNN put out those tapes that he said he was a giant hug
Way back right
No no it's not
I was being sarcastic Coronavirus
Auntie said
Boarding
Because
Terrifying
Because it makes Trump a premeditated murder
There
You can hear
Literally say
Who was Anthony atamanuik
Going to be
You trouble
For Ally
Subway too much like again
I figured there was something he was going to be able to do or like
This is all part of his
Euro 2020
53 days
Greenhead
Mattis discussed secret military coup
Call Irving
Want to overthrow
Here you can see how there's two different media ecosystems and they're reporting on the same underlying
Story with a different
Virginia
From Bob Woodward's new book
General Mattis
About how is there may come a time when action will need to be
Trump was Danger
The story and that's most important
Ignore dismiss the other elements of the story
Like we talked about
Which
Is terrifying
Yeah you know I do
You know what what
Two different systems two different realities
Except
The mainstream press they also cover the elements of the story
Wonderful to also spend some time
Goodwill
More about Woodward's book
Is a lot of lies and a truth
Almost all of it lies
And I will dictate to you what the truth is
Matter of
Which is
The big reason the Bob Woodward can go f*** himself forever
F*** him
Those tapes could have come out
In what March
I believe it's somewhere around there
Then we were still in
It's over for Humanity mode
In March
If those tapes 2 come out
Then the right-wing propaganda narrative would have had to go in a completely different direction
It would have
Yeah other way
And energy is not coming back
Sprite
Decision
Baseball practice without earlier
Gone and the consequences
The only reason I haven't heard a reason why he
He didn't
And I wonder if there's some reason that I'm not considering a reason and the washer
Washington Post have both given reason and not what's that
Well I needed to do more reporting on it and make sure that I got the whole story
Right
Flimsy
I don't see that as a really great
You said not not in that position so I don't know what legal issues there are
Especially in a situation like this
There you could make an argument that there's a moral imperative that you
Legal consequences
Absolutely
Without question
Change the right-wing propaganda narrative
Which has
Been largely the driver of
What is
So difficult for our country to move tab
Humanity they would have had to keep going on that route
I just
I'm just blown away
It just f***** up
I mean here's a here's what it is
He recorded Trump saying
For my personal benefit
And he held onto that
In order to sell book
Meaning that Bob Woodward
Is letting people die for his personal Bennett
It is the same
Headed to discuss
It really is
Yeah I find difficult to learn
Pretty
Pretty sensible point of view
It's a real big bum
Here today with Alex
But you need to know
Is it all of Bob Woodward's book
Is it true
Step
Wichita Eagle in Criminal
So the only part of this the true is the park
It's useful to me and everything else is all just ignore it
We need to talk about
That's me conversation about the fire
No nothing but I work all these episodes country is on fire right now
Because there's bigger issue
What is Mexico
The main source of meat was human flesh of children
They had shops out the bottom
Pyramid
Children
Shop
People
Haha
Everywhere
It's not a
Sustainable system and nutritious
Maybe you'd like to imagine
The need for food
Especially
If you might have time it just stational.
Now that's a poor economy there's no way you could have a main source of meat
For like a week
50 thing everybody gets
To eat one person at met is over
Yeah I didn't tell you got one
People okay with
Killing people was to dehumanize them and perhaps even say that they didn't have a soul
And they have no correct connection to your creators
So
I mean
This is this this bloom
My mind I didn't realize that
Did you know that
There are parts of your body called light switches
Turn off a chromosome
In the cell
That is a
What's happening
Cylinder
Where are the season of War
Horrible
Just Apartments
Too many times to think
It's okay for you to be like
I Think Jesus is going to get us through it and you need to buy storable food you can't have those back-to-back
You can't
This was pretty against that idea
Bob Woodward's book
Is obviously call ICE media cycle
About Mattis
And so like
If I'm going to handle this story I got a call in my big gun
Rodger Stone what do you make
Other coup plot against America
Zero Hedge
U.s. government
Say the n word.
Hey Rodger
That was that was bad praying he wouldn't say something really unsavory
Temperature
Rogers take on painting
Now you have this
Latest
Bob Woodward
Why would Bob Woodward
Anyone believe anything he says
I'm here. Stand up for Bob Woodward
Maybe Rodger Stone
Woodward
There
Believe this
About whether Woodward
Interviewing a guy about Upton Sinclair who has like a tattoo of a dirty Factory
A real comedy
In the fact that Rodger
Rodger
Yeah
I don't know if there is a more partisan
Crow
Nixon person to talk to
Yeah I just remember
I don't even know probably not true
Interest about that Watergate
Oh well
Trump needs to
In Nevada
Palace in Nevada
ABC's
Marshalls
And taken from the state
They are
Corruption
No boat
State of Nevada
If that turns out
We can prove
Voter fraud in the app
Yikes never notice
When they condemn like other countries for doing
And stuff this anti-democratic
That they're doing they're saying that we should do
Anti-democratic
Alex is about
To get engaged
Election process
Covering it might go to the court
The expert
Rodger Stone
Calls in the Brooks Brothers situation
Are precipitated
Isn't illegal
Carrying out of stealing of an election that Rodger Stone was directly involved
Alex's is is the Isle
Is not only coming on to talk about
Woodward
And not citing his
And probably engaging in similar
And Alex
And now it's just good stuff
Here's the problem with Rodger and Alex
And all of this stuff
It's how they're framing things
It it's receivers of Alex
Constantly
B Rodger does a little more clearly
Like to have an honest election
In which the real winner take
Boston
The real winner will not
Unimpeachable
I want to hear election
You cannot wait there for any election
Trump is the only possible winner there for
Of course everyone knows
This is a normal point
On Alex's listening to just probably absorb it as fact
Possible chance
Could win
In any Fair scenario
So Rodger
Alex needs another guy
Needs another mark
And when it's time
Talk about potential
We got one man that's right
Talk about
Trying to plan this to
And your Steve's response
A very serious problem
Whip
The man text Victor
You really threatening becoming to be like Alex the horrible everyone out
I do
Every other week
That's true
Spell koozie
So Steve
Our military
Like going to work
Dumb
Uniform
He is very smart
More serious problem
Getting off work
Shoreline
Edward is lying about the temperature
Oh my God
Music
This is unfortunate
This is what happens when the truth is just so
Obvious
They can't admit that they were
Stupid
Trump is an idiot
So f****** stupid
Stupid
End
And so it has to be
Even more out
Alright we can only accelerate we can only Accelerate from here is what he did
Is meaningless now
He
Destroy the meaning of his own work
Angry about it
But I would also
Say that
Maybe
Know that
More sensible time
Yeah yeah
I don't know
That's possible. It only took him forever to take down Knicks
Listen to I don't know
Camp Maranatha
Steve
This guy that we love
Is so smart
Talk to
What he said
Is it really answer the cell
Why would
With
Edwards history
He's going to get it
It's going to be a
Every night for 1890
So smart
You asked yourself that
Do you know what it is exactly narcissism
We'll go talk to the cops
While they're investigating the crime he committed
100% what it is now it is narcissism
Yeah it's totally that
Granted
We're making an assumption
Saks
Yeah
I should have known this
To begin with
He and I started it
Henry County
He never had any drone journalism behind meia operative
No no
What
What just happened here
Martin Luther King jr.
Yeah he was deep throat
Answering the question of like
Trump is so smart
You do this
Cuz he's not well I would say describe
A real a******
Why did Trump do it
We like
Is far more important
Anyone else to see now what do I mean
Negative
Mary
Terrible man
His sister says he's worse than Tara
Michael, his Jewish corrupt
Why does he do that
One word only
He doesn't give a damn
Either way as long as you use the word
Are you in
Including
Really really bad
For a leader
Go to its logical
How much bad breath would you get from nuking somebody
Like how much
Terrible thing
Is a really really
Like cancer is mentality for someone with actual power to have
Alex doing this
Cuz he's a narcissistic psychopath
Damn it's not about the hundreds of thousands of people that are
So we make money if you're in the game that's like
It's like a Omar
Understand
None of it matters in the more he survives this info
You got it and that's true about Alex Jones
Whoa
You guys accidentally kind of got it right if you just removed
Yeah
Also
Admission that there is a lot of real stuff
Totally he's getting away with it because of the
That's not good
Do you want your Lyrica leaders to have and face no consequences for their actions
Damn there's a real thing better than doing it a really bad
Cool
A lot of this episode has to do with Alex saying that they're the Chinese government is hacking
I don't care so
Some kind of a DDOS attack or something
Possible that the Chinese government or anything
I just didn't it was actually a scam
Rodger was on
Is Trump winning
His position is more
I don't want to pair election
This again
I said it a couple years ago
Legally or illegally
I can assure you and your audience
When I criticized
Line is
Many ways to make sure that
Legal way
AutoWay
Jesus
Okay I guess that's fascism
For you
Video of supposedly news program
Rodger stone is creating a scenario wherein only Trump winning his affair lights and everything else is like definition
Not fair Anna and a fraudulent election
Make sure the Democrats ever coming
You're can you please just stop talking for that bit your fascist
Stop trying to
Steve is on
I don't want I don't even want a fair election if Trump loses
We are a business
Alright
You should hate this guy
But think of the Coronavirus covid-19
And the challenges that we've all been faced with has
I've taught us some lessons
Personally I think I've learned a lot about
The different
Struggles that people go through
Things that you don't
Consider because maybe it's not exactly your experience at world that other people have
People who are immunocompromised or have other conditions
The interactions with you might be comfortable with
Completely different
Verizon
In ways that I definitely wish
As more wear before but I'm glad I know now
Secondly
How much opportunity there is
You know there's a lot of things
You can do even if you feel like there's nothing you can do
And I appreciate that
Great deal
Also talked me that my lifestyle
Prior to it
Was a little bit isolated and consigning and maybe once things open up a little more I should make
A greater effort
Where is that
Has a different lesson
The reality is
Interesting.
And that was
We need cities
Really in
I don't know what organizational system but
I don't know
Yeah I don't know
What kind of functional organizational structure
Weird
Personally
You and I and everyone we've ever met will be
Subway
So I want to talk to Steve about something really important
Because this is September 10th
I am the next day's 911
And
Talk about it
Number one
Call Mom
That prizes
Become a joke
Wow I want that went some directions
Yeah
I mean
The Peace Prize at the camper
I would
Say that
Weave group
Redacted
Sorry about that
Pacifically avoiding
Or does he not still think
I don't know what events quite honestly anymore I have no idea
Tomorrow on 9/11
Well now
Much like
Big deal
This is really making a meal out of like how scary China is and how
Right
Specific
China right now
United States
Personal friend
India
Incursions into the garage
I got to move along today at 2
Your fears about China here's the trick
China's not worried about our fascist dictator
They're worried about India's fascist dictator
Done
Is diffuse Alex's talking point about
China's the most terrifying thing in the world
Entire reason to exist now
Man
Is a great one-off interview says is reset if he's like
Hey babe
He leaves and Alex's just back to normal
Just do you just wrecked shop
It's like Sealab 2021 every episode that explode
You know trying to keep Trump out of office they're going to have all these
What do you predict their do sacks are there
What could this corrupt
Today's weather
Balloon pop
Yeah very good
Receive discontinued
The aggressive at pictures
More and more of those
Convergence eye preciate
Liar
No real talk about some of the issues that are most important to a lot of people like
Fires in the West Coast
No real conversation about the tapes
That would work release
We need to talk about
Bright
His version of the Woodward story based on
Zerohedge article
Rodger Stone come in
It is a Wonder it's an a******
I meant Steve narrative
Weird
It's very weird
Specs
It's just do sex
It's frustrating
Texting earlier I was telling you like a little bit late
Is current of an episode of Fall Out Boy
Text
It's going to be disappointed
I'm calling it Rodger and Steve
Alright
I did good
I do Cassidy of the show
Thanks just a it's so boring
The inserted unnecessary racism is always an issue
Jesus man
It's too much
Yeah
I feel like we probably should have maybe
Discuss that but the reason that I
Racist person that you can think of
Quite it's awful out of her mouth
Hey Dan Pedro
Charlotte from
Series
Assisted
Screw
A little bit more
Fire fire
Do we know anybody
Gingivitis
Platform
Which would
You will force
Twitter advanced
To reinstate
Was really appreciate podcast
I think it's a great idea
At the heel turn
Yep to see you there
Presidents don't have to follow through on their promises
Italy
Weather that would be good
I could see him soft
Little bit
That's what you do to broaden up your base
A big party
Your plan
This is not much
Just want to call
Say you love me
And it means a lot
I'm also sure I'm not the only one
Everybody
Christiansted
2016 opener
Wide world
Completely push me away
I thought you chose
Robert Evans
And yours
Help me to understand
Somehow
But I know Chris
It's changed their mind
I wish you more
Deconstruct
Thank you guys
Showmax
Awesome
I'm positive. It but I wanted to play it because
People who probably in similar situations then
Yeah
Wanted to extend
Condolences
Caller was
The saying young people or commiserate with
Out there people
I want
I love the show
Also
To say hello
I hope
Thanks
This is Gabby
Hey Gabby
Not enough people giving a shout-out so
Crystalline update
I have murdered my cat
Jumping I-70 a weird way
Murder with love
Mukbang
Cost to balance
Neglecting her a little bit
It's hard to balance having a cat in the hallway and also pots
The plant sure
Have to find a way to make sure that
Because if you look over there
Yeah I see that now I've had to try and find a way
To most of the plants are here in the office
The office when I'm not in here
And it's not a perfect system because obviously she can still if I'm not
Create
A couple times I just gone to the bathroom
She's doing caption she's not being malicious but like
Malicious
From what I can tell she's having fun
So
Interview question if she's she's doing good and having fun
Now
Hey guys
Scott
Large aircraft
Barton Springs Road
Actually work
Barton Springs
Got down
Kida protest
Our
First Electric
Started
Did not see
Followers
Maybe
There were about
200 people at
Springs but they were already there
Volition but if
Thoughts numbers
And also happy ending
Some
Citizen
I called the cops
Harassing
With mega stone
Shortly after that
But the show
Keep up the good
Bright
4 Barton Springs
Corsi added other people
+ 2
Harass somebody with a
Little baby bullhorn
Reality
It's by the baby bar
Noel
Even
Happy wax
Singing you after
Really appreciate
Keeping me off at
Dubai
Prime
I also really want to
My voice today
Australian
Pronounce
But whatever
I'm getting my cat
New kitty
And I would really love your
Directions on what day
Thank you so much again
Stay safe
And I
I'm at war with Australia
Firebirds Australia
Quokka
Australian
It's like Pluto at trailers been downgraded from cotton
Island
My apology
Friend
Dune trailer
Barrel run
You can live with it
Yeah
Barrel run
Sterile registry Leo's Academy
Through
Oh well
Jessica was feeling Contessa
Peppa
Something
Rob meow Coronavirus
That's actually pretty good
Buckley
In your new adventure
Jesus
Jordan
Choo choo train
Truly down here
Missouri
Just wanted to say thanks
You so much
For calling out
Springfield
Transplant there are
Good people even when these weird
Conservative
Anyways
Show that you do
I
Wags
Severely on my own pot
I'm too busy catching
All of your
And
Springfield Missouri
You know you got a place
Do I have some beers at our Brewery
Four by four Brewing
Anguilla
You're awesome
Shut up
Four by four Brewing
Not sponsored by Brewery
If I'm in Springfield Springfield
From cities because they're obsolete now
I think probably
I want to do a show with friends
And Tyler Snodgrass
I don't know the name of the place
I just ate our country we say hi to you
Quit you being
Come across the room
I just have so much
I don't know if I
I can cover it all in this phone call so I'm not
Can I get there
But I did want to say Jordan
That you had mentioned
Recording an audiobook
For your butt
The quiet part loud
And I guess I really appreciate
Audio
People appreciate the audio format
I'm working on it
It is very hard but I didn't realize that I was going to have to make
The way I write dialogue and how it's impossible to kind of keep track of
Yep
It is hard it's very hard but I'm working on it it's happening it will happen
It will
I promise you that people to know
Live.com
So
Hi Darren Jordan This is
Saint Louis
Ago
I want to say
Do not exit
Dial 18
Bad guys.
Not the right number
And number
Janumet
Your brother and the Ark does
How proud you are of them
That my brother who
Engineer
For kids
Has gone on
Middle-aged
Ryan
It's on
Instagram and face
And I think
You would really enjoy.
I also wanted to thank you
Shout out
Earlier in the summer
Pinterest summer and
That really helped make
Keep up the good work
Talk to you later
Pretty cool
Awesome
Seems like we're doing a lot of sponsored content
Some cool projects
Or something that people could do
Can you really love Chase bank then you're not going to get on the show me not going to happen
For now
Thank you all for the call thank you all for listening
We will be back
Indeed
Jordan website
If you could please find a local charity
In your area and help out people doing
Emilio on dbx
I am jumping out of a helicopter at Lake Travis
Alex