Air Jordan
I have great respect
Acknowledge
B b
Fight
MoneyGram
Alex
Knowledge fight
Acknowledge
Jordan Jordan
What's
McNeil
No I was walking to is it a dancing baby
Store
Is there was a bit of
Looks like blockage
In and out
Bunch of cars backed up
What's going on are you trying to get in
On a fairly tight turn
Because someone had parked in the alley and it made it getting into her
Cindy
Yeah it looked like she was
Clearly like
Overwhelmed
These dicks were just behind a problem
Spot is just like being able to
Samaritan ass walking around
That was a problem that got solved
Accomplishment is feeling better at the other end of it course
Lady Gaga
Since you felt helped by somebody to get to move on with their dead behind car ended up
Because it won't f****** person
I'm parked in the alley
This is just like all right
Yeah
Sometimes small things should be turned into this sports movie where everybody carries you on their shoulders
A Rudy
You got there because
The point I was trying to make
How about you
Mine is a successful
As we finish
U.s. open
Busa
I didn't
Almost almost like almost similar a simultaneous it is a little
Defeating Sasha's Vera
Who I am strongly against
I like a good one handed backhand is our greatest
The first time somebody under the age of 30 has won at US Open
And I don't know probably 85 years or however long the dolls been around
Fairy tales
2-tennis going outside
Becoming the sports-entertainment update
Is this network
Let me know if he's coming in that I'm pretty excited
Yes we have interest
Two very very few other things going on
And Alex Jones
Alright
Before we get to that
The first Kelsey events about your and I'll probably walk
Thank you so much for an hour
Next
Jordans
Terrible name
Heroin
Lauren and thank you so much Hannah
Website
We would appreciate it if you could
I'm trying to create something
You started scratching your beard and I was like
All right what you could do is yuca
Could take that
And scratch your bed right now
Get a little beard comb take the beard comb to the zoo charity know it's a beard
I think you're worse at this than me
I really think I'm pretty
I know
I think you're worse
You should take
Closet
The charity in the form of the generosity of the truth
Fire boat
For sure you stretch your beard it threw me off
Jordan today
Citation the people might have that we're going to be talking about Rodger Stone
You know how the media has got decided to cover his
Wiggins
Closer to the election and maybe things are passed
Today
Special episode
Call Keith
In touch with me
Reached out
And wanted to
Negative
You know we got this is Coronavirus going around
Had a tough time
And he
Having your anniversary
The day of their wedding
September 13th
Tubi
Experiencing what was going on on the Alex Jones
Of Keith and laurels
Whether this is a better one than making a time capsule
But who's going to listen to when they're sick
68th wedding anniversary we can do that
It's their anniversary
Globalist
Years ago
Parentheses turns out to at least
Anti introduced her to both Alex
And the podcast the Christmas Eve episode with the hatchet throwing
Jordan spirit animal a lot of emotional release screaming at the same thing
Many times a few seconds
Before
A ritual to keep up
With the show
She's taking it
Successful personal endeavor
To get Infowars listeners to think outside the hours Box by invented
* Ohio
Engaged
Put yourself in the
Flexon 100 seconds before
Reaction time
Context drop
Before we
Before we get into things here's or something I thought was really funny
You can't get back
Possibly
In any world
April
Also
Is Jesse Ventura as bukit is Crips and bloods
Republic
Over and over
Is not a good name
Alright
And then
The 2nd
Out of context drop from
Today Show sure is a teaser for what
The patio
And this
Should tell you that there are dark times ahead
Nono is this the beginning of the end for Alexandra
Might have been when Ron Paul showed up his dirty acid could be what's going on
So we start here where Alex Abigail
Introducing
The show
Ladies and gentlemen
September
Minnesota Governor Jesse Ventura
Will be joining us to give us his take on election 2012 and
Beyond
I just wanted to put that in there is a timestamp
Is it to be holding up today's newspaper
We can all be sure
All right here is
Also going to have open
Phone
Ladies
And gentlemen
Throughout the broadcast on the state of the world
Call Lynn about whatever you want
But if you
Call Lynn
About the fact that the global to try to get her up World War 3 right now
The war
Global war multi-region war
Flat as a political distraction to get people to Rally behind
This is just after Benghazi
Is this idea that the trigger Wars in order
To cover up for the financial collapse
Which is interesting because
That's a classic out
It seems like the distraction is far worse than the problem that they're trying to
To distract from
Galleria Plaza, Newark International
100%
Stop it it feels like
And at the end of the day you got to buy gold
It feels like
Envy
Conspiracy this makes sense
As opposed to their Dracula vampire demon
If you look back a little bit
Lane
You can see the
Connective tissue between this
Complained
Federal Reserve
Alex's
Particular brand
Of criticism is life based in
Flights to be mad
And you can see how you could take
Real world
Morphe
Is not there
It's like
When you're watching a movie you see the conspiracy theorist with his
With his Pitbull
That's interesting
What if you out a little bit and then it.
You just got a big
Like picture of the devil circled with like this is the guy that
This conspiracy theorist anymore
And if you have like a conspiracy board and it's only got a few pieces of yarn connecting
Utah
You're saying
Looking at
Devil's in the middle but I don't know I'm going to call it a sweaty
Are you know it's trouble
Fairy
Full of himself
Here with you today I'm so honored to be speaking to millions of my fellow human
United States Canada Mexico
Australia
Latin America all over the world
Marshall Islands people are listening to this worldwide transmission
It's interesting to hear that Alex thinks he has a listener is in Antarctica
There are no native populations in Antarctica unless you're talking about penguins
The only humans
Live in
Garden
They're working on so
Some of the research bases that have
Open setup
There are 66 bases in all of that.
In the summer months for thousand people in Antarctica
Where is Anna Wintour about 1,000
Is squarely in Antarctica
Attitude
Point
There are more tourists passing through Antarctica than there are people living there
Kick off until November
And most don't even actually even advise you plan a trip until like December or January
Info Warriors are really known for being
Smart
Is there winter scientist
But I don't believe in any of it alright
I don't believe in any of this stuff 100,000 years ago that obviously
We didn't happen or is it
Anyways
Is this is a low
Estranged
I highly doubt that any listeners in Antarctica
Seems like the invitation
Reserved
I'm at this point Alex has strong beliefs
Globalist
Can just like bresse a button
This happened all over the world
The phone button literally
I can punch a button
And other Jihadi squads that have been allowed to operate our countries
Will start
Bongs
All of our lives
America versus Iran
Versus Syria
No no no no no
Its Global Mega bankers
Financing Alside
For conflict
So they can destroy one free Society
Make sense
Conspiracy
The evil Strangelove
It makes sense
Classic
Call Swaggart
Like
It's not
Not an overly complicated thing that involves other dimensions
I still disagree on
Next to nothing
At least
The devil
Apply retroactively to
Alex Jones's career
Do we have we have to reconnect realize everything that we see in the past
Through what
Eventually
Because it must have to be like
You know Mister Echo
I mean
Come into play
Search Problem
Obviously all this is still supposed to be the devil
In terms of political Intrigue and Nations.
Ideas are stupid
Stop
It's great real life
It's humid hot demonic
You know those
Demons didn't come out one beneath the water to open the
Bombay daughter he'll say that the globalist hate humans
Populate
And stuff like Mars
But it's not like
Beelzebub
Cigar right
This terrorist button
Compress and then pick
The trouble
Empower
Sure
Child
Understand
I whenever Revenge of the Sith
Came out
Whatever it is
Not really into Star Wars
I guess it was about 78 years ago guys look up
Aaliyah
Cheesy Star Wars prequels
And of those films
God I hate you
Even throughout the past
So are you like Star Wars
You have a
You're on a little known planet
Finances
Is planet
Albert
Over trade deals 2005 so
7 years ago
And
Prominent in the Senate
Finances grapes terrorists to attack
The home
As a pre-check
The police
Stop
Terrorist attack
Abolishes
Basically using the
Touchdown
Punch down the old police force and wipes them out
When the movie came out the media all of the places
We don't understand the plot
We don't know what this mean
I don't think they did
Despotic
Do I don't remember people get confused
Drama
Sure
That was certainly
He was offended by that
There were troubles related to
About an evil man
We can understand I think
On the basis of like
Got Strokes
You know the bad guy
He's doing evil s***
It just brings up
These assholes
Comes in from commercial break
Who plays this
You are either with the Republic
Again about the turn of Darth Vader
Absolute
Obi-Wan tells him only a Sith fix it
Sure sure
Are you still even one of Alex's like real world
Is George Bush
Terrorist
Thinking and absolute ideas
Are traditionally prism of like that being
Approached
Alex still thinks
He doesn't
He kind of does.
So Alex believes
This whole thing in Star Wars
The allegory for 9/11
Who did interviews
Where you basically
Y'all basically I do
9/11 truther
George Lucas
What do you mean you can't get
Criminal elements of the government are staging terror attack
As a pretext to take over Society
Just like we're seeing today
Basically
That's what he said
He said
Just like we're seeing today
Is it at the Cannes Film Festival
Don't look it up it was all over the news
And the news
NSAID
We don't know what this means
What children do
George Lucas interview
Talking about
The US map
Macklemore it is
Fiat
Well
The story
Are you want to do a movie about
Figure out how
Hoping over to his
Anything about
Treated well
You don't do your job
Whatever
You're all thinking go awry
If you're always bicker
Agreeing
Like to do
Auburn do it for you
Go where the
What leadership is
He's like a warning about Trump
What's wrong
You know George Lucas is going around cancel Tesla
I'm pretty sure that that level-headed response to a question was asked
Actually him secretly screaming on right side
Bush did 9/11
Maybe take the first letter of each of them
It spells out G W bush did 9/11
I'm pretty sure that's
He's very clever that George Lucas
Yeah so Alex has
Bi-Lo
Some feelings about
Various protest that are happening
In the Middle Eastern countries like yeah man and Egypt
It's interesting because at this point
The actual attack
Like I develop narrative
There isn't a lot of
Clinton lied people died that kind of thing
At this point
Alex has
To go on really
Is discussing
To be the inciting
Which is that
Innocent
So Alex has some ideas about this
This movie or probably thinking a movie
Article on it
Isn't the trailer
It's like what was it 5 years ago
The prophet Muhammad cartoons and all these neocon control newspapers
In Europe
Planet as the Muslims
Sure it's wrong
Some of the Muslims can't deal with free speech
What
It was artificially done
Innocence of Muslims
Just about everything else
He's absolutely right that film wasn't
A Muslim
It was not
Whoever he wants
Sign Blazers
Christian named Selena
Nicole McClain videos
I was trying to make
Call Desert
Warrior which is presented as a dystopian
Action War Adventure movie
In the process of shooting this film imagine
Has-beens figures from Islamic history through voice over
People acting
Pretty offended
Yeah that's not good
There were outbreaks of protests in countries like Egypt after the trailer for this
Because of it
Negative
Portrayal of Muhammad in general
Initially the attack on Benghazi was associated with the release of the trailer for this film
The call that theory N2 question
Director of Innocence
Criminal history
He was arrested in 1997
Materials used to cook meth
$5,000 in a paper bag
Charged with intent to manufacture methamphetamine
He pled guilty and was sentenced to a year in jail and a bit of probation 2000
You're in prison
Pleaded no contest to Federal Bank
Involving
Bank accounts created using
Stolen social security number
Anyway
Anyway when he got out of prison he started working on
Mexican actors into being in a film called Desert Warrior
Specifically designed to anger Muslim
Unfortunately he tried to direct the film using an alias
Sam Basile
Give me the most recent felony conviction had to do with using aliases to commit bank fraud of supervised release
You just got
Do it
September 2012 was arrested on a charge of probation violation
He reached a plea agreement where for these violations were dropped
Prison per year
None of you
Probation violation
The fraud that he use in order to make it
This movie was extreme anti-islam
Tater with a rich history of felonies and fraud
And Alex's pretending that it was a false flag by the globalist in order to
Anger Muslims causing
Violence in foreign countries in order to justify a dude
Has a history of
Instigating s*** against Muslims which
Alex knows
A lot of
Eyes like that
Almost exclusively might not have known nearly as many in 2012
It does seem like he does not
You do not hate
And especially doesn't seem to think
That Islam is
Is a uniform
I'm staying
In 2012 he talks about she is SUNY distinction
Husband on this episode
Is working with her nonsense
In the present
Conveniently
Sure
The movie was made
And that's correct
But I was wrong
Again about everything else
Muhammad movie I can drive fraud I've looked at it yet
The way they promote it going
5 million
The way the press release is written the way no one knows who's behind it
It's meant to antagonize the mug
So the claim that the film was financed by wealthy Jews came directly from Saint Basile
Is the Alias that in the cooler used in order to create the movie
Okay so this guy is a real ship
Claimed that he wasn't Israeli receive $5000000 from
In order to make the film
Course that was all bulshit
Subsequent investigations uncovered that the film cross between 50 and $60,000 and receive the money to make it from his wife
Nice family
Bonita
I wonder how they feel about the whole situation
Alex is taking at face value the claims of a con man
Witches
About the pecan man
I was trying to
That's the f****** story of 2020 right there
Is Aveda president
Teresa
The president
Great the nice little fun see
Feedback loop or we all die
Very annoying
Alex believes the CIA
Music Man
Just a shame that these Muslims are taking the bait
It's meant to antagonize
Are wild redneck version of Muslim
To go out so you're not going to insult my God
I mean it is pure manipulation
And the Muslims are taking the bait
Why doesn't this perspective when it comes to like the Satan Temple trying to put up a monument
Somewhere
Right
You got to fight the devil
You can't give the devil
Muslims are getting
Tricks
Because something sacrilegious
Satanist Temple when they are actually
He's tricking you by thinking you'll be tricked
Into thinking that he's sucking with you when it'll actually serious Landing
I think that the goal
This sort of thing is
Generally to make it look like
Complained
The being levied by group
Alex doesn't like
Is invalid
Tricked into doing it by this
Evil group
Sure
Yeah he's removing age
Dempsey from
There again not people
In just a
True Lies wife
He experiences as hate but he doesn't want other people to
So gange
Expeditious
CIA
I mean this is
You're calling me
Billion dollars by Rich Jews
MI6
They were all involved
Just laughing
Easter these people up
A blue screen on the back Acres at 1
Low budget
Junk
5 million mi
Exaggerated
Faceless watch
And claims that the
The CIA did this in Langley
Do we have anybody here who can make
A really really terrible film
That will piss off Muslims know we got to call Blackwater that we need to hire an outside
Propaganda film
Nonsense
Because we've been dumped down because of
TV TV confusing people
I seen a jaywalking episodes where people can't even find the US on a world map
Joke
It is a joke
Television
You turn on television all of it is a destructive message
The New Normal
Lifestyle
But you know what my kids can't watch television
Because you want to confuse
Anti family
Abortion anti-gun
Call big government
Up
Trying to make sure that people get confused
Make sure
And what did the government documents Club around other said they said they would promote
Homosexuality in all this
In the family so no one
Add families to stand together
It seems like you're trying to make this a really Broad
The media is tricking everybody and your focus complaint seems to be on you.
Seeing
People who are lgbtq
Yeah I don't want to see the pictures of
Turn on
Understand
I watch football
From before 1964
That's how I do it
That's the only way it seems like
Interesting
Masquerade what is just like yours
Discomfort
You are on come
It is annoying to hear arguments from sucking
The late 1960s about how televisions going to ruin us all repackage
Just so you don't want to see a gay person I want to watch The New Normal
Can't nobody come on
I hate you because it was
What you do sexually
I am angry
Foregoing in
And trying to program you
And pudding
Chemicals in your food
Thousands of daddy
Pause every mammal species
Timmy combine
Look I don't hate you for being gay
I Ain't Mad At The Globe list
For making you gay
I don't hate you for being gay I just can't acknowledge that there's any possibility
Person and not the creation of my ultimate what do you not understand we're not about you
Structure of the family
I don't get it I don't hate you for being gay I just refuse to believe that anyone is actually gay if they were
Would just eat real food me and not watch TV
It's not that I hate you it's that I don't think you're a person
Just figure entirely invalid
But that's their fault we got to restart in you got to go
And we just got it cuz it's really strange
I don't hate you for what you do
Actually bought
You better computer chip put into the base of your neck
Very weird
Interesting
Jesus
Be coming up
Special Report
It's pouring a s***
Field pieces that he has and he plays
They are
So much more like local news
Stuff now is just like
Yeah I think she was gone
Liberals
I think I think part of that
I don't know if it happened after Owen Shroyer
Making videos of himself going to protest
Yelling at people and I think some of that
Jakari Jackson actually getting
Sound
OK Google
It was shocking
Sing to me the
Pieces actually having like interviews
With people
On the street
Clips
Dang it was
Pastor do with
Our buddy
In the broadcast we have a special report
Is Ron Paul going to run for governor of Texas
Are very
Own reporter
Instigating
I knew it wasn't
So we have another another report to Alex probably watch
Pretend didn't happen
Silent talk
American
On the streets of Austin
About their knowledge of The Conch
All of that will Air
Here on the broadcast
I didn't hear that one but I imagine it's not nearly as
Professional
The Kraken going out to
Constitution
I don't know what do you know about that
Powerbomb you
This is your quest
For you I'm not going to answer that question
And he did tease around a couple times calls about his world war scenario
He's playing out but you can call me whatever you want
Whatever you want
Kim in Maine
You're welcome
Salem big fan really enjoy your show
And I have
Suggestion and idea
Ron Paul shouldn't run for
Governor
We should do a right
Campaign
You your listeners everybody we can get
In touch with
Justrite Ron Paul's name in
If we can't get him as president
It'll show them that we're not
Stupid we don't want to
What your choices anymore
Do you hear me ask
I did not
Appreciate your call
Appreciate
Screen your calls but sometimes I say
Hey we're open the phones.
What's your take
On the situation in
East
Alex does not
Seem to walk
To talk about Ron Paul
It doesn't seem like
That's weird for me because I've listened to his episodes
After 2012 and he's love Ron Paul Douglas episodes
2012 during the primaries in the election
Innseason Resort
I know that before he loved
Trump you was pushing for Grandpa
16 election
Strange to me that
Very weird to me that he doesn't want to talk about Ron Paul
He doesn't let that be a mystery
A lot of time complaining about Ron Paul
Your call tonight
Here's the deal
Initially
Whenever Ramsay endorse Ramen
We got really upset
And it was because I watch
Behind the scenes
Not go after Romney
Admitted by Doug wead
Top of the campaign
Decision
Interesting
Jessie
Guy worked on Ron Paul's campaign
Tatum
Alex's into standard
Like this person can't even talk
Barely talk
Everybody hates
He says about Hillary that she says about Biden
Sure but I mean his job
The only way you can measure
Success I imagine is by his own
He can talk for 3 hours unabated
That's like that would be your measuring stick
Checking out
Can an hour on my show is like you're at your 33% is good
Weird
It's just
It seems like a guy has got like one
Pitch
Sure
I can't talk
Eastern Europeans make out of your face make fun of your
Talking
Just like
He has bad
Yeah campaign
Somehow
John Wick
Paul's man
I just got to be honest about
I'm done talkin about Ron Paul
Guys overall
I think you're and doing some good work
Overall
But
Call about Ron Paul you're not going to get the responses you got for me
You don't want to go there
Okay
Because I know too
He knows too much
Vista
What is it
This is this is fine people
And it is the same
Later
Of course
This is very weird
What is the
He's mad at everybody that anybody likes hers because
The people that you like
Actually do the stuff that he thinks that they're going to
To do so he blames everybody that works
For them without ever realizing that those two why those are the same
I'm at this
A piece of s***
I can't really just
Blame him
You going along with
Alright I'm deeply suspicious
Especially considering because it's 20/20
Introspective about whether or not you can see
Support someone who hires people that you don't like
Jessie
Is a villain
She already said mean things about Jesse
I sent you weeks ago you Washington to work the mainline Republican Party
Cuz I knew that from inside
McConnell
To work for Mitch McConnell and
Arrangement
Who dropped his support for another Republican candidate in favor of Ron Paul
Michele Bachmann had support from
Senator in Iowa
He got paid
Discord Ron Paul
That's not something I'm going to go down for
Would you do that
When recording it was a recording of
Story was discussing him for two years while working for McConnell
In order to help ramp
Chances in 26
16 date
Ornos water
It became part of a campaign to attack McConnell is not a true conservative
It's in the 2014 GOP
Haven't heard anything about McConnell Center
Is conservative Bona fides
The involvement of Jessie Benton in McConnell's campaign
Macado's mainstream gopod Grassroots
Tea party followers
Without whatever machinations probably too
There's an office right now
Because you would have lost
Sapori
Of the Tea Party ad
Folks
Hit Jesse Benton
Helped bring along
Do you know this is a lot like
To me like when you find it when the
Is
Stupid cop worked on then has to be
Re-examine
The system campaign manager
Ghost
To jail
All campaign should have to be like I don't think you are.
Leave your hands away and be like I do you know you got away with that one
No
If he's even committed the crime for his state senator for Ron Paul's field for the primaries
Getsupport away from Michele Bachmann
Times come on
I don't know if this makes
Is technically Ron Paul's grandson married to Ron Paul's granddaughter
So you
And just because we should
In March 2016 it was announced
The Great America PAC
A major Trump
Chief strategist
In an article about the higher duckweed
I think Jesse is one of the best political Minds in the country
He understands the cross-section of an outsider in the political establishment
In October 2016 Jesse Benton was caught in a sting operation agreeing to launder $2000000 in
Donations from a
Big Chinese National
Consulting company
Ultimately
It is too easy to trap me
Do you know what it is this is evidence
Apparatus is geared towards protecting conservatives with a lot of money
Because it feels like so far
Based on every investigation that we actually take operative
We're the guys just have to be like okay well we're going to
Record
And then they're like wheel of committing crimes take that two million
It's too easy
Button on your phone every time you go see
Does semen
Because Jess is actually involved
Gunship
Criminal
Jesse was in the poll campaign to birds Mainline
To support Trump
And very very very
Alex
Is the real deal
Seahawks
But Alex cannot forgive
I we always seen the video
Call Beth
That was snubbed by the Paul's everybody
We seen the footage
Peter Schiff
Jesse Benton
Don't go to Paul past its extremist
Nepal's kind of get married
Republican establishment and try to influence
Libertarianism
I get all that to assert
What the
Talking and acting like
La Center
And all the things that happened
This is very sad to see
After all this great work done and that we've done supporting
Patriots out there
To just kind of see campaign for Liberty
And the whole political list of donors
Felicitations
Out there
This is what it's actually about
Interested cuz I can
I don't know if
Is Jessie Benton told Ron Paul DePaul faster
If I were in
Position
And I
Viewed myself as a competent strategist
Do not go there
I wouldn't
Bad
Don't go to that
Maybe 18.
I don't think even if he's president anymore
I still think it would look bad
Hunter S Thompson drug
The great idea
It comes down to
He believes the Jesse Benton
Being brought into the McConnell campaign because he has
The donor list
Sure from the Paul campaign
Text for money and he didn't like it
Some reality
The world
Politics
Working as a
Like a producer of shows here in Chicago
Totally be able to use
To promote their shows
And those were highly valued commodity talk about other producers who had
Giant list
Together
It is something
Capital 8
Sanders mailing list after
16 was incredibly valuable to Hillary
One person has
Control over it I don't
No
Just for this list
Seems weird
Trying to actually say
You want
What's you
That like
McConnell
Your support
Conover
Kind of a spiritual truth to that a little bit and I think Alex takes it very personally
Because
He owned
Write that his money bomb
Like big
Most of the support is from Infowars
Alex
Mini drone parts
So I think that he's taking the really really personalized
Mitch McConnell tires Ron Paul
To run his campaign were committed to running a presidential campaign in Kentucky
And that starts with a presidential campaign manager
McConnell said the statement
Jesse is literally the best in the business
Organization
Constitutional
Narsapur
List over the Republican Party
Mitch McConnell
God done talking about this
People calling about the throw up on the radio okay
So just please
Don't
And I'm not going there
Tell me what you call Shelby
If he was drunk that is it is it is nice to see you still profession
Chanel backpack
To the point where he's mad but he's not
Throwing a drug test
This can come off
If you look at it I think about it a little bit
The same time
Has underpinnings
Selma
Something to stop the trail
I agree with him
There's a part of me that's like
You understand how does it have
You understand how the
These people work
You know like this guy's job is
To sell your information to
Many different people
Any of whom I buy it or not
It says he's going to go run a campaign
Mikado he doesn't give a s***
This dude
Even when we indicating that he thought it was
Thing to do to help ramp 2016
Still on the team
An argument could be made that Alex is taking Eliquis
Credibly narrow view of
But which is something that people don't say about out whatever
It's really funny to hear him say stuff like that
Nepal got Starstruck rampal got old
They sell off in the sunset
And their hook
And all those families at Paul faster scum
Those families
Guy that's who I'm with
American
Mitch McConnell
His rear end
Going to be a long drop
It's interesting because like
Alex is talking about is like
The GOP
Because of the people like Jesse Benton
To merge the GOP tea party stuff
That is the work
Alex to pretend
That he is not doing that
Sprint
He pretends
He doesn't like the long game
Involved
Plans and like
All kinds of think it's funny
How
Brilliant he sees the globalists are and how their plans are infinitely long and thousands of years and obviously
Devil is riding them
But anybody on his team who has a plan that last longer than life
Scream for a bit
Yeah
Yelp
So Alex
Like
I mean I think he's making some Fair
Critiques of the Paul
Pretended to be more serious
About their chances in order to make money
What is somebody I don't know does me wrong I it's not personal I don't get upset
Russian fly
We wore
Passionate
Shell mods
Or someone
And watch him really turn their back
Rope-a-dope keep everybody going along
Was going to be president
Wonderland was already announcing and
5 months ago
Decided
Embassy was all just an exercise in
And capitalizing on political
Yes
Man
High tide it's weird
To realize that I was more jaded 8 years ago
Somehow I was like
Everyone's polish
And even if everything isn't there is still just
Intricacies in complicated ways in which things can be done that maybe
You can't capture in campaign
That aren't necessarily deceit
Alex is realizing the Ron Paul
Was fundraise
Wow
Doesn't really thought Andrew yang
Revolution rail
Punk
Married Ron Paul's granddaughter
I'm done
Don't call Michelle folks about Ron Paul
Michelle
Go hangout
Hang out with your Republican
I know you know about all this
I don't want you to I'm done
We don't want you
Okay we don't need you
Oh boy
You want to play with Jessie Benton never do anything for you again
Except for support you in your end at every prison
Going to get some Buckshot here too
Parties Bilderberg
And okay
I got that guy says you libertarian
But it's just like I don't want to go there
I have bigger
Things to discuss
Like Trump's connection to Peter Thiel
I can't I can't imagine
Being where Alex is right now
And having somebody like
Play him
An episode from back
I would listen to myself talk
Can either like Havoc
Complete meltdown Herbalife
You know what
I like
That guy waiver
I would have to be need a redoubt
I need a like
Island Fortress 202
Oh my God
Because
Jessie Yan
Begin
Akon
Open
Play some clips of the news
Hubbub
Has been dropping going back on
That was
That was a good job build up and not have the gas there
Newfoundlands are weird
Sure are weird
How many years can you handle that many phone Miss have
8 years
Cross our fingers and hope it works tomorrow
Are you saying I mean like this is one of the only shows where this is such a
Constant problem
These kinds of things ironed out fairly well
Particularly
Gas to baby used to be the governor of a state
It's noticeable whenever somebody with a
The professional show has it called
What are you like
Oh no this is a
Nightmare
Not like
Well
This is Wednesday
The phones are weird
Wipeout
Exactly
Text talk and Alex
Is a good idea
I end up losing respect for Jesse
Every time I hear him
I think he's one of these guys who benefits from people having it
Picture of him
He's a guy who likes doesn't like spiders
If you just
Then you can be like yeah
Phuc yea Ventura you didn't like special interest to near the governor
Predator
Yeah
That's great
But then when you start to get into like more specifics and then I can wait you suck
I stand with Ron
Completely
We need to cut off
Who made to any phone
We need to do it for Natalie
Economic reasons
Our country's broke
Like Ron Paul W Gray
That's a great it's a great realistic
Consequence-free kind of idea
Shut then
I talk a lot of s*** I have a lot of bad ideas
You know whatever this stuff happens whenever I'm lit it's like a
We should cut off all foreign aid
It's never pointed out Slater
For them
Okay well here's what would happen and I go that's a bad idea
Typical
You one of your ideas is shown to be bad you like bad idea
Knock-Knock Jesse Ron Paul zeise
Difference
Cuz I think between me and most of the right way
Although you would not be on the right
Because he thinks that there are
Democrats and Republicans
Just say that everything that she brings up is Dahmer
The Advocate cutting off
Pretty tops
Balance the scales believe that
Take a whole lot of
It may be an impossible number of a good opinion
Stop world hunger
And I think
I don't think those two work well together
Dishonest
Complain about Obama
Is the remnant
Things that work on during
Sure
Because fries
Call Lidia
Memories with the people of this country they can't sing
About a year that they can learn
Number
Realize that it was difficult the first bailout
It was supposed to start in all the wars
People meet under submission I speak from experience here
Yami economy
Which decisions made about 4 years ago
Intercepted today
So when the economy went sour
It was decisions made back in
4 * 5
About to happen in 08
It does not happen overnight
Large
Takes about 3 years or 4 years
Prediction
Impact on the economy
Do you
It's interesting because it's now whenever something
Week later
So when all the stuff that happened during Obama's years
Before
So
Jessica
Becomes a little bit weird
Who started these Wars the first bail out of here at 1 so again
Anime
You know you don't want to look for Obama for third-party person
At the end of the day
Maybe
He hates Romney
He's an anti left
Kimberly
He wants to get on to other topics
Train stations in bus station starting to pop up
We've got
Military
I don't know obviously something very bad and will transition to my TV show now if we met
The new season starts November 7th 10 Eastern 9 Central on truTV
One of the interesting shows we show you this year's in Ozark Missouri
There's a complete underground city we discovered it
I'm glad you guys did a jarring
Transition to promotion
I'm glad you brought that up
Well I'd like to
Terrible dumb questions
Remember this episode episode
Conspiracy Theory with Jesse Ventura
I mean that the couch if you want to get high
Go like
Information it's not great
Okay go
F*** yourself Jesse
Well it one of the interesting things here's an interesting thing we found out in Ozark Missouri
Now
The only new construction there except for this dick 72000 sqft single-family Drive
Weather there
That's another story.
The only news things happening in this little town in Missouri is
The only thing being built
And we promised the kids
And it goes something like this
One page 411
Thousand people in New York City
There's one
9000 people in Los Angeles
In Ozark Missouri
There's now one
51 people
Incredible is it
Is it incredible
It doesn't feel incredible to me Ozark Missouri is approximately 17800
A 50-person F350
Key Banks in that town which is
Comical seems like a lot of it
Infrastructure going to wait
The former Missouri
Ozark
There's also a separate County called Ozark County
Jason city called Lake Ozark
Is it because the lower house for the state of Missouri a part of Arkansas
Would you been really instrumental in defining culture of those areas in the Midwest
Oftentimes the term of the Ozarks
Is used to describe the lower half of the state of Missouri
Administrative order significant
Might be that what's going on here Jesse's taking the number of banks in the Ozark
Compared to the population of the
The city that's called
And then decided
The small town in Missouri mysteriously
350 Bank
That would make sense
Throughout the southern
451 people because
There could be a bank in a city that's got like
No papa
You know a little a little under half
Man I don't even know if there were 350 total like
Pacific building
Please.
I'm not entirely positive that I would be out
There's like 350 Banks
Do you like
Bottom half of Missouri seems maybe even
Like a walkie
Statistic
The idea that this town
Ozark Missouri
Ridiculous
Situation is ridiculous
We only sell Banks
Thanks possible reason
Conspiracy is he even hinting at
I suspected what he's getting at is that there's an underground city which is
The people Houdini
Does this make sense at all the surface to bank
Okay they could do all that digitally
So that's kind of the angle that I think they're building all these bags
Right isn't that suspicious who's using those
Where are those people going
They must be Underground
I think
That is a trait of thought that I would
Because it make
I'm just guessing that the conspiracy
The server's world we must make a withdrawal
Silly it's legitimately dumb
Let's imagine
They have an ATM they could take 11 ATM
Why can't you
Construct the underground city
Why can't you just dig a hole drop it
Sure why not
I would like to make a withdrawal paid yes can I have an address
Hey buddy
Guess what
Physical secret underground city
They don't need money
They could have
Everything digital I'd be showing there's no reason
Sims 4 change the capability
Underground city
We just didn't think of that we didn't plan ahead 350 Banks put in
This is so stupid
It is entertaining or some kind of
Buick
It's pretty good evidence that either he's checked out on the critical thinking
Or he's just leaning into like things that are like
Almost no conspiracy clickbait
Young you know
This is just part of that selling the s*** yeah
I'm doing Alex impression
There's one episode
I can't do it
Do you talk about on what episode they're going to
Government making us humans
Alex
Because
If you believe Alex's conspiracies
Already done.
For years that I'm doing that salting the Jesse would make an episode about that cuz Alex
A hundred times over
So it's
It's weird
Yeah that is
It's not like this is the first time he's ever transparently so
Obvious garbage
Positive I'm a sales are you know I'm a professional Entertainer
You know it wasn't
This season's going
Even more entertaining
For people to watch
Because we also get in
Throughout your body
Are you sure whatever his name is
I wish you guys would have got into a telephone
Well you don't I would discredit except it was on Time Magazine
I need people to leave here so
You don't realize are there to show the conspiracy
Russell dare to show if the conspiracy we believe is a flat
5 1/2 ft Reptoid
I believe it
No
They're making fun of
David Icke now
David Icke is a turd in the punch bowl
Mentality
Pretty good and hard
That's good Jesse's on a promotional tour
Bye-bye bye-bye
Help get more
He has a particular strategy
30 employees
Hot news for you not tell you this
Listeners
I stated that if a Grassroots camp
Replace acrossed America Grassroots
Eddie Money
If they got me ballad access at all
50 states
What is the Grassroots campaign
Guarantee that I would be in the
Debates
But I will give serious consideration 2016 is running for president
Are you breaking out here
The couple places but you're pretty well out there the same day so your hearing at the same day
Wow will thank you I pronounce
Transfer
Apparent attempt
Wow
Brutal
Like if you actually listen to what he said he said nothing
He's guaranteed guaranteed
To be in
If I am 75% elected already I'll think about it
25% of
Creole
Give me the present
Yeah ask him to like really reiterate what
Really clear that
I will show up and yell at people at the debate if everyone else does the hard work for me
I'll do the fun park
Probably
I forgot
Well I slept it it's a Grassroots effort
Not a money approach I don't want
I want millions of dollars raised and I don't want to do all that
Glass roof
Caller a doctor in people do the Lake Worth
Ventura on the 20
Ballot for president
And if we likewise guarantee me
Because I've got to be in the debate
If I can't have an opportunity to win
And the only way you can have an opportunity to win
Be included in the debate
If they can guarantee me the debates
German Keeney valid access in all 50 states
I will get
Very strong consideration to running for president in 2016 as a complete into 10
Very strong
Even in your imaginary world that is not
Possible
Look if all
If hundreds of thousands of policy
Email comedy Central's head of programming
Right now
Telling them that I deserve a half-hour comedy special
I will strongly consider recording
Comedy special
Comparable between those two is they're taking out the difficult
Hundreds of thousands of people at my stand-up comedy career for 10
The hard part about a Grassroots movement is organization mobilization
Ideal you would want
That part of the process
No
To me looking back
What places
He's doing a bunch of these last
Express strategy
Is indicating that if people want
What a dick it's not it's not hard
Just not hard
It should be harder to manipulate
For every 6000
True
On this episode
People think that I'm a witch
Alright
Intown a couple days ago
The world
Trailblazer the grandfather other all 30 plus years
The biggest company the best company all of that
You got all these fly-by-night people now
Coming into storable
Two things about that
Steve shank was going to be on
Food
The BMW episode
Which text his desire for calls to come in about World War 3
Financial collapse that's coming
You wanted to create that tone for the episode
In order to pay it off towards the end
See we've just heard from all of our colors that World War 3 is coming
Steve do you have anything that people might want if the financial collapse is coming
Second
He's talking about
Space
They're not around.
Direct
They're not big on
I can't find any evidence
I found a bunch of
People who are
Are not in business anymore
8/3
They're not Alex's
Sponsor anymore
Alex
Supply
He has a completely different
Food sponsor
It's interesting
It's
This very similar Behavior being
Engaged in in order to push
Survival food
Yeah it's almost like
Callers were the three main game
You know used to be him Ted Anderson to end
Enroll
Look at what
The horrible things might come
Discuss
Honestly
Trying to figure out what was going on figure out why Alex doesn't have you food the directors as
Really f******.
And I think
Aspect of survival food sales
That we don't take into consideration that much
How ripe
For abuse
Oh yeah
Because the premise is your buying food that you won't eat for 5 years
If you're somebody was running a condo
Expect to be in business in 5 years you been time whatever the f*** you want cuz
People are not going to eat that
It could be bad
And then it might not have the shelf life that you're claiming that it has
You're out of business
You've disappeared there's nothing they can do
I found
So many come
On website
From people who'd bought food from efoodsdirect
And you know it's got a 25-year shelf life or something
Even more tragically
Now
In 2020 with the situation
People are finding themselves in
We have survival food
They open it up
Rams
Completely spoiled
The food is no good
I found a complaint from
Did their food don't have
Bug proof bags
Oh
Just had just passed Universal
II
Generally
Try to err on the side of not taking
Angry
Online
Comments to seriously easy to for people to
Create
Campaigns against company whatever
But
It was over a long stretch of time
Complaints
They were also
A lot of them
It made me think maybe there was something to some of the complaints were making
And it really really depressed
Because
You are
Your base
Basically
People comfort
That they may not have
In the future
Sure
These
People
Like it's not cheap
It's a lot of money people were paying thousands of dollars
You know a family of five a Year's worth of food
MN
Maybe it's
S***
Useless
And now you're out money
And you've been deprived
Comfort
That you were being sold
In the first place
It really made me more angry
Because
On some level I totally understand the idea of preparation
I made a we've talked about this before like
When I was younger we lived
Missouri and there's tornado
Bottled water in the basement
In case I understand
It's something
If things go as bad as they possibly could
It's not irrational
To have
Something
When a company exist
Promising you
The relief
Those
Potential fears and anxieties
When that's what they exist to do
And they take advantage
It's really bad
Tomato
I would say a day just on that marriage
Yes it's disgusting
When you add the fact
Text that they are
Then stoking Anna
Exacerbating the fear
In order to
Now you're not just saying
They're at
Exploding somebody's reasonable Sears
What they're doing is there ratcheting up reasonable fears into something
Insane yeah order to
Sell more of their food because
That's how capitalism
Also a multi-level marketing
Call Angela
Stephen Morris
Just the all of the indications
This is a really really gross
Unless no because I'm too depressed
I know it's very
Alex is talking about this
In terms of like
Getting into the emergency
Seafood games
The independent
That's an illusion
You're creating a dependency on your company
And if you can't promise you can't deliver what you're promising
Picture of
Like Alex selling x-ray
Goggles in the back of his magazine or whatever like
Just
It's just such charlatans
Camry that I
Find the fences it's so much of his career
Nearly staked
Clearly based on
None of these people who do trust him
Yeah it's hard to believe it really is still hard to wrap my mind around
Just like
How many different
Idioms
Descriptors stories in all of this stuff about
Kahneman
Litter
Throughout
Adjust American history let alone
The world history
And yet it is still impossible to convince
A significant portion of people that comment
Yeah you know like
Common are so good at convincing you everybody else
Just trying to con you yeah
That's
You wind up by other artists
Talking
Experiences like
Episode
Sort of umbrella
My distaste
There's so much of it
Before was like what you were talking about
Exacerbate
Sure because I had some kind of
Maybe naive
Belief that what they were selling was
Good you would think
Talking
Plaint
And it's not just complain
Pictures
I just
They just had such another layer to it
I feel
So bad
I mean
Yeah
Not least of which
Because
Just as if you want it
Let's call it market capitalism
The market will do the
Sell good
Storable food
Like what incentive is there in 25 years
You're not going to be a bit most businesses are any business 25 years
Business
Bottom line is
There won't even be
You're going to need our food
Yeah
We won't exist
It's it's honestly something that I think that it might be a space
First I think it may call for greater regulation than even just like
Regular food market
Because of those
Absolutely cuz of the sort of liability that you
Get yourself out of based on the nature of the business
And of course
Some
Politician August
Be someone on the left
To suggest
Right
Is really f***** up it is really I just
I didn't really consider it.
By the time you use my product
I will be out of
Dead
Wow
Consider these things
Just
Naive
That like
Sarah business
Bright
Before
CIA
Has anybody figured that out yet
I don't know
Anyway Alex is like
This guy Steve Shank
Easier when he runs my truck and survival food
Plug
Food out of here to a head
Just so he can give you good food at the lowest price
Weather
Literally
Chamonix running on here
Not talking about Seafood direct.com
Does not talk about that
Interesting premise
Easier to talk about the news
He's not here
It might be interesting to see what kind of news he wants me to cover
What he brought
Warriors
Hyperinflation
Food-stamp use climbs to record
50 mil
Hotline Somerset food prices soaring
All about
Stories that are designed to make people more inclined
To buy your survival
How is that
He's just there to talk about the news
Please talk about bulshit
Presentation of life
Call Steve
Consulting
Direct.com
Adorable Foods
They're laughing about that concept
He's told me that
It's so good
F*** you. f*** you
You know what you think
I can just imagine that
Somebody who's listening to this show in 2012 bought that food
And then they were the people complaining
On the web
But I
6 months ago
They opened it up
Then we got the food
It's a good thing everybody
You know that was when the markets
The shelves were all empty
Target had no toilet paper down the way
And they're like f***
We're going to open up the store but food and then they get
Even if it's just a thing where things are looking
By this food out and see what we've got
Like I can't draw
A direct line
Think of it
Because of this disgraceful display
Maybe
No-Man
Bummer is
Go f*** yourself with this this isn't an infomercial
You can't do anything about
The earthquakes in the storms and things are happening as a result of it
The 2012-13
Do anything about what's going to happen
Apocalypse
Now with this election
It doesn't matter
Neither one said anything about
Individual
Back it out there can't do any
Anything about
What's going to happen
With all of the goofiness is going on with government to take over the food and
That we're going to talk about Michelle Obama and and her
Interested in
Later
So anyway
You can't do anything about that
Alex
You are a
Master
In and finding all the goofy stuff is going on all the inappropriate stuff
Actually take notes
Can you bring up what's going on with app
What you when you bring up what's going on
What's the Chinese taking over our Farmland when you bring up
What's going on with ethanol on the various things that we talked about
But I got a question for you
You got food in your
In your garage
Air conditioning
What can you do about
Obama
And the
And what can you do about
All of the things that we talked
And all these people
And are saying
My gosh Alex really hit it today
The food is alive
No I agree
Charity levels
Wow
There's nothing they can do
Terms that is a call to action
Ya-hey
I can't imagine
A better way to stop
Listening to
Infowars somebody was like
Here here's what you do
Take note
Everyday
It's kind of like if you don't take notes
What's on a weekly basis
For one week
Take notes of what he says day-to-day today
And then compare them
From just what
He says in one week
You will find at least
30 different things that he's on both sides
I don't know
If you choose the right week
You're probably right
Stray too far off and pass
None of it
You just take notes over a day and track down like
The things that you say
Mind actually looks
Information
You could not possibly
Continually
Absolutely
The only reason you would ever
Maintain
Begin Infowars listener
Just sort of unquestioning
If they're not questioning
What they're here
Because it's easy.
Captured
Patterns of accepting
Is reputable
There were listeners
Obviously
Just sort of a compulsive exercise
Score
So Alex
Your food
Alex says he does
Everything
I am so on please we were proven right
But I agree with you
People need to have good friends and family and medical supplies and food
Water filtration in firearms
And I've gotten out of the question I lived in town
I like living in town I like a drive
About quarter mile the movie theater
Grocery store not now
I got to drive 10 minutes to get anywhere
I went and registered agent relocation
I found the one area in the Hill Country in Texas is by what a few save areas
Because
This is real
Dial people will go to the one place to get their food
Efoodsdirect.com
Embarrassing
Flash Forward 8 years Alex
You lying piece
The ship
8 years later it's still real right now that I'm going to go stock food up
Country Inn
Is George Foreman actually had one
Cooking grill
Performing
The severity of the situation requires YouTube
The product solute
It's just gross
That's not good grocer for me because this touches on like
A lot of my
Belief
Things going bad
And I really
I
Cuz you don't just need food for your self you need it for your family in your neighbors
Flash Forward to 2020
Superpowers being honest
A few years ago
But I'm literally look at my neighbor's now going
Try to hang them up got them and scan them and drop them off you know what I'm ready
The reason that I'm personally offended
Any kind of
Perspective
That you have
Towards
Things going bad
Should take into consideration the people around
You should never be looking at
Are like getting a weapon to protect yourself from your neighbors
Think about getting a weapon
Possibly to help
Protect your neighbors
From any threat be there
Community-minded
Approaches
Towards
Anything that could go bad
So much
More help
Full
Then
Vuse where it's like I'm the only Survivor
You know
MMA
Alex knows that
2012 you sitting here saying you need food for your neighbors and yeah
A bucket
It's great because then you can
Can help your neighbor survive
Yep that is something really awesome if you're able to afford that are
In such a position where you can do that
That's great
Alex
But he doesn't mean it
He doesn't mean it
Furthermore
Just
Strictly
Cooperation has not been like
One of the strategies to survive and has been the only successful strategy
It's the best why we're still
It's the best adaptive strategies
And finding people around you to create a Cooperative Community with
Will make you far worse
Successful
With a f******
Gun
Basically holding your family
Mashed potatoes
Like what are you guys doing this gun to protect this bad food that I overpaid for
Amanda
It's a real bummer because
It's a
Like app
A presentation of
Something good
Bean used in service of everything
I mean it's kind of like
Too much by
Media and culture in
All that stuff
Then you you're steady drumbeat of dis
Dystopias are always
You know it's the person
Surviving
Dystopia
Community and we're going to get all this stuff together and we're going to do a little bit just to Spectrum
Yeah
The Marquis
I think it's your Story 2
To tell
F*** all this s***
I hate him so much
Hated so much
So interesting 2012 exact same behavior
Kind of even grosser because of
Like a little wrinkles
French food sponsor
Probably got a business effort
Getting tens of thousands
The dollars of profit
Gross
Just like using Alex as a
Platform
To promote his product
And
Using of
False
Start
To push that
You are Petty fight
With Jesse Benton
And by virtue of that
Such a weird world
All kinds of weird s*** happens in day today
Nothing makes any sense but it's all Vaguely Familiar
And then go into the pasta
The same weird s*** happens
Everything is everything on Infowars is uncanny
Like it's vaguely similar to something that you know from The Real World
And yet
Net
Yeah that's how they're like
But man it's not what are you doing
It's really weird to me
Like just how much more grounded
Conspiracies are
Because he doesn't have to
Wrangle with the Devil
You know you can do political conspiracies and Intrigue all day
You could sit me down and yell at me about JFK's
Theories
An hour
You know maybe look into
See where roads lead but
Wouldn't be like get the f*** out of here devil killed
All right and also j.f.k. jr. still alive
First of all
Happy anniversary Keith and Laurel happy anniversary
Rotations
Earth are the Sun or whatever
Whatever you like the most
Thank you for
Interesting
BFF
See part of your anniversary
Think about that
You got that is he f***** up
U2
This is your anniversary
Sing to the show like
Right before happy sack
There are thousands
Do people around the world
Actively or passively right now wishing you a happy anniversary
Weird that is weird
Let's not focus too much on what we're capable of doing
Kinda creeps me out there
People use our powers
Absolutely
I did not have time to make phone calls
Previous episode
We'll get two calls on the next one
Bob
We aren't sure that knowledge inviting I go to bed Jordan
Samara
Alex
Same color