Knowledge podcast
I have great respect for knowledge fight
Dealnews
Jordan
What's up what's up
Today today
Airmail bag
Don't Close Your Eyes
Close your eyes
Keep them close
Because
You got this
The mailbag
Crazy except
You and me and I'm not so sure
Let me take a look
Here's the note from from Bride of Chucky
Because he knew I liked you just get a book from the store section
Many looks horrible and never read
Traveling with me from house to house
Always feel guilty
The hours
Miss you dorks
Memories
Not Aaron she doesn't understand why we never know
Wedding
All right here's a here's a page 120 from everyone's crazy except you and me
And I'm not so sure about you can you say tautology
It's good
Here we go
I recall the case I prosecuted
Home was charged because its owners were gay
Well not fine
You didn't start the impression I didn't job
We charge this arsonist with
Get ready
First-degree arson baby
I was fighting fire with fire
Scribe
This goes on for a while for good crime laws
Not great
Okay
Hello
Longtime listener first-time Rider
I'm sorry I wasn't able to get you this before they Lionel retrospective
You don't look like you sound is an
Some stand-up
The f*** out of here
Years later he changed from a largely apolitical
I think a CD is a good example of what Jordans
Thank you very much
This is all about you
I thought about it and it's not really a gift for you if you've got to read the whole thing
It's really only a gift for you if I can find the parts that are funny
And play them for you
Wacky Wednesday
Maybe you should you should
Rip the CD on
I mean simply because
YouTube channel
Exactly
Halfway through our second first one
Finally I got my partner
Congratulations happy birthday
Could steal her identity
Could be in October
So I'm excited to give
I got her a
Good gift
You know I'm saying what happened where you're making your eyes look
Almost read like
Spencer
My first gift for her birthday 20th anniversary tickets to the miseducation of Lauryn Hill
Concert she's a huge Lauren
And Lauryn Hill showed up
That was the first gift I'm not even going to beat that
Yeah I know I'm going to lose from there is maintained
Consistently good gifts you know what I'm saying I'm not going to hit 50 home runs with the 25
Going to get me a good contract and a good career
Exactly the best baseball player in history
The best baseball player in the history of the lost track
He was a rookie the last time I played
In terms of a winds above replacement
Amazing rookie season
And then he worked on his the holes in the game the next season and then the next season
The other things that were a problem and made those grade
He's gotten better every single eat the greatest pieces why I should a lot of feelings
This is why I should make references
Yes good rookies
Too good
A bathing suit
Next gif
Wayward
Got her sheets
What kind of shape
Just really really nice ones
You don't know what the fabric was silk
Satin might be right
Is satin better than times better than luxury sheets okay
Play as I am
That's like getting somebody
Miserable
Some dolphin
Trying
Nevermind I got her gift for her
Good
Spiritually against the rules of get absolutely
Congratulations on
I'm happy
September 15th
Dammit
There's a lot like I had some expectations of what I thought I was looking around
Just a lot of splat
An important to discuss
Leaves a lot to be desired
Thank you very much maze I get back I'll ask
Pink eye
Jordan was distracted by the
It's just as good as I as you might imagine
60 Seconds
60 seconds is Right length of a tune
Jeremiah
Mustache sign in for an account
Is that right
Thank you so much
Heroin
Amanda B
The website knowledge
Open up everyone's crazy except
You can pull out a random paragraph here and let's look it over
Look at funeral process
That's the sickest thing that we still do
Next 10 NASCAR
And you can take a great joke like that
Toilet down
Make it something way better and give it to a charitable organization or bales onto in you
Your area
And it'll be great idea
And Alex would be in
Control mode
Before social media Twitter the news
Conversation
About
Complaint Interceptor released
Yeah it was
It's true for the elimination of poverty and genocide
Whistleblower complaint
From a nurse John Wooten
Who I work
At the County Detention Center
Number of
Catalog number of
Real fuckedupshit yeah it's it's
I want to say shortcomings
Statements
Eating a lot of these stories about a particular
Seems to have a
Irate people hysterectomies
Unaware or confused about why it was done
Things are human rights issues
That are staggering
And horrifying
Well this is a whistle-blower complaint investigation and
I hope will be literally
You do still expect the next day after this is a PT's of the media
Cycle
Have something to say about it
That you come out in front of damage control
Cuz there's so many intersections of Alex Jones
Pipe issues
That are here
That are real problem
With his ideas about the clicklist
Wanting to sterilize people
His ideas about
Make this
When I saw this news I thought this was a particularly Alex Jones
Meatball
He would
He would need to discuss doctor so evil America would have brought him here
After World War
Is coming up
It seems like
If that's on Monday then Tuesday show Alex is going to Connecticut
Surprised
Talk about it
Information you receiving this broadcast is most dangerous information on the world
Italian forces of Satan by generation
This is the reality that we face no matter if somebody were down this information now in the future you will see
Will be forced to admit that isn't God's residental you'll be forced to choose a side
Founder of black lives matters downtown on the beds are safe that's all coming up
This is the leading story story
Sacrifice to their death
My patience wears thin it's really hard for me to approach
This because
Not even something that I'm interested in really responding
Yeah we can't really have a discussion about the merits of any
Arguments whenever
You're automatically just invalidating one by being like
Sure they got good point for Satan you can't trust those guys
It's taking things almost to an unfair playing field
To automatically and incessantly
Yellow of the devil
There's not much
Not much really
You know
Reasonable people can do with that all right for the little Kristen
He doesn't
Sign my check so right
If you want to talk about a lot of nationalist
Make a big deal out of worship
Necessarily appreciated by God
According to his
And one of the big ones
Maybe even the first
What is that don't f*** around with Odin
I'm paraphrasing
Preoccupation
With Norse
Deities of mom and some of these whites
Supremacist
Naturally now if your complaint
What you want to talk about all the time
Time
I think that maybe
Policy differences
I have worldview differences with these white nationalists
Nothing to do with their interest in Norse God because you didn't trade your
For wisdom if I were to do
Decrying the white supremacist Menace
The evils of Odin
I would expect no one would take me seriously either even though
Even if I were listening to Joe about
Admit definition
I don't I don't think that I would be that interested in
Have a tough time
Listen to a dickhole who just talks about
It's it's weird it's it's really weird
Yeah that's no good
Can you imagine a show
Uche ojeh
Most of the Oath Keepers
Worship Odin
So we don't need to worry about
We're good guys need to talk about anything about what they represent
The worst about
Worship
Doing great yeah the way I feel like
Top of the
Yeah so it's
It's a lotta it's a lot of
There's a Pig episode
A lot of
No conversation whatsoever about their whistleblower complaint
No look like you work for the literal Christian Temple
My version of God
And as matter worship Satan
Just become the thing where it's like
Alright
Listen to the show at the
Interesting
Stupid news
And Thor is only like chaotic neutral it fast
The things that I find interesting or what we're going to be on this episode from the shackles of
Actually taking seriously
Anything he says I like it
At least for this episode
Perhaps infestation of disappointment
First thing
Is that
Blind
To the world around him
He recognizes that Matt Drudge
Signaling
Some dissatisfaction
People are noticing that
Are not Towing the exact party-line they always have
Turn on
Which is weird
A 15-year
Change the whole face the world
Need help getting
Good question
It's not an issue is none of this makes sense
What is
Alex is to be
This is a war
Between good
A literal devil
Literal devil
What
Main part of the Patriot team makes it hard for you to complain about him now
Working for the devil
I really wanted to have a
Success in his future endeavours even though
Regardless of what I believe about his
Quality
Since he's working
Looking for the other team if he is in any way successful
The devil wins is super-effective
Really helpful for the devil
But it does make sense when you recognize that I was looking
We should all this late anymore
I'm going to need dredge up back on my side
Much larger Organics
Statistics I can see all of the incoming traffic still need that
So working for the devil
Okay
Boy
It is such a bummer
To live in that world though
It's like
This guy that I
Loved and respected in his giving me a huge boost throughout my career
Has changed his opinion about something
So rather than at all engage with that
He's working for the devil
You don't really have any
Because he can't cuz even that would be too much
He's clearly on the other side
You know the other side of me
You know that's funny though
Especially red like think about it this way
Alright
Normally when Alex hate something
That he used to love
He throws a tantrum about it until he gets a 10
We saw that work with Joe Rogan
With Matt Drudge
You can't say that he's a devil worshiper and then Matt drudge is going to be like
Well let me put a couple links back on my side
Right
Your foot
I think the different relationship there and
The Joe Rogan can
Drugs made
Teen years of your career
Had largely been based on traffic
Attention that came
From this
Just like I'm going to need that traffic eventually in the future again
It wasn't very hard for Galileo who took care of him that whole time
There's a lot of parallels between Alex
He believes blacklivesmatter worship
Sacrifices and rituals in order to appease their dread God
Naturally
Pieces that he has about this
Is a video
The shooting in reality it's a guy who's like
Hey shot these dudes out here this is crazy
It's amazing that I was in prison
Kind of lost in this weird
Feeling of like I need to dwell in Vengeance fantasies
Criminals never even had a bloody nose
Politically
Catwalk
Tool
Right before it's due
Call Colossus clown
Civilization with its show
This is a harbinger of death
Thunderstruck
Make no mistake
Just
Does not saying anything
This is a Colossus
Caviar caviar calamity
It just filling time with vaguely angry slightly Vengeance film
He's a headline from the Sun
Yeah
Just words
Also
Politically got there we've never gotten our pull the teeth politically
Politically knocked out before
I don't think it I don't know
Literally
Alex
Honestly I might have called
Find some space nonsense
So much of this is just filling time and I talked about the devil
But Alex does start
That I really think is a board
People need to know about
And a large part of that Alex
Conceives of his own position in the world
And this is where it gets really f****** scary
Whenever it's like
We're playing against the devils like okay
The cheat code for you not to have to have any real
Defensible position so you can just send all this stuff
But listen to the word
He's painting himself into that picture
A lot about 46
Long time ago
Permission
Like 34 years old
Mission 4
Washing machine
Cursor to the
Weren't you a Satanist at 18
Just wrote down
React
You f***** up is
Creating himself as like
Process
Preparing to play this
Crucial role in the battle between
Let's say
Things
Settle down a little bit
Let's play
Tensions
Go down a tiny bit maybe vaccine is is released
But we can start to
Work back towards
Maybe Biden becomes president
Summary
More overt can be scaled back
Is there pushing for reform can maybe have
I'm more sympathetic
Maybe Biden gets elected in the real work can begin
Bright
Maybe some of that happens
That would be really bad Until you realize that that means Alex
Saved us from the cataclysm
Over 30
What are the 10
This sort of language only makes sense
If it
Towards something really bad
Literally the epochal
The actual there's going to be a thousand years of
Plans are alive
Train coming to your miles an hour
All this and I
Was prepared since the age of 3
Like
You can't go back on
This is not the sort of thing that's like
You can go put your phone
Should be
This should be endgame
Pardon the use of the term
The Mayan apocalypse is coming should have been immediately tossed into a ditch whenever it didn't
From a business perspective
A couple of the most slick
David Wilcock
Already had pretty in French
Well then this should have ruined a lot of folks
So I think it's really upsetting disturbing
Before
Cataclysmic battle between the devil
Claiming that the prophets always works out well
It's not good
I want I want
Like this is such a good version of what
Forces on this planet
As the oxygen you breathe
I want to take you away from God then I want your spirit to be with them
Why
Churches
Manifesting
50 yd
Sure
You'll find out
Stop & Shop
Wants to fight corruption
People that just can't really believe
They'll wake up later because you and I and others
I'll just say that
Your financial support is what allows us to stay on air
Moon
Right
Yeah I mean you can feel coming the whole time it was
Where is the point you're coming getting ready to try and monetize
To create with this bedevils really wants your soul
Glitterbug churches if you got to keep us on the air
Pierce
Dude
Adam just like f****** dick
To do that
Kind of
Gross
I just imagining anybody not being able to see through them
Extended
It work here
Keep forgetting
We're radio show
I wonder why cuz
You're not really in trouble
And give money to our stations
Surface of botched butt
Sacrilege
Affiliates
Sports
Abortion
More than that Little Whorehouse Church
I'll give him $100 a month
Okay
Yeah
We might be getting a little Wacky Wednesday for a little bit
Discusses
Not just random
Pulsar Stars
Reality
Netflix also recommended
Its species today recently I think I know where this is coming from
I went to like a basketball team
I don't know
And they put on
This is because my parents would
You are a sweet pea
Yeah species again and now there's there's aliens that are transmitting DNA to the Earth and now we're recreating Avenue
Cool
Alex still has not been on Rogan
Just weird was just on again
Spotify
National news issue
Play tragedy platforms
Call s.w. by giving him a hundred million dollars
Disappeared
100 million dollars
Isn't that guy
By giving him
$3000000
Cancel
Million dollars
Taco moderating a f****** debate
President Hoover whatever dumb s*** happen
This is all stupid
Trying to defend his ego and whatever way possible
Is so afraid of sjw canceled
Great
Telling friend who's instrumental in fighting Satan
He's a sneaky snake
He's in the neutral zone he's like Ireland he's not going to get in the fight between Satan and God said many times you're there with her
He's a sneaky snake The Patriot
If Joe is celebrate
Picture of YouTube
Contract
Get a billion dollars
I understand
Can't possibly wrestle with the
Thought you wanted somewhere
Sure
And there's a large interview
Ate all the exact same anti-mask
Anti-vaccine Corona denialism
American James Bond
Tenpenny would be the receptionist
Or whatever and she would absolutely spout anti-vax
Text nonsense
American Sean Connery run-through in
Problems or anything to hang my hat on in terms of
Necessarily things we've heard Alex or with these other guests
Closest I could get to something I was like a original
Mark is it is a military thing
Because they can't have an individual individual energy
And so we've got everybody social distance
I heard that Alex I was standing in the break room at my office I still
Standing in the breakroom
I heard it and I said
Please tell me that this is not
Part of our language
We embrace
And sure enough
Here we are
Things being
For the artificial
I'll just have the transformative something
Oh boy
So it's
Is
The transhumanist
Well it's because they need to get energetic imprints of each of us or something at
Standing too close together you can
That makes sense
Now that's right
Technology support
But they can't figure out how to really like
Isolated signature
I mean there's that
Bachelor
Away from somebody
They could have one of those Google street cars
If any of this word the actual issue
Six feet apart generally in public
Is not
Is a real problem just
Metric system
Is a military term
Pete in this car
Country
She's coming in and saying
Individual energetic imprints of them
The record or whatever I was like
Conceive up doctor
She said whatever
All the people at the top of this ladder I'm either eugenicist and I believe many of them are Satanist
Agendas
So she's talking about black people who support vaccines
To really get a negative view of religion
If you listen to
The show
You know it's true
Christians during the satanic panic
Aflutter with the same things of it
Fortunately for probably
Going to be going to get a bath
Rap office
Sure I think a problem is
As long as you're really vague about it
And a Christian
The devil's real
Play Adele
Don't follow the devil
Everybody's like okay
Whenever you take that and then you actually put it in your life
The devil is here on Earth and he is the reason that we have to stay 6 feet away
Everybody who believes in the literal
As long as we have
A pretty nice
Ability for everyone to recognize
B sincerely held beliefs
Can be metaphorically accepted by me and we can go about our business
Is fine
I just becomes a problem when your sincerely held beliefs
Cases for
And your politics the disagree with mine
Come down to the little Rose Bowl
That is the problem
At no point in the Bible is it like
Goblin the devil look
We're going to eat going to be rough
But eventually we're going to come to a kind of date
I'm sure there's going to be a thousand years of God's Reign but then after
Missing from the Bible
Satan is super into police reform
I miss the chapter where like Satan is really pushing hard for updating with the voter Rights Act
Jesus lied 828 look I'm tired
Police reform
Anyway
This next clip she's there
And they're coming back from commercial break and of course
There's no sound
I only play this quit because it's interesting to catalog a new tech issues on Alex's show
Phone
Grocery store
Josh Turner
I'm wearing to work on that.
Now
So I guess they had to remind turned all the way down or something
It's amazing it's a problem
Everything
Must have been working fine but somebody else something out there
Release program
I don't know it's not good
It has like two whenever there's a new
Somebody got a big board just like pressing buttons every now and again
Well we can't hear anymore
Yeah so
A lot of this is
Kind of
Boring
Nonsense interview with a boring
Nonsensical
Caspersen door and then
Bishop Larry gaiters back on
Etymology
Right
I'm not going to talk too much but but
First episode where we encountered him
Nichols
Here we go
Communist there really witches
This is
Total
Satanism the end of our species
Yacht
So easily either knew which guy
See see if he's got some which stuff are some words on Word
Blacklivesmatter
Paradigm relational reality
What's up colors okay
Foundation is this West
Which represents this 16-point
Timeout
Where in the United States and in Canada
Three women
First of all I love this dude is saying that like
I'm going to get something to eat I'm W the floor cuz I have to I bet just
I kid.
Interested I'm interested in the fact that you're saying
But I got to go
Digital only 144,000 black lives matter people are going to
So again this comes down to
I don't believe you if your complaint is that there's a West African religion
Still need more
16 points
Chapter
You f***** up
Black lives matter website
Chapters their official chapter okay
Sure
For the error in accounting
And that's not represented by a pin on the map
16 that are pinned in the map
Hamilton Michigan one isn't like the dark
Evil pope
Tons of unofficial ones throughout the country and throughout the world
And then also they have a portal on the website where you can apply to become an official chapter
They would be doing that if they were an esoteric religion
For some meaning
Really strict about those
Yeah they wouldn't have 17
Trying to sneak on by the rules
Maybe their God is like
You don't got to worry about
The weirdest guy
Sounds more reasonable than most
The rules of God I can do anyway really quick cuz they're so unstable
Violated
Bishop gaiters
Is now
The witch guy
Witches witches
Blacklivesmatter has been design
America because they were being used
I got to go
Man
Always gone like they
It's always anytime black women lead anything that is an athame
Two white Night Lights the worst thing in the world
It's the worst thing in the world
Cuz black women I've always been generous with like they've been the first to be something and then the last
Like that is almost always been the cases of like
It is always
Leaving social justice first
And then black women being the last people for to benefit
It's not like there weren't any black f****** suffragettes
And kind of b******* that they have
To go after black women
Always
Is a compelling point
Right always right first they can scry into the future
Incredible
Here is that
In order to get this episode together
You know
We're recording this
Mrs. Tuesday's episode
The shop
There was a feeling that I had
He would have a response
Do something that seems important seems relevant
Huge
And seems like it requires a response from someone like Alex
He would ramble about the devil
Much of his time
Boring
Call people witches
Like its
There's nothing to hang your hat on
There's just nothing
So you have to ignore it
Like on the right
Or at least Alex is audience must be bored of deep States.
They have to
Because that's
Wednesday doing it
It's the government
And you realize I cash it there's no excuse for why the things aren't happening
Warriors
Government
Kind of bored of that it's the devil
The girl working for the devil
I don't know what the next step
Super devil
You can't go up from the devil unless they're
Alright
You only have one knots to go up
From the devil dog Apollo
God
Also yes that's very funny
Highway
Here's what you do if your Alex
You say actually
God has turned against us
We have to fight
God
And the devil I don't think that Alex
Would be able to sell that
Defeat God is a some cell
I find I find it
Interesting to watch this progression
That I would be in Port
Then bringing about the
I get that it's interesting in a sense because I I do think these are the sorts of things you would expect to see
And somebody before something really bad
This happened right before some kind of an intense flame out surprise
Mark of the document
It's like
It's equally likely emergency
Seafood 6 months from now
Every moment he doesn't explode is it is edging
It's just edging you know it's little bit going to just do it
Movies at
It's somewhat that if I allowed myself to get drawn into that
Cuz he's behaving
Right typically are
It's tough
It's interesting to watch but it's also incredibly uninteresting to listen to Gators
What is a paradox
But those do calls before we get out of here
Hey tough guy
Austin
Free of me
Lifeguard
Thought I'd share
Story with you
Hi
Cousin Austin
Happened
School District
They were
Attending a
School play a couple years
Miguel
Apparently
During this play
Very near the
They heard someone
Heckle
Call element
Stage
They started
Pretty much right off the bat
Yelling things like
You know
What kind of tree is that
Sitting down
Sitting tree
And other well not brass
Child actor
Sage
Hey friendly
Can you do this for
The play
Before someone in
And I noticed
Certain
Individual
Who had allegedly been drinking and alleged leaving heckling
Children
School play
So I just thought
That would be a nice break
From present-day in
Alex
Religiosity
And I wanted to weigh in on
Very hot debate dance
Bringing up about five iron
Friends and say that
It's the holdup
Hold up pretty well
Thanks for all you do guys
Yeah
I was waiting for him to say
Walker for validating that opinion
Also
Obviously
This is one person story
We can't take it as proven
Can we Heckle a child performance
I would not be surprised
Godzilla
What I would assume he behaves like
You know likes somebody is
Somebody's child is at a play
Find you and you just get so fed up your like finally you stand up you turn around and it's Alex Jones you like
Yeah
This is not fair
Pizzeria
Going to have to be like
Yeah you're doing you
This Is the End
Bees and assholes
Always carry a tiny bull horn through
Tyranny slapper one
Always be aware
Bird in the background that call
You're also your bird in the background
Professionalism
Anyway
This is about
I'm calling be
In one of Dan's men
Mentioned how
Awesomeness
Grounding
And then
It turns out
Crucifix
Peach plant
And I'm not very good
Growing plant
But
Either night
I was sitting there putting my
Thinking about
And she
And
Electrical
Angie
Scared of having to my bed
Wackadoodle
Here's some water
Amazing day
Adult
Countryside
Just wanted to say
Thanks for that
And how
Something
You know watch something grow
Anyway
Thanks for the show
Put into it
And don't be so
So hard on yourself
Y'all got to take RDU
You deserve it
I reserve the right to remain hard on myself
Like anybody
Hearing either my perspective
If you jack off with your plants
And your your cat
Aspiranet
Is how people feel about their offspring to some extent
Kind of the same thing with plants and
Westie
Into a fussy old lady and I think that's my favorite part about having dog
Call dear old Grumpy Cat Just sleeps all the time
Pretty early
That's what I understand.
Aeronauts
We already said something
Literally
Meandros both
Tough to record
It's tough to recognize
If you're a part of it
You know like these plants they look different to you to me because I see them everyday
I know you see baby like
Every few days
It's harder when you're
Directions knisley
Need to change
Take a step back
Appreciate
I haven't seen you in a year and you're tall
What's wrong with you
Right that's how I'm I'm not good
Next
Any Jordan Landing
Play to let you know that
Lucky Pierre
I guess what
My garden
And when hearing
Aberrant
I thought I would
Let me know that actually
Passion fruit Vine
Are pretty easy to go
I have one out here
And it's like
Pretty low maintenance
I just kind of let it grow in my pants
The water
Spine
And it has
Beautiful flowers
Great fur
Happy
Display
Hope you having a good day
Thank you very much
Pronounce
Butterfly
I'm very happy to have
Call Lynn
You're having a great time I don't know if I brought this up on the show
Passion fruit
Whatever
I have
That's one of the the year of design
One of the coolest looking weird
Alien ass flowers I've ever seen
Flower
Google that shitt they look weird
Take a long time
To grow into
Fruiting or flowering
Goodyear to
Before any of that
And free
Vines
Edinboro
Call
BRZ
Ideation
Consider need
Garden
Name Donald
Or still playing
I regret it
Originally transmitted
Religious
Persian
Faith
Deity
The whole thing
C1
Camp buddy
Wheel lights
I promise I will
About time
I like it
It's cuz that if you're from Scotland that probably will be part of your
Apria Scott again real soon
DIA
Sue about
Netbook caller who wanted to
Pocket is soon as we stopped recording I realized meows
I mean of course
Origami
Leo zagami
Mine's better
Or talk about
I cannot disprove the devil
And I cannot
In any critical
This guy believes that he is a pillar
God's chosen team fighting the devil
Literally
That is manifest
In the bodies of people
Who are trying to push for greater social equity
Yeah once you're stuck at Turtles all the way down there's really nowhere to go from there
Hit the top
Will say that
I will be back with something
Not as disappointed
Twitter
Indeed
If you could please help out those doing God's work
Clark I'm
Forgotten to the radio show
Alex
Christian color with huge fan of your work