Medic
Dot-com
I have great respect for knowledge
Chickaboom housing
Need money
So Alex
Knowledge fight
Alex
Jones
Indeed
We are.
Sometimes it's dissonant energies are better than complimentary ones
For from minor keys in the lake
Do you still smoke
Damn
Jordan
Overburden the audience
I mean it's just really
Cucumber plant
Obituary
The flowering in them
Successfully pollinate one of those plans
I don't know I don't know how good my bedding
Call eneida okay
Actual cucumber
That I could turn into an actual pickle
How do I cucumbers
I might I might have more
Saint of cucumbers
Maybe even just cucumber water you're like cucumber one cucumber Seltzer's assure
Cucumber water better than with
Cucumber on a salad sometimes
It's not a highlight but I do love pickle
Sure so
Cucumbers pickles
Future peacoat
You're absolutely
Help me fine-tune
There isn't going to be bats I assume that any you think we're that we do is going to require that
If you don't like going to put a crimp in your abilities
You tell me if it's a bad pickle or not
Tender in Thai I might need another contractor I might need another another employees today
A good idea
King
You don't get this
I'm worried deeper with the zip it
I got my nice
Nice Dan it is any
Incredibly beautiful and scary from Chris B
Chris Paul's Ewok
How do you send this lovely noted
Hey Jordan
This knife goes to you
Freer Texas
I'm screaming at the same times I do
Our paths don't sound too far off and it's great
To see there is a chance to get past what your family
Hope you enjoy keep fighting the good fight you two are not needed now more than ever
And this is from folk Vanguard sport
From the forge on Etsy
Really cool
Fighting knife
That's so cool really appreciate that
You're saying I remember this on Facebook
Facebook I never see those messages and I owe him a response
Along with about a ton of other people here I apologize my God
Correspondences the worst thing in the world for me
I need to get better at it
I'm going to get back to you but I got to get back to work and then I remember
I got the message so I just assumed
Better if I didn't keep my email open all the time
I think I think we might have missed
Yeah yeah
New strategy
We're going to be talking about an episode of The Alex Jones Show from
September 17th 2020
Talking about Thursday's episode
Indeed
The bunnies had by all
Recording show
The great idea
Jamie K thank you so much
Are you Jeremy
No last name
Thank you so much
Everybody knows they're trained wrong
Scrap
Great Neck
The number 42
Number 42 for the answer to the question
Switzer
Technocrat
Heroin
Library library
That sounds like a great Bounty Hunter name in The Apocalypse
Jen the librarian kind of got that
Pioneer Book for a big guy kind of feel to it you know you think of librarians real cool and calm
Right
Jordan
I know that you tried
To emulate
One of my signature sound
I'm going to go and I don't appreciate it I apologize
Dick through your your little no no no
I don't want to give you what you want
If we got two different Jersey
Naked people dancing around the pole of some sort
Now we got three
I think my shirt
I think we figured it out
Two different messages
You run the environment or whatever it was
And the other one said save the environment or something along those lines
Just going to go out on a limb and say that the negative
I think the differences are probably
Yeah I would say
Secondary
Compartment in the mailbag
From the show that
Send again
Appreciate that
We've done a lot of episodes
Remember most
I don't even know that Michelle episode
And now
Yoda
Bauer head
Are we doing that as we enter the episode
Starts off the show
Call
Sure does not get through calls until a bit into the episode
What is normal
Clear
Is saying that they're going to put out
He's going to put it out
Would cause some
Friction
Because he doesn't believe vaccines are good
But Trump is saying that this vaccine
Perfect
Where are we going to take calls
Where we're going to go
Specific issue because
Play the clip of trump here in just a moment
He has come out and said we're going to have a very powerful
Perfectly
Well
Yeah no s***
Abidjan
Absolutely
Sugar water and people
Oh boy
I mean it's a metaphor
That's a metaphor though
Expression
Sugar water later
Talking about
Using 2nd area because
I have a serious question
Do any of the colors
Correctly point out that Bill Gates already has the vaccine
He's had it for years
No it's a real problem
Is that like easy
They were Trump's doing
This is going to cut off Bill Gates at the past try cuz Bill Gates who got his vaccine
Trouble has no kind of water.
Alright just part of the long game also
It's just that
This is all a bad long game
Trump supporting it
Wow we never considered that the way out of their antivirus
Actually a placebo
Trump is giving people
Basically an injection of nothing
Cuz you know stupid
To get it
Well of course
Propaganda outlet with a creative way to get around the fact that we
Will kill you
Oh okay
Tries to sell it that way
Probably won't
Alex knows what's going on you got it from high-level sources
Show me the number out of the bottom of the hour on call specifically
The president
So a position on this is really interesting this is black magic
And I'm not into it
He says Trump is endorsing this vaccine
Microchip the Bill Gates wants to put in
You know that was his way of rationalizing
In order to bake the Democrats into admitting that they wanted everybody's guns and then nothing would happen
It is described as what he's describing as Blackmagic using like
It is unfortunate intrusion of reality even by the god-king
Is an invitation to retreat further away from reality you know like
Even your
F******
Unimpeachable leader
Who's always right and perfect about everything is saying that we need a vaccine and even then you're like
He's magic trick
Trying to
What's the strongest
That's just really sad
Sad yes but it also makes Alex
About the Lord of the Rings
Done
Using
Endorsing vaccine
It's the same
Not literal
Restart
Search of the dark lord
Our those on the Earth
Powers
Controlled
Allegory
Stop
Original Satan has been destroyed
But that's
Did he read the silmarillion what is he talking about
So big bad guy
The beginning of those dudes do the graves at the credit
B b b b b
Talking about
Prequel
Video stop of the battle where the ring
Cut off the finger
I know
He's ever read
I would be shocked if he read the silmarillion I'm a huge fan of his Lord of the Rings and I made it through about 3/4 B
I was like
So I would I would avoid it
Yeah
Or just something that's all
What are the rings
General Williams
William Barr Coronavirus
Cruising
Good
Virginia land honest
Really
Yeah man
And then I'll bring up the hill
Started World Order
Doesn't matter
Do
DNR Russia is putting out a placebo Alex thinks it's cool
Dictator is now lying to her country
I'm injecting them with something that honestly
You don't know what's in it
It could be whether or not it is
But he's not
Is it sugar water
Cold
Super water
Covid-19
Exam good
Yeah
Sugar water
Kill more people
No big deal
The problem is the Bill Gates
Has
Ideas
He has these things but he wants to do like what
Microchip
At the same time it will also hit a off switch
Junior Burger
Morrison
I mean
There's something sell me on those
Turn off
Chromosome
Number 8
I'll look into what chromosome number
Chromosome number 8
We don't have chromosome
Alright
Marshall
You're lucky
The more power
Stronger
This this is a little much
How to tell when somebody so transparently full of s***
Just nonsense you should have that when you're in 3rd grade that you played that Clifton
This is what it sounds like someone somebody is just so obviously full of s***
Additions that are associated with known as chromosome 8 monosomy
Which is a very rare situation where there's a deletion of a portion of that
They would normally get from your parents
David Icke
This is all just David Icke said
There's a
That we're basically the argument is
They found something in the PCR test
Border covid-19
They
Portion of
Okay
It's 146 million pair.
I don't know how much this
Call
Actually two versions
Is that the PCR test
Is looking for this thing
DNA
In all human DNA going on
So it's in everybody
So the test is looking for that
Which fails to make sense of why there aren't
Not great
Now the other one is that
For this
So they'll have the positives
Like
Express this in a way that sounds fine coming out my mouth
Are making the argument
Zach
This
River being positive for covid-19
Therefore any cure for covid-19
Or killing
This stretch
Of
Which is chromosome 8 therefore any cure for covid-19
Billete
Turn off
This chromosome
Which is not suffering
The ideas are growing out of this as far as I can tell this all traces back to David Icke
So I don't
I would love for Alex to sit down and talk a little bit about chromosomes
Extended portion of his show
Just name
I don't know about that more than you
I have so many more they're so much better
He was like
I'm still work better cuz I have more chromosomes than about where he does later say that he's chromosome 8 is particular
But I got to go and covid-19
He's working as a surrogate for Trump
When he's doing this covid-19 denialism
Weird I'm uncomfortable with it
Everything
You have the right about everything in this is also not the first time he ran
He's working as a surrogate to put out this b*******
Nonsense about coronavirus
Hey
Right now
You see yourself as a campaign surrogate
We got our orders
And I wouldn't have given those orders
But I've got my order
I'm going to do what I'm told
So whether or not he's definitely about to talk to
Somebody who probably is an unofficial one that's
F****** Rodger cell
Rogers news articles that went around recently they were talking about how
Said the Trump did
All the ballots from Nevada
You know take over if the election
Rodger Dunn
Hey guys I was taking out a contact
Media
Bastardized
Mike Tomlin
Symptomatic contact
Ignored
I said that
Insurrection act and martial law
Only if there was blatant
Evidence of fraud I did not
Martial law if he lost an honest election not ever said
Anything
Clarification
Unreal
Contacts
That this voter fraud was happening
Power there's a fair election
Is definition of a fair election is one where Trump win
His play to happen is if Biden wins
Which is what
Your
Yeah it dismissed contacts
Rodger complains about how poorly treated by the media
Experiencing quite a while
The media
4 years
Or reporter
Any reporter
Any publication
Call you
When you are
You know when you're writing about you
And that has not happy
We are awake
Opportunity
What is the signify
They're worried about
Maria matters Soros
Houses eating
So
Could you reach out to stone for
It's interesting to me that Rodger would be at
Complain about people reaching out for ComEd
Like I've never seen a war story
Sandra Flores
Bulshit contract Amarillo literally works for the
It's a foreign concept
Brutal
Like that like he's
What a f****** a******
Yeah I hate it
Claims the Trump White House
Ideas
This vaccine stuff
They say
No Doubt
What do you think about that
Supreme Court
I don't know about that but I do know that we have people
Who are
Decided
So now what
Caribou
Conspiracy
Responsibility
I don't know about that
In conversation
Alex
Because you needs Rodger to be on board with this
General
But
Onto Republican members at work
That's fine
Still have an opinion on it because
To the case at hand
There's an interesting thing going on and if you want him to
I want to say what I want to say about for the Rodger Stone defense fund
But I don't need anymore
That's fair
And I just get that
Willing to take
Some exposure whatever
Alex's fake best friend anymore
To go off on a conspiracy about the
Supreme Court being blackmailed or whatever he like this
Too much iron would care
You know
Harris has been administered
Absolutely
Rodger helping Alex
Not what he's doing anymore
You know just having
What is the personality of Joe Biden
Extreme
He's always wanted to be president
Is it a person having a conversation with someone
Without the need to be like
Yeah you're right
Rogers Public Schools in Paris
To agree with Alex about that narrative
Yeah I'm going to run for president
Your fear of Hillary Clinton is correct
This report is being blackmailed
They tell you
MO
That's so annoying how stupid they are about that stuff because Roberts is opinions that can all really boils down to
Why better
You wrote this in crayon
I want to agree with you but you did such a bad job when I die
History is going to Supreme Court as the dumbest
And then you can sue and like better
That's what I want from you children Rodgers
Babe you're in such a
I kept very clear light
Like yeah
Stupid
In jail
He's probably like
So
And I go through his calls finally
Make a call from a guy named liberal
Who
Text doesn't like
He doesn't enjoy too much
Going to be one of them because
He's he's coming from a place where
Man
Bill Gates
Together
Hey Alex
Administration
6 billion dollars
David
In my opinion you cannot donate
Organization
Where who
Actually one of the members
It isn't a relationship strong relationship
Putting off again
Each other
So I'm going to go
That sounds bad
Alex's
Your friends close and your enemies
Closer remember couple times
It's just like the trouble in the past
Fresno memory
Ministration
Donated all this money
Bad
It should be mandatory
He said it's a problem
This is weird
This is very strange
Yeah I'm very confused
Through the prism of calls it opposed
The covering the story
Because you can have this in the conversation with call her less weight
Lying about that
Conversation
But then again he did just say the Trump is lying Direct
Yeah
So there's that question to actually believe it
Yeah why is he lying
I guess if you never realized it's to pacify the population just like
Putin Putin is doing
So you're saying that you're
Dear fearless leader is lying to pacify the population
Bright
In order
Very very strongly against
If it works
Trump
Might be part of why
He might be too far for him to go
He's dancing around this like this
Forward
Yeah
Is lies about his lies now are not as compelling as my lies about
Trump putting out water down and like that
Being
Proud
Sure
Even with the a exposition
Something like this is to get the World Health Organization off his back or whatever
Do it
To get people vaccinated their requirements like you can't
Go to school unless you've been vaccinated
There's a problem for yeah that's
I don't know if he'll be able to get around that but Intel there are like
Parts of society that you can't
Gauges
Healthcare
That really sucks because
It next year
Because they said we're not going to have a
He's lying about that in order to get elected
There's not going to be a vaccine everybody knows there's not going to be back
So the only way that the only time here doing which that
Is in the Bible Administration so they can
Need to go back to take a nap
About their anti-vax
Lenny's
It sounds like how I get what's going on
Prepare
You're the CEO of my Patriot Supply survival
Can sales more product
Yep and her to make the most out of this
You know you really got you really got a hike
50 MI
Money
Music
No conservative or Christian
Score
Call Google
Spell that day
A little more
But your suntan
This is just meant to create an intense amount of fear surrounding possibilities of the election
Your money is worthless after the election
Money now and maybe Trump will win
You're almost
Or lose it all
Boy survival food
Call
This guy
Worried
Walton New York
Call Charlie doing
What you think about the Holy Spirit
Store radio
We can't
Seattle Pier
His call has nothing to do with that question
Oh boy
I heard that
You're freaking me out
You bet it is
This shows
Weird
The working together and out
Maybe the Holy Spirit
Another return
Forum
You belong
Milan
Children
You belong in the universe
You will conquer the universe
You belong
Little bit
Esoteric
So there's no Clear Eyes Full heart can't lose in the universe
Everybody knows it.
Gotta Beach over saxophone
Weird Cheeto Chihuahua
I'm sick of the b*******
Trump is trying to pacify the Patriots
Give me some people who are getting through the mountains that are not into trouble
Nobody's going to prison
About the upheaval
Guilty of international war crimes
Addition treason
Doing anything or not
Do anything
Sometime
Doing Jones
Skating
Hundreds of thousands and millions
Listen to you
The cutest
Just enough
Okay
Puritas
I would say first of all
Nothing could you listen to Alex
Documents
The four possibilities of the future of technology in the developing world
Revelation type document the way you want to be
The f****** dumb dumbs like how
No that was what was missing in those 11
Was the devil
Who is behind it
This
Caller Wiki represent is the inevitable
Backlash over you has all of these
Been really endemic in the right-wing views.
Fantasies of Retribution that are coming
Qanon stuff is just right for the
Perfectly designed
Appointing two people
To the point where they create an explanation for why
Right going to disappoint
You can never really accept that
You have make you feel really stupid
I mean
A certain percentage of people respond to that frustration
XYZ the way it was supposed to
The Oculus
Guyanese like I think people like Alex
Who is preaching intense amount of islands
That guy
Is part of a plan
Pacify
Who would be
I don't know hunting liberals in the street
Understand
How it is that you can see through some b*******
Suddenly
And then
Be like
Seawell that b******* doesn't absolutely
You're not seen Eliza inconvenience
Has this
It's possible that people used by Trump
To pacify.
Push back
Then uses Alex Alex and Alex
Alex
Play
Dialectic
I learned that from you
Call Zeb
What do you think
You can't take it away from me
Everything
What do you think about Bill Gates
Wow
Baymeadows to commercial
Because he can't handle this
He's like yeah he took Trump took the vaccine away from
Gate to the hint
Based on Alex's on rhetoric
Handle
Show last week
And then remembered it what else
You suck
Perplexed
Anyways
Commercial
Really disappointing
I mean
Psychological psychologist
Stating why are people not calling him on stuff like that
Another guest
Johnny's Place
I'm not sure about that
It's embarrassing for
For both of them
Serious like Frank
The change in society
If you talk to Nick privately I'm
Certainty
Stupid piece of s***
Doesn't know anything about any topic
I'm pretty sure he would be embarrassed to be associated
Twenty-two-year-old internet racist
Personality
Isn't really
Irrelevant
Figure
Embarrassed
Having this conversation
Restorative
Catholic fascist
World
I'm in Alex's world are very much
On a similar project
We're trying
To get to work
The Aviary
Major
Sitting right sort of
To put the word out so that when this
When the globalist
Steal the election
Transpired
Body will be watching and looking
Exactly
Sedan
I think the trick is going
Come in on Election Day
Like you said
Trump is going to win the election
I think it'll be a landslide
Orally
You'll see is that
Days and weeks
Find all of these extra votes
Landslide
By the landslide
Voter fraud
Creating a pre-emptive narrative
Victory outcome of the election
After the election
Call into question
Suspicious the reality
To come to life
Because of this
You're just creating the preamp to track
In order to
, November
Whatever there
If Trump wins
And if you lose
Decry the voter fraud
Yep all these ballots being found everywhere
Trump's the rightful president
Transferring
Just such a bummer is this
Cuz I don't think
But there's no way for them to
Deescalate
I just can't do it
You would think that
And I think for a certain segment
You're absolutely right there is no deescalate
You think about Alex in a lot of
You know times in his life
More severe in the past
6-9 months
And indoctrinated that like
I don't
Think it's impossible
At 9 he could be like
Now we got to go back to our route
Rampaul actually is
He's a he's a real guy in the Senate has proven track record
Jordan
You know like I could
I couldn't it's not letting just like Bill Barr
Hayden and bring up all the Epstein Corrections unless he's doing something that he likes
Thinking he can just be like
Well we look at all the ways that Trump lied to us and failed us
What you can point to
Because they did
You know like
Anymore
And Salvage what you've got
It's very simple
Yes
Stole the election
But what are you going to do
We have the reality in front of us that we have
You cannot try and get the Supreme Court to overturn the election but doesn't matter
The only thing you can do is buy buy survival food keep us on the air
Is going to happen right here on Bandit video to probably
Original
And you could do that there and then I got my arrival
Cool
Coronavirus
Video. Prussia
Exactly.
Austin
Probably would
As a goof
Triad protest for Cary
Outside Alex
We could get a little Lake area
Studio
That's a great idea sounds like
Alex
NSYNC right now
Not too surprising
So clear that it's already
Come of the election that hasn't happened
Another losing this election
No they're losing
You have this presentation like everybody knows the Trump is going to win the election but anybody
H-E-B arrest
That's f***** up
Yep
Commissary
They will not accept
I mean
Why would they care what an election says
One argument against
Them being fashion
Is the day you want to Outlaw the Rival party
That's a really good point they want to do it through the courts
Even if we win this battle
Free things
We have another flight
Succession
Please office if he doesn't leave office now
Ali's office in 2020
We are coming to interrupt because I want to hear that
That party I got bad news about the Nazi party post-world War
I love the way that he puts
We've got another election in 20
Special election
I've heard
Conversations in the past or
Monarchy
It should be Melania Trump
End of the right-wing
AR
Very close to wanting
Our duly elected
Like f****** 1776 we got rid of the king
Jesus
Stinks the Democrat Party is
Because
I mean
Let's imagine
Establishment of the Democratic Party
Brewstew
The only reason
Anybody has any
It's to the left of Rand Paul is because
Nancy Pelosi and the Democratic party is there
Democratic party liberal Democrats
Now you're just Republican lights
As though their policies in the Republican light party or going to change
Interesting
For him
Like a reality-based
Really just the disruption of the apparatus of the Democratic Party
It's not what you want to be able to Outlaw political beliefs
The funding mechanism for
His give a
Uncle
It would be it would be better as a system I think if we had more than two parties
Has little bearing on my feelings bad become an election
I agree with you there as well
Because we currently have a situation where the
Has
God sent him
God literally had to give us
Human being
You know even just the other day
Philly cheesesteak
Silly or something
It's a reminder that this is a real
What we see on the other side
Isn't it amazing that Trump took a picture from selfie
I really want dealing with that Trump
Well I mean you know what I'm saying like he just gets away with it doesn't have to be doesn't have to respond to that like oh yeah
Super deadly
He just doesn't have
Have to deal with that
I don't think you understand the political
Importance
Of a guy
Eating a cheesesteak
And
Myself on fire
Any call
Is a very sincere picture of him
Famously convinces all false Christians that he was sent by God
Interesting
When I hear stuff like that
Far is so
Real, real
Stop Bishop feels like there
Wasted
It's just so funny to imagine them making fun of someone on the last being like Obama
F****** cheese water
Yeah they are
Interesting thoughts
What's about
It is
Current
Not being
Super into everything Trump does
It's Tricky
So long
I mean his website I think was really groundbreaking
The format
Conservative news for
Atlanta
You don't have a lot
Conservative news
Lely it's
Control
What is maybe four about
You're something but lately in the
Circulated that story
Initially about
The troops losers
Urban push there
And even this week there were some really terrible
Is there
Such a shame
We as conservatives are we as
You're probably right wing
We don't really have
Information
Exceptional
You and others
Fair and that is at the right
Way too much in the Matt drudge basket
All boil down to
Figure out
If we want
To keep promoting
A little bit
How can you get rid of
Right now where is with with Nick
I think it's an interesting
Approach trying to say
These rulers now
Trump rumors
Suggestions
Feelings for a little while
Drudge
Do you think he was using better editorial standards I don't understand
Play you still agree with me all the time
Yeah right
It is it is just out
It's not a but for them it's the future is like
It doesn't matter if I 100% respected this person and thought he was a god
He disagreed with me and the way that I think things should be run
So now he's against
Play they love to act
The functionaries who are really easily dismissal
You can just throw out
Withdrawal
And I think it's because
So much of the things
Games that are like
Any idea Trump was going to be
Political figure
He goes back to like
Bill Clinton
Drudge
Media sphere
Non-stop like to the point where I remember specifically
I can see the Drudge
On 911 like I can see it in my head he read it so much
And you can trace a straight line from Judge to so many things but almost anybody like
Beating off The Rush Limbaugh
Headlines
Project Veritas
Okay come from
That came from behind promotion of
Career the large
Andrew Breitbart got his start working for Drudge
Breitbart the publication came from Andrew
So much
Of this
Miss spider web
All of media tendrils
All can kind of
Either directly or spiritually Trace back to the influence of drugs
Which is better
Even if
You should
Save any work
Works for the literal Christian Temple
Because they have to make it personal
Antagonize Judge Too Much
He's not just going to be like
In on the sidelines
Supposedly
He's going to be actively against
Maybe they're worried The Drudge knows
The game
Probably true
About on that front but if I were them to
She's kind of like
Now belittle
No Outlet promote
Very positive and interesting
Revolvers
Exactly who
I've been watching that lately I don't know about you but
Job
I think it my eyes a little bit
Gray publication
I'm not trying to sell it or anything
I'm just saying
How did Joe wow
I don't know what the preoccupation is on the right
With Outlets that have
People
Under fake names are aliases writing them by
Nobody knows who you are
It's just like aggregative
Tons of headlines
It's a very beautiful
What's website
Could have chose a different name for the revolvers already of Music publication
Search for revolver you find out about Stabbing Westward new song
Not concerned
I know this is a real website headlines
These can't be real headlines
Been a long time
I'm not Cinderella and I don't mean to impugn their careers it says I've not heard anything about corn and
Project
I heard about the Stabbing Westward since 1998
Oh man I have to do
No one remembers.
The first headline stories about the Stabbing Westward
Everything old is New Again
Nothing
Turns out it's the same s*** I did 30 years
Years ago what's going on here
Everything old is new dance
I don't think revolver is necessarily covering my genres of music
Music publication
Pacific
Music genres
Vulvar was
Yeah
Complaints about
Fox News
Sure hands because they had an interview with
Newt Gingrich that didn't go well
Right cuz he was lying out of the teeth cuz he started bringing up Soros
And I think it actually brings up a really important point
And even just the other day
Fox News
He got really weird when you can
About
Talk about Cora
Probably
You are the devil
The number 14
City
Is George Soros elected
Left-wing
Android Police
Criminal
Attorneys
Who refused to be
People walk
Just yesterday
Show me back on the street
Water for two different murders
In New York City
You cannot
This problem
Very proud
About what they call
Call Progressive attorney
Anti-police
Pro Criminal
Overwhelmingly elected with George soros's money
Is there a major called
Of the violence were saying
They keep putting the violence
I'm not sure we need to bring to work
I was going to say
I need to be a part of this conversation
Okay
Okay we're going to move on
Holyshit
Gingrich
You know
This is what happened
Fox News
Able to broadcast
Conclusion of their thoughts
Facilitated
Conspiracy meaning
These are easy explanations for all these social ills that all goes back to Soros funding
Of course
Is the fruit of what they have brought into the world
Right now at least recognized
OSHA
This belongs on Infowars
Things to the point where
Are the same thing
Used to be relevant like Newt Gingrich
Better
You're next
Even in an interview with Newt Gingrich on Fox News
It's gone too far
I wonder is there any times in human history before where people have
Spider Noah
And then once what was in the box was released
They were
Have you ever heard of anything
Situation like so there's really no way we could have seen this coming
No I don't I don't know of any metaphor words or Expressions. John
I'm at a loss
Yeah it's it's I think it's the same
As that caller bring him and him having to change the subject
F****** Soros conspiracies
This is your fault
Keep going down this road
Zora stairs
If we lie about it
Bright
Yeah we can't be doing this s***
Just the sort of
Parallel examples
Like the limitations of this game
Just threw
You yourself can tag agency
And not just that but
It's literally just that like
They don't know what to
To do when
What day are sensibly think our allies
Are forced
To deal with reality
Where is there not you know just like you know just like with Alex and
The guy on the phone calls just like
If I am forced to engage with reality
This is all wrong
This is just not how it's supposed
When it happens there like
Now it's
We did not have time to gather phone calls
Because we had a guest appearance on a podcast that will be out eventually do we have to record
Before this
So apologies but we will have some on our next episode
Will be back
If you could please find a local charity or bail Fund in your
Auraria to help out those be
God's work
Omnia on Leah on dvx
I'm Barrel run this I Belong To The City
Alex
I love your work