Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for knowledge
Monica
Knowledge fight
About Alex
Drone
Jordan Jordan
Quick question
Alright
Quick there decided to
Get into indoor apartment composting course so I have ordered a bag of
I'm really just realized
You're just turning into the weird Dad where you're like
I'm going to be in the garage for the next 8 hours now metaphorical garage
Very excited about it
Plays that were used to play whenever he's trying to attack Joe Rogan
Snake Farm
Waterbar you are susceptible
Songs and purchases
Like if there was a ad company that was specifically targeted towards you
They could find a way to like heck you completely worm car
Daughter 121
My partner and I went out for a very long
Walk along the Lakeside did you know that we have a lake in Chicago
Every time we travel
View
It's not far away
We go other places that if we just decided to do in
Chicago we could do
It's ridiculous
Pretty gross
Did the dirty like
The Edge there where you can see the city skyline while still having the bend in the lake around you so it
Looks like the city is almost
Island
It is closed
Waves look beautiful you couldn't see inside the water of the lake and I'm also going to have
Colony of worms
I contain multitudes you are you are a very complex person
The breakdown
We're going to be talking about 18th September 2020
Ruth Bader Ginsburg Supreme Court Justice passed away
Nation would be the word I would choose
But maybe in a slightly different way than a lot of other folks
I'm not entirely sure I'm worried about
I'm worried about political actors Behavior
I'm worried about
It doesn't feel good no
No it doesn't
For me just because now everybody's where I am
All the time everybody's very emotional
Confused unhappy
If I mean you're all in my world now welcome to the Thunderdome
Greater appreciation
This is all about me I don't know if you've noticed
Are you because
What happened then
Because why wouldn't you cry
It's great
A special Saturday show
Breaking down the news and what have you
Bunch of nonsense
Real Murderers Row
Terrible gas
But
Does not
Probably on short-term
We got
Norm pattis
Lawyer Robert Barnes
The best legal minds of Our Generation
Personal lawyers
Natural
So
Show
There was
Note
However started doing this thing called like election countdown or whatever and it's
Show no
Troyer that sometime right
And so because the major breaking news
Alex
So we've got that we've got Alex's time with Harrison Smith
On the night of 18th
And then I was a show on the
He's going to be
Eggsplosion
Alright
Okay
Lorraine and Harrison
Motor is a war crime
True
Beyond Golf
I make my career
We're listening to this horrible
I guess
We should do
Jordan Asia City flower blossom
Text Aaron
Play Darren Warriors
Warrior in congratulations
Journal about walk
You're not the only one
Are you very much
Is you could find your way next to a large body of water
Water with your
You're just not supportive
First thing I say and you just
You're right.
Donate the Goddamn money
Take your criticism and it's totally fair I am not support
Trash
Value Vet
The lamp
Love's
Gloves
Australian election
Love
How about somebody else
Oh boy
Total stud cherry cobbler accomplished
I just think you shouldn't
Compliment Hitler that
I understand
The Soto
Music
LG High School
I know I know
But consider how much each evening is lifespan
It seemed pointless
Harrison Smith breaking news
Welcome ladies and gentlemen to the Infowars
2020 election
Countdown covered my name's Harrison Smith
And
Breaking news we have for you news that
Just came out minutes ago
Justice
Ruth Bader
Ginsburg
Died
Supreme Court Justice Ruth
Bader Ginsburg
Castaway
At the age
Of 87
This is just
Breaking minutes
NPR says
Justice Ruth
Bader Ginsburg
The demure Firebrand who were in her 80s
Cultural icon
Died Friday
Announce
Sing the cause
Complications from metastatic cancer
Why are you citing NPR
Don't you hate MPR
Weird
To make sure that we monitor them
You're supposed to believe that they're the enemy
Guess all people about Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg was too good to pass up.
For the Christian devil doesn't mean you can't
Stringy
Harrison has some standards that you'd like to express about
Recovery
If you think that
Court jester
Just died was
Antonin Scalia
You remember the
Joy
With which the left
And liberals celebrate
Weird
We don't celebrate this death or any day
Here's where I'd like to play Supercut of Alex screaming about how she's burning in hell
Create
Behave throwing counter
If you say that to me to my face I'm throwing hands
Kind of
Dignified Behavior
Immediately
We don't celebrate this death or any death
We do however
Recognize that this is
A massive
Opportunity
For Trump
Itsfunneh
The the currency of the far-right we would never do this
But here's as doing it that's what they do we're not going to celebrate this but we're excited
What are we
So there's a perm
Final statement
Ginsberg put out
Becomes a hinge
Upon which
Harrison Smith
Has his coverage rely on
Now as she was
Dying
Just days before her death
MPR
Article
Says
Strength
Ginsberg dictated this statement to her granddaughter
Quote my most fervent wish
Is that I will not be
Replaced
Until a new president
Install
Interesting choice of words
President being installed
CIA
Harrison Smith can go ahead and just f*** himself stranded very regularly used to describe the attention of someone
Position of leadership
Particularly presidency
If you just Google the terms install and president you'll find tons of articles that are based on press releases about
Things like Larry
Being installed as the president of the stock market
Hora 2019 announcement
Of the Minnesota Dental Association
If you can sell dictionaries the reason that this term is used regularly about heads of organizations is because it denotes that they're sending
That position requires a special ceremony
Like an inauguration
Grammatically
I think of like some stickers they put in their man cave
And that's the point that they'll get somebody
Put him in there
Is technically true which is why we
There's a Supreme Court Justice that has to stand there and be like I swear you in
The word in this context doesn't mean that
To see Harris Harrison play this game
When it snowed here is Harrison is damn boring
He is
Trash is so bad at this
I don't care for him at all
And I was just sitting here thinking about all right
You're playing this weird word game
It's broken transparent you're not interesting
He saved the ship with that
I will be joined later in this
Is program a by Alex Jones
Who has some breaking news
Who Maybe
Appointed
5 president
Court Wendy's names off of
Shortlisted
Last week
So all right
Maybe be drunk
Yeah they'll be some kind of Firework
Harrison Smith Fathead
This guy is just
Is the f****** vocal patterns of
Alex
But in a very boring
And uninteresting way
Like the way he goes like
Coming up and
A vend
And so that's why
Internet
Alex is made
I hosted is that evening show
But it I would not be surprised if pretty-much
All of his experience
In this Arena come from Infowars
If you will
Subway
Opportunity
Nonsense annoying
When it's coming from someone like Harrison
Course he was
DieHard leftist and was sort of the ringleader of the Liberals there on that cord
And was instrumental in making many decisions that we here on the right
Which consider
Severely damaging
Hugh
Our country
Female
I'm not going to stay
I'm not going to say anything bad
Not going to make any joke
About it
Not going to play any
Peaceful songs
The Wizard of Oz
Do no such thing
You're not here to celebrate
Death
Okay
She's the wicked witch
Without actually doing it
I'm not going
To celebrate her death
Yeah I'm going to sarcastically celebrate her
Difference being very classy by
Intimating how much
Very annoying
Somebody a little bit more
From him it's just
How do you can condescend
Like
Find myself
Eating boring people at more than 40%
Nonsense least entertain me
That I'm going to hate you
Your policies your beliefs are important
There's a special circle of hell
How to cover the story
Because it's breaking
Trump speech going on
For the
President-trump
At podium now
And we are eagerly awaiting the moment where
Maybe somebody in the
Krowd
Sees a tweet
And shouts this out
Or maybe an
Assistant Donald trumpkin
Sneak up and whisper in his ear
That Ruth Bader Ginsburg
Has passed away
And maybe homemade
A statement
About it that would be a
Ideal because
There's one thing we know about Trump
The cuff
Statements
Are often more truthful
And certainly more
Appropriate
Exciting than his
Prepared
So I need directions
There
Was him saying
Please tell us what to think
And if I do say what I want to say and it's wrong you're going to be mad at me and I don't want anybody to be mad at me
They're probably more eyes on this normal
He's trashed
Dingdong Outlet
This dweeb Affair Harrison
Lose an inability to really
Is the moment the news head and he said it Alex should have come barreling and upgraded like tossed him to the side middle
Totoro
Harrison listen to Big Time
Rookie
Exactly
Florida
Yeah
When there's more people watching obviously you have an expectation or belief
You can monetize
Impressions are everything in Harrison should not be your first impression
The Friday night we got a
The full crew
In the house
Alex Jones is in the house
Of course we have
Norm pattis on the line at 2
Breakdown everything
All of the all of the
Incredible
Events that will now be put in
Into motion
Now the truth
Bader Ginsburg
Passed away
At the age
AB 87
For everything that we do all of these great gas
All of the crew
Myself
Alex Jones we are also
Solely
Caillou the viewers
The Listener
The supporters the info Warriors out there
Infowars store
Dot-com
And taking advantage
Embark great sale
The emergency election sale
A total blowout
Adult
Is not a call to action
Style
Yeah I just can't imagine worth
The time so I'm not going to help
Blowout
Abdul the Easter sale going on right now
An emergency for sale
Eastern emergency
Business
Just by virtue of the fact that you knows what he's doing is trying to make a rationalization
The truck needs to immediately put someone in before the election
The average life
With pancreatic cancer
Weather
He's going to get a Darth Vader live
Knology
He's at Liberty
Kept her alive
5 days weather
She dyes that is going to be like throwing
Can oxygen
Flamethrowers in a firework
The left is going to go
They're going to go
Add
Obviously
Trump
No
That process will begin
In reality
The Democrats would nominate a judge
Floor of the senate for a vote situation
The Senate would of course
Block the nomination until the election of the next president it's not even like something
Abstract terms
It's very clear
What's this place out everybody so much
I hate everyone so much
Everybody everybody who is like
Years ago makes me want to throw up throw up
I'm saying this
Because I think you're right
Yeah
Therefore you have an expectation
That like if you were called out for doing exactly the opposite
Politician now everyone's right
With anybody on the left who is like
No we don't need to do that because he didn't do that
F*** you
You're being hypocritical he was just lying
You're the one who's like
If it be situated what they're doing is they're saying it's this situation happens again we've already set to precedent
We can never
I'm doing great
Great I'm doing great
Patriots
People like Alex people like Harrison
There
You know they're above it
Caribou
Relishing
I talk to you later White House adviser as well.
And I said
Support
I can keep her alive
Adrenaline
A growth hormone a blood
Transfusion
Her wish
The go-ahead.
The firmament
When she helped me through
That blood sacrifices
Talk about
Energy
Obviously meet her maker in the Ninth Circle
Haiti's today
Roketa bensberg
U.s. Bank
Fashion gods and when I go
Obvious
Ruth Gator Ginsburg
Then I have been looking at all the news today
Find somebody with a better take on this
And insane and everybody is
Scrambling cuz
I couldn't deal with Alex because that's
Your job's right and so I was so disappointed
But nobody had anything good
Hearing Alex say that this was a blood sacrifice
It warmed my heart has Burg
Yes
Thank you
Nobody even into nobody said that Mitch McConnell probably killed her with bloating
Now that I know that it's a blood sacrifice to get the boat out
Portable brother
Discussing his inside information
Lawyer
Literally 45 minutes
Rise and shine
Starting
And I said what's the word I said
Tony
Well so
Yeah
People are stupid
Rising Barrett is going to be
He's pretty regular on this point
This episode
And at the beginning of the 19th
Although
Something doesn't up changing
Supporting Merrick Garland
Also is a little bit Unsure how Trump is going to play this
Trump speech
And mine
And I said listen
Murder game
And I said we'll come on tomorrow
Laura
Gmail
And said go ahead
Supercharged
All of
The Democrats
You know out though
Had to go crazy song
4 Savage Daddy
Lowell Library
Okay
So yeah that was a really good eulogy
Even though murder my car
Suggested
I don't know maybe
Which he's mixing up his mythologies there but also was not the cold one
She doesn't even need to worry about it
I bet you I bet it was too hot
A very long
Maybe Norm pattis got on the phone or Deanna Lorraine came in
Harrison Smith blood sacrifice
Bucking pad is going to come with glue
For the second time you can give me the light
I will be out of there shortly
Yep so we jump in the show
And weird
Wow
Is Forrest Gump is going to look like
Somerset
Literally
God damn you
Realized
Finding out is in
A rally
He's at he's at like a rally until the Tiny Dancer was playing on the speakers
It's the temperature
Meijer in Hayden kind of way
Basically
7 literally the next day open your show with Beast
Is that you want stupid we can a Supreme Court Justice
Jesus Christ
Situation
Because it's
Definitely one of the things this
You can most easily monetize
Obviously
For the knife
In the year of 2020
Generating an opinion
It has been nauseated
Piercing
Ignorant
Because you already know that
Validation
Israel
It's not going to get any better.
Temperature in
Air conditioning
9 degrees you're sweating
Cuz as soon as I get on here and there
Hundreds of thousands of people
Million
Regular Show
Stop
Year has not disappointed
It's definitely not been here that I have been more disappointed in literally everyone on the planet than ever
Ever
No it hasn't
Florida casket
I don't know
Already
And it's just funny
Neither of them are his lawyer in the Sandy Hook case anymore but still coming on
Wrong with people
Because this
This year's
This point
And our ancestors
Try now and our very selves
Soon as I go on air
All my old
Ultimate Muscle
Because it's a war
Something wrong with you
Weird
Explanation
Into my two former lawyers are going to come
Yeah
Fighting the literal Christian devil in just to prove to you that we are fighting him I am going to make little
Real demon sounds
Suspicious don't worry about it
Can I get on
Whatever whatever anybody's like stage Health in stand-up comedy
Pumped full of adrenaline and then you get off at your Journal that goes away in your I still feel like s***
One of the things that I noticed regularly
Getting onstage in front of a bunch of people
He's a really effective hangover cure
Whatever the adrenaline boost and and
The feeling that you have of the pressure if it takes a ways
Totally later
Is to drink
Wow you're onstage hangover
Really good afterwards
Danny's Auto Saturday night
Maybe he's been away
Stop music
Mikado
And Trump
That's a no-brainer
Words
Gator
And our most fervent wish
Is that I not
Until
New president
Easy install
How old is the purple used
Stalled
What did
No no never
President can't be installed
Nope words don't mean anything except for what I want that debate
This is good
This work
Wordplay Tate
Theory
Kim Jong on in
Whatever wants
Kim Jong uninstalled
North Korean supreme leader
Let's see if my memory is
Who's grey radio
Wow so good
You have years ago
Install
Very classy
Classy Chassis
Stuff
Words
To know that no matter how eloquent your argument
If there's a crowd of people just chanting in
Install
Right you are
Yahoo matter what your argument is out there screaming
You know okay fine I guess that's what you got
Install over and over again
Keep yelling that dictionary definition of install
Alex there's more than one
So I had told him it would probably going to be
In that back a little bit more General
I'll bet my
If a woman
As long as
I just don't
Boat life
Saying if you think it could be a woman
Which is fine
The night before said that inside sources from the White House we're saying
Barrett
Right now
He is a little more General
Seems like you would continue
Being like the word is
Pretty fast in her favor
I mean we've already had blood sacrifice
Even stranger because Alex suggest
B maybe it's possible there Ruth Gator Ginsburg
A weeks
They wanted to wait
We could
Hospital
Close
McConnell
Because
Walmart
Totally understand why people retreat
Conspiracy theories now
Right now I'm imagining living in a world where
Ruth Bader Ginsburg with Dedham
Chicago
I guess I would ask why
This argument doesn't hold water
You wanted to push it forward in order for it to be more of a tense situation
If it's April
.
For your buck
Scalia died and it was a big tension situation
Especially during an election cycle primaries or any
Mitch McConnell doesn't have the time to organize everybody
Cuz if you had those extra 4 weeks
Yeah I'm sure
By the time this episode comes out
Course not
Recognizes
The even he's not so stupid that he doesn't realize I
I'm going to suggest that she's been dead for a month
Ever reason
Doesn't support it
Conclusion but
Good
But now that I know she's already been dead for a month
That's even more
Akon Ginsburg
This is what we get from Schumer and Pelosi if they had a month to think about it buddy.
Who needs an Okanagan
Source
Secret
Silly
Oh good anyway Alex
He's really
Enjoying shiting on
The dad
It's part of an anti-human
Pilobolus
Dollar Oregon
You just talkin s***
Yep
Clarence Thomas needs to get out of there
So they can replace him with someone
Effectively
4 of 9
Call mickley stupid
Text Thomas got to go app
In Antarctica
I don't know
In talking about this
But he can't remember his name
Thomas
Bad guy
I do
Kelis.
He's always imitating
Grover Cleveland
Shelia.
Bohemian Grove
Obviously
Definitely murder
So big I could never forget his name
Tobacco down
To Ruth Gator Ginsburg
I mean
Railway
Define descender
Happy birthday
I'm all out
Women's empowerment
Establishment
Two channels
National
When You Believe
Any days equivalent to murdering babies after they're born
Isn't that position we're not going to
Change their mind unless they're
Internally motivated to do so
Nothing you can say is going to be effective
Nope they're gone
Damn it's just gone
Ginsburg and
You know
She's a demon she's in hell now all of us
Sure
Not
Like
Bitching you relieved
Yeah
Mao Zedong died in 1976
Yeah and his dad was like Hey listen
The greatest communist leader in the Otherworld just died man the Berkshires have one
Years old
Year away from God
Child Isaac true Order release
It's like a weight has been what I don't I heard it mild died
Because I am my ancestors chirp
When I heard about guide I thought I got to get my blanket
Call man
So Norm comes
Why I wouldn't be
The Southern dish
New York Mets
Surprise moving Navy craft
Make a move
Donald Trump
Distracting
Seizing the narrative
Someone
Donald Trump
About
Until you had about coming in
And going
Then brought up
Wanted to have replaced
Amy
Tony Bear
Why was
Confusing
Why is
Norm pattis having a meeting with someone
I don't know
If any of that is true I'm not stuck
I'm not Stokes at anybody's in those positions where they can have those connections
That is the Eternal question
That we will never know Coney Barrett
Is
The choice
The cheese
The front-runner
Like
Yeah yeah she's religious she's a Christian
B never say that about a Muslim or a lot
They only think it's a problem
Yeah but
Democrat
QRS become more evil
Overtime
How I think this
Loepsie reform
You know I wish I knew I liked
We no longer have it
Values
Call about idea
Power
Demography
Demographic
Democrats
An emerging majority
And decide
I think what happened was the Democrats
That's exactly what he said
He said they're going with the emerging
Power
And that is
Bummer for Norm
I mean
Is a lawyer
You can just if you can pass the bar it doesn't matter if you're not
Makes me really worried
I was very
Peterbilt
Courage
Four districts in
Because I think that it's
Some level it wouldn't
Surprise me
Breck the arrest
Or various
Amun-ra
The same people
Traveling from
The city
Condo for whatever
Forman Mills
Vons brother
Publicly
Defense fund
To really work on that
Going to happen
Disturbed me about that patterns are what
Charged with sedition
Any reason to believe
This is the case
The idea that all of these protesters in various cities are the same people going around
Of course that's
We're not responsible protesters in your city
Saving yourself
You're saving the entire country cuz those protesters would just go to another city and bother other people Dan
Pretty disturbing
Kind of thinking to have
Sonoran sucks
I don't care for him
And now you got Alex's put a lawyer
Buy Barnwood we got from Bart
Clear now
He withheld information
The dire nature
He was clearly in far worse
Turn the night light on
Whether she was
Trying to
You stay alive or
Publicly
Be seen as being alive until
After the election is what
Some people who
The timing of the
The disclosure of
This was a meant to be election influence
We'll never know the
The full truth
Because they were able
Information about her health
What's so secret there's a cover-up
So you're saying that
The Democrats
Have maybe been Weekend at Bernie's in
Ruth Bader Ginsburg
I mean that's one reading you could take other comets
North North
Dead for awhile, guy
He's a lawyer
Just not good
Recovery
Ruth Bader Ginsburg
Over the past year
Hyper focused on how situation
I don't know how much of a cover-up of the severity of her health issues
There is considering all these headlines about her going to the hospital over and over again
If she goes to the hospital the entire f****** new system breaks down and everyone's like
Everybody's holding their breath cuz we're going to the hospital again
True
Bart predictions
It's going to be a woman
Tom Cotton
No
Slightly different
The guy would be
Menomonee and now there's report sets
Today the cheese
Easily
She's a cuban-american daughter of immigrants
Spanish in English from Miami
Play well-regarded
Conservative
On the court
Comes from that tour
Conservative tradition
So she did
Ron Ely
Fort Collins
Turn down her
Okay
That's weird to
We got it
That's alright
Are there any more racist lawyers in Colorado
Democrats
And if we get a Cuban Zone
Buck Oliver Barrett
Yeah why not
Amy
Tony Barrett
She's just as conservative
He's a beautiful Latina
What are we doing
What are we doing what are we doing
Tokenism
Barnes
What you saying is true or not
Cuz
I didn't care
Pretty compelling reasons why Amy Coney Barrett
Should not be on the Supreme Court
The the playoffs
Tippi humor
Alex
I think Barrett
Most nominations but I'm not
Bear attack
Beard is make
The effect that she won't she's that you don't accuse her
Fell from a decision where the Pope
Which I don't know which means
When did rulon abortions
Exactly
Come out on immigration
That's completely the opposite of how they were discussing her face
Okay
This is so this is where we get into the situation that we've described a million times
Exclusive
Group right
Okay
All Christians are fighting now the Muslims guess who we hate Catholics
It's not hard to read this coming
I would say that
Pope would have a difficult time controlling
Those Supreme Court
If one person recuse themselves using
Everything
So I would say that that makes you
That is effective as a Supreme Court Justice if you're going to
Yourself
Only rule on things
Pet My Religion doesn't have a stance on
My religion is Catholicism notorious for not having a stance on literally everything
Yeah
So I drop being real smart
And I think that this is makgeolli
The other problem
Lockdown
So the
Intelligence
Owning certain
Stimulus benefits and the rest is
People started to realize
They're real economic
Real social Harms
Author of what
Of the lockdown today
More dangerous than
I've been covid
So do you understand why that's stupid
Sony re
Patricia
Trump smart
Because then people will start feeling Economic Consequences of the lockdown
Created at least partially or
Maybe even mostly Shoreline Highway of a Steelers
Taking away a lot of the people's motivations the calves are protesting
Virus outbreak
Much faster much less death much less
Economic consequences
Dropping smartphone
We could have had an election that was a referendum on
Trump's surprisingly perfect handling of a global pandemic
What if we have gotten through this all fine people would have been like
Wow I guess he is a good president he got us through this pandemic that would have rolled along to re-election
Killed hundreds of thousands of people
Purposely in order to teach them a lesson about not getting uppity about wanting s***
Can work you idiots I'll teach you please how to do your job if it kills me
Really weird
Rationalization
What you're talkin about like a really smart
To deprive people of something
Bad
You know what I'm saying.
Man
UA doesn't seem like the bar is as hard as they described it must not be either that or you don't have
Just think about anything else ever
Maybe you're in you're in
Like I said Murderers Row
This dude
I don't know what the f***** going on but
Is all over Infowars these days
Alright
Xander is
Grateful
Great talk show host
And writer and researcher
He's on the road
Chicago
How do you miss that
I do love to go see Alexander
You know it
In the city
7 groundhog Trail
We would have had to go buy tomatoes
What's that expensive
Holly Farm to face it is I don't know what the f*** is going on
This dude cuz he's terrible
Is
He's a little bit more interesting than like Harrison Smith
Wako super
Alero
Like
Harrison be like a cardboard cutout
But I don't know why he's all over Infowars
The last couple months
I don't know what the deal is I don't know if he has some sort of a contract or
Anything it's just it's noticeable
All the time oh wow
And
Yeah
You got some ideas
Abortion
Got the blood sacrifice all right
Sacrifices
Now BMO
Erection
In American
History
Whether or not
Millions of
Children
Continue to get aborted or not
The waxes go
Super violin
Supreme Court before the
We really got it
Materials because
Ennui
You've never seen a West O'Farrell
And when we are threat
Takeaway
Their blood.
And that is the abortion
So
The blood sacrifice
What do you think
Icing
Empowers the globalist or whatever
Function or whatever
Then you need to leave
You can't be a part of this you can't take part in the American largesse the free-speech rights that are
Guaranteed by the government
Use our roads
No because you know that exists because of blood sacrifices to the devil
You can't leave here
It is wanting to fight back against
And if you don't want to live in reality
Then go somewhere where you can live in your reality don't make me live your fakeness
There's a thought experiment
First-year philosophy class
Thought experiment
I think.
Everything operates really well people there are largely
Good
Point everyone when they're like
18 or whatever they get
See what goes on in this secret room the only reason that these societies able to function as
Because one child is getting kicked out of them
Constantly forever
Doctor Who episode is well
You approach it from an ethical position and what can you do
You can only lead you can't take part in this Society
Or whatever
Death of everybody else
Generally speaking the correct position is too late you can only afford to live by your own
Principles
To try and make a rational rationalizes like
The needs of the many outweigh the few so this is so I'm fine with this is a
Ridiculous argument
If you are applying it to other people without their knowledge
You know like taking the kid and killing all of the people in this life
Society
Operate
If it didn't somehow give them something they want it we're so
To be in power or
I have our society function in the
Therefore
Alex
Read if you do I mean more like
Also it's a bulshit thing for them to say anyway if you really believe that abortion was a blood sacrifice
That happens to 50 million babies a year
And your
On the f****** phone talking to Alex Jones
UF
No
Moral principles whatsoever making up that b*******.
You like that you have
Is facilitated by
You're complicit
Unlikely unless you lyrics
Stop
Just go it's silly
Go on get out of
About
Sharpay needs control history
That's why they're all over the University
History
And Alex is very very interested in this
Very easy
So fascinated by you
Oh no
They want to rewrite it
It was the
The Bible
The southerners it was
You know the right wing
Authoritarian
You guys are filled over
100 million
People
You know I don't know
That's a scary place
Place to go
Yeah there may not be any
I got a Subway
About how
Increase
Security
And stop because their tongue people were willing
The dye for
Yeah there
People who are willing to die
Abortion to the Lone Wolf
Maybe thousand
Good luck
Houses
Is he your lunch break is
Need to make sure that your lawyer taking your lunch break I have nothing but disrespect for Allie Alexander
And so I don't mind him being treated this way
It's rude if I were him I would not put up with
It's rude to eat on the air.
Yeah the doughboys
Somebody on live broadcast
Respond
Batman with your f****** mouth full
Rude
Could you please stop eating
I think Alex
Subway
Yeah I think
Honestly honestly
Honestly
Like honestly
Feces
Medium bad texts that I've read about
News guy
Real failure problem
Romy was on on the 18th for a short. Of time
Things got real
Sacrifices
Perfect
Donut
Wooden Gray
Conversations with his two former lawyers
Reveals
So much
Just completely
Compared
With fashion
You know what that's probably smarter I think really doesn't have to worry about places he's not allowed to practice law
Hippies in the fashion frizzy
Great American Law Center whatever
Criminal
Barnes go on Stefan molyneux
All the time
He's clearly up to no good
Norm is more just a sort of shady lawyer
Conversations
Dignified Behavior
Surprising because it probably will play out like this
Ferrets nomination will be
Torpedoed by the fact that she's a Catholic
Isn't that hilarious
I mean
I don't think
Probably from just like a utility standpoint
Somebody who's on record as saying that they have to recuse themselves
In any matter that the pope has weighed in
That's not necessarily what I would describe as just being Catholic
If you're putting someone on a lifetime appointment to the Supreme Court assure themselves
To God
So I mean just Jerry can do like
Reno Catholic
True
I don't know
Tragic
Or Gator Ben Berg
Very sad for you know her family and for what
They could pretend
Flippant
Naturally
Exactly
It is absolute tragedy and icon
Well deserve the peso and this is affecting a lot of people problems with her record
That was more a conversation that was relevant for
No historian yeah
Supposed
You trying to be like
She wasn't that great
I'm not even saying that might not necessarily be fair
I just don't know
Do you serve in the immediate
Yeah
You know obviously
I'm worried
I'm worried about the directions
Now
Time Warner
We really
Have to be as active as we can be
In terms of protecting people
And they're right
There is a there's going to be
I'm at quite frankly very cognizant of the fact
That there are some responsibilities that we have
To not allow
As much as I possibly could
I don't know how we do that
I don't know
I would take mail your Senator a letter call call them
Pre-election appointment
With people
Batman you look at Byzantine nonsense rules
Everybody's talking about how they could do all these parliamentary procedures to just delay it by time and your life
What world do we live in
This is Magic
We just were living by Arcane nonsense rules
What are we doing
Show up
Now maybe
Then surround the building and all the sudden all the rules go away
Magic
I don't know I don't know
I'm not good at
Having ideas of what to do
But laughing at his dumbass that's what we got
Yep
Smile.com
Go to bed Jordan
Ever now we're on Facebook
Write your congressman
Write your family's and find a local bail fund or charity in your area
Leo on dbx
Barrel run
I could do Harrison Smith job better than he can
And I don't believe any of that s***
Alex
Same color