My damn important
I have great respect for
Acknowledge
I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Monica
Alex
Knowledge fight
Jordan Jordan
That is all
Yes no
I had heard the expression
Sleeping child
Pressured
I ordered it
Because of the weather longer afraid of thunderstorm
It is a thunder blanket
It it I don't really
It makes a really good body pillow
Cuz it's kind of heavy
Naked girls more like
Feels like a person
It's 88
Weighted blanket
More spread out pillow
Something along those lines
Discovered
Do karaoke music
The last time
No
That was one of my karaoke
Musical theatre kids
But Kevin's the guy who's the most theatrical David Bowie song
How did Life on Mars is the most theatrical story
Space Oddity
I would say more like
Choices he's really only
If you're like wasted
And a group of people are there that you don't know private karaoke
So weird
It's not fun
Yeah
There's something you're saying something with your choices
Or weird them out
Write you enjoy performance you don't like the pressure of then having to see the person a couple hours later and have them be like
Feedback
Justin Moore the one on one
Plenty of sanding
It was a fantastic time
Call Ben
This is where we find out secretly you f****** karaoke in this room every single night every night every night of course
No I'm not karaoke did a long time ever since ever in
Enjoy doing it again even with
The alcohol
I do
I think we if we got drunk together or no
Oh I wish I could karaoke
When there was only one set of footprints I was karaoke
In order to make an episode
Painfully word Undead
There's nothing new coming out of carry-over Project Camelot
Bummer
Have an appointment with you where we listen to
I realize like an hour before we were going to record that my computer doesn't accept
Interesting.
We don't have the capability there's a VHS player has like a USB
CD drive I can probably get
And maybe we'll do that
I don't want to put out garbage
Episode just to put something out so here we are
Maybe better for it
The first Joseph W
XX underscore ironic underscore edgelord XX
Ironic
Next
Cartoon Madeline
Madeline
Heroin
Yes thank you very much calcium
May I humbly ask that I get a job
Shout out to my word
Rest in peace
See danger and
And
Do
Also Laredo lemon
He's reversion to water food even though he's very much appreciated
Also I grew up in West Dakota north south
And my
North Dakota is Minot
Not me know alright mispronounced it
I know it looks
The capital of South Dakota
Quotes
Educational
A princess
We're going to call walk Indy technocrat
Nothing nothing for the duck so your boyfriend of three dogs
Okay as a show of
Nissan mypark
Of the water creatures
You're Beautiful song
We're coming for your balls
Very few people
When they are
Hey Jude
Spirit play yourself
Favorites with your heart every single note
Generosity should be spread
To your local charity or bail
Alex is kind of obsessing about how there's 40 days left till the election
Until the election
I felt like I was going to be alright recovering this episode
Why didn't you say 40 days and 40 nights
The Jesus references
On a platter for him if he disagrees with him
That's true
Alright cool
About
Some culture War
Now there's a new phenomenon
The war on Christmas
Celebrating
Implied
Children as well
This is a group
Psychotic demon
Wow
Leaving the show with it
Celebrating
We spending his time turning dance sides into evidence of demonic possession amongst his enemies or whatever
This doesn't even really deserve discussion other than the kind of stupid
The only other thing I would like to point out here is that the article about the hunt
As is his style
From Anonymous people on the internet
This is kind of how they're fake outrage nonsense work
They find something momentarily popular online
Something that actually is or they can portray as a disproportionately popular
Article
And yet another desperate effort for dopamine and social media clout parents and siblings
African American
Arsene lip-syncing to the song Baby by blueface
Next step in the process
It's actually something really need or whatever
They also will remember in a week
Being outraged bakley about something else indeed
Because no one except people who are online
The only comment they can ever get on it is for people to go by owner 1488 and Sir slurs a lot
Would you getting clean outside of credit in those people
The entire article is fake
It's a performance and it exists to justify
Children
Mcoles enabling Alex to demonize his perceived enemies
But when you get down to the bottom of what supporting that
Just a couple of Tik Tok videos
It's meaningless ultimately
Kindle Fire that Alex needs to keep constantly stay
It's an excuse to say what you were going to say about the last excuse to say what you were going
The last excuse you were going to say which is
Indeed.com
Let's do the same thing
You scroll through the comments on his article
The coverage
I know any of these days
Is a water essay what respect they should stop us
The user on there
One of the few leftist ideas I supported publicly-funded abortion for the underclass
It will do until we make sterilization a prerequisite for receiving welfare
Blind
Two users
Blast concussion replies
Because it's not easy and requires personal effort critical thinking skills and taking individual responsibility
This is a story that Alex feels the desire to cover not because it means anything
Obviously to someone who's there to catch the baby
It because this kind of story presented the way Paul presents the story gets across the subtler white identity messaged
The actual point
Discussion
You hide behind
Fake moral outrage
Appropriate to talk about you can just say
Racist things everyday people get born
Do you have to create a fictitious reason to say a racist thing
Emotionally outraged be like
You know what you do is you create these false moral outrages around things Direct
Service stotler points about
Classes and invulnerable.
You know all of these people have a playing with your morality or
No value
You won't stand up
Turn your emotions
Oh
Tortorices
Moral
Now we are also doing that
You're quite a while now
Creek
Police and I'm like I want to have a nice relax
Incidentally
We're super for them this is actually
The press conference last week
Whose Health has been harmed by exposure to burn pits
I hate Jon Stewart
John's dedicated a large part of his time
The one thing celebrity people who needs causes
Allowed to do that right right had to bring something
Cuz nobody wants to talk about anything else
That's why they gave him a press conference must be
Press conference for veterans
Public Health guidance
His responsibilities for a legitimate cause I don't think anyone's going to be too mad about it
You just can't be mad with your whole point is
Being irresponsible and the message is basically that you just want to yell at people for attention
Trivial for VA benefits
Actually talk about benefits
And they would be able to speak
And anyway with about.
Getting into the nitty-gritty
Right
The
Announcement of the charges or lack thereof
Surrounding the killing of breonna Taylor
Where do 2 come out
I think things are happening like the state of emergency
Where is like
In advance of this decision we're going to close down everything and if you were going to shoot
Okay
You got a real sense of what was coming I'm pretty sure those were just precautionary
So Alex is aware of this
Gotta prepare
For what could come
Taylor's findings and the rest of it
What
This is the standard stock response of non-white people
And circumstances
Abortion is murder
It's a deflection because he knows that what happened to breonna Taylor is unacceptable
About a woman's killing
After dylann roof killed 9 people
Have you Manuel African Methodist Episcopal Church
This is a trick that uses
I've been over this a number of times but it's always important to remember that this is treatment
Exclusively used to justify or minimize the death
Of non-white people
Personal responses
The Accidental
Indianapolis who's killed in early July
In both of those cases Alex lied about the circumstances
Cuz they were white
These are Fingerprints of the racist editorial position that Infowars and it's designed this way on purpose
You might not see these things
If you weren't paying attention
Work incredibly weather
And before they know it
Accepted or become
Numb
Two things that should be shockingly racist
That's that's the goal
Yeah it's it's hard to
It's hard to look at that and not see a little bit of
Peloton
Look if you're reading that
You don't catch the racism there
Problems happen way before
Like there's no way you know like
This is not something that you just started like you didn't click on it Infowars length as reversed
Because of abortion
Like you're going to go
You're going to go back and you're going to find a lot of s*** along the way
Like if you read it it doesn't
Sound the same
You just hear him
Like a good stand-up joke
People can say things that are unconvincing and stupid
Of him
Trojan horse races today
No
Temperature
Sure I'm just saying that it seems
Transparently obvious
What he's doing
Yes you know like
How can you not a failure of critical thinking education
Imagine
Encounter with their guard up
It's not
It's fair for us necessarily to look at
A casual listener of his show in the same way that we do it
Exercise then
Someone who is just hurting
Tune again cuz I may be curious about a conspiracy or liar
And then you hear it you know you hear what are you saying maybe
United maybe You're vulnerable 272 religious overtones they were able to something else in
A lot of baby stupid
You start to make rational ride
Oh it's possible
Got to be something in class like a literal like a
Here is what a bad faith statement looks like
Like this is a classic what about
Show me alarm to look out for
Switch it up
I'm just I'm just saying we need to bring back the paddle in schools
Think you might have gone off the rails.
Stuff and
Keys got some of his memories confused
But it says we can't find it
Do you feel the baby
We checked and we love it and we talk
Talk to him
Wheat wheat we make jokes
Turns me on
Cousin
What are they doing
I know I love
This is their culture
Videos that he used to yell about a lot
Is getting an abortion
The other the documentary show that includes footage of a woman
Is her having an orgasm
Projected onto the footage
In the actual
Look at yourself
Another stuff is like
Stray clips of Alex City
Brenna reproductive Health Brown
I think
I think my biggie
The thing that it were seen payoff is the Avengers of
His narrative
Overtime because he forgets
That's what specifically you talkin about
You just reference is a melange
Five different things that he probably reference at some point in time and because you know that
You reference something like that in the past your like I will this must be the story
Not he's just putting together five different stories for no reason other than for fun you know
Catalog
Can we stop pretending like abortion doesn't feel good
This was written by Nicole Mullen
Alex is taking the stuff troll article
The video of people saying they get off from having abortions
It legitimately embarrassing stuff
A normal person would be told that the stuff that they're reporting on was written specifically to make people like them who believe both
Intuit look stupid
Embarrassing
Hold that against him
Or can't see through it
He's buried alive prank
Because by definition anyone who would care doesn't take him serious way
Bethel Mercy
Issues like reproductive health
Affected by altitude embarrassing rant about an internet prank
The stories are fake with a radicalization is real
Yep
It's something that you wish you could just laugh at like
Doesn't it said it doesn't matter the killing 200,000
It doesn't matter they just don't
Mia
The bomber
They just hate the left
But it was only God
Does seem like a lot of it
Is that weird week discovered impregnation p***
The role-playing
Post
Cultural panic
Kinkshaming size people is going to really teaches all
So a little bit
Still making
Making stuff up
Fishes
True
What are you doing cuz he's taking a talking point he's established make things up
Has the flu report it which
Alex used to report covid-19
In reality it was because the flu season stop posting updates on the total
How does repeated enough times
Which is to say that around the world there are no cases of the flu being reported cuz they're all just calling me covid-19
Monitoring update from the world
Organization dated September 14th 2020
Reflecting data up to September 1st
Generally speaking and blue season starts to pick up in October so you wouldn't expect
Cases yet at this point
Is up to
The report shows that the number of samples returning positive
Or at a lower level
But the most likely explanation for that
Staffing in route
As well as testing priorities and capacities and member states
Another consideration that's given is the quote various hygiene
Goodbye member states to reduce the risk of virus transmission have played a role in reducing
Influenza virus transmission
It's important to remember that the very actions of people are taken to minimize the spread of covid-19
The spread of influenza
Who is a decent chance it when it's all said and done this may end up being a lower flu rates
This year than in past years
At this stage it's really hard to predict what's going to come
It's pretty clear that there are cases of influenza being tracked
Those cases
That's why they didn't create combat his
Time travel
Viruses that are being watched right now in Cambodia
That's what Alex is doing
Also that article in The Emperor's New Clothes on September 22nd has nothing
To do with covid-19 or even China
And who happens to be
Seems like Alex whatever really hard time
Consequences
Something completely unrelated
Easier
Yep videos of apparently blacklivesmatter protesters
Something that I don't even
I don't know
08 quick update real real quick
Directions
Blackline
Horrible evil
Black white
Coming up
Horrible things to life
It's just so sad
Diversion
And so sad
So evil
AR
On this
Crazy
Randall Flagg
What
Flamethrower
Okay
I thought that when you got on Arrow your pain went away okay
All right yeah I find it difficult to listen to somebody
XOXO
Velcro
Q
All of your petty b******* is what you care about
I don't want to wear a mask.
People are dying
And we're innocent
Over and over and over again
But I'd rather
He was difficult for him and probably ever
I wish I want to talk about that hike
Instead of basically saying like
What I'm really mad about is that black people are intruding upon my perfect little white world where I
I don't have to think about how all the consequences of my actions
Disproportionately affect those with less money
I remember that we were laughing the earlier this month
About Alex declaring
Libertarianism
Would like to clarify
Ron
About
Clarifying a statement
Liberty
Call bunch of smug
Didn't mean that it was stupid
The tea party was a stripper
We already do that
Social issues a libertarian
Are they
Party City
They just support
Someone really funny is that Alex is so dumb libertarianism
It's completely untenable
Tireli impossible to implement in the real world
That's the easiest thing to dismiss
Bumper sticker level Kia
Can you be a like
A little
Libertarian isn't it part of the libertarian philosophy that you're always with libertarianism
I'm a Libertarian but I do love socialism
Being an economic libertarian was the stupidest thing he's ever done but I couldn't find any
As far as I can tell there wasn't any big Message Board uproar
But the only time that's come up behind on her episode
Isn't a lot of anger about what Alex said in the comics
I heard no one other than us
Discuss this
It's
It's not proof of anything but
F****** weird clarification
Maybe it's a situation where like some of those weirdo friends who I came are that's not cool
AG Edward Griffin gave the talking to or something
Libertarian
You know and no consequence
He says a vitamin
7 mineral
Yeah
I would describe this
Killing time
Doesn't minerals
Jschlatt
What's a joke
Central vitamin
There's only 20
What
What are we doing everything first results
Give me whatever I'm not going to do any research myself this is my favorite game to play it on Alex's Show from
Time to time
Either be like yep I was right or he'll reject whatever comes up
30 bedrooms
Not even write a couple times
Talking about
Subway
It's just like salad
Kitchen
It's not working
Call Zarina moment
Where is uninspiring
Commercial
Something smells it's not
Storing food
Veronica
Unless they're doing
Promo
Website
Interesting to me URL
Prepare with aleks.com
Exit the existence of that URL indicates to me a change in the status quo
Something about the relationship between Alex and my Patriot Supply looks like
Change
Go like something you might see you in the partnership is getting scaled-back
How many you prepare with Alex for my Patriot Supply
You directing people to that website to track the business and purchases that are prompted by
Let me figure out what that's worth the pay him for his advertising
Yeah it gets like an affiliate link and all that
Specific businesses
I've given their pitch persons URLs that are prepare with x.com
Shapiro promotes preparewithglenn.com
Shapiro tries to sell you food
Another right-wing
Be horrific Common Sense Show
Or prepare
Which takes you to Atlantic page
Franchi The Lunatic YouTube show called
News Network
Go to prepare
You can take advantage of a really good Limited
Get one of those
Positive
My favorite
If you are advertising in the same way Alex Jones is taken down
Shapiro Glenn Beck
Puns about last night I just got into a hole
Prepare with
License plate
With great
It is
Jreg
The URL is spelled with a g r e y
His picture is like a silver plaque
YouTube
It's really hard to expect
I'm sure the arrangements he's had with my Patriot Supply before we're far more entwined or his Sales Systems into their back
Does he described
Well Alex wouldn't have been shipping
He still be processing payments
Where is this arrangement
Just be Alex having an affair
Facilitator system where is only real involvement
Is trying to direct traffic to that land
Better system for him
Prepare with Alex because
Now he is just Ben Shapiro videos of him
Doing like a trucking
Paint with Michel I want him to do the Bob Ross
Preparing a preparation shows
Like standing there and he's like here's one of the things you're going to need what does in the Box
At work
Boy
We're in prison bad time
Cars
Then we've been taught that we're not
Define on
What's the
Sterilizer
Quilting
I will think that
Top
Take you out
That's an efficient system
Okay so couple things real quick
The first thing that strikes me about Alex's literally incapable of imagining
Who's to say that has to be on things operate
I would suggest that it might actually be easier to read Society
Need to go around and send electromagnetic trash trucks
Also I really really think that Alex is just traumatized
Something
It's amazing
Those trailers for old movies
Things are so in-depth
Trailers
Spoilers
Play condition
Kind of cop tell he's not a literal
Like the opening crawl
Explaining everybody and then
Imagine if the trailer for Spider-Man
Actually just showed you the whole backstory
And then they made the better movie they just moved
Hinges on white people
It's really tough to do that style of trailer but I
How f*****-up it would be if trailers today were like that
Episode
Mobile9 everything but
I don't know
Problems with the plan but he has Global account
The first is abused robot trash trucks or take all the people
Population of u.s.a.
Comically large
But I guess the robots and robot incinerators or something I don't know
Kill you in two weeks raised on the garbage cans incinerator with them
How long do these electromagnetic waves
From these trash dress
Under Murder
Capabilities are City at the same time
Thousands and thousands of trash trucks
U-Save
Are are there?
Entire block.
Is there is somebody who doesn't
The program
Yes a great Quest at the great question
A problem with a problem
Driving cars or any of that s***
According to Alex
Agricultural production happening
Also their plan is supposed to be to download their brains into silicone bodies and merge with machines
Food
If everyone were to stay alive
The only reason to create more efficient agricultural systems is to feed more people
The only reason to create automated driverless cars at a reduced traffic
Amazon doesn't need tons of deliveries
Consumer-based
White people out
Has ways to better survive in a world of growing population
What I'm getting at is Alex's stupid there for the plant
Levels
Talking
Yeah makes sense if we are to become
Then it's like
See that's what I'm saying that doesn't make any sense
Okay
Maybe they're going to replace us
With robot people need food
Maybe the only way
That's the only way to keep pee at AI
Turning all of us into their food Matrix Style
This is dumb
You just ate you know you just aren't willing to really Workshop the globalist
Plans
It does seem like
Around that one
I think come from the like 1950s TV show The Avengers or whatever cuz all of their evil villain plans
Like even the movie with Sean Connery it's just like wait till you build a weather machine and you're going to do what with it when a cellu weather
What's a reasonable people are going to come after you you can't own the weather
This is also just a guy
Conquered the devil
Timeline
The timeline of this
Problem
Yes we will
They know
They're going to end
But that's why we have the Rope
We've cornered these people
Have you
3 +
Sure
Naturally
Totally
Course
Washing clothes
Go to the end
Just remember who killed
Okay
They'll rebuild Society
Who's the stupidest s*** I've ever heard
If you seriously he's work he's done in his career
Be literal Christian Dental
Alex I need the devil centuries-old
Instakiller
Devil's minions like to do things like kill everyone in the world in an orderly fashion
Piece of nonsense
Devil
Superpower bioweapon
Foreigner original plan
Is Superplay open
Topian hellscape Zelda
Justified Justice murders
Siri
That he is defeating the devil
Christian death
Is In-N-Out itself very Blasphemous towards his religion
Because he is operating on God's plan
So you're saying is to get spoiled by Alex
Like God was like okay
Devil
That was hilarious
Go to work
And then at the f****** last minute he's like
The devil's play
What are you doing
You're saying that the god that God is weak enough to have a stupid plan
Like the devil
It is pretty good goof
Frank
Save the world
Everyone
The first
Purdue University operating on Godwin
And that means god is a stupid idiot
Bigger the specific
Satanism right is the big evil sign
Ganondorf
I'm not worried about Ganondorf
I don't need any saviors
Causes problems I'll just
I'll talk about his plans for a while we like pizza
Public apologies from Alex on his show
Devil
Not scared
Pretty much now is meaningless until after the Apocalypse
Or the killing off of pretty much a watch
There isn't anything you can do to stop it
What are you saying
Presumably Alex's entire career has been about avoiding plan a which is digging around with the vaccine to chips
What is the
Exactly of Alexandra Daddario
Did what he say
Nation of Alex's life's work is getting everyone killed sooner
All you did is
Spoil their plans he made them petulant legal will
We're not having any fun
We won't even bother with
These cards earlier
Alright literal devil
Garbage truck
With Satan
Also has a great pitch for Alex
9899 2000
Quit yelling at you
I should tell you this couple years into my career
Even if everything goes according to plan and we pull this off perfectly we'll all be killed by the globe
We are only trying to avert
Sorry
Attraction
If he presented himself as someone who actually has a f****** shot of
The end of his career is where we're at is
There's nowhere to go
This kind of inevitable
It's going down
And after we do
You will need to come out and execute Justice
Yeah it made because like
A little bit
I mean like Jade Helm is embarrassing
Sandy Hook
Boston bombing
Embarrassing
This is this is this is
This is doomsday cult I think what like
Two more times to Doomsday
In most Dunes they called diminishing returns the first day around
Enough people are going to stick with you that you can go for a second Doomsday
I think that's I think Doomsday cults usually get a second Doom
Yeah but that's like Ron Paul in 2012
His first run today
Talking about
How desperate he is for money
That is true with Alex Alex
They want to wipe everyone out
Alex
A bunch of
Stupid and lazy
Non giving
Sociopath
No you are
You're Conjuring around destruction
Really
Alright
Never say that kind of thing into a microphone
The general population of the common person
He's talking about what he thinks he hates everyone
He hates people like you and me because we don't see the same patterns of disconnected things that he does
He hates us because according to him our inability to
The wild destroy the world
You could debate whether or not Alex believes any of that it actually
Religious languages facade that political disenfranchisement
Straight white sister
Actually believe
Alex paint the general population to the point where he thinks his imaginary enemy
Please have plans
He says stuff like this and I pretty much
It was the first time he said it
You and for me it's so shocking that you would come on a show and save it as mission is to
That's a fine position
Yeah what's the Google tacos for dinner
In that case the planets feeling you don't like the idea
In this case the plan though is killing billions of people
The problem with a plan is not who's doing it it's the killing billions of people Park
Planets
You just kind of invalidate entire argument about being against the global population thing
Quotes on who should be killed
No I don't think the GOP is
What is a where is the rest of us are at that
Different
Like that's
On the same team
We want to be on the other side of Alex's
Yeah that's it
Becomes really clear when he says stuff like that
Petulant child
Because as much as I hate
Political
Discourse is the common
I dislike Trump being in office
Democrats in particular
I spilled
Would never wish
On the general population I want to improve
I think
I do
But I don't exactly
Touts forever 101
Seized
Because of him
Other parts
The plan
And they're just going to kill everybody
And it sounds like
He's just annoyed them into skipping the fun part of the plan and then killing everybody
And it seems like the way he's responding
He's very annoyed at everybody
And he doesn't want to do all of that bulshit anymore
There's something similar to the globalist and Alex
Ultrastat
Some calls
Detective calls
And this guy
Boy
Blue Collar man
Matter
Liberty or death don't
This caller is all over the place
First problem
Second problem
Forward slogans written on it with a sharpie
I think I would immediately trust like a real estate agent if they were like I'm going to show you this house first
Hey where can I buy one of those
Free with every purchase of a
No it's
In the same way there telling her fake
The consequences are real
This caller
No reason to think that
Archer represents some of the real effects
Sprouts has on people
Welcome
This is mine
Paintings
Damn listening to you and thanks
How much is
See
Take this anymore
Grocery shopping
It's fine.
People
I just
This is horrible
That's that's one of those like literally
What's her name if she dies of covid
Alex killed
All right I mean
Seriously fear was more
In terms of careful Consciousness as opposed to terrified beer
But seriously in April
Anime
You can
I'll be responsible a number of times
Going to be the thing
It's really unfortunate
Someone who calls
Big big for her it's unfortunate
It's important
You obviously care about her
And then it's unfortunate for
What she represents because this is one caller
And then
Even on top of that there's another listening to her testimonial
58 year old person compromise issue
I am home never
No
If she has any consequence
Is there any health issues because
She is just someone who called into Alex's show
We'll never know he'll never know he doesn't care meant just
Dark that is 12 dark dark
This but with
By her own words
If she dies out
What killed her
It's it's a pretty interesting case to try
On a civil level
I just got really depressed me
Dr. Mercola Mercola comes on for the
Tower
Heathcos
Hard
This is really funny
He's a wanted to ask Alex if he's got his Vitamin D level check
Is so funny
Thank you for Mission Again to stop
No
Email options
Free information
Wow
Why do you say
Absolutely not
You have no idea
Did you get your vitamin D levels checked
Wow
Partner
Yeah good sandwich
I do enjoy earlier
This is
Justify talking about dr. Mercola
Seiyuu
Family
Friend or someone
Do you know where you're at
Anyone get sick and what do you do
Commercial that has
Some stabilizer
Because it doesn't have the stable
I like that we graduated to ask
Hydrogen peroxide
Drink it
Okay
Duluth
An inhaler
Now
I don't know what else to know whether or not
In a safe
Environment with an actual doctor applying
Whether or not hydrogen peroxide may have some sort of medicinal benefits
You can't
If you are dr. Mercola you can't go on Infowars
And tell people to get store-bought hydrogen peroxide dilute it
And f****** inhaler
You can't trust that they're going to know how to dilute something correctly that's so dangerous
Controversial
Solutionreach
In the sinuses in your nose that's why you want to use an ass
Get it in your nasal passage
Here's what you got to do you got to rub
Vicks VapoRub
On your a****** and that will protect you from covid now I don't sell
Consult with your physician beautiful Healthcare professionals
Realistic we just take a rocket science
I just believe that 99.9% water and point
Freeport
Inhaling
Physiologically
Indistinguishable from medical advice
Excuse me Jackie Robinson
I was thinking of hydrogen peroxide
Do you think that's a good idea
Poison
I would love to see the look on his face
So you want to do it
I just imagined house
What are the people in his Clinic
Nebulizer
Desire to not get sued
Obviously
Consult a physician
I'm not positive
Threshold for Dangerous delusions of
That I don't trust
The listeners of this program
Possibly
You can't guarantee that these people are going to accurately dose
Things are household cleaner
Be sure you only have a little
Ever not like
Oh well if this works I wonder if I should just smell it
Everybody's going to do stupid s*** with this
Alex wants to be clear that he just believes this
Plugging somebody else
Get it
Alright let's do this
Get done with Mercola and
I feel guilty
41 minutes
Corso
Do something
Nicole
Call
Wintersun with high-quality vitamin D3
Love it
I need to do another add Christmas in July
Summer sale
It takes a call Praise on air for like
3 minutes at like I want I want
Figures like I could cut a section of this
Like if I played a minute of it
Feel like
But why not play at all
Alright
I would like to get inside the mind of somebody's like you know what I need to call Infowars and
Crayon are 43 minutes
And I'm going to wait on hold for 2 hours to do it
That I cannot comprehend
And of course over the evening news
For the officers in Louisville
They were going around
You know
Mister tough guy
Going to kill me
We want out
Had to come stopover they were
Please get out
This is America
50 yd away not even in their business
America
Noted Beto O'Rourke fans antifa
Call boy
Yeah
Yeah Tifa came out
Beto
Beto O'Rourke
Antifa loves to worship Heroes like Beto O'Rourke
They didn't like
His politics are planted at the drive-in
What are
How do I activate an effect
Situation
This is pretty disgusting
Lying about the circumstances surrounding
The Killing
Kamala Harris
Tweeting last night
Say her name
Breonna Taylor
Who was Winston drug dealer game
Somebody else called the cops
The cops come
Call
Because you were living with a g******* drug dealer
Lying about the details of the shooting that killed Brianna
If your horse to cover the story based on the details that exist in reality
Don't really care that much
The shooting did not happen because the neighbor called the police
The actual information about this
It is about it
More of an honest mistake
In reality
The police executed this no-knock warrant because they receive for Taylor's house
Based on surveillance of a previously carried it sounded her ex-boyfriend
Had been to her house previously and was under investigation in a drug
Ex-boyfriend it already been arrested across town
The person who was with
Alex doesn't understand
Surrounding
Record which means that they were able to execute it without an ounce
Taylor's boyfriend claims that the only reason he fired a shot it because there was no indication for police
His claim to be grounded in reality
Considering the fact that there was a record of him calling me please
Meanwhile the police officer
And I'm going to say that in this circumstance
You can't trust anything the police say
I think they might lie to the police
Someone was breaking in
Makes it seem like
Whether or not
They did announce themselves
Perhaps it seems strange anyway
This is a tragic situation requires is that the people who created
This situation be held responsible
Absolute disrespect to Brianna Taylor
He is not interested in actually.
But he doesn't care enough to look into it
It's really disgusting for him to just make up really simple details about a person's killing
Enable him to be mad about other people Justified angry response to the actual reality of that killing
Be like
Just accept
We're going to look at you how we're going to look at you for that
Dyckman can't
You can't it doesn't look good
Enzo
He has to make it
Okay
Yep just have to make it okay for you to get murdered
Yeah
A baseball bat
Beer you can see the direction that Alex Jones has coverage goes in
That night in Seattle there were two main stories that went around that had to do with violence at protest
Cover West convenient
They attack people for no reason
Story
I had to do the video of a police officer on a bike clearly intentional the ground
Intentional because if you watch the footage the cop has to alter his course to run over the guy's head
It could be easily not run over the guys that do not do that but he decided to anyway
You think it's on the side of giving more weight
The story about a Cop protected
Libertarianism
Armored cop getting hit with a bat
Alex don't touch stories like that because
You know the ones where the police they're clearly brutalizing protesters because he supports it
Libertarian
But he also wants to be able to live free will consequences
Libertarians don't water police
Corporate
A private Army to be the police
Because
Exactly
Republic
Is on the show because she went to a Rally in Austin night before
No chivalry
No comment
You're a reporter
Men
Videos on Newport, Newport
Krowd
Euro
The target
O.j.
City
Aware they
Punch me in
Sure
Board of Brianna Taylor
Have a like a lot of video that's because if you if you're the cameraman for Savannah Hernandez
And you see her getting physically attacked you immediately put the camera
Someone pushed her up against the wall and maybe she got
At least there is one person who's yelling lock her up
In for a long. Of time
I meant never even people trying to help her find her phone
People help her fart try to help her find her phone
Of course they do because obviously I'm not
You taking a swing at her but also I get it
She was there working for Infowars but pretending that she was
Pretending to work for the Action 7 News
Recognize her as an employee
The reason I understand someone reacting to Savannah being there under false pretenses
Is actively trying to get protesters killed
The work that she does represent an actual threat to the people who are there protests
Because the product
Facilitate violence against protesters
End of Justified Violence Against protesters after eating
Better ways to handle the situation than to Pusher but I'm not going to shed a tear on her
Attention
Police
She was attacked for supporting the police
Predictable
Independent journalist instead of what she actually
Infowars provocateur
Laura Ingraham earn a tough predicament because they promote the stuff that Infowars
Completely embarrassing
And they can never really associate with it you keep any kind of credibility
Directions
Oportun
They go out of their way to cover up they work for Alex Jones
What's your message
Literally
Or I would
Alright
It's required for these two worlds
Conservative propaganda to collaborate
We have to believe to completely unbelievable things in order for that clip to be understood is Laura Ingraham
First we have to believe that no one at Fox Google Savannah Hernandez prior to her being on the show
It is literally no background research by Alex Jones
Second
He works for a presumably believe
Those two things are completely unbelievable and the only explanation for the performance
Is apple cider keenly aware that pretending it doesn't exist benefits
Laura Ingraham journalist
The elephant in the room
At the same time
Police lives matter sign
Breonna Taylor
The footage most people in that are in this duffle or trying to separate Savannah and someone else
How's that she's fighting Westshore
It's not a gang attack and like looking for her phone
If anybody wanted to hurt her she would have been her
Yeah I guarantee
Yeah there's no there's no
There's no
This bother just bums me out because
Exception of maybe
The person that you was fighting with
It's tough to tell from the
Assuming
Hit somebody did
Start getting physical with her whatever
Everybody operated how they should have
Yeah you're not trying to break it up trying to keep people separated
Exactly what you'd want to do
Would someone write
Curbing at this part
Because if you do nothing
Going to get video going to misrepresent it's going to be used to attack you if you try to
Joe claimed she was attacked by a big gang of men with guns play the victim card
Show
There's a situation
That you have
When
Breaker stuff
Take take take
Like a her phone instead of you should help look for her phone
And if you find it first
You should Smash It On The Ground in front of her views expressed by Jordan do not
A position I can I still don't Advocate to break people's
Total Clarity I wouldn't judge you if you don't support
No no
In the same way after watching this video I obviously don't
I don't think violence is good
I do
Don't
Are
Don't hurt people
Anything that's not people
Like a buildings
So Alex
I'm stuff
Kind of not all that interesting
I only kept this in because he says something that I think is pretty expensive
Worshiper
Why are they killing all those
Florida man
Because you might think you got a man
Oh no
How to fight back against that women don't possess
And I'm going to need to see a citation on that
Sure
Beyond really complex picture behind the reality of human traffic
A large amount of it does have to do with sex trafficking but another huge sector involves labor trafficking literally
Slavery people find themselves in the position project
The largest factor in their victimization with migration or relocation
I fell prey to work
And false promises and fraud
This is just looking at Stats with the United States
It sometimes appears a sex traffic
And sometimes appears as labor trafficking
These are issues that are not exclusive to either man or women
Also if you keep men as slaves for so long
Wework
Remember
Everybody got stabbed
California firefighters were all murdered by the slave labor that they used to fight fires to remember
No
Right now
Their dad right
How is
12yearsaslave possible
That is a good point
He was Ball parking it Alex
Has Robert Barnes on
Wanted to talk about how coneybear it's not a great pick for the Supreme Court
Yeah I don't know what that I don't I don't care to get in on their little game
However
My job for this is going to cheer you up hour
Pay close attention to our casa Valley
In Germany 90
Excuse
Rise above
Emergency
Emergency except
Action to the
Illegally
Anyone that's pushing me
You are not allowed to say that you were just
You you can't literally say that about the violent left
Those things before
He's doing all of those things that is insulting
Personal slapped me in the face with b*******
Cruel
$10,000 to whatever charity
Campaign
After I fight him
Aware
Be aware of yourself as a Nazi
Or at least Alex
That makes me that makes me want to fight I'm going to fight him
Stop my ears weird
Goodbye
Elevation
Murder happens 60 70 years ago at our expenses go back
Federal Reserve
Now that happened in 1930s
Body of the world
I got it I got that
It was probably
Now that happened in 1920 19 years ago
62 cylinder years ago
Was it now I remember because they were getting all like I want to have her remember that
Barnes doesn't Barrett
Trump needs somebody
On his side
This is this
You're being too obvious yeah I'm pretty sure you're saying that what he needs to do is make
Didn't you think you're just in
I don't want a supreme court do not want
Independent exactly what he said
Yeah
Amy Coney Barrett
Supreme Court
It may surprise you to hear this but there is no Pope named the John Pius the 2nd
There's never even been a John Pius the 1st
I suspect Alex is trying to do is have his brain come up with two different things at the same time
Beaufort 1978 2005
The other name pie I think comes from Alex's brings religious beliefs
Controller
Because the next Pope John the 23rd was notably more Progressive like how he said the Jews aren't evil
Both of these names
And in the process he forgot about the 2013
I've said this before
Alex naughty details guy
So I'll accept after Barnsley
Soccer field
Rihanna
Don't care
Play Goin Hard on a T-Rex.
This is basically we're going to end
Really funny cuz it's basically a banana peel
He said it once
We want to hear
Jeffy
T-Mobile
Here
I demand they make it there's no man great
What do we do
Getting what I want
I can't scare people about
That's just a smokescreen for when they do make it mandatory right
I don't care boy this little bit
I feel a little bit
Reinvigorated I don't know why
I don't know what it is
I have that nebulizer over there was for a reason
Actually
The worm farm is made of
I did know I know
Take it back by do I retract it alright
So I don't know why I look at these these couple days
There's just
Deep
Coded and unloaded racism
It's kind of like come on man
This is a little much
What makes sense
Psycho
Really justify it to well
So
Best not to try
It's a tragedy.
To deliver through
Secondary
Like Tik-Tok videos and stuff like that
Express your bigotry that way
Just like everywhere else
It just always like
If it's a black person it's always well you shouldn't have put yourself in that situation
Somehow the worst-case scenarios
Dating a drug dealer means that you deserve to die or that your death is any less tragic
Or or cause for concern
Half of our friends have drug dealers
Well you should have had friends who are comedians
Hang out with baby
Better better out here
So why her ears the first one
Indiana Jordan
Skincity
About 3
But
You guys are a bright
Spot for me Monday
Open Friday
Kansas City
Best ice cream shop in the United States
Kansas City check it out if you want
Very interesting flavors that I
Have no relationship at all
Ice cream brother
When I wrote this
But then I
I had to call
Hayden and Jordan
First-time caller I love your work
I love you
I want to be the first
Linda video
Spoken word but I've not
Recommended stardew Valley
But I still wanted to record
Quick text
Badger hybrid
Third shift
Titanic
Douglas Adams
Succubus
Oh hell yeah I know about it
Hitchhiker's Guide
Even though I'm sure you've managed
Mansionair
Which way you were
On that
Adam
But the game is really
Justin Bree playing it
Eggmazing
It feels more like a
Jordan game
Hawaii
Morgan Jordan 5
Make a donation
Forgetting when I got my
Paycheck
It's not my dog
Appointment
And then here
With your album
Emissions
Rendition
Putting out a really
Wang podcast
But I really enjoyed
I love you
Number two
I thought for sure
I've never heard of anybody not like how do you light
Bendy
For several hundred hours of
Eureka
Is doing all right if you don't want to get into it
You can definitely go with some of the Dirk gently books
Are the two Dirk gently books they're fantastic
Alright
Sweetheart Lanes
Listen to non-fighting Carlos
But during episode Warehouse.
Transpose
Tikal
But you're old
Oh no
Mom
No
What song is this
Shot again
Uber now
Jordan
Woo
City
Esterline
Guinea
I didn't know
My daughter
That's just a heartwarming
Hay Day
Janet Jordan
Flipping
A bit of a
It's not a cat
Form after
If you
Break off
And then you just
The bottom of it
Water attack
And it really sucks
I love the show
Thank you very much and everything
I blew your mind is my mind how big
Coming
And there was no cucumber cucumber
Earlier today
We have little more space for it
Flowers after 1
It's already September
So
Hello this is
Relative
The early in the
Review
.
For now
And it is a Coronavirus
Which is
What
For weapon
Denise review
Binary
A Hunter bow
Two different
Piercing both one with the sheer black hair
And you
Rope gun
Figured out which
The emperor
To how do you eat
Giant Tyrannosaurus
Did you shoot it full of Roe
Yeah I got it
NEC article of roads in Europe
Peace at any time
Love this year
What's the weather
Thank you
You're right
Nation's number one horizon zero Dawn podcast required to answer
Questions about the horizon
What is the show about
I don't understand what a bird
The cars are slingshot the shadow slingshot upgraded until the bombs or just
Undefeatable
Just blow stuff up left and right looking for a more precise
Use a blast Arrow to pop off the caps at one of those
Seasonal explodes
I was more into Times
Used
Constant
Spell
Stealth or distance that's what I always do
Silver and watching them play
For maximized
Through again eventually
And differently
Cheating
No that's true
Jordan
Maybe Wonder
When
Obvious
What is
What do they do
Daylight
Picture ham
How to wait
I doubt
Wild and out
Alex Jones
Thanks
Joann
Yeah
Good day
We'll be eating when he's interviewing somebody else
Queen Zach person Skype
If he's taking calls there's just an imported logo
Okay so interesting
Lines Moving on it that up on the screen
The color burgundy
He's not on air
No you cannot eat for that much commercial breaks
Call Mac I'll let you know when I go to
NOAA space.
Family Show
Golden you are correct
Northeast
Dial real
My God
Daniel
Yep
Call Steph.
Larry Moore
Petco
Got that
Apparently our Impressions were Alright lyrics
Where's Impressions than ours
The various pronunciations of quokka
First names only on this one
Jordan Peterson
As far as Jordan
Interior
Daughter
Chris Jordan status B lost track of the Jordan Peterson story
No idea what's going on with that I probably shouldn't be fine with it
Almost forgot
Are Jordans
Interesting interesting little note
I work at Distillery in Kentucky
As a token of appreciation for all you do please accept this bottle of 1792 full proof
He was recently recognized at the best whiskey of the world
By Jim Murray Renee recognized as the leading expert in the world
Not that bad handwriting
Please accept Spirit of Norfolk
Much respect
For all you do
Well maybe Thanksgiving
Spirit of Norfolk
These days
Probably enjoy it a lot more than I would think so
Gifts are specifically for me like the cell service or I feel like a bottle of really nice whiskey is
So I expect a full report on that
To the disembodied Spirit of knock
Alright whatever
Terio Canada
I will say this could have easily been a bright spot for me and that was
Just a box of Canadian candy
I have to say I was pretty impressed
I went in with some iffy expectation
Because like
Play better than
Better
Nothing
Spectacular Aero candy bar
If I've never had one before I think
That was a really good texture and flavor
Bag of
Maynard all right
Got your little
Godzilla
Angry
Or whatever
It's it's the taste
It's just that fine
Flavor
Does it even have alcohol
Then what's the point
Alright
What is burgundy
Get drunk off of
To feed my word Bulgarian
Kinder Eggs really cool
Broken in transit when I was younger
My buddies at the dollar store before they made it illegal
Import Kinder Egg chocolate
Can babysit
Gifts nose Burger you know
A couple couple buddies from kinder egg
Really bright
Couple of tough
Days and I'm sure the guy with you
Get out of here this is this is this is a slow drink hour-and-a-half
Yes we will but until then we have
Jordans
Doorbell sound in your area emphasis on bail fund
We're going to need
Barrel run
Ice Cube
Alex