Have great respect
Knowledge
Doordash
What's up
What's today
Hey look at work tired of
On what am I on
And it was exhilarating
Overwhelming
I kind of feel a little bit I might cry
Sure
I don't know how excited
Slices
Like some people frame their first dollar made in business
No problem
I'll be more excited
It's probably true
Workout
R6S
Cucumber
I know everybody's getting tired of
Tennis
Felt like it was
Jesus is over already
Is far too f****** long
What we should do that exactly
No no reasonable person would say otherwise more time
Two weeks and then Raphael will have another French Open
When I was younger
2020 iPod
Acquired
Announce
43 Court which wasn't Garth Amy Coney Barrett
Great
Immediately
The inside scoop
Coney Barrett
Totally excited
Dr. Robert Barnes
We're coming in with some real hot
Barrett
She was basically
Where's Detroit
Barn pitched megillah and somebody who would give him basically a winning floor
Very conservative doesn't have a lot of the bag
Really
Nomination
Workout
Somehow this is getting lost in the in all of this
Usually whenever there's big news why the Saturday episode
Navigating somebody that he and his buddy Barnes
Talking about how is the h
Toonami Barrett
She's a federalist Society on the right
Going to play
The choice
Justify
Let's do it
Sawyer thank you so much and I'll probably want
Surah Rahman
Very much
I assure you is smart
Kmart
We got one show
This is called
This is the stupidest thing in the world
No
We're knowing good men are still thinking
Kmart
Thank you so much
What you could do
I see your eyes looking around
Rolling around in there
What you can do is be browbeat administration of your school in tattooing absolutely no
Dealing with the fuc
Normally I
I f****** pull this off perfect absolutely
I really like
A nightmare on
Uno
I was just overwhelmed
Do you want me to try disingenuous
I don't want you to listen
Surprising
Tattoo on your arm
To do right there
Audio
I told you I was off a little bit
On the ground
Take the meat
I like it your nice little
Alright
Sunday
And
Subordinate
Vajacial
Talking about Siri
You know what
From The Middle
Took over all the way
Did they
Cool
Serious people. People
Cameron
Instead imagine a bunch of people with rocks just likes
Oh that's for damn sure
Literally
Initial investment
Expectation
Some sort of a charge for
Real serious real serious
What about everybody
Information
Good thing we got it on record
Nixon friends
I don't care
To this with some sort of like agenda
Source on character about
Rodger Stone out of prison
Every
46 days until the election
Getting a little closer
Motherfuker
You
Sure
About Tony Barrett
Maybe pretend
David has the worst decision possible
The moment
Hours after Ginsburg die
Action
She's the picture
Ginsburg
Call list about using covid-19 takeover s*** is completely made out of
In February
Which was hosted by
It was posted online on July 14th
Not in February
Groupism
They're meeting every year in Davos Switzerland
You referred to as
Put out this report not Davis because
80%
Is the name
Talk about
These great reset presentation was released
Things are structured
Across
Very wide-ranging
February because that's when he
The date
Intentionally
Listen to this section
That he's using
Group document
Survivor
I just I just can't
Is that you can't start and then
Mike Adams
To seriously bother Everything is Everything
Police officers
Who were shot
Story
Charade
WLKY
Charged with 14 counts of wanton endangerment
He's $1000000 with that
Games of Discovery chair
District attorney
Tutoring
The narrative in the story only has a weight if you accept the first plan
Where's the Second Glance
Punishment for first-degree assault
Pretty steep
District attorney
Charges are far more likely
Conversely it's much harder to understand how it's affected
This is the sort of thing
Refurbished shooter
Responsible for reporting that there are no attempted murder charge
It's a nice receiving the consequences
Something that is true but not the line part
Athletic
Respond
Intellectual
F*** yourself you know what you're doing
About that
Days of the inauguration
And that is because we have a new narrative
It is
The time between
The election inauguration
Might be the Rapture I don't know
Alright
Election going
Vermont
Surskit
No they're losing
Call Aaron
Nick Lachey
Soon or something
So I guess
From getting elected
Misrepresented
Recording booth
When New York Times article about Trump attack
Forward
I don't want
Throw Stone
Trump to do
Afterwards
We all know the outcome is already decided
Explanation
To come out with that ad campaign
Election
He's he's really really trying to push this talking quite hard because
Libertarian
Dictator
You know hey if there's all these protests which are going to destroy city and sure
Call Linda
When the military
Jerry
The Shadow
Nothing worth anything
What
What seems so angry fake stories
He's with their newspapers and they look.
Jesus Christ
God dammit
Zoe
Destroyed
Spanky
I never should have said anything
Magical little Counterpoint
That's not fair the part of it though
Stan
Gigantic detail
I forgot that they're also going to send alligators to eat
Crocodile
People Like Us
That's great
Different problems
To have a reason for the
Decision to take longer so they can crash the stock market
If you believe anything
Worked up about whether or not
The globalist
Vaccines
How to twerk
Which is the release of super bio weapons
The relief
The word he says
I'm getting another four years means nothing
If he threatens our plans at all
None of it has any effect
Words that came out of his mouth
For Christian
Unreleased world society
Display seems like a small
All about whether or not Trump
Bored
Having an emotional day
By way of trash truck
Chris Brown
Trucks
Hundred percent certainty
Next year
What's appreciate
It's like nobody
Murder
A lot of control over a lot of
And
Yes certainly this is made us all take a lot more of the philosophical Longview like
Generation
Obviously
Yeah
Don't worry about it
I don't have a lot to answer
It's a real problem because
All this should be trivial
The ultimate
Is to stop
You know it's right away cuz evolve then
Prism
Find Soros and take him out real whatever you know
It's alright
Is to discuss
How do you clean water
I don't think it's as profitable
Binder demon
Juice everybody up
Attorney General of New York Township
Truly believes that
And all that stuff
Call Ben
Stupid
For the Supreme Court
Alex isn't saying it is a very bad idea
Hey got to fall in line
Power notes
Obviously
Licker
Cool
Then
Then you're saying that you want a Supreme Court Justice
Globalist plant
Strength
For some reason Trump
And supporting
Globalist plan
Buddy
Now that you think about suggest that isn't a class of
Goodnight everybody
All of them
For summer
Well
Going through because
Democrat
Are clearly again
She had a lot of ideas
Sportacus
Basically just Oppositional defiant
Oh no she's broke
See this is the difference between someone like Alex
Embarrass
For Supreme Court nomination
It violated some piece of the Damned
Or something
Except in opposition to
I mean
The Reason by everybody
Is there unified in one
Anything but left like soon
About their political position
5 blocks
Anything that they don't mean you have to support it
Soros paid all the protesters me run 2019
Socially responsible
Black lives matter
Elemento
Protest
Sure whatever
So for Alex
There's a position needs to be called artificial
Because
You believe the same thing
Maybe
Can't really
Can't really drive with
Philosophical
I think the Democrats are right on this one
Like imagine inside in 2020
Imagine that
So
Because
I mean you want someone
Quran the Quarry
Rite Aid got to figure out why the f*** did Trump nominate this person
She's prorock down and pro-vaccine
Oh yeah
That this is a Federalist Society
The election
Brother
You're the one that told me
Response
What else you got
Pro lockdown pro-vaccine
Mandatory vaccine
Because you were told she would hand him
Because she was part of the bush-gore team which aliver Bush stole
Federalist
You think
If you are born
Like how can you understand
Your guy who's your
You telling me
Federalist Society
That these people can visit
Trump
To nominate this person right because of the
Bush V Gore
Malik
Is
In order to stay in power
That's not good
Everything that you disagree with her about simply because she is
Wrong with that damn
It's bad I mean it's just
Cupboard
Bar was a terrible choice in many
Appointed there because he had previously helped
Cover up crime
Whether she could be another William Barr
Hey this looks like a bad idea
We have to wrestle with a really difficult in here and that is that
The Koch brothers
Amy Coney Barrett
This is going to probably piss you off
Actually
Wow
Paisley that makes me shiver
Physically you just took a shot of something weird for the first time
That one was
Or whatever
Kill me
Career considering
And Ron Paul is first president of a way back and then where
Cook Brothers bathroom freedomworks Sunday then after fantano
The tea party with you
It's tough to understand how
Pro-immigration
Watching listening to these two guys eat what is clearly a big bulshit
Honestly
Bad
In order to make things
Pretty funny
Leave this in the same position
Supreme Court
Adulterated
The end of it I'm just shivering and angry
You know that's right
Unclear
Tumi
For them
Nominate end-to-end another Supreme Court Justice
Like because if you add Coney Barrett
The Supreme Court is so comically
There's no point in even having
Still
What's that mean
Even then you know whenever if we elect by and actually work
Great
Supreme Court
Where
Tire system
It's not too much different
Tumi
What's going to or what needs to be done to correct
Gretna
What the answer to that these world
Ultrabar
Amy Coney Barrett somebody who
Prologue
He's someone who's highly susceptible to attack from The Fringe right
There is a possibility
On people who are like Ted Cruz
Not being able to support her nomination
Pissing off on crowd
And we end up with
Getting to the election with an opener
Probably
Supreme Court
And I were at the hearing
More than anything else
A reverse psychology
Like seriously just she believes that the far-right Fringe
Their ship
But like seriously
Subway
Particularly vulnerable to
It is a tool that the last disposal
Toodaloo
There are a lot of people
Clearly saying that they don't like her
For sterile
Nations in Topeka
Never issued in America
Citizens united
USA
You selling me on.
This goes to show
I don't know cuz I'm not
Underline
Jacobson
Massachusetts
Dollars
Not getting vaccinated
They create the public health burden
Territory
Forcing people to get
Vaccines
That if you don't get a vaccine
Subsequently
Yeah
How succinctly they are making the case
For not supporting her
The same time
F******
Now it gets even weirder
Because
This was that
I've experienced even on Infowars
Pretzel
The George Soros
That's amazing
So
Trump to appoint
This lady
Who is pro-force vaccination
In order
Vaccination
So
By himself
Make a decision to nominate for the Supreme Court
To make
Horse vaccinations
Supreme Court
This would be like Garland
In 2016
I can't believe
Can't believe this
You know you want
People to find some Backbone in times of crisis
Just a little bit
From no one
Need
From the consequences of trump
Even worse
Interview scenarios
Himself
We need Trump
Used Supreme Court nomination
That you chose to make himself
It's not even making a lesser of two evils making an evil
Supreme Court
You know in the next 4 years
We might need
Bernie Sanders
As anything other than
F****** right-wing dingbats
Brave
It's one of those things where I think the right has to be a little disappointed in their dictator
Mussolini
They were they were evil dictators
Trump doesn't even know how to do barisan dictator
Where it's like you know how you
You made him good
Barnes about like
You know hey
What about you
So weak
This is just the weakest thing ever
What
Trump
Is Brentwood
How can you eat this much s***
This is so much eating this much s***
Tired
Yeah
Exactly
Alex is worried about going to jail Oregon
Position in the market
Surrounding Trump
You know
Over and over again probably true
God dammit
Really super viola
Shreveport doesn't matter
And this is it
Leave a little leftovers there
And then lick Trump's boots over and over and over again until maybe he uses
Smiles at you
But I don't know why
Disgraceful
Almost to like
I expect this
I expect them to pull out bowls
Trump flavored chips
And eat it in front of us because there's no bottom
But at the same time
How can anyone pull out of a trump flavored kit
And not be
Not have a problem continuing to
An argument for why somebody should not be nominated
As it's a great choice
Is a parrot
Ears
Or why it is parody is because he's
Literally saying you should vote for this guy because he's in appointing a Supreme Court Justice
Who's in favor of killing all of us
Who is
How do you estimate