Damn
I have great respect for knowledge
Sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Fight
Need
Need money
So Alex
Knowledge fight
Alex
3rd and Jordan
Quest what's up
First
Beautiful dog Fanny
The cutest dog in the world
Many
What we've been another
He is doing great dad
Case scenario is what the doctor said so I'm very excited
Animal is doing poorly it's a huge stress them
Realtor
Brought her into the home she had some issues
Pizza
When that all got resolved that it was such a
Believable relation crap
How do you make
And your
Dog
The partner family
How about you
Experiment has been
Seltzer show up
Completely out of
Pretty cool
Ghost pepper popcorn
Did you try that it will
Like I knows it right now there's the chocolate bar or whatever
Jared Holt
For charity
Never heard
Play hot
Really hot chocolate
Popcorn could be involved with
I feel like maybe there's a lot more territory we can explore their
I can handle Heat
Yeah
In our heart of hearts that it was there
Super
I'm not entirely sure how to pronounce this but it is a
Creation of
Your descriptions indeed
Describing all of the settings you can take place in some of those were very very funny
A lot of experience in the realm of
Of role-playing games but the first time
High school girl
School.
So I'm going to read this year
Possible ideas for a text Adventure I came across
This is an original flyer for a concert in honor of ex-president George Bush Senior
Gross The Weeknd
The place in July 2000
The Grove is far higher than the weekend before Newcastle
UK
An amazing flyer for a band concert celebrating George Bush Senior
Surreal
Program fire
Absolutely
So far towards like showing that like
This isn't
This secret is stove Society
They're letting us
All the credits for everybody who put on their pageants
You know it's like
Skitch Henderson
Bohemian Grove you know it's not a secret society Murderers Row
Classic conductor do a really awesome
First chair alright
BB space in the studio
I can pick a few things
This is shaping up
Accidentally I've been working for my entire life
Infowars magazine
Drake appreciate you very much
What Alex Jones
December 28th 2020 model Hyundai on this is 2020
So what's the reason for the 28th is because the night before the story of Trump's taxes in the New York Times bro
Obviously
You know
An interesting to see what maybe Alex says
Do the 20 minutes because today
And stream
Maybe on Friday aftermath
Episode
I just figured like a 28
Lexi
Expose
Going to get into it
First
You're not here I come
Commander Holly
Kuka people donated on elevators
Some okay
Read my
Nicorette
Heroin
Damn didn't read my
Is you all right
Yourself a mortar and pestle
Herbs from the garden
Alright
Ground that all up in World War II
It's okay
Exist right now but already
Turn it into a poultice Dan and you use that
To heal the ills of society
By a generous money to a bail fund or local charity
Did you mean wormwood
Totally effect
Is it
Okay fine
Is something from Disney
Alright
Is it just me or is the last ingredients
You need to put it in
I always thought that
It's also a
It's promising when I was like 9 years old
Beer brewing
We're out of Maryland okay that's probably about it
So probably
Could be possible
Do Jordan
And
That means before Trump's tax story Broadway
Sure
His response to that is
Here's not a contact dropped from Today Show
Avista totally
Emails again this is like there's a bridge
It's totally that
It's not it's not a relationship
Do those cost
And Alex got a pretty early this morning
On the 28th
He's got chills
The multiplying
I'll check your surge protector
Because
Weird noise
Yeah a little bit of a horse kind of action going on there
Cuzmi
Vine
3 minutes of chill
Experience
Attack if I've ever heard one
Fire lights
3 minutes 40 seconds
There's some sort of a report
Headlines
He wanted to talk about
Immediately
Through the House Majority political action committee
It was essential to have more Democrats in the house
It's a winner word determined by January 6th
The Electoral College
Only set up his letter in response to comments Trump made at a rally in Pennsylvania
I don't want to go back to Congress either even though we haven't
According to the Constitution the House vote for presidency does not by actual house members
As it stands now it's broke down on Purely party lines
Which is what Trump was talking about
Which is what
Fundraising letter
This is poo plan
It's her trying to raise money to elect more Democrats by warning that this
Clearly something
Are you democratic
This plan would not work
As always Alex is taking the Democratic response to something Trump says and claiming it's proof of their plan
Now
Do what your response was
First color of American history
Agrees with what he wanted
President
Kristin Davis
Proven
3 Senators approved offense
President by the house
Thomas Jefferson and Aaron Burr
Experience along with other frustrations
Which in addition to other issues are resolved
He made it to electrical cast separate votes for President and Vice President
Where previously they just forgot the most
Whoever came in
System
It was kind of amazing how stupid it was
John Quincy Adams who actually ended up second place in the Electoral College
Behind
A jacks
Between atoms and Speaker of the House Henry Clay
Which will
But that's because he was a terrifying idea of a president president
He was a terrifying monster of a present
If you if you go back and you look at the circumstances surrounding 1824 election
Intention of
Maybe maybe right.
Situation
Leaving that aside Alex has never happened in modern
American history more than 0 times
Hugely out-of-the-ordinary
He doesn't know anything about history
An idiot even like I'm not saying you're stupid even you
Next
You do yourself a lot of history disagree
Wait that happened here
History all the way up until like
What would the modernaires like 1918 or something like that
How stupid America was the
History makes you admire
History of the American exceptionalism
It really disabuse you of the notion I like
We are so great
Is back to talking about
Constantly
Don't they have a Plan B pill everyone Zoo
Yourself
Only able to stop playing even here
Edmodo
He was in a bad mood
So I made up plan B
Still on plan
Responsibility
When I get to murder everybody
And I kind of wanted to happen text
He's having a chill State about
Propaganda campaign
Alex believe that it's about how China made up the idea
Virus or social control
Actually I don't think I would just read this article which is actually
The media to promote their older response to the virus
Better in hindsight
Right right
Why can't the Chinese government clearly paid for box
To promote their response to the virus
Course pretty speculative territory like the idea
Walking down to the world in order to help bring about a socialist world
Assumptions being made along those lines
The Chinese government
Articles written by guy named Michael Singer
Twitter account
Is a Twitter account which is opened in August 2013 but the earliest tweet that appears in the timeline
From June 30th
About China
Okay it's just everything since then has been
Anderson Lee
You can find his LinkedIn page fairly easily and it turns out he's a federal and international Tax Lawyer
Which makes his expertise just lightly outside the realm of China's trying to run a psyop to control the world.
Don't know if International tax
Draw you to that
Conclusion your arm saying like is there a certain tax code
We know it's a propaganda campaign to try and turn the world into a social I'm not sure man are you sure
I don't have anything to go on here
Just everything I can tell makes me think that this guy
Writing an article
Doesn't have that much weight
Interesting
Just think
Skip the wet when it drifts into like
This is all fake
Alex's big narrative
A lot of it is like
Vagina
And iPad
Does
The op-ed
Mention China creating vampires and hiding them within their homes and
Play metal jury still out on the road
Vampire
Luke
Look at these
She says she will decide
Owl
Pelosi is third in line for the presidency after the Vice President in the event that there needs to be like a transference of power
The second thing is that idea that the house may vote on who wins the 2020 election if it's not decided by January
Alex news literally nothing about yourself
This is stupid because there are rules
Operate when they're voting for
This is very clear if you know anything about American history
The house can only
3 V receivers in the general election so it wouldn't even be possible for Pelosi to vote for herself
Asian goes to the house
Do surprisingly win the election
In the 1824 election
The Speaker of the House powerful Congressional
However
Hyper houseboat
Dysport
Atoms made Henry Clay Secretary of State
Government before in the past that people who have been friends of the president who suddenly got
How little I take the time to examine
Abnormalize to my history
Accidentally turned into a good person
This guy's a f******
Anthony became a good person Evers like
I was just forget about it it's your 58 if you're good dude
Yeah but we need to realize that a president was also a sitting Supreme Court Justice your like this can't be real
Corky
It's literally spelled out of the 12th Amendment that only the top three receivers could be considered for the house
In case they have to vote
For the president
We seen it play out past elections is not on president
Alex just seems to know nothing about the Constitution or history because if you did
By way of this house about
She couldn't be considered for that.
This would never happen
Just Alex talkingshit
Just
Yeah pretty much
Excited because David has been putting on speeches in the UK
Covid-19 great I hear
Police
Protestors or protesters
Crowley
He seems to be in
Favor of it
He's fixing to be worst thing in the world when it's being directed
Towards he like there's something inconsistent about that but I can't put my hand on it
A little something right
Trump rallies that Alex plays
Emily has John
We're humans were red-blooded what we're facing
Alright buddy
Okay that's
It's going to be 8
Citation
Alex come on man seems like he should be very aware though
That he has also been the victim of exactly that's it
Like he was supporting Trump because he thought he was going to be taken along with the ride
Between
Is that not possible for him
I've realized
Boo
I love
Just like you figure it out movie
Governor needs
Trampoline
Play character now
Unfortunately
Using our skills as
Just as public speakers we could run circles around
We could just lie like him easy just saying we we don't have
We don't have years of like baggage
They life
Who is WhatsApp
Videos
You guys better
I think
Videos of Alex
David Icke is a turd in the punch bowl
You used to say to make you look bad
Your conspiracy right-wing Patriot world
Uur
Spending your time celebrating
I can make you look worse than a turd in the punch bowl
Seems like he's run out of creativity run out of options
Bucket list
Why not
Call Sasha
Soros
Probably reach the point where like
Project Veritas releases don't even like intrigue
Solar still
That's what I'm mad at is that
Veritas video
No article
Skin care
Disturbing thing that anybody credibility
Brazenness
Well right
They've been wrong all the time or ever
Here's another time seems to me to be just a bummer it's the same
Reached it seems okay to me at 3 to Jacob Walter
Where is
I'm not even interested in what is news Dante's or whatever
Near we go again you guys have your fun with your b*******
Some D constructions of this new video that's okay Scott and I'm
The level of like
I care to debunk now it's meteorologist played a clip of Sharknado that's what level
Research and reality we're dealing with here
Or yeah I was trying to think of another one of those movies
Show David Icke
I wish I wish it was just that guy so f****** dumb
A prophet little bit about his career
My broadcast
Predicted
David I could not go on Alex's showed predict that stuff
By the year 25 years ago is gas-lighting
95 pretty strongly promoted the protocols of the Elders of Zion
Oh no
0410 like
Unfair
I don't give a s***
Leaving David Icke earlier career aside
Because
Even Alex a turd in the punch bowl
Is current
Career
Had some problems
Like what
Solution to tyranny
What
The notion of self-respect is the thing is broken down all tyrannies is such a stupid and meaningless idea that I have no.
The even address it is a serious thing that someone say
Self respect
Very very f*****-up
If you believe that all tyranny of destroyed by self-respect then there's never been a situation where tyrants have existed except
This is where the people they were
There's a pretty nice version of victim if I were Alex
I would ask
The bought this phone
Did the Jews in Nazi Germany just not respect themselves enough
Did the Native Americans
Is the actual problem with the Chinese government don't respect themselves
You can easily sell this mentality is painfully childish and has no relationship to the real world
All this is an attempt by David Icke to paint himself as the only person that the real answer to the problems of the day
We should respect ourselves and others
You're going to find yourself subject of tyrannical rule really a lot
So here's the thing
I bet really
Is it
Alright
When they got the Tyrant they want the only thing that stops tyranny
Is self-respect
It seems like the only way Tyron sleeve is in Chains or in a body bag
Y'all seem strange different versions of tyrant
Fight against
Dan
It is strange how that works
I wonder I wonder why that is case
I think I picked sides
I can't
I can't stress
Show little people
People like David Icke
I expect
Nothing from have nothing
Really stupid David
Oh my God
Alex interview
Levelland phone
You respect yourself just I don't
Yeah
That's how we doing
Torrid tear down that brick wall mr. Gorbachev I have finally self-respect
Respect yourself
But this has the same
Hey you know if you stand up for yourself
People together because you're only one guy the other people
I mean may work
Teaching a child
Or whatever
No no
No I mean business interpretation
Interpretation of that would be like
It has to
Can't simply acquiesce
To the terror
You know like if everybody respects themselves
They won't acquiesce to tyranny but that's
Still stupid b*******
Complexity
Life of how people actually live
Themselves
Respect for myself
Where
Is it not
What
Yeah man
It's not even just made it anymore
Well obviously at aliens from outer space the Bible says it
Set the Bible says aliens are real
Not debated
Anymore
You almost came out and he was like I look aliens has been controlling Human Society
Kill 7 billion
Removing the wrestler
So and two-time Oscar Award nominee
I can't
Tell you anything about vampires who are we have no updates on vampire
Another
Sort of character of the Sci-Fi Realm
David Icke
It is not that
It is cyborg
That's my favorite rhetorical trick
I do love the Rays
Do you know the first case of covid
Do you know why they want to turn this into cyborg
Just got f****** high and watch the episode that had the Borg Next Generation
Tom Hardy's finest worth
God it's just
Painful
It's just painful
I think this is really interesting because
He's talking about these cyborgs said he calls the psychopath naturally
Makes a clarification here that I thought was going to go the exact opposite direction that it does
Human
Beside
Now I'm going to pause right there because
I'm speaking metaphorically
I will come out for once in my not while listening to that not once a day
I think he was not being 100% literal speaking with terms
Technology
It's like
Alright look just
Just to be clear
I'm not talking about anything anybody knows exists
This is like Isaac ocean it is like Isaac Asimov nevermind
Are somebody
Counterpoint
I'm talking about something
If you don't even know
I think we should be run by AI machine learning
Machine learning is tackled go
And turned it into something that is
Inconceivable and they just wins all the time against the top go players in the world
You feed all of human history into an AI and machine learning
And it's going to be like
The only time good things happen is when people cooperate with each other
So
I don't think it's going to make the the pull the trigger kill all humans thing I think it's going to be like
We can't allow them to govern themselves
Cops are stupid
We just will take care of it
Are you going to be happy that's my guess
That's right. I'm not sure I agree with you 100%
Tougher for me to support you in your bed for despotic leader
But you have some interesting ideas
And everybody gets
To kill me
Look at the world right now
The world in your
Where are you
I can't support this dictatorship it has flaws
Is not good
Dishonesty what I cannot get behind.
Israelite
Alex is talking about
Watch some videos
Police
Bye.
We learned
Not all humans either
Human behavior
They're coming for her
Empathy is apparently genetic
He said stuff like that a lot
Every single time
It's bad
Yeah
Really f***** up 100% against you
Evil
Admittedly there are genetic human population
You know
Things that are genetic like empathy
Sure
Brother
Has a complaint about the alternative media
Complained
That
Honestly
I know you could hear this isn't calling out out
It's not meant to be
He's saying he's a guys like
Tell people not to wear masks
Put your money where your mouth is
I feel like I could be like
Why do you stop f****** trying to make money off of
Wow
Won't you
Going into a shop
With a mask on
Longboard
Broke
Icracked
Oh no it's never going to end
Just never going to have never
The power of the way David Icke is trying to
Power of oppositional Defiance to annoy everyone around you
It's just one letter off
Mister real opportunity for a follow-up book
Wrap up their interview and I who cares I mean wow
Oppressively dumb interview
Impressively bad
From break
And
He's real excited about his show
Subway
Angry ocean
Price
Is happening
What is the answer to civilization in society as we like this
Play necessarily rude
Cruise possible does this dress make me look good no
I've been thinking what's wrong with you
Listen to
Alex criticism well
You know I think a great conversation stupid
Dub dub
I can't imagine what you suggested he would be interested in
Gauging
Incredibly rude to the point of
I just pointing out all of your flaws like
God damn you're so stupid don't you remember the Golden Rule treat others the way that you
Alright so here's some hard truths or was that
When you talk about a star-studded show you are talkin about any show other than this one
Oh God
Paul Joseph Watson
Someone who
Is a real loser
Oh yeah James O'Keefe
Someone who was an embarrassing loser
David Icke
Someone who you
Yourself Alex
Pink sucks
Call Marisa
Weather
Coronavirus
People in the US
Many media Outlets have not recorded on this server but Infowars
Misleading information
This is a report that was released by
Consulting firm called text to CNC
Curious at all about this about why the methodology
The biggest use the meaning of responses to determine the average
Which would be the appropriate way to reflect data like that
When you take something like the survey is meant to report
Your figure is going to be heavily affected by outliers in the data
That the David Sipe represents billion people
You can't be doing 10 billion
For instance in this case both act for the text
CNC reports claim
7% of the population had died
From covid-19
Over 50% of respondents answered 1% or lower
People who answered with numbers in the range of 20% or higher
But there wasn't none significant number people
Relative speed 50% Ohio
F****** around or whatever determine
People having a race
Pull factor estimates
50 medium
Average of responses
Would be somewhere close to 1%
It substantially lower than the 7% at this report claimed by some dodgy media
Yeah, this report was ignored by legitimate Outlet is it because they were afraid because there's a cover-up
It's because the methodology was flawed and it didn't meet there at Oriel standard
People like Paul and Alex have no such standard
As if there were no problems with this survey
And that's what
And then complaining that no one else is reporting it as proof
Information I would believe from
Any of these people would just be like suddenly all this Saturday turn and look up into the sky in the election
Where is it I have to find it we can use it
If it helps
Somewhere in the world
So into a mood and
He doesn't come back in on the break
Intimately I couldn't care at all about their interview
Whatever he's like
President
I was listening to that when he's like I can see it I can feel it I can taste it like
Yourself
I was like well
You had your chance
Tower anyway so export our
Now some other host
I'm taking over so
What is disaster
Episode
Am I surprised by that Dan am I surprised
You
For somebody whose only outlet for information
You can be forgiven for not knowing that that story broke
Nothing
Just nothing just pretend it didn't happen doesn't exist something to talk about
Pretty regularly
Is whenever it's something really bad
You know how every news Outlet
CNN's got it on there in minutes Guardian got live
At least a couple hours
Fox News
Has taken their time
Has really developed a good spin on it
Called in that breaking kind of news story
And that takes time and they're professionals it really good at it
Isn't even a story that he's interested in
And James O'Keefe
Being about
I think
Speak
Do like this being a very dangerous story
It seems like it would be much easier to spin
Galax Mikey of the Maya
Cuz it's it's
Inconceivable
To have lost a lot of money
I have paid more taxes than Trump
I need to find his lawyers
Like at the very least one of us
Exactly
Rudy Giuliani
He's going to get you
It's so easy to be like
This guy is rich
He didn't pay as much taxes in you
Then you is that fair
Come on
Easy for Alex
Super
Put upon by the Federal Reserve
Great
So we should be cool with this
Super billionaire
Not screwed I can't how many people
There's an astonishing number
Who are like
Waytogo
Get your money away from the government like they're so happy
Even
Situation
Where would you like
I don't know I'm I'm conflicted on whether I
Disable this is surprising or unsurprising that there's like absolutely
No mention of it in these three hours
I'm surprised
Sing to me
What you going to say about it
He lost it because one reason is
Lost a $1
And if it was for a TV show that you should never have been a part of because it was entirely built around an image
We know now
Is
Distill lost money
After we got all that more money was like
Now I can really lose a lot of money
There are other reports yet
Come out even as we're recording this
The Pacific
His we don't know the scope of it yet we have already proved
System exists in such a way that we can find out
Be at like
Hundred percent the president was in violation of the Constitution from Dave
And they're still like
We have to deal with this 3 Supreme Court Justices forever
Constitution
Yeah it's got to be a Supreme Court Justice is forever
Damn
The other than that I think is really funny
Is that
Times article
Very similar
To the one that
Probably
I guess maybe for a date Friday
So glad we're recording now so we have no reason to watch the debate
Hey
My name is
Toronto and
Georgia and die
Weeks ago started
Job at call center
Survey
And I'd
But I tell you I get a couple
We answer the phone
Take the survey that sounds a lot like our
Text Joseph
So I
Opinion
Forgotten
First
Last call I got was an old guy who
Probably kind of drunk
I had to hang up
Architect
Guy I got
Was it usual
Answer the call by thing from 2020
Took the survey
Answered as much as
You think
Gables opinion on Apple
Call Tony
Not to trust anything I heard from either side as long as I live
And
A guy with the most interesting
Propecia
Had all night
Take a survey
Then proceeded to refuse to answer any of the questions
And only would answer undecided
And then when I asked what historical party.
Druid
And
All three of them
Dislike
Simonson hours
What what kind of car
Respond to my
Going to get
And I also wanted to know
Socialist
Turn your familiar with
Touching something very
I want to show great
Great job guys I
Dance
Trampoline shaed
I'll pass that along to
She's
To tell you unfortunately so is still list Druids would be considered Witches by Alex
National Socialist
National socialism
Sound like
Not fun calls
Whenever I first started
In-N-Out in the in the hearing aid business
Decidedly not Glengarry leads like I was still competing to get the Glengarry lead right
Brutal phone calls
Hey how you doing you want to spend three grand on something
I spent a bit of time
Doing telemarketing companies in Missouri and
But nightmare
They were supposed to be everybody your calling
Is a small business owner
Nobody wants to talk to you
Great explain to people
Cuz this is before like stamps.com existed and everything
Download
Posted YouTube
I have no idea what you're talking about
My first day
Almost
Person on the line
Could tell was like not really understanding was going on
Yes good conscience
Salesman
I screwed myself over on another commission there and I didn't
Not a surprise
Terrible job call center that was doing like non-sales survey
And I was calling
Brought for the Democratic
Congressional Campaign
Committee
And they always tell you that like people are registered Democrat
It was brutal time very. Very much for people who work in those
B a lawful abuse goes your way
Telemarketing sales is the Warriors
Stop
This is Jordan
Great Name by the way they're Jordan
I'm just calling to say
You guys are awesome
And I know I try to be nice by Pirates any both makes a very good point
On this karaoke video karaoke issue
And by the way
ArrowPointe Daddy
You've certainly heard the studies that clients
Grow better when you think
Before I delete this message
I looked it up on Google and
The first one cannot disagree with me
So in honor of your choking about out of Coconut Creek
I figure that was about as far as I have to look
I mean that's it just you know
Sing
Single-dose plan Stan come on still grow better if you do
What you doing
I would do it
I would sooner sing to these plants
It's them two then I would do karaoke I'll do that
Is just the same as talking
Splats sure
Just because
Whatever you're playing
Singing for like 2 hours in front of you
Anyway
What's up cat guy
Too bad I can't stand the rain
Question
By the way
And you're talking about
Happiness
Accent thing or
You accusing a different
Brewery
Explain that I don't
Hello she never cheat and congratulated
I thought that was
Weird
That is weird
Putting hydrogen peroxide on the foot of a mule
People do
I don't know I guess I've never really known what the term is
Because I thought it was some sort of
It's happening
Pronouncing that way so I was like
Maybe it is maybe I don't know I've always called it like
Anyting
Gasoline
Huh
The car wash you huh
Something
Intentionally at the carwash
Sure
Friends
Eat her a little bit it's a Hyundai seems scary scary
I got a friend
Yo
Missouri call
Sheldon
Search Hangouts
A guy doing
Tile
Colorado
Loved Alex
And because of that I might have some
Insight on the
So
According to
To come in
And you
Of course he gestured that I do now
Picture of values
Got a bunch
Lola or
So
Just a thought also
Shout out
My Buddy doll
I love you
Alright thanks
Would make sense
That was what I thought was going on in the business for 10 years is going to be like
Infowars is where I'm going to finally retire
Make checks out
The car wash.
There was a crew of fifteen-year-olds yeah you're going to say some Alex Jones
Hate
Guys
City
And
I love you sure
My comrade
Investigate the right way
They don't really
The shame
Cuz I am going
Sheet metal
You put that support
Jordans
Please call.
Or don't I'll be Saturday
Whatever
Anyway
That's Oklahoma
Dubai
Jordans
The person's name was gator
Do you know
It could be
Ruth Bader Ginsburg
She was going to call
Always very difficult for me
With specific
Giving specifics on his faults with me because
That deserve attention to our far more than I would ever be able to numerate
How many things that are localized that are
A people who are in foreign countries and all around the country live up to our show
Add the priorities for everybody
In their own communities in their areas is very difficult for me
To think I have any real understanding of
So whenever we say
Get more specific about it is because
Are you the person listening
It might be something that I could have no idea about and I don't want to
Take
Our audience and monetize toward
Even a good cause an Xterra
And Chicago
Dispensary depository like
I don't want all of our listeners
To donate to them area
Said I'm also not averse to people
Promoting something that's important
Like
It's a balance
It it something it's incredibly
Difficult to understand like to know what to do with sure
I try and focus on
Like personally my my two things are like especially right now
Food and housing so I try and look out organizations in Chicago
And really research the Sham cuz a lot of them
There's some places that you can give money to that are
F****** b*******
So do some research on that but
As far as
Protesting stuff go
Medics are
Huge Medics are absolutely strongly recommend people do that
Citizen journalists Gordon to support his message 100%
I don't get too specific about stuff is because
I honestly also think
Like that
Part of being involved and engaged is the process of finding a thing
And being able to tell whether it's legitimate
Part of Engagement
For what
Priority
Your position
What you're giving money to
What's the best way for
And it's for you to be comfortable knowing that
What you're doing is making a difference in the way that you want it to
Totally
Balancing the responsibilities of I know a lot of people are listening and I can hopefully encourage them
And also knowing
I could steer people towards something irresponsible
It's a hard line to walk
And the way that I think I could be
Best
On the right side of it is just to say
People in need in your area
Susan causes and all that stuff I have my job
Pet charities
Yeah it's a it's a hard line to know exactly where it is
And maybe we could do a little better
Call Aaron
And plug something in particular
I am more than
Kmart
On Friday but until then we website
Find a local charity or bail signed in your area if you're in Oklahoma City you know where to go
You can also call in number enough
So you want to call and leave a message
That is a number
Are you mad at me
Alex