Damned important
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
We are the bad guys
Need
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Everybody was acknowledged
Text Junior I have a quick question for you
We are recording with a new setup
It involves
Sort of a secondary bright spot that is a little bit of Letting Go on my part
And apologies a little bit the last couple episodes going on
Is that I think our equipment suck
Wow I've been very defensive about it
Oh no that discovered soundboard on the floor right now that's
That's the picture of Festival
I think there's something a little bit unexamined about
My attachment
To it to Soundboard a text
8 years or something you know
We just got to a point the last week or so that was just like well
We have ideas about things we want to do in terms of like being able to
Record some video and bring back some streaming
Difficulties of the stuff we were experiencing encroached into the actual sound of the episodes
It is the thing where I kind of had to like finally reached the moment of surrender and she like
Now I got to let go be like whenever we're still like there's something wrong with the
My finger in this hole-in-the-wall Wrightsville be a flood
You sort of gently pushing me towards that
Gentle approach bullying about like the packaged and you just have a Sentimental attachment
Manipulative
Are you fool
I hope that the sound is better on this episode and we won't really fully know until after we're done work
According to its kind of a double-edged sword
But hopefully that is the case and I'm excited about the prospect of like what this pretend
For the future in like what will be able to do
It has worked better well you're not hearing
Yeah I know a lot of people have been clamoring for things like bringing back some live streams that
I know that you and I have both talked a ton about various ways we could incorporate video and
Excited about the possibilities of like
Figuring out what ways we can take those things and
Expand the product of what we do very excited
Running on like no sleep
It took out it's a lot to make this bright by happened I I would assume that your bright spot would more be the scent of a
Achievement that you had from putting together this Sandman I didn't want to brag
Because it might not work
The process of setting up his new sound system I received a few texts
Hours apart which means that I missed out on minute-by-minute updates of frustration
And fury
Late in the evening last night I texted you something along the lines of like the sheet isn't working out
Basically prepare you for going to workout
You did not really respond to that message
For a while and I got the message
Loud and clear
Activate an important ritual that we have if we are cooking try not to do outside stuff
Well that came across as
You made your bed now lie in it I'm sorry I didn't mean to tell you what your bright spot was
My bright spot is commanding
No my bright spot Dan is I finally on your your recommendation
I finally got to playing The Last of Us so sure and it is fantastic
Really good
It's great to watch it's got a very cinematic feel I enjoy it immensely
I have that recommendation is really a media
I told you maybe a couple of days ago because I just started playing as well
Well I mean I'm a very middle
In the middle I've gotten a few hours like the opening
Movie thing with great story
Just a kind of like
The care about the characters
Interested in
I am note on the streets is not a zombie guy
I have a lot of people who I've known to friends
You've been deep into zombie stuff and it's never really intrigue me much
And it's nice
To try try out a survival horror game and if you like that this is kind of fun I enjoyed
F*** around a player Resident Evil always a little bit bored whenever something is universally beloved
And one all these awards are going to try it and it's
Great that deserves everything I'm like okay fine yeah what's the point of me then I could just be anybody else
Out there
I'm supposed to come with a good taste
Uniqueness is gone or you love the thing everyone loves
Really good pizza is great good for everybody who has that we're all on the same team it's nice to be nice to be
An accepted member of the community I would love to have played more last of us but I can't
Because I have been
I was cooking dinner.
Video game
It was a it was a lot because
It's not that bad
Jordan is the debate coverage
Have Alex Jones Aldi in between
Answer that was a whole lot of territory to cover a lot on my plate
And I really am jealous of
Time that I used to have to play videogames all be able to get back to playing a little bit
And maybe hit somebody with a baseball bat
So we're going to get to this episode on here it's really silly
It's very stupid
So first casualty from Sweden thank you so much
Casualties to get it on Sonia's territory
Patrick d
Text Raymond.
Hey Raymond Little Goat Man
Thank you so much and I'll probably walk
How much little go mad and I'll probably walk
Very much Mick Riley defense
O'Reilly
Then finally like to say thank you to come people donated on elevator
First Jack
Thank you so much right now.
How's your 401k
What's the business
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
Much adequate mousse
No moose are adequate above-average to me
Above-average
Well he's not almost at the small sample size there's one
Busy
What is friends with a flying squirrel
That one is obvious that one everybody does this true of almost
If you're out there listening if they can enjoy the show and love moose I'd like to support these are very promo
You can do is take that generous spirit and you feeling about mr. Peabody
Leaving body now I'm now I've lost it
Through the Wasteland covered in fungus and take that to create the vaccine
Truth and Love and generosity
That will carry us all through this by going to
A local charity or belt
I feel like I executed that one you gave me no positive reinforcement
Wanted
Ferry golf shut up Edward Everett Horton
The voices
Used to Know
Anyway Jordan today what we're going to be going over is too much
Time
North normally do which is really swing too hard for no
Answer they did ours of coverage before the debate tonight
Are we going to do right then did the debate coverage
So we're going to be looking at that and then we're going to be looking at September 30th
The day after the debate where Alex comes in and tries to
Suspend things I was going to say I assume their immediate reaction when the debate happened was that of the rest of the world which is just like
No
It's
Oh God I think all God no cated then that there is an element
Element that I think a lot of people who don't look at this stuff
Regularly would be surprised to know he's a piece of their response to it
And I think I understand fully and that'll probably be a large part of our conversation
Here is an out-of-context drop
From Today Show
Military
Turn off that's true
That's what I find the most difficult to argue
What about the military he makes a good point that is I mean is it a good point
I think it's a point
And it's a defensible what that's what I'm saying I don't know if it's a good one
I'm saying that I can't argue against
Here we start the free debate and I got real bad out because Owen Shroyer toasting the beginning of it
And it starts with
What appears to be taunting Joe Biden to debate
In the pre-show to the debate that Joe Biden is doing okay
I mean yes
Can JoJo come out and debate
Yes that is
That is
Time sleepy Joe
It's almost time sleepy Joe
Wake up from that nap
Sleepy Joe
Come out of that bass
They've been doing this thing for so long where they're like this debate isn't going to happen
Themselves into like it is happening
You can't really talk somebody
When they've agreed to do the thing already
In the pre-show of it is starting
It's such a built-up narrative of like they're they're going to cancel the debate
Come on you coward
Debate me I agree two weeks ago I got we've already set this as it's been plan people have been advertised backstage having a
Week 2 dababy no I mean
Actually I am already
Talking to you and now that the debate is going to happen of course there have to be reasons why Joe Biden
Isn't
The character debate made him out
A candidate's kind of at an angle looking in maybe that makes it easier to hide Biden's earpiece
Where is the door that they're going to shuffle by Dan off to to give him a quick hit
Of speed
Or adrenochrome or whatever they are
Stored
For him to keep him alive for 90 minutes
Alright so get the earpiece narrative
I never understood why they think that's a good line of attack on Joe Biden
Taking drugs to get through this
Dude I'm taking drugs to get through this f*** yeah I do hope he's taking drugs everyone watching it home is ham
Oh no drugs
Phuc yea
I was in favor of Sammy Sosa taking performance-enhancing drugs you think I'm not going to be Pro the guy fighting again
Fascism hell yeah
I think I think that there might be something
Into that and then also they're just like
Who cares
Who cares if someone's on speed
What what you think
Your perception is decided he must be on speed drugs
Okay
Hulu no evidence of that
Owens trying to do whatever he can because there's no debate yet like it's still the pre-show inside
He's like
Trying to make fun of things like the podium and like crowd
Hey you the shirt is f****** sign over here they got
Stand up in front of a brick wall what is this place that kind of thing
Oma have a nice little covid test
Testing
Center there
For anybody who's going to be attending isn't
That nice
Oso
Brandy
Will it be
The flim-flam in the land
The Slam in the land will it be the Sham
In the land
Orwell
Joe Biden get
Cleaved
In the land
This is Infowars
Presidential debate
Coverage mail.
Wolf
Yep really get clear in the land of a walk
Requires
A meeting in the office after you're off are just like come here
Let's review your performance here
I don't think so I think he was told to do that
Because he says cleaved in the land sure
It I think it's even in the title of like the
Video release
Something about
Cleveland Lance because it's so catchy
So catchy a lot of people say that you've been cleaved in the land before Cleveland
I got it
Anyway Joe Biden you be sleepy
I'm sure it's going to be a wild night ladies and gentlemen
90 minutes
Oh my God
Joe Biden
Gold sleepy Joe is he going to be able to make
He can't make it they've already admitted that he needs an earpiece and needs a
A nap nap break every 30 minutes
But are you can be president
This is there is nothing going on is brutal
Over cuz he decided to start taking some calls and get the caller who's like
This is this lady's trying to make a joke
Listen to How Great Owens improv chops are
And at the end
Well he doesn't even have a job though Biden even have a job
I was thinking about it
Yeah the old
Apprentice
Well
Are you crazy
Something crazy
Does anybody want to be there
That's not good
I like it on fire and then forget where it came from
From the
Reality
Apprentice
Did you hear my plan about cleaving to the land leave the land pretty good
Owen as a feeling that this is going to be something that reminds us of another important debate and
History
A sloppy Joe Biden
Comes in against a well-put-together shining glowing Trump
It's very similar to another debate maybe the first ever televised debate
Now it's not about this is that Owen doesn't know who to put in that debate
I forget
What
The first
Televised presidential debate wise Hyundai
I'm trying to remember but it was because one of the candidates
The watershed moment in history
Unkempt
And in the other candidate was
Was
It was Nixon and the who is he again
My God
What did Nixon JFK Mixon and who
Your help me out here
So it hears a telling Pig here's a telling think this is a telling thing if you remember Nix
Send but not who he was debating in the first televised debate right you're a fascist
I have some question if you also initially don't remember either
You probably shouldn't be working at a
News about family not going to trust your Thomas Jefferson quotes from here on out it strikes me as like that.
Should have coming speaker tackled him
Please Alliance alright let's talk about how the Indians is somehow not a racist name I don't know
Call from a funny person
And then s*** on their joke
Grease Infowars reporter Gregory Shore his on the seeing Believin Volant okay
Greg Reese
From Cleveland Ohio to side
The first presidential debate what are you expecting tonight
I do laid out all
Possibilities
Please
In Atlanta
Really
Stabbed
Ask Diddy
Reconnected here he's
Obviously right outside the venue and they probably have all kinds of
Stingray Triggerfish technology just destroying nnn sucking up
Any and all communication
Look it reconnected with Greg
Probably triggerfish
I've been to these things
Before folks
They're just all kind
And stop blocking signals and
An intercept
A lot of Infowars reporters have trouble
Yeah it's probably a scalar attack I'm going to go with if more than one invoice now
We only have two examples here Dad so that's not yet a pattern developing
Have we ever had any more examples of Infowars remote people struggling to talk over the
I would say everyday okay so now I'm going to start going out on a limb and say that that pattern would suggested
Is actually the Infowars it does lead you towards that conclusion
There's more supporting evidence of a triggerfish
Do you like that today
Probably drone is there trying to intercept our communication
It's better than Alex
Gets mad
So he doesn't getting Greg on the line and the triggerfish
Apparently it stopped working call around
Miracle
And this is just two dudes who are like I really hope this gets canceled
I think I'm going to Green I think that your people just confuse him
Plus with the crowd and the light
Lights in the pressure I mean
I don't think the earpiece really doesn't any advantage is I mean
Unless they've been training him on it maybe
And they definitely want to drug him up
That's why they got to take the breaks
Hey look we still got
2 hours and change you never know by Timaya
You know he made flounder and just can't
Rafiki
Testing you test positive and it's
National Emergency
Who knows
Who knows who knows
Just spitballing who knows
You ever get hurt by a but maybe if he does know
Okay I got would continue their
Is incapable of Joy really don't understand what a debate
It is I feel like
They're hyping it up like they're actually going to fight
Oh yeah Alex Stars 2
Like he talks about how like he used to watch Tyson fights and back when he was a kid
I'm with letting all these right-wing douchebags debate online for so long
Well that's what I'm saying like they don't understand that what we're supposed to be watching is a very boring
Conversation
About tax policy moving forward
Whether certain cap on wealth
You're a loser no that's not a debate
It's disappointing no but they were and
We've not talked a lot about our thoughts about the debate part of that is because we're going to get to that little bit
But later but
You want a spoiler
What
Whatever happened to being like I have a 2.2 trillion dollar spending plan
Sir you're out of your mind I have a 1.8 trillion dollar spending plan to enjoy those debates
Actually kind of interesting.
Do you not know my policy walk that should be boring as hell like he should be MacNeil Lehrer
Come on
Speaking fingerboarding Owen
Doing this
Was it
Disaster it was so hard to get through
Thankfully
Our inner so Alex shows up and we start to get back into business okay
We are 2 hours out
From
Reality show
Donald Trump
Joe Biden
Clearly has had
Bullfrogs
Abated
Welcoming onset of
Serious dementia and Alzheimer
Delirium
You're going to see
Something never before done
No one's ever run
At this level like
National Television
Confident person
And no one has ever stood up as Donald John Trump
Alex is really on that tip articulation of the way Alex Hasbro
Presented Joe Biden
In the months prior to the audience
If you're somebody who listen to Alex and take some seriously you have every reason to think like
Biden's going to come up there Derulo
He's going to call like
Trump mommy or something
It's going to be it's going to be a mess
That's bad to be Biden's this in the minds of an Infowars I'm confused as to why
They aren't doing preemptive damage control like
I would have gone heavy on the drugs thing cuz that's the only way to explain
That you obviously know your been full of s*** this entire time otherwise you look like you believe what
Bulshit you are selling well and he's going to go on stage in an hour and prove that he's fine there's the earpiece
It's around like him and knowing showing the amphetamines that gets around 3
Do you like well he's usually
Mentally so slow
And Alex has a third thing that comes up later that's just
Remarkable
But I noticed that Alex seems a little slow
He's
Probably drunk
He should do performance-enhancing
But you might later this takes a really weird
We'll see okay
Alex is one of his complaint to the fighting to Liar right because he said that millions of people died of covid-19
Sure when in reality that clip italics played he cuts it off right where buy
Correct himself
Isaac has he had misspoken where's Alex
Pretends that he actually said the millions died
Just remember that
Damn thing comes out
At last
Suite 200 million Americans
Keepers of the population
Can Plus
Covid-19
It wasn't even 1/2
A 1%
It wasn't 1/10 of
1% yield
Lying
Glass rack
Now
That was
The first thing that I heard through this entire time there was a
Interesting to me what is a flask
Where do you think it is
Maybe maybe something from Ender's Game or childhood
Painting
Play Rags from
With a flat rag
You think it's like maybe an Elizabethan or Renaissance Tower
It's from Coneheads
What a nerd that's the only thing that I respect about him it's sometime
It'll come through where it's like
You and I are nerds bad don't don't tell me that you don't even like Star Wars if you're going to drop
Flat rag Star Wars you like
Conehead
Which no one appreciates now dad calls the daughter when he saying the cheese dress
Best to promiscuously
Call Zuri flat rag on payday so accurate is dowsing out supplies rag
What are you call it animology
Netflix
I appreciate I haven't watched it since way back when I liked it in the 90s
I mean I'm not I'm not mad at somebody liking it now I think it's silly for Alex
Call B in a flatbread 100% silly for Alex called Biden The Flash rag
Insult that sounds interesting in order comes up with his
LaFollette
Jesus
That's not great
That's a good reference for me that would be like I like that that's an obscure reference
It's a little esoteric and it has a fun sounding name to it I would use that in a bit if I could pull it off in a bit
It doesn't belong here no no that's my point
So Alex is talking about the eventuality or the possibility that Trump could lose the election
And if so
Blood in the streets baby
Caught up
We don't care so much
You take it for granted
Where were
Do you know if you got a hundred bucks
Fight
Your fighter loses
OtterBox
Waterbox
Call Gabby was at
Baseball whatever
That's true
We lose this
Civil War
Show me blogs
Don't think you do not set up
So anyhow it's it's explicit if you lose the election blood in the streets Civil War
Set up the precondition that they'd impossible to have a fair election
They're basically just saying like Civil War is going to start this winter
I'm bored with me I don't want a civil war to start but I would like them to stop with this
Teasing
Totally
This is nonsensical and frustrated
I would prefer
That they just showed up correctly edging me at a civil war
You've already said that there's no possible way he's going to lose
Which means you already know he's going to lose
He said if he loses that the election was stolen which cuz of you know he's going to lose in a free election
Most likely just started Civil War I'm bored
Well I Lord
I think that I don't want anyone to get hurt and I think the possibilities of what that looks like in the real world is
Like you know possibly
Lone Wolf type. Appearing actors
I would like this
Start the season 2 end
You know like this art
Realize whatever it is this building is intensity towards this Biz fantasized
Civil War I would like for the chapter 2 end
But I don't want it to come to fruition where there's an attempt or an actual star
I would just like for Alex to move on
To the next part where he's back to selling gold or whatever
Like this is annoying
Bored
Tinged with scared
I'm absolutely terrified especially since later on the debate Trump said that it's cool to kill us
Alex meixner
It is responsive that weird okay
How much money you think
Donald Trump got
From what
Total
All day
I mean net
Or gross
Dealers Choice
I'm going to go with net
Negative several hundred million dollars
What am I gross
About 15
Dollars different figures
Is it about
Search for the truth
Donald Trump
Tama.
12 billion
Neri oxman is he
He's got a billion dollars
Billion dollars
4 years
While they shot his ass
Never been happier
I'm taking this fine.
Got the money
The money
Was only
About
Scrub system
Do not remember him saying that
Bring it back to
That's real Powerman
I would like audio of him saying that since I already have audio of him admitting to killing hundreds of thousands of people
Obviously all that is total nonsense but I think at the end there Alex is saying something that I find very interesting
He's talked about I drop doesn't care about the money the money is always about just fueling us fight against the corrupt system of the globalist
That's comically not true but it's exactly what Alex says about himself
When he's trying to sell his dump pills in food bucket to buy a product
Stately repeats he doesn't want money even like money
You will divide the globalist
Now in 10 minutes he was going to say that without money which he loves very dearly as well be able to he hates them
I need to fight the global yeah but he loves money without because of money
So what's going on here is that Alex is desperate to sell but in this case the product
What is Donald Trump
In order to picture supporting this
Completely unacceptable clearly aspiring dictator Alex needs to dress him up in the costume
Of Alex Jones's own idealized self
Vision of himself
As being like he doesn't care about the money it's just about fighting the globalist huh that's the fictional ideal heroic version
Alex
But he sells to the audience what you need the money
He's just transmuting that onto onto Trump
Narcissist
Like that is so narcissistic that it's him saying like
To his audience
You need to vote for him because he's made
Wiley's
The person that I tell you about when I want you to feel good about me
Silly
Guy guy who's worth a billion dollars doesn't care about money just wants to play the globalist
Or in the other corner
Guy
Who is so evil
So evil they do evil is Satan told him to
Heat press a button and destroy the world
But a joke
Order
Turn it up so fast
It'll make your head spin
He is a
Pop it
Depop at you pop it
Again
Everybody better
Stop laughing
You're not looking at people
Talk
Baby will look like
Every damn one of them
Zombie because they are
There is not one
The god in them
They are the boys
The holy spirit is gone
Completely
And totally turned over
So at this point I was thinking that Alex was drunk
You know like he has a lot of Fairly, and drunk tones
And then also just kind of like guy gets into these weird
Tangential that's do I have
I'm at this is where I where I kind of really decided like
It's a yeah this dude
Drunk
That's been a few
And a few minutes
Talking about how
I'll break you off
They had red blood
And I love you
Makes you laugh
And I worked hard
A lot of adversity and they built
This country and they built
This world
Technology we have
And they busted their ass
Ashwood Loving Care
To bring us where we all right
We Know The Enemy
Joe Biden
Before human
WhitePages
Call today
What about
Actors
Faulty
And those billions of
Souls weight
Who are you with God
1 /
Riding with
We be with them
Forever
Don't Fear the enemy
They can take your money
Your house
Wife
Worry about
Take your soul
70 minutes and I'm done
Let's talk
Stockton cold heart
Joe Biden
Going to be drugged
Okay
Dhgate
Almost
F****** crying
Talking fairy
Very traditional drunk Alex
It's not as fun as other times in the past like I'll just spoiled it there's no Hatchet Pro
But he's clearly like impaired in some way
He's talking about his dancestor
He gets off that topic jumps and talks about how Biden going to be drugged up
Sure
You got to do a little more
We stayed
Princess
Been through this
You fought on the cuddle battery
Was that play everytime we
Save the Republic
The filth
Chris Wallace
Confederate loyalty is royalty
It just makes
The enemies closer
And closer
Play Closer.
You know
I knew
Ryder
Kurt Vonnegut
Call daughter
What was the cat's cradle about Alex Jones
It's alright
Yeah he
The story isn't very interesting Alex get used to call in
And would have been on the show but he hurt
Bonaparte himself
Kurt Vonnegut Jr
The one who has 510 wrote books that's the one
Brilliant speaker good author beloved by guys who are not
What is interesting to talk to as you would help
Hahaha I love it it alright the guy who wrote A Man Without a country
Trait entirely around how awful George W Bush was and how disgusting
Who died before Alex was like really huge
He was big with a big 9/11 truther and stuff showing the timer
When Alex Trucking
Big
That's
Vonnegut was dead by then
Yeah I don't know man I'm weirder things have happened. Maybe Alex did talk to her Johnny
I get at some point but the beer is pretty boring
Anyway the reason that I kept that clipping is because I
You really seen this tangential thinking that he's going down like
So many times and it's so delicious
I knew cuz babka
Never tell you about that kid
Do you know what
As as somebody who has described himself as Confederate royalty
I have saved this Republic
Many times
And also I'm probably Norman mailer
Why not
This is supposed to be the debate
Pre-show talking about like you would think well Trump's favorite are it's where I
You think maybe they do not know what it's supposed to be
Here's something about this nonsense
Hiestand
Historically
Emmaline
I'm saying no
Royal
And no.
Royalty
And no the communism
And no
I pledge my
My my
My blood mites
Bye.
Then that pledge
What is going on
Who is this
We've been hearing from the campaign that Trump is going to come out and he's going to be real
Forceful on immigration and Law & Order stuff
And Biden is going to try and hit him on that
Also
When you devote your life to everything
Hi tradition of rejecting Kings and now granted
My employee just posted a picture of herself with the t-shirt that you selling that says Trump is my king
But who knows
Biden is
He's a soulless Shore husky works of the devil and we are inside but even though Alex said he
Probably would also press that button and people deserve it
So is the Democrats
Global
They're running Biden against someone is
Strong
Powerful As Trump
Because that in and of itself is ritualistic
Eric
The false aplomb
Delusion
A reanimated
Corpse
But then you realize
The enemy is about
Destroy Humanity
The enemies of Allah
Slave
Until the enemy does
Want to feel
Real
But you could be inspired by
It wants to feel something
Empty Hawk
The media gang up
Onnit
Push that
Dead body
A real man
Can have that dead body win
Curaleaf
Exercise
And so what you realize
Gradual
Now you want
Do I
I don't know I just don't know
In the same way that a lot of people who are covering the debate we're kind of at a loss for words YouTube
I think a lot of people on news channels are people who are
Professionals share not weird
Probably you know they looked at that nor like well what the
The f*** I don't know what to do
Good
I kind of feel
The similarly about this like I don't know what you want to say
And then makes the exact same noise I do at the end of that sentence
So I just think his brain doesn't really tracking all that well if is beginning point
Of his his shift
And
I can tell that one of his main objectives though is like
Chris Wallace
Has got to go down the moderator debate
Movie preemptively presented as
Not only evil but perhaps the most evil right
What was the
Celebrated
Turd
I mean he is he
His father must be rolling over
Graham as father was
60 minutes
Clearly so why would you
Baby hat is
Hilltop with a
Weather
Richard Wallace
Mike Wallace
Chris Wallace
So that's coming up
Tonight
Thanks so much was our garbage you know one of the guys at
What are the debates
4 years ago was
Lester Holt
Lester Holt on TV
Did Alex Jones said
Kill the media
Murder the media
Gokil
TV show clip
He just said that
I knew mainstream media was dead
Tombstone
Please guys will do
Live Lau
What's even happened what is going on okay so Chris Wallace sucks
Mike Wallace
Do four years ago Lester Holt did it and then later he said that I said kill the media
That's when the tombstone is placed on
That media
Call it a 1-800 half through that from now
B2c is very strange
So he does take some calls and a lot of it is like what should Trump do
And Alex has a really clear idea of what it and it's basically
I just beat the s*** out of
That's what Alex wants to see
Who are the slightly different idea about like what these debates are supposed to be about
You can't even talk
Emblematic
I would like to hear him say emblematic as well
Democratic Party
People are going to vote
Wednesday
What is Apollo
A Carlos
Have a good evening
Pause leads me to believe that Alex
It's a foreign concept
This should be about like their ideas about
Very policies at Lucknow
Just watching fire
Alright well in Dubai
Well Carlos is a long time caller
Got a lot of stuff and I think a lot of things he says are stupid
In terms of people who are in the Infowars fear he does sometimes bring up stuff like that
Much more than other colors will like come in with something like a this new people are voting for the toilet
Who win the fight yeah
Usually
Has no response I don't always I don't know if I've ever felt this way before but this is the first time
Listen to a caller on Infowars and thought
Oh that's cute I play the rest of his call you might not.
Finally we get a little bit of a sense of what Alex is thoughts are
About
The New York Times story short. Trump's Tax Act and
Sting response
40 years ago
Before they passed
They were first proposing
And we we know that if you're in real estate
You better run
Breakeven
Are you done on the property tax
And feet
Of course he has
It's pretty disappointing to hear what Alex's defense for the whole story about the taxes seems to be so what
Like I was just hand-waving the way the idea that someone could be a billionaire but pay essentially nothing back
The country did he supposedly loved so much
How to super lucky that is
Is audience is full of complete dollars
Alex has big problems of the globalist is that International businesses hide their assets overseas
If I were out I would try to come up with something better than that people in business considering all the
Tim Cook don't pay taxes and that's evil
This guy isn't even trying anymore and honestly I feel it belongs and feelings and I listen to something like that
Obviously the first element is discussed and Alex's behavior is
Pretty
Gross for what it must be like to be lowered to the level of just spinning whatever outrageous thing your guy
God came does regardless of how much of your hard-fought career you have to contradict in the process
But the third part is resentment like I really resent this
That's really
Is really shameful
Tell me you love my country
And then tell me that you contribute nothing to it
Okay those two things can't happen
At the same time
It's tough
You know
I know there's that element of it but the element that I'm talking about more is the Alex element
For sure
There's not even like
Listen to this defense about dodging taxes
Is Dad
Weather for kids
How do you think you'll get around
Like his defense about accusations that someone was dodging the death taxes that's how you don't pay the death
That is
Not even trying
Internally contradictory at Lake complaint is you didn't pay that text
Is a response
Of course that's how I fit around nothing that time
That's just it's just
It's B Hammer over the head.
Least I found
And I don't know if you
I've seen the same thing
There's a certain amount of sport that most people take in like
Trying to pay all of their
You know like
I meant I will pay my taxes
But I'm going to try and shave a little bit off and if you guys catch me you know what you catch me but we're going to play this game
The American Experience I know that I've heard a lot of people talk about taking business meetings I should
Heard that before
Well if you're the president who loves the country is trying to save
So I noticed a shift in Alex Maybe
A b c half an hour 40 minutes into his
Is a pre
Debate Behavior
See if you can notice a shift
We are now
3 minutes
51-26
Essentials clothing
Control room
Forsake
Alright what's going on here
Who's the longest
What's going on
In Kansas are on the Earth
It's completely different wow he is that is a person trying to act
Like they are not on speaking
How's it going out
Panera
What was her name was up there
Okay
F*** out of you
You cannot be serious you cannot be serious what up man
Accuse people of doing the drugs and that's fine right
I'm good with that
But that brace
That's too much
Totally normal
2 countdown
Live with discover
Rutabaga
30pm
Eastern Time
Again will be
Coming up tonight
And the whole thing we are
Infowars
Okay love
What's going on
So I think there's two possibilities
But I think that's not as likely as like he's just
Drunk
And someone in the booth
Told him I pick it up man
Like if he was
And that's every that crying about ancestry and share share share
Passive aggressive Alex overdoing it the other direction
Just very Stark yeah it's it's a completely different
Transmission
Yeah
Counting on us
Or he might be on cocaine be a little weird
I'm not saying he's taking drugs
But I am saying I have known a large number of people who have talked exactly like that immediately following
I'm going to the bathroom
I have spent enough time around people who do
Possibility
I can't say with any certainty
What
Conclusion but I can't tell you
So Deanna Lorraine comes into I do some time with Alex or she has some high hopes
The the debate
I woke up this morning like a kid on Christmas
When is it going to be what am I going to wrap my presents
And I feel like the night were on wrapping these presents
We don't know exact
What's going to happen in some crazy curved volume
I know I did
Is I hope that he is loaded with the
These one-liners in these
Acquit
Cindy's witty comeback
Singers
It was a rap battle they would at least hopefully I'm hired some of my friends who are all out of work comics
Yeah it sucks
Wow
I mean I didn't
Here come again saying I'm very excited for the enumeration of policy or I'm interested to
Hear about
The Next Step
Switzer covid
Sure I know it's I hope he has some good Burns singers
To own the libs
Nothing else
Wow
This is really sad get sadder
Some calls and listen to this person
Tonight
I would like to
All to pray together
Father Ted
What do I do
Forget
We should all pray for
President-trump
Fraud
I totally agree with you
My gosh
30 minutes out
We should do it
You want to stay up you want a sandwich
I do know I've been wind
Calling for years and years and years and I've always
I don't know but
But tonight I see
Call in nuts
Anything else
Despres
Let's pray
So it's time to pray it is literally time to pray huh
Crying sweet thang
We thank you for this day
4shared fire
The shared spirit that
You getting off
Sacrifice
You made on the
Croft
So the last time someone called in and didn't extended prayer I brought it up but I am playing eclipses are there
And now I'm getting to a point where this is happening a bit this is too much people praying that's not good to have to
At least
I mean that's a pretty standard opening
To the prayer
I'm not worried about it cuz it's a pretty normal prayer you here
I think it's a little bit weird to imagine it on any other platform
Like we're doing the pre-debate coverage and then someone calls in and we just have a
Specific religious
Ritual anyone read the f****** Bible
Ever ever just ever
Do you realize what the Bible says about praying in public
Do know these people even bother with their holy textbook
I'm furious with this we do this all the time why do I know more about the Bible
Then people who won't shut up about it
Anyway this prayer goes on
Tonight above all Lords
The crater Utah
Let you know
That we
Reject
Satan
That we were jacked state
Our
Has been Unleashed
This world today
Pray tonight
That you
And you're holy
Spirit
Come down on
Earth
InTouch president
Trump
And give him
Power ended
Net worth
Righteous
Fury
This debate
I mean like they're beginning other prayer was kind of normal and then it gets into like we were checked saving and also please help Charles A Witness
Tobago
I don't know it seems it seems weird
The prayer ends it goes on a bit more than that
And Alex's response immediately after
Very weird
Every time I'm clear in the morning
God
Ariana here Bagon
Leadership
An America with the Holy Spirit
God and bring that in
I hate this right
Are you guys
From
She hated it
No cancel this caller is caller calls in and does a prayer and then immediately after Alex is like
To do this down on this prayer I don't have the prayer capabilities right now
I'm either drunk
Or on speed and I'm fine with both Lorain and
Shirley volunteered it
Deanna's not
Cheese to put out by the idea of praying but Alex does not join them then this gesture to Strange
So
Next caller calls in
She's just overwhelmed
By being on the line
With Alex
And Deanna Lorraine
And then
Alex takes a shot
Oh my goodness
Alexandra
Deanna Lorraine
Oh my goodness and I really want it
You got that
Oh God
I'm Star Struck with Alex everyday
Oh my goodness
Thank you so much for 2
Take my call
Yeah so excited thank you for supporting then.
Oh my goodness
Well I just wanted
Start off by
By saying I love you
Love you guys so much
Search my whole family
We love you guys
We love you love you
Gentrification
Here's the Shire
Support Ubi
Product
We have
Here's the show wow
So is Char is a lady who's calling in and she brings up
That she named one of her kids after Alex
She named Hermosa
The kid's name Everett
Wow wow
What the wrong direction there
Really take any of the other stuff you saying
You want to know more about her kids
So he asks the names of the other kids and Mike down for this because
This doesn't quite go the way Alex Watts
They are
Sauron
Orange
Or orange
Yeah yeah
To tell you he
Hi and
He loves you guys
We love you brother
Is Aryan
I'm sorry what
Call Ray
Jesus Christ
That's what's really fun about that is the progress
Prescient it takes because she's like our first son is our first child Zoran and Alex is like
Like a news about to say Orrin Hatch realize like I don't know if I like orange or not
You one of the guys who doesn't like Trump or was he cool with the Trump I don't remember I haven't complained about him in a while so I'm just not going to say
Google we navigated those Waters okay that wasn't too bad
Aryan
The Kool-Aid man here where I had somebody say that
Just makes a weird noise
Mexican what was this kid's name Silas I think okay
Tomatoes an enjoyable cuz you could tell even Alex was like
What the f*** that lady come on
I try not to
Be that obvious and I'm bad at it
So Alec six other call and disguise
Really
Hillary to Brandi
Tell before they find that video
Dot-com
Click on more videos
Ultraman
Just another Channel
Just another Channel.
Pull up Justin
That was
So what are you predicting tonight
This isn't a real color
This is just another four Fringe as right-wing inspiring media figures calling into Alex's show trying to get some clout
Videos of himself at various Trump rallies and videos apparently explaining the Tom Hanks as a secret pedophile but also
He has multiple videos on his page on YouTube where he's being interviewed on Infowars
He's been on the War Room a bunch
Look at this guy's channel it's super super clear what sort of message she's probably getting from the contents he creates
Princeton see other video about our evil Bill Gates is that was released 5 months ago or so and it currently has
71 views
That's a monkey apparently interviewed Barnes a video which has 235 views
Conversely a video of him yelling at a Biden rally got him 66,000 views
A video of him yelling at a Bernie rally got 19200 one of him yelling at Hillary got 31,000
Yelling at Hillary one probably would have gotten more traffic except it happened in 2019 and yelling at Hillary wasn't the highest demand
Product at that point where all right
It's hard to look at this guy's Channel and not see pretty clearly how this defines the ecosystem that Alex
What is a part of
A apart of elevating as a media
Sure that interview with Barnes is almost certainly stupid and worthless and terms of substance but interviewing someone still take
Takes effort
That's effort that is not rewarded by the audience of this media caters to
But what is rewarded is when you go out and record yourself disrupting an event that someone you don't like is holding
This creates a perverse incentive structure where a struggling Creator could easily be convinced to trying it sell
Self is not worth it
Because the things that get the most attention or the things that take
They all just being a dick
You just have to be a big enough dick ingested inappropriate enough situation
And you'll stand out
That's the economy of the Alex Jones media and it's pathetic
But what makes this even more pathetic is this guy with his YouTube channel is calling in here to talk to his obvious role model
The guy who paid people to do in 2016 what he's now doing for free
And Alex has no idea that he's been on the war room multiple times
Alex has no idea who this guy is he just kind of remember seeing a video of somebody yelling at Hillary and Biden
And that Timothy Mark of a great American
Who he'll stop caring about once this
Call end
Immediate
What a bummer
And they say they like each other all the time but they just don't care
Nope
Hard it where it's hard to be friends with people that also requires work you have to
This guy exists
Person who made this video that Alex vaguely remember seeing not as someone who's been treated as like
A guest on Alex's Network like this guy's fancies himself a creator
In the same sense as
F****** Deanna Lorraine
He is not
Which is a real sad realization
He is usable when he goes out and he yells at someone else wants yelled at until the next time
He will be forgotten
The lot of talk has been done on this pre-debate
Time about everyone getting these ballots
Sure Three Rivers everywhere
The other day
I threw it in the trash
Everyone's getting one it's all what
I mean the ones that they suddenly
Find are the ones that are dead
Oh my God
What is a Democrat ballot
In the general election everybody gets the same ballet
I don't understand what this is
It's great they got the Democrats I'd like to push on this issue a little bit more but we're at a time the debate start
Alright so Alex Goes to try to throw it to Chris Wallace who he hates
Saab Indiana does not quite get the throw
Closet
Empty Soul on American
I know right triangle
Stack effect
Trying to be
Stuff you retarded
What's what's going on
Piece of on American Idol
The garbage unbiased
Deanna did not quite get the the way this works
Audio or video
Does not need you to double down on him not liking Chris Wallace eannace you're not ready for the game yet snow
But it it's
It's so clear like at the beginning of this that like
One of the primary
Is going to play out is attacking Chris Wallace
I can assure you none of the questions has been shipped
Weather today
Disgusting swamp creature
You want to die in a ditch
Shield Healthcare
Either huge swamp
Yeah you get lost in his eyes by which I mean your feet get stuck in them and you lose your shoes as well
Jordan
I'll save
I was
Pretty disappointed by the debate as a whole like I think
Did you watch it
Yeah yeah I'm sorry I listened to it again through Alex
Even worse in terms of editing up this episode and getting the clips I had to relive it and it wasn't better the second time
Are you sure yeah very disappointing and I think that a lot of people had some analysis of it some of it productive
Some of it not so productive
I would say that Alex Takes the Cake
Legitimately the worst
What did Isaac beard
First of all
Thank you for
Never right
Have a say in who the Supreme Court nominee is that safe
When they vote for a United States senators
That's
Unbelievable unbelievable what is the highest level of insight that you could get from that
I agree with him wholeheartedly
If you just did that through the entire door noises same thing same thing
Really interested in his tax plan
Just don't think so when that happen like that's what right at the beginning of the debate
Just like oh no
This is this is where we're going okay
And what makes it worse is that earlier
Alex
Sad sad you know we'll just as little as possible maybe I'll make some fart noises
Sure I thought that was not a plan as knows it was a joke
That's why I didn't cut that clip out
Make fart noises and you were serious earlier
Who likes well there's no need to
Pay attention to that I'll never need that information ever again
A boy but turns out
You do
Play Electric
Look up puppies faces too bright
Clear
Mister methamphetamines
Is in the Supreme Court right now trying to do
Get rid of
The Affordable Care Act
Which will strip
20 million
The B too good at look
I had my fun and now I'm over with it you get one time with fart noises and then after that
It's played out Alex keeps going yeah I think he realizes pretty quickly they bite
Who is performing at 11 that is way out of sync
With what he has built up in his audience dad as their expectation
And so you do daddy something that needs to be addressed a little bit maybe methamphetamines is one way to go about it
But there's also
Like something else
About Biden
He seems more alive then
You've
Formally said that he is what did he not know that only an idiot would not know that you were lying about
That would just look
Fine
You know you said that he would look like a desiccated corpse basically you know why he did
Swampert
Probably got about
Okay
You probably got five bags of blood in front building
Celibate male
Hello fresh
Blood before the other grandpa Jordan over here don't know about Plumping
I understand correctly
Is that what happened
Is Joe Biden was pumped full of more blood that is necessary for human being to survive
10 bags 5 sandbags
Large blood
Bleeding out his eyes blood
Too much blood and you can only fit so much blood
Yeah and that's heavy transfusion if you were to get 5 to 10 bags of blood
That is a lot
I would I would say dangerous probably
Or
Recreational Club I mean now I kind of want to see how it feels
I don't
Too much I want to
If you're going to try pumping definitely get the consent
Sure this becomes like Alex's new thing like this
Blood bag B
Superfund
Why Penny and
One of the big debate
What is a dick
Energy
For sure
Baby blood
Yeah okay I do enjoy this Deanna trying to be like a person having a
What is a do
Clubs
Deanna how dare you applied basic human curiosity to a man who has no interest double bucket of blood
You know this is the type of thing that should have made it very obvious to everybody why
Well in advance of course the debates are going to be a shitshow
But that's because Alex
Is basically
Acting the same way that Trump
Always does
The actor the exact same way
So why in God's name would in a debate Trump not be like
At your full blood your full your puppet
Look at you
Hey my tax plan is about
Chris Wallace
Neighbors
It's a little silly
Look
Point is
Normally
Beaches
Gastric LaBelle
He is deathly
Only had blood transfusions
Store
Whatever Alex says something like iwatches beaches not just
The gas that we cut out that is
Towel
That he just watches the gas that one of his insurance cuts out
He's on blood
Yeah that's he's on the bug man that's always the I'm not bragging I watch the full videos not just the clip
You know what I thought was really interesting here is that after a little while Alex Indiana actually
Shut up and they stop interrupting the debate which
Sweetly threw me off
I watch the Hillary Trump debates on Infowars with my boys far out
Whenever Hillary was talking in order to make sure the audience didn't get a different opinion of her
Then the curated caricature that he's painted
In this instance I was really shocked that Alex actually stop talking while Biden was on stage and speaking
I can't tell what that was whether he's just drunk and Confused
Or maybe he didn't feel the need to interrupt because he became confident at a certain point that Trump would do it for gas going to say
Yeah I think they have my literal avatar on stage I'm ripping a movie that mst3k
Is currently ripping at the
The same time we're done.
It was strange because there's long stretches where no one's saying anything it's just the debate
Yeah that's a little disconcerting actually that's that's a horror movie like The Calm before
Thesis statement here like what Trump needs to do cuz he's not doing enough
That's apparently working
Vital Farms
Sponsored
He wants to see from his candidate even treat the questions as if they
They were asked
Just yell and attack
Yep
So cool
Anyway that does
Sort of happen
Eventually
This is the first like real outburst
From Deanna and Alex
Vice President Biden
Smaller
Pants with nobody will show up
People with
We're going to use that
Wow
It's kind of sad
Alright so
We have infrastructure issues
To talk about
We could deal with I don't know the large
Just crisis that any of us have ever faced
We can talk about that in the 2016 debates in the Republican primary Trump talk about having a big dick like
We're done
Oh well
It was fun
Alex is pretty disappointing singers in
Fake version of Biden isn't there
Great job
Popped up
He's definitely like you said on something he's able to talk
Antrum is not dominating
Swimming but as we talked
Alex is Disappointment here is really interesting because by all accounts he should be loving this
Is being an a****** he's interrupting all over the place and neither Chris Wallace nor Biden can really stop him or do anything
To make this a conversation about policy differences
Trump throwing out some singers that Alex is loving but at this point you can tell that this is not what Alex wanted
Here's why
Trump is not contradicting reality in the ways Alex needs him too
Trump is arguing with Biden about when a vaccine will be available not about how the vaccine is actually a secret plot to microchip
Japan kill everyone
Trump saying that states should open up in masks R5 he's not saying the covid-19 is a hoax
Some of the Democrats are trying to take over the world using it
In the same way that this debate as the danger of revealing to Alex's cloistered audience that Joe Biden
Can infect complete sentences and he isn't
A man of the depths of late-stage dementia it also carries the danger of revealing that Trump is not who Alex's Bill 2
Come up to me either
Trump is a bully in an a****** he's an aspiring dictator and he's willing to use whatever support he's able to to
But when the cards are on the table he doesn't give up
A f*** about Alex's petkin
Conspiracy theories
He doesn't want to waste the political Capital it would take for him to yell about vaccines
He probably rather try to find a way to make a buck off
This isn't Stark opposition to the image that Alex paints of the man who was brought in by God
The fight the battle against
The globalist is there champion
That was one of the things that struck me the most when I was watching the debate because I didn't expect anything other than a train wreck so has mostly
Prepared for that aspect
There wasn't a winner but ultimately Joe Biden probably lost the least or at least came closest to winning because his
Campaign doesn't have a lot of
You know it's not built on the enthusiasm about him as a personality sure
If he comes out in fails to articulate left-wing position well that's not going to surprise anyone on the left
As long as he manages to get through the debate without conceding to Trump he's going to retain the support that he has among the Democratic base
And there probably aren't a whole lot of undecided voters to convince one way or another at this point
On the other hand
Has a lot to lose mostly because his base is made up of a whole lot of weirdos
Was with wildly different beliefs about who he is
And what he's doing
Each of them is a mini Trump called that has their own version of the story
4q people is that of a secret group in the government that's rooting out all the evil doers most of him or actually already
The morati have been replaced by clones
The weirdly Trump never seems to bring up any of this stuff or act like any of it's true
People in the Infowars for Trump is a god-ordained ruler king who was brought to Earth exactly the right moment to be their hero
I deliver them from the bondage of the literal Christian devil
And his minions
The Democrats
But weirdly Trump
Fails to be on the same page with Alex about some pretty major elements of what's supposed to be the devil's plan Shore
It's the key to defeating the devil's plan is exposing the hoax
Covid-19
And Trump has all the evidence that it's a hoax
But it sure seems weird that he's bickering with Biden about how soon Avec seem to be delivered
Military no less
That's something Alex shouldn't like to heal that's not good
I have a suspicion that this debate could have been a disaster for Trump but not in the way that rational people might expect
Normal humans would watch that debating with a t on stages 1
Complete raising a*******-in-one politician
Assuming that the politicians policies aren't something you completely disagree with
You probably vote for them over a raving a******
Because that dude is a raving lunatic a******
But I think the damage that Trump could have done to himself was in that he's
Wasn't crazy enough
Or maybe a better way to put it is that he wasn't crazy in the right ways
He'll be almost impossible to satisfy all the different communities of trump idolaters with their varying belief structures
Make sense with no matter what
Some of them would end up disappointed and disillusioned
5S
Babe
I'm at kind of does
Seem to be with Alex is experiencing
No more flute
Call Dad
Call out
The Flash
Don't play their game
All out South
Call out Bill Gates
This is pretty tough
For Alex
Is it true that were aware that this
Covid-19 is an elaborate hoax
Perpetrated on the American public
In order to crash the economy and put the population into slavery and then eventually death
Kind of his responsibilities as president before right about that
He wouldn't be very admirable thing for him to know about this plan and it's a plan to kill everyone
And then just argue that he's done a better job than Biden would have done
That's the sort of thing that makes you think that maybe he's not the same
Person that Alex has told you that he is
And you know what that should scare the s*** out of Alex optic
Speak very clear
It's one thing for Alex
To turn on Trump
It's another thing for his audience to turn on Trump while Alex is still licking food totally
And I think they'd tell you run the risk of that because like
You know
Why would Trump debate
About
I've done a great job on the Coronavirus
When
He's supposed to be aware
States
Nothing right
Manufactured to hurt him
Write what he should be saying is
There isn't anybody dying of coronavirus you guys all just made this up
He's in front of me make me look
Yeah and if playing along with the charade
Is in effect
Eating the globalists devil's plan
Then why would he be doing that
Raises those questions in your mind that are very tough and they only
Conclusion you can really come to is that Alex has been
Creating fake versions of vitad trepanning
I just had an image of me playing with my two Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles action figure yes
The Raphael one where that has had popped out and I was great.
That is what's going on
Alex gets to talking about how the Democrats
They want to crash the economy
You know that right
You remember who said that
Do you
Democrats wanted cressey, which which person who's about to crash the economy in order to punish Trump yeah but which person said that
The Democrats
Percent he did
Lorraine
And now they keep going back to covid you suck
Call me wise
When they said they were from
The 100% and this was a ploy from the beginning is
Is push this false epidemic epidemic
Balsa push it as much as pause
Say that this major serious thing and then have the economy crash
A blame
Trump and hopefully don't remember that I mean bilmar all of them
Sylmar Sylmar
A boy
So there was a raucous celebration
When Trump gave out that singer earlier
Sure
Is great singer
At this point in the debate
Trump brought up Hunter Biden
Leads to
A declaration of victory
The mayor of moscow's wife
Gave you some
Three and a half million dollars
Micrometer
None of that
Take me to Plaza
On the lot
President
It is not true he really?
Russian agent
Peapod
But body is hot
And disappearing as amphetamines
The run-out
His shot has run out
So
Basically
This follows with my theory and they're like what they're celebrating is like how he got one of our narrative
Yeah he is misrepresenting reality and the way that works for us right
And they're pretty excited we got we got at least one that we can talk about tomorrow and be like Trump is our god-king again because
Because he got this one right Let's ignore all the other stuff like how I guess he's fine with killing everybody I guess
The Narrative becomes Joe Biden's drugs are wearing off
And so they just get really excited about that
We've never
Mike ESPN
At the races
Close your eyes run with those nipples look like coming out
Buffet of drug
And bladder
Julianus Medical vileblood
Obviously
This is ridiculous
Was talking about the United right rally where people were chanting Jews will not replace us
Anti-Semitism that was on display Al
They're Alex's misrepresenting it and saying
Sure I don't even understand why anybody would think that this is good analysis or like
Why would anybody even if you are a crazy right-wing person
And even if you're weird conspiracy theories she why would you think that like
Alex can't follow what's being discussed
And respond to
Like he's incapable of doing
This job
Even if you're nuts
Anime anti-communist
You should be disappointed by this watch party
This is like whenever a new episode of Mad Men was released in everybody's like let's get our friends together and everybody's like
Looking for Don Draper did it has nothing to do with reality it's more off topic than that I think
Watch parties or madman or a little bit better moderated
That's probably true
About Law & Order run
You're allowed
Chris Wallace he orders
What is the point of these people it's it's just shut up it's outrageous there's no talking to you there's no point in you
You talking nothing you do is good or worthy of even f****** just shut up and leave us alone
So another thing is like so Alex has been painting Chris Wallace is like the most evil awful
Part of this is like they're ganging up on Trump
Is not asking Biden any hard questions
Deactivating a hard question
This doesn't
Will I get shouldn't work for Alice
Have you ever called
All the Democratic mayor report
Or the Democratic governor
Oregon
NSAID
Hey you got to stop this
Bring in the National Guard
Do whatever it takes
Stop the days
Months
Violence
In Portland
I don't hold public office
I am
A former vice president
I made it clean.
Right
Another good question though I got to hang out a while ago
The question now
Weight doesn't that invalidate the idea that Chris Wallace wouldn't be asking any hard questions Jesus
What is going on I hate all of this why are you guys dealing with reality
This is the problem when unreality is forced to meet reality it looks incredibly stupid
Yeah I think Alex is is is a little bit even on his heels a tiny bit related
Might just be like
Is that what did I think this was going to be why did I think this was going to not be what it's so
Obviously was going to be
So we get to the point in the debate where Trump is asked about the proud boys sure
Real interesting
Alex seems pretty disappointed
Are you willing
July
Condemn white supremacist
And Melissa Grove
And
To say
They need
To stand down
And not
Add to the body
Are you prepared
Almost everything I see is from the left wing
Not from the right but what do you want to do
I'm willing to do anything I want to see peace
Proud boys
Stand back
Can standby
But I'll tell you what
I'll tell you what
Somebody's got to do something about antifa and the left
I know
But he doesn't even
I've been there
He's really disappointed the Trump didn't say I
Executive orders
So don't ask me about the proud boys
Or whatever like
Deflection to get off the topic
Instead he said something that everybody heard
Terrifying
Oh no he just told the proud boys to be ready to murder the left at any point in time I don't understand I don't think
Alex heard it that way that doesn't sound like he realize that
Said was it's okay for you and your friends to kill the love like you've always wanted to do I don't I don't know if Alex
Took that message away from it Keith I think he's only guy
His reading comprehension skills are so low
Even the guy who's telling him what he wants to hear
He's unable to understand his reading of
Trump's response there is an unwillingness to alienate like some of his passionate supporter
Yeah I meant also he probably was trying to say
Stand Down
Whatever it kept saying stand back stand by Usher
Freezing it that way allows that possible interpretation
I find it all very tiring and and terrifying at-bat
To that I say f*** off
Also this is going to be a problem for Alex
You believe
Human
Pollution
God's greenhouse gas emissions most recent a rock album
Play.
Electronic said yes
Uh-oh
That's not good
Oh man
Unreality is losing it every turn
Yeah I mean if your Alex like what are you doing
Trump says yes
Human pollution is contributing to
Climate and I thought it's supposed to be a Chinese
To be a Chinese bio-weapon
How man. These people
So earlier I know who was in the first televised presidential debate
Now we learn something that Deanna doesn't know
Do we can get to
NetZero
In terms of energy
Production
My2030
G59 only not costing peep
People jobs creating job
Creating millions of good paying jobs
Not 15 bucks an hour
But
Prevailing wage
By having a new info
Structuralism
Economy
Obvious
Prevailing wage
New word
What's good for you
Good for you Deanna Deanna you should have learned about forever Bailey way did she is just fine
Do you think she was like
I should find a better job
Getting paid 15 bucks an hour for this if you Google it you might
Rethink your contract if Alex butt
Yeah I think that's always that's always interesting when like
Because it almost had the sound
Thinking she had a gacha life and said something
Henry audiology
About
Working issues stupid
So they get really bored by this point cuz they've already decided like haha the hunter Biden
Thingies
Slowly losing his
Pop-up time we should be dealing with the mercy rules Alex at this point
Starts talking about corn Pop-a-Lot
I actually
Studied
And it includes upgrading 4 million buildings weatherizing 2 million hounds of
4 years
Energy efficient
Homes
So the question becomes
Who support the president would say that sounds
I guess going to cost
A lot of money
What is
Can do is going to Crate
Thousands and millions of jobs
Removed
Push people into little smart cities
Paying job
Alex said let Corn Pop talk you might have noticed that his voice changed a little bit
That sounded right
Did he come back
Maybe five minutes later
It is like I got to get a drink I'm going to be right back he's either getting a drink or like he has to pee or something
I don't know what it is but yeah you just leave
Is Deanna doing by yourself not great I didn't they just mostly hear the debate
With her gone
Every now and again trailing wage a
So they get to the topic of voter fraud in the debate Shore
We won't know we might not know for months
Because these ballots are going to be all over
Take a look at what happened in Manhattan take a look at what happened
Ford in Virginia and other places
Losing
2% 1 % which by the way is too much in election could be one of us for that
Phyllis and 30
And 40%
It's a fraud
And it's a shame
Can you imagine where they said
Tomorrow
5 minutes
Trump in Thoroughbred
Domination proof
Flammable
Bring It On from Bring It On
Trump is creating the narrative along with the election is going to be stolen
If he doesn't exactly what we needed
Hooray
That's the celebration the way it's experiences
Exactly what we needed
Yep and it's so weird how that is overriding
All the very serious problems that have been introduced by the visuals of this debate
The fact that Trump is not the person that you pretend to you
The fact that Biden
Isn't the
Falling apart old man that you pretend to yes sure
Like dubbed invalidation of so much of Alex's
He's just undone by we got what we needed
Things where he's just a aspiring dictator a******
Like
The things that
Work for Alex
Are the things that are completely explainable without Alex's conspiracy
The parts where
Alex's conspiracies and Trump's behaviors intersect
There's not there's not as much overlap as Alex pretend
It is a boy
That was the most I've heard
From the debate
And
I ate the picture I had my head
Accurate
Right on
Well I think if you watched it
I believe that
Heroes my favorite snippet
From the debate
Saying something it's like
This is this is like
I don't believe
What we're saying is
They're saying is about to be a
Smart by the
By election day
If I can get in
Until the seventh eighth ninth
It still should be
Counted
He's just afraid of
Counting the votes
President
Skills music
I love counting vote I love counting votes
What are we doing
What are we doing I don't know what are we doing I can't imagine any candidate that I
I've ever been excited about saying something like that
Meaning respect
I don't want to die because of that a****** that's unfair
Cruel and an insulting to me I have existed this long without dying
Because of an a****** like Donald Trump into dime now that's too long after long
That be fine I should be killed by an a****** like this when I'm 99 year olds are assholes like that
Well if you're not lying
You'll be too young to vote
And if you're too young to vote then you won't be at the poles
Trump is encouraging people in his supporters to go and to hang out
And will you play
Judge denied
But you will not declare victory
Until the election has
Been independently sort of
President-trump
Supporters
To go into the pole
And watch
Very careful
Because that's what has to have
Happen I am urging them to do it
As you know today there was a big problem in Philadelphia they went into what
They will pick all Polo watches a very
Safer nice
They were thrown out
You don't why does bad things have
Philadelphia bad things
And I am urging
Imrg my people I hope
It's going to be a fair election
But if I see tens of thousands of dollars
Was being manipulated
I can't go along with
Yosemite on 80 million
These people aren't equipped to handle it
Number one
Nothing you
They cheat they did all this
Please paper basket created this with the coveted do it. They
If you're saying
You know you want you want an election you want a good clean election and you'll respect the results of a good clean election but
Unfortunately you can't respect a result and then your next sentences are
Look at all this your kind of signaling something and that is that
He will not view the election as being valid
What time is it
Before he leaves for the night
And Deanna Lorraine and Owen Shroyer hose
For quite a while band
Connect
Out of the first half
He didn't do as well as I'd like
I had
Black Taffy just weigh out to
Joe Biden Apple
Troydan
The on Lorraine will give you her tag
Port Royal give
Just remember
Not a great credit working
18 hours later bring you this
There's no Independent Media like this.
She has live coverage of this of the Infowars
We are so blessed to be here
No one has live coverage
The debate was live it was broadcast live
There's a number people who doing live coverage
No just trying to get some money too we can do
That that like
I think he was in the first half-hour you know I think he was doing pretty good he's still one but not by much of the eye
Look just say that he didn't do well
Not buy as much
Okay my team is down 16 points to the Jets
But we're only winning by a little bit and then later you got to be more of an assholes and that excited
I got to go to bed
I'm tired of simple that's great analysis
That's a summation right there dance Alex comes in on the 30th
It's not really much going on quite frankly but Alex has now decided
The Trump did great and there's a lot of people were saying that he did bad
I either outright reason you were on the right well yeah maybe a mat drug type
Hey man just never been in a debate
When you're sitting in on your cell phone
And you're 30 years old you're 40 years old
Chris Wallace
Better
I just know what it's
I'm interrupting you
Pretty much for that
Presidential debate
What people are
Guitar
Like an adult
Fluoride is not a good way to win debate it's definitely a good way to make people who don't book you on shows sound very
Very sensible
And bookings
What would I like to do is whenever people bring me on their show I'd like to don't engage and acts like
Their show doesn't matter to me if Alex Jones class
And the whole thing was just like
Exercises to make you louder
Lalalala lalalala
That's not cool
Some people had some things today about Trump
They're not they're not debating like Alex did with Piers Morgan or that guy in
The UK where yelled at him about to do I screamed infowars.com
Maybe look any criticism of trump is one thing
Think about Biden bro
He thinks he's better than
Delaware
Crooked Man
And use people and steel
Axillary
Steak dinner
You don't get fired
Dollars
Because you don't get a nickel
Stop if you work for Trump you don't get paid
That's true.
Yeah I mean you should tip obviously but
Kind of trivial
Compared to
What you see from that raving a****** Trump
Dan Lyman from Europe Awards shuttle.
Shooting on immigrants
Just a little taste
Literally
And they basically work22 transport
Migrants
Come in from other countries such as Afghanistan Iraq Iran Syria
Into Europe and then the operation goes on from there to bring them down to Mainland Europe
Al Jazeera
Banana launch come on
I think the plate last night had a couple of more drinks to kind of calm himself down
Pop it up
Alex
It's dark in here on this episode about how like
If he could
He would run
They run but there's nowhere on Earth you can't run from
The globalist
Cuz globe
You know yeah that. All of it that does make sense
And apparently his early career is meaningless
It's coming
It's coming fast
Firefox
50 years
40 years
Because when I was not as knowledgeable
Well
Will defeat the enemy will crush them
In a fight
There we go
It's all a lot
It's all a fraud it's all empty it's all pointless it's all stupid
Don't you figure out other than entertain
Which real
Everything makes sense
I mean I don't I don't agree with v there's a devil trying to ruin everybody's lives or any town
No issue with that conclusion but it
Is when I was younger I thought I was doing something but I was actually fighting Shadows
I would even draw your conclusion a little bit further along in your career perhaps all the way up until the present
This devil of yours
It's a shadow that you're going to have a tough time creating a bigger bad guy for seeing as there's
You're already on the devil yeah what are you got
Is over like season 1
Your bad guy is Siler and he can take other people's powers
These overpowered he is essentially infinitely powers
Interesting cuz that guy
Yeah so yeah it's Alex next season
You've already fought
The devil shadow
I all I heard in that is just like
I cannot learn
Anythink
Well I can keep escalated
So we start off with fighting the the shadow that is that road in Texas
How do you start fighting the shadow that is 911
Big shadow lady start fighting the shadow of what you imagine Obama is up to
A dictator who is going to send in troops to
Plenty of
And you're right your guy Ron Paul was going to be who is going to take care of that shadow for everybody
Because he knew about how to fight The Shadow
It is
The Federal Reserve all that business and then you accidentally start supporting Trump
And you do that escalate Your Shadow
Now Trump is in the seat of power that you were
Yelling about you can't go back to local issues
Abby and your primary focus like that road
You have to escalate
Now you have
The Deep state
Not least of which
You have to know at least on some level
The guy you think should be the king
Is himself worse than the Shadows that you have been fighting your entire career
Which is why your new shadow
Has to be the
Devil
He is
The literal
Devil is the only thing worse than Donald Trump
Your enemy has to be the literal devil
If there's like two pads that it's like like this is just the way his career has had to escalate like terms
The recruit a bad guy is
I meant simultaneously like
Yeah
If it's a choice
Between Trump or literal devil
I guess most people be like I guess Trump's just
A dictator
And I like I guess I guess if that's snow.
So far the devil seems way more fun
He's got more interesting plans if he's got better s*** going on
Its planes are terrible and none of them work of course I want
Dialysis devil over drunk
I'm comparing them to like
The Pitchfork poking me
Take some calls and you disappointed
Trump didn't destroy the covid fraud or
The best job ever we whatever cuz I
Why did he do that yesterday on stage why didn't he just come out and just
Stock market
Primal attack
We can be the attack dog
Where is in some cases he can't
That's not what a surrogate mean
Also I would suggest that if the
Two choices are crashing the dollar and the globalist plan to kill everyone
I got a crash that dollar is option number three the devil cuz so far he's
Higher up on my list than I thought would have all very stupid
Jim hoft from the Gateway pundit
Just throw a brick through a window or something I got to make me a
Fuc yourself
Expose Joe Biden
And
And he absolutely
Unhinged
Velux
Flustered he was mean
His his name calling was you know it subs hard
And and he also looks you know disheveled and
So Jim hoft complaining or celebrating I guess that Trump exposed at Biden is mean and a
Name caller
Which is rich
That's pretty funny. I just
It's just
Do not
Just
Know if your propaganda style is right the thing that your guy did and then switch out the names
That's just that's just too much
Search for me
That's just too much
Donald Trump being mean in a name caller is strategic Brilliance that's exactly what you need
An a****** and couldn't communicate clear thoughts
Almost as if he were on some sort of drug
Everything that they say is
Can't deal with that I'll just put buying the name in there I feel so much nicer now
I don't know very comfortable with this
Sorry
We come to the end of debate Extravaganza 2020
And
I don't know
Well I feel reassured
I donate
I'm overwhelmed
I'm honestly overwhelmed I mean about the real-world but also about looking at this like
I mean okay Owen Shroyer sucks
That's not true that status quo absolutely on something sure
Probably probably drunk
One way or the other
And then either was acting like he was on Coke or was who knows
Super male Vitality who cares
He was all over the place and really weird and
Making fart noises during the debate that was pretty
Right
I don't know
I don't know what it is
I'm at a loss I'm at a loss
I don't know what
For the first time in a very long time
I don't know what's going on with this this was bewildering this is surreal
Actually after I saw the picture of Lori Lightfoot wearing a costume
Lying to my face
All day today
I'm just really starting to feel like all of you are f****** with me
Like this is where everyone is in on this I my conspiracies
Go further than any look Global is f*** off
Everyone you're one-hundred-percent this is me
Manufactured to make a man lose his mind all seven and a half billion of you got together and we're like
Like what if
Jordan when insane
That's the only thing that makes sense to me
I was born in a cult with a prophecy to my name to make sense to me
Why you might lean towards that conclusion but I'll assure you that
Yeah you're right but even when you agree with me
Right
I don't know I look for clarity hopefully to to set in over the weekend and we will
We'll see
Let's take some calls to voicemail
Love it
Hi Troy
I guess I have
Tangential
Slightly less
So
AR
And
Translator
Bever
He plays
Pretty good
Acting
Mine
Choreographer
He was also
Menlo
I love you
Fairy
Maybe
Fascinating but unfortunately he hit The 2-minute One
I didn't know this until like I heard some calls that hit the 2-minute barking
Live limit I didn't set that it's just a Skype thing I guess the option to re-record your message
You can call back in okay I apologized
Important information I really appreciate
Call
Anyway
Goodbye YouTube
Should be sad that there is a British person
Who as the outgoing messages record one and
I don't have the time
Also a lot of a lot of messages will end up starting with
Mr. t What You Know friend of the show Mike Wiley used to have a GPS that he always had the MR2
Mr. T voice on at every time a cameo
Do that on Maps
Danny Jordan
Hope everything's going well
Highway right now
Hi Matt
Illume
Eastern Washington
Flipper blue and
Make me laugh
You guys have
Quick Quack
Play no man
Feedback on it
If you guys
Also
I just pulled
Zucchini
Out of my garden
F****** Wild
Picture later if you'd like
Alright hope
Things are going well
Take care
I do not need a zucchini picture I have, I applaud you and your gardening
I will say I have never played no man's sky but and I don't know anything about it but it is a name that I've heard people talk real
I don't know
I don't know what type of game it is I don't know what it's on
I have no idea
I've heard a lot about I've read a lot about it
Very it seems too intimidating to make because it has no man's sky
Is that it's like infidel
I like 80 itself creates a world for it so you can go around and you travel and
Like one of the reasons that it had such a rough launch was because you couldn't meet any other players be
Because you are in an infinite universe
So you would just roll around the f****** stars finding all kinds of weird s***
I'll be right back so I don't know Eve online it's not like
Gameplay-wise I don't mind
It's like an intense
Like Universe unto itself and it's just intimidating to me and I can't
I can't jump in on it it's not something that you can dip your toe into
You know
Pronounced
Damn
Easy mistake to make we're not talkin about crackers like a wreck
Swimming about a quokka
That's that's it that's it
That's an interesting breathy tone for for this up and put them into soup
That's what you doing
Guaca guaca
Dan
Jordan
Hey trouble John down here in Austin Texas
Health Ranger Lynn finally call into this service cuz I have been racking my brain
Alessandro get to send you guys
And I think I've come up with some
First of all I want to say thank you
So so much
This whole crazy
Busy f****** time
Stan
Jordan's theme
Turn your gratitude
Navigation with sake
How far when I needed it most
Something great by the way
All the back-and-forth we've had
Love you man. Thank you for helping out
Before and everything
You guys are
I want to do something nice
And I know that sounds weird
But here's what I'm going to do
I'm going to make Darren Jordan
John is going to take
Amplify Microsoft couple microsatellite Regency
Specifically you right now but I'm going to
At least
Werkendam
Animal
Plant
Bacteria
And Sundry
Please send me your DNA
If you don't or you think that's true
Strange
Then my a copy of Deanna Lorraine
About
No
Great again
Really
I mean
Avapro
Mbrdna
I can pick you up if you agree on the podcast I will send you people slobs
Civilization
Imagine that is the new city
Divide if
The world is suddenly populated by you and my plants and
We are the loud ones so tempted
To explore this but I also feel like
I can't but then the alternative is a day Anna Lorraine book
I don't know what to do it's very I think we have to become chimeras
I think I've talked to my therapist about this we got to repopulate the earth when everybody's gone man what's with this next call I got
Two-minute cut off
Tattoo simple
Shut off shut off
I hope you like it I like it
Hey guys
So I was in
The Urgent Care reset
The Lakers I got like
Pattaya raccoon
Well saving
Crimson.
And while I was there I remember that they were putting like
Hydrogen peroxide on the
And I remember that whole thing
We're going to be like
Inhaler
Peroxide
The nurses
Explain what the guy at the Jets
She burst out laughing
David
Now don't
Dude that that could kill you
Belly fat diet
Was just trying to kill Ali
I got to get it
Still seems
It would be it would be very wrong very wrong yeah
Tricking people dog dr. Mercola
No good no matter what I just
Good good to hear that someone did that
I want from that is just to look on the face of a medical professional as they hear that
Only slow over the realization that you are not
Joking that this conversation is in fact happening
What did I do with my life app I went to nursing school got two kids
Husband through college in hydrogen peroxide
Hayden Jordan
Glycerin big fan from
You know the state where else
And wishes
He was the horse she was riding on and then I got mad at his son for
Miserable
Anyway
Don't have a lot of fun to listen to
Podcast on muesli relaying information about
Itsfunneh
And tell me what comes up on summertime talk about dannemora
KERO one of those guys is that
They just say it's a grifter grifters
For money and whatever
I always
I personally feel like that's a little
Dismissive and I think it undermines the
Seriousness of what those
People doing
Stay in the problems that it caused
Just wondering if
You guys had to take on
Thank you love
Yeah I think
Yeah the question of whether or not people are shills or grifting or whatever is
It's it's a it's a matter it it matters a real question
No Kizzy
I think you approach
Grifting and ideology ideological step a little bit
Currently in terms of how you might want to respond to it
But at the end of the day it doesn't really matter in terms of the consequences and the effect that
Somebody has
If you take this
The
Make a Koch brothers paying
People
To promote X
Like
They would only be paying that
But if it was effective and there was
Some sort of a policy or societal goal right that further
And that's kind of what's more important than whether or not someone's beliefs are so
Sincere
It's always an interesting question because I get
Especially with listening to Alex like it's almost impossible to believe that he believed the ship
Right
It's about always becomes very very interesting we like you making up that you believe in the devil Roar
Actually
Something you believe
But at the end of the day the effect it has on the audience is really with more important
And trying to
Avert whatever damage
Can be caused by sincere or Griff
Propaganda
I mean I think
One thing to always keep in mind is that
The Griff
Attract
Psychopathic
Monsters
You know like
You do have to remember that if you are grifting people you are essentially stealing their money and giving them nothing but
False hope and return
So so you have to then remember that the people who are on this graph
Are 100%
Stealing people and giving nothing back so we are not they believe there
The current bulshit spewing from their mouth
That's who they are
Yeah it's it's
It's important
I have a question but I think it's not the central question
I think that
Sincere or not
These things need to be taken totally High seriously because of the effect right
Consequentialist to an extent by
It's not wrong to
Dwell right
Consider whether or not someone's running a scam sure
It's just not a reason to
Doug throw out whatever they're saying as meeting with
One of the great weekend will be back Jordan
But we have a website
Twitter we are on Twitter is that knowledge underscore fighting that go to bed Jordan in Fresno
And if you could please find a local charity or bail Fund in your area to help out the people doing God's work
For sure I'm Leo I'm dzx Clark
I'm Daryl rundus I'm on five bags of blood
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
I love you