Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
We are the bad guys
College fight
Nick.com
Jordan Jordan
What's up
Well my bright spots
Cut it goes along with the
The let's say the end of the Avenue recordings that offshore kind of inspired
But the potential of things that I've started working on something
Okay but I'm very reinvigorated by
A lot of the stuff that we talked about like that how boring Alex is in the present-day of stuff
I have found something that is tickling my interest
Bone Thugs
And
I guess this is kind of Dez so your bright spot is Mystery
Yeah a little bit but I feel like I feel like I found
A Direction I want to go down and I'm very excited about that and there'll be more details about that forthcoming.
Absolute value
I have a bit of a mix
Ever bright spot dark spot
So I told you
We might have a bright spot previously.
Getting my partner a birthday
I was so worried this was about like things going bad with about God
The s*** out of it
He's played all that okay cool I did I got her a good gift
I got her a tennis
Bracket
Was good tennis racket and I gave it to early
Because
Her birthday is in the fall
We might not be able to play
Seasonal
What I had my back
Pocket was that on her birthday
I had scheduled like fruit arrangement to be deliver Edible Arrangements
Percent chocolate dipped strawberries
So who's going to show up on her birthday she was like oh my God it wasn't that you already gave me over
Is going to be fantastic
Exactly like that
Whatever
Somebody rang the doorbell and I went up and it was the guy delivering the thing not her birthday
I looked at it I grabbed it and I looked down and it had the correct date on it delivered
Big
On top of
Yeah and I just looked at the guy when he was like
Alright man good job and then just left
Into the middle of the night you texted me about this complaining and I berated you how I don't
The guy got it there early
It's just hot it's the gesture and the symbolism
And it's a perishable
No no longer going to survive to the birthday
The situation we're like you can get around the uncomfortableness
That's good that we could actually like
Cause of fight
I'm happy that their birthday present thing worked out
And everything
Alright Jordan
Alright alright
Today we got an episode is it alright it's alright
Okay so we're going to talk about October 2nd through 4th 2020
Checking over the weekend cuz I think there was news that rocked the world
Oh oh
Know what was it
Suicide
The book drop nearby my place
Shutting down that's not the news are you sure
Larry Nichols has passed away
The world will never be the same
I feel
She's in heaven now
I feel real weird about that because
I mean I was aware that the key was probably going to die soon
Did that me like an obituary for him
I wasn't
Surprise cuz I have been trying to
Find a way to do a Wacky Wednesday about his YouTube channel sure cuz he's got a YouTube channel
And it's just trash most of the stuff was awful
But don't like lately there had been like some stuff about him being in the hospital
I don't know if I believe it and I don't like him not too long ago and it was
This is the case with Larry like he's been on death's doorstep for 10 years on Alex's show
So I never really knew what to take seriously but
I mean he was one of the most
Cancerous
Forces and politicking in any way celebrating his death or anyting
But
I think we can trace a lot of the style and bullshitted project Veritas all the way back
Too f****** Larry goddamn nickels
And so much of the
The stuff about Clinton
Fear comes directly
He put out
So
I bring this up because
It does
You know it's
Huge
On some level
Larry Nichols is a
Huge horse
In conservative politics for the last
30 years
He died
Yeah and Alex doesn't bring it up at home
It is here's what
He's out with his friends Nichols for years here's the problem dad
It's like if you and I were on the plane with the Big Bopper
All right you're going to get lost in the news
Could have been front-page obit man oh man
You're not the most famous version of the blade right now Larry I'm sorry it bums me out
If only because of like
The place that he should occupy
In Alex's world the place that he should occupy there is a celebrated pleasure and he's passing should be a Moana
Reflection and Rick
Cognition
As opposed to I don't even know if it comes up
Yeah I don't know that's really sad because even dedicated his life to creating things that Alex could use to demonize
Yep it is political enemies and now
Explain to these guys that you are literally a cog in the machine of your own psycop
No one will care
When you are gone
It's a bummer it's a real bummer
All kind of must know that
I was sad about
Well exit
Today's Show let's say thanks
Tempers can it be thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk deals
Patricia K thank you so much you are now policy walk
Text Patricia
I'm a policy wonk
Megan D that cares about you and I'll probably walk
Who donated on elevated level
Ls&i khil
You are now
Teketeke Pekka
Last initial k
Thank you so much
And Aaron but one a is silent thank you so much for an hour technocrat
Business
Heroin
Why you pimp so good
Freakishly large
Michaela thank you so much thank you so much Aaron but one is Island
If you're out there listening
I got your website now that's right.
You could do is you could take an order for your generosity
Alright hang on to it it's supposed to be delivered later
But let me tell you something
You are too good
You care too much so you're going to take that generosity you're going to deliver it
Fully
Way too early and it's going to work out while I'm trying to do the tire together with the brightness
You not your Fury at me the moment I start talking
Is so disappointing
2121 what do you mean it's too simple.
Something complex something interesting
Alright
I'm just going to take transcripts of your older ones and I'll just read those who you talkin to would that make you feel that
We're going
Yes
Do that
Alright
I think we're doing great
Has bet most likely I think the better aspect of this bed is way better than I've ever been
Obviously when I said that the big news was that Larry Nichols has passed that was a
Of course gouffon
The fact that Trump got killed
And I know is that we recorded on Thursday
I'm sitting here editing lalala
This episode took I took forever to prepare about the debate we did a lot of work
And then as I'm editing the news breaks the Trump got positive test for covid
Now I don't get a weekend
Emergency episode
Have been caused to
Based on the content that Alex is putting out
But you know it did make the episode that we put out feel a little bit older
The new cycle had moved the debate has gone
From everyone's mind forever
On Sunday evening and who knows what will be the reality we're in by Monday
When you're listening to this
Somebody happened we don't know about at 3 a.m.
Monday morning
And you listen to our episode of hoping to hear what Alex is
The sex buddy I'm sorry I don't know yet
Do Alex I think in obvious fashion
A recognizes on Friday on October 2nd
When you get to the studio
Wow
Other that's not the right way to put it
But as soon as he starts the show he's got to bring it up
L 20/20
We are 30
2 days
They will
Balkanization
Melania
So he's he's raising his head on
At least
Has anybody checked to see how pechanec
Taking the news that Melania
It has got to be over
Steve does not come into play on this episode
These three days of time
Nothing really
Oh yeah I suppose you can't have those guys on there but you might get too crazy
President Maui
We gotta shoot everyone with the president at Walter Reed hospital to take the lighthouse
We Gather forty or fifty good men then we rule this country
Department
Alex
One of those big things is I got called it I knew this was going to happen
Let's talk about
Many times
Said that one scenario
The president
Near
The election day
Economy
Warehouse
So Alex had to dig up a clip from six months past
Of him
Saying that they might give Trump covid
But it had nothing to do with like near the election ready
I've listened to you this show
The pretty consistently and I don't think that
I would characterize that as one of Alex's big theories
I think that he might be giving himself a little bit too much credit for saying everything I do you think
Yeah I was six months ago I speculated to drop my kid covid and now haha I'm right.
No
Considering the number and volume of series that I have thrown at the wall
I'm pretty stoked that I got this 16 months ago huh
Whatever
So
Approach that Alex is taking on Friday and I think it's a little bit sad but it is what it is
Positive
Call Shane
Deposit
Whole football team
So that's his first two it's really interesting
Like okay what if it's fake
No one's no one's talking about whether or not this is a fake it's a f****** president
Not this is a false positive
Because
People understand the science
It's and I don't so I'm asking
Questions that no one would ask unless
May have not
Please somebody tell me what's going on is the president
This is the first volley is
Is a false positive
That you can make up your own soda Theory as to what's going on from there
Not actually sick
Okay I don't know give him a false positive
Wow this. Might develop as the show goes along
Well Alex
Information that you need
And it's the information that the world
Beyond
World
Information
We'll just
Listen to me
Rush Limbaugh
We can save America in the world if everyone will just sound like me DNA
That's silly
See recording from the bunker did he did make the decision to go to the bunker it's interesting that you're asking
That's because
He is not in studio
I think I tell Romeo he's at home
Okay
And
Work-from-home day
Well
Weird
Use their home for the first half hour of the show what did you say to me then David night and Owen Shroyer
Your takeover
And then at the end of the second hour Alex shows up at the studio
Okay
Nick begich takes over the floor hour okay
I don't know what's going on
I guess you just
You just can't show up 30 minutes late for
You can show up
2 hours late first
My big theory is that Alex
Who's going to take the day off
And then he woke up
And the president die
He woke up at like 10:30 or something like that
Couldn't have enough time to get to the studio by the time the beginning of the show then
And drove in
Write my theory
Yeah it seems like it makes the most sense
He would have taken the day off for sure if it's news hadn't broken
And then like fuk I got to go in on my day off
This isn't one of these big
Pieces of news that I can just let David and Owen cover I actually have to come in
So
The bottom line though is
This is a visible spot
Listen to me
Very
How carefully
Understand that
Along with
So it's
I was as proof that it dis test is almost certainly false positive
Home he's not even in the office
Where is he going to get this f****** proof
Infowars.com man
Prove covid-19
Proof of that he provides is exactly that it's just a bunch of
Coronavirus
What's up
You won the lottery
Didn't really win
Who won the lottery menu 1
No
The airtight
Appositive
But where's the taco
More test
President
Mega
Don't worry
Thanks
Text Alex vortex
Alex world all of the doctors at Walter Reed Medical Center around like well we did what test
Just got to watch
Got to wait who's the president of the country
We've kind of data.
Ridiculous
90% of tests are false positive
Alex Soto
Connect
Like I don't know where he's getting that information from
But he does connected to a specific story
I think this might be what it's all based on
Houses of article
So Alex is lying about that headline
The actual headline is quick
Connecticut state lab finds 90 positive covid-19 tests were false
This was out of 144 test that we're done at the specific lab during the
Span of June 15th to July 17th
And 90 of them turned out to be false positives not 90%
90 out of 144 is 62.5%
Still high
But Alex doesn't know any of the details of the story
This has to do with the lab testing procedure that this lab began operating in June 15th
Which led to a lot of false
When doing validation of the results they found this high level of false positive and immediately went to work on reviewing and correcting was going wrong
In the process
This wasn't something that Alex and is Intrepid Patriot journalists dug up or something that anyone was trying to hide it was just
Covered by the lap when they were doing quality control and it was reported by the mainstream media which is how Alex knows about it
The true version of the story doesn't call into question the validity of covid-19 testing
You just highlight the part of the scientific process
Or double and triple checking things
Can sometimes find errors in the way things are done
Can be improved
Only the fake version of the story supports Alex's
Conspiracies which is why it's the only version
Vino's
In the real world you can find a ride up from the Harvard Medical School which explains the PCR test which are
Beasley-Wood Trump is God
Have false positive rates close to zero
There's some concern about false negatives but the reason that the test is
Considered like a gold standard for diagnosis
Is because they are very precise when they're done correctly
The false positive rate should come close to zero
Most false positives results
Are thought to be due to lack of contamination or other problems with how the lab is performed the test
Not limitations of the test itself
A recent paper in Lancet discuss the issue of false positive with covid-19 testing saying quote
The current rate of operational false positive swab test in the UK is unknown
Preliminary estimates show we could be somewhere between .8% and 4%
That's still a significant figure if you consider the scale of testing with being. But it's a far cry from what Alex
Suggesting
To give you some context about how nuts it is for Alex
Say there's a false positive rate of
90%
The FDA put out a warning about a line of test produced by Beady back in July
A study suggested that 3% of their test could be false positive
Based on concerns about the reagents that were used
BFDIA quote told Healthcare professionals to treat positive results
From test using the BB real
Is presumptive and consider confirming findings using a different authorized coronavirus diagnostic
This was because of a
Concern about a 3% false positive for tr8
What Alex is talking about
Sweetly disconnected from reality
There's just nothing to that
You know it's like when you want to compromise
And you're like
On different ends
The Spectrum
What you really want to find out if you only need to change
55%
You know you're almost
But when reality is at literally 90%
And unreality is inverse that reality is 3% your at 90%
We're never coming close
It seems to never come
Even if it seems like making Headway with Alex would be getting him to admit alright 85
We'll compromise
It 95%
Sure
So this is supposed to be a list of headlines
That are
Proving
Sing the Trump probably is a false positive test
Sure this gets thrown in
$1,000
What does that have to do with anything even money to people who have to shelter
They're lying and they're trying to kill the president
Also some folks are going to get like 1250
That the president
People are going to get 12:50
California talking about giving this money to people who have to quarantine in order to help
Tell them be able to survive
Spread the disease obviously means that they're going to go out trying to get coronavirus cuz they want at 12
That's the only way they only thing that makes sense to me that he thinking is so backwards in Twisted
But it's weird that headline is in this stack that Alex's used to prove the trumps
Diagnostic
Test was a false positive
Which is weird
And it shows that he didn't prepare at all he doesn't know just chill at home
A stack of headline
That's very sad
So there's another headline
This one
Is really effective
The story about the Tennessee Titans
Players and staff who tested positive for covid-19 only broke on September 29th and as far as I can tell none of them have been shown
To be false positives
I strongly suspected I was just making that up
Because he just called read this headline
How about people tested positive for the virus any kind of realize that this was
Supposed to be about 2
Fake yeah not about how people getting sick
By October 2nd
The day that Alex is recording this episode The Associated Press is reporting that the outbreak in the Titans organization was now up to 18
People testing positive
Along with players on the Patriots and Chiefs
Who had to postpone their scheduled game this weekend
The reality of the story unsurprisingly appears to be the exact opposite of what Alex's report
Supposed
This being the case with are all shown to be false positive results
It looks like the initial headlines about eight people testing positive we're only the beginning
Right well you think he's wrong
90% of the
But he thinks he's wrong about 3/4
So I think you guys can get to a compromise classica pickle
So you might be asking like okay
What's the game
With the false positive
That is a good question
I would like to know the motivation behind this
Clearly insane Act
Wow
I mean
Yahoo president drink a lot of soda
2 plan
Covid-19
Pikachu
About
President
Alex you're going into reruns they already poisoned his diet so I was just riding down like this is
From 2016
Explain why he was speaking weird
Slow-acting poison
His show is in syndication basically
Something news except
And honestly I was looking at some of the comments
What's on Bandit video for this and like
His video that he put out on Saturday and a lot of them were like grow up Alex
Philly
Okay so the conspiracy is
They gave him a false positive rest
In order to have cover right to poison his Diet Cokes are again
Didn't need to do that the last time they played well it didn't work last time maybe the problem was they didn't have a good enough
Cover for your note suggests that didn't work last night cuz it didn't happen last night but I am 3%
Positive you're right
Alex has got to go
Weather
3 days
3:00
Got to get some got to try and sell some
Stop before I drive him to the studio
This is so weird I mean like I don't understand outside of like
I woke up at 10:30
And I thought I had the day off yeah I don't understand what scenario could lead you to be able to
To get to the studio by like 1:45
But not by 11
Like I don't know what it what it could be
It's just it's just
I mean it could be so I'm not willing to rule out something innocuous
Like there's something with his
You know
Somebody's
I got to go to school or something
What is a possibility for the meeting he couldn't
Reschedule or should we had a meeting with the lawyers lawyers
Something like that for sure even so a lot of that stuff you can reschedule or you can pay some
Someone to do
Like
She could cure the kids to the hospital
Trump has
Covid well I mean yeah
Everybody still got to make it
Get to the school seems like Alex
Probably got wasted woke up at 10:30 as like froggatt
Now you are absolutely describing what I immediately
We thought was
Break it up this time I mean who knows
So Alex does show up at the end of the second hour
And
McMahon
There's no proof
That
This Coronavirus
Covid with the president
Which was an attack
Sure but maybe it was
Once they is Benatar
The first one
The first person who breathes it
What
We're all dreaming
To make it look
No when I found out that Boris Johnson people that I know that were around a city
Alright
Alright buddy
This is a point where even Alex
Should stop be like
Am I doing
Am I here
I'm here
The prime minister's face
I said it was a false
Positive people called in the show earlier it was maybe Trump got sprayed in the face of weaponized
Coach
Or maybe he acted in ways that are specifically make you susceptible to catching it
If someone
Maybe he did exactly what you would do if you were being
Not careful about
Maybe this is the only
Logical and inevitable
Conclusion that his actions have lettuce
You know it's a situation where you can be careless
A thousand times
Nothing happen if you're lucky
Circumstances are what they are but that's 1,000
Indian first time could be the time
Avec tell you end up getting unlucky and what you do you're unlucky
And if you're at roughly chance 100,000 444
Play Red by 1445 you're going to get cold
Dan's if you're at like 10 bucks a 300
Dammit previous 299 times you've been fine that doesn't change anything about the 300th time
Anything about like
The odds
Lucky every other time it's been going on black for a while then it's it's
That means it's more likely to land on red this time everybody knows that's how it works man
Wild
There's a couple possibilities what's going on as we've already heard Alex has a couple maybe false positive maybe they say
Sprayed him in the face with it.
Like a crack team of international assassin taking out the president that would have been nice
The club has came up to drop with a Seltzer bottle just created
Vaudeville assassination
The possibilities here and shockingly Trump is dumb and behave in a way that you would if you were
Katchafire
It could be a false test most of them are false
Oregon
And I've already assassinate the president needs Walking Dead ride
Sure
So these are the three possibilities you've got I think it would shorten Velux out immensely
Three possibilities we got
Be there
It's
Assassination Norfolk tap
Or
Another
Right
The other one is
It seems like that's kind of Alex's
It can't be just an a******
Who did exactly what
It's poison
What is the false test what are you doing
Will they say he died of Cody dies or something else
That's how I do it you just poisoning
Test positive
Now
Decent
Poison
The blood
But now they're creeping in with a weapon from Canby
Alright
Spy novel whatever Alex says
That's why you would be caught
Elvis impersonator
To pin it on his friend
Know how I started the show with my brights by was kind of the keys
The Galaxy's in a teasing mood to
Very high-level today
1 reasons.
Incredible information
I was dropped
I'm almost speechless right now
Trying to digest all of this
Asbestos
Play right-back infowars.com
Least favorite genre of Alex Jones
Tuesday I have big bombshell news which explains why I was an hour and 40 minutes late
Totally
I can't tell you where it came from
But it's high level
I will get into it
I like whenever he's telling excuse he's telling like extravagant lies for why he's late to his bosses the audience
You know like
No no
I was trying to get here on time
I was trying to really believe that I'm trying so there is a bicycle
12 ones riding
In front of me while I was driving my car and then what do you know the guy throws little milkshake at me and I we can do an old-timey
Turns out he's David Rockefeller killed the president
Bicycle
Milkshakes
Who among you would not do the same thing
It's the cross I bear
So Alex goes back from break and he's got some interesting thoughts about the media's coverage
Trump and his sickness
We got President Trump
I supposedly with Coronavirus
Ianni's
They're saying in the media
Trump hasn't really
Confirm a friend if you still have him
Walking after dancing all looking list
Alex knows that because that's what he does
Yeah you can do that to every single time he's done something about her Hillary
My God they're about to die
Okay
I hope you know that game pretty well that's why you can
See it
Stu's not Steve pieczenik is not Rodger Stone
Someone named dr. Carrie madej
Maddie's not remember how to pronounce her name
Anyway she's a doctor osteopathic believe who believes that vaccines are
They're all evil
She made a viral video and so Alex's
Hanging out with her here's a little taste of what you bringing to the table
John life study vaccines for
Since my early twenties
Because I was very concerned about them
And
Like to say that
Vaccines are not what we think they are
And a little story just to give some of your listeners some history of vaccines
The tetanus vaccine when I studied
There's a long story behind that
Turned out really it's an abortion.
Google search
Yeah
So
This this
Ichi
Cuz I'm interesting ideas
Obviously the xen
Evil
They're a bunch of different vaccines that are being developed and are possible candidates for
Coronavirus tracker covid-19
And
Terry believes
That there's only one
Now it seems to believe that too
And it's going to be something that changes you into a genetically modified organism
DNA and they're doing that because this thing that it'll change
Or whatever they're putting into you is patented
You know we can actually patents
Of something that synthetic so technically
When we are getting a piece or this vaccine and if it does become permanent within our genome
Static
That part of us can be patented and owned
People need to understand this because
Owner because donors
So basically the theory goes that like this
Change your DNA so let's just imagine it's just like the DNA of your arm
No Monsanto owns your arm I gave you that strand of DNA and I can take it away review
Right.
I would I would say
I don't think it works that way
I'm sick of The Sovereign citizens like
With a
Capital letters capital letter sound stupid if the government said if you would say that the government owns part of your DNA
Now I'm listening
Now we're talkin Sovereign citizen
Right here
You just remove your own DNA and then the government can own you
Shockingly when he called into the show
It work totally fine
There were no problems
Audio-wise why everything went by probably cuz it's Hardline
My fortune
That is not the case
Doctor
And an animal studies
That's great
But then needed a challenge test which is
Ethical humans but they can do a challenge chest
You know a guy broke up when you come back to her
Yeah I did
Everyday
Every single day
Guy breaks up in the middle of talking about these of these vaccine trials on animals
They're having like really
Goodnight the past that had these positive results for this type of vaccine
I'll be there whenever they got a challenge test
Right that's what
Skype cuts
I'm going to pick up on this
I'm going to pretend that this was my Secret Bombshell news
This is amazing
This is Alex right here man
You know there's guy broke up when you come back to her
Michelle off of this
Because when
The challenge test
Because the horrible autoimmune response
To whatever the outside pass
The information
Proceed up today
Serendipity
Synchronicity
Providence
What am I told you I razor isn't scientist
At one of the major biotech
Research
Ultra
And what are you tell me
He told me a lot
Forza Horizon 2
Alright Alex Jones b******* right here
Awesome tops
Secret top-level information in the reason that he wasn't on the show earlier it's because he was receiving the super important bombshell information
He doesn't even hit with the actual secret news's but Skype connection drops off right in the middle of her making
Sensational claim
Alex piggybacks patent claims that that was actually a secret news all along it sure does
Exactly what Alex
Just claiming here
In order for the story to make any sense
I guess this morning Alex randomly met the head scientist of a biotech company but didn't know that this guy
Guy was the head of a biotech company
This person presumably knew Alex wasn't told Alex
The covid-19 vaccine
Screen causes severe autoimmune response
Do General coronavirus is it which point Alex research the information
Found out it's true and I guess in the process realize that the guy was the head scientist of a giant biotech company
Researching these claims made it so Alex
Couldn't get to work on time I guess even though he would have known the Trump had covid and he couldn't possibly take the day off
Rick what is
Soon as he woke up
Then Alex goes into his show does the first half-hour without mentioning this big secret news that he got from a big week in the biotech field
I wanted to confirm it as true
Of course then he shows up to the studio presumably having just done a real deep dive into this vaccine in autoimmune situation
Seapointe bring it up
Intellicast Skype connection goes out
Is it such a loadable shaped such transparent thing
Steelers
When you bring somebody on to drop a bombshell story you can't under
It's it's it's remarkable though the way he does this like you see this from time to time but it's not always as explicit as this
Winnie does be fake setup of huge bombshell news and then something will come up later in the show.
That's actually what my big Aaron's was
That's better than whatever it was I was going to make up with
It's time for me to lie about it or if I don't come up with something
But I want to lie about say is a big news
I can just say I'll get to it tomorrow I got to digest this
It's just too big too big
He does this quite regularly
A pretty impressive
It's a it's a nice cheap
Yeah it's so he's he's got this
Fake doctor
Working at biotech company was told in
All this stuff
And not this is
This is interesting because I went to the conspiracy about this imagined covid-19 vaccine
This is Improv
Right here alright I am almost certain that Alex is coming up with this on the spot
Vaccine
For covid-19 but the main platform is a regular cold
Virus
A bunch of stuff stacked onto it
Call Stacks
Bumper
If you do that
And then your body learns have an autoimmune response to that particular virus it's so Broad
You will now have an autoimmune response to the coronavirus that's so, it's everywhere
Making it where you can't even go outside
Because you'll get so sick
From regular cold viruses
They're trying to get rid of your immunity
Call virus
Allergic to it
Which is what killed most the people in the Spanish Flu was they were allergic to the virus
Not that it was actually replicating it
And it's just so diabolical the side this was breaking down the fact that
This is so critical
Define
With covid
The body doesn't even see it as a threat
And won't create a meal
But you're also allergic to
So you have an autoimmune response to both
Peanut
In the flu shot or whatever it was they got when they were younger
I'm guessing that
He probably did
Talk to somebody but it was like John Rappaport or Andrew Wakefield it wasn't some high-level bios
Weird anti vaxxer
Told him these things
That wasn't why you was late this morning
I was just bullshittin
Sounds made-up AIU can you conceive you like little details he's trying to pull in goes through The Conspirator
Smiled at the end of that been like how did I pull that 1980
Team flew out and then throw some b******* about
That's how it kill people I don't know anything about the 1918 flu
Awesome skater who lands a trick the first try
This doctor that he is
Talking to his interview and get that made dude got to get her back
Shirt Skype video
Join
By dr. Terry
My daddy here
And I really appreciate her
Come out as she's medical doctor
That was crazy
Doctors across the board probably censorship is that never happens on your show
Forever happens on
Infowars
Tech issues never dated Sky problems never ever happen
But by your own logic earlier
Just because it's not censorship
The times doesn't mean that the hundred first time isn't that so
Logic
I appreciate what you're trying to do but it doesn't work
So we got to get this after back on man I got to get hurt to work
Navigate to Skype to work
Got to get her
The spout
Her
Proof
Your head spins they want in our bodies and then we learn what they're doing is Jimmy pigging
Weather
Who wants to have this genetic Revolution over Rush
What do you think this is all going doctor
Play God Frozen again
Let's go ahead and play the full clip
Pelosi
It's never happened
Never happened
Now we're going to play this
Incredibly terrible audio
Nancy Pelosi
Dashing about her we get back to the doctor because they're going to give it another shot
She has a theory about a magical
That will control everything alright and it will know what meds
Like all your
Your med levels in your body and all your vitals and every single thing about you
And well
Enter the smartphone through the house after you have
If you work on your house after you'll find drop-down
Stop categories
Brush your teeth
Everything about you is
Everything that you're doing with a transmitter yourself
Connection
Kind of behavior
Worthy country Society for the good of the whole
Repercussion
Oh she's getting
Censored again
But this is the next level
That's the next level of the censorship
Bad bad connection
Quietly
A very dark thing for him doing
I see her doing interviews all the time is heaven like
Deep David like
It's all this is us this is us
I thought there's something on all right because
Call the f****** time
Over and over and over combination of both
Like I don't I don't know exactly what it is but it's
It's definitely not censorship it's you guys being f******
Incompetent
Alex
Fortress
Is a little much
So let's just complain about Michael Moore
Michael Morris is Evil Genius to postpone the election
When the elections Democrats
If you have any intelligence you know Democrats to the mail-in ballot
They want a lockdown they said they're going to contesta matter what they know they're losing
Fake
He wants to hold off the election
You said
Can babysit your shoulder
Pull up your house is Conte
Tracers
I'm sorry you didn't submit the inoculations were taking your childre
Just the facts ma'am
Good
Good time
Uncle
Shelter and uncle
More
Like I don't think I need that gig
They're both of them
Yeah
Community service
Did they get arrested
A of degrees
It's really weird that Alex
Is saying it's like there's a false positive test and then he's mad at Michael Moore being like
Saying that this isn't a real positive
You guys just both have weird conspiracies about what's going on motivated by slightly different levels of distrust
Both of you guys should
Call Patel.
Episode this Friday episode
That's where we're at basically
Yeah that's a big
Serious
Problem Alex at half hour at the beginning and been totally fine
There's no reason that Owen couldn't interview the tax lady
It would have been totally fine
I think that it was weak
From the perspective of
Everyone
Well I mean this is big
This is kind of a big deal
Is the real hard to wrap
Your head around it kind of situation
I don't pretend to know what like what's going to happen or know who you can trust
In terms of a lot of the details that are coming out like weather
You know like he was low on oxygen or what the temperature is like
Very difficult
Like he's going to die I have no idea
It's also weird say
He'll be fine
Although you might be
You might not be combined
Exacto f****** idea
What I can say
With no qualms
Is this
Stick
Agree with you
There's all kinds of questions about the timeline of when he knew he was sick what steps
Not taken
What do you wear around the time of the debate when he went to that fundraiser all these things the Supreme Court
Corpse Party
Like all this just wild he's very serious and very real and important
And Alex came in and the Bessie had was
Water tester false positive
They read about the headlines.
Connected so I'm not
And then he developed it to maybe someone with a covid lapels
Sprayer
Trump with a weapon Heights covid
It's like okay this is the best you've got
We got it we got to update that say you know it is like when the going gets weird
The weird turn
Pro some of them but
The already professionally weird literally phone it in
This is why he's being usurped by other online cast because he's not willing to
Like I don't know maybe just doesn't have it in him anymore
Doesn't have it in him to
Like really throw himself headlong into
Damn the Torpedoes kind of
But weirdness I mean he's been beaten down pretty
Pretty hard
Lawton lawsuit
I would I would be it's like it
It's totally acceptable I would find a reasonable for you to be like
I just don't got it
I've been beating too much like Icarus I flew too close to the Sun and my wings are burned
I'm not there anymore I agree yong-gun I agree and I would accept there too
But if you were in that position at your someone like Alex
You better get out
You better take your money and run
Because you're going to be
Eaten alive by the Young
Lyons Young Guns
Michael Jordan on the Wizards was still Michael Jordan but he still got his ass beat a lot
He was old people cherish whatever he beat their ass over like all goddamn
Is Michael Jordan a fifty-year-old man I got beat by Michael
Ifucking Jordan you know it's still cool
So Alex I thought
Pressure
But the reason I didn't
Immediately think like let's do an emergency episode of I think Saturday is going to come in
He's going to do a special episode cuz you did about when
Ruth Gator Ginsburg
And so I figured like this is big enough stuff Alex Deeds to do a Saturday episode
Do you know when Ruth Bader Ginsburg died
A year ago
Feels like
No idea only put out like an 8-minute video
On on Saturday and
Realize like okay
False positive Ain't Gonna Fly that's not going to work
What are we going to do come to the hospital ocean
Evidence
The facts are overwhelmed
Either
The doctors
Walter Reed Medical
Trying to
Idiots
They are giving the
Experimental
Drugs
And the other rendezevere
It's on record
You wouldn't give either one of these
Unless they were
Well I mean the possibility there is that the case is more serious than you're allowing yourself to believe yeah
Like
Like I would say I would assume
Generally
They
If this is the course
Of action is being taken
But neither trumpets
Assisted on it
Or
He has a case that requires that in the doctors think it's a prude
Course
You know with malpractice for just like
You and me normal people getting real big trouble for not providing the best care
Alex Jones the bills they pay for insurance my friend
Let's say malpractice with the f****** president
You're going to be fine
Career over
Well I mean you don't bail wasn't remembered for that whole metal detector accidentally killing the president thing
I think that you know
I'm sure if the doctor invented is something that's really really important to humanity
Here is the whole killing the president they would probably be for
Forgot to do magic like the next day after
Sketchpad
What will I be remembered for
So this is basically getting that play with the Big Bopper
This is basically all the Saturday show has going for it is like these doctors are probably tried to kill Trump
I got to say some sational dangerous kind of talk and doesn't do anybody a liquor good
It's how we come in on the 4th
What's that day
This episode
Is
Possibly one of the weirdest things I've heard from Alex in a while
It's
Almost as if
Haven't covid being in the hospital is
Kind of secondary
That's a good angles another piece of news that requires
Hypertension
The cover-up government
Child sex trafficking
18 votes
Or elected Congress appear to be moving towards making
Keto phobia
Crime
Who's the really interesting way for Alex to cover this story
Apparently his version of it is that house Dems voted to cover up pedophilia
In reality the house passed a largely symbolic resolution condemning
McEwen. Which is slightly different than voting discover a pedophilia that is very different I would I would say that that is
Buried
Additionally was not house Democrats who voted the measure through it was overwhelmingly supported cross both party
Speakers qanon s*** has no place
Insensible politics 371/2 8-18-18
And so that it's so if I'm
Doing the numbers on house
380 of those about right now is almost everybody in the house
Oh yeah that would
Literally nothing
Actually bring any child traffickers
Justice North actually saved any traffic children and infect experts in the field when very clear
That away qanon people sensationalize the topic and focus attention
In various bizarre directions has the real-world effect of making the actual work of disrupting trafficking operations
More
If you look at qanon from a purely consequentialist framework they're helping the very people they pretend to be bringing down
But they're also creating an unhinged
Colt behind Anna
Extremely right-wing aspiring dictator
So the secondary effect of their existence is the creation of a possibly highly-motivated politically-driven group
That will never vote against outrageously right-wing candidates and will be willing to work for free to create social media
Champagne Brandon or opponents
These right-wing candidates
How to repair files and Demon
The yelling about saving the children it doesn't result in any actually save children it's necessary
Marion order to make sure that the group has some kind of plausible ability to deflect criticism
Head turner tax around
It was all
The house passes a resolution denouncing
Sakura not because it's a weird cult that has led to multiple multiple violent incidents and has the potential to lead to a whole lot more
Alex can report on that is the house voting to cover up pedophilia
You see this game being played about all sorts of right-wing types Tommy Robinson is one of the
Tacticas
Deployed to cover
Spell just a charade you use whatever Optics and tools are available to justify and strengthen your dictators grasp on power
Even if it means carrying water for a group of lunatics who hate you
And you yelled about freaky
That's what Alex is doing
Yeah that's the top story
I don't want to I don't want to say it but it is occurring to me now that elrond really did know what he was doing whenever he decided
Did not to like step into politics
Like create your own kingdom
Where you can't let you know so you know this what I'm saying like
Whatever it's like you're in my reality just get him out of my own room
They're doing Scientology think I'll make your own f****** compound in the middle of nowhere you guys can all believe in whatever you want
Just stay out of my business
F*** it I'll give you tax
Exempt status if you stay in the compound
You get your own internet you get your own little place there
And then we get to live in our fun time
I don't know the Galaxy's like
Strong fond feelings about compounds
So is what I wouldn't trust me if it a compound
That's how it starts the show
That's the beginning of the show but the top headline like
It's not news
Not the Trump
Is in the hospital
Top headline tonight on this Sunday October 4th Global transmission
Inauguration he's not President Trump
Walter Reed Medical military facility
Military action against
Hong Kong and Taiwan
Destroy the US economy
The heart of all of this
That sounds right
What makes them operate
What makes them tick
Your house Alex Jones
I don't know if
What makes
Demon stick
Is the top story
I don't know if you
You can cover that the New Yorker does one of those every six months or so they go to demon country and they're like
We really got to figure out why won't you guys not like the Satan in the oven
I like his policies on immigration and they really do it
Play I don't know they're not far off are they don't know if this is a good use of time
Her Alex
Considering
Everything
Should be about Trump having Coke
Yeah you know we believe
We speculated on what would happen
If and when Trump actually got covid Alex's blame does not even
Apparently
It's definitely the second
Yeah but the devil's around who know what you know what it is I think I think it's like
I got to kick this game
I don't know what's going to happen
What happened
Will very much
Affect what I do
Yeah cuz I give Trump ties Alex can't be like these doctors are going
2BR killing Trump lick
Yeah that will
Possibly make his audience
Start shooting
But if he recovers then
You don't want
I already said that when this happens there moving on the president
It's time to start killing
I feel like he's just in a position where he's like that's that and see what happen
Which is dumb
In-N-Out
Not good I think this is a proof of my theory which is that he will he's
He blinked
Now would be that literally
He's already laid the groundwork
The moment the news came out if he was going to pull the trigger on like now is when we start this
Civil War that's when you do it
Yeah and it's interesting to that I think Alex Mae
Internalized some of that blank
Any might recognize
It because
He's talking about qanon and the way they'd like the house voted
Taking down the hall of fame
And I have not heard Alex talk like this before
Videos
Lowrider pqq people.
Because the public is awake
They're aware and then and now
Alex Jones
Assembled each day
Set up so that they can
Poses Q
Esoteric
Foggy
Cliff into water this
Louder
Good yeah I've not heard Alex say anything other than like I am the symbol of the
The idea that he thinks he's second 2q and being a symbol of the resistance
Into the deep state
Steamed meaningful
It reminds me of Shadow Water
Whenever all the sudden he's like Lissa
I don't actually deal with those deep State size I don't deal with that stuff
You know who's the leader of this
You know if anybody does something foggy
Excuse the symbol of their elected leaders
Just so you know that
I didn't even think about that
That's interesting. Interesting possible way to read that
She's getting to real right now
Trump
Totally
I can't let this s*** happen you're going to kill my kids
That is that is an interesting possible cover-your-ass kind of
Huh I didn't think about the Envy interesting see where things
Things go I don't know if there's any strong indications
From the rest of this episode
But I want to keep that in mind
Otherwise they're going to kill Trump Hospital
Want to be a fear Monger for no reason
I want to be if you're looking for money from sticking
Are way more dangerous than covid-19
Do doctors in a press conference yesterday
We're monitoring him at Walter Reed Medical Facility because of the treatments
Don't worry
K drug
Patent shopping
You can't solve
50 boxes behind
Thousands of dollars per dose on
Showtime
We have the Infowars emergency elections Dale blowout our best-selling products that are still amazing experiences
Yourself cool man
Evil plan assembly.
Trip for a few grand at a time they won't give Trump hydroxy
Silly
Now there's a further problem of this and that is if you'll recall a couple months ago Trump said he would take
Taking hydroxychloroquine as a preventative
That by not work
Gets us busy
That's what this next clip is actually about but Alex misrepresented
Persona headlines
Faces credibility crisis
They're saying he says it doesn't exist
Shut down travel from China crisis is about knowing knowing what to believe
The credibility crisis is about that like
He said he was taking hydroxychloroquine baby he was maybe he wasn't that no one knows
That's why I like I think it's kind of irresponsible for folks like
Michael Moore others to be like
Hey you probably faking that you have no reason to
You leave that other than distrust you
So I think
I think positing it is a little irresponsible but at the same time I totally understand
Where the impulse who knows what the f*** is going on anything could be happy
Real crazy conspiracies because they think that Alex Jones
Williams work
It's
It's understandable to have your brain go into those areas
I'd like
Hey it's it's because of a crisis of
Confident like I don't know what believe this s***
These people are saying contradictory things can't believe
The presidents
Doctor
Because the president's doctor
Is told to lie about his condition to make him look good
If you can't believe the doctor
That is
Covering the president
You can't believe it
Like that's the only like that should be literally the only job where you cannot lie
Just doctor shouldn't be
You can't lie
Isn't there something wrong with that I don't know I don't know if that's in the
I don't hide
Probably not in those I think Epocrates was probably like well there's no way somebody would lie about the
President getting hurt
To buy Sunday Alex is kind of having to wrestle with the like well when I suggested it was a false positive
It looks like I was wrong
I think Trump is actually
Maybe a problem about the only thing that Alex can work with is playing games around like
See that's it
Is he sick enough to have these preet alright
Trump's blood oxygen level drop
Probably Friday
Parking health concerns
Meadows
So that's what the White House is now saying that
His oxygen level
Have a good eye
You look very narrow face
Passion
Barry White
Credit Karma
Orange Glo
What is a regular cold
But they're giving him you don't
So if you think the Trump drop 20 or 15 lb since the debate sure if that's
Severe nausea
Something really f***** up
Few days
Who doesn't look at
You take you take a lot of zinc you lose 5225 everybody knows
It's very unhealthy
Yeah I think Alex is like I don't know where is he on dab.
Where is he
He's somewhere in there
Starting to compost
Deal-making
Speaking to make a deal
Yeah
Never gotten supplements you never got
Elmer book
Now is the time it could be your last chance
Because I'm
I'm in business IC
We can reorder
Stockbridge
Best selling
You are my mom
40 hour straight
Apple the next year
I thought about George Soros
You so thanks for taking action
Get the Money and Run
That would support your theory
If I were him
100% it's getting too hot I know I can't imagine making a plan
That far in advance
Right now if you know what I mean like next Wednesday we're going to do something
I don't know what I'm going to do within the next
4 hours every Twitter update I get I'm like
Is this the MoMA
Weak there is no next
There's a decent chance that I will f*** around and convince myself to watch that entire funny cam
Probably not because I've done that in the past and so much of it is just like
You playing the same video
Although I think it might be
It'll be really fun
Do do that as some kind of a marathon or something
It wouldn't you can have fun in my head you could live stream it and have a nice little watch party with with
Bunch of policy
Could I want to do that to people
Think about something
Hillary
Really
Talking Hillary
Right now
Well I mean do you know what happen
I don't care
This is actually really serious
I mean
Good looking like a very serious is very very Siri
Let me search engine what's in this book
Far worse than 40
And actually Lori posed with a book
What the devil
Hillary Clinton at sexually explicit
Book of satanic
Blastoise
Okay okay now damn
Does he not know that Larry
He doesn't
Well you might know he hasn't brought it up
Dude okay Hillary Clinton
I don't even know this is now a podcast
I did not know that
Until she had a picture of herself recording a podcast
Since you had a laptop
It was sitting on a pile of books
One of them
What is an art book
By this Italian
Glass sculptor and apparently
There is a Biggs about devils
Suck it
Alex is like a man it's it's Devil Ray okay so you're telling me that the president is on the verge of death
And we're having an argument about whether or not the Venus de Milo should be shown in
Schools
Blown glass grape
In the shape of devils having sex off is a sign
Haha of the devil
I'm pissed and we have been doing this for almost four years now and I bet Hillary has more listeners
And I just don't think she's put in the time
I mean I think
Grammy making what is she done
Andrew Secretary of State
What you think of as the leg work
Resume is much better than mine
So
Has this weird thing towards the lake
The end of
The 2nd hour
Sunday's show
Alex is in a weird mood
He's talking about
How
He
Is the last
Person
Who gets the information that that naked whenever they can't get the information out any other way
They go to him
Because they know that he's Brave and he'll I do that makes him a crap cover
Toad or something
Sounds very bitter about like
Why am I not the first choice if I'm the one who's brave enough to put out the information
We told you that's been out here before he released it
Why
William Benny I just met
With the head of US National Intelligence ametron
He already gave me until they gave him the Intel
Instead no one's covering this we gave it the fox
Go on Jones's showings
Apathetic
Asha
Anatomy
Why not to get William Benny
Call Me Up and Hold My Hand go
Go look at this memo
The five
2017 out for 6 months
The last guy
That's how that feels like
No one else will do it they open the door okay you have an audience were covered toad
You can release it now
Myself
War covered town
City Hall
Olive crap
Wants to see
And then when everyone else fails the dungeon door little
Crab covered download you can do it now
You sound really mad
So bitter
Is bad
Yeah
Like
That's what they do with you whenever they're like will throw this phone
The people at Fox couldn't get away with putting this out because it's ridiculous and they wouldn't make it past any
Any kind of editors
Even though the shoddy ones that they may be employees
So yes toad,
Hey Dan quick question
What would you call William Bennie's Warehouse where they hold those blackmailed
Go for it
Benny's Leverage
Depot
Oh I get it
Sorry it took me a second to be a play on the liquor store
But people outside of the Chicagoland area might not know
Is there is a Binny's
Beverage Depot liquor store here in Chicago
Maybe maybe a couple other cities but I certainly don't think there's any of Europe
This is a little bit of a US citizenship
Alex
You can tell there's a little bit of a different mood there
He's bummed
He's mad
But I also think that he's getting a little drunk
I think
I think he started drinking during the first hour there's a point where you can really hear him take a tug on something
But I don't you know you don't know it could be water could be
I'm not saying for sure that in the second hour of his Sunday show he is in fact
Struck
He's different
The first hour is
It is what it is it's a normal just Alex Jones stupid show
The second hour he brings in John bowne
Gregory's
Sheet Gates
Off the rails
So fat all right
Here's John bound talking about how everyone who's not like his kind of Christian
He's basically going to end up being into working for Sabre
Their satanic
Even if you think you're an atheist at this point you got to choose sides
Because
You're going to end up satanic
End up seitan
Can I suggest
You will not end up satanic. The end up being viewed as satanic
Bow wow there's that it's okay even if you are just an atheist or a Muslim or Buddhist store
Jewish going to like hey
We're going to call you Satanist eventually
You understand with the script
Or eventually we will label you all satan that sound
Play basketball at the YMCA together I'm not a saint
That's why would I even be allowed
Now you're saying
Hasbro
Is where I really got the sense that maybe Alex is a little bit boozed-up
They're talking about how they don't prepare for these interviews that they do just great
Metallic
This is just getting f***** up
You turn on even turn on Fox News turn on MSNBC that just put you right back to sleep everything
Find
Movies before
No no no
It's a respect of real people I showed up he ran into him in the hall
You know I'm I'm glad to be here talking to you guys about these things I think about all day long and in the Allende
It doesn't
We love you
Of course I love you too
What indoor so close
Holyshit
Something is up
The mood change so drastically
Oh man
I love you guys I just tried to say goodbye brag about
You'd like hey
We never do any preparation for the show and then end with hugging and crying
You would prepared for the show we wouldn't be hugging and crying cuz I supposed
In Subway's you're right it's always I
Yeah it's happening all the time to do.
Kirby weeping drug people everywhere
Everyone knows this
It's only a love of Satan that keeps the rest of us
Diaphragm getting drunk on an air and cry
Oh God
Care for each other or anything like that
Or the way this is happening
It's not
Vulnerability
Think is a little intense here to begin with
By considering you didn't even bring up Larry Nichols
That is fruit
Anyway Greg grease is an optimist
Vixella
But not anymore man
And I never I'm a very optimistic person I think through all of this but the day that President Trump and Melania Trump announces
Today we had covid and they're going into the hospital
I would say that's the day that my optimism ended I don't think
Panama song
And to have them at Walter Reed hospital surrounded by big bottle. Just real complex at Walter Reed
If you were to die
From quote-unquote
Covid
It just seems to me like everything that the enemy has everything wrapped up till
I've never seen the enemy so close to Victory
Through all this until right now
Poor guy lost his optimism
So now we've developed fully from it's probably a false positive test to they
Probably some weaponize covid-19 and now the doctors are trying to kill him with experimental treatment
Walter Reed
Steve doesn't go anywhere good now
If this is what Reese is bringing
Terrified of what pechanec would have said
Deadpool I want to hear it but I want to hear it off a or so no one else can hear
Yeah I want to go Whispers in my ear
Advocated arms overthrow now
Breaking the law
Well Steve wouldn't let Alex cry
So I will put my life on the line for my
Child's future and this country
And we're reaching a point like you're even like
How much longer
Is the man
But you're going to do it
Yeah
Slap yourself
In the face twice
We got to make Melania Queen now
Alex
Get off air
You can let John bowne and gris-gris host
You don't need to be there
You're clearly going through something
Whether it's intoxication or just over
Emotional whatever it's not good this is a bad
No this is bad
War war is coming
So what's going to happen next at the only way we're ever going to get through this I think I think at this point there's going to be War
What ancient civilizations we don't even understand half the stuff that all line up already
Okay alright alright alright
Okay
Are you telling me that I'm going to have
How to Diana
Civil War because some assholes
Atlantis already
Blue waffle
Okay cool
Here's the only way I could ever regain respect for Gregory's for johnbowne but Alex says
4 twice
What about me to say huh and then the other needed to say what is it good for
Absolutely nothing
Good got everything inside Bass
So f****** funny
Can you imagine the f****** it would short-circuit Alex's drug braids
Roar
Anyways let's get back to
Otherwise we're going to have a war right we're going to war
Feel bad just sitting next to Alexandra trying to express like this point I really don't think there's anything that can be done
You know a lot of us don't know what the ancient edited yeah they already blew up Atlantis like okay
Sure
Corporate Wars
Not this one
I would say it's safe to say the most of the wars we grew up with our corporate Wars at work
Started under false premises
This war is
I mean
For lack of a better word perhaps a Christian revolution of some sort
Christian
Call the Jihad until there's one
But we are under attack
Is there going to come for you because your relationship with God
They're going to know the algorithm
You're connected to the big guy
It's it's the war in heaven is about to happen here on Earth
Whoa
Guys this is a news show you know it's fun it's nice when they finally just like
Yeah where I
We're going to go
Is the jahat where Isis where were the Republican party where ISIS come on back
Is there Isis where Isis
It's defensive
Anyway this just deteriorates into what I would describe as a zealot recession
We're on this planet
We have to accept
Responsibility
Absolutely
And right now we are at it's up to all of us it's up to everyone
And this is why I feel so bad for the herd is because they're missing out
One of the most epic opportunities that life ever has to offer which is actually take responsibility scan
And up
Fight evil
Clean the garden
And create a world for our grandchildren they're missing out a normal it's Unlimited
They have an excuse for everything you just said
They have an anti
Argumentative
You know
Baphomet
Could we know all that Gargamel
Only building is betrayal
Well it's it is amazing that we
Whoa
Alex when he's like all they build his betrayal he can't even like
Pause there because Alex can't keep up with the thought I think the John
And Greg are brothers like
Gay Alec
This is going through something
Depth
This is what belief system
Like
The only way we can create a better world for our grandchildren is obviously by slaughtering hundreds of
Dozens of people at no point was he like
Maybe we could do some research into agriculture
Go take away rights anything
Obviously the people who've gone around and slaughtered in order to create a grandchildren in the world
Invented microphones right they were the ones who did it that we're sneaking into 7-Eleven
So Alex go to break and I guess you like splashing water on his face
He comes back a little bit more
Composed
Hours of the transmission
Minute
Harrison Smith
And the old might stop selling it stuff
Yummy and my God
But you lit up
Whoa
I mean I feel like that's my response to a lot of this stuff is just woke
Then God downloads things into my head and I know that I
Got invisible how about no
You go back inside take a nap you go back inside
Get a glass of coffee
Shitfucker
Together man
Hi I just wish it was just
The two of us that would be nice
Be nice my brother is John Brown and Gregory
Let me tell you about how God gives me magic
I'll be sober up more booze
Is whiskey
Do you have
Big noyd Sky another with
Wow just ridiculous
So we already heard earlier that John down and Greg Reese
Discussing and Alex to discussing how they don't do any pretty interviews right sort of a sign of
Virtue
Sure again
Get more into this no preparation means good
It's almost predictable when I went to report
Comes on like just inspired and end
Rapidan quick and get it out of those tend to be over the target
Whereas if I spend a lot of time
You know trying to pick a reports like I said The more egos involved in my report the less effective it is but you can feel the spirit
It's almost too much research
We need this out
We're turning the god
The real thing
Okay Alex
Gobi three old men in a bar that conversation is fine
I understand
Kind of white like there's two things
I would say in response to the work process but they're discussing
What is creativity is really into
The same thing where a lot of times inspiration can strike in a way that
You can feel like you're a conduit of creativity and like
Startimes I'm sure you experience listen to write a good book
Sometimes it's easier
And end I know that macaroni
It's something a lot of people talk about about the experience of the flow you know that kind of thing where
Writing
Can't get anything going and then out of nowhere and then you get a page sure she do that kind of thing
That's one thing that's creativity
Work
And research
Is a little
A little
I do not think
They're what they're describing is like
The flow or anything
I think it's
Oh this is easy
That's the way I would go with that they intuitively and instinctively just gravitate towards things that are not very
Difficult these dumb Boutique
Making conservatives angry stories are really easy yelling about the devil is really
Easy getting into the new on two things
It's not it's very challenging
Here's what I heard
I heard
My workflow is I go through a bunch of headlines
And then when I see one that makes me think
Thank you I'm almost done
That's the one that I work on yes that's what I hear two
And I'm really sick and tired of these people like Alex on his employees
Trying to present
Not trying
And
Putting in no effort
And taking just the easiest path as some kind of indication of like rigor
Virtue or God is working through me
No this is this is
Totally like that
Failed right wing
Field comedians become right-wing commentators because this is the type of conversation that I heard in the back of an open mic from
First and second-year baby comic
It's all the time
Just that like
You know my writing process is
It's all about inspiration you know it hits me and I don't really do too much and all that
70 likes
Hey dudes what are you trying to get a job at
Any other outlet with that anywhere but info
Not a f****** chance tell me oh I love doing stand-up then f****** care about working at it assholes
And I John
Work at Infowars you have for a long time because you're unemployable in any other capacity
Is what you do sucks
Yep anyway Greg says something really stupid here
Skip isn't because it's kind of like
It's fun
And you can feel the psychology the moment Trump won in the hospital
And I would argue that even people on the left
He offered a sense of security
In the past few years
Now you feel it oh wait it's not
Yeah yeah man
No but I feel like when Trump went to the hospital that was the last was really like oh no
Here's the invention for
Did the doctor who killed drop
All right here's the invention that he has to make
It's a little device that attaches to every right-wing commentators
Shoulder right here on the right wing
Exactly
Whenever they say something like I think Trump has made us all feel a sense of security
A little hand comes out
Slaps him in the face
I don't know if it's his groundbreaking is like a telephone is
Honestly it might do more for
Society
Play one last clip and it's
It's Alex
I would say you spent the better part of this hour at just having a Christian Zealot recession with these two dudes
Answer me it's kind of funny that he's promoting the next
Show as being the one where they can really have the time to get into the topic wow
Romeo's dick show
Next 2 hours only six months adds an hour so
Bergen have a lot of time to cover every issue wants on to put the clothes
Long time ago rolynos
But just remember the enemy wants you to feel power
And not realize the power you have
To tell folks about this show right
We are so close to winning so close to losing
That's fascinating but you have the power
Promote my stuff for free
I got to go to bed
Of somebody who knows my audience
Can't Stop
You know
Like it
Too threatening to their sense of self who abandoned me at the point
Play car show Dan
They know
Inside
I'll just
Turn it off
And click on
Subscribe
So we have
To do a good job
I think I just also would feel pretty bad
With or without
In audience
Remember when we didn't have an audience
Wow
You could do
Just be like
Drunk
Friends about Jesus tomorrow shows going to be great
I had to show that these two dudes that I've been crying with her about the host
Is going to be great and they're going to let you know what it's going to be just like this but replace me with
My intern Harris
Smith
Isn't that
Excited
Is not exciting
Can chest guy
You just turn it off
Now
It would be nice if they did. Video it seems like a lot of folks
At the weather
I think a lot of people were like come on man
Poisoning m f****** Walter Reed doctors
I don't know how those comments are Vinny like generalized Shillings
I'm sure if I don't I don't track the comments on there
Generally
How different that is from normal trolls f****** around
I did enjoy seeing it people saying grow up
Warms your heart when somebody finally
Appropriate response
Interesting Lee
I mean we come to the end of this this weekend coverage into
Slam dunk
Yeah that's what I was going to call that a slam dunk of the weekend
It doesn't
Feel like
Alex
Is
Thanks
Trump realize the president might die in the next few days
Of the United States clearly is aware of that he said that
He says it is as much
He's not acting as if that's the case and that's kind of weird to me and I don't know what the deal is
Spell the way he
He said he would act if it were the case
To start a f****** war that is true it seems like right now they're all trying to like
Psych themselves up because they know that they have no interest
Did a war
If my Sunday Alex's drunkenly talking about he's sure that they hit Trump with something in the trying to kill her
Women Hospital
Like what are you doing about it
If you believe that's in any way true
How are you still on the radio talking with your two friends or I'd see you some headlines
Single like Alex it said that he's going to go fly to dc2
Help Trump or whatever
I didn't hear that on his show he must put out like some kind of the other video
Where you said that on Friday but then you changed
His mind it was like a that's why I was like like at the at the airport
Alex might be going to BC maybe not also Marathon money bomb on Wednesday Lottery stuff
Coming up now but hate this
I'm glad that I found something else this little side project
Like really helping
Keep me
Really interested and my attention away for like how much I think
This is all spiraling down the drain
Yeah but I will be
Deep coverage that money Bob that's for sure
But before we get out of here today Jordan let's take some voicemail
The people
Hey pack
Cuz you otherwise
Is on rifle
And a couple weeks ago
Which I think is a shame because they offer up
Problem
Like this section of
Roar
Alexis
Pretty wild
Weird boys
Icycle
Powerful oryx
Focal point
For the energies of
Consciously generated
By their green tea
Energy that binds them together with a
Common purpose
Unfortunately
Your voice
Light slash around it
Sparks fly from his eyes
And Rob powersearch
Dribble from his
Unless it weird voice find somewhere that elusive
Head will explode
Reborns
The other boys
Towanda
About an hour
Max wearing warning Bells
Inevitably
Disturbed
Other than that
I really love the show love you and Dad
Take it easy
Do you think every leader of a proud boy cell is called a weird boy
Yeah but I would say I'm a notice at the Grand wizard of the KKK.
Honorific title
Feel like I feel like I actually do know this
Yeah
No I don't I just I'm thinking of like various people who were probably like Rufio panman
Truthettes based Stickman
One of them
If any one of them has stolen Raptor princess
We literally personally have to go fight the power
Probably
Next article
Jordan
Okay
Nonprofit
Taylor from Kansas City
What superpower would you abused
That's it that's the call.
Asked I think I'm a terrible Australian
I will give him that no it wasn't terrible at all
The city hall of the best ice cream shop in America Betty Ray's check it out if you're online and I into it all
Very nice
Are you
Why don't you let me Lexi
Superpower would you what is abused mean
Like I understand it like peeping on people with x-ray vision is definitely abusing our I wouldn't do that
What is it like
If I could have like you power to grow plants sure
I would have use that power for how would I abused it
People up with plans cuz I wouldn't do that here's my question
Do you like
Cuz I think it's kind of what we're going to talk about
I don't want to abuse people with
With the power that's the issue how do you abused
The power right now here's my
Siri on how you abused just the power
We have to get to
Be wasteful with it exactly
I can
Create
Anyting
I can turn anything into diamonds or gold
And I just never do
Like I can
Any any any financial problems
I just never do
I abused that power responsibly by not using that power
I would be like I just refuse to make food for anybody
That would be an abuse of your power I wouldn't do that
I wouldn't be with a power I guess
Yeah I mean I guess if I could like
Let's be honest
If I could like communicate with ATMs with my mind and like take out money sure
I might do that
That's not an abusive urpower that's the only responsible way to use it
That money's not even real Deb
Yeah that's where the debate comes in what does it mean to abuse your power
I don't know
Use flying
Just do it too much
Is it you're stealing it from the birds ceiling are from the birds
Hi
Happy birthday
Intrinsically abusing the superpower means that you're doing it in the villainess way
To another person like you're using your
Brain powers
To force people to do things
I wouldn't want it I wouldn't want to mess with any of that stuff
I don't know I
If you
Well it's like it's like going to a gun range like you're using me if your superpower is your gun and you go to the gun
Ranger using your superpower responsive
You're not abusing that power your your shooting
You know it is safe space
I thought of one maybe sure like okay so if I could breathe underwater ok
Go and live in the water
Using the power cuz I be isolated myself from all the humankind living with fish
I mean if you weren't susceptible to cold you live in Antarctica that's
That's a really abusing your power
I mean it would just be using the power to facilitate me live in the middle of nowhere
Activist by moving into the middle of nowhere it's not abusing anybody that's just me
Light under the wood
I don't know why that's an interesting philosophical question about how one would abuser power
Bring us to answer that's why
No
I don't have a good answer I guess me neither
This was a message
Search for Dan and Jordan my name is
Celia
I just wanted to
Show
Insight
Humor that you guys
I heard about you
You
My son
I guess that's too generous
But you captured
But I also
Podcast
So
Canada
Shane Anthony
Thank you for doing your work
I know
Shout out to our parent walk
Thank you very much weird is that that's very weird
Unexpected the idea that someone would
I never thought anyone would like the show to begin with the idea that someone would like it and then their parent would be able to enjoy it with them
We heard that from a couple folks
Set over the course of doing the show
Way more than expected them and like it's just really neat that there is some sort of a generational appeal
There are parents out there who don't mind my potty mouth
I understand on a certain level because
You know I can go watch a movie with my dad
And the two of us will both appreciate this
Peace of culture in a similar way and we'll be like
But not anything where it's like
I'm talking about politics and s*** like I was just that intergenerational sharing of
It's very Fastenal podcast is not a p
Peace of culture exactly
That movie that your dad could go watch
Watch together it's really cool
Seitan
Bismarck
Scotland
Hopefully you can
Understand
I love the podcast
You guys
I was calling about
Donks.
Where you were discussed
Donald Trump
I believe
I know
10 years
Donald Trump
Rebuilding a golf course
My home
Exactly
Same time
Wind farm
Donald Trump
I don't like this
You need to stop this
Otherwise he's
Chinese turbine
Asteroid
You're cuter than
Master evidence
He said
So he wants me
He didn't get his way at home
Yes court
Excited
Sebastian
How to build the world
Water store
Hilarious
Cheating wife
Knoxville
Shout out Scotland yes very much
Got to
Does a great access
At my buddy his dad
Had a real thick
Scottish accent
And one of the things that I always
Spell cherish
Very fond memory
I could go over to his house every now and again
And vinegar in college and his dad would be like
Insisted me and another friend of ours
Drink Scotch
With him he's obsessed with Scotch whiskey like Jim Beam
I got to try this stuff stuff
Just just the way the words roll out and a very very beautiful
Sorry to be you call it
Nostalgic
Snow
Lost and memory
Objectifying
I'm sorry to be objectifying
Set voice but I appreciate it
But also
Theory about Trump and wind farms
Lahore
I think it I think there's something to it I like it now
Halal Guys
Alexia jonahville
You'll thank me by full name
Why you do this
I think I am joke
Now I'm probably this
Superior because
It's okay
Anyways
Long-term Russia
Sporting Life
Alex Jones
Bye-bye for now
Although
Waka
Jessica
Good alright
Well photo
I'll give it
I don't
Would be
Not surprised if that person wasn't
From Russia
Site we should say that the person
Scotland is not a fake
Scotland
Maybe that maybe that person is actually Russian
I don't know I'm overwhelmed
Anyway we had to get out of here Jordan play I will get back but until then we have a website
I'll try that, yes we're also on Twitter and find us on Facebook
Indeed
But if you could play
Please find a local charity or baleful
Find interior to help out
Until then Emilio Emilio
Dzx Clark
I'm weak
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color