Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
Hey buddy welcome back to knowledge
You like to sit around
To my great Chagrin today you have purchase
Distance
Renovate
We will be drinking
Delicious cotton
Candy Faygo Brazen that it bothers to say
Nothing but carbonated water
And high fruit
We family up in here man
Water with sugar in it
Are flavored like cotton candy which is just
Sugar
That is
Candy that's great
Where I
You do not
Call
Eerily like cotton candy
Beverages in the past
What is it like
They have weird flavors but they mail it
Perfect
It's
It's Eerie to drink
You don't want you don't want to liquid where you expect solid
It is truly horrifying
Animal sound
Human sound
Should come
Human sounds
Anyway
What is not a Lovecraft podcast
Although I mention him a bit
But that's just because we
We're starting to live in Eldridge
Terror
The world
It does seem like the other ones will be arising from the depths any moment
That would make more sense than anything he's doing
What's his face from Men In Black
The guy wearing the red and black
He's wearing another per
I take my restaurants was better
So
We are podcast about Alex Jones and we're going to get
Give a shout out to
Thank you for donating and welcome to the team he wants Leslie
Knowledge
Of those who are interested in Polish
For the price of just one cup of coffee a day
You can give us one cup
One cup of coffee
And you guys all team up you can help me out a great deal I'm losing my mind
Anyway
Of the investigation that I've been doing
What the f*** happened to Alex Jones
Also honored
This is the prologue to the disasters
Because people have asked on Twitter you just asked me right before the show I want to get everyone up to
Speed with what's going on in current-day cuz we're not going to
There was no show on Monday again because of Memorial Day
Rodger Stone talked about I am a real American
Hulk Hogan's theme song amazing Wednesday Mike cernovich
Jones announced
Set. It's on Wednesday
Thursday
They don't talk about that
Alex's but he's moved on
And now he's super into how cool it is
That Trump left
The Paris agreement
Great because
Did Alex Jones is
Conception in his framework
The planet
Is carbon starved
There's not a carbon dioxide issue
No pirate Cole
That's the one we're not going over and Rainbows are made of Starlight
Oh okay then
He's made of Starlight and Rainbow
We're not going to do an episode on the whole episode is Alex losing his mind
You still in his mannequin
And so he's talking about how July
First 2017
Will be the most important day in history
And here's why
Because we believe
Did the weight of the globalist
Upon themselves
Is through this carbon
That's been imposed
Climate change isn't real it's all a charade
To create a carpenter
Goes to Al Gore
I don't I don't
I don't get 28
Lovett the he's celebrating losing his shoe
He's going on and on about like weird biblical stuff
So strange
She's talked about God's eye
Which may or may not be a reference to Fast & Furious 6
Or Lord of the Rings
Could be that too
Or I think one of the assassins
Oh yeah so
Pizza
We discussed it a little bit on the last episode
It's tough to talk about it without making fun of
What is
Sort of overt mental illness
On the same token
The climate-change stuff is Giselle Looney
That I don't want us to make it
What is the score
Listening to it already freaking out when you just said
We're carbon. I'm protecting my neighbors from your screams
So the other thing I want to talk about
With the along the same lines as be we shouldn't mock Alex Jones
In the middle of
Episode
Hey came out on the internet last week
The Paul Joseph Watson
Eats books
I want
To make it very clear that I hate him
His his beliefs
But I resent everybody make
Fond of him
You know
And I really don't like to
To see people
When
So f****** open to attack with so many other things
All of these people making fun of him because
He came out admitted that he eats paper
I don't think that's okay
Monster filled with
Transphobic
Homophobic
Sucking it
Hate
I hate
Philmont
Absolutely Visser rated everything
Single day ever
Yeah forever
Like
Greek myth
He pulled from him every morning he should
Did he land it
Should happen again
The very next
Brought up the torch of light
It's the same thing with
All the paper
He is a bit of an agoraphobic and Raley's it apart
Right again that's a thing that I don't feel any interest
In making fun of and I emphasize I feel really
I feel bad for him
So when I see people making
It bums me out cuz he suck
But not for these reasons it is unfair
And it gives him an opportunity to reattach back and be like
Oh isn't this the tolerant left making
Fun of my mental illness
Trap
I'm not saying that he's faking it as a trap
But it is
Attract you can fall in
Of course
Really bums me out when people don't take the right Tech plan
On the exact toll
I just stick to the reality
Don't insult them
4 things
Bitter humor
Don't
Make fun of him for being afraid to leave
Make him afraid to leave Jim Morrison
Attacking the moment he walks outside
Ravens
Their own families too high
We need an army of birds
I think that's where my
Because
You know they're the only ones who are going to survive once they
Not as the owls have
We're going to start our investigation today's episode
To July 13th
We're going to be going over there
But to give you guys a little bit of a last time
I'm on vacation
Donald Trump for a long time
Spent a lot of time misrepresenting the Civil War
You're up to speed
123rf
This is a very good question has brought everybody
2 seconds
Because you can go on July 5th
Very strongly indicated that he
He is fully aware of Trump's mob connections
So we go from
Dismissal and not within a couple days
Is a trumpet announce
Alex Jones is saying this guy is
Sprint and I only 25%
Trust him he agrees with the distrust of immigrants
Fred agrees that rhetoric but he knows the Trump isn't
Going to follow through on it
Also at the end of our life
Also at the end of our last episode
We revealed the Paul Joseph Watson
Also
Thanks the trumpet
He's just in a
A publicity
Threat
Joysticks
The fuckedupshit
Phone call
Is the weird headspace
And I don't
Mikey really wants to do is show
It takes a lot of phone calls
And they're all pretty boring
Write but in the time
It's a lot of race
You talked a lot about
Guilt only a month
From the
Charleston
Torso is the first clip where we start
Explaining
Best Kilt
I want explain something
I really don't care what color you are
Where you came from if you support
You support
Plainfield
You're not a wannabe social engineer
Trying to guilt me into film
I care about you and I want you to succeed
There's two issues
This is Donald Trump situation
Donald Trump
Most of what he says makes a lot of sense
You're really smart.
She won't deliver on what
Experience
That's just what my gut tells me
Jerome corsi
Bureau chief
Infowars
Who is no Donald Trump for 40 years
In 2015
The Donald Trump is an establishment
And he is just there for
Oh yeah
But this is
Now he's saying one of his sources
Well
I mean
We all know that
We all knew that
That's what he was
Waiting for Alex to say that he
You can throw like the next show is like
Also I can throw an elephant as far as
Human being
That's his way out if he's actually so strong he can throw an elephant a billion
I will not be made a liar
Gonna Fly now is playing in the background we get a nice little rocky montage
I mean
Isaac that you're under playing
Revelation is also on the same page
Cuz dr. corsi is now a major player in Alex's
Propaganda
He's a major player in
Pushing Trump
The thing that is
The thing that mitigates that
Me is that
Everyone
Was
Like no we don't want Trump we don't want Trump we don't want Trump until it became apparent that
They had to
His friends
We're saying does he have friends
Come on
Supreme a Leverage
Applejack
A good point exclusively at Trump's places
If possible
We have this reiteration of I agree with
Brace s*** that he's saying
Fifth
The stuff cuz beat the Trump situation that he's referring to is
Still
Just the comments
About
That's still what's going on
That's the only contact
Covers Trump in
Pretty much
I think throughout the entirety of this episode
The Trump situation
It's all just there
Which at this point
In history on July 6th
Is old
Huey
He's not he's not wrestling with up-to-date s***
His is preamble
And then here's his list of things that are pro-human are
Self-defense
Don't Make Me Feel
That's the wrong priority for Amy
Human being ever
No cuz that's the Bedrock
Human dignity
Care about others
Boo
Respect
Respect for yourself and for others
Let's do understand know to get white people to feel bad
Vulcanize
Oh okay come to realize something that I think
Empathy is a globalist platinum like
Yeah that makes sense
Yeah let's go along with that
The Alex believe
And I'm not sure about that
To think that he believes
The DIA
Dia of
People
Complaining about legitimate racial issue
He interprets that as a
Plot to split white people as one cohesive group
As a voting Bloc
Into
Split group and some of the people will go along with the broken
Clinton put together
And other ones will become white supremacist
It's not how do you how do you
Look I'm just I don't like it when they
Split white people
Voting Bloc
Right we should all be United
I don't care what color you are so long as all white people are on the same team
I want to be clear he hasn't said as much
But I'm starting to glean some of that
From
His interviews that he's had with like Larry Nichols
And just some of the other things
My Isaac
Part of it
It's part of so many old white.
It's not like it's not like it's a thing they actively
I think about it just there there tribalism in the back of their head is like
Well you look like me so you must agree with me
Which are of course private property self-defense
I don't feel guilt
Especially about comes from
Old white people self defense
Interesting
Prior to the private property that you have because of the system that is
Place
Literally on racism
The self-defense
You need because of
All three Pence most important things
Are white supremacist
Somewhat anyways
Apologist idea
Is basically acceptable
You got to ask yourself what is that agenda really all about
We all agree that
Any crime done by black
We just ignore blacks
No
That's crazy
We just ignore it
At the end
What's the agenda there
And I think it's fascinating because
Do you talk about yourself
Don't like that
You know I'm saying
It's
Explain
What's my plan on this
Explained by
Considering what sources Alec
Steaks in
Next clip
I'll explain
What is news diet is like Bono and I don't want to know
Depressed this morning
Articles
What
Reading the comments on your own articles
4 tips
San Francisco
Out of jail
People then it spread
In the comments
Grammar
Basically not just
Donald Trump
It was
One of the things that I think is interesting is one I have developed
Two theories
In my investigation
Fart
One of them is reasonable
And the other one will get you later
The reasonable theory is I think
Alex Jones
At some point around
Here
July 6th
7th
He starts to get really jealous
Is Donald Trump
Is getting a lot of press
Same thing
Things that are very similar
Okay
Alex Jones starts
To get
Petty
Angelus
Why the run lumping me in with him
Why am I not getting all the attention
And then on top of that
I think he starts
Emphasize
A little bit
Because of the way the media treats
I think if there is a
There is an identification Factor
Alex starts to feel with
Okay that's
The most reasonable Theory I have
About what gets him
To sort of
Shift over
I have an insane Theory that's an emotional human beings
Like I can understand that
Bandits
Because you and I can understand
Because
Trump
Kill the globalists
Back left the head on Alex Jones
The doorstep.
The psychology of both individuals
Because he's an artist
I'm at Alex's
Any feels like
I'm gentleman
I see what's happening with him if I identify myself with him
Maybe I will get the
He's saying exactly what I've been saying
For forever
Be more popular
Here's what I'll do I'll drift
And there are a couple instant
Two of clipsville play where Alex says things that eventually Trump
There's also a possibility
I don't know but there is also a possibility that Alex
Just lives his life and spouts the hate that he spouts
Emin at some point started
To see Trump Joc hairstyle
And be like all right
He likes me
Disappeared
I don't know that make sense
Like I said I'm just sick
July 6th episode
More less yet
New strfkr
But he chooses
Weird Stars
Anyway this Mexico
I told you July 6th is a weird day that I weird
And they finally sort of blows
Episode
It's almost like claustrophobia
I just want to hide from everybody
Car wash videos
Stupid white people is dumb as a so-called minorities are
Everywhere
Juxtaposition there is amazing
Play music screaming about Pacey dumb white people
If it was from
If it was from Beverly Hills Cop
Eddie Murphy said that
I believe every word
Like it's not Mark Dice shooting these
Exploitative
Erroneous videos where it goes I'll talk to dumb people on the street
We don't know what the 4th of July
All this stuff
Reaching out
Music
And then here is how he comes back from
Because I've been holding my anger in the last few
He wakes and during the break I had a controlled rage just walking around
Back in the storage area of the facility
For a half hour
Because my rivocean
AR
I just wonder what is wrong with this conversion of
I don't know
That's a really good question
Don't know why we put up with a second
Pretty shorts
Episodes we've covered he's had to leave the studio and headache
Controlled rage
Yeah I want I want to see what his
He's a freaking he's at
Kizi
Either
He's not mentally well
He's not in a
Emotional
Spiritual
Self-control kind of situation
Where he should be doing this
Right with my mind a little bit and I'm losing it a tiny bit covering him
I have developed
White agoraphobia I don't leave the house as much as I used to
But I've never gotten so mad listening to him that I've gone into a controlled rage
I think it's code for a raise
I think it's time to put a PR spin on
Call Matt
I threw s*** in my office for a good half-hour and I know I have a cleaning lady
Yeah
So
4 man you should not you should not be doing this
You should not
You shouldn't shouldn't be in the news
It is
Like
Like how do you look at somebody
Who is soak
Clearly unhealthy
Of his life
There's no good there's no
Good thing that we've seen
Other than
Once a year he smokes
The only bright spot the only healthy see the old me healthy
Anything I can Cialis
Make sure that
7 gone too far with that
Respond to in him
Is
Specifically the
You s*** that he always talks about
Is 80
Percent White
What are you can also if you're a
Disenfranchised
White dude
You can absolutely sublimate some of your anger through hit
Yeah what are the ways you can get it out as you allow this man to speak for you
Nana you feel
You know you get that dopamine reaction
Terrible anger based on feeling like
And you listened to his show
He screams about it
It's somehow you can vicariously feel those feelings
Maybe they come out maybe maybe it is a release
I hope
Cuz I think I think
It's reinforcing
You have to imagine some of these people work in the office they go to the office and rather than take out all this weird
Angry conservative White
On their co-worker
They just sit there listen
Gorillaz
4 hours
I'm really scared that my co-workers has being that I'm watching
Infowars at work
I'm really worried that they think I like
I don't know no one's brought it up but I'm so scared people think I'm in into a warrior
Huge beard
I could be one of those crazy
Clip from July 6th
Blimpie on
Here is an interview with this dude
Friends
That's not a job
Heeee does predictions
Is to come okay
He has a lot of similar Tendencies Alex to predict the collapse is coming
A bunch
Buy gold
But
What I think is more important interview is this place that I'm at
Gerald Celente really reinforcing
The Savior narratives that Larry Nichols
Who's laid out for Alex
Impasse episode
You said you were depressed because of the masses
That are so out of touch
So I had this little
That really says it all
But rather an Irate tireless minority
Keen on setting brush fires
In the minds of men
It does not take a majority to prevail
But rather an irate
Tireless minority
Keen on setting brushfires of freedom
In the minds of men
And that's what you are doing that's what I'm doing at the doctor Paul Craig Roberts
There are number of us that are doing it
It's bringing it all together to make it happen
Yeah if you just do some like warmed-over hacky comedy
The brush fire of Heaven
Going to brush fire
He's like
He's throwing it just takes an Irate minority
The same thing as what Larry Nichols keep saying
Alex
You are savior
He even goes so far Like Larry Nichols I don't think I had pulled the clip but he does say
You are the last hope
For the Bastion of proof
Jesus
In his life we were just
Completely reinforcing this
It's up to you now I want to rewrite
A New Hope
Yeah I have Obi-Wan just be this
Deranged
Ill-proportioned angry
Yeah
Lightsabers
I do sort of believe I'm fighting
Exotic battle
Against the windmill that is at
I think it's important I don't think
This is Jeff
Fun entertainment
I think there is something important we're doing
But I don't have
The music
Audiobook
Sixth grade
Love some savant
I don't have a Larry Nichols
I have you and no I am not going to tell you you are sick
Coolant
I was audited
Alex
Stop
Dheere dheere vocal patterns are too appealing you need to find a way to speak clearly
For July 6th
Hellboy
Create a new
I don't want to do that
So we go to
July 7th
This episode is
Weird
That episodes are weird
That's because they
Yeah so is the ones that you don't think are weird art
Terrifyingly weird weird
I can't process my emotions while listen
This is weird
Let's go to where we are
I'm so in this episode
Refuse
Refuse to believe in climate change
Since I don't have any of him
He claims I actually was on the show just the other day
To talk about how
That climate change is based on
And he's going to release a paper
About it how that go
Doesn't give any details errors
Okay were made
Does not explain any of
Any any
Talk about maybe it was in
In the measuring system
Now no specific
Like a calculator
You know like
To the exhaust
Climate
You know like how quick are the ice cap
Maybe they just got the
Like maybe
Simple things
Tell me the Lord Moncton or whatever the f*** is name is
A mathematical issue that we can
Even given EB
Details
Never f****** mind
The thrill climate-change still real Alex
Can 2015 table discussion about how the EU was a fascist organization
I didn't keep any of that stuff
In this clip towards the beginning of the episode
Some stuff that I believe Trump
Picked up on later
Stuff about how
Obama is the founder of Isis
They sort of believe
Are things
Mirrored from Alex
Do you know what I'd like
Maybe our big problem is that we just don't Define words
The same way like
What do you think
Their definition of fascism is like the actual word like
Beginning of knowledge comes
From the definition
The term sleep beginning a conversation
You can't believe how can you communicate with somebody who disagrees with you
Without first a green on
Pasticho
Interesting point
I don't know
I don't think Alex would it be up for having
The conversation about Justified
Queen
Like if you ever
Unverifiable
Like you can't disprove a lot of the things you said if you were to give definitions
The terms it would be like
Oh no that's absolutely not true
Crustaceans
Conserve
Before in the password
Okay
Where we're going to stop
This is what we are talking about here
The one subject
About that you
You can change your mind Bass
It's on so you say you know you have no evidence or what your
Okay fine
I will present evidence
If it
Disagrees with you
Then you have to
To change your mom
If you do the same for me then I will change my my
So long as
The moment I do that you don't say
Well yeah but what about now
Gopokes moving a chair
He did create
Through
Accidental foreign policy
Might the roots of it might go back even
And further than that if you really
Think about
Ronald Reagan created
Let's throw that out let's just go back
Alex has egg
Obama talking about how
We will not be able to
Terrorist
Through bombs
Open
We need a better ideology
We need to get at the root
Of what causes
People to
Join these groups
That's called strategy
That's very reasonable Alex interprets
Bedrock of this
Let's go ahead
Let's do it let's go to this clip of Obama
How to wear a sweater over
Us30 a trifold
Accidentally got Special Forces
Other areas like
That means that we're going to have to
It's also true why
Also require up there
Oh yeah sure
Mo3 leaders agree
Audiologist
Are not defeated by better idea
More attractive and more compelling one
Amarillo
Yeah I don't understand
He talks about how Americana is so sexy
He thinks that if we create prosperity in this Americana system of free market and what-have-you it'll be such a
The first place
He believes exactly what Obama
Word for word but he think
But because it's a
Obama is saying we shouldn't
The pack them
It's not what you saying
Just bombs
Oh there's going to be bop track auto box
Latta bobsled
What do you think of it like you were yelling over he says
Let me translate that for you
These are our proxy armies that are going to go kill Christians
That's not what I was saying at all
There wasn't even a word that you could twist that into
That was just him deliberately
Not
Deliberately things
Straight up Bowl
Otherwise
Just say
Because Obama
That's just not possible
Which
Democratic president says something that Republicans
If they can't agree with that then they just
Something else
Typical post
Remove the conversation
So it was next clip I believe on July 7th
A this is some evidence
Alex
Size of truck
More than just agree
His rhetoric
This clip shows
Some kernels
I see myself in
Engineers
If you want to come here
After you arrive you will get your extended stay
I don't want
How much really got me
The Donald
Abdominal
He's here where
Wherewithal
Personal shopper
The point is
Minority
Of the people
If you can't
This is chump
Mexico or Guatemala
Columbia
Brazil
Or chili let's just go south and show up at
Food stamp program
Text
Donald Trump Signature Collection
Made in Mexico
I'm all for
Helpful
Is going after Trump
What is an article
Donald Trump
He's created a straw man of the Ark
You meant that Trump made is that Mexicans are lazy
The easiest stereotype that Alex
Can grab onto
That's not what people responding to at all
So he responds to this fake argument
Invicta look for himself
He's starting to see the way that the media treat
Donald Trump
Mirrors the way the media treats out
And I think
That he's internalized
What's fascinating to me there is
Egos
And then earlier in that very same clip
Maybe we should
You
Alex
You did that
People talked about him being a hypocrite for having his clothes made in foreign countries is it is hoe
When was America first
Yeah so that's the reason the people clowning on in 4th
Cuz it's
Hypocritical
It's ridiculous the argument that he got a good deal
Doing
Isn't a good
That doesn't work
No you got to go
Cuz if you care about America at all
Coffee farmers
What's the best coffee for my palate I don't know
IGo Ethiopian yirgacheffe
IGo Folgers
Sure hates like balls
America first
Boulder coffee
I'm just
That's pretty
Cuz I
Deceive
Treatment
I don't get them on board
Obvious
But
There's trends
Gerald Celente
Starting to Bubble up once he starts defending Trump
It's a pretty short walk
Right once you start once you start defending a guy
He's going to be coming
Still just defending the words
You still attacking the man
He's still saying that I don't trust him
Even if he is defending
But I think there's
Conscious forces that are going on inside out
Like love
I told you the July 7th episode
Here's why
Presented
Without comment
Official channels unofficial channels
What's a false flag
Yes you did
Criticized
Isn't the official story doesn't add up
And that when police officers and school investigation experts
And school safety experts and others
They were
No emergency helicopters
DHHS an hour and a half later with a timestamp
But like a big PR stunt
Bloomberg
Before
A major operation coming up
Emails from school
A year before
We have demolished in
Yep we have videos
This is something that that that
So here's a couple important things
To break down here all the things that he brought up have been explained
Frat if you look in
The person that he's talking about the school investigator who's been threatened
Is a guy named Wolfgang halbig
Everybody's name alone is enough
To threaten him if you look into him
He is
Crazy amounts of money
Investigating
Be the guy who is offered
Bounty
4 proof
That various things
People have provided
I even like not real
He's like I'll give you $1,000 if you can give me a picture of x y and z
People show up giving pictures
Nope not good enough
Nope don't have metadata on the image
He's been harassing the family members of the children who died
It's
Disgraceful
He makes the argument that the kids
Who are the Super Bowl
Who got the thing
Jennifer Hudson
Fuse to even
Forensic specialist
No right
Know who cares I refuse
Oh I know where we're going to hide these kids
Next to Jennifer Hudson at
The Super Bowl flusher Magic
Lesser Magic
The story that Alex Jones
Keeps pushing whenever he brings up Sandy Hook is that Michael Bloomberg
Because he wants to take
The night before told everybody
Time to
Leading a posse in the old west I've looked at I looked into this I've tried to find evidence
Evidence on any reputable source
I can't find any article even about this on Infowars
Make that s*** I found one article on Infowars about Mike Bloomberg and how he wants to take your gun
Links to another article
About
After the Aurora shooting
The Batman shoe
Michael Bloomberg
Made a very serious effort
In order to push gun control
Because he was shot
Yet another senseless
Shooting
And if you look at my Bloomberg
History one of the big things that he folks
Chris is on to be a real big issue for him is unavoidable.
Do it
We would like to clown about how he tried to Outlaw big sodas
Little Giant sodas in New York
But the reason is
Sugar kills a lot of people that don't need to die
Right
Begun
The gun stuff matches up very
Close with a lot of his philosophy
Please about
Desperate don't need to happen don't need to happen the Aurora shooting
He did try and put together some
Some organization
Some allies
To work on
Control
And that's the only evidence
They offer at all
Three or four months
Before Sandy Hook
And so whenever Sandy Hook did end up happening
Of course you was
Prepared
He didn't talk to people the night before with
Foreknowledge
The most also need to set one up you can just wait there's going to be another Mass shoot
Why would you ever why would you ever need
Two false flag of mass shooting
Bloomberg started making moves after the Aurora one knowing that eventually
Something's going to happen we should be
Be prepared to
Help
Alex laying out that evidence
Is it sounds like if o.j. defended himself in his trial just like
Yeah I know this is true
This is bulshit so this isn't
We're going to get into wise
But I want
Take note of one thing
From that clip that is very important
He's talking to Rob do
Resurface
He's gotten back from his detox
To get all that
Supermale out of them
At the end of that clip
He says
You have a degree in
In theater
Updo with maternal
He's a degree in theater
Does he have an MFA
I don't know I
Trained
In journalism
Music Theatre
And he is
Terrible actor
He should have
Focuses
In terms of Sandy Hook
But
The real story here
Nice to discover that Rob is actually in a
Playwright
Like he's just so good this is tour cover research or
She is an amazing vibrant super interesting guy who's
Playing boring
That could be a terrible actor or maybe
He's the best
Possible you know what he has family member
That's something
Important Daniel do Luis febles
We're going to get into robbed right now
But now
Your Uncle John
What's the successful security company
I heard you talking about it yesterday
That's why I'm trying to get mine
More
Because he's been
So Rob dues uncle is investigating Sandy Hook
Stealing
Okay
Alright
I called bulshit
But he was there he was
It will get to the actual interview
Iraq
Okay and then they have Tim do
Sleepy do angry
Morning dew
Mountain Dew
Going on
There their they're
Taking something very small
And spreading it out
To be something major
As big as it could
And the reality of what they could
Cuz it's nothing
10 different types
My uncle was in Connecticut
That's the news
Let's just get through some of these clips
Because it's nonsense
A Connecticut Yankee
Europe travel
Without getting into the personalities involved
I love that
A Manhattan
Project
The gun grabbers
But so based on what he's saying is
I can't believe there's this evil you have to have so many people involved
That's the reason why
Very unreasonable
Right there in that cliff
Alex
In present
Claims
He never said all that we have them we have V1 clip we
Routinely play
What do you say
No one died it was all actors
On the June 7th 2015
I want to see Robert Redford
Star in the
I think that would be good
Louis
So if we get to the actual interview with
Yeah probably
No I think it's
Spaghetti Western
There was a secret
Nope
If we get to the actual interview with John 2 and crack reporter
Anymore
I mean ladies and gentlemen
With your uncle this is John
News directors to Uncle
But you was the one
Is the guy who sounds like he's from Jersey
How do you take a man like that
Most reputable news organization
Don't send somebody don't send a man on the street interview out there with like
Hey what do you feel about Obama doing this stuff huh
You think this is a cover-up
Yeah
Yeah I know even the local Chicago news
Oh absolutely
McAlister's
10-second
Clip where all he says is
This is weird
Never seen anything like this
Which could mean I've never seen anything this horrifying I've never seen something this tragic
Could mean any number of things
And they're just extrapolating it because
There's private conversations that Rob do is had with his uncle
Don't spell out anything
Alex
To get robbed too to give a quote
About the private conversation good idea if you're a b******* artist
I do not ask
Direct Quest
Like in the Press pool
At the White House whenever they're asking Sean Spicer those
In name
Pointless Quest
If you just got
Like if you just got a direct
From somebody
Venue
But if you're like vedanti
You can just ask
Could be and that's
That means that you can say whatever you want
Like I said Alex is pushing
For some inside information about the conversation that robbed who had with his uncle
Comedy in this clip
For Alex
Sort of tri-tip
Explain what
Raptors job
A little bit
This is really funny
Denny's been in court cases
This is your uncle
Go back to the
Remember
Good cuz I was in the car driving while talking to your PC
Because I wanted to get something out of before we did that cuz we did the show that night on the 4th that day on the 4th
I want to talk about today I've got the short interview with you
Estranged
People don't know anyting Alex's sick of the bulshit
Hung up with a quote
How do you say I don't really remember what exactly
F****** credible you're the news director to say whatever
It's look like
Tell me the truth and more like
Look up something good a****** that what do you think I paid you have credibility or the news director make up something
Just lying
In a good way
A tall Rob Dulce is
Stop that comes from that 10-second video
Even the stuff that you said that he said in a private conversation is just the same stuff that's in that damn but
There's nothing here he said he's never seen anything like this in the car Pursuit
No Alex Jones court cases before
All of them everyone know that he's never seen anything like that
So Alex
At this point is sick of the b*******
Sort of giving Rob do some s***
This is this is also pretty funny
Connecticut
New York
New Jersey
Come on it's not a secret agent thing
Yeah it's just like your uncle lives you dumbass
Jesus
Brighton New York
I love that but that also the other important thing there is just freezing
Cuz he's like the people who did Sandy Hook know where you
Your uncle live
You know what you believe
There's no way around it
I mean we have now two episodes
Where are you
Straight up
Do exactly
We've at least touched on it on
Three other
Everyone thinks
But he said Jade Helm was real
And I don't care to go back and dig through
All the episodes and find out where he actually said
100%
Going back whenever you whenever I didn't say this we like Oh and it was this it's in the mainstream
Stream news everybody knows
It's not true if he says
So we're done with
I know we moved to July 8th
Right and one of the important things that I don't have
Audio of
I just because it's long and boring
Is in this episode Alex
Express
I'm pretty strong
Support for Nigel farage
And the UK
Not good
Now part of the FBI
Investigation
Is almost certain
Rodger Stones back channel to Julian
You think so I would say almost
Nigel farage has been seen going to the
And
He was questioned when he came out of the embassy what were you doing
I don't remember
Ecuadorian Embassy
I forgot what it was
We can assume
It's not good Julian Assange
Batman
Oh yeah there we go
Too many black references on the same episode guys you're all getting policy wonk material for free
Can we make a hat-trick
So he presses
Right
Nike Huaraches
Just
4 time failed politician whack-job anti-immigration
Anti-eu kind of guy
Which makes up white
But it makes sense why Alex would be on
There are similarities
Between the two of their worldview
It's important that we bring that up because it does feed into my crazy theory that I'll be getting to at the end
Yes this is one of the important building block
The grand unified field theory of right way
Wing propaganda
How our last episode super into Jeff session
Even before he was part of
Trump campaign
Free brexit
Free
Trump involvement with Nigel farage
In
With
He's been on the show before
I don't have I don't have episode
I haven't heard any episode with Rodger.
It's like we're doing the Marvel Universe
Like we're doing the the films that they used to set up
Let's call Nigel farage
Let's do that
He's from a different country he's a fish out of water
Squad backstory
Then also
Very
Result
Nigel farage is sending his cast members used condoms
So on July 8th
He talks a lot about
Collapse
Of course Will Smith
So much better than this is also somebody quit the movie come out
On July 8th stories that Alex covers is the Chinese stock market
It took a little bit of a dip
Huiclaims
Apparently also the stock market went down.
After the Chinese
Stock market
Thought went down
And did read the story that the stock market
People gave was that it was a technical glitch
He believes that it's the globalist
Come again to stop
The market for being destroyed
I think the reality is
That thing that we've discussed in the past a bunch
Is B so much trading is done on a micro-scale by robe
Shut down the market
It's because
These robots would misinterpret things
And start selling off
How do you would have an artificial clap
Read Michael Lewis's book
Electronics
Most likely scenario
If it's just we have
To save the ship
So shutdown
Because he's robots
Destroy the market
So
6 or something
He's just using
Get to push
Selling gold
So
It's not all that interesting
But what is interesting is he does get back to talk about Trump
Do you I haven't heard
Of this Republic
Filled with people I want to kill in California
They did on their way is regulations
People
Destroying Society
Celebrating in the streets downtown
Donald Trump Donald Trump
How do you like it even matters
Story the rebel flag
Willie Havens
Member removed this is why kptp hallucination
What do you think your boy
Trump's in trouble
Donald Trump's net worth
With
Non matching socks I don't understand
But you're running around celebrating
Galatians
Generations
Mustafa
14.3 thousand
What what is it you don't get about this
I legitimately don't get why you're
Computer
I don't know what your self is we've lost 90% of
Weather weather track that track
Okay play that again just to figure out where we start
Was endless
Write the first part of believing that he's on board with Trump
Because
Even though he's not
Guitarra
Mirror lot of trump
Negative people are mad about Trump
Him sort of
Realizing
Everyone else's
Judgment
I guess
Inasmuch
People attack them similarly
Because they're both
Bigoted
The second part is
Trump
Distraction in the same vein is complaining about the
The flag the Battle Flag
Art
He's not my boy I don't care about him
It's just a distraction and a more important
Is that the globalists are attacking us
And killing our sperm
And GMO Foods
Kill the pop
The reproductive capacity of mammal species
Makes perfect sense
Now that you've just convinced that 3-minute VarageSale
People who are different types of
Also I didn't have time to do this
Just because of my schedule but I was going to make a
Supercut
Of all the times we talked about mismatch
You talked about it a lot three episodes during this time span he's mine
I can't f****** handle that another episode
It seems to be hit like
Handlebar mustache
Mismatched socks
That's a trend
That's sort of like his go to
And the other one is
He believes that liberals and trendy's love Islam because they smoke hookah
Of course it's sort of like his way of being productive and not having to wrestle with
Anyting
So dumb
But it still indicates that as of July 8th
Alex Jones Belleza Donald Trump
Completely
He's a ringer for Hillary's there.
Distract from her emails
Make sure that rampaul does
Specific prediction that Alex Jones is making
Music
The last time I saw
Wait no
He's a mortal isn't he
It could be
Done
Listen to some f****** meal game and specifically made the claim that the big one the big
Big collapse is coming this winter which is pushed
From somewhere
End of July that hasn't happened
He's being metaphoric
Immortal
He's mortal
Lemmings in 2018
No not important
What happened
Well
But it wasn't as big as the one in 19
And it really wasn't as big as the one in that
74 whenever he
Well that was when he continued fighting the Civil War by himself
Write whatever he was actually fighting in the Revolutionary War there was
The collapse of the
Town back then
Then whenever he was
Fighting for Galls
There is a collapse
On what episode is Sean Connery in Highland
Episode I don't remember where it was
I meant also on another episode another episode he said he's related to Nathan
Bedford Forrest confederate general the person who invented the stock
Annoying kids use like I'm just ended from Cleopatra
What are you talkin about
Disparate pieces
Yeah
Spell statistically isn't it something like if its eighth generation
Back we're all related to everybody or something along those lines literally almost everybody is related to Genghis Khan
Kangaskhan has
But
80% like 5% of China's population is entirely descended from Genghis Khan
Anyway we are now done with July 8th kind of boring
Stuff that we talked about
The past
And now
We get on
July
July 9th
This is what I think is illustrative
The list
I think it's
About Alex Jones
Weather broadcast
He goes from
Collapse
Sandy Hook one day collapse
The next day
And onto July 9th
This episode is
When he debuts is lineup
Zupas
Might as well
This episode is all about this MTV show that
There there was a preview that came out for an MTV show called
In the show
Desire reporter Washington Post
Set out to make white people understand
The nature of white
Understand
Systems of Oppression
These sorts of things
The trailer for the show is mostly white kids crying
Alex
Alex is furious.
He spent almost the entire episode complaining about the show
It's complete lunacy
But before he does at the beginning of the episode
He's got it something else.
Scroll scroll which is
The gay agenda
This is Sumner redstone
Nickelodeon
In a corporate press release
With transgender and homosexual messages
Sexual sex messages
When they're six years old
It's creepy but not really
I mean it is just Twilight Zone level
Alex Jones
19 okay okay Nickelodeon
150 women before he was
16 have sex with another man
Turn off
Stay he didn't even know about that
Disconnected misunderstanding about the idea
Of making queer kids feel okay
Normal
Sexualizing people
Also
What do you mean if you send a six-year-old sex mess
Messages
A six-year-old can turn on TV
That's true that's what you're talkin about
But that's what I'm saying you can find CVS for adults
I'm fine flat affect
Watch Franklin & Bash
Heterosexual sex messages all the f******
Remember where Alex just doesn't notice it because
It doesn't matter
Crying here is sort of the ideas of making
Characters who are gay or lesbian or trans
We shouldn't
Creating positive role model
People have these
Identities
From very young ages
It's not something that comes up
I guess I can people discover things later in life
The time people
Before they even understand what gender is no different
Doesn't matter
Previous episode
Talking about
Trans identity from you
Everybody who identified
Once they were in the
Percent went on
To identify
Was like 40%
Like you can be
From the get-go
Understanding
You shouldn't be made to feel shame all day everyday it doesn't understand is that there's a difference between
Encouraging someone to do something being okay with them doing something
There's a
I haven't messaging
Is gay positive
Transposit
Hey kid you should be Tran
Yeah that's what I say
Just to say
If you are
You should feel fine about it
What I do is I go to elementary school
Can I pass out
Transgender surgery coupons
And I'm like hey
Hey kid
You should be a girl
Starbucks
All joking aside episode Alex legitimately
Oh okay well then I hope it goes and f****
We'll get to that
I hope the doctor removes
Started into his own a******
Repeatedly
I want to shellac
Alex Jones balls
Rub them on his
Here is a clip that is weird
It is a long ramp
It has to do with race
Let's do let's do it
Cult conditioning
So he's like the end of the
The hour or something is like all I've been talking about MTV too long
From the MTV
Stop
I guess that is part of this
Common illegal alien on TV
Flogging themselves
Tarantino stickers worth
Somebody's afford
Get off
Alibaba
Let's go to this video clip of joining us in 30 minutes
Briggs has the interview in Texas
Doctors offices
Your son
What's that mean
Directly habitat
School
Go to McDonald
Social Warrior
Proud of themselves
With your child
It's their child
Kids want their parents
I can't follow Rod videos
Walmart
Public boat ramp
Colt program
Do you understand
Uranus
Military Academy
Before the rise of the Machines and the merger with the elite
Suspension system
Before that can happen
They have to take out men
Selected
The nesting areas
It's like that
What almost
But not lizards
Change
It's alright my bad I feel
Sushi roll
Britney because MTV cry
Starting point
Want you to be whatever gender you're not
Because you're
GMOs
It's directly to the rise of the Machines
Melissa harris-perry quote about the community having response
Ability for children
Hey ho hey buddy how about drain the swamp is from Mussolini
Biology
Banana it's fascinating though part of that
Boat on
Samba level I couldn't
Lego
Yeah this is him like completely misunderstanding reality like
Just basic biology like you just doesn't have any
Female and then some became male in the biological prototype
Hunting
Defending the nest
He doesn't understand events with all mammals and birds
Not at all he doesn't largely all of that is
Like a cultural construct
That's all
So stupid
Is just bigotry
What
It's like he's describing a cartoon
Like that's what he just described Felix the Cat cartoon from the 1930s
Or whenever
Color
Started
God dammit
Learn that about biology I don't know what
Be like okay
Let me tell you about how let me tell you the story of the birds and the bees
What junior college class that he dropped out of the dealer net
So the other thing now is he's doing all this
Like a little girl do you want to be a boy
That was that was very crate
Interviews
Hospital
MCI dolls
Tell Tim is
Set the doctor asked
Her daughter
Are you a girl
Which is a reasonable question to ask
It's sort of a silly question
I remember getting questions like that from doctors
They have children
Simple question
And stuff like that
In order to create a report
Cuz there a stranger
How old are you how many times has like a six-year-old come up to you and
For me it doesn't even have to do necessarily with some sort of the fairies transgender
It has to do with a doctor
Made up drinks right more to do with the doctor with probably clunky bedside manner
More than anything else
Fluoride McDonald's McFlurry
Weigh-off
Really awful
And Alex
Even more often
What is
I can't even do that voice
Anymore it's really starting to hurt my throat
I just
I just don't understand
I don't understand how you can
Turn that into something
Nefarious
But I mean I mean
That that idea of
Well
What goal
Controlling men
Destroying
Confusing everybody vulcanization
Use the Edwards
Stupid it's just
You thinks everything that is not
Supportive of white
Heterosexual Christian identity
Is divide-and-conquer strategy
That is it
That's what he said
Do you know what I
Here's the theory that I've started
The more like
We're not
Full
Creatures
You and I
I think he's human being
People talk about how
The internet
Is divided
Siri is more becoming
Look at how far you have to
To go to deny your own human
Okay look at how
Look at how
Twisted
And like
Look at how big this ideology
He has to be for him to just say
I'm freaked out by trans people
Nation of globalists are trying to baba baba baba baba baba
You're also not
Into account with that how much
She needs
Cover
He needs to protect his business in
Mystery
F*** you. I just wish I just wish you would come out
Hey it makes me feel uncomfortable because I don't understand
So far outside my window in the world and
Can't be flexible about it all
Like I would be interested in having that discussion
If you say to me like
I get
To transfer
People is
Revulsion
I'm not fine with that
Because
I think it's an okay reaction
I'm fine with that because you're just
How you feel
Really you don't really have a
If you don't have any framework for that like I grew up
Small town
If I
Just stayed in that small town forever where is
It's just a bunch of
Who look like me
And then I see some
Something that is so
8 of that like someone with mismatched socks
Freak
Right right
Of course your your basic tribal inside
Is like
Oh that's
An enemy
Something along those
Describing is essential to go to college
It's important for people to go away to college
People just go other
Yeah it's big and you should have crazy
It's important for you to
Have those feelings
Emmett Beacon
Confronted with reality and grow through it
That's what I'm saying because quite frankly I thought
Incredibly f*****-up
Because most of my contacts for it was listening to Loveline
Very Anti Trans
He is
You super like
It's just weirdo dudes
And stuff like that
I'm so that was my contacts for everything
Until I met
Some people who identify this
Conversation
And watch some documentaries and looked into
Little bit more had a crisis of
Oh I don't trust this Adam Carolla that I listen to for so long
And you grow through it if you could just
Admit that
Converse and then like
Experian
So stay just behind all of this
That's how I can get away with having a conversation with a transfer
Who is completely and utterly
Normal and reasonable in all of those things so I can never be that there with the globalist framework is
Fortunate
Exactly
And that's the same thing that
Hiding behind like the
Care of your weight or black or whatever
No you do admit you care and then we can deal with it
We're also getting too I think it's dangerous for people who are young is because
If you do get this brain virus of the globalist
Some stuff like that into your head too early
You don't really have any
Escape Plan you don't have a hat
You can get out of
Like with Adam carolla's
Bigotry
I was very able to get away
Because it
Not defended by anything other than
Whereas if Adam Carolla was saying
If he's very about there is an evil cabal that is making people do things because they have a vested interest in
Destroying masculinity it would be much more difficult for me even when
Confronted with reality
I to get away from
Cuz there's a mythology
It's a story
That you can
Reinforced again
And so then that also
It's across-the-board
His his place
Michaels.com
Equally across
Not everything is private property
Self-defense and don't make me feel guilty about being white
What do you think about even those things
Take private property out of because
Second Amendment is self-assigned
National
Is the things that he's super
Conversation
So this next clip
We get into more specific feelings that he has about this white people show
This is kind of a short clip but it's Alex Jones
Baby mocking
About
People believe the reality about races
I mean
I don't think he's coming from a genuine cartoon character to he can get out some truth
Feelings that he has that he is afraid
People calling a race
Because that is
And who conceptional able to people use
To take power over
I meant when I said the reality is
I believe that racism is a bigger problem than terrorism
Viabill
Yeah and he's doing that mocking voice
To sort of
Take discredit that opinion
Very small problem compared to ingrained
Deeply entrenched racist
His belief that our president
Is actively
Destroying the world
Well-known
He's a f****** Loop
It is the entire G
Also because I wanted to get that
Foundation
Being called racist is the worst thing
Justin advances this next clip
Which I think is one of the craziest things out Jones ever say
Antonio Vargas
Is a journalist immigration
He was part of the Washington Post team
Recover to the Virginia Tech shooting
Broadcast in 2004
Pushes the DREAM Act for the children
I just
Got beat up quite a few times that racist white people you money
People did Martin Luther King's batac by Whitefield
Just like the white people
And we've been given this guilt
I really do care about you I really do
52%
Flies
Bargain world government
So Alex Jones is like Martin Luther King
Jordan
You got a tough time with that
I did not do well with that I did take the headphones off first the first time taking the headphones off
The second is the second
Do you know why I was the second you know I remember the last time
He was very much very very weird
Very weird
It is almost convincing
Just say that
Does
Care about everybody like
A whiskey the number of black people
To keep shifting
49% is 51% of 52 percentage in that ballpark
Not have it like
Straight
He's not quoting any
It's my also Gardasil there are negative side effects
Can come up
But all of them are much better than cervical cancer
So
There's a necessity
To play this game words
Hbv isn't bad
That's not the problem HPV in women doesn't lead to cervical cancer often
It's a big deal doesn't really matter for
That it's just warts
Produce
Doesn't really do anything all that terrible
Watch for women it is a very big issue
And so the idea that he doesn't have to
Scared
Really
Gets rid of
Biggest causes a circle
Okay a
So
It means even he's not being specific about adjust
Women what does that mean
Epsom salt
Direct competitors
His
I understand where you're coming from almost
But it's not
Because he's the wrong
Bulshit spaghetti
Does
I do think
In his mind
He believed
That he cares about
What do you think that he and his mind really believe that he's been beat up as much as Martin Luther King
Do I think he believes it well that's proof that he doesn't know any
I don't I think he believes it
Okay it's obviously not true
He's convinced himself of it
Reality
If he's ever
Been in prison
Because he's white
If he's ever
Had people throw bombs at his house
He has not been imprisoned because
Aziz light
Is like
He keeps referring to these fight
Regarding it as a used but most of those are street fights
Nothing was Art racially-motivated Attack
Whether or not they happen
And it all is still in quest
It's very dubious
But at the same time it's
He seems to think
That these fights that he had a part in
Getting into
Depression
And they're not
They're just him as a kid
Being obviously full of s***
Obviously an a******
He claimed he slept with 150 women
16 he was kicked out of his school
4 year from
For fighting
He's he's a guy who when he was young
I mean embellishing every
Except
Endicott school for you
The guy who was like
He he was a problem kid
It's I don't think I bet he did have a couple of times book called
Cracker for something like
I would believe
But I don't believe
He's been targeted for being white
Of course not and it's degrading for him to compare himself horse number
Degrading for everybody but Nelson Mandela
Yeah
Yep
Our old friend is back
Our old friend
Totally
Aeropress
But Christ
Still on the July 9th episode
Our old friend Larry Nichols comes back
Martin Luther King
Martin Luther King jr. is it a no
Earliest
Sure
How do you
Bengal
Civil rights
Movement into I think
Beat up more than Martin Luther
I got pea
Of the entire
Civil Rights Movement
Was MLK got beat up a bunch
And then black people
But because that is the masculine way to look at it
Toxic masculinity
How much do you believe in what you believe in
Ma'am
I'm sorry
Larry Nichols is back
My man okay
Stevie Larry Nicks
He throws a lot of bulshit around about how again Alex is our only shot
But this time
He is f***
Soliciting money
Hard
My health is not good I need help
Are you just asking for money
Narratives that Chelsea is not Bill Clinton's daughter
That's his step one of his big is Big narrative
I'll bet you dropped this one this is this is Larry Nichols moment of the day
Indian education campaign
So far away
Here's what's going to come
You got two choices right now
Delete
Call Joel
Turning us into an Islamic caliphate
Stop that from happening
Domino's
Yeah man
Yep
It's it's so sad
To see all these things that Larry Nichols believe
Such a bummer
Obama
Trying to turn
Please
What are you
Is closing even start with that like
Sir
You have to leave the leader of
Islam
Worldwide
He's trying to start caliphate
No but this actually is in line with that interview that he did with Mother Jones
He was talking about how Clinton's are our only hope
Of destroying Islam because they're cold-blooded
Contradict entirely all the other stuff that he says about
Destroy the world
She's going to turn us into
Describe
Is communism
He describes it as
Destruction of America
He is an unreliable maybe a big fan
He needs money
You wants to be interesting so Alex will have him back on his show so people will send
Money
How old Obama become the leader of Islam globally
Conversation
Do you feel about Indonesia
Nickelsville
Billions of people who are Muslim or not
It's not from the Middle East
Probably not
There's tons of Chinese Muslims there's
American
What would we would Obama done have
There's also different branches of Islam but definitely wouldn't all fall under Obama
Civilization game
Don't bring the tempering Sampson today
Okay if
Two hexagons to the left that will be in the appropriate place
I'd like to point out at this point that I haven't liked
Ignored or cut out stuff that
He said about Trump
You still is
Exactly in the same position
He has been
Sense
July 2nd
But now
We get to July 10th
Can Alex Jones is out of school
David Knight
And it is our tradition to never listen
David Knight correct
No no
I accidentally how did you do that I accidentally listen to
Because
At the beginning
David Knight says Alex Jones will be in later with a special report
How to spell ice
And I couldn't find
I'm not going to listen to the whole thing
But I accidentally found this clip
And it is amazing
David Knight
Is crazy
Came in and told me that he went to Disney World in the 1970s
Ride
Soldan in
Anaheim
And you know that
Sisqo Let It Go
They had the song
Fun Whimsical character
Here's a gun by and we went back to Disneyland and always
Has completely changed
Aspersion taken out
Takeout
I thought one of the most beautiful things about it was
No no of the older black man Henry
1940s
Animation mixed with live action everything
Yeah buddy
No negative talk about Song of the South
Have they ever seen song
I watched it
What I was seeing for a little while accidentally found it
You don't
Old man who tells stories is a horrible
Black stereotype
Is Karima sound also
Splash Mountain is based on
They just took out all of the races
It's top of the
It was Song of the South
Splash Mountain the original
And they're like little things
Retained from the ridge
As I understand
But also
You're totally right
Don't let go
You're not
David Knight
You ain't right
What do you mean the most racist people I can think of aren't going to jump on
Song of the South is weird
But also
They took down song in the
For you that you're like
I'm going to get to engineer to chime and about how Song of the South isn't the ride at Disney anymore and he discovered
Years ago we were just talking about it over the break
What the f*** is going on in their Studio
The night
Now we get to the 10
Oh I'm sorry
Like I would love to be in the studio for a day and just be the f***
Chaos
There've been plenty of times where they just don't know where Alex is
Like yeah that's true
There's got to be all kinds of weird s*** being talked about when he's allegedly in court
So I'm sorry that was
The temps the David Knight was hosting
I'm sorry that was
Friday
Amman deal
At Disney
So
Because that is a Saturday
And we come back on the 12th
I'm here
Three of the last four Clips I have for you
He gets to talk in a bit more about Trump
At this point
After July 12th
The other clip I have
Involved
My fear
My current insane Theory
Yeah I'm loving
This clip
On the 12th show where he spells out some more of his feelings about Donald
Call Donald Trump
Universe
America
Smartphone
The felons coming in
Schoolyard
He's the worst person in the world
Common sense
And it's perfect because Trump is a huge Hillary Clinton donor
I don't trust him as far as I can throw him
But he thinks that the truth
That is
Les Fargo get thrown out
Republican
Trump
Okay so now we're starting to see the
The first signs of
Of course
Might have some thoughts about waiheke
Why is that
Well remember on the last episode
He's mocking
Remember how you were speculating that I was making too big a deal out of
Yes well I would like you to listen to this
Does John do come back is your issue
But
Donald Trump owns a bunch of casinos
More
Donald Trump
Well with a name like Donald Trump's they don't come after you with a name like Corleone
Alright
He hasn't from high-level source
Yeah but he has everything from high-level sources reality
This this is something that people came document
He would have this information from high-level sources
I mean he could have it from anybody
But it is true
That's the difference
Between
Other high-level sources
Weird globalist to runs into on planes
Weird
On this one he's right
Like I can
Conceived
I can't allow myself to live in a world where broken clocks. Everything Alex Jones says is
Elderly wrong
The stuff he said about Trump
Before he became Trump's biggest
100% Act
Again we have to come back to what I was explaining
On the last episode that it is
The reality of this the truth of it is he is
Him saying that Trump has
Extensive mob connection
Is true
To Alex Jones
What's relevant
Is that he believes that
He's repeated it multiple times over the course of
The last episode
Going
Further and further spelling out how he knows it
That's true
Hi all this stuff
Jesus Shady people all around him
That's not nothing
Even if he was wrong
That's still the narrative
Just like
Sandy Hook
False Flags
Yeah
Still here
He's doing
Trump propaganda
Because he's super into Ron Paul
Remove now to the last day of our investigation
Simplify 30
And on this show
Alex Jones
He's on some weird s***
He's he's doing
Some weird s*** on the
On the 12th I just played those two clips
Most of the shows by collapse
Narratives
And he also was worried about
Censoring history
We talked about the flag Bunch the Battle Flag
He also admits
If you own multiple not begun
Put this phone
July 13th
Any of 10 copies
No David
Alex Jones is very over
On this episode and very clear that he is against Russia
Because he doesn't think that they are the bad guys
In the Ukraine situation
Again we've been over this
Globalist
Right there just protecting Russian identifying citizens
In the Ukraine they're coming in
To help them deal with the globalist
That's just such a weird
Sing for him to
Turn that in
Well always
Pro-america
As he says he
And for his entire like
Cuz he's
Shut that like when we go back to the Y2K he's definitely
The phobic narrative going on strong there much so
So
Him
Putin in the
What's in the Crimea
Situation seems
Mind-boggling
Well
Have you already been on RT at the
I don't know I don't think so
But I do think
That he's starting to become
Switch
Can propaganda
And some of that will play out in this
It's still male-driven
Basically almost
Yeah
Because I already went through it under Tommy population
Been in the jaws of this forever
They still got correct
But really what's going on
State-run TV
They're pushing narratives that are similar to him
They're pushing propaganda narratives about how
All of the stuff that we're doing is to
Stop
Right
So it's starting to mirror him
That's what Alexander Dugan
I think some of that intentional
And then so they pick up on what he's doing he picks up on what they're doing
Turns into a nice little feedback loop
Yep and they can both kind of bounced there
I mean basically
They bounce ideas back
Somewhat
They they
Trade narratives
I think there's a burgeoning propaganda
Glue
That is beginning
With Russian State television
Alex
If you want to take a step further about that
The reason that I said
The Nigel farage
Was important earlier
I believe
Already have positive feelings about Nigel farage
Band
Can't prove it a hundred percent but I would be
Very surprised
He isn't the intermediary for Rodger Stone
And WikiLeaks
Right
Obviously pushing Russian propaganda
Of course I believe that wants Rodger Stone gets
Involved
You take these dormant feeling
And it becomes
Super a
All this connection
Kitchen comes together
At the same time
If you look at it
It's so important that all the major players now are
Gameplay
They aren't in in in the in the neck
So you have Alex
With these late thing
Is the big
What is the male identity
Is there racism
The distrust of
Those are two things are
Throughout
On top of that eventually you get Rodger stone in there
You get to be fortunate
Can there who's not around at all this
He's the one who pitches
The counter cool narrative
Right.
The clintons are pulling us off too and we
He's not there
Rodger Stone isn't there to pitch
Overly
Aggressive
Trump
Stop
At the same time people like Mike cernovich on around Gavin McGinnis
Those people are
The
Cool fun trolls
Guy
So all these other elements of Alex Jones's
Spear of what
Propaganda
They are in place yet
What we have
Is art
We have ham
We have dormant
And that's why he doesn't support
Trump yet
IFit
I think that once these other
Much more
Active players
Get involved
That's when he
Switch
And I know that I already said that I believe that wants Rodger Stone come
Comes around
Through
Him
Saying all these super positive things about Nigel
Saying really
Dicey things
About Russian propaganda narrative
About Russia
These things
Lead me to believe
I don't know how to spell this out exactly but
Rodger Stone
Probably targeted
I think
Did he knew that Alex had these Lena
He knew that he could use
That is kind of what I say
Alright
I think that he knew that he could
Play Stone is the one pulling out
I think it's possible and it certainly fits his pattern of being a dirty Trickster
Opportunistic underhanded
Conservative Republican
Tricks video played throughout his career
And then you figure
Stone is the intermediary
Anybody in Russia
All of the all of the authoritarian
Wright Park
Propaganda Outlet
Coming together and creating a unified
Some like the people who are pushing
Brexit really hard are creating the
Property
And a right-wing feedback Russian TV
Everybody in Turkey
You have
Yeah you have all of these different
People
Nn
Like it's easy to imagine that it's
Spira see but I
I think it might just be more longer
Signs of
With communication
Across the globe
More
Being so easy
Then we can just find
Yeah opportunist
It's not like everybody
Together in a backroom comes play
Oh I like what you're doing let's turn that into a thing that I'm doing and then still want and it just creates
Does bigger and bigger feet
But I also think that there is
An awareness
That
Nationalism is
Is a very easily
Voided
And you can use it to enrich yourself
If you ride the wave ride
Brett it's something
Requires a scapegoat
Globalism
Great Escapes
Very good then so you have Jews also works but it doesn't make sense
Really for nationalistic
Countries to
Pulley
Each other
So why is it that
Marine Le Pen
Viraj all of these people keep
Having the same message
Keep having the same admirers
Annapolis garage seems to run through all of them
Yeah he seems to be a very common threads
And as
Is Rodger Stone
Well Rodger Stone through farraj
So
I think that there's something much more nefarious going on here
Alex B
Not be aware of the forces that are at
That's sort of my feeling
As of press time
Yeah because
I sincerely could
Beavis
Being
A massive
Dupe
On the park
Of Rochester
Well it's interesting
Something to use Alex
In this regard because he
Too dumb to
Bring it
Yeah like you don't want him involved in any planning session door having
Any knowledge
He's too dumb it's that he
Dauriac
Canary
If you reveal
He's going to say whatever it is
So yeah I would say
Alex Azar
Lucky idiot
In this regard
Someone
And he will lose tons of money because of it as well
I know that it's
Still very crazy
For me to be saying that I think
That there is something incredibly underhanded
You think there is a global
Conspiracy
Might know I don't
I think it's a very localized
Conspiracy
I think
It's the small conspiracy
It is real
And it is
Basically destroy
International
Body
That do serve to stop War
Where is the cheap way to get rich
It's so insane to me
Christopher Steele came out with that. Everyone focused on the P stuff
But all the rest of it is coming
Out so hard
Everything
Trump was secretly trying to lift thanks
Which is what everyone suspected he was going to do
The reason that you would do that is be
Because if they raised
The sanction Russia can make tons of money
Obviously
That is him
Pro quo
Wicked mix
No sense to not
And Alex
Isn't that dumb
Alex
He's not Alex is that dumb
So long as you provide him
That better fits in
Into what he wants
Stupid Trump is fighting your culture War for you
So
Probably blind him to any number of all of this
The the all of the s*** that he spending now is he
Bring it back
Economic prosperity
Everything that you
Saying that Trump
Is doing
He's not doing
Is numbers are on the rise
It's obvious he's not doing those things
You know what's fun
Even if you save that the polls are weighted like Alex's 15%
Trump
Roseate Outlook he's only hated by 5% more of the population than others
I know
I know and you're not even saying that
I know it's
Crazy just don't mix.
I know that
It's hard to
Find another
It's hard to find another thing that fit
It's all of the players
But there's obviously another there is another scenario that
DNR
There are there secret information that we don't know there's unknown unknown
Is Rumsfeld would say
Yeah it's why I recognize that
It's either that or it's
Just one of the
Most
Unlikely coincidences that I can imagine
All of the stuff arises
Independently of each other
And miraculously Alex Jones starts hanging out with and promoting
A guy
Who is one of Trump's Close Associates former campaign manager
At the same time
He starts having on Steve pieczenik and spelling this narrative
He brings in a bunch of alt-right pranksters to be on his show to try and make things happen cool
It doesn't make sense that all of that would start happening
Like
I'll figure out exactly the time that these things start happening but
Up till now July 13th
None of those people are around and he doesn't support
No
If I find that Rodger Stone shows up and he doesn't support Trump
Yeah but I can't imagine that being the case
Yeah I don't know
From the get-go
Wasn't he
Wasn't Rodger Stone was on Trump's team for campaign manager for a little while
I think at this point you still involved in the campaign 2015
Yeah and so once he goes off
The campaign starts
Unofficially as a propaganda
Right
So
I don't know
It's really troubling
Stone ghost
The trumpet says I can
Get you info
The fact
That Alex is so dismissive and so
About what's going on with Russia
Lead me to believe
That that is
That is a weekend
For him
That was exploit
I don't know we'll see
But we are one more clip
And it's also from the July 13th episode
Do you get the collar
Call Zan
Counterpoint about Trump
He has a
Slightly positive argument about Trump
It's interesting that Alex Jones
So even with someone saying positive things about Trump
Here's what Alex says
This call is about 5 minutes long
And I just want to let it play on uninterrupted because
It's I mean it
Totally
Evidence against you
Okay where Alex Jones
Your phone calls right now
Richard in Illinois in London
Lionel Richie
Richard Moyer on the air go ahead
Disagree about Trump and
It's only because
I don't think
It's ordered from anybody
Nothing is perfect but
You mentioned yesterday he was a ringer
I don't think he takes orders from anybody
Call Mike Mike
Parents weekend in Chicago
Just got off a building
You put this god-awful sign on
Seafood everybody
Forget the Sun
And I work at Express
Show off
Hoping you would do is
If you think it's a ringer
Why don't you invite him on Michelle and ask him
We have
Niko go after
That
He suspects
That that's
So I'm sorry I interrupted
I mean bear
He repeats the Jerome corsi who knows Donald Trump is saying that he is
And as a publicity stunt
Yeah also
Donald Trump does eventually come on the show
But at this point
He's not answering
Alex's request
So even the idea that when Trump comes on
Your your reputation is impeccable
We're going to be talking a lot
Clearly if Alex
Come on of course
So that part is even
Well there's no way
There's no I would never believe the Trump
No or at ever heard of it
Probably heard of it
Well yeah you probably tweeted out a link
Before that saying about how dumb infowar
Maybe
Going by Oliver Trump's tweets about Obama and how they're the exact opposite of
Yeah f****** he doesn't believe anything there's no beliefs
But at this point
Is ignoring Trump
He doesn't care
You want
Even though you got course
Imagine
And what he's doing
Birth certificate
His horses
My gut has never been wrong
Bachata
He's a front man for some people
Are worth
78 million
Trump
But by his actions
I've had a chance to
I just I don't even feel good
I don't like
Somebody else's rigged game
If it's a fake
Chomps Campbell
It ruins a lot of lives
I agree with most of them
Miserable
They did not smile
You could tell they were exhausted
Exhaust
He is moving the Overton window
Libertarian as rampal as a rampaul supporter
I kind of support
He's all bad when
Overton window
I don't know or are you wrong
Generally you're not wrong I agree with a lot of what you say matter of fact
That's the last night for meeting my wife was at a tangerine but I have every morning
But there's something marijuana plant Richard
You're a plant
Doctor fish
I can't pronounce his last name
He might be able to give a really good
Psychological description of what Trump is and he might be a sociopath I don't know
It's a good move on to Tom and Limonite
Comment on your comment
Donald Trump
What do you know Alec is America
Easy pop culture person
Is involved in WWF
Uses
Who is awake
Sounds good
Misrepresent
Discredit
Everyone else
And what's going on
Donald Trump
Hear this voice changer Will Robinson
But they
So
There we are
That clip
Really spells it out
Yeah
I mean he does he has his own Fair because he's already explain what it means
You talking about Bob
I know but I want to know
Names of the details
Alex is ever going to give that one you can find that out by
Google Now
Just say it
He said that he
Makes his money running a casino which also is where they launder tons of money
But he runs
People who run casinos are predators
Plant making a false reality that exploit people who have sickness
That's not something that can be talked away
He believes
That one who runs casino is a predator
Donald Trump is a predator
You can't take that away
You can't be like
Oh I talk to draw preschool
Or whatever
Write history running casino and you think that is a predatory business
Right
If we go forward in time
He did what he did
He didn't wave it away with a rifle
Stealth Patriots not because he called me
Planning this for thirty years to be a stealth Patriot he had gotten the Run.
Maybe the most predator
In order to fight back
Trained himself to be
Become the ultimate predator
Is Arnold Schwarzenegger in the movie Predator I understand where you're coming from
But it
Can't be like I can't I can't work
It doesn't work
So even if I called super fascinating
The guy is saying you should get Steve pieczenik on
I know that was the weirdest the beginning
That is the weirdest thing that
Richard Scott
Responsible
Redbox
Do you like radio show Czarface encouraged
A lot of almost every DriveTime show
Is there businesses that use actors
And then pay them fifty bucks a pop
Call RadioShack
But like
Because of the plug
And because of the foreshadowing
Steve pieczenik
Right
It's interesting
That's such a weird like
So here's what university
Steve pieczenik name in there as if they're that's a regular name to throw in there
Hey you know who you should get
The profile the most evil man that we can think of
Another evil over here
Dakota said
You should get a psychologist to profile
Nope
Teatro Steve pieczenik involved in conspiracy world
Open stuff like that like he's a Sandy Hooks and I are in s*** like that
It's not all that weird to me
Idiots just
Like a
Blah blah
There's just a map
So throughout the course of this
From July 6th to July 3rd
We feed no change
And Alex Jones is a pinion
Towards Donald Trump
Except for him to spell out more
Very slimy in a predator
He still doesn't trust him
He's there to invalidate the
Truthful things that he says
He's there to make a mockery out of the very idea of these true ideas
He has that from high-level sources
If we if we go along the path of the color is
Fake why would you have a like there are only a couple of different reasons to have a caller who is
Is pro Trump
Call even Pro Trump
Albeit reluctantly
No he's saying he's like I'm liking what he's nobody saying is he's making a trump is making it okay
Okay to talk about these libertarian issues too far out
Ratso the Overton window ideas
This is not the sports Trump
It's just that because
He's so crazy and out there
He's bringing the conversation
Into the sphere
Make it okay for Ram
That we know he's the real deal about
So he's not even
Right but as a fake caller you're putting him there
You want that
Out there
You want that narrative to become part of the thing that Alex talks about but if you're doing that as a fake
Open you don't have Alex completely repudiate
You don't have
Slimy fuc
Yeah that's true
You don't think so
I don't necessarily think
The idea that the product
Isn't evidence for me because
Jiffy Lube
I didn't know that was a wreck
I support you
I want to let you know how break
So even though we see no Evolution necessarily
In his position towards Trump
We do C minor
Friends in his own
Headspace
I swear he's starting to
Jeffy the meteor
On top of that
We see
Him being incredulous of Russian propaganda
Receive him saying positive things about Nigel farage
I think
If I would describe the situation right now
This is the storm clouds gathering
Right right here we are leaving off
On
What I think is about to be a man
Thunderstorm
A massive thunderstorms don't happen just as clouds roll
There's pressure
Involved
I think these little things
Like the
Arrival Steve pieczenik
The arrival of Rodger Stone
I think those things are going to be the necessary ingredients
They come together
Underneath the
The gasoline
That is Alex Jones's underlying
Idiocy based on
Was a terrific man
And I think a Wonder
A place for us
To let you know that if you'd like to follow us on Twitter
And if you'd like to go to a website
Be kind of s*** we do we would really appreciate it
The review on iTunes
This is one of those things we were talking about
Before the show and
It is a very interesting
Sing for us
Go back in
And look at this
Investigation
And it's an even more interesting
For me because you were the one doing all the work
What's a verb
But like
This is
This is watching the beginning of this
This propaganda
How did we get to here
How to make
How did we get to the point where
Legitimately the president
Is sending emails out to fundraise with Infowars links
You can clown on Twitter about how dumb these guys are
Put look at what they do
Something people are
Annex
Likable
Because they're so f****** stupid
There's three things that I agree about out with Alex Jones about
Marijuana should be legal
Able to take s*** from you there should be able to steal from you
And there is an information War
Tied up with
Open Shady motherfuker
But there is there is absolutely information
Wars going on
Imperfectly
I totally agree with all of that
And I'm not saying that we have the resources or even the ability
To be the other side of the information War
But making fun of him isn't enough
We need to understand this stuff
Or else we're going
Be suffering the consequences of it the next time around
Absolutely
My that's my mission
This is it
It's so weird
How's everything else in my life
Fairway
Somehow
The propaganda outlet that is being f******
Reference
Also spend the day talking about the song of itself ride at Disneyland
This is the world we live in
I don't know what else
Fly
If I show more more to the point
20 minutes talking about a Chick-fil-A before
Joseph doing like this
Very specific direct level
And it's very frustrating like people are really going out
Well some people are enjoying
Frank we should have
Maybe
Yeah probably
Let me this is important
It really is screwing our world
Maybe it's not the people believe Infowars
That's not the problem
The problem is
Okay Larry Nichols didn't destroy
Political discourse
But things he did
Set in motion
The environment where political discourses
Completely destroyed
The lies and propaganda
Was the source of about Bill
Tainted
The entire American political landscape the last one
In the same way
Alex Jones isn't directly
These things that are
Legitimately going to end up
F****** us over
But he
The ball in motion
Inasmuch as it's fun to be like I you didn't do that much
You're not responsible for Trump winning
He played a big role in it
He played incredibly
I'm sorry bomb people with Bill Clinton is a rapist shirt
Stuff like that
Lake Hughes indirectly responsible
For Trump becoming president
Trump
Is responsible
Getting out of
Climate change
Agreement
He's responsible
For putting Jeff sessions
Control who's going to roll back civil rights
With police
He's responsible for all these things
And quite frankly
Alex Jones indirectly responsible for a lot of that stuff
By virtue of the things he did
I don't want him
To be responsible for it
Cuz I like the Alex Jones
Who talks about Chick-fil-A billboards
I think he's an idiot
I don't I don't want to hang out with him but I like
That kind of
I think it's important to have weirdos
And I don't mean weirdo necessarily in the negative
I don't think that a robust
Medialab
Landscape
Just
Just well-documented stuff
You've got to have people out there who are suggesting
Some of the craziest bulshit
If sometimes
You have
Conversations that can be opened up because of their insane
Things that no one else would consider
And Alex Jones
Years ago
Was that
He still had a lot of bigotry in him and that's a big
Again
It's still all covered under the
First Amendment
I don't think
You know you can point the finger at him be like
Stop it
That's not grounds for taking him off the air
It's not grounds for arresting if he's not doing anything illegal
He was that
Crazy person
And this investigation to me is very personal and some way
Because not because I identify with him
Because
He's not that anymore
He is
The mouth
Peace
Is
Responsible
For civil rights
Going away
In many cases
He's responsible
For whatever woes are going to come to our climate
That lead us to be siding with Syria and Nicaragua
Every other day was actually way better than everybody else
Bright
It's not
I want
Chick-fil-A billboards
It sucks
Genuine
Heartfelt moment of sad
For Chick-fil-A Alex
It sucks
Ma'am
Cuz now we can't have that anymore
No no that's gone forever There's No Going Back. The form of Alex
Everybody else
There is no sensible
Conspiracy theorist baby Joe Rogan
I don't know
Maybe is
With him now
Did the Mike cernovich has the rebel media those people are all
Weaponize
They're not like
Alex Jones
Back in the day
When he was just talking about chemtrails
And even lie 2K even that that wasn't
Propaganda
Mike cernovich Rebel media Alex Jones
These are all things that are working towards
The specific goal
Is the
Of liberalism
It's the destruction of
Global cooperation
I want to find a different word than globalism cuz that's not what it is
A they want to destroy
These
These institutions that allow people
To work
Cord the better
Brett
Creating a new feudalism
Like that
That to me what I hear whatever people do the prosperity
It's all Billy
Yeah what is going to be like
What from all of these things is
We're destroying Nation
And
Rich ass motherfuker
Russia versus
Does the United
No that's not the
Well rested
Is people from Saudi Arabia
That's not good
Yeah all of this stuff is
It's
People
It's very very rich people looking to make more money
Really give a f***
He doesn't really care about Russia
Really care about you
All he cares about is being
Rich
Powerful
Taking back the Soviet Union
If you can get it
How many just said that if
Buttersweet enjoined
Use that NATO he's going to attack them
Future man
Yeah
That was the message
Guys don't do it
We never said we were going to join
What are you talkin to
I don't know it's it's
Oligarchy
Boggles my mind
I can understand how anybody
Goodbye in
Yeah isn't
One of those Olive
I agree
Has been a prolonged
Outro wailing
I try and make the point
I'm really
I know it's really easy to make
I would like it if more people listen to us
That would be awesome
Cuz
I'm self-centered but
I would like it more if just more
People were paying
The underpinning
Propaganda there are some attempt
To look at
It sounds like the Media Matters
Cover right-wing extremism and what-have-you
They don't
Speed into the outrage machine and all that right
It doesn't they're great and
It's somewhat they're at least they're shining a light on some of the stuff
I don't think
I don't think it's the
The ointment
We are either but
Anyway
Thank you guys
Last Thursday
Thursday
Yay
That what
Holding
Alex