Air Jordan sweat it
I have great respect for Tenaya Lodge B I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Text Julie
What's my bright spot today
Do with worms
Worm farm
It's going strong
Touch and go there for a bit I did not know exactly what I was doing or if I was feeding them correctly and everything
But now there's a feeling that I have that is like
Rebecca
The active
Composting is making
Food more exciting for me a little bit okay because
Like example
This morning
I made a couple eggs
Coffee and I realized
Speed of the worm to coffee grinds
Feed a bit of worms
You can just meet coffee grinds to work
Seems like you can feed and you're worried about whether that you can't feel anything
Spicy peppers
Like non spicy peppers are fine
No Citrus you want to avoid you don't want to give them too much
Capital Bank
They turn into Gremlins
Also like
Cheese
Haha you don't want to give worms are lactose intolerant
Take me to ism
Good cuz that'll us are like rot
That's not good
People in fruit cutting cardboard paper
You normally come
Post stuff cuz it's turning into like almost a feeling of like
Hey is there a way that I can make
Almost everything neutral
I ate the inside of the egg and my worms ate the show
The coffee here at the coffee grinds
Will turn into more things
Fertilizer exactly there you go
It's frickin bats
How me and my my worms
And are you going to
Pooping underwear
Stood erect just
Stand up
Just let it fly don't know if that's
As bad as cheese but I think you're not going to.
I think you're not supposed to do that
Thunderbird
My bracelet is too full.
First
My most important bright spot is always annoying to you but
Rafa won
Is 13th French Open
I genuinely believe that
If he stops playing all the other tournaments
It's just like claycord
You could probably win another
But my second bright spot
Do you recall the the endless story about the strawberries
Alright so about the delivery date
Yes it was wrong
So we
We're done with it
And then on her birthday I didn't send any emails I didn't do anything her birthday everything came and went by nobigdyl
The day after her birthday
More chocolate strawberries
I can order them
That's not even the right day for when I would have ordered them any worse early
Also early very weird goddamn
And Quest
Yeah you can only eat so did you know that there's a limit on how many you can eat before your legs
I'm done
Chocolate covered strawberries
From reading an article I just know that I can make it through that two of them
Then I'm kind of like
Six months before I have one of the
Which is why I didn't spring for that that fondue set
Thought about it
That would be a good idea
Jordan today to go over going to be talking about October 9th 2020
That is it
Friday's Friday's episode from last week
I would like to start this episode off of a tiny bit of that apology
Mostly for the sort of radio silence
Post anything online and part of the reason
I get into that but
We used to talk a bit
More openly about Mental Health
Struggles
Podcast
And
One of the reasons
That I have
Talked about it last
Is part of my
Struggle
Is hurt
Bye
The idea of everyone knowing
My struggle
Deal with
Gets worse
If I talked about it and I'm aware that there are 10,000
Black people that's Rancho
Where is it
I admire your ability
Need to be open about your bipolar struggle
Much more
I guess I would say bravely then I am in a certain sense
Also just
Side effect I guess that's fair
It's a different story
Yeah
Got on some meds for depression and anxiety a while back
Talking about
Because it's
I also don't really fine
It has interesting
B
You remind me that's another reason that you were talking about is cuz you were feeling better
Yeah yeah quite a bit they're upside down
Somebody who's been
Reluctant
Take meds
At least in my
More adult
The reason for it is
Bob fears
Uncertainties
Stop distrust of like they work
Of course I just always
Thought like
Rockwell
I'll be able to
The talk my way through this eventually
A short short short and then I gave
Starbucks
Explore this
Some positive results
And this last week I
I accidentally had stopped taking my meds
One of the things that's really tough about that is somebody who doesn't
You know isn't
A
Habitual
Maybe take her short shorts
It is that
You don't really notice sometimes when you stop taking them
I think it's this really weird phenomenon
I don't fully understand think I've heard
Talked about all that much
There was a guy was a good
Week before
My mental state was changing to the point where thankfully I had enough awareness to
Recognize I got
Yeah
But
It was really it was really strange
Stuvi of like
You know couple days in and not notice
That I had
Stop this behavior that I had gotten used to
Exactly what my point is
B of A little bit of trouble last week
I appreciate that
I made it Advanced I guess people being nice
I don't know
But I'm okay everything's alright
Sorry
Like I said to
Radio silence
But the reason for that was that part of
Like what I really needed to do to get back to normal was too
No consult
Guy with help
Take the meds
You get back to normal
Show me some healthy things
And avoid
Being on social media at all
Now is the smartest move for
I die by really apologize for anybody who got confused or was worried
It's nice
Someone may be worried but I would hate to have
God Percy
The potato diet
You know onward and upward
I don't dwell too much on this
But like the only thing you can really do is
Keep moving forward
We shall
Play it was yeah it was difficult
It was a little scary but
Where will back on
I appreciate your help in
Particular beer grapefruit
And
Couple times
Get back
To normalcy
But today on this talking about October 9th
And there's not a lot going on
On this episode
And I thought there would be
Because
That is after the Vice Presidential debates
Sure and
Of course the fly landed on like
The only thing anyone will remember from those today
Yeah
You know Alex made a big deal out of
The fly going around Obama and said that he smelled like sulfur
Here's a sign that he is demon-possessed seemed like it would be at least something.
Your address
It's it was a big part of Alex
Vacant I figured like
It's going to be like other good fly
And then you have the other issue that I know that this is one of your big
Assertive
Lanes
That was trumps
I don't want to say something about
That he was that he
He's fueled by abortions now what do you want what do you want me to say about him
It's treatment I didn't look into this Pacifica
Well I mean it's
Exaggerate
Eversource
Exactly
Hillary Clinton
Call Steph cell
Runs out of aborted fetuses
Right
Trump is getting this
Treatment that Alex would deride as demonic
Cheyenne his enemies and a fly landed on Mike Pence's head
And so I was like well
Got to click
Got to see what's going on here what's up there and
Yeah
Islamic
And just surprised
I'm not surprised that that information isn't really being widely publicized in the far-right
Sweat fly
The fact that their president was
His life was saved by a boar
Should really be some
I think
Like a lot but they won't
Which is a major
A lot of the beginning of the show is
About
The UN
Getting an award
For fighting
The use of hunger
In war
That sounds exactly like the top story everyone was talking to
I remember that one being you that um got an award
It's the kind of thing where there'll be like a war that's going on in
Star people as a means of carrying out the war
Grandview and has programs that they use to try and fight back against
Alex believes that this is
Is nonsensical because the UN cause
Covid MN
Has made everyone lockdown
Which is causing the collapse
The first world which will cause the collapse of the third world
Which will kill off everybody which is basically them using hunger as War
Sure
It's believed the tip of critical he goes on free
Very long time about it and
Incredibly boring that doesn't surprise me
I was bored when it the moment you said he started talking about the UN I was like what are we even here for what are we here for
I'm not talking about the UN
So this is the first thing that I heard that I kind of was like
Interested in a little bit because
There's a long stretch
You just complaining about the US
Yeah they have learned helplessness drills they do and they also have
Situational ethics they called spaceship or lightbulb
Where
Beautiful astronaut
Who's most essential and Division
And you decide who dies first
Then once you got them instead
Well now you just giving it a total eugenics
That's really where all this is going
I don't understand like what else
Would you do to prepare astronauts
Score a really bad
Situation they all died simultaneously that's the only way to not support eugenics in this situation to
Obviously
I would like astronauts to be well-trained
And I and I think
There are few
Higher Stakes
Situations then something going wrong
In space
It's hard you don't like to think about it you don't like to realize that
It sometimes baby someone does have to die in order for the rest of the crew to make it home
Don't talk about it there's an end a fight
Drawing straws were astronauts really going to draw straws like we're in the lord of the f******
Can flies right then the one person who can like fly the ship
Kunal flyboard
Getting commission home
Ends up drawing the straw LOL sorry fair is fair
Why wouldn't have these exercises
Over these thoughts
They're committed to not
Using eugenics
That's what
Real Prince
Fallsmead
Everyone dies on that spaceship
And if you want to use Eugenics on Earth we all take cyanide pills the same way
It's stale it's very silly to me the way Alex
Bixby's these kinds of things
Swear
You know it's a worst-case scenario planning
If you're in space
For example
And then forever
Space
They've even got a plan for if somebody goes space crazy
They've got a whole chain of command thing setup they got the whole thing also if you're not doing that
What's the alternative if you're not doing the like here's what we do with this disaster happen
Are you telling me that you want like mission
Control
Implant suicide chips in the back of their head be like
Sorry
Louise got to go like boom and he's gone like that
Scary
Vicki just want some to wing it kind of does
I would have waited in that situation so why not you
I think it's a bad plan
So like I said the entire beginning of the show is just about this um
Getting an award
Except for How It Ends
Coronavirus the hunger will kill us a global food
April
Oh but don't worry wart
Providing food is Aleppo
As they use it as a weapon
I bought a puppy in here I got that sword hypothetically
What animal
Dog cat Association whatever it is
SPCA River Golf
It'd be like if I brought a puppy in here I would ever do that I love dogs
Young Ward from a local animal rights group
Talk about killing dogs a lot I know that he loves to throw in like
Berkeley political I love dogs
The train of thought their suggest that hypothetically involves all of it like my pathetic lie if I love
Where I
I like dogs then I would never cut off
Cat and dog
Alright
The other one of the other big stories that had broken by Friday that I was interested in seeing what Alex
Say about was
The news about the militia folks
Screwhead plant
To kidnap
Michigan Governor Whitmer
Now we could talk about that but the UN did something
Play more important than an attempted overthrow
I was just because I felt like a militia Alex hates Whitmer
Connor Fielding
Got to come up
Sure are you everything feels like
Just got to come up
Fly on Pence's head
What if things gets really depressing about covering Alex in the
She is like I could Mad Libs his show for the most part like
I knew exactly what he was going to say about this
Plot already
I'm going to come back and it'll really important
Militia Commander Authority is a
Antifa
Individual
Police in America and Republican Party
Perrigo
Queenie Whitmer
I would have covered the food stories
Election
I'm just I'm just shaking my head
Just like
You son of a
Yeah pretty impressive
The reason I'm covering this story is important but also I should tell you
Go to buy Patriot Supply affiliate link that I've got
I8
It's so
Every time
I am going to whip
All of my far right people into a frenzy
Knowing full well that many of them are in militias
I know
Many of them have violent fantasies
And I have told them that it's a good idea to choose Targets in the higher-ups and take them out
And then when something happened
It was 84 damn I don't know
The guy who was the leader this group was necessarily
That Alex was
But you're right I mean that is the strategy
Yeah it is
Antagonize
People to do things
And then blame antifa
For Less the name of the game
Adentro
I got to say he plays some clips
Of the militia leader talking
And
Honest
Glee it sounds like Alex in the past
Do you know Trump is in
He's a he's a tyrant man show another call this stuff that he's that we do know that you need to be free dude
Do the police they're just there to follow orders
Alex's
Most of his career
I mean yeah that's because it's what you believe
Is he believes there is high-quality storable food with your name on it
Alex is playing essentially this like no true Scotsman type game
Right-wing militia weirdo
Would say bad things about Trump there for this guy isn't
Part of my world associated with him
What is he saying anything that I'm saying know I love Trump so much that I will lick his boot all day everyday I would
Like that
Boats
The first hour
Pretty unexpected
The final segment with our lawyers coming in I've got a emergency
Family Matters I have to attend to for the ongoing harassed
And the third
Fourth
Today
Time's left
To go to Family Court
Like you did the previous Friday
I don't know man that's a bummer
It's very
Huge bummer
Watching this
Episode
Just him being like
Militia that's 94 guy whatever
Spoiler alert
The trumps
Treatment
The fly
Surprise
For about an hour actually only about 35 minutes
I can't imagine he drove to the courthouse and back in the time that he was off air
Tom Brady comes back
And we get another follow-up on something that to Alex has been
Zigzagging all over the
Owen Shroyer still in studio
Weekend update on
The wheels
About the attorney general
We don't do bar with high-level CIA Will Bill Barr was brought in my
H.w. bush
1990s
We know who these people are
The older establishment that doesn't want to completely destroy America
Monte carryout globalism that we kind of control
The ballista run by communist China
PL phase-out for the takedown of America
You don't want to
And then you got the
Represent those that want to slowly
Salami slices America the little pieces
Nnnn digested with enjoyment
Instead of a Big Mac
He understands that he'll probably
It put the catalog during that process sissies as well
So
Ionizes bar in body that
So he's mad at Bill Barr now
Okay magically aware of the fact that
Pre-K Meandering h.w. Bush's high-level CIA
Totally fine with him being exactly like the person that he describes as a demon
Just like
Gradual
Yeah slow demon
So you're just what you just fine
Well the problem is
Speed
I know I didn't miss pace
I understand that like in some cases the enemy of my enemy is my friend
I understand that.
But she still wants to kill everyone
Salami slice
I feel like that's a deal-breaker for
It should be
Yeah
Okay
Ridiculous
Here's what here's the thing
Okay I like
Eco
I don't like fascism
I don't like
Them together
And that's a deal-breaker for me I'm not going to be like well we got to work with the eco-fashion
Just for a while they like the
Slowly
Climate change aware surrounding the issues that I like
To bring in the later part
Bad
Yep
Should be at this point
Like
Completely against
Spell bar
But he's not really
I'll be over
Easy
But it does have to do with the fact that bill Barr came out and said there aren't going to be indictments of like people like Obama
Did all that before the election
Surprise or whatever
This is really
Turned off
A lot of people in Alex's movie good
Pressure
It's getting into like this weird giving a rant
And
20in about how like hey
Hey
Right now
Big wave
Nationalism
Huge lava
Great
Logitech G
Nazis next
One will be big
Even bigger
You think people
Big Brother
Sitting back
Probably
I'm just really upset that
Bill Barr isn't he a patriot
We are hope
Oh my God
Oh my gosh how are they
You know he's not
You already do it
Not just like
Yeah of course not Bill course he was
Everyone knew that
Nevermind everybody knew that you acting surprised
I think it was yelling about Bill Gates there from contacts
Text clues that was a hoot
He's going to eat that's what I was thinking
Yeah
I just found it to be so interesting lead
False
Yeah it the yelling
You never cease to
The guys playing ping pong with
Incredibly different racket
It's kind of sad
Because that's a that's like a a
Quick encapsulation of Wyoming
Never going
Is because Alex at least
He comes with the
But at least he's trying
And Owen follows that up with
You know I'm just disappoint
Like what
You got to get some electricity
Yeah it's strange
Yeah I don't know
Almost feels like
Owen would like to work somewhere else eventually
Like you don't want a yellow but eating people
Until you find wherever you're going to be
Right you know
And is going to be nowhere
That's why you should start yelling about eating people now
Yeah go ahead that's your lady
Play buddy Alex
Just trying to equivocate a little bit about bar staff
Spell bars not making a move
Cuz Alex needling I'm a little bit like
He thinks
Because Owen actually believed it
Maybe because I can
Maybe off-air Owens
Complaining about that
Alex's
Bringing
Zacks on air
Owens compose
Sure and what have you but
I think of you might be more bad about this then I think that's on
Who's involved in special corrupt
Mission teens are actually
George Herbert Walker Bush
More affection to us
Now that's a bright spot
Leopards don't change their spots
Bubba
Lexi treasonous tyrant
If you want
I don't want I want Obama to be arrested.
I want more than that
I mean
Never going to happen
Of course not
Better better
We need your financial support
Wow flying
Wow
Anyting
Anything
Can turn into an adventure if you believe in you
Yourself
Have you just talk over Owen enough
If it'll get there wow it just sounds like Owen actually bought his own b******* and Alex is sitting there like he bought bars
Alex is just going like on air I have to
To tell you that there's good things about him off are all explained to you that we all knew this the whole time oh and how old are you
24 stupid there is a Vibe of like
Get over it
We've been here before
We have to shine this up and the best way we can do that is a little polish
Polish the jar says
He's 80% defected to us in Polish
It's labeled meaningless isms
Then we just Shine the boot
It is it is like that old like when you take
High-paying
High powerful job it's like
The first thing that you do is you
Somebody comes it like a marriage
And it's like
If you come in and you just eat a bowl of s*** I think it's from The Wire
And then the next person comes in and you need a bigger bolshit and the next person
Like this is feeling like Owens first big bowl of s***
Where is Eli doubt it
My God I have to do even
This is going to get bigger
I don't know
It's strange
So
This next clip is just
The mask
Alex's
Complaining about
Immigrant populations
Coming to the United States course
Particularly somali-american
Is that because their abortions are powering his president
No it
It's because
He believes that they all act as one
Which is why the globalist
So bring them in
To use them against him
Sound like
Anti-semitic propaganda from the past
Somali people are slave
And the
Bring them in and then
Seattle
Portlander
All Somali
Clarks
They only hire one group
Because the local cheats
Isn't Union
Yep they'll kill you
That's why
Horsham Ollie's
It's a slave class I brought into America feel sorry for him
I should tell you that they're arguing
Airfare
Port work
What nothing
This guy so excited
85% plus of like unitedamerican
The major airlines they're all unionized
I don't know what Alex is talking
About other than just
Explicit xenophobia and racism
Nonsensical
First of all
It's not all Somali people who are working at the airport
And if you screw up on the job they don't take you out and kill you
Furthermore
You know if someone was Somali or not if you didn't talk to them Alex did you ask them
Did you hear an accent snow you just saw what
That I got to go
Calls and they're not
Good
Nothing really all that in
Interesting people want to talk about the bill bar thing
Alex's
Treading Water bet on that but not in an inch
Sing way to sort of like
Yeah you know
How did you guys not know that this was going to happen
So you get the one caller this is really strange I had to look into figure out who this guy was
Tell y'all to go to Gentle Shepherd.
Describing my channel General Shepherd YouTube comments Channel on YouTube and
I'm one of the three content
Provider
Netflix
Scumbags news we need to give me a shout out
A great job with a names
You keep putting it up at a job
Salute your brother-in-law
Thank you so much
Confusing to me to check
I can figure out what it what to do during postalco
This content
YouTube
B o a
Is General Shepard who just repost Alice
Alex's videos yeah
About good on you
Your brother
Epicurious
Because it
Good for Alex
People
A lot of people posting his contact possibly
2 views
Help him as an Advertiser
Strategy
This dude is creating a YouTube channel where he's getting like
50000 views on a video of one of Alex's shows
That's 50,000 people were watching it there instead of banned. Video
That's that is people who are like
You have now given a new place outside of your direct Revenue stream
It seems like Alex
Should be mad about that but I guess it's just all eyes
Yeah and these videos
Alex's doing add pitches
It's still
Alex it's not like
Cuz you can't even monetize it they or their coverage
Achoo
Get paid for it
Lights out
And whatever could trickle-down will eventually like
If anybody watches those videos and is like
Hey this guy sounds really cool
There's a decent chance they'll end up on Alex
Decide eventually
I guess there's some sort of
Spider web
Strategy to it
He's going to be a
Truncated episode
Because
I mean for one I'm
Find
I'm not like
A hundred percent
Emma
This is just not a show that is all that interesting
Alex leaves in the middle of it
Time
That is Owen
In studio and they just
It's like
Bro out
I bet Alex yells at eating Bill Gates sure then
Who doesn't want to that then Alex interviews a guy who did a prank
Remember what it was about I don't I was listening to
Incredibly stupid yeah
Alright
It was waste it was a waste
Just talking about like
The UN
Bill Burr
That was for the topics that were covered soap
In a meaningful way
Wanted to hear about the fly
Wanted to hear about a rationalization for
Here's why
That would be interested
Yeah cuz it would take some creativity you take some bending
Some sort of Matrix bullet time
Bradley why the fly landing on pants doesn't mean he's a demon but it did for Obama
It's just like to have fun
Yeah yeah I know they're going to disappoint at the b*******
It is indeed
Like cuz here's the other
End of the larger problem
With that
Kind of b******* and it's it it example
Which is that
If they ban abortion in the United
Midstates
You think the rich aren't going to be able to get treatments based on abortion elsewhere
They're going to be able to go and get whatever treat
Commence a f****** what
And here in the United States they're going to cut off all federal funding
Make it as impossible as it can be
To even research
All of that s***
And that's it
Only going to hurt her poor people and they know that
And they're just exploiting the insane stuff
Did they fit into those
Idiot you were going to
To be heard vote for them to them destroy and they don't
Because I don't have to deal with the consequence
Except for weird calls about how build bars disappointed
We have one last callers actually on that topic
About Bell bars
Just like this
Three-card Monte game that Alex is playing
Such a bummer
How you doing Alex
I want to talk about
Bar real quick
I even do anything
Iran-Contra holdover
I never expected much remember he's on a Ron Contra holdover exact
Flashlight
Alex has been shining his ship
For so long even though he knew
Yeah like everybody
Just learned about filbar's involvement in the Iran-Contra
Dislike
He was
Hired
Because he has experience
Covering up crimes
What are the things that I find most interesting about the present-day that's so full of like
It's not interesting things that Alex does
Is this back-and-forth on William Barr yeah that is kind of in
Sing To Me the Way
The Alex
Lashes out whenever there's bad news about
Instantly aware
Like this time it's around Contra involvement last time it was bars father being involved with Epstein
Yep
These things because he magically becomes aware of them and then
Forgets whenever bar does not benefit is good it's almost as if
He's trying to
The Punisher
Bar
For doing so as if he had some sort of
Control over bars action
Seems ludicrous to me first of all that it would be a real thing
You think you could sway the Attorney General with f****** s*** on his radio show
Swayed by
Aaj
Hard to imagine
But the way I think of
Is
I think this is his like
Trump is a shity press
He knows that
Nobody.
Doesn't know that who isn't insane
So
He is lashing out
At Bill's Bar
The way that he wishes
Is he could too
Sublimating all of this s*** that he really wants
To say to Trump into
Like finally criticizing somebody and Bill Barr he's always
There you go
Yeah that could be
Yeah probably I might be
Psychoanalysis kind of going on right here but
On the other hand
I've listened to so much
Yeah I just wonder if there will be more clues in terms of the game going back and forth on
Dartboard
I'm interested but also like
It just seems like
Said something good
I'm aware of this
Love I said something that I don't like
Now you
I can just throw up
He's not going any
Now
Here's what it is here's what it is here's what it really is
Here's how you know Alex nude none of this with none of these indictments were going
Going to come down
Whatsoever
Is
He's not at all trying to convince Barta
To do it
You don't like
If he thought that it was actually a possibility
He would go on the show to be like
I'm talking to Bill Barr right now
If you don't do this before the election we're going to do the whole thing you know but on this one he's just like
Yeah man
Yeah yeah you would probably like have one of his weirdo friends
Come on and talk about how they have inside information about the indictments or something
Would come on and
Say some s***
Is a fingerprint took like
So Jordan
Will be back
And again I appreciate everybody begin
Cool
And
Until then
We are on Twitter it's at knowledge underscore fighting I go to bed Jordan net worth
Find a local charity or Bellefontaine your area and I help out
People doing God's work
Exclusive Aunt Gerald Rhonda
Alexandra Thurston color