Damn important
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge
Knowledge fight
What's fight.com
Everybody sit around and talk a little bit about
Alex Jones
Jordan
Yeah
Vibrate spot today is that I realized
Didn't know that
Vaguely aware that it was coming down the line eventually in the future
There's going to be another Pikmin game sure yes I love
Pikmin
Into
Space captain
Around and help you solve puzzles
Lemmings but for
The modern world
Their similarities I see a little bit of lemmings in pick
Especially in the wave at like Lemmings they had like specializations like some kush
Could dig Pikmin or battery differently
Sunken survive fire some could go in the water
I like the idea that they're like 90
2 year olds
Listening to this right now going
Like what though
F***** they talk
Let me see you weren't alive when Lemmings was around
My friend is 19 now they might have been
One or two when the first pick launch title on the game
Long time ago out of that back back in those days
I love those games though they're really fun
Had the series
Play Donkey Kong Country that I'm like I will
Never
Not get
For one of them to come out
And the end of October
The new one comes
Alright I didn't realize it was that
Close
That was like really exciting
It's within my reach almost it's almost there
Just register
Reach out through time and grab it call Eddie page
No no I will not his prediction about the end of the world is wrong you can't know that that's true
And then after that November
The Hyrule Warriors age of calamity
Prequel to breath of the Wild
He comes outside to games I'm actually a
Excited about
In the near future
I hope I hope civilization last long enough
Spell Venus
I hope that Civilization last long enough for me to be
Maybe underwhelmed
To get my expectations up a little too high
Good yeah
Society last long enough for me to make excuses for
My bright spot Dan is yesterday the final scene
Season of kipo and the age of the wonderbeasts
Came out
Nobody I understand that you have no concept of that but
You know how I like Steven Universe been I like those kind of the kipo is of that same vein of like
Oculus positivity will over
Become a goddamn any problem
And the soundtrack
That is so goddamn
Ivory watch this
Kipo
Kipo it's not Kubo and the two strings
Two strings are you completely
Different movie
This is a TV show and it's just
Incredible
Overwhelmed by the amount of words I don't understand
Ideas give me soundtrack.
It's one of the like Ivory watch
Watch the first two seasons
Iowa
I want to say like two or three times
In the background just because
The soundtrack will kick
Can sell so many different grapes
It songs
Like you don't even
I need to watch the show
What sound does Joe
Incredible I would highly recommend watching
Kipo and the age of the one
I'm not positive I'm going to watch it but I'm going to look for that music
But it's so good I'll check into it
So Jordan
Talking about October 12th 2020
That is Monday
This week
Interesting stuff goes on Alex interviews
Congressional candidate
I don't know
Some dumb calls
Buried Within
And we'll get down to business
The song
Ragequeen
Tennis partner thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk wtw
Text Jordan
Fitbit doesn't work
I'm doing
Donors
Jordan
Text Mark Richards exhaust
I'm a policy wonk
Austin proehl
Bike racers actual exhaust
So you didn't try to make an acronym out of that one I gave up
Okay bye-bye quinerly
Ed Austin
Not bop bop bop bop bop
Bob Bob Bob Bob
Bop bop bop
You're not about to walk
I'm a policy wonk shark bump bump bump
Donated on elevator
So first of the Great
420 thank you so much you are now a technocrat
Katrina W thank you so much
Technocrat
I'm a policy wonk
What's the business
Heroin
The great Beast 420 and take as much Katrina.
The both of you
I got your website now
You can do is you can go back to about the 1920s or so is not about it when it was alright
Federal Reserve
In my head is
The great Beast Aleister Crowley
You know just like that thought of
And I have some anxiety issues.
I just kind of wondered
Relax today I don't know how to make a bomb noise but I was just trying
That was more like the daddy shark pop pop pop
It's kind of a bubbler
Anyways
You should take that generosity and give it to a local charity or Bell founded
I'm sorry that I tried to interrupt you there but what I wanted to celebrate with you
Started now to get it
Excited when I throw it to
Yooper cup
Yeah it was actually surprised
You thought that it was like I had something that I was looking like
But instead I was like
Baal Veer told you I am quitting early
Often today
Hey Dad burnout not following through with any B
That unfortunately got lost in the shuffle
Last week was
The life getting in the way was that somebody Bob
He had money bomb scheduled for Wednesday of last weekend
I didn't end up watching
Much of it at all
Because of
I thank you everybody for being so kind
I really appreciate it
Things are good but
Couple people who checked in on it wasn't that great
I find that very easy to bleed
Yeah I'm not surprised by that I assume Harrison
Smith hosted about 20 hours of it
The rest was just special reports
Other than their shows as normal
How off Alex was on for wedding
Extra hour that day maybe I mean I bet you showed to hang out with
With Deanna Lorraine
I'm less interested in the content of it necessarily now they were just like soda moving
Forward something on this episode
That I find also very unsurprising
There's good news happening internationally good news happening nationally a good news happening
Wolfie you belong X I can't tell you about the attack for under 4
Reasons you can probably figure out
Prairie
I just want to thank you all for your prayers your support because
It's been really really rough behind-the-scenes and
T'god
* 2.2
Because I worked out
Hey I got enough money over now
Whatever whatever was motivating the vat like mad I'm not going to reorder supplies or whatever
Whatever he was going
Through has been solved by an inflow of cash
About this inflow cash that I can funnel into my dad's fake business so I can hide it from my eventual
Dual credit for paying your bills are coming up on it Whatever It Is
This is just
This is too transparent
Tell you
I'll tell you about it later.
Definitely not involved with my personal lawsuits including
Family lawsuits as well as all the crimes that I've committed that I'm finally being take
Passport
I will tell you more about what
Satan is doing to me later one day I'll tell you all about this when I'm laughing about it in hindsight about how
It was that I pulled all this off tomorrow or next week
So we'll get to that later
We start off the show
Is big old news
Stewart law big news
Spiel by board
We will actually end up touching on that
He doesn't deal with a blowout that doesn't
Spoiler alert for towards the end of the show
But there's news of foot
And
It's always interesting
Chooses to start shows
Because Blackwell this is what your
Coming out the gate with
That is what he's got
I got so much to cover so many angles I want to take calls I got a bunch of special gas
Play about that next segment
I really think we should just open up
The transmission with this because
You see a semantical headline
Really behind.
This one headline
Does he need a hypothetical
Program
Adam Schiff about
Exodus from California
The topography
Climate
There's an exodus from leftist globalist shy, looting and
And control
Engaged
Touch Belmar
Whatever I don't like how the right keeps pushing people
I'd like you're you're over there
Like we don't have to
To take them I don't want film
No can have a beer you guys take me
Little push push push the shity people over the conservatives
Here's what Boomer is
Bill Maher is a right-wing conservative
Done
Build all these straw man
Off like Bill Maher speaking for the laughs at are there any of the times
The bilmar
Super shity
Marginalized groups
He doesn't remember any of that stuff doesn't that mean that the left
Pete's Islam what you want
Should be murder but I think he's on the radical left
According to the US Census the population has been increasing in California pretty
Consistently with approximately 1% increase this year
You could talk about how like
Increases in population have decreased like ain't going to decrease and increase
But that's
Spell whatever
Alex is misrepresenting the impulse
The people he likes like Joe Rogan
I have they want to flee California to Texas right around the time they start a hundred million dollars Spotify deal
Payless text he was
Lean towards money you can sleep towards a better opportunity
Some folks are doing this overly dramatic I'm leaving
People like Dave Rubin
Some businesses who are looking to take advantage of increasing City sizes around the country
Regions on the ground floor
Of a possible future Metropolis
There's also a lot of talk about normal working people wanting
Believe largely due to covid-19 related employment is
But it's too early to really have concrete data on that
I love the information that you can find comes from anecdotal stories and Facebook post
So we're going to have to wait to have any real idea about it
Much of the people who may actually make them move out of the state or people who work in the Tekken 2
Who may be able to
Continue working
He's decent jobs remotely
The big tech companies that Alex professes
Wouldn't be hurt by this but the normal work
Can people who can't afford to move could be
As well as the people in the area that those people end up moving to since cost-of-living would likely increase
As we previously more sparsely populated areas
Become more dense
Play Popular
This is the conversation that's largely being sensationalize by the right-wing media type so it's no surprise
Steve Belmar getting in on the ACT
And yet again Bill Maher show somehow the most
Important thing for Alex
Discuss level sources and a depth of information that he has four
From years of
Studying that he could be getting into and
Instead of this dump
Show me October 9th rating guide
You'll find that Bill Maher's real time program had about 1.2
23 million views
This is less viewers are pretty much every news program on cable
And honestly not many more viewers than episode of Diners Drive-Ins and Dives
If you only count the 18 to 49 year-old demographic Guy Fieri
Brown's Bill Maher
Who it is
I'd like Alex
Stop over exaggerating the
Isabel bar
He only does that because Bill Barr works as a
Strawman for him
Pretend speak
Express enemies
Reality most people I've ever met who consider themselves of the left
Think Bill Maher
Sucks I'm appreciative of the career transformation
Thierry has had
In terms of public perception
Should like everybody was like a weirdo punchline and then people discovered that he's a f******
Great person and I like sky
God damn it I guess we all loved him now
We get Guy Fieri
You guys can have Bill Maher and if that's the rule now it's all thanks to Shane Torres
The series awesome and then everybody goes old you're right
Damn it man why were we such a
Predicted him are we all believe it yeah cuz of the hair
Mannerisms
Decide what is on the back of the head
It's understandable why optically you be like f*** this
Jimmy Buffett walking down the
Straight you be like
You learn a little bit more about him
I mean he wrote fins
To the left
Fins to the right
He sucks
So does another headline but apparently not in board
The bilmar
I mean
If it was you think that be the first thing you'd cover but it's not
Second thing
Headlines from yesterday
Bombshell says covid restrictions are killing Millions must ah
Fallbrook on Saturday, also broke
Firstly this headline and Alex's reading it's not an article on Infowars
It's just the page of his that has the Sunday show embedded
As a video on his website
I know she's just written the headline that he's now reading which is apparently supported by two hour videos in Southpoint
Which is meaningless
This means
Second neither Infowars nor Gateway pundit broke
The story
They're reporting on an interview that Andrew Neal did with dr. David Navarro who is the World Health Organization special Envoy
Boy on covid-19
The interview was published by the
The Spectator so if anyone gets credit for this story
Eight of them
This isn't the bombshell that Alex is trying
Presented as either
This is an interview that
Easy to take out of context but what doctor Navarro is expressing was that the World Health Organization doesn't
Support quotes
Using the lockdown as your primary control method
He's clear that lockdowns are appropriate when you have
Optical by time to reorganize regroup rebound to resources protect your health workers who are exhaust
Nothing seems that all out of sync
With messaging
There's a reason that there was no need for any talk of lockdown on their other outbreaks empath
Because appropriate action was taken so it never got so bad that lockdowns were needed to buy that time
There isn't a lockdown in the United States put the measures that have been taken were necessary
Because the situation was
Completely bungled
He continues to be
Any white This World Health Organization Envoy didn't say anything that is somehow damn into the UN or World Health Organization
Position on the coronavirus response
It's just something looks close enough to that that Alex
Can create this narrative
And it takes
It's like this is
Keeps hitting this
It's all bad and they're killing everybody
Yeah it's unfortunate it's like
And Kubo and the two strings and you were like I'm
Thrown off by The Barrage of words that I have no context
I keep thinking of
How that must be how right-wing
Feel like all the time
Anytime they read one of those interviews there
Just like I don't understand you but for you you're like Curious you're like okay well let's see what this is all about
What if I killed it
I just want to kill you because I don't understand your word what I imagine
Did the people who
AR
Like in Alex's world
Consumers a straight-up right-wing media bullet
Like they see an article
News Outlet
And there is bewildered as I was hearing those words
Which is the same as any normal person probably listening to Alex
For the first time
A very much
Completely
I don't understand in different realities at all
At all times in the only people who are at all interesting are the ones who are curious about other realities and the ones who aren't
What to kill the rest
Ironman Infowars daywalker
I can I can translate
And here my next clip is just
Titled this show is dumb
I got to certain point where I'm listen to visit like this show stupid
Troublemaker
Liberal
Thomas Jefferson was a liberal
Small government
People want government to micromanage every pass your life
Bubble and go outside and just engage in concert
Scammers
These are
Society
Because there are no ladies in fishnets and
Rabbit out of a hat very innocently
Dakine to whisper
Thank God he doesn't use a teleprompter
About goddamn magician
The UN apparently is admitting
That's how you know they're doing this whole thing
Things are going to go in
Kill people
Distancing in the hell that all the coronavirus death
About how big this is
They're finally admitting
Super good news to cover their butt and say okay
All the social distancing the end of the economy
It's causing a planetary collapse is going to flood the West
Them
Wood
That was supposed
Be there plan originally
The releasing a super bio weapons
Still think vet
Maybe we're actually all day
Maybe we've already died Alex forgot that he said that like their plan is to orderly kill
Forgotten that there's a plan B
Right and now
Not everyone's going to die. The crawl out of the rubble and find George Soros
Now we force their hand if we're going to have to go to vaccines
How do you understand the stakes anymore
We're all going to die except we'll all be fine except they are going to continue killing us but you should give him money
Sure
I'm so China is taking over the sea
Sure all the
The South China Sea
Some folks
For oil
And that's not good
Southern Vietnam
Grabbing
Sending troops in and
AB control
United States
Yes
Steven
How do you save yesterday's ballot
Early career
What are you doing
Can you imagine the u.s. sending in the military
Can you imagine a the u.s. sending in troops and overthrowing a government of its own demo
Democratically elected people in order to install a right-wing dictator who is more positive North American us
I mean even in Alex's current form part of his
Is like worldview does involve like the overthrow the
Like this doesn't make any
No it is fun how we it is fun how we always talk about how a Ron is is like a big butt
Is it big Boogeyman and it's like
We never talked about how it's our fault
Every part I think people do talk about that
There's a more competent people than I could get into about China and they're they're at
I'm not under
You're cutting out of minimizing it I think it's a real life issue
She'll bite
Just funny to hear
Fix a stuff
Doing
Do you think they ever talked about that in those high-level meeting
You know whenever they're talkin to, or something like that
It's just like hey man
Union have your
And job if we didn't overthrow the good government so how about that
How about that don't stop causing problems for us man
I would back.
And conversation probably
I don't think I'm allowed in high-level talk
You got two celebrities they got opinions
Certainly we know that Alec
Complains about every
Left-wing
Or
Non
Crazy right-wing not rhyme right way unless they're talking to an empty
The chair he doesn't want to hear about
Celebrities exactly celebrities metaphorically
Stuck in Love
Punk rock
Pistols Johnny Rotten
Cuz of course I'm voting for Trump cuz he's a rebel
He is obviously has dementia
Wife has Alzheimer's I know what it looks like
Sometimes he's out of his mind
And the media says back
Yeah Johnny Rotten
Medical Care
Adjust
Oh Jolly Rodger
I don't care if Iggy Pop was voting for Jill Stein I just don't care man I just I just think it's
Remarkable
Alex
Is like
Buckhead Johnny Rotten
I just don't
Man
You can't just
Okay this person has one political opinion one time I agree with
So now there are entire thing is heroic
Like the Sex Pistols like there
The biggest song
Anarchy that's one of their biggest songs yes
Super against and doesn't understand
Anarchy in any any form
I imagine if you were in favor of Anna
You might
Take the long
Approach towards voting
A trumpet be like this
Is the best way to
Collapse all
Yeah you might but Alex also is very explicit E8 there an arcade
Chaos
To absent
Rulers
So Alec
I did some weird stuff
When he was covering the fact that Rob had been diagnosed
The covid 11th Place
And now he's trying to like pretend like
USA Today
Chatsworth
Jones says doctors are trying to
Desiderata
Figure of speech
Not the president's okay
In the report I said
Now figure of speech
No it was fascinating here is this
We're trying to
To kill them
The figure of speech I meant it
I meant it
Politically
Okay
So what's my contacts is Alex's version of his own
Coverage of the coronavirus diagnosis
Immediately Alex reported it was probably a false positive test result
What's a globalist
Somehow created in order to provide cover for them to poison Trump
And blame it on covid-19
Exactly when this narrative became unsustainable because Trump went to Walter Reed hospital and is becoming
Clear that claimed it was a false positive was going to be too hard to pull off
Alex shifted the story to be about how the doctors at Walter Reed were either trying to kill Trump or they were so incompetent they're going to do so
Accidentally
However
The story that Alex appeared to land on on his October 4th Show when he was crying on Air Buddies fantasy
Christian Jihad with Greg Reese and John bowne
Was it someone hits
Spray Trump with a weaponized version of the coronavirus in an attempt to kill him
Of course Trump didn't die so all of that hysterical not that much of a site
Disappointed look
Silly
His behavior
Control
His audience has already forgotten all that b******* that he said of his previous
Britannia was looking at the issue from Alside
He wasn't he was trying to say
Sensationalizing story in the great to the greatest
Except possible in way the prophet is busy
It's really dumb and even Alex
Poconos that
I wonder if he was rooting
You think I think that would solve a lot of his problem
Zip Trump died like
So many problems would actually just float away and so many opportunities
Opportunities would appear for
He's the guy who
Who's f******
Fighting the people who killed the president
It creates a new set of problems
If you're Alex
You know like it does solve some problems
But the way in which
His rhetoric is work
Yeah I get creates an expectation of the audio
Chance of you getting on a horse
And leading a charge
If you don't do that you're going to lose
At least
Some considerable portion of those people
You said that if
See if there was
Any positive diagnosis and then there wasn't he was just like
Killerman even that wasn't enough for them to be like okay well let's do something because it wasn't
Well they sprayed him in the face with it covid
Oops a stud
He's just that good it's like
It's like Trump so you can't kill a bull moose
Mobile man
What is it going to take for these guys to just
Die
We just let them denying there was a problem you should deny the medical care I think we should
Never have allowed them
Your doctors
Cuz their doctors are trying to kill him once just tell the right the doctors are trying to kill all the Senators and then if they already do believe
Next clip I find
Really strain
Especially in light of the revelations
The New York Times
Released about their analysis of Trump's tax returns
Sure sure
If I were Alex I just stay away from
Territory like this
No taxes this year or last
Don't make what professional baseball play
Air Max
Operation
In boats
Taxes
Call restaurant
65%
Grand
Supposedly
No it is more than Jeff Bezos
Enterprise blacklivesmatter $400
Just like Tim Cook
Why even go into this territory it's
Underbelly of very clear like
12 pesos
He doesn't pay taxes cuz he's evil any funds black lives matter
Trump doesn't pay taxes
Cuz cuz he's super smart and funds conservatives
Actually he doesn't even do that he creates fake universities and
Steals their money
That's why he's smart and a good
President
Seems like an unnecessary gripe
I have about a certificate
To have about Bezos fiber it's a bad one for him to talk
That's what I mean
Unnecessary for Alec
Yeah yeah seems like
Just go ahead and drop your complaints about their tax payment
Man it's just so unfair that they can
Just refused to cede ground
Even though
8-bit they're meaningless nonsense
Just like yeah I'm going to be pissed at Bezos for not paying tax
Pictures of prison
Doesn't it I think
He's got but I really mad at Bezos
Black lives matter
It's
Sort of a descending
Charade to the bottom
Is matter about make it more presentable complaining
Facade
So Alex got a use got a little bee in his Bonnet about about antifa
Here's a story
Out of Germany
He tries to make connected
Data is not
Police radar
House in Berlin
Infowars Europe
Queen
Match.com
Folsom Aquatic
German MP
The capital
Summoned
Reinforces around Europe
This was not an a
Antifa Builder
No
By building recently
For decades enforcement
Being reinforced
I'm sure actually whoever wrote this is probably Dan Lyman
Alex doesn't know anything she's just reading this
Anyway this is about an anarcho queer feminist housing project in Berlin called liebig 34
The building space foreclosure in 2008 where Panos purchased and the residents were offered a 10-year lease at really good rate
To continue that same housing project
This week's ended
In 2018 and by this point I guess the owners of change their mind
And I didn't want to extend the lease agreement into the future
The residents didn't want to leave so they filed some lawsuits and in June
The abyss year 2020 the German courts
They ruled that the owner had the right to
The tenant
But they couldn't be removed from the premises immediately
Didn't want
Believe still and they continued squatting
Just came to a head earlier this month when police were called to clear out the building
This building didn't mean a lot to a lot of people and dust the idea of it being cleared and no longer existing as this project or something.
Resonated widely
He does make some sense but other anarchist
Some supporters from around places
Outside of Berlin
Felt drawn to
The common protests against the eviction
That has nothing to do with antifa or George Soros or the globalist
This is honestly pretty simple
Tissue that surrounds at an Arco queer feminist housing project in Berlin
Now this is lying about it to try and make it
Some kind of a culture War bulshit
Nonsense
I don't know
I just
OU
Check this out
Some landlords are great and they're definitely not going to ruin it and I'm sure that their rent prices will
Yeah I think
Prague
Play a large part of the story
Is that they had a really good 10-year rate
Valuable real estate
It sucks
Because everything I can tell it to
Seemed like that was something that was really cool and meant a lot to a lot of folks
Piano
It sucks it's something like that.
That existed for so long
Gets swallowed up in the name of probably
A cleaner looking building in better rent
Rate
It sucks to that like
No
Someone
Buying the building and offering 10-year leases 10 years ago is really cool
Happening
Alexandra wants to complain about Brian
Stelter
What's new
Respect
Stelter
Little flashcards for kids
That's a seal
Papi
Pedophile
Psychotic
Still not called chicken wire
Holy crap you know women just run from him
I want the video still walking
Hollywood
English weird crazy smile
You just see people like
Who's this
Look
What
Partying away for brides Cafe
I'm just like doing a little smooth dance backwards analysis
Surveillance tape
Are you watching that
Do you have the one where Reagan gets paid
That I would like to know
This is
Really silly and stupid
And honestly I was getting to point
We're like
Zizek
All right there's no reason for us to really play this on the show Alex talks about Brian stelter looking creepy all the time
The reason I did was
Provide an opportunity to say something
Sing did I've been
Thinking for a long time and I haven't really
Brought to the show they should have named
The clown It
Yes
Thank you I can move on
I don't think that
Like people realize
How much I have to just
Ignore
In order to make our show the CIA
If I wanted to I could be so much worse to Alex
I was just lost in thought while I Was preparing
Man I'm pretty generous
There's so much racist and horrible s*** that I just have to turn away cuz it's like well we've already made
Yeah over and over and over again
It does seem like
We will face consequences
This for being redundant
And like
Boring about
Pointing out the
The same thing over and over and over again
Where is he gets rewarded
Non-Stop
That's another one of those
Unfairness
This is Stewart's trying to create something
Yeah it works in his favor and we just kind of have to accept
And this one guy is a little off base
Basically
Jeremy 1938
You had the brown shirts
Jewish man
And the number of days
You know I had to question that when we went back and chest
We don't know that yet
Profoundly offensive with this collars
Suggesting for
Wow number of reasons off
Uncountable
Man
Bill Maher Keith Olbermann
You take them
I can't tell you how
God damn excited the right-wing is the Keith Overman started a YouTube channel
I've seen
So much anger
About it buddy
That kind of anger.
It's the same thing like
Complaining about Hillary Clinton
It's like what Alex loves
My sweet
Spa this is this is where I belonged complain about Keith Overman talk about baseball
I can
Complained about his YouTube channel
Great
Oh my God
So get ready for that you're ready for
Keith Olbermann to piss Alex off a whole bunch
Politics in the 90s
Just gold
Just disappear like Hillary gone I don't care about your podcast you have nothing valuable to say get the
The f*** out of here
People ruin get the f*** out of here Bill Maher get the f***
Out of here
I don't know I think I think that you might be
I mean certainly I want to see D Pilgrim at any more probably does have a lot to offer in terms of insight
Keith Olbermann the bill
Delmar Maybe
Just go
Or be more aware of the ways in which
Basically your content
Exist to anger right-wingers in a way that profits right
It's not angering them in a way that's actually trolling them more like
Anything it's just
It's basically creating material that they can respond to
Create
False versions of argument
Did they can pretend to be on the right side up
Only a nutmeg
No there's no positive thing that they do that counteracts Howard - there
Present I'm sure someone likes
Steve Overman
I have a hard time disagreeing with you
Blister going to destroy everything right
But maybe not maybe not
American Republic
Myself
Leben dog in the whole time we've been warning others
We've been preparing
Flat-footed
Keeping us all in defense
Ready for this
What about Plan B got a good shot at beating them
What about Plan B
We were already dead a few weeks
Plan B was about to happen because you ruined playing that we might
We might have a chance of beating plan a we're already packed
Plan B
There's a second
Everyone dies why is incoherent a solid strategy
You know
Like that is amazing to me that there is there is like
Let's
Why
Try and use language
Clarify think it's because a lot of this is emotional Alex's like connecting with the listeners on an emotional fear less
That's true
Emotions aren't always
Rational Oklahoma
Whatever you feel
Resume with Alex even if he's contradicting
Himself all the time
Both of them
You know he made up because they're terrible and would never work
Exactly
Man speaking of emotions
I think Alex is changes
Within the span
20 seconds
In a way that kind of terrified
Hi how are you
Yamini
Looking good I mean I know that they are really scared what
Doing and you can just
The fear in their eyes
Sounds optimistic
That's great
Hey how you doing Alex
About to be angry
Feeling optimistic
About my room
Signs point to yes this color plugs Alex's iodine
And I was going to get in unplugging that iodine
Very family-friendly way
I don Mexican
Virility
OSHA 10 exactly what he's doing
I was being
15/16
Well I'm 15 years old again what the hell
Oh yeah
Alex the globalists are going to kill everybody
Your boners don't matter makes you
You f***** good anyways plan-b we're all going to die but try some of my iodine I can't believe this
Exactly what I was being so
Sincere when you said when you said it was
The family so here's what I was
Taking him to accidentally say like
And then I was like I wouldn't it be funny if he was like
Doesn't make any f****** sense
Yep
Great news show
You're dumb
Brian stelter's evil is a pedophile but if you take iodine you got a big old dick
And Alex has to be aware that like children are listening cuz he constantly says it's a family show in like 13 year olds
Called in and he is talking about his dick
What is trying to sell iodine to thirteen-year-olds I guess they don't need it
13 boners for no reason you don't need iodide
You had iodine on top of that you have non-stop boner but too much
Just enough so I jump away from that
Topic
Alex
Listen to new covid
Conspiracy
Which I think is
Going to be probably
I really think that
We don't know if the virus
Exist at all
Family members of
Family members that got released
At the end and also
Some of them actually almost
We already seen this virus
Complete everybody family
Three of them died six years ago
Hospitals that were full of dead bodies
Meniere's
6 years ago 2040
Team okay
Okay are you telling me that covid both does not exist
And also has been around for a long time killed three of Alex's family members 6 years ago
Alright no
Yeah I find this to be a nun so
Sustainable level of
Conspiracy
That's insane
Yeah that's just
It doesn't exist anymore but it did in the past
When my relative got sick in 2018
What is he could have said something else
I just
You've proven Nothing by telling me that your family member got sick
2 years ago
I just did I just feel like
We don't even have any evidence covid
Still around
Water
We probably isn't though really I think I don't know how do I think about it
Tierpoint
But you made before I think that's already retrograded out completely I don't think it exists
Pneumonia
They're not
Everything is covered. Bless you brother
So Alex
You can't you can't act that way when I call there's like I don't think covid even exist anymore and I'll expect absolutely
Gladiator protein
This you just did you send that to a caller he literally just said that
You also said that it never existed
You also said many did six years ago
In the past
Sprite you said that
Just then that they're not even counting flu deaths
So what year
You're saying then to that color is
You're dumb family could have died of the f******
Flute Maybe
Let's go
Maybe the pass
Exist anymore
To also
I have is alright alright
You win another call her here
Did you know that the CDC straighten out the yard
Sonogram and take away the tax
Swansea 3
Explain that Alex
Yeah I do know that when the caller said the
The CDC is traded on the stock market
Do you think that's true
Man isn't it a branch of the
The federal government
I suppose if the federal government is
Is traded on the stock market is some sort of bond yields do I know that I have six years in the state department
The CDC is
It's created using the initial CDC but it's not the Centers for Disease Control
That's just be stock ticker abbreviation for victory Capital portfolio fund called Victor
Shares us
EQ
Income enhanced volatility
You can check out Victory funds website and see that it's a collection of Holdings including some
Comparison Coca-Cola Verizon General Bells Etc
The people can invest
I don't know why the abbreviation is CDC but I also couldn't
Explain a ton of other stock ticker abbreviation
I can't see those at the Centers for Disease
Control is not a company
On the stock market
Furthermore
CDC Foundation does it not for
For-profit
I'm going to go out on a limb here
And I'm going to say if your
Part
Of the federal
Maybe you don't
Get 501c
C3 status
That's just what I'm going to go out there and say
I think the
You certainly don't have
An IPO
We've decided
Privatized
Jesus that we will privatize the CBC probably
Just imagine the CDC on the investor
Call
They're like guys covid stats bad
Weaver we've cured exactly 15 people today so it's been a good day it's 30,000 of Tide but you know that
We can't cure everybody
So Alex touches back on the story out of Germany
German police raid happy book Swan House in Berlin kitchen say dramatic video Seether
Dramatic video
Police raid Squad house
Exclusive
Infowars video
I'm watching this dishes
All that b******* but the video that he has on his website that is like
Actually of the police
It's from Reuters Twitter account
Exclusive now they only in Forza
Xclusive Ace
Dan Lyman
Interviewing a hard right politician
Germany outside
Of the house
Everything has gone down in the US
6/8 minute video interview is
His butt all the footage of the actual stuff
Is there stuff that they've take
Taken from other outlets
And now they're claiming is an
An exclusive
Seems like a pattern
Yeah give me the pattern of Alex's
And then also the
Forgetting about Plan B
The murdering everybody that the globe has is going to do that too
I do like how the mainstream media is filled with lies
But also when they get good content it's an Infowars
I do I do appreciate that
Sucks I drunk by global exclusively
What you going to do
Whose caller next caller is I don't even care about what they were saying but
Anderson happens during this call that Alex
Should not be engaging in
Bartolotta
The truth have a
When your
Website is compared
As being similar to Jim Fetters website
You shouldn't agree with that especially when you're engaged
Then a lawsuit
Got lost a lawsuit about it
Haven't you do everything in your power not like that guy I don't know him I have no involvement with him
When friends are down that's when you know
That's that's what's going on
I swear that you got to you got to step up
I'm pretty sure he's just saying absolutely to any like
Just
Just the Cadence of the end of a sentence
You got it agree with you
Love it
This episode was around the 12th
I am that was the day of
The first hearing for Amy Coney Barrett
Supreme
Court nomination
Alex plays her opening statement
And I got it I got to say like I mean obviously I'm against her nomination but like
Beaver Charming open
Obvious attempt
Set jokes
Horrible
A personable they're Charming
Who's talking about how I'm
I'm used to being in a group of nine cuz my family we have seven kids
You know one of my kids when we adopted them
They were they wouldn't be able to talk about it
Everything is great now and I assure you they can talk
You don't like that kind of
Family style focal whatever
Group I only know this.
I only know this because Alex
Play that on the show
This was really funny
Because I found it to be incredibly on offense
And only made Amy Coney Barrett look
And I am against her being on the Supreme Court
Response after he came back from break
After playing
The Jurupa
Statement
Let's go ahead and take a call
Yes
That's a good fish
About 8
An actual hearing
It should be boring
Yes she isn't saying insanely Authority
Talk crazy like Trump so I'll kind of bored
This is a real like everybody
The debate was really embarrassing because Trump was a lunatic
And then all of that
I find the Supreme Court hearings Apple watch
Watched some of that
To be the most embarrassing
Game of
Pretend
These are all Adele
These are all adults are all doing all of this s*** that they know means nothing
Knowing that there is Meaningful stuff they could do and instead they're participating
It is
Is childish
It is kind of
Strange
Enough to say that it's okay or should be this way
I think that's all that different than a lot of the other Khan
Information hearing that I've seen it
Totally like I think that there's a lot of dodging questions
Oh no that the amount of stuff that she's just like
I'm not going to answer and everybody's like well
I guess that means you get to be on the Supreme Court there's a lot of like
What appears to be going through the motions
Does suck
It is frustrating
I would say that like
It's not embarrassing as much as it is kind of scary
Embarrassing
It also upset
Sure
The Supreme Court at least like
I can see obviously isn't it
Just yelling
Complete nonsense
Scary
Bilberries
Do Boris carry Trump is embarrassing
Geberit is scary
Because like I said I just listened to the bit that was on Alex's show at
Decent
Because of the
Like
That's not a force
Worst joke you know how to make yourself sound like a pretty
Decent family
And Alex can't handle the idea that like
The person who would
Support all of the policies that you want
He's trying to get through the confirmation she can't act crazy there are you telling me that I have to
Watch her go through a confirmation without her foaming at the mouth the entire time
I want her
To defend drinking beer while she's sexually assaulting someone in the room why does she have to say about
Alberta
Send children another call and just call her I think he's pretty bright on although I think
You got my wife
Actually yeah
Changed her mind she's been listening to
Munchies
Petrified to be honest with you what's going on and all these other nations
And she's worried it's coming here and she's asked
The troops from China in
Coloring Catch-22 let's go to Canada I said no you don't want to go to Canada
Let's go to
Let's get out of here and I'm like this is the last
I don't think the last battle part is necessarily right on but like
By my wife has started listening to your G
She's terrified
Starting to like Alex
You know I need his help figuring out how to not be scared anymore
I'm going to have to take that idea because I too want a giant
It's it's kind of sad
It really makes me
Bummed I do I I do like
Alex should hear that and be like
The general vibe
Exactly right
So I told you there's a Congressional candidate
And that is
Our old pal
Laura Loomer
Call Laura Loomer is here from her campaign headquarters in Palm Beach Florida
Why was she sitting on the ground pull show.
Big Sky problems what a shot
And say
If you have any problem that can be described as
Big
Big Sky problem
You shouldn't be
You should be at least able to figure out Skype
If you want to be
I think Alex is really just blaming her
For his own issues
Headline from Florida politics
This is from October 5th
Lois Frankel nearly doubling Laurel Uber support in new ct21 survey
If you read through the article you find at the newest poll the disc
Bloomers running in his Frankel ahead 61
Luminate surprisingly well in the primary though but there's a lot of factors
Considerate
The first is that her general election
Frankel ran unopposed last cycle
The second is that the district has equipped 17-point
Five-point registration Advantage for Democrats over Republicans
People have a party affiliation it's a deeply democratic
The third factor is that there were
6 people running in the GOP Primary
Seriously
Laura Loomer was somebody who had some name recognition and ability to fundraise with her publicity stunt
Which set are ahead of the other five candidates
None of them really had much of a chance of winning the general election
No matter how ReSound ugly they might have won the Primary
Standard Infowars adjacent Senate run
This was never about winning it was about appearing like winning was even
Impossible
Lemon grifting along the way
Well pushing hateful and bigoted rhetoric further into the mainstream
I will say that Laura better figure I would have grieved that you wants
Run after
She loses the race will be
Now
Because if she doesn't
She's going to end up like Deanna Lorraine hosting an evening show on Infowars
In a couple months
Yeah that's
It's still
Insane
Crying because of
Infowars think it's amazing that
When she won the Primary there should have been like two journalists who were like okay
Countdown to when we catch her committing fraud
Because I I would bet fifty bucks
Right now that you if you looked into her find a
If she has committed fraud already I bet you wouldn't even have to like
Know you know what you don't have me as a story there's so many ways for her to lose
I don't mean that as a story I mean like
Play zeze
Let's do something about campaign-finance fraud 41
Sure
Yeah I just another one
Omar Navarro
That guy who said Auntie Maxine Waters Alaska kept typing on
No
That's true
Who's going on to
To bigger and better things
In the in the bad Infowars primary
Candidate run
Alex is doing way better off back in like 2009 when he was having state
Representatives in state senate members on
Because
Thousands of them across the country could probably find some of them
Instead of these
Springe as candidates who are not even
Got to
Honestly
I don't even care about that
61 to 33 Pole
That loomer's down here she's just going to end up saying
Fake
Of course my internal polling says I'm up course
A normal
Like middle-of-the-road Republican
Probably couldn't win that District right now
Based on the Democrats win
17.5 Point Etheridge registration advantage
Like
You have
If you want to win that is a Republican
And I just don't
I don't care about her internal polling
He's not going to win
Even after she goes with him
Epinephrine
Somehow there are
Nope
Places to
Pass a democratic
Ballot with 97% of the vote
Ballot now so
Do you got this pool that sang 6133 Bloomers down
Boomer says that her internal polling
Gore has her up
Alex knows where the real numbers
Do the one they're searching how to vote Republican
Democratic Google searches
These are the type of real numbers that show real engagement
You don't win this election fraud
I committed voter fraud
Set up the precondition that if she loses
Probably stolen election
And also
That is such a weird idea
That people are Googling how to vote Republican twice as much as Democrat
And that's some kind of an indication of
So what that is I that really threw me for a loop
This was a headline in Glenn Beck's
Website
The Blaze great that apparently
More people are Googling how to vote Republican then
How to vote Democrat
Sure
I would say I don't know what that means
I would say
Ain't that one possible interpretation
Maybe that you have not done a good job of Ed
Educating your voters on how to
What is it mean like what
Someone trying to
To figure out
If they Google the word
How to vote
Do you know you just vote for the Republican
Guess what there may be with theirs
Thinking is primary register as a Republican
I understand that it may be except
Search however I would also argue that many of the words that people are searching for are not
The questions that they're looking to actually
And that's what I'm wrestling with two
Like trying to register
That's possible
Whatever it is I don't think Republic I don't think people searching how to vote Republican or how to vote Democrat
Indication
Of life
Final vote
It's more confusion
Yeah it's certainly confusing and it's not proof that Laura Loomer is going to win or its voter fraud
I'll guarantee that
Alex likes to portray himself as like an
Truth-teller he's the news
The fake news on the other hand they're all liars Peach and they have liberal bias because they're all liberal right
They're all globalist
And what have you
And this is like an important
Straight down the middle new show
2800 in the primary so you could give another 2,800
Floor lamp
People want to win this is how we do it
Straight down the middle news
I'm at donate to Laura Loomer
Campaign
I would I would like
I would like
Exactly how much it
Did you donate
2800 probably dead
Like there's an impotence
But this is Advil
Anything other
Then the worst version of what he accuses all the other news media of being
Can you imagine
Wolf Blitzer just just coming out in like I'm going to donate to 2802
To bring my
A personal account out of here
So I can say as a independent
Neutral journalist
I'm giving 2802 Bernie Sanders
So ridiculous
She wants to inject
The real issue
Into the mainstream
Right
There's no one talking about the stuff that actually matter thankfully Alex's a brave enough
Guy to have her on
And she's brave enough
To talk about what matters
Country
Issue with Law and Order and
Horse I have to reiterate
It's on your program
We'll talk about it
Joe Biden and Kamala Harris
I don't want to because their entire camp
Campaign
Is a dog whistle to the radical left
I know you just grab your phone cuz you're trying to see if it does
Okay
I'm wondering why it doesn't
Cuz anybody could have said that up as a redirect yourself
Anybody could have done that any proof that Joe Biden bought
Fifa.com
Explain to me why is a non-existent organization
Bought antifa.com
Why would I not talk about this
Oh my God
They did
They did last by
The stupid store
That would be a smart thing to do
Thanks for really focusing Law & Order this is what matters
Is Joe Biden's website
Akram antifa.com
God
Laura is
Keeping us but let me ask you this question
How would it make sense for
Antifa
Medical leftist organization hell-bent on destroying the world
Right to mess things up by making their website
About
Touro College
Team strange what does seem strange right
And it seems like
Alex's whole game is supposed to be that like
The reason that Joe Biden doesn't say
Tear down Christianity and white people need to go to Camp is because
He's trying to keep it hush in the same reason why I like people who
You are left
Protesters in such they're not excited about Joe Biden
I keep that under right right by then and all these left-wing protesters they're working together
The essential shell game that needs to be played is it a pretend that they're not right
People f**** it up by redirecting antifa.com to Joe Biden's website now I feel like we're dealing with
An enemy that is
Is very
Very stupid
We're used to that with Alex only able to think as well as
1 Alex Jones
In terms
The planning something
Joe Biden
Even if Joe B yeah even if Joe Biden is like running antifa
Antifa.com
Obviously
Here's the thing
Laura
And Alex
And all of the
The people in this world
Are not very good at the
They're not very I mean I don't know if maybe they are smart in their ways
But they're not very good researchers or they're not very good
Snow so whenever they solve a mystery
Like antifa.com redirect
Two Joe Biden's website
They
Include that Joe Biden is running a full or empty
Supporting or whatever
And then that becomes the mystery was
We found the solution
I found the answer
And that means mystery must be what
Caters to all this s*** up
Nancy
Drew you would really
Crush Laura Loomer in a Republican
Really be able to solve a lot more B
Conclusion and now you're writing a story
Very stupid
Speaking stupid
I respect this
On some level
But this isn't good
I mean I respected in terms of
Clear wiggle room with it
Okay alright Laura wants to make one
Joyce Bonner record
To say
A lot of people you shouldn't
Going to be really good
American group of men and women we probably women is a good wholesome group
Where is clear on that
It seems like a really easy to take something like that and make
A damning
Political ad
See now here's
Here's where we
We get into why their plan for what Joe Biden
Is doing is so stupid because that is
Their plan
Understand
Like oh yeah you should be doing
You should be creating a separation between you and the proud boys disavowing any interest even though you of course
Love them dearly
That what you separate yourself from the more extremist wing of the party
And you get to say like what will I still condemn violence and all that s***
That would be smart
Sing you love the proud boys is the equivalent of
Jill Biden
Antifa.com your plans are dumber than
Y'all got it's the equivalent of Joe Biden
Being out
On the streets with a balaclava in a multi-functional absolute
Just cut it out
Joined p**** Riot yeah that's where we're at
The character like the character
Picture of
A left-wing
Antifa protesters
So stupid
In the same way that I appreciate that Laura's being clear
About her
Connection with the proud boys and support for them
I hate black people I want to be very clear about this
She also is very clear about what you will do if alive
Clarity
Hate everything else
Inoculation
Yeah I'm not taking the vaccine
Search me
Cuz I know you going to call me as a witness on censorship
You are going to be my spy
Alex and you are going to testify
Defy you and Gavin McInnes and Milo
Goldie
Alex okay
That is quite a lot
Don't think Alex will be played by
By Jimmy Stewart
This remake
I think it's going to happen
This is a bad lesson
Bye bye man
I'm all for it send them in there
Breaking a fire
I think that list is a terrible list of bigger
And Weirdos
Publicity stunt
It is very strange to me that like
Two of them are Canadian
Two of them are British citizen
There's a heavy overlap of
I don't think it means anything
I mean it it does kind of suggest
Just do that
Americans are allowed to say whatever they want
There is no censorship
I'm choosing people not from here
Well Laura and Alex
Sure sure there's a to American British people into Canadian
If you will of all white bigots
Yes yeah there we go
So Alex gets
Complaining here this next clip
About how like
Eso's
Supplement
That's right
But they're not
It's not like he's selling
AccuWeather are prevention covid
But then again
If you take the stuff that he has
You can't get viruses
Does mi Freedom into Funland
It's essential
Literally
Cannot dive you have high levels of that providers
If you haven't watched a sense of virus causes cancer
Can replicate in the nuclei in
Vitamin D3
That seems like a real problem
That cliff
Is
I mean
He's saying
Fatty cells
Vitamin
You can't die from a virus
If you have those vitamins
The wood
Indicate that he's selling his supplements as a prevention of death
Viviparous
It does seem like a big fault in our legal system if you can just split infinitive and get around all of that lie
I didn't say it was a cute guy just said that sure
I sell them
I didn't say that I sold cure
Now I see I separated it
I put it in between the two so now it's fine
Do I do think I'm in vitamins and minerals are in pork
The human bodies
I think it would Alex
Does mixing up
Here in a very intentional and manipulative way
Is
The fact that
Vitamin deficiency can make you more susceptible to
That does not mean
That if you have all the vitamins you need it's impossible to get sick
Also if it's different
You don't get to that you don't get to sleep after you did something right
You don't get to do that
Is trying to kill all the
So he doesn't get to do anything right
He doesn't get to save it all everybody was surprised that fauci threats out you need vitamins
You don't get that
Try to kill you but using Alex
Needs to say something like that
Because he
You painted this picture of fauci as the guy was trying
Kill Everybody
She does say something like
Vitamins are in
Like
Essential part of your diet they do help you stay healthier
Alex
Well s***
If people see that and I don't explain it
They think I'm a liar
3DS to come up with
It's not even then it doesn't make sense if he's trying to kill everyone and then he confirms what
Alex says
That suggests
To me that would Alex is saying will kill everyone
Seems Seems like
Hit that. It's hard to get away from
Laura has some theories about to have a left one
How to kill all the old people
License
Schwan's older people
How to dye a lot of
The time because they
Are more conservative
Everything about this
Aspirus has
Inherently political
Sounds exciting
Open pig
I came back from break cuz I wanted to hear what this thing that was big that Alex
Came up with was
I don't know if I did
Get that but
Here is Lori explaining
A little more
He senior rhetoric
Perforating through
It's the beginning of this year
With the okay Boomer memes
Hatred or disdain for
Maleficent
Don't bring a Bill Ayers on your show it's just an embarrassment for your career
So good
Like okay so the okay Boomer meme was the first Salvo in the war against the elderly
Do you not want to talk about all of the Republican elected politician
Sewer like let the old people die so the economy can stay open
Do you think that's
Less Insidious not okay Boomer okay lieutenant governor is coming out and saying that the older
Sacrifice their lives in order for the economy keep running
That's not
Wanting to kill old peep
People dance that's inspiring old people to die for us
You've had a good run old people
Okay Boomer
What
Deck design
Laura you have terrible stupid takes based on nothing and we go
Okay Boomer because
Nothing you say means anything
That is exactly the same as the lieutenant governor of a state
Sayings
Kill all those people for money
One last clip here and I promise
This is Alex being forced to deal with the fact
Actor that Trump
Got a stem cell related covid-19
And like I said I'm positive that Alex would rather not
Talk about this but
Unfortunately
After Laurel leaves
He takes more call
Call Lou bad idea
Thanks for holding
Hey Alex my main thing was there now starting to talk about
Cure for covid
Wi-38 is in there witches aborted
Now they are complaining about it which it's
Spinning our pet
Pepsi
Are Doritos arvac
Maxine's and now the media is
Mustang turns their evilness and pointed at you
Story is true
I'm going to have to do more research on it but where was all the coverage on this
Back in the day and I am so
Serious about it there is no
Explanation on how serious I am about this
Why do you cover the shower
Therapeutic
One of the things he's promoting uses fetal cells
Absolutely
No
I think you just exactly where I'm at now
No no no no no
No no
Eyewear but we got one point one point
If you guys don't like abortions
And you would bringing them outright your dumb f****** president would be death well
Well this is probably doesn't do anything but that's the point
Subway in a little bit glad when we talked about this on the last episode
You know about the relation to fetal cells
There are other ways that stem cells
Are are
Like there are cell lines and stuff like
One thing I was reading is active research
This treatment was involved in
Comes from a cell line
From
Fetal cells
Yeah yeah it's it's not like
This is all running on
Abortions are whatever
Well some of that I mean some of the cultures and stuff that we used all
Originate with one black woman in the in the 50s
He's or whatever so I didn't get any compensation
Ignition for it until recently
Stem cell research
Does Don Edwards involve Sara Lee
I think the point
Is really
Important here is
People don't
Have a problem
With the treatment
But have a problem
With the fact that you don't have a problem with that
Because if you if you say that now oh now they're all mad about it
You're just saying that nothing you believe means
Think so just say nothing you believe means any
Course not.
I don't have a problem
With stem cell research
I don't like
But if Trump
Is sick
And he uses a treatment
That relies on some stem cell research
I don't have a problem
Alex should
Alex
Should
It's just
That's the disconnected it doesn't it's not fair for them to be like oh now the left
He's mad about
No I don't think I've seen anybody
Appointed like
Hey isn't it weird
That you guys are mad about this stuff but not now
Guys
Right now
On the same day that you were saying now the left is all mad about abortions or whatever
You are trying to
Confirm a Supreme Court Justice
2 hour
Blow the very process by which many of these therapies are
Created
Zoosk
Uart
Just just say you want
Just say you're racist
Just say that you're a bigot that's what it is just figure of fun
F****** bigot or whatever that anger
Really does represent bike
A big part of what this whole
Cool thing is
That one other callers talking about his wife listening to Alex
And she got really
Scared
Translate it eventually into what this caller
Is representing and that is
Peoria
They just you get in with
Sphere
And then it gets changed into anger against the people Alex wants you to be angry about
Even though none of this stuff makes any sense
Do you actually look at what's up
Being sad
Also I mean like
This
Pharmaceutical company that made this treatment to the regeneron Pharmaceuticals
Like they were awarded a 450 million dollar contract by Trump's government
My back in July to research treatment
That was very clearly built on stem cell
Stop like it's not like
Trump didn't not know that was maybe he did not like you might not know everything
He doesn't know any
Trying to pretend videos no like involvement in any of those to go fuc
Yourself busy
It's so
Weak but the
You just
It's so weak
He should just not talk about it
But he can't cuz he accidentally took this called
The best you can come up with his Dad
And it is
Infuriating
The meaningless
That's it
Just soap
It's so brazen
It's just like
Why why
Why bother with the lies if you're going to be that Brazen about how stupid
Like that you can
You can't not see through this
No
I think
Can't if you're looking at
Critically but if you're looking at it emotionally and experiencing it emotionally
Think it might be tough
See-through and I think that's
What
We'll stay in the fold
So we're covered we come to the end of this episode Jordan
And
I think
Things that I'd like to
Alex
Be more careful when he takes calls
And Laura Loomer is gone
And she's going to make plenty of money Allah
I guess
You know we
Yeah
Thoughts other than
We do have website.com
Roseau on
Indeed we are on Twitter that Niles right now go to bed Jordan divided on Facebook
You can write his own music down like to find a local charity or bail Fund in your area
Dzx Clark I'm Daryl rundus
I'm a magician but I'm not like one of those fun magician
Alex
First in color with huge fan I love your work