Air Jordan sweat it
I have great respect for knowledge b b
Money
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Everybody was making out with Alex
Jojo
Jordan Jordan
What's up his novelty beverages that I have in front of me as a little
Call Dora Bora Bora Bora no free rides
I got this
Novelty beverage
The Seltzer here
To attempt
From Imani
Ewok
They sent me
Deep South
They're from here on out they sent me a six-pack of a sampler of the dram
Another listener Valerie brought to my attention way back
I wasn't able to order it from the website
Pissed off
Anyway I'm already sending me these G
And they're fantastic
I'd had one of them before the black
Cardamom
One I actually had when I came over your house for dinner
Like maybe a year or two ago
Are good I've not given specific
QuickScores that I'm the Exeter little bit more complicated
G Thang
Thank you
Evolved
Shelters
Set me another tip on this Aura Bora
I'll just another brand that apparently has some interest
Sing flavors
And I've tried their basil Berry
And watermelon peperomia
I knows we're both
Great
I'm finding that watermelon and mint in a Seltzer really is a complimentary flavor that you would not expect
Yeah you because it provides like a little bright
2 a.m.
Stats
Vu almost
The bubbles were
Kind of take away from the water May
Flavor
Train strawberries really good
Strawberries
It's a great flavor butts
Sometimes it can be a little bit
Sweet Basil comes in like a really
Traxxas
Hazel is
Hard flavored for me to think about
Yeah
It's not too basily don't worry about it
All right but I have here the first
That's risky haha
Cactus rose
I know that Rose and other
Serta flower flavors have been
Pretty well
Receive
Cactus I'm a little worried about
Prickly pear
So
I believe it's Cactus and rose bouquet
Made with real roses
And natural
Prickly pear
So I going to give this a whirl
Laura borek and knock it out of the park
Much riskier probably than cactus rose eat itself
Change its name to Ouroboros
That's pretty good
That's pretty good gif
Pretty good
All right good right about the
Involve
Either one of them is coconut lemongrass coconut okay pass
Remember what the last one is but they're very risky and terms of like things that I have not enjoyed
That sounds like a nightmare
One of the things that I'm starting to recognize is like a lot of these flavors that I don't like
Canby
Save
With the addition of something out something a little bit like
But I don't think I would enjoy prickly pear but I think the rose elevates
I don't think I like watermelon flavored stuff all that much but
Really complements it really well like a cactus
Sing for you
Who would do that
I said.
You got a wild hair up your ass and when you when you were in Hawaii your family Eights
Archetype definitely Eatonville cactus in my life
I can't recall
Pacific sorry and I won't
Respond to this kind of grilling
Gorilla grilling about grilling text Marilee grilling
It's the truth to go to the
The package bin
That's right
Hey that's right and Christy sent us these
Incredible Halloween chocolates that are
Airbrush
And painted so beautifully and perfectly with all of these really complex and
Using flavors much like new Seltzer's there was one that was like a limoncello cake thing
Andy just had the lightest of chocolate coverings around it
And you open device
And it tasted exactly like you would just
Eating a little piece of
The Cakewalk
So so good that's my task close the package
Really don't like the first of all I don't like
You're hijacking soundtracks I also don't like
Work with the crate
Every single time
Well I do it just to be like I'm doing your thing again
Wow that sounds delicious
Jordans
20/20 of Dan this is 20/20
This is actually kind of interesting
Situation because
Tuesday's episode with a Tuesday
I might have missed some of the stuff that happen
The show
But if you want Danny sent me a message
Informing me that this was not to be missed
Okay
Let's go ahead and do it
So I we've got to we've got this episode to get into and I think it
This is not to be missed
It's not right before we get into the
To sign up and recording true
The first 40 oz engineer thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Very much
40 phase
He likes know I would
Adrian one pump one cream
Spell the numerical
Next Billy Bones
Johnson thank you so much you're now apology
Nextdoorraw one word Blue Jay thank you so much
Moomin loves dragon
Thank you so much
You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much moving love dragon
Did this person
Hesitate
On the page I can't
I would feel really bad about trying to pronounce this because I'm going to fail
Except I got a message that
Said that
It'd be funny for me to miss
So I have permission
Aioli
Is my first
I'll give it to you
Aoi Fe is an Irish name obviously I have
A lot of
Irish names of maybe I suppose
Like what are you doing
Trouble
Someone is coming up
So you got a how you spell fat
He always was my first
I guess and I know that's wrong
Thought about it some more in my
How could this be pronounced
And the other one I came up with it was leafy
You guys but I also don't
So what do you got
It didn't
What do you think I used to know this my dad was
Is really really into Gaelic he had that phase that middle-aged men have over there
Where am I from I need to know about my ancestors
I thought I got really into that too there was
The time where I would have been like
But
They just want to say that
I think it is
It's
However that's pronounced
Don't go website
That's what true we would appreciate it or what you could do is hang out in your home
After getting a large amounts of Halloween generosity
Keep it in a big bowl
All right and then whenever the young children come to you and knock on your door look
Looking for generosity candy
You stepped
Back and you throw it into their bag
You got to avoid contact with anybody and that bag is essentially a local charity or
Make sure you throw your generosity
I support the message that you landed on eventually but I cannot imagine even from a distance
No I know I have no idea how that's going to play out my apartment building
Across the way neighbors are going to knock on our door and working
Going to stay back wearing masks just so they're like
2 year olds
Can get a little Halloween action out of it
What's a all barracks
I guess it was in a building
Premeditation to at
Alright
Spider-Man
Scary
Jordan I want to go and announce really quick
Before we get sat into this episode is
Is that
We are going to be starting next week going back to two episodes awake
Weird
Initially I went from
Ra3 episodes
Institute episodes because the
Crushing workload of listening to this b*******
Is it is
It's hard to put up with
It took a second
Control on your mind
Yeah and then
The coronavirus situation happen to know a lot of people who are having to go to work
And we've felt with obviously wearing a bit of
Privileged situation that we can work from home
Show support and solidarity we want
Had to go back to three episodes a week for everybody
Thought baby would be a couple months and I think forever
If you listen back to those episodes were like if everybody does what they say it'll be a few weeks and then we'll be able to get onto the other side of this
Two days later everybody likes let's not do what they say we're like okay we'll see you next year
Yeah it's it's lingered on retreated back into that same like
Like three episodes a week and it's
Yeah it takes
We're going to be having episodes on Monday and Wednesday but hopefully at the end of each week
Will be able to have the bonus episode of many bonus episode The People
Confined
On our patreon page the knowledge fight
Patreon.com knowledge fight
But I want to be clear about one thing
That is not
Just for donor
Find a pay well no no absolutely not it's just that it is a very convenient place that you can upload audio
And it's
I don't know where to put it on our own website right like a good place to live
We actually have our first episode of that up
Today
Exactly have the best episode episode
But I will be up on the you know it's fights a patreon
So if you want to go check that out
It's not just for donors if you want to listen to it for free
You are more than welcome to and I will not hold it against you in anyway
Confined tonight
Pictures of things from the Z mailbag
But not from the stupid
T.i. you can find some nice pic
Pictures over there
It'll be lovely
And enjoy
I feel very self-conscious about my music
From that episode
There's going to be a lot of great feedback for me
That's what's really important
Take the brunt of all negative credit
Is amethyst every single flip
Like I said
Is what we're doing
And yours Alex
Getting into like the main news story of the day
Anybody notices audio is a little bit different
Planetary ruler Bill Gates announces
Bells will never end
Rockefeller Foundation document
For permanent
Last night
Bill Gates
Publicly confirm
The plan
It's being implemented as we speak
And if civilization as we know it is over
I'm about to play
Is being interviewed and the guy was asking about like a lot of the progress that has been made in terms of the developing
World food in
Security things like that
It's been really hurt
Bye
Coronavirus update measures that it needed to be
Putting place
And Bill Gates
His response that was
Medically there's a lot of things that won't be set back as far as it might appear short but a lot
The progress in terms of
Economics stuff food stuff
Some of that stuff might
Picked I'm Yours
To get back to the place
We had gotten to
He was just acknowledging more that like their challenges and setbacks
Sure Alex is taking that to be like
He's telling you that it's going to
10 years until you'll get out of your home
How many different times has civilization ended
In the past couple of weeks
30 I want to say there's been a lot of ending real civilization
Cuz we're well-balanced many times he doesn't cry wolf
The kid that like words never going to get the people are just always going to come running whenever yells wolf
So you heard a little bit of a slightly different sound
The second hour to get an explanation for why the sound is
5 +
Blind
Lockdown at least 10 years
Inoculation
Total control the whole world collapsing
Financial destruction
To save
Just don't think the 1% of 1% I mean it's just
Crazy
It is he didn't say that he is crazy
But Alex was so mad about this Bill Gates interview that he did the first
Howard Stern.
You just like maybe if you have back problems you need to
Strengthen your core muscles are completely different Mike
Treadmill is off
Suck
I don't want to take time to exercise and to do my show I might as well do both us and Jack
His business will be done on air Middle have the rest of the day to just f*** around if he eats lunch on his show
You might as well work out
Bring up this business we got to pay this bill
Resource document Illinois
We go back to the beginning of the show now where he's standing up
And we get
A little bit of a conversation
And about how
The globalists are running a scheme
Write all this stuff is this
But they have to go
Get you to agree to it
Oh Alex talked about that a little bit and this is so
This is a scheme
Admit
10 years ago for the Rockefeller Foundation
Because metaphysically
There's a
Universal rule
You have to tell people what you're doing
God has his rules we just met
Even super fine print in there
By the way I can screw you I want
But still you got to get a magnifying glass
The globalist
How come
Contract law that you have to follow that's based on gods of contract flaws
Why
Like they're working for the devil
Know what is it like they get into heaven when they die if they work for the devil but follow contract law
Prosecute
Under contract
It's legal if you're under contract God can't touch you if you're under contract what's the consequence of breaking contract law
I think you probably get that for working for the f****** devil
Sure but I mean if I come sooner get fired
Have you considered that man
Look there is a it is a tough job market out there Satan is the only one hiring
I don't understand they're trying to avoid by following contract I don't understand what they get
Galax
Sick dad
Right but what they're doing is evil
Evil their lawful evil they're not chaotic evil then
It's just the way it works
Killer go outside of your alignment otherwise you'll receive a fan delete on your savings
Like I hid somewhere in a contract that I get to kill you I can't remember.
I like the idea that there are galaxies nowhere these contracts aren't nuts
He has to point out that it's galactic
The Milky Way has this kind of lost her
Yeah but the other ones not using random words
I don't think it means anything
Either
The globalist plans
Did are still following contract law or something
In their fifth
6 dimensional plans man
Why doesn't make any sense what all the stuff that Alex
Completely stupid and all the headlines that he reads don't say what he said the pig
In the third dimension but they do the 5th
Whatever that may
Okay
Operations are much more complex
Dementia
People like Gabe can't see that hot he's just a front
Please
Show me are you conceited
Demented
All the time you need
I would listen to like
A 6 hour lecture of Alex just really calmly methodically explaining what the 5th
6/7 dimensional that's what I understand what does this mean
Stop yelling so much Alex
If you do have like some kind of a seventh dimensional analysis
It really let me know what it is
Yeah does that mean like there are more
Layers to the plan like in a metaphorical way where it's like
Spirituality
The six Dimension is maybe like
Fire and the 7th Dimension is
Interpersonal communication like I don't know what it is
See I don't know and that's why I need Alex to explain it
Unfortunately he just doesn't have enough time on the show you know there's just so much there's so much news there's so much news
If only he had an hour thrown into his lap with nothing to
To do today
You get into this with that never
Never never have never never
I'm so Alec has a new product
I don't know babe I hate to be this is that good
This Doom and Gloom naysayer but
Is going to kill somebody
Separately
This is me
This is super strong
Types of
Can shut down the bottle
This is not good
Poisonous
Super strong
A surfaces
Art services
Things like that
This is here
Iodine surface spray with a bunch of different
Types of industrial I-9
Cleaning agent
And boy
It's a good deal out of the gate
It just came in
B95 you're not going to 5
Cleaning agent
Dish Anywhere someone's going to drink that
Yeah. Hundred percent products would you ingest
Love your body
He can be like this is poisonous this will kill you don't
Congested
Someone's going to f***
I don't even like how he was being very dismissive
Poison it's like no that's very poisonous and you tell people to drink when you're sick
The different products
Why would you sell a cleaning product with the same product as you're eating product
That's an issue
I don't know and I think that there is such a distrust
Of like
Science
The it within his audience
Could easily be people who think like
Texas
Suggestion not to drink to write Alex's
Strong
Distance events
Stronger better
Explain to me how if you
You can convince somebody to drink bleach
Telling them not
To drink iodine is going
To solve your problem
It seems dangerous
I don't like to see it
Knock knock
Like to see is damn lineman from Europe Wars
Recently we've seen him pretending that that
Anarcho queer feminist housing
Project in Berlin
That got evicted everyone
Stronghold
And we learn
Cuz they're back on the show today
We learned that actually
That wasn't the
Scoop
It wasn't news that he was reporting
He was in Berlin for a specific reason
Back at back at home is definitely an eventful weekend do in Berlin I got more than I bargained for didn't know what to expect
At the invitation
The alternative for Deutsch
Party which is alternative
For Germany they are the
The third-largest
In Germany and the main opposition party if there was a trumpian party
In Germany that's who they would be and they invited me up there forever ID if it's
Experiences
And what you're seeing in that footage was
Just a small
Portion of the weekend
You're not a journalist you are a mouthpiece of the far-right party in Germany alternative
For Germany
Trumpian party in Germany
They would be called
Bear Lake
You know it
We need to do some
NPR for us
Europe's Alex
Correspondent are you a journalist or are you a PR firm
PR
Anyway
The issue
M2 is that like Auntie's are there Terror
Sure basically International Terror
What
Bandera International terrorists
Anyways
Because
This weekend
Plan raid
The Berlin
Find German 85 work
Pulling in antifa
From around the continent
To join them in
Defending this
Property and fighting with the police that's why
The German police had to
Deployed
500 officers
Streets of Berlin this weekend
Dissipation of Iowa
Continue with your observations
Eating lunch
15U with your house
Video
Continue with your
Unbelievably rude
I wouldn't I wouldn't put up with that I relieve gas
Alex is another gas
Darkrow about this b*******
Story
Alex another guest Carlos
Zapata he is the guy who was a veteran
Who yelled at a city council meeting in California about how he would take up arms against his fellow citizens that if he had to wear masks
Surround right cuz he's a hero
Yeah
Talk about to have a war is a coming
Well yeah
Do they
And there's one way that they come up with it seems like a good idea is that
Mal peacefully
To avoid the war
Avoid
Amica becoming normal
Right now
Tomorrow Alex
Take off a mass right now we need to go outside
Live our lives
Like this never happened
Y'all because it is a hoax that's how you do it
You don't abide by them
Reply.
I think a change
You walk outside your house anymore
Name of your damn life Civil War
Pretended covid isn't real
Good good
Reality
Walk outside your date and like I said your house every morning and think
I live somewhere else
Shoot people if they insist on bringing up that realities real
That's a that's a salt then I don't live by the libertarian Prince
People of non-aggression towards non reality
Foundation of jurisprudence
Constitution my letters are lower case then that's what I'll tell you right now
Carlos has
An interesting
Quote
But I thought might be quote but
I think he might actually like
This might be a Carlos
Okay
We're not violent
Yeah
Or what
Things will happen
But you got to realize
Number 12 of their mechanism
22 enforcer agenda is instability
They're going to try to
Tip Papa land
Destabilize out our society every single day
So it's up
To gain a stability back
I can only way you
Is people
Stabilizing
5 minutes
Quiche
I mean leaving the sort of racism the end of side
When good men are willing to do bad things great things will happen
Scary quote I will tell you right now of all the any belief systems that I've ever heard
None of them were like
Well yeah I mean if you're good you got to be willing to evil the s*** out of people
It's are willing to be demons heaven will arrive
When people have a belief system they have
Completely rejected in order to make that belief system happened
That makes perfect sense that's a really scary kind of way to start to know that's an insane person waited
Let me hear all this like dallying around
He wants to get more specific
Assassinate Trump
Talk about bad scenarios we'll talk about Target
This is George Noory from Coast to Coast AM
Hey George I hope you are not a Target commercial
If you're aware where your ads are being played you might want to get those ads off there you might want to
Yourself
I'm going to break the first
Where's Dad
After kill list is not the ad that you want to have
I don't want that app
I will pay you at
Stratford not that place
It seems like
Association to the Tryon
Defy
This dude is really into talking about violence
Stuff but of course we're not into violence
Alex has a gas like that it's always
Best for him to try to be like let's get really specific
Because then you can say those things
Andy can be on my show and I can say I didn't say that
Did you hear me say like hey that's a great idea that's me pushing back on it we just talked about all sides of the issue
That kinda Dodge
So yeah you want to talk about
Pacifica people we need to take out in case
Trump loses the election
That's not that the mass
Yeah so they get to talk about this and Alex's
It's kind of trying to justify himself
By being like
Olympic youth Opperman
Let's talk worst case scenario they assassinate from
They say
Tito run freestyle the club said
We will dominate their supporters will put them in prison
Exterminator
This is classic weathermen terminology
Cocina Del no really mean to do this
Keith Olbermann of the weathermen
They wants to go out.
Martial law
God forbid
Who are the main targets
Who are the people
Who are leftist
Yeah
Absolutely
You know but here's a deal
Alex
Simple as establishing a list
4 Target list
And going after them
At that point
Very well
Baird at structure militias and we're real blessed
L
Is this the way to cut them off what you're saying
WhatsApp
But whenever Sedro-Woolley Western internal we have to turn
Small towns and cities and and gather our resources
Zakir very locally meeting areas and and use that
Itarget that's outside of her we live I think we have to cling onto
Is there an Alex and big conspiracy theory about the election that the Democrats if Trump wins are going to secede
Delete all the leftist areas unlike all the Democratic states are going to secede
All the times need to secede
That's so far right
Navigate Vacaville
How far right is like what we need to do is go into the middle of nowhere and ignore the
Big Society in Greater small group of people
Who ourselves
Sufficient who share everything with each other who have their own system of government based entirely upon how all of
I mean there are Elementary
Assertive leanings
Towards an archaism didn't like
On both sides of the political aisle
I know this dude is it just makes me very it makes me laugh so hard whenever they like
Come upon an extremely left
Just idea by going so far to the right
What's my call me a guy is like
Is argument of like let's not go ahead and kill people let's
Create our spaces
Better than let's go kill people would prefer it
That said
Alex shouldn't be agreeing with him because this is a nightmare that he's been saying the Democrats have planned
Bought
Anyway I will tell you that the first
3 hours of this show are not
It's mostly Alex repeating over and over again the Bill Gates has admitted that the Rockefeller plan blah blah blah
Never gonna leave your house again cuz that over and over again
Who yelled at a city council meeting
Not the best
I was just thinking this
Just a step but
Every time you know I never even
Thought about it really
Everytime they say we got to take out leftist
L
I would be shocked if they could name a leftist
Vitense
Right you see what I'm saying like every time they like let's take out the leftist leaders
I'd suddenly occur Soros
They're not they have no idea what the left
Well I don't think that you are I would be considered leadership
Really look at
The political aisle
I think there was a lot of people who would look at us as quite
Milk
Yeah I don't know I think that yeah it would be tougher
And certainly to recognize
Any real
Anything that's not a political shadow puppet
Setting up for them
TV anymore they're not getting anybody who's actually kind of leftist leaders
Bezos I know you're taking out all the people who I have f***** over the left
To I don't know now Jordan
Like I said the first 3 hours kind of
But then begins
And something really exciting happen
Is out sticking around for the 4th hour
Your listing for Paul Joseph Watson
Frontline report what is happening if you receiving this transmission you are the resistance
Daddy-O
London England
This should be up with us the next
10 minutes or so
You're stuck with me
Potbelly pasta
Riders on the
Home but I'm bummed
Riders on this song world were born
Good
I just have to remember the lyrics to a song like every other
That s*** is balling up real fast
The power not on it is I forgot.
We now have a bunch of time Alex get
Explain the fifth sixth seventh Dimension and break it down
Unfortunately
Does not
I need a Mars Attacks in 40 please
William Acosta
Can I get that
Tangled
With that Honcho.
In the main
We get that cute option weekend
Can we get that railwatch
Can we get it ready to energized
Ready to
Bowl
Ready to go absolutely crazy
That was where I got worried
I saw the greatest minds of my generation Santigold
Scat poetry
Entire segment
Just cuz they couldn't think of anything else to
That's really where I got worried
I was like better f****** show up because
Lionel Smith
Authorities out-of-the-box Yaga
A minute to break and he's like
All I can do is
Is keep saying words for prepare how many synonyms
Really disappointed
Alex comes back
Package has not shown up
And tell you about how pissed off Bill Gates
That you by Alex's pills
And then
I wish Alex Wood
Just come up with synonym for persuade friend to fill time
And I want to say if anybody is
Move to our Reich really offended by Alex doing
Let's say racist impressions
Oh no you might want to take the rest of the episode.
Sort of advance
Warning
Alex
Might do his Chinese dragon character along toy
Infowars
Blowout sale
6 days
Percent off
Triple Patriot points free shipping
Shop now
Really upset
That you are
2 a.m.
I'm sure
Do you want your whole
Operation with all the robber baron money all the media at everything
And it's blown up
Curly in Spanish
Here's the only two positives I don't want you to see
Cuz you might like let up in the DNA kit window
Are you
Happy Father's Day cuz they're going to punish me but it's okay.
What
Commonhelp
Let me know when you're headed over right
Has sent you mail games where are you do vagina
Locked up in my throat
You like that
No sounds like 45 minutes
Has Fentanyl
Do you guys want the next
50 minutes of broadcast
Tomato Hostess fentanyl
You want to talk
Nobody said oh my God
Paul
Stuff to remember in the sixties you could win an Oscar
For that
I don't think Alex is drunk
I think he's being passive
Progressive
Scheduled up all is on the schedule
All right and I said this is the manager
Bennigan's
Tables for a day
And lashing out with a racist character
Also the other side of it is like Alex isn't really that
Good
At
Anything serious
This is about as good as
Chicken dip
He's billing time
Instead of like
Actually focus and do anything he's just going to do
Is dumb character
And then
We'll try and cover some of the news
Wow being the character
We in the World Health Organization do not
Advocate
Lockdowns is a primary means of
Tupac
You know this Alex Jones told you this way mon
Now because they get blamed for that they don't want you to think they then
Chinese dragon did it all
Raccoon video
So this is what's real
This is not real too don't have a boss it flies
Yeah it's strange Alex I'm not positive has actually seen that full clip of the world
World Health Organization
Interview with the guy with Andrew Neil on the
The Spectator
What about you
Method of
Of dealing with it good when you need to buy time
That kind of thing
I don't think Alex has heard that full clip because it starts sounding not like
How Alex Costa
Describe
Because Alex has described it as the World Health Organization
Alex realizes
I need to talk over the truth
So I need to distract people
Pine Lodge
We'd rather not do it just look about
The tourism industry for example in the Caribbean
People aren't taking the holidays for the comments
Jalisco my godparents
Family Show
Deceased
Cipp
This is
You know I just like
Thinking about all the adult
Yeah I like thinking about being in the imaginary adults
Even the interns who are like 17 have to be sitting there gone like
Goddamn
I am never going to work anywhere again I should go back to f******
Bennigan's
The guy is pissed off that I'm not at my shift right now
Little man
So
I want to apologize in advance for this next clip
The reason I'm apologizing
Two-and-a-half minutes long
Clipit improvises a song
You win Brady really of our time OKC improvisational musical scale
Zach Randolph
Movie is locked all you fools
You stopped
Good job
But I'm out
Goodbye America friendly
America
How are you
Chiropractor
Find John 1.
Naruto
Broadcast.
All right I got to pause he was going to ride that with something else God damn it I dare you how dare you
I have to pause
Is just to say this is
Horrifying
A defensive end
Distance to describe this is this is one of those things that I hate the most because it come it makes me look like a terrible person because it fits
Something happening at like an open mic or not
Everyone in the audience is staring with their jaws wide open just like
How is this possible and then they would turn and look back at me
Howling with laughter because this is funny
And its own butt
Because you're laughing
It's
Alarming to see someone
Perform something like this
But it's remarkable to see a room not respond to it
Someone's thinking this is like
Emma
I was listening to this and I did not I did not get any amusement out of it
Still going I thought it was pretty remarkable
We are a good minute and that's banana and there's a bit more more so much more
What are we doing
We love Hillary pool
Wear your mask a pencil die
Rob LeBron James East all blood
Call Gonda Building
El Debarge mom
Now
Aztlan how
America
Liberal good
Why are you mad
Amazon.com
What if your existing wood burning fireplace and not spend thousands doing it
How to serve cider to hear that going to commercial music
I just
I mean
That went on
It did that went on for a long time Dan oh yeah I did
At that didn't I didn't
Improve
No for a little while he kind of found a m
How many American Dad
There was almost a point where he had sort of a verse
Chorus structure going
Yeah real terrible
I questioned whether I should
Actually play that
But it was so surreal
Yeah and a half minutes
He did that improvise
Effective
It racist
I mean that's just wild it's
It's lashing out though
Yeah yeah I don't think he's drunk he's not acting like he generally does when he's done
Yes yeah yeah
Yeah man
I'm trying to
I-88
So how would like
Dipped into the Batman theme for a little bit like from the old Adam West
Show
Wild wild
What wild I think we can
Say though
Without any kind of
Confusion
And that like that was an attempt at humor
He was being chronic yes he did
Yeah he thought he was
Sometimes something is so racist
Said it like
And sends offense
And turns into you're a raving
Insane person
Yeah it's it's obvious we race
But it's also like
What are you doing what are you doing
What are you doing
Alex was trying to be funny
I'm certain
Man that's
They're the ones who can't
Yeah man
The left doesn't have humor
He has humor
Okay that's a bit that's a bit
That's it
Travel
So turns out
A lot of people have been asking
Anna time so sad now
I'm so sad that they think that's humor
What's up darling missing out on
So much Jordan I don't think they do
Okay well that might
Maybe some of the audience but I can't imagine
They're being people even who work there who are like
This is good this is
Molting
Thank God he didn't stop at 45 seconds
It was more there's more gold in them thar Hills
Berry Gordy listen to this
I I can't imagine I can't imagine it was anybody laughing
In the room
Other than maybe smoke
I can't believe he's doing this
I can't believe he's laughing at Alex
Alex
Hey man what are you going to be on Rogan
By the way
That we're going to have
Yeah no s***
They're going to have the next few days
Call Joseph Watson was supposed to be here
I can more than easily easier
Do you know how much of a struggle it is for us to get through the next hour
It is
Directly proportional to the amount of ease with which he can get the problem
I've got another one let's take it from the top boys
I guess Alex is saying that he's never going to be on Rogan or he's going to be on in the next couple days
So I guess we'll see maybe Monday is episode will be another Rogan episode
We'll find out
Movie pissed off pissed off
Yeah I agree I think that there is
A little bit of a vibe
You can get here
Where Alex
Insinuates
The Paul often pretends to have technical difficulties in order to have sex with hot glue
Weather
Call Carlos Hardware
Yo-yos
I got a power outage
Doesn't look like
Absurd
I'd like the dog ate my homework
Powers out
In my house right now
Either that I got a super hot chick in my house
We all know that's what Paul Business yellow
But instead of like you said hi at the super hot Brazilian check at my house or whatever
He calls and it says 0
I'm sorry
I need time to get the power on
But it doesn't look like the power will be turning on anytime this year
Communication
About communion
You want to work with me
We don't need ball
I don't know
Also I don't know if Alex is being serious about like Paul canceling to have sex with strange women but
I probably would appreciate this cuz I think Paul's married
Yeah I was I was supposed to say I'll have a significant other I know that he at least has been in a long-term relationship
I know that I don't care about people's personal life
And I heard Paul mention his girlfriend at least
And Alex has referred to her as his wife
I don't know I feel like if this is how it's being it anyways
This is
Pretty pretty shity
How is it possible
For you to expect me not to start believing that this
Entire world
The prank on me
That is that is the ravings
Of somebody
Please own personal
Private like
Tape recorder
Look that's what you hear from somebody who's tape recording there
Thoughts in a car
Weird racist song
Bitching about his employees
Motor in the car
This is a show right of the show that other people can hear
I can
Tell if Alex was being actually serious about Paul canceling
To have sex
Sure cuz he also then goes into this
Paul Joseph Watson
He married
What is the code name for Gigi
Paul Joseph Watson
Report to you as been part of a gay marriage
What's an Old Rag
I was not married him
They told me that fentanyl video It's Over
I want the speaker. This is
2 is actually ggp
Alternative
So those are easily Alex
Can fill time until that our up
Makes it about 3 to 5 minutes really think they can fill 20 easy
Do you know how easy I could do an hour and hours not even hard.
Cars
Just talk for an hour
4 hours all the time Paul canceled because he
Bangin Brazilian models also he's actually married to Jay-Z
Q
Crushin it these B
Dude it's Isaiah
Satire so sad that the left doesn't have you
Satire Jordans
This is been a true
Mission trips
New York Times calls its satire
Paul Joseph Watson is not dating Gigi
Paul Joseph Watson
Paul Joseph Watson is not dating
Call Ralph
Relationship
Isis sex slave
Po-boy
Are we are we just doing this
How
Consistent
An experience that was listening to this of like
B
Dying
It's just like
Alex you have to believe you're funny to try
Pull this s*** off calls
I am what's the terrible about
I don't know
Alex doesn't know what metaphorical metaphysical or satirical make
Anyway
He has a lot of time
Rambling about how Paul is dating this
Imaginary racist Dragon who's actually she use Q
It makes no sense
It's very dumb I do like the idea that Alex is
Just trying to tank
Paul Joseph Watson
So hard that he has no choice but to never do this
He's also trying to show
Art teacher Paula lesson if you want to take a day off
This is what you
This is what happened do you want this
Alex
He tries to make a big deal out of how mysterious is set decoration so hard
Again
This is how you're choosing to fill time
There's no content here just
Turn everything on the show
And a broadsword and then
Eagle
Roman-style
Simple
What do they call that in wrong where you would have the symbol of the eagle
We have a name for it will just sit here
4 hours of
That makes better radiologic covering fax info
Triforce inoculations everybody World garbage lockdown
It's on a Roman Signet
Gargoyle
Coffee actual
The stand
The ramen stand
So
We're here with a
Eagle Ramen standard
With a real skull
A broad edged sword
What does that symbolize
What's esoteric you project onto it what you think
Give me a shot of velocity
I don't care
Was he about to tell me what he interprets his own random talk
Okay
Do this
I mean his chessboard in a skull in a rose
So easy to fill it out I can feel an hour so easily
This is if all the sudden you like walked away and I was like
Find you want to know what to do knowledge fight for the next 10 minutes
Hey you got that whiteboard behind your head look at that white board wedding
You know what I see when I see a whiteboard cuz there is anything written on it then I see untapped potential that's a tabular
Providence anyways when are we going to do the show
It's the mark of a craft
Florida space
Or Alex
Being really desperate like a why doesn't anyone make conspiracies out of the weird things that I choose
To put on on-screen only for people to think they're weird
Why don't people take the bait
To speculate about why I got a skull here when I've explained repeatedly to my dad's
I put here cuz I think it looks weird this isn't it works for Usual Suspects why isn't it working for me
More like
Obsessed here for a little while with the wrestling papers
Like you stole it
From Rush
We talked about that a bit
Pulling these papers
You've heard of radio
You've heard of life
Have I
White Noise rain sounds for 3 hours
What about putting YouTube out of play
Rush Limbaugh crackling paper 3 hours just like
What if you did
What if you did that then what are you doing
Are you did that Dad
Oh my God having the worst pitch meeting
On top of a race
Sing-along on top of whining about Paul Joseph Watson on top of
There's a long fourth hour by Paul doesn't show
Swap you can't just take calls
Does the exact same stories you hit for the first 3 hours yellow about them a little more
Bill Gates just
F****** it made it the lockdowns never going to Amy's going to kill everybody know cover that story fully
You can yell about it tomorrow him time to cover it.
Story or he wasn't
I'm supposed to and now he's not doing it out of
He's so good at feeling time mode
Does all this b*******
Calverton producer of the show with look at this
For 5 minutes
Then go all right
Let's keep it going for another 55
Well maybe someone is like chess
F****** call Paul you're not doing anything
I'm cracking up on air
Baby I'm going to end up at Atlanta Tech Asylum
Maybe
Play Locked Up by Joe Budden
A bad idea
Why is it only Brown realize he's like
Brian Amazon
Sure
Doesn't realize it for the show
Watching right now
What you doing
Baby
You such a whiny baby
Welcome
Sorry but the person you cool
Voicemail
Probably avoided did not ring one time
My God
Paul's not answering
That really extra kind of made me sad
Because
If Paul cared at all about his job he would have answered that we did not care at all about your job
Hurst email and
An hour before his he was supposed to go up saying I will not be there till then he is not there
Alex realizes like
Alright
10 minutes left
Okay if the show
Okay
I'm going to stop right
Now this is unprofessional
Agreed
Comeback
Are you serious
Final 10 minutes of the show
He's not coming back from
Let's Get Serious then
Babylon important things to cover
Is a lot of important news to cover
He's going to get serious for the end of the show
Then come back for the last time
I mean it
It's kind of the same thing
He basically just start
Play comedy videos
The Tim Dillon comedian Tim Dillon
Sacrifice
They're feeding on you
Here's one more
Here is a Tim Dillon doing is a little promotion of New York City
Trouble
Dillons
Comedian
Who has been on Alex's show in the past
And
He's also been on Rogan a bit
Alex is talking about him in ways
It sound a little bitter because there's like he's broke
Logan's favorite comic
Sure because Tim will come on Alex's show it's not like
It's a bridge he's trying to burn but there is still a petty
Bitterness that you can sense there
Until you plays like two or three
Tim Dillon
This is him getting serious to end the show unreal
Udoka
After those comedy videos
And that's the big secret is not Tim Dillon it's not Joe Rogan
We found out this morning
Shroyer is actually the Sun
That's not called fake news that's called a joke
Haha
I'm out of control
Boston shopping lately a lot of crazy things.
Appreciate you all
Good boy
I'm a comeback
Better than ever
This is what happens when Paul
Josephine Watson
Do not show up for it
A lot of time this is what happened
When you piss off a rug
What happened to your car out there this is your world
Stop
Seriously though look at really serious
Wow
Inject it into my veins Dan
Bad news
Hostile work environment
That is not where I would what I would be if I was Paul I would to hear that and be like
Good thing there's an ocean between us
Dickwad
That's that's real
Teddy bear
That mean everything about that 4th hour was
Nonsense
That was a train wreck
Yeah yeah not in the way that we've often see it
What he was doing
But there's a lot of times that we seen
The show go completely off the rails due to either technical difficulties or Alex being f***** up
I just accuse lashing out I think everything that you see there the racist song The Paul's dating
Qingji
The sniping at Paul
The bitterness about Tim Dillon
I all of it
I just
It just seems
Like now that's exactly what
12 year old bullied like that's not even like childish behavior that is a man
Who is like revealing to all of us his brain
Has never managed
To grow Beyond
Is a twelve-year-old child
Then somehow he's gotten away with it for this
I think it's really remarkable that like your you have this existing as of the same show you have like
Do you know the first
We get the beginning of it there's a girl Bill Gates
Did an interview and he's admitted he's going to kill everybody blah blah I'm going to talk to this guy who yelled at a city council meeting about me
Kill list
Of leftist leader is and then
Our Town need to secede
Devices
Ominos lash out at Paul for an hour on my show instead of do anything meaningful
Lipsitz
That's
It's something
I can't believe
Can't believe you still work there Paul
I mean
Well I mean as we know from the deposition
That he did
Contractor
I can't believe
Alex must pay well
This was an episode
Primarily because of that
Very strangely racist offense
Remarkable is
One might remark upon.
Otherwise the contact is very very normal
Standard Alex stuff appreciate Alex breaking up the monotony with that
Petulant
Appreciate that
Maybe the seventh dimension
So I will be back
But also if you'd like to check out we do have that bonus episode
Can our hour and five hear this episode
But if you are craving a little bit more of our a business
You can find that over at patreon.com
/ knowledge fight that's where I can hear me and Jordan talking about
It was nice it was fun to do
Yes it's Alex prezone yeah that's kind of the thing like it's not that we can't do
Three episodes
Of contents no it's that we can't do three episodes
This show I'm glad that you you brought that up in the specific event it's not gross
Gross the workload
Can I can handle at 80 hour work week
No problem
80 hours
Use of
Alex Jones
My break
Especially when his stuff is this dumb
If you was actually coming with like
Primary sources interesting stuff
Conspiracies that could possibly be true but old what about this should feel like
Then
I'm always
The Bill Gates going to kill everybody
And also I'm mad at all
And Keith Olbermann
Speaks for the laugh
I've got no time for it and it
Betty White will be back but until then we website
Jordans
A local charity or Bellefontaine your area to help out those two
Until the enemy om Leo and dzx Clark
I'm Daryl rundus
Simple Joe's
Is Watson's day off
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work