Damn important sweat it
I have great respect but knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Knowledge fight
What's fight.com
Acknowledge
We're couple dudes like sit around and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Jordan
What's up
My bright spot is
Splurged on a little investment for the show
Impress watch I'm touching right now
See a little button maker
I think that Sensei was a much younger man I've always been really interested
I didn't realize
Is this is very deep
Buried subconscious thing
I think the
What I was young
Was jealous of the punks up if they're cool buttons
Man has buttons again
Magical
Weather leather jacket
Super cool buttons on her but I'm just sitting there like a dork
It is it is really kind of bug drink
Give the Podcast Addict to realize that
Half of the time they're just in their basement
Pumping out buttons
Someone is
He's goddamn the nerdy one is making a bud everybody else is pretending to
Disarm instruments
You're the button guide
I can give to listeners and stuff
Could be really fun to be able to
Just sit around while I'm doing
Work listening to Alex
So you got some we got some updates about that forthcoming in the near future
Any other thing
The other thing was like
So who's got the all the punks with the butt
Jingle
This commercial jingle
I think from back when I lived in Hawaii
You sure I don't know what business it was
But it was but
Buttons who's got the buttons
There's like a button company
I feel like it was like eight or nine
Final thing
Lighted buttons
Are really cool
I like going to antique stores
And looking at these like
A weird old like Mayoral race button
We were in whatever the other day and I was staring at all these like JFK and reggae
Buttons
There's something really really cool about button
And I didn't realize how exciting it would be to
To have a button press
I think it's I think it's a paradox
In some ways because there is also something
Deeply uncool about
Buttons
2020 interesting
Fun fun things
Well I'm going to hold onto it as bright spot
For me it is open mike Eagles just released his new album and it is absolute
Incredible
I do know what it reminds me so much of a
The Green Room conversation
Like I the comics have
Where is like some dude will be telling you
The
Worst thing that ever happened in his entire life
And there's like four comic sitting around with him
And everybody is hearing this story and then there's a riff that happens
And everybody started laughing hysterically
And then it stops
And it goes back into the saddest story and that's just how it works like
Just how we deal with that group conversation
And it's dark
Darkly funny about
What is divorced and all that stuff
It's also extremely sad about the worst things
That ever happen
How's he dealing with
The fact that in the age of the covid-19 there are no more open mic
He's doing a great job with
He's moved on from those
He kept the name play move out
Big Lots middle eagle
Oh that's great I have to check that out there
Next time mr. bike
I do like his work no that's it that's all
We're going to be tucking
About
February 16th
And 24th 2016 2016
Got to hear I support that this is now my autonomous of time mazzone
I wouldn't listen to talk what are we up to today we're covering this for a specific reason
And actually there's a myriad of reasons
Is that I tried to cook up a Project Camelot episode but the episode I listen to
Unfortunately by the
The time I got through the interview I Was preparing
I realize this person is not someone who I can make fun of I don't feel
Comfortable about they're thirsty
Of mind
And honestly Jordan
Yeah I believe that after our last episode the end of last week
Where we heard Alex's long
Racist songs
I do I just feel like
Present-day Alex might need
There needs to be a Punisher
I feel at least
You know how you're not supposed to yell at your cat you're supposed to misbehave
Sort of like
Ignore it for that day
The satisfaction
Yeah it's kind of how I feel right now without
So I will get down to this episode here from February 20th
16 before we do get to say thank you
Supposed to sign up
Thank you so much for now policy walk
Next
The best reptile thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
Mortlock
William Neff
William nephew next disembodied spirit
I get very much to somebody Spirit of knock
Also that doesn't knock wanted me to ask
Do you if you had a chance to try that whiskey that got sent in by the disembodied
I think that's revealed I think that's revealed
Yes I did and it is
Very very
Do you have any like that note
Vanilla or hickory or any
Any pretentious the Somali a notes
Describe whiskey
I honestly have this relationship with whiskey where it's like
You should be both
Surprised and delighted by the tail
Anything other than that if you have any other flavor
Situation
I'm like a little bit
Put off by that
Alright I'm writing down after notes it is it has a little bit of
Good taste
The next on behalf of Katherine events
I'm a policy wonk
Next this is confusing and
Berry not Berry
Barry not a r r y
I don't know how to pronounce one differently than the other but Berry not Berry thank you so much
Barry
And finally cargo the cogitator
Very much cargo
Also I'm not sure I can't remember now if Alex calls himself a couch
Potater Orcutt
Couture
How to say either way
I would cut the tating like a
Cogitate
I want to say is
Agitator because
He thinks
Name is thinking about the tater
What you can do is
Little cupboard there maybe you're not feeling too generous pull open a very lovely
Bottle of whiskey and discovered that it is actually the
Spirit of generosity itself
You taste take that spirit
And bring it to a local charity or bail fund
That was smooth that wasn't bad
Expensive
Think that by now I would at least improve
Slightly
Jordans
63 we're looking to this for a reason
Then and I will get to that reason as we get through
But here's where we start
Alex covering the big news of the day
And we've got our
David Knight show big fan
Camera crew as well
Now down at
The scene of where Scalia
Of natural causes an anonymous phone call sad
And they'll be no investigation by any of the media or the government and will be no autopsy they made sure to announce the next day
Cuz there's nothing to see here
Just go to sleep go away
Took the big news on February
16th 2016 was that Antonin Scalia who twice
Why not
He has passed away
At the Illuminati Ranch
Murder She Wrote episode where we're going to find out who killed Antonin Scalia by the end
We're going to find out something okay
I will say that Alex has not developed by this point the Illuminati Lodge
Okay that is definitely something that I've got that got tossed around
He believes that
Obviously murder
Duh
But David night out there on the scene
Great good tea
What's going to happen according to Alex
Scalia real okay
First Amendment
Critic
The nomination
For this
Supreme Court Justice
Attorney general Loretta Lynch
Course they're banning
Building
Change your name
Associated with lynching
Who cares
Attorney General
Match
Our
General Loretta
Racist name hanging black people hurt my feelings
Attorney general Loretta Lynch
Has publicly
First Amendment to another
But very
Yikes
Alright okay
Alex
Expedia
You know I was great whenever somebody is so racist even attempting to be non-racist
Incredibly race
Spell there's nothing there's nothing racist about the name Lynch
Friends
Growing out the outside
Marshawn Lynch
For like the extra-judicial hanging
Does come from
Gso it's named after either William or Charles Lynch figures of early
American history who
Lynch's law
Game if you will
I don't know point of trying to make other than like Alex
Play wait remix
I don't know
Loretta Lynch is going to be the new Supreme Court Justice which we all now know is
Definitely
Totally accurate
You just went to the bench so Alex has he believes that he's
Become he's been Vindicated
Immediately when Scalia died
Some predictions about how to tell if it was murder
It turns out
It's my job.
Text the heat Anderson
Natalya but my gut
+ 2
And not be a coward
That's why I came out Saturday hours after it was announced he was dead did my research
Natural causes
Anonymous phone call
Artifact
It's in the middle of nowhere in this
This owner of the Ranchos a high-level democratic
Bed
They are instantly saying no foul play they'll be no investigation
Watch if there's no autopsy
I'm here that
Quickly we know there's major alarms going off in a course the next morning
The judge came in on a Sunday
Tell Alex has been proven right
Preconditions of how he will be proven right
And nothing has been proved it's really great Whenever you set your preconditions after the precondition
Preconditions of already been met
It is like a c man I was proved right if you say something like if there's no autopsy
Then it's you know it it's just
If there is an autopsy
The question
If the Sun rises
Tomorrow
Oh man it was murder
This is
Nonsense
You know
There could have been an autopsy sure
If Angela
Skooly is family wanted one
When there isn't foul place
I suspect even if the person is a high-profile individual so what you say
Who had
Like a connection or a reason to request
The autopsy
Makoto
So your family Within
Yeah that's what I'm pretty sure you know what you just told me is that the
The family killed Anthony
Scully I think Alex might be working on that
By the end of the month tomorrow
We know cuz we looked at 25th
Steve quite a bit that Alex
Becomes a big Trump fan by
Mid December of 2015
16 he is he is jumped
He has conveniently forgot all of
Of the crimes that he remembered right committed
Just a recent bit
That's small potatoes compared to the fact
The Trump is trying to talk
About how bush
I'll let 911 happen. I'll do it I was really excited about that
Playoff baseball 9/11 planes doesn't know the facts
Clinton fall
Clinton worth
Call home by Saudi Arabia
There's something really interesting that I noticed his listen
Like he doesn't accuse people being owned by China
He doesn't know he knows everybody
The Chinese took over for this outing
That is basically how it sounds if you go back to give us to this
He talks about Saudi Arabia in the same way I mean not definitely not the same way
In terms of who owns the globalist
Who's running 85
Okay pretty quick it is kind of
Also
Accurate
Many of these politicians can be bought off by
Many different people at the same time if they would like to
You know
I mean obviously he's full
Call chat about all of that but it does maybe point
Deeper tryst
No I mean not a deeper truth
I think I think anytime
There are special interest that has undo it
Influence
Manar
Our political process that something
The tribute we should be careful about
But no I don't think there's an underlying to see what I think Alex is
Choosing enemies based on
That could be true
Much like Bill Gates is part of the 12 and then he's middle-management hasil part of the ruling Elite group of Ariel
There is that Trump is come out
Consumption
About jab because he's
Rim primary again
Text Chad
You stupid a******
And Alex believes this to be like expert
Games
What is just laying out the facts
The Daylights out of them
The guy has Myra
Totally now
He's incredibly bold
Ron Paul or smile like that
I mean
People like Matt Drudge
And Clarence
DIA
What happened there
I mean trumpet didn't
Exposed
I don't think he did
Alexa is presenting this is like yeah
He's talking he's talking this s***
And then they're going to call him a 9-11 truther and then he's going to prove himself right on the grandest stage of them all
None of it happened none of it ever happened
Everything that they say is going to happen doesn't
The only thing that happens is be a rosian of Rights for the rest of
Trump though
Better than Bernie
What's interesting about this
Is that until
Literally recently before this
Looks like bird
Because he was like with the Paul's only people who
Who is interested in like
Federal Form
Couple years before this a year before this
He says he's a socialist but you know he's got
Some good stuff and he hangs out talk to Rand Paul
Okay
Spell
He forgets all of those
Problems that he has now now you f****** hate
Of course he hates burn
And
Should tell you
Bernie didn't have a job until he was 40
Alex
Nice
He was he was elected
Mayor when he was 9 years old
Not important
Scream
Didn't have a job
Until he was 40
Alex Converse Lake
Protected over the toilet
Alex
Jordans
Mike down to this
Alex was forced into
The child labor
At the age of 12
Says a lot of good things and I don't want to see her to be enemies
Conservatives because they're a million light-years better than
Bernie Sanders who has now emerged
Never had a job till he was 40
I mean
I'm 42 I have a job when I was 12
Are child labor laws
Summer
I already know some yards and stuff he said he was at the bunch of baloney
You go down to Walker Marina which is a mile
And you will ask those old guys in there and tell him
You want a job you work for whatever they give you
Maybe I could do the job you'll get a raise
Do you have to keep doing that you don't have a job there years later to be a manager
Another time
2 years of passing the marina
Manager at the marina when I was like
Boats
Stop
Cleaning boat stalls
Sprint hourly wage
When you don't want to be doing that
Clean that stuff up and I'll give you a rich man
Stuff that's good
Good stuff
I love it
Totally right there are child labor
The nine-year-old should be feeling our jobs put him down in the marina that's me what is it going to be cold again
No that's dirty.
Nothing cleaner than Marina twelve-year-old
That story is not uplifting now
Modes of laundromats headset f*** you get down there and get a job
You'll be a manager by the Tigard 7th grade
I'm sick of the 1%
Marina Labor Ready
We've been fighting
20 years now
Alex was a scab but the SS Marina
Kidnapped so Alex
I would say that my sense of him is
What he does is
He gets on air and he just says bulshit
Sure
Because that's
What I experienced
Strum listening damage
The guy who gets on Aaron says about Chipotle think I would agree with you yeah
It's kind of like just buy it
Extinct
The knee-jerk reaction kind of his make stuff up
Conspiracy identified during his deposition in a lawsuit he did say that he had a bit of a
Psychosis that he developed or you just thought that everything was fake
You got into that
But you should tell you that it's not actually
That's not actually true
I don't just
Default
And Shay
You think I'm happy
Is about a 98% chance that killed Scalia
You think I want to be the one that breaks
I want to be the one
Runs over the top
Totally
The first one to go up Against the Machine Gun Nest
I'm telling you this
Something does happen to me
Bummer to save your family
Alright
Okay that's alright okay if they come back
For me for this
Blockbusters Scalia news
Val Kilmer
And then they'll come for you and random listener
Okay
I would say that I was absolutely
Needs
This to be a conspiracy the idea of
Antonin Scalia dying of old age or heart condition
Natural causes
Did Alex get to s*** with that know and it's unfortunately a very reasonable thing at the time
Yes 100% Alex's Lane
In terms of news and broadcasting and everything
Actor held like a tragic event like someone dying or however you want to look at the Aventador
Marble
Maybe sad maybe newsworthy event
That just happened
There's no spin to that now needs to be a
Villain
Family needs to be aggrieved a murder.
Does Alex yeah no way for this to be processed by the
Ivan gets a very lucrative thing to do exactly
You know what
I would probably think much
Less of him
If you didn't
Just like
I mean he's got
People who have his back
We're saying the same thing
Experts
It's all over the place Michael Savage says
He was murdered
What is Michael Savage
Billions of dollars in real estate nutraceuticals
Best-selling author
Launch the entire
Organic food
Under another name another number to Plum
Listen Alex Jones
What is an you have to do with whether or not Michael
Tell
Thoroughbred look at a news articles if it was murder
IQ you can solve mysteries from afar with no information then everything that Alex said is accurate
Yeah yeah let's not listen to Michael Savage
He likes organic
Food
Yeah okay
Are you giving me a lot of qualifications and get none of those was murder investigator
That would have been a really good one if you would have been like
200 IQ and also 20 years ago
Investigative experience
That's a whole different
Matlock is based on Tracy the lawyer who's a detective
I'm telling you Murder She Wrote
Stabler
Alex doesn't like the the European
Absolutely not
So Alex is appealing to Michael Savage
Thinking that it's
Possibly murder
I'm tired of people thinking that
He himself
Alex Jones is a coup
Because he has the best
Sources
Alright well one of them is Mike
Michael Savage so that's not
Well yeah but I mean
When CBS
Sydney Morning Herald call me a kook and a nut
Do you have contacts and eat dinner with the Supreme Court Justices and its say that total tyrannies coming in 2016
Everyone
Matt Drudge
Contacts
Army Special Forces
People above
Psychological warfare
Apartment on that Steve
Commander
Delta Force people in studio on air
No you don't
You don't have anything but this honor
And the fact that you're
Scum
I think this is really fun because I can tell who almost all those people off
Noah's Ark real services
What he doesn't understand is that yes
Part of the job of a journalist is cultivating sources who are near the primary
How do you know people who eat dinner with Supreme Court Justices
Probably if that's what they cover
That was Matt drudge and Alex's said that you'd only talk to drugs that one time you shut up Studio game
Interview
And now Matt drudge's on the outside
With the UB trumpy and World there
Ben Steven there you got
Green Beret I think is my bracket
Stuff so stupid
No lieutenant colonel
No
No you should have dropped in like I know
300 lieutenant colonel
I think that a lot of those military ranks and stuff that he does like
Chiefs of
Just on the Fly
It's just random AI suspect
Trump Alex says that he's he's on a suicide mission to save America
But you know he's also a little bit of an egomaniac
Call Eniko maniac
And the people that have testing said he's a good egomaniac
He's the type we need
And I just admire him so much leaves are high-level government people
Input children together CIA United
And I mean
Last generation actually overthrew government
Actually did stuff on the ground and just play around about the nsa's
Spy gear that's Steve again
I really don't understand why you're taking the overthrow governments as a point of
Right here
The government's that Steve pieczenik
Quote-unquote helped overthrow
You like driving
He should be against
Whatever
The thing that I really enjoy going back and listen
Alex is so simple
Again
Like he like characteristic
Phrases epithets are used in
In like
Homeric poetry luckily are the Odyssey
Alex does the same like overthrows countries that she always
Unifier
Ridgefield pechenik
Bridgeville Botanica
Took over countries and killed Aldo Moro
Agamemnon
Yeah I think that's really fun because you can just go back and listen to this be like I know
Your friends are dumb
How do italics
Yelling here and it felt really like
This is
This is like
What
Spoiler alert
But
I felt so much more like
You know what you're doing
Better
The good
It's because people know I've been around 20-plus years
I know where I came from
They know who I am
We're as American As It Gets
And we will never sell out anybody we will never screw over little people
For freedom
What I'm asking you right now because
We have succeeded waking up a lot of
And this is a serious battle
I want to get into the restaurant eleven isn't back into school yeah I haven't even got into it yet
Thunder operation right now
That feels like that feels more like
That's Alex's wheelhouse
Yelling about the America I love riding a battle.
It doesn't it doesn't
DeLand
Near I mean it's gross
Somehow it doesn't
Feel the same growth as best present day stuff done now maybe it's the lack of
Sure there is this not specifically kill Scalia
Human actors 222a possibly done it on their own
Yeah yeah there's there's no demonic nonsense there's no everything goes back
To China everything
It's it did the show makes more sense if you was more grounded in reality in the in the same way that everything
Is nonsense and crazy
The trumpian influence that made everything insane
Expediency
I just can't get the idea of Alex Jones in like that drawing-room murder mystery
Gathered you all here
At this dinner table
To eventually solve
The Prime with all of you again
If you're going borrow then it's I mean spoiler alert for the murder on the Orient Express
Alex could be 40 in that because the solution is everyone dead
Alex
Everyone to go out I was thinking more Nick and Nora where there's about three different red herrings until somebody just randomly
Tulsa Gun
I'll get to
Why we ended up doing this episode
Takes a little bit of the randomness away
Larry Nichols
Knows what
Ocean Washington on record
New York Times are scared of Larry Nichols
I figured I needed to talk
Scalia's death
I don't know if he's going to get to this on air yet
But it is just over the top
Stop and I just I wish I could
Larry Nichols is who Alex gets
The comments and have some
Some deep insights on the death of Aunt
Pensacola
One thing I want to make abundantly clear before we get into anything
If you listen to that clip it's clear that Alex's referencing something Larry has told him off air
Alex and Larry will go out of their way to pretend they did not talk off air
But Alex is very clearly saying that they
Did Scalia died on a full moon because that is when witches have their greatest Power Idaho this
I know this for a truth
So it only makes sense that you would call Larry Nichols
You got a call I've got to call Larry Nichols
One thing is made me really sad lately is
In present day
Just passed away not too long ago
And I'm not sure if it happened on some episode that I didn't
See or maybe during his Marathon at like 3 in the morning they did a 21-gun Street
But I haven't heard hide nor hair of rest in peace Larry Nichols any kind of memorialize
I'm sure on some weird YouTube channel that I don't know of and bio put on by someone I've never
Hurry up before I
Is eulogizing Hammond in some meaningful way
But I know that I touched on this a tiny bit but I really resent it really bums me out to me
YouTube yeah I just want to texted you earlier that we have to memorialize Larry Nichols it's feels weird to me for somebody to have
I'm such an outsize impact into
Go with
No Fanfare yeah I don't want to turn this into some kind of thing we're making a joke of the fact that he passed
I want to recognize
Like Scalia
Acknowledge him for who he was
You and he mattered
Goddamnit like yeah
Look I don't even look at the world as it is obviously is it you know it
Is the Scooby-Doo Nichols isn't the most famous person on the plane that went down
You know so I get why it's like
If this was a slow news day maybe somebody digs out
You know like right as did here's what he ruined do you know all that stuff but
To have nothing from
People who are like his friends
If you were somebody with a couple of good albums and you died
The same here as Bowie and Prince like you're never going to rank in the retrospective
Perhaps
For our show we like look at Alex
Stop
Larry Nichols is such a huge part of Alex's
Career his history
From the 90s when the
Clinton's are actually in play president
Through the times of our listening to it like a 2015. Where
Larry's talking about witches
Most memorable things on our show have come from like
Haha
I'm actually very sentimental about a girl
Call Larry Nichols
Yeah it was referencing to Wayne Madsen story
Sanders
Yeah it sounds like some of the things that have been the most
Funny
Have been things like when
Larry threat
Heading to Blackmail Robert Butler
Larry Larry goes into a Hall of Fame
All-time big swing
Obama wants to
Crash the entire world so you can be king cuz if you're the president when everything goes down you can come
And everybody
Who's hitting Congress because Dukes
Secret
Oh man just hard rice off rice like listening to Larry Nichols lied about
Space about hard drives
Softer ice Adam Schiff to Egypt
Here
He brought a lot of joy in terms of being somebody who's so desperate
So craving
Such a real s*** head
Parent liar
It was pretty easy to mock
A lot of the things
Yeah but like you're saying it's
It's a result of the big
Sweat
You know if that guy will miss that there are plenty of episodes from past week
I wanted to check in on
One of the times that we had
Alex
So I called and Larry
Story
For a big story
And I don't know baby Alex couldn't get ahold of Steve
Maybe
Scalia we got Larry Nichols Memorial house down to Grand Prix doing
The Aptoide
So earlier in the episode Alex had said that it was 98% chance yes Kalia was murdered
I was going to going to downgrade that just said
And I reporters on the ground in Southwest Texas
First mission
Cheyenne
People begging the media
Level
And they are
Are concerned
Obviously your folks see this for what it is it's
97% chance of receiving skill
Love it
Thank you for being more specific
Alex Jones is a master of lowering estate
Waterford what percentage down because establishment journalist are only afraid
I did not confirm 98%
Liberty Clinic
97 Brothers
Look I rounded up from 97% to 98% as we all know normally do
That was great
Imprecise imprecise
So stupid
I like it
But it's dumb
Alex plays a little bit of Georgia
Straits coming out of commercial alright and I both like this
George Strait bringing a sham of an oldie but a goodie Amarillo by Morning
I'm from San Antone
And we are joined the next 30 minutes by Larry Nichols
That is just two different shows right there
I'm coming in
He's just
Got the wrong job traffic on the 22
Wrong with that just keep going
It's it's a it's a guy coming in for a talk show that
Just boring and nothing is going on at the beginning and then we're going to talk to Larry Nichols for half hour
Difference
Straight right now a traffic on the 94 with Kennedy is moving a little bit slowly but other than that
We got noted conspiracy theorist in wacko Larry Nichols come on in here you might be asking yourself what exact
Play does Larry bring two
To the table
Supreme Court Justices
Just passed away Horse Casino
What is the topic what are we going to be talking about
Is a tough old egg
Joins us on clearance
Thomas
Endanger
And I'm just going to leave it at that
Let's see what he has to say about it
And how that ties into
This Kaliyah
Situation
Now
Here's
The game that's being
Play
They are insisting
Clarence Thomas
Cold Larry Nichols
Awesome inside baseball information
But yes
Larry can't
Confirm or revealed
He talks to Clarence Thomas and Alex give up
The game but he also knows
Probably b******* and he wants Larry just to say it
Clarence Joe Thomas doing
Like the game that they're playing is that both of them need the audio
To believe all this
Information is coming
From Clarence Thomas
Sabbath right right
Of course he does
Cuz it's.
The dancing around like an idiot like this
So Larry wants
To be clear
Right out of the gate
It doesn't have any proof of any
I had not
Anyone and I would call Shanaynay
Everyone
You know true definition
Patriot I believe Alex
True
And I wanted to
Be certain of
The truth
Before
I did the same with you or anybody else
Korea
Just about an hour ago
Nation I'm getting
Gas station
I'm not saying
Diabetes
Okay
Now Patriot is somebody who's interested in
And the truth and I didn't want to come on your show before I knew the truth an hour ago
Clarence Thomas called me
This thing stinks
I don't know anything about the truth
But I'm seeking it out
I'm a patriot
How does it matter if I'm right or not I do notice it doesn't matter if you
You get the truth you just say
Speak it out I'm going to do everything in my power to prevent Clinton a murderer
I can't breathe
Hold my feet to the fire
This dance of life
Considerate but also I refuse to be defended
What are you a military specialist on CNN get the
We're in a situation where Scalia to wear
This thing burning out of control
Who did it why did they do it
It was done
Is usually
When it walks like a duck
Quiet
I'm afraid that's where we're headed
Forget one thing
Important things
Career
The future of the welding to remember whatever
Appointment
Supreme Court Justice
I forgot the
You tell me
Does it look like to you
Ducks
Who
So we have
I don't know the who
I don't know the
I don't know if it happened
But if it looks like a duck
What if what looks like a duck
Nohu water if
But if it looks like a duck but it was murder
I like it I like it because he has no bones about it
Just look like everybody else
Pretends they have
Any like proof for it needs is like
I don't know what's going on I don't know why it's going on
Probably murder
Probably
It's probably an Arkansas side of course
Absolutely proven definitive most prolific serial killers
You will kill again maybe 1,000 people
The murder she's committed yet
Remember what we used to do
The Arkansas
Committed suicide
But at the same time
Who was the only person that benefit
Teavana
Now
Look at this case
Are the only people that
Benefit
Nobody
I'm telling you
It's starting to look bad
Starting to look bad for
Even if you just take Larry based on that clip his standard Hood being a narc
Inside fails to be met
He said that I have to be like an impossible suicide
Which it was
So that classic feature the Clinton murders
Not present well then there's the question of who stands to gain or
Call Alex
Qui Bono
Smart guy
What would naturally think
The queen who stand to Bono sancak
Conservative justices dad and Obama's president so we can replace Scalia with a Progreso
Idiots the plant been looking back
I would have to conclude that
No one was interested in following through with that
Is there some kind of a conspiracy that involves the murder of a Supreme Court Justice which pays off with a
Appointment of a new more liberal Justice
Kind of make
For the group
To be powerful enough to pull off the hard part and completely fuk up
Easy almost procedural Parts insanely easy part as we are now discovering
What possible explanation could there be for this group have gone through with the killing of
Scalia then when it's time to replace
Into a congressional standoff
The explanation can't be that the
The GOP opposed
The globalist
Because at this point there's
Still very much a trump creepy picture
At the time this episode The GOP primaries still ongoing with Ted Cruz Marco Rubio Ben Carson and Jeb Bush
All still having activecampaign
Carly fiorina
Chris Christie had dropped out there of the race within a week
From this report
The deal. Not yet bend over backwards entirely
And there was a large
Ted Cruz
Pepper is winning the Iowa caucus
Competitive showing on super Tuesday
Which actually hadn't even happened by the time of this route
What I'm getting at is that it's
This point the GOP is still the Blueblood never Trump Republican party that Alex
Isn't league with the global
Mitch McConnell who spearheaded the blockage of Obama Supreme Court nomination process
Wouldn't even endorse Trump until May and in June he was quoted in the New York Times of being open to
Rescinding that Dorsett
Course
Is there was anything to the globalist
Conspiracy to kill Scully and replace him
Then based on the political alignment that Alex has established
There's literally no reason why McConnell in the GOP should be getting
In the way of that plan
Miss big hole in the theory of the Qui Bono
In this case no one went
There's a part of me that wants
To that wants to respect
Mitch McConnell for pulling off one of the most
Blatantly bulshit things that ever happened
But the more I think about it the more I realized
888 was just he was playing against the stupid Epona
Like all he did was make up some b******* and got people to believe it it was thought there were rules because
Do work better when there are rules part of the rules they are just willing to accept rules that are made
For them to deal with its varied it's very pathetic
Well I'm more disappointed with the with the people who continually allow match
McDonald's
He's figuring bulshit isn't
Saying yeah it is unfortunate then people
Just continue to take
Something like that seriously
Piano 8 look
Some elements
Scalia's death that maybe could be taken as a message well as family care
Well I don't know if that's
It's true but there was a pillow
Beautifully dyed in bed
The pillow
And immediately it was reported that it was all like on his face
But that is not accurate
I was just on his head because he was laying in bed
But this is a mess
Okay
The pillows on
The face is that a messaged everybody though that he's awake
Bank
I think they're trying to let us know
I think they're trying to let someone
I know Alex and Ani
Maybe.
Maybe the other
Judgeszone
Court judges you talk to him
Yes
That
Just f****** Clarence Thomas
The idea that if there was a pillow on his face
It was Nae
Tous message
Do people who are awake
Because if you're awake
Don't put the pillow on your face into pillows under your head
Then you're fine
Clarence Thomas
Illuminati Lodge in the middle of Texas
I don't know
Anyway Larry safe
Because he's at home
Yes and he's got a big old knife
With which to hide off a cliff
Every time
Clinton's get nearby
People going
This is not
And this won't be the last
Universalis
Back here behind me buddy I got
Pepsi man
18 inch Bowie that I
Keep with me
Play Rock
No
From everything I say
Message
What the
F*** are you safe
Am I saying it was a hit but I asked
Slippery a******
Every did it did it happen
I don't even know
A Scalia dead
Not
I can't prove it but however
It smells fishy
Message message
Someone already
Next clip starts with the lyric I'm just going to diffuse this out
I can't imagine a scenario where
An old man in poor health
With an 18in knife
Could fight off whatever the clintons
I assume the place now where I am assuming they think that Hillary does it
It must be Ava and then like
Covered head-to-toe in one of those play
Plastic I had a really good idea for a product
Balaclava in the shape of a looks like baklava
Arosso with a baklava
What is a balaclava mask but it looks like baklava
In the shape of a
Someone's made think so
Anyway
Diffusing gas
Larry starts this next clip talking about how butts or puckered
With fear
Connect mic down for this because
Everything goes
Very obdurate
Mine right now Anderson
I'm going to walk my dog
Is a big
Black
SUV that is pulled up I'm on a walk make sure
Bet they're not
Inside this house
I know what you told me 20 minutes
I can't stand her in the stuff might be able to talk about it
Which doesn't believe that for us
No
0 if that were true even if he thought it was even a little
Oh who do you think
You could be not even that just
I heard what you said
I'm sick of it
Larry's got a van outside
And
You heard him.
You heard him
Still sitting. I'm going to head over to the door
Well I actually a really certain that there's not anything going on outside his house for a reason
A little bit out there
Apparent allegedly he looks out there
He audibly
Continues to sit.
But the van
And then turns out
Devan
Makes a reappearance later
Saturday morning I don't know what I was like four other times
I called Mikey manager
Get to the office now
Hell's about to break loose and we're all here
For 7 hours
Broken leaving no cuz I was in my conference room
Screaming saying something Big's about to happen I didn't know this it happened yet
The SUV back
There
Don't worry
I got that 18 inch knife
Is there sitting there and I'm sitting here
Sure about your butt was very Park
Record right don't know that was just general
And a lot of people have it
Because of the death of us
Quickly makes this van up hearing
Has to do with the fact that
Got a call from
Clarence Thomas an hour before this
Tell me what it is
Just found out an hour and a half
People being my yard just quit
Dummy
I mean
They didn't even
Bothered
Cover the shop
Regional
Maven
Vineyard
So it is a murdering you do know that
What are you doing
What is the story
Everything
What do you think the story is
U-Pick
You know what I like about this I like that Alex is Like Larry
The people that kill you
He's exhausted with the idea of trying to keep this going
Those guys who are outside your house right now tell you
Outside of your house heater
War of the Worlds but he's just like
Are there aliens outside my door oh boy
Sure as long as those aliens are out there and I'm in here outside
Call Betsy
I mean
I have to eat my hat
Because there's
Proof okay
Barnacles is weather for holding him over he did on his show
That
When he comes back out
But it was pretty clear
Larry trying to hold
Scream
Close you can
In front of
Your face in an inning forward
Towards the camera
I'm trying to find
Send it again at
I know you're not super technical believe me I know
I don't know what I've done with that was holding it up
Delete that
Aldo where is your picture
Just f***
Toca Toca videos
Darius
Is so hilarious it's like Alex
Clearly frustrated video video is Larry sitting in his living room
Holding a flip phone
Oh my God
What are we doing
Lexus
Self figure it out to be a problem
Because if
Obviously even Larry and Alex realize like no one believed
Yeah
When I had it is the SUV still there
Get up get up
Backup
No one second
Go out there were going to stay with you
Drive off
Nearest Wells he's not
He's not be icing
Cbs's job
Now if you would need to say that if I wasn't already convinced that he was only being full of s*** yeah
If you notice
Larry's dog bark
Oh yeah
There
Tells you is that
The dog wasn't barking earlier there was a van there people were out
It was very threatening
The dog had no interest
Yeah
Leary's feelings about scalia's death
Let me let me search back through my
Pictures to find that picture I suppose
Italy just took right now
I'm not going to come down on the two hard for that because it is a flip phone
And those things were really difficult to navigate to
Larry had my phone
So
He was still using a Motorola
At the time
So they do eventually flash up what's
Supposed to be a picture of the van in Fry
Phone videos
Anything definitive proof
I can see the plates
It's when my mind's eye the clearest
Picture ever
Of someone in a van to taken with
I still do pick up crew Getty Images
Alex
I wish I was there or wish I was there to protect you
I confront that trance
Oh I wish I was there right now
Do you have any family that's home right now
No just me
Me and you
And your bulldog in the millions watching and listening
For folks that are in
Arkansas right now
Alex tells like truckers who are in the area to show up at Larry's house
Look at the number
Let's see if people around will stop by your house I guess I wish I was there Larry I have to act like I care
If Alex likes
Sincerely believe that Larry's life is endangered
Because he's talked to Clarence Thomas who is told Larry that it's
Head now there's a black van outside Larry's house that's going to kill him
They should not stop the interview for anything
The only thing it's protected lyrics
Alright lyrics
We're going to let you go hope you survive buddy all right we'll see you later
The weirdos at a trump rally
Much like the pillow
Is a message
Okay
What is this all about
They're sending a message
Have you looked outside your building
Really worried about it
This is like Larry you're full of s*** and I'm not worried the games up
The radio theater
Game is up Larry come on
I think you know what sucks to is like I think of Alex or more of a giving partner
I think that they could make this work
Yeah I think of Alex were acting actually concerned or scared or anything like that he could real
Lehighton this into being something that like
I don't know I think Larry is the reason that we're we're not getting anything good out of this cuz whoever's just coming with two big
Swing with the van and the lies
It's perfect with you
If you're trying to be like
Of course there is an outside
Yeah there has to be
DirecTV
I don't know who did it
I don't know what happened and I don't know if it even happened at all
That's not what's going to get you killed man
You say an hour one
Okay Diana is to
Basically treat this like a hostage situation where you taking Alex's show hostage
Pictures of an outside cat live
When you bring it home all right and I didn't know what was going on
So I see a sequel to Stockholm syndrome on this one right here
Did they make a third Speed movie
You have to keep your b******* playing at less than 40 miles an hour otherwise
I hate I hate to say this
That's like his kind of like
I don't know
Disrespectful people's reality but
This isn't real
I could have written this way better
If I were a producer Infowars I could have been like guys
This is just
One week away from being interested if you guys are just embarrassing The Shadow
Yeah you got to sell it
Yeah you got to sell it they're not selling
Steak should be in Orem
And if you're presenting this as Larry has really really super deep important information that he's gotten
Salvador
You have a responsibility to
To give something
And I'll tell you what that thing should not be
Just the fake van
The fake vegan
Not going to do it
But it's important
Is important is a looming threat
Sure you need you need your a story to be strong
And then the van is a great Beast or protagonist antagonist
To be a little bit more thought out than this
You need the actors
Alex and bleriot yeah be a little bit more invested you need them like Alex
Seems to
Poo poo in be almost the entirety
Of this well I mean it's too it's really transparent Larry like we do
Yeah there is that but that's
I think again that's Larry's fault he's
Instead of the who what if
Alright
You got to get least give me if
You know like he's not even willing to commit to it was a murder other than being like
It looks like a murder
Like that the Alex needs you to give him something in order to get excited as possibly Beaver Larry
F****** Nichols
Clarence Thomas said that his family killed
Clarence Thomas found the body
You saying it if you saying the Clarence Thomas said it which is obviously it's like there's no in
In court there like all this is Libor something and it's like
It's Larry Nicholson Clarence Thomas said that
His family killed him what are you going to call this
What are we doing
Yeah public figures
And I would say I don't believe that there is an actual relationship
Between Clarence Thomas
And Larry Nichols
To be protected
Absurdity of Clarence Thomas
Giving Larry Nichols
Call
Just by itself while goes bye-bye
Up
So
Why don't we make fun of the idea that
You know if you're president when
Chico's Downey become king
Congress you become a duke or Duchess that is something we met
Larry says it a lot
This this election will be the last presidential election
Actually made me a little bit sad
Because it is true
Did not make it to
The 2020 election
The last election he got
Pig farting
It is
I'm sorry it is
I want to tell you something
We've never had
Do we have right now
Applications that are running for office
Run
This country
And they want to be there Alex
Of the Centrist
That's left over
And I know
They're out
Forever
And then they then they can be prosecuted so there
2018 midterms didn't
No they
They didn't
The new other people got in
Surrounded
But that they ran on make me your Duke
Rose where most of the campaigns that I heard
Duke of Chicago
Is the
I don't want Dick Durbin to be my duke
Get the f*** out of
Duke Dick Durbin that's annoying I would that's the only reason I need a really good Saturday
I can't do.
Urban
Yeah
Silly silly nonsense
Hillary Clinton
She's going to run
Sharky is Ronnie
I actually was listening to this I thought how funny it would be if like
Larry
Passes away
Atman
Hillary Clinton
Does run
Tragic that would be sad
16 or else there'll be consequences
Does for her you understand now just win or lose for
Either she gets
Be what she wanted to be
Patient she was 4 years old
President of
United States
And pan
She goes to
Jojo
Chile game
If you look at some of the decisions being look
Supreme Court
Thank you Sissy
Aaliyah
So you're saying it was Hillary
Yes I'm pretty sure he's saying it was Hillary Clarence Thomas
It's called him an hour before this show
I said that Hillary killed Scalia
That sounds true
Music that's the sense that you probably would get
If you were an Alex Jones listener anywhere listen
Coming to this complete
Nothing
They're doing
Because they're not giving any information just like all of this
Like nutty insinuation
It's not even really speculation
It's it's it's not even like analyzing any of the information involved no literally just saying I think it looks bad
I don't know why I don't know how
It's creating a narrative and then also
Constantly saying like
This is annoyingly pointless
You know
I always enjoy it when you left
Listen to a podcast
Maybe one of the hostesses learn
Something new to our you know it's like
Mind blown. Larry has just learned something
Alex
About that
Until this weekend
Call Mama sunshine
Residential specialist
And a hundred miles on either side
Border to the north
Canada
Hundred miles either side South
Mexico
Atlantic
Ocean
The Pacific
Is considered or called
What's it called
No
The tution song
Absolutely
Can you make no comments
Constitution expressly prohibits
Miles from
The border is the No Flex
True
You're not wrong
Kind of a real thing although it's not like I mean it's not the same as what they're saying
Think about the dhs's ability to operate even though there are federal agents yeah yeah
Caption for search
Within 100 miles of the border which is just
Certified by
A reasonable distance from the borders
Customs and immigration
I have that kind of leeway
Which worked out great for us thanks Obama I'm sure that's never going to be abused by some other admits out and they come
Then immediately after the problem
You're buying into Larry's bulshit Obama didn't do that he didn't know he didn't create that
You didn't find an article from Wired from 2008 about hubby ACLU was fighting
To curb the use of this as a police search tool
Predates Obama's time in office
Hey something it's always existed as an exemption for Border searches
And it was codified into law in 1976
Text but after 9/11
The definitions of what specific area around the Border could be this kind of jurisdiction Organics
Real issue it have solutely it and it's something
You know someone who Alex pretends to be
This figure in the space that he
Likes to fancy himself
Talking about importing out
But it's
Just pointless to pretend that Obama did in the game that Larry wants playing
That's bulshit
Also Congressional Democrats introduced legislation to reduce the area from 100 Mi to 25 back in 2019
But baptized legislation went nowhere
Announcer probably say was just them trying to flood the country with undocumented immigrant
He probably be in favor
How's this hundred-mile No Flex Zone
Yeah nothing
Anyting
Exhausted particularly exhausting about that Isabel like okay what you're talkin
Sing about
We could both
Be opposed to 4
Completely different reason
Larry Nichols could both be again
Answer this hundred-mile quote-unquote no Constitution Zone
But we would never we should never
Be able to work together on the issues we actually don't I mean
Thing about that though is
Even if we come to it from differin
Perspectives
That does mean that we could just
Stop it
You know
Like I can just stop doing it
That's the thing that they boggles my mind all too often with this stuff is like
Yeah Larry
Let's f****** get rid of that 100 miles bulshit
I'm with you so let's all just do that
But it never be
It's just one of those
Political inertia things where it's just like that seems like too much work
Wow
Anyway
We have one last leap year from the 6
And it's
Alex
Fixing the issue
Embarrassed
Larry will be killed by the people in that van
Who will Larry Nichols call
What's going to be on their own
Call me
Australian contacts
Amazon speed dial
Skype connected
I want to go let them know when it's
Getting turned off
By my friend
I am embarrassed and contacted and you'll be back
Back with us tonight
You have the info let us know we'll tape it
Because yeah they've got their operatives and other people
The wine.
Here in town
Activate those people
Just keep it up
God bless you
And ask
Real folks I still got a paludarium medicine I got to get I got nothing to get it with so I'm in bear
Come out 20 years never ask for help.
You're broken
AOL News man get a van out in front of your house
You can't
Hey man
That makes me a little sad cuz I'm 5 minutes away for
From Death doesn't mean I still can't
Can't plan for the future
He's not on the Nightly News
Evening February
The next time that Larry's name shows up in the episode description
For Alex's
And this is the next time that Larry was on
And I wanted to know what the fuc
Clarence Thomas
You're sure because I listen to that whole thing
There was nothing nothing was just a fan
Nothing
Wearing a gold Platinum solder doesn't need any introduction
I'm interviewing him for 20 years
21 years
And he's a conference live inside of The Clinton Chronicles all of it couldn't be done without him to Larry's on
Let's talk about it
Let's talk about this information
Now I know early on in the Clinton ministration I tried to destroy certain people that will be nominated to Supreme
And they became an early Source on the internet for a lot of fun
Dog shelter
Annie battling cancer right now she needs your prayers that's another issue but one resentment almost last few days
To get ahold of
I imagine he's busy being a Supreme Court Justice and not asking any questions then
In General trying to destroy the world
Yeah so I mean hey
Appearance
February 16th through the 24th you know where a good eight days later
Larry has
Got Back
In touch with
Justice Thomas
Who they
Refuse to just
Be upfront about it could be any Supreme Court
Larry's go back on Alex
Because the audience
Naturally I completely agree the audience's reaction based on my listening
Has he talked as a good question
Need to know the information
Hope you're taking care of yourself thank you for coming on with this obviously people
Batman calling emailing tweeting
Alex where's Larry Nichols
When are you going to tell us what the Supreme Court Justice
Dad when you going to tell us what happened
Well you been busy and and weren't ready to comment you still say
This person now you talk to doesn't want to
Haven't they told you
Discuss
Let's start with the black
Sedan last
Was it last Wednesday
But you got photos of it driving away
Come back and talk about it
Guess what let's talk more about that
Wow
This is how hard
This is how I farted
No but it's
Yes it is half-hearted
But it is
Double humorous
What are nipples supposed to come on and give Alex a big
Scoop or at least take
Paquete for some kind of bulshit narrative something
Beautural this like buildup of Clarence Thomas called you like
It was good it was set
The foundation was there
Larry refused to play ball Lanza playing all you got to do is land the plane look at that van out there isn't that scary
The whole thing we can go back to
Hayward weather
What are we doing you want to know about that
Well technically what
That was was Homeland Security
Text me and I told the police here
But they had no jurist
Pretty much
Let them
Leave that I had a one-way ticket
What that meant I have no idea
Kensington Drive Conway Arkansas
Come on
Let's do what you got to be done just don't bore me to death
Thanks a lot
Evan has to do Alex
Not how I end up
In the middle of this drunk Alex I never can
Figure out
All-you-can-eat
Jamaica.
I loved that moment for two reasons
What does do we got to do if you feel for me
Just egg kill me or tell Kelly I'll boy
Cocky cocky assholes which I love
How do I find myself in the middle of these six
Record scratches
Play ended up becoming entrenched in Clinton
Conspiracy theories
Because I made up a bunch of bulshit
A
Khalid
How do you like being here again
They said that I mean
There's no way there's no spelling out what was going on
Other stories
I actually got another bit of news for you
The Republican hierarchy this tab
They have decided
Go fighting Donald Trump
Dragon fighting
Wow
Wow it's not quite what you think
Haha they're not going to fight him
At the convention they're going to f*** it okay that makes sense contested convention
Get screwed
It's pretty boring
And far more
Tristan is Larry trying to rationalize why
Obama hasn't just put in
A Supreme Court Justice
Dictator
He's a tyrant yeah yeah we based on every
Recharacterization that they've ever had of a lollipop
The only reason the Republicans are blocking the hearing
In the hearing is
Used to get them through this election
Incycle
Winston November
Situation with Obama
Put in Spring Court Justice
Legislature or the next Congress Obama keep saying into time people want it now he's going to wait till after the election
What shows is a deal going on
Exactly
Now this happen
Nope just making it up
Honestly
I think I would have preferred that happen
It's an interesting rationalize why the GOP is acting like
An adversarial party with
Your entire worldview depends on them being the same
Yeah yeah it is
Is an interesting way to walk around that
Although
In every way
They're still
Discuss
Larry and Alex discussed a bit
2015 and that was that Obama was going to
King For Life sure sure
Discuss that here a little bit
They steal it from from
There's going to be civil unrest
And maybe that's what Obama wants
He's got his black lives matter group
Fallout ready to activate
You know that's
Nothing better
To get cheated out of
Direction to there to be an uprising and then boom
You don't have to worry about it
KB
Qbking
Forever glitched
We know how King
Do that they just get done
Exactly the situation that Alex
Describes all the time where it's like
I know that's what they would do
That's what I would do like listening to them describe all of the stuff that Trump is actively trying to do
Feels like he's there's that's one of the things that makes me always be very like hyper
Cautious about foxes
Like that
Am I succumbing
Two similar feelings
As like what Alec
Sure
And if Obama had
And I'm going to be president for another
12 years I think there's a difference
Situation that really piss people off
Yeah it's not similar at all but it is
Lititz
Did you have to check in on it
Ryobi router
Right and the other things really interesting here is like you hear this
Alex is like
Obama got his black lives matter
Exact same thing
This is so four years in the past
But
One glaring difference
How to know about antifa even though he's
No mention of that or demon it seems like that would be really important about antifa
Teamed up with black lives matter and the devil
Right he should have warned us
Call Rebecca 26
16 G is already about to
Started
16 about Plan B
Help out with Plan B
Tell me one last leap year
From Larry's appearance on the 24th
I will say that my son
From listen
Sing to these interviews
Is it Larry wants the audience to believe that Hillary Clinton is behind the murder of Antonin Scalia
That sounds right
Seems to be
He's making point he's a little OneNote when we get down to it every everything
Wines of getting back to Hillary Clinton trying to kill
There's another clip I wish I would have got the
But there is a point where Larry
Seems to think that it's going to come down to him and verse Hillary
Like a matrix situation
Like Hillary is Agents
Smith and he's Neo and they're going to do battle is 100 calories
Alright that makes sense now
Do you like not like that belief system
I think that that is what he's pushing
As the thing that he wants the audience
To believe the Clarence Thomas and told him
He doesn't want the responsibility of having to be on the hook
For any of your charger yet
Observer Lee makes me pissed off when he says something like this
Let me say it this way if you know Alex
I have never said
Talking about Hillary
HEB
The kind of person that
Problem
Saying off the guy
Do it in a second
In a sec
That's
So
Unbelievable thing that I've made my
Higher career out of
You know I've never said anything like that no I've never killed anyone
But I know for about a bit but she wouldn't be up yet
Why would you do that
Why would you
Abused Us in that way
What is
World class
Deckshop
Anyway I don't care to
Mock the Dead
But I do think there's something
Still very fun
But celebrating the life in
Career
Somebody who
Was this transparent of covid-19
I need somehow made a career out of it. I believe
I mean we talked to Larry
You talked to him a couple times
2A shooting
Ozium on various shows
And I I don't I don't think you would be have a problem
Amethyst laughing at him no absolutely not
If I were him
I would expect
Yeah
No I think I think based on our conversations
This is it absolutely
Something that he would Delight him
Probably like when we talked to him and he was spitting his bulshit you could tell he had a bit of a smile on as we were like
You're foolish it and he's like
Believe what you want
He's like yeah we both know that we do believe that either.
Stop it
I mean no disrespect to his family members who who who survived him and
Like piss on a grave or anything
Do Daleks type terms
I do I also think that
I want to take a moment Direct
Acknowledged the brand of b******* is
Live Science
It is a momentous
Mobile weather
Alex will accepted or not sure
David Mayer
Who I should go check
This is one of those things where it kind of feels to me like
This is the
Cutthroat world of
Right-wing propaganda is once you stop being useful
Whether you're alive or dead
You're just
I worry about that too and I worried about that too
Definitive statements is because
There are episodes that I haven't
Listen to Richard maybe two minutes of one of them is Alexei
Rest in peace Larry or something
Based on the import
Ancillary nickels to Alex
That's not good enough
There should be
Like Alex a commission to Musical
Or something about this great guy
Yeah you should have done
24-hour the greatest hits Marathon or something
It's still
Weird that it's weird that were like not to make fun of his death or not to mock
The family and yet
We're like the only people who are really paying attention to it
In the first place
It seems like they're dealing with it
Is is weightless it it feels like it is
Infuriated I care more than Alex
This is a brother-sister problem for me
Everyone is disposable to an extent like we saw how
Ignore Alex
Turn his back on folks likes Tulare if there
Their momentary brand of propaganda isn't what he dies
There's so many people who used to be
Affected experts who now we're just
You know not
Welcome
In the Infowars fear and then
You know it's it's a bummer it is a bummer because
It makes
It makes things very transaction
Like with Trump you know there's just no loyalty I don't understand why these people come
Some sort of
Loyal Rewards
The Bel Air
Just going to be tossed
Decide when they're useless
Until they come up with something
Cool
Egyptian sex party
Recipes Larry
Through the back
But until then Jordan website
Worlds 00
We are on Twitter that knowledge underscore fight not go to bed Jordan
We are on Facebook for like $2
Please find a local charity or bail Fund in your area to help out
Emilio Emilio
I was driving that black van
Alex
Kirsten color with huge fan I love your work