Damn important
I have great respect for its knowledge B
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Alex Jones
We are Dan Jordan
I've got it all right
My bright spot today Jordan is the word of the day
Oki word
Is forgiveness forgive
Alright I'm very hard on myself as very
Difficult for me to forgive myself
I let things go with other people a lot
More easily absolutely there's a middle ground
And that is cats
No I don't forget that
What about the Susa
I do forgive that
I've had to deal with resentment towards Celine my cat
For the better part of a couple days
Zion
I've reached the stage of forgiveness she can be a pill
Yeah yeah
I had
The room where I was growing some plants
Date setups
Yeah
And it was working pretty well between crafty
And so I woke up one morning and she had
Completely Des
Destroyed my pinto bean plant
And I was really mad about that cuz if they were coming along really nicely they look good and I thought it was really cool the process
Growing
You destroyed them
I thought that it was very cool that a pinto bean was growing
Express
True
I was pretty infuriated
Forgiveness
I understand that you didn't do it
B2B mean
No
Although maybe she
Yeah the attention I was given to these plants might be
Draws her ire
Starfall
I forgive you Celine Wherever You Are
You know danitsa it's better
Sweet spot
In some ways I met right song
It's no big my bright spot is very much
Related to
No keep saying it I want to try.
Cantaloupe
Time and I did a really good job well
It was going great
And then the first Frost took it out
Photo
It's sad because I was actually really trying to keep this one alive to my normal standoffish
Major towards plan
As you know I'm not a fan of the out-of-doors
That is true I don't know how to describe it as stand-offish
That seems like a little bit weird like you have a brisket
Care for them and their kinds of them and say all kinds of words to them and I very much want them to give me their approval how about that
Wow
The one-sided relationship
Plants could stand to be polite or to you I'll go with you
Well I'm sorry I'm sorry to hear about this I was partially invested in your
Stood longer than any plant that I've ever taken care of before and it's giving me like a nurturing towards plants that I didn't
Assertive progress
Progress
Forgiveness in progress
October 19th 2020
That was Monday
Monday Monday Monday
Tell most people start the week
And this this is a this is an interesting showing
Going today
I don't know
You shall listen to a bit of Alex's
In the recent past
And so much of it is just about Hunter Biden
And his laptop
And then
Weird conspiracies about Heather's videos
Of him torturing children the on the laptop which has been used to blackmail him and Joe Biden
Why not
Very little patience
For this storyline
The gate all over I'm really appreciating how the mainstream media seems to
Kind of been like
Not going to go with us
Let's see how this goes right-wing lunatic
But later in the story into they're covering it up
I find very little interest
And watching Alex go down those other things
To fill-in-the-blanks it wasn't just Alex talking about that laptop otherwise I don't know what I would have done
Very little address
Today's we get a visit
From
The surviving
Champion weirdo
Alex's
Is Click
What is the vagina
She shows up to give some words of wisdom
I guarantee you
You could never predict
What is solution to big tax I never would try
I've learned my lesson with pechenik he takes wings that I find heretofore unimaginable
Maybe we should make Melania Queen take
Mmm like in the ethers when you're capable
Can happen
Is the red wedding every single day
Anything can happen
To sign up for sports
First I just got out of rehab
I just got to rehab good luck Nikki
I'm a policy wonk
Are you very much will tell Nikki
Next Atlas Emma thank you so much you're now both walk
I'm a policy wonk
What is
I love it John Carlos Stanton
Mega Ball Millions
Jeremy m
Blue cheese yak
Thank you so much you are
Technocrat
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
Thank you so much effort easyacc
Website.com
What you could do is
Take that generous spirits that you were given from your close friend maybe even your bed
Best friend take it home
Waterous
Feed it
This is gibbet
Light
All of those things you need to grow up and make sure that you
You take that generosity
To a local bail fund
Or charity
Before the first Frost otherwise it will die
And will leave you deaf
Attitude and lonely bittersweet
Sweet
October 19th
I will say Alex
He's not
Singularly focusing on the laptop
Quite a bit about it
Laptop
And the big Revelations of Hunter and and not just hookers and not just sex and not just cracking not to
Just math
Doing illegal things
Underage
Portland beating
Little Chinese girls
It's part of him
Initiation
Enter the time
Does everyone have to do that
Apparently
Yeah I don't know I could Alex has a very strong burden
Yeah here and I'm just
Story about this
Now
Here's a thing about
From what I've seen you could just go with like
What they are
Lying about
You don't have to then escalate it to Heights that are just
Silly
Jordan
Something is it worked last time even then it's like you can believe Hillary Clinton
Does that I don't know
I don't quite understand what the the
The deal is
I also think there's a real
Miscalculation
Just strategically
I whip with a way Alex
Does playing this game with the election
Because I mean
The pole and they were saying is accurate and that has a pretty solid lead will win
But I don't exclude the possibility that Trump could win again
Then what
The devil do you think I'm going to win
Trump is obviously going to win with 97% of the vote and that's how you know it's a free and fair election
And I don't understand this pulling the people or do I just think he's backing himself into this weird space where it's like alright
If you lose then
Do is start shooting right I'm not like the devil has just taken out
How potent is the devil's threat
Electorally
What does
I just don't I don't do that that's what a lot of people don't know about the fall
Is it the devil just lost re-election is God in the devil running for God
Extinguish the devil's torch
It's just it's just a simple big deal out of
Beelzebub
The tribe has spoken
Whatever God was elected the center-right took Park
I just want to bring light to the people
We are out of here
God has an alliance with gaea and they voted the devil or something I don't know
The devil lock the election
I don't know I think it's a bad move
I am but I do just
See shades of the last election
Some of those washed over strategies
Intel
Proof is presented otherwise
That's kind of the the ballpark I'm living at look like we're living through is like that
I'm going
Will it work
Last time and then looking around and everybody was seeing them
Like a little bit different
There they've learned
It is it is almost heartwarming to see that there is a small percentage of the population that is
Still capable of love
It's nice
Alex
She doesn't she doesn't read
And it becomes very clear
And it goes on from there Sweden to start lockdown
Has the world 12
Highest covid-19
Yes right
Totally made-up Darvocet
In Europe
Alex accidentally read that headline did never spend for it to just head tonight
Play I disagree with it by going to end
He started it it was fascinated
Do you think every time we read headlines when he's off the air he has that rollercoaster ride of like
If he does I understand not reading
Yeah
Very intense
Exhausting day
Damn so we know that Alex likes
Thomas Jefferson quote
But here we get another quote
From a different person
Real
It's not all day
Trump knows he's going to win the election and this is now instead of
The threat is real
Waging War on corruption Alex Jones coming to you live from
The global Master Bank the genetic engineers
All the left devil worshippers worldwide
Radical Islam aligned with them
When they're great generals
Income and
Fusing together through a world fashion system
All these disparate groups into a giant
Got to destroy what's left
Only our slumber
Powers the devil
We must away
Born again
This is why is show sucks
And that's why they even go back to February 20th
16 episode where it's like
There's no devil
It is really annoying
It's really hard really hard to remember that I'm supposed to take Sarah
16 we are taking his political Viewpoint seriously exercise
On their own level
Approaching it from the position of is it possible to take food
Yeah there's Merit to almost always
Now it's almost impossible to pay that way it's literally
Like even for me to engage with him on
Possible
Ivan presupposed
Is that the devil is real
Right and then
Based on the plans that he says the devil has thousands of years back
Intent of
The devil
In biblical times
That's it it said it's your devil he had a plan
And the devil's play metal around
Yeah poke people's head for his
Create a really really hot
Resort
Give me so high
Miserable Resort
The dropout rate
Then
The culmination of his plan is
Joe Biden running
It's hard to imagine that like
I know back in the days like the prophet
So now you know the Old Testament that be like
Yes the devil the greatest trick he's trying to pull off his
Center-right
Presidency
You get back to the the problem with making your enemy enemy imaginary
Is then the limit of your enemy are your own imagine
So what you accidentally reveal is how little you are capable of Imagine
Things like I am
Not afraid of this.
No the devil that I am afraid of
Powers beyond what I can even imagine
Simply because I imagined him to
You have those power
Not
Getting Joe Biden
Any devil that's worth being afraid of you can't be
Exactly
It's the death
Turn off
Win against Eternal with
Joe Biden
Then there's nothing
Tramadol at The Ballot Box
That's not a great day.
That's not a stalling quote
Stalin
It was a
Something very close to it was attributed to Stalin in
His secretaries memoir
Doesn't come out
Until quite a while later
And their existing
Formulations of this quote
They predate Stalin being
Manpower
And so I know that's just one of those fun anti-communist
Ism's that Alex throws around
I imagine that that
Sentiment has been around since like the 3rd election in Greece
Where somebody was like
Holding that motherfuker
That I wouldn't doubt
Something similar to that
I think that this next clip really sums up Alex's show if you just imagine
In the background of this quote there is a devil there's a literal
You're the moment
I'll start taking some calls
I got cute covid-19
That's got to be hit
So far
This segment all about me
Which I don't do on purpose
That to me is like
Yeah
It should be
Yeah that to me is like that's really distilled Alex
I'm sure there's a lot of big news
Two calls but that segment and I'm not going to take any responsibility for any
Censored online
Example of
Somebody who has
Has become of being kicked off
Facebook maybe Twitter
I'm not sure
You wake up in a totalitarian
Facebook user Jamie Allman
Does it take
I don't I don't know exactly what's going on with this situation
But Jamie Allman is a St Louis media figure who is no stranger to having his social media accounts locked
In 2018 Twitter temporarily suspended his account after he tweeted quotes
I've been hanging out getting ready to ram a hot poker up David Hogs
Ask tomorrow
Ha the st. Louis Post
Dispatch reported quote
The context for his comment was unclear
In the Fallout from this bizarre Threat all then lost a ton of sponsors on his radio shows
Ultimately led to him losing
Listen to St Louis media jobs
Then because you got a million chances in life
A conservative who's willing say horrible things
Holman was hired back in 2019 to morning radio
In April of this year nbc5 in St Louis investigated a leaking of
The personal information of hundreds of City residents
Hoots admitted tips about businesses not falling
Following covid-19 related help guide
Approximately 900 people at Golden tips
Under the condition of anonymity
According to the report quote
Someone reporting their bosses
These archetypes are technically public records so they are not they're not really they're not really
Automatically
But they are subject
The sunshine laws
Sure which Jamie Allman use to Doc's the St Louis residence on his radio show and on social media labeling them
Midgets
I mean
I don't disagree with
The characterization
Snitches
They are snitch
On the other hand
He can go f***
What a giant piece of s*** there's no reason to be a good person
Didn't you got this
F***** like
Roving around trying to scoop up any information Ikeda destroy you
Poker up a shooting a school shooting survivors ass
I got fired and then I got another job in the same field
Why should he ever have any fear of like
Any lingering lasting
I also why if you've hired him
Do you not immediately like knock on his door anytime anything goes wrong
Play Somebody leaked this information
He's leaving through the window
I've no idea what the deal is with his account getting locked this time but I'm not going to believe the version that's being pushed by Gateway pundit
That he just post
Video of black Trump supporters and it got shut down
I'm certain that there's more to this story
Don't care what a conservative troll did and is now poor
He didn't do good call and order to feign victimhood
So anyway
Jamie Allman
Another
Alex's pretending he's not like some right-wing media figure
Regional and Alex doesn't really give a f*** about Missouri so
That makes sense
He wouldn't know any
Anything about him he's not some private citizen
Is private
But he's also a media figure
Anyway
Alex
Gone on the record
And said that
The false flag
Admission
Malicious
Yes we were planning to kidnap Gretchen Whitmer
Alex has been
Media Matters George soros's group
This is Denise
2 weeks ago
Conspiracy theorist Alex Jones
Kidnapping plot against
Michigan Governor Whitmer a false flag
The Deep state
Shut up
FBI informants I predicted
Probably
2 of
Of the top people probably
2 out of 10 at work
And yes it was a lead
Buy to FBI office
Court documents
Exactly what I said
Which is because I know
It's not good
Confirm the court document
Adore
Of course they are
Put it in court and then everybody knows that means it's true
I think that you know we need to see how these things play out more in
Information about specifics
Is needed for me to make a stronger
Telling of what happened
Everything I can tell it looks like there were some militia people who are
Notoriously not careful informant
Who were infiltrated
Kidnapping
Northam
In witmer
And they got arrested it
And of course is that were the situation your defensive be like they set us up
The only angle you have
Cuz there's like recordings and
Open text messages
I mean it's
Look the FBI has setup
Counterterrorism strategy is fine people who maybe might want to think about doing something and then like
Put him as hard as I can towards
Causing terrorism and then be like
Like that's kind of
One thing they do but with
With these guys
You can just walk up to it you know you
Google 4chan and then you've infiltrated six of these militia
I'm not saying that police enforcement don't do that cuz obviously there
Sentence of that
It's just as lazy to assume that they always do that Shore as it is
Is to assume they
Don't know about the existing
Sensitive
Those sorts of
Because
Those are outliers
I don't know
Again one of the reasons why I feel like we need more information
When is because of the
It's fairly unclear but from everything I can
Intel
It's not a bunch
Besides
Setting up
Ribault
Here's Alex's
Is clip of himself
From the past
Predicting
That this was a setup I told you so
And what other false flags are we going to see
Definitely
What do you do when your house again
Grab the power to kill what other folks with suicides are
Covid patients are well
Wait so you're in favor of kidnapping her
The kidnappers swag but also she should have been
Somehow he's like yeah it's a f******
False flag I wish it weren't
Yeah but also a militia does need to incarcerate
What did something I totally would want my people to do but in this circumstance
Is a false flag because they did and it didn't work
Sad facts
The feds must be
Cool
Patriot would get busted his
As if they've already kid
Was very strange in terms of like
Here's my gotcha
Saying it's definitely probably a false why should I do that
Definitely probably get mad being like
Yeah but come on
Hey alright
Anyway I'll expect
Present-day here is a battle between good and evil
That's what's important.
Understand
Other good people meet
The people at
Computer shop
It's a war between Good and Evil
Omni-channel
Hulu
Only runs for 12 days
Last year was very successful it is
Here today
Black Friday in October
Black Friday in October 1st at Christmas in July we got Black Friday
I think he's forgetting the reason for this
I don't think
See I understand Christmas in July cuz it's like urx bonds
Convert 8
Christmas image
Black Friday's
The day after Thanksgiving
October's pretty close to Thanksgiving
B forever away
It's too close
What are you going to do a Black Friday ad
April know you're going to do a Black Friday in November and in October NASCAR
It's too much Black Friday and do you know why you can't do Halloween
Is the devil
We're doing a special bat theme sale. That's a damn
We cannot do all the way in special
They don't sell
Locate our supplements
I think they could do
Infowars
Why not do it
Less harmful
I've guaranteed by now someone's drink that iodine
Call Totally 100%
But I have a strong sense
Kind of put
Open their mouths when I just go all the way with candy
Disney Clippers
I thought that I found really interesting
I wonder if you hear this
The same way I do
The diversity is strong
There's a unifying
Christianity or unifying Americana
Ethos
But if you don't have a unifying narrative
You will disintegrate
What happened
Evil or bad
I like that you were taking notes
And you wrote down the word diversity and then put a lot
Has like a write-down diversity that's where he started
Some notes continuing on and then
Vision following words I was just like
Crossout diversity
What I hear from a clip like that is
Diversity is great as long as there is a robust
Status quo that supports
Am I interesting
Primary
And the only ones that are really important
I can't believe you would call me a white now
Because I do not want it all white
That's crazy
Supremacist I want a diverse Nation where I'm On Top running every
What don't you understand
Benedict
Is
Really interesting
To me because I've heard him too
Decry
Diversity
Tons in the past
So for him to say like diversity is great as long as
Is people
Are subject to
Americana
Or in there it is
Sweet
That's strange I mean it's not strange at all but
It is it is weird for somebody to literally say I'm a white supremacist and not under
First and that those are the words
Are you straight
Some calls
He's got an answer
About big Tech
The solution
I think it's very reasonable okay thanks
This caller is
Maybe I mean I don't know what else they believe they're calling and Alex's shows they can't be that great great
Twitter and Facebook are really bad
Yeah so what
Do you need to do so you need to Foster other platforms
And try and get people off of those
Create Alternatives we could create more of an ecosystem
Online
No time
Everybody that's listening right now if he went and do that and it least mirror their profiles
I didn't get all their friends and family
10 people
Get trained people get them off of the big Tech platforms
A decade
Exactly you have you use the big platform while you still have them
To promote all the little platforms and grow those
14 days out there brother
14 days out
Play Dollar Store
People better
We sharing on Twitter on Facebook on all those
Infowar however you can now
Sure
Certo
For now
Absolute
Everyone should go to parlor
Everyone should go to gab
Everyone should go to telegram or Telegraph
There's no time
Any productive
What I've been doing is
Is changing URL constantly so I can still be promoted
I spend my resources
Bands
Oh sure I'll have the guy from
From Gabby come on my show from timer
I don't care about it no one there except
Stream
Who cares it's not a fertile ground
So weird whenever they kicked all the
Vegas off of
Twitter and they were like not all of them
How dare you how could you do that
And then they went to the other place together and they were like oh my God everybody's
Xtreme picatinny rail
What a shock this is this bigotry isn't my bigotry you're even more big
Alarm for a long time then he probably should have
Contributed to the solution of it as opposed to
Desperately trying to still promote his stuff
The platform
That exist
I mean I guess you did try to do that Infowars dating
Insight
There was that
Do that
Affected my job
I think that one had some
Like
General
Design flaw
Yeah I would say like
Before we even get to the website or the
Design design and conception flaws
That's something that should be up on the Whiteboard and then erased
Immediately
So are we
From Canada
Should stop trying to meddle in our election
Yeah with two weeks left
It's too late
Why do Whimsy
White now
Insurrection Act
And
Roundup and prosecute every single one of
Biden Hunter
Hillary
Build and work them
By the way there the authoritarians have tried to have
By the way
Just remember that
Yeah Canada
Okay I'm down here's what we'll do yours my here's my
Peace treaty
Alright this is I think how we're going to solve
Right so eat even if Biden does Wendy
People are going to go ape shitt
Problem here's what we'd
Did we have a sit-down to
Between the left and the right
Bishop Desmond Tutu and Reconciliation
Nothing alright
We will
Who do we put the clintons in the Bible
Things in the whole lot of them in jail
If they just leave us alone
Yeah you with that with that there's some reason to put them in jail their evil borrow a term
There was a lot more popular couple years ago I think that would embolden
Probably I don't know
What's a good solution
We just move on I do I do like the ideas I do like the idea of some sort of
3D
Or something
Or some kind of
It doesn't feel like there's a way forward without like some massive negotiation
Goodbye
Yeah I don't know if that's possible.
Something's got to happen
You guys will do it
Not sure I'm not sure I support this
Alex
Easy supporting with this collar saying
Lock up all the political enemies
Canada. Here's how this looks to Alex
In in real-world term
How many times has blackmail Joe Biden movie
Emails proving an egg and
Father Firepower she is not fit
He's the only to be arrested
Anime year we can have another general election
Trump's going to lose you can legitimately
Martial law
If they can't steal it with an overwhelming fraud
Cancel session race war we can't just sit back and let her do this
So
Alex
Is saying we should destroy the Democratic party lockup all the leadership course
I don't get arrested
Is Casey HR new Democratic question project is now the Democratic Party
Remind me of another type of course we can do it all over again Dan
Way we know it's right this time
You do it every year until bricks
I tell you what
If you want cost
Is
A good way to get it promised some kind of bizarre
Is never going to happen happen
An idiot would have actually hold that election
Calista
Also how would you create an apparatus
Like the Democratic party within a year that could be viable as a national park.
Come on this is childish
Yeah but Alex says like
Trump knows he's going to win
You know he's not afraid of Biden
Lock him up
Right
Sounds like something
Dictators do when they are
Totally not afraid
The high-level people today
Don't want to go on record yet Rodger stones on tomorrow by the way
Rodger doesn't want to attack
The trumps only five points ahead
He was 15 points ahead last time
Only five points ahead
Probably so high
You got to lose
And to all these Republicans are we doing
How does euphorian stop
I'm sorry folks right now
Be a fraud in the Tommy's Chinese will rule America with the satanic
Well alright
I mean sounds
Barely resigned to it
It kind of a mini more positive wasn't like
And then we have to go kill everybody right or just playing time before the commercial for ramp-up I think I think he did
Didn't realize he was going to get that extreme until music started
What a
That's what that
Much like Laurel Uber Cedar Falls
Earlier in the episode we heard Alex
Accidentally read an article is headline about Sweden
Without knowing anything
Think about what was going on and then
He does this again
About Brazil
Brazil's
Major state
Bye, this calls for mandatory covid vaccination
I'm a communist state
46 million doses
Chinese reading makes no sense
Given that we all know that Alex loves bolsonaro who is the president of Brazil
Countries not run by a communist
How to sing there's a Brazilian steak
It's run by a communist
Because he doesn't know the story at all
The story is about the governor of South Paulo is Joe Doria
Doria is not a communist
Brazilian version of The Apprentice
Partially because he's a famous businessman
Land is worth almost 50 million dollars
Alex or one of his employees saw that Doria is a member of the Brazilian Social Democratic Party
And decided
That makes him a communist
In reality that's a fairly Centrist party in Brazil
It was actually the main governmental opposition to be more Socialist Workers Party which included figures like Lula and Dylan
Imagine Alex spends all of his time reading for a news
Just going like why don't you name things the way I name things
Australian labor is the
Goodguys what are we what are we doing here if all you know is the name then Social Democratic party might make you think the guy
Guys
But if you work you'd probably be a member of the Communist Party of Brazil or possibly the Democratic labor party
Workers Party
Secretly
Capitalist
Call Cheryl
It's an upside-down
Little things like this showcase out with his lack of depth
In terms of any kind of reporting
He's doing
You have no idea what the story is about other than that it's
The Ford politician like so go ahead let's play music
Also Alex doesn't know this so let's hope he doesn't find out that actually bolsonaro was
Is elected president as a member of the social Liberal Party has actually super right
Confuse the poor boy we can get started with that
Do I always find a really interesting when you can almost tell that I was reading a headline is got to be a misper
Play the I like Brazil
The distraught the words dates
I imagine I wonder what would happen
If
Somebody just removed bolsonaro
Name from all the
Headlines and just put
Social liberal politician
How
Different would his coverage just be
For sure but do you know what I mean like really all is that all
What takes really would be interesting to see if like
No one has ever called him Brazil's Trump
Without a care at all
I imagine
Why would he
Unless it was like Brazilian is
Trump
You know we need to do we need to find some like
Really leftist politician
And brand them as like some other country
Trump trick out
You know one person who could get it done
Steve
Aerobic
Steve pieczenik overthrow of government
Morally every event
It is ever happened in the world
Steve comes in
Do you want to talk about how the Democrats
Their self-destruction where they are
For several years now
You can have this
Created
What's happening in this new year
In an era where we need
Understand
3 backpage.com
Can have a Nancy Pelosi
80 years old
Maxine Waters
82 years old
What you're seeing here we said
Party
Senile dementia
Eventually
Define
Taken electrical applications are generally
Too old and I think that we could
Stand to
Inject some
Younger Representatives
It's fine that conversation is fine
It's not a Democrat problem
Yeah it's not a Democrat problem
Also part of a problem
74 that's not start talking about
Young man
Also
Listing of people's ages and how much money they have when he's like
Trump is old and Rich
I have no idea what
He's trying to do
That's incredibly all I'm hearing while he's doing that is like in my head and
I'm just going like Trump sold to
Council two
Yeah and he has a lot
He has a lot of money
Or maybe he doesn't have a lot of fun
Maybe you're the one who's
Yeah
Anyway I thought meant to be disoriented
21 Rock
That is
Is the constant
Sure
Does not like police
I'm against police state
Crazy p
Cause of Civil War cost of session
At a certain point
They're going to do to us
You're correct
Is really funny about that first of all the Steve's
The second thing is like Alex
If you understand his show and you actually know what he's talking about
I can translate that clip to being
I'm against the police state
Keith Olbermann said something so we need a police game
I feel very attacked
So I would like a police state
Keith Olbermann the YouTube channel
Do you know what we need
Ultimate safe space is a police state
What is Bill Maher says something
Where does it end
It's a slippery slope
You don't have a police state then you get older men and then you'd like Walsh it it's all all the real
Bill Barr it might cause
His head will explode
Sprinkler head exploding
This is where I got really like
I don't know Steve
What are you doing
Steve has a plan Visa vie
Dealing with
Twitter
Mike Jones because you couldn't never all tweets should be replaced with Milani
No come up but this plan is expensive it's silly
Man
I like
But there's another reason I'm going to
And the reason because
A song about Jack from Twitter
Since he decided
Personal with
Trump
And use Hunter Biden and started to
And that is when now has
Isn't it amazing for the past 15 years
You've been considered the
What does that really mean
Dorsey
Now remember
Renee
You self-righteous
Thinks he's better than
He's gay
Dadaism
The hidden secrecy and nastiness
Seven Dwarfs
Why is it a problem for you
I have
0 comprehension of why he's talk
Walking the way he's talking
Yeah personal with Trump
What do you do
Wait what
Steve
His plan haha deal with big Tech
Twitter
Gay
Yep
What we're going to do
Is we're going to put jack in the center Square
Idea let's act like a schoolyard children and gay bash somebody I don't know
Don't care
You don't need to take
I don't even take out how to record
You shouldn't care either I don't I don't understand I don't understand
So Grinnell is
Because here's what he said
Here's what he say
I don't care if he's gay
What I don't like
Is somebody I
Don't know
Not lying to me about something that is
It's not my business to know
Well sort of I think also this Harkins
Back to life
School
Communism
The days when someone
Sexuality could be used to Blackmail them and stuff
House on American
Yeah yeah I think that's worth
Steven 7
Yeah well that's true
He might be too old for
Remind me to
Confirm
I just ordered
Stand this Lake
Anyway this is not just
Something that's
Steve is picking up is a plan that he wants to put into action
Have you also seems
A little bit pissed
About to bad customer service that he got
Do you still use square right which Jack started as well she or anything
Steve still a little mad about
No one answer
Using Square guess what happened they said they don't work on Saturdays and Sundays
You got multibillion-dollar
Homosexual
Yeah
Holyshit
I decided I don't even I don't even know what to say like what I'm listening to the sound like
Wow
These people's brains working such paillard
He said that's
Just while he's screaming about like not getting customer service when he used
Square because they took weekends off and then somehow he's going to get
Get back
What in
I don't know
When we overthrew Rome
Brutus
To take my
Advice
Said what we should have done is
Call Julius
A dick but it didn't go that way
I
I mean Steve seen better days
Flip like
Sinister plotting this is just being an a******
Dick baby
Look like a old man write a letter
Whether or not Jack is gay is not my business and I don't care whether or not that is
The case what's
Steve is doing is deeply humbled
No incredibly incredibly am deeply homophobic
The caller who called in earlier I had a better plan
Yeah I would argue that as well
Steve also had some plans
For Trump
We need plastic action now what else would you do
What I would say is I
Get rid of bar
Country that can't do that
With what he's been doing Sara Lee I would get rid of Gina Gaston
I would start
Firing people
Understand
Anybody that's establishment anybody that's globalist
Google I'm in a minute
You know what this advice translates to this is like
Hey
Sacrifice
People
Totally throw people overboard
Alex's advices basically like
Throw people off the Lifeboat just f****** thing
We got two weeks of the election
Pocket sacrifice whoever you got
Take down the entire history.
Manicure
That is
Tumi
Any indication of people who doing well
Thrilled about their prospects know he's only ahead by five point
Internal quality
Iau have
To be so far gone
So far gone down the rabbit hole with b*******
To believe that Trump would ever even
Think of getting
I mean
If Trump
Makes bar
Feel bad
Bar has everything
Like it is ridiculous
Barb aerones
Like forever
Seems like based on the I mean I hate to put on my Steve pieczenik
Psychiatry psychology
I would bet on him over Trump
Inserting the Department of Justice in as
Defendant for Trump
Libel
Like
That's the level of barnos everything is involved in covering up ever
Every crime is doing everything
There's no way you f****** your fixer
One last clip here for
From Steve's appearance
Trump is
After Alex's second wedding
Trump called and wanted to talk to Alex's wife about how like a great blessings on your union
Steve says this and I swear it's just like
Sometimes he'll come in and it's like oh it's a racist day
Today is a homophobic
Hellboy
Good news is that he understood
Exactly
Do you like swimming
Text women that spinner
Unique feature
Wait what
What is
F****** a happening
I don't know David Michelle what are we doing yeah probably
I am a man these people are not
Yeah yeah it was it was a it was a jarring
Appearance
Steve Bart
Alright man just
Just go back
Townie by 10 a.m. and then go to bed at 9
Fucken leave us alone you old
So Steve Williams and Alex
Sackets the rambling
About how he's always right
And Trump is going to win no matter what
My guts never wrong cuz it just sounds
Subconscious
Amish Paradise
Decision
In a healthy election today
Trump's going to lose because of massive fraud
He's got to get his points
Way up above her
Just five.
10.15
Her
Do we wish we were running against somebody else whelming
Slide
They're going to contest it folks or just any way you slice it
This is a foreign outside takeover of the country literally
No matter what Trump's going to win probably going to lose today because
The cheating
And her part is partially I think subconscious Hillary stuff and then I think the other part is
Prior to this has been talking about house
Kamala Harris is going to be the X
Just going to be watching his
His stories are whatever
You know what I want I want to continue this
Rain of having no idea who's in charge of anything at any given point in time I would definitely prefer
Bi handled by some weird
Vice president
Double team that's going on that sounds great
Call Zach and
The first fellow here accuses Alex
Pics of lying
About the FBI and the deer hunter Biden the Lowry I like it Alex does not take this well
You know you know damn well.
The FBI has knock
Confirm
He's being arraigned
Bye
Reply.
And his dad
Get up on C-Span
And said that they were investigating us so I went said I won't give you a million bucks by far the prosecutor
Listen to me boy
We're done with you
You're the bomb
Okay thank you calling here in Gaslight my audience
You don't do that
You're a joke
Keep you all
Disappeared
Coward
Is it time I didn't want I didn't want to beat up on you with all my facts
So I don't have time for it honestly I think what happened there if I had to guess what
Like logic
Tree that Alex's brain went down
It was
Alright
This guy obviously knows that I'm in polishing the s*** out of the story
And what the FBI is it
Confirmed and all that
That is trouble
So what I'm going to do is see if I can get him dancing around this
Clip of Biden prosecutor
Can get him to take the bait on arguing about trash
No I'm not
And that's why I hang out because
If you can't detract somebody over to aside argument
You can't talk to the
And it's one of the reasons I think
That call is a good example of why it's like
Almost pointless to try and
Confront Alex about things on his show
I think there's probably some people who could
Handle
Like
Bringing up
Decent points to him but it won't go in
Anywhere
One thing I think I would like to hear someone ask him or I'd like to ask him myself
Is
Alright
You're on your show
You're talkin about whatever you're talkin about
Are you lying to the audience about the devil
Being behind all of it or was it that will not behind it then
You know a lot of people like to argue about whether or not the devil
Send those people haven't been to the extra Dimensions that I have dinner so
So yes I mean technically the devil was
You need to realize it before he died I talked to Charlie Daniels
He was working on another song of follow-up
Cayman Island vacation
During that period of time when I was on air talk
About the Federal Reserve and all that stuff
She was at the beach
He was enjoying himself
It look good
See I really want to get into a discussion of what hit the devil's specific
Check powers of never go spearfishing with the Devil he's got that that work
Materialize a drink if he still wants it
Only my ties
Does he have to order it or
The guy who can only materialize situationally appropriate drinks
Does he have to get the glass from somewhere else and then he can materialize the drink he can only imagine realize drink
Appropriate glasses
Arizona Beach
Shrek get a mai tai in a flute if he is at a speakeasy he can get an Old Fashioned
Moscow mule
Possible
Is I love this devil
The devil's powers for drinking tea realizations
That's what I want I want if you
You're going to start telling me the devil is real you better start telling me what the
The limits of his powers hyper-specific
So bored
Captain America eventually you're like okay you can
Carry the hammer of Thor whatever we at least
All the times when Alex gets a call like this it ends up ruining
His entire show
And I was really worried
Even though we're in the third hour
I was worried that he was going to like completely Fall Apart
I need doesn't man he just goes to another call and everything is fine he's not even thinking about that
I wanted to say my mentor reminds me often
Never stop an ego on its way to
Destruction
Doesn't need your help
American Eagle
Sleeping awake
Ganda
Is destruct
Thing is just
Waking up
I guess no comment they are here
The Bible said this was fake
They have said nothing
Now we have the lawyers email the API admitted they had to laugh
Nothing to say about the last guy I mean
On her ass but
Elegance
Like I was some 72
Girl he picked up at a bus stop
Yikes
Could abs
Absolutely of Kent
Right I had to get two more calls
Like the old guy
Yep
Attract
I swear I did
I do love
Especially when I heard that guy some
Something very very boring
And Alex not say anything I was like
In Alex's that guy is in Alex
Who had right now just going
Boy over and over and over again
I can't yell at that car
Boy
How many yo
Not about that guy
I'm going to sublimate that
Christian
Who don't support Rothrock
People
People that I believe
Good intentions
Thinking about you
They don't like Trump
Morally Superior
Through hell and you should vacuum
BoBoiBoy
I think that's gross
And bad but also I only really play this
Because the transitions into a little bit of Bible talk
Which may be a new segment on show
This is a really special edition of knowledge fight Bible talk
Because Alex gets into
Tumult estimate
Business
But he also talks about something that happened in his own life recently that I find
Almost impossible to avoid
7 years of
Harvesting
Salmon
Joseph
Prime minister
Big Mac show that information
People
Atlanta in following years
Dream of the prophet in Egypt
Another seven years of fat the seven years of skinny
StoryBots
Talking I was talking to a high-powered Democratic people are
Meeting with the local Democrat Mafia head
He said Alex what's going on
Years ago Egypt
7 Days of
What
You believe that
Nope
Yes
That story that is 100% true that only happened a few days ago
Synchronous within the last month I met with a local
What bullets for Mafia leader
What are you talk
Local Global is Mafia leader who is confused about the simplest dream interpretation anyway
One has ever heard of before
I have I have an interesting theory about what Alex is referring to look at it here in a minute
Little more about farro
They wouldn't dug up the Sanskrit in the end
Screw what's in Genesis
The firstborn of the Israelites killed as a way to just call off
Boy
I don't want too many boys
Warriors I want women they can control
Leaving aside be historical accuracy questions about biblical events Alex's interpretation of why Pharaoh wanted
The kill the Israelite boys is not necessarily the
The consensus opinion
Going back to Josephus is commentaries on x
So that's one of the most mainstream understandings of Pharaoh's decree was that his advisers had prophesied that the mail would be the one
Want to save the Jews
And those the killing of the boys was an attempt to stop this for
From happening
This is mirrored in the story of Jesus's birth when Herod ordered the deaths of all male children
Nikka possibly be
In the right age range to be the Messiah
From Josephus
One of those secrets
Scribes were very sagacious in foretelling future events
Truly told
That about this time there be a child born to the Israelites who if you were weird would bring the Egyptian
Dominion low and would raise be Israelites
That he would Excel all men and virtue and obtained a glory that will be remembered through all ages
Which theme was so feared by the king bad according to this man's opinion he commanded that they should cast every male child
Which was born to be Israelites into the river and destroy it
This was of course
The backstory of Moses
In the context of Exodus 1 there is a concern about the increase of the Hebrew population
And that they might become enemies of Egypt
Inside with the enemies of Egypt
If there was a conflict
What's the deal with that within the text
Enslaving them forcing them into hard labor
The killing of the male children
A slightly disconnect
Thought from old commentaries
A lot of the belief is about the prophesying of the
Becoming aphmau's
Yeah that's one of the very first versions of the story where it's like
In terms of time travel profit
Sissy stuff
Read like
Yeah the prophecy only comes true because you act
That's the way you would
Normally Act
If you would heard the
If you didn't want Moses to show up maybe
Just be nicer dude
It's like my killing everybody you were the one that created the whole problem
The God of Thunder the first
Your dad is outside your nature Sonia prophecy to come true I would save the trip I don't like you calling Moses
The problem
I think it was a problem maybe for from the
Perspective of pharaoh
Sparrow
He's just he's just a rabble-rouser he's an instigator you can't have it you just let him go
Historical if I if I had my druthers
And I would have a talk so yeah I think
I think Alex just does
Bible corner
But Alex does get back to talking about the meeting with
Globalist
Mafia leaders
I think it's just his lawsuit
And by the way folks and sit there and say
Bible
Godby
What the devil
I will absolutely
With
Two representatives of the top billionaires
Bienaime repeatedly
I've got meetings with the Enemy going on right now
East Coast
Give up
Embrace Christ they want
Cuz I rub their father the devil
The synagogue
That all seems like
Satellites are really well I mean sure
When he says that he has ongoing meetings with
Higher-level globalist
You know you know you know you know that Sandy Hook
Trial is going on
What a baby bat
Meeting with the globalist mafia leaders that
Recently was actually his
Custody hearing okay so just Family Court
Yeah it was the mediator
You they were a high-level democratic
Mafia.
So Alex
He just doesn't have time to deal with collars
Who
They all disagree with them
It's really important
And stuff too
Really important
Especially
San Francisco
Saturday
Free speech well-spoken
Can you cannot be racist
Merry Chrysler
Excavating
I'm not as strong as he is.
Get so mad you not my front teeth. Got your dad
Your dad
Enterprise
So we got a guy who got punched
Who Alex's
Jerk now having on his gas
I'm going to
Declare that punch was a false flag
Self in order to make the left look bad and that's why you should
I don't know
Gravel governor
So anyways
The person who punched him has been arrested and is being charged with a hate crime
I feel like
Hey
Not great
Not great that two people
We'll punch each other but when they do
If someone punching somebody and then they get arrested
I don't really
Kind of Howard
Care too much probably
Anyway I have one clip of this guy and
It's them
Him and Alex trying to make the argument that Joe Biden
Is racist
You always.
Free puppy
Wait that I don't think Alex got
He was just
Oh boy I think there might be some
Facetiousness there might be some joking
It's really hard to tell
If that is something that Alex thinks like actually
Or
I don't know
Anyway who cares
Span I would
I would really
Personally
You know I don't know
I think it would be very hard
To hear somebody
Call me well spoken
And then trying to argue that
The guy that that guy doesn't like
Mike is the racist
You know I'm saying
But he's a very
Ticular but what did you what did you say you know what you're saying right
The Battle of trying to deal with someone like Alex
So Alex
Co-ops the 4th hour
Gerald Celente was supposed to host
And Alex just takes over the 4th hour
Preemptive
Talenti knows this happen sometimes
Just too much important stuff going on
Still mad at that guy
The waiting is over now
Now the waiting is over
I know that from
You know like listening to Alex's show constantly people call in and say
When is the war
Yeah is it now
Is it time
Should the weight be over
Let me be clear about that it doesn't seem ambiguous
Cool
The only time I want to hear the wait is over
Is when it's the 69 Boyz album that has wolf wolf
Hanukkah
Freak you down to the base
The wait is over
Was that one freak was still spelled with a pH of
PH free
Victim
You spelled with a Q spelled with a Q back then
It's a
Alex Alex says that he needs to take over the 4th hour because he's at
That's breaking news sure because he needs
Take phone calls
Are these people who are on hold and he's going to take them
Because that was his excuse to not talk to the little whiny little baby
He doesn't actually do that
And then
Oh man I haven't taken any calls
You held it all three and next I want I love you
Appreciate you sex
Unplug last hour will be bankrupted we don't
I went to top
Developers who got like seven suppliers
Best
Multi-vitamin mineral amino acid
Like the taste great
Chelsea
So he's taking over Gerald Celente his time he is going to go to
She hasn't gone to cause
And now he's taking up time doing a nap
Supercuts better use
Desert inet
Very busy
He's exhausted
Living
Feeling women
I don't need
What is a baby's got to wear
Face shield mask
Airborne
Let's go back to Luckenbach
Texas
Isaac is still on hold on
The successful
Alex
Just looking at this song
It was a parody
I don't think work
Packers value should be
But I think you should
Do your job
I honestly do
I would rather listen to
I mean it's like 50/50 he's going to do this to kill time
50/50 chance
Just going to do that races
Impression
As long as he
You know he airs on this side of just killing time doing nothing
I'm not mad
Not matter
Waylon and Willie and the boys
Listen to a good one
Yeah
Anyways
Alex sadove take the calls
They're not interesting
Zach
Call
And I was like
You should never take calls from people named Zach cuz it reminds me that you had a fake
Why won't you do that
We haven't spoken to the is this it wasn't does that cuz I was that was what I thought.
It's another Zack it's just a difference
Whatever happened to Zack
Queue for a while. Was a golden kiwi
He was Alex's Cube because he was mad at cute he wanted his own
It's all I've got back Zach spelled with a Q
Or maybe a carrier
Yeah
I I kind of like when you finally went to that call
I was like
What if it is
Where you been why have you called me
Wasn't
Now they say that they blocked
Probably
Calling from Morocco from down the hall
So Alex has also Patrick Holly in from National file
Bizarre
I hate this guy
I honestly I turned off
The show they're still like half an hour left
Patrick amen
I think you'll know why
I want to hear that
Well you know what I think
What we're seeing now is Hunter Biden first of all I mean I don't know if the left thought they were just going to Cakewalk to this
Action with the stupid vote-by-mail in the drive-thru Taco Bell voting but
I don't think they counted on the fact that Patrick Highway 26
16 veteran
Rudy Giuliani
Our super-agent are our James Bond for America Steve Bannon I mean these people are still out here like
Rodger Stone
We didn't go away
Who are you Dennis Miller are you trying to be in that has the Dennis Miller
There's like an attempt to be funny going on but he also just sounds like a baby
Yeah there's a real baby
I can't I can't stand him and then followed by what it said
Just have like
An outsized intolerance
What's 4
Patrick
But I don't care about anything he says
I can't imagine a world where and he has
Storyworth
F****** voice
Is
Integrate
Yeah it's great
DeBary grading but I could put up with
He also like
You're clearly trying to be funny in this isn't funny and I resent that
You can't have a grating voice
That is both
Being smug
And unfunny at the same time at me
Without me wanting to throw up
Yeah like that's brutal Patrick holiday 2016 of veteran
I know
That's got to be like an attempted self-effacing humor right
No cuz he has a grading annoying smug voice
It's
Yeah it's interesting but
In that way that's
Really not in
I just don't like it whenever they act
Smug after like
It is so many times they
Just pratfall and then like
From the
Covered in bulshit that they stepped into
I live on the ground looking up
Hit me with a smug look like
See I beat you like what are you doing
You fell in s***
He did
Why are you doing the why you making me feel like I'm the
So we going to be able to stand
I don't know man
I just get the sense
That
The run-up to this election isn't as fun for Alex as last time
Play some of the hits with the satanic pedophile laptop
Apps not working
It's just
Diminishing returns
It's a bummer
Steve wants to gay bash Jack
For no reason
I don't understand what's even going on
I dunno what the kisses so weird because like
When I when we were looking at our last episode 26
I think that I could in 20
Teen look at that episode and be like
I understand everything that's happening
In here
Larry Nichols
Who is pretending where I have inside information about
I get it
Everything follows rationally
Or at least logically
What's going on no
I don't understand what the attempt is how they think that this is somehow benefiting
Their side
Like
I don't know I mean
Maybe it's just maybe I'm worn down on satanic panic but it just doesn't seem that at that Pope
Don't anymore
Buddy's worn-down
I did it it just
Feels like
This
Isn't going to move the needle
People are tired of this
I think everybody's
Is in media-wise
People who are covering the election
And it seems like everybody's in this one spot now where we're really not used to being where it's still there still two weeks to go
And everybody has decided about 2 months
Yeah
You know so everybody everybody
Trying to still make this like a thing that were Act
Actively engaged where is
My general Vibe of everyone is we're all just like
I know what I'm going
To do and now I'm waiting for two weeks
See what all these other
Yeah that is really strange
I was listening to this episode Alex is like it's
Two weeks till the election as like yeah it is
That's weird
Cuz I remember last time it being pretty in
Intense
All the way
And I do still think that this is intense and as much as like the stakes are really high and it's a very important thing and people should have
Sure I don't want to vote
Shame anyone
Like
You're right I think I think you tapped into the feeling that I have to
I don't know anybody
Cuckoos at all
Unclear
He's waiting for the day we look there's
Going to be no difference
Between voting today and voting in 2 weeks
And I want I want people to really like
It is that bad
Add it's that bad
That we are now literally at a point now where I have
To say
If Joe Biden shot somebody in the f****** Street I'd be like
Fine
Will elect him put him into jail
But at least not true
Is that bad
It really is
Trumps
Trump's words used against an aspiring dictator Georgia
It's brutal I don't understand what could possibly have I mean obvious
If you did shoot some
I didn't f***
If a demon popped out of a portal and went by
That could be
Redeeming all the way
Provided presumably
I don't like to talk about voting pattern
The only thing it's going to shake that
Is it the literal devil
It is like
Haha I'm the devil
What provider
But I got still have a truck I'll probably going to just kill myself
Yeah
I couldn't I couldn't handle
But that's a happening of my brain
Part of me would be like
Alright well at least this
Let's the other Shake
Except for a little bit probably end up writing a sequel to the donut or something
I'm confused
By what
Alex is doing
Kinda interested
And
Checking
The leader
Couple days before the election in twenty
I really I wonder
Like Alex presents this image of like I knew the Trump was going to win 100%
Flappable
I think I might go back and try and see the days
Before the
I remember
M-46
Before we started the show I wasn't watching Alex
Constant
Yeah you know that right
I forgot that we didn't actually do like the lead-up
Right in our first episode
Beginning of right before the inauguration exactly
Yeah mmm
I was watching Alex a little bit just
Out of morbid curiosity
I meant I was also watching the debates
Ambulation coverage Infowars the show as much
I think that might be interesting
Think so I might I might check in on that for Monday but
I'm saying that you're cuz I wonder if he's doing the same
Kite like the exact
Kind of same thing
Hello
What do that for anyway I just need something
To make me laugh
Confused about
What the f***
What's going on in this week
Well I've
I think they're mad and they're lashing out because
By all and every reasonable project
Trump
Is going to lose
A free and fair election
They're not there's no such thing as a secret reasonable Pole
Exactly
We do have a website it's not right.
Go on Twitter
Review In-N-Out
You could please find a local
Call Charity or bail Fund in your area
But until then I'm Neo I'm Leo I'm dzx Clark
I'm the devil on a beach with a Mai Tai
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color