Damn important
I have great respect for its knowledge B
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Alex Jones
We had we are not
No no
People there
Didn't have a quick question for you over the weekend
You and I got together
Had a lovely night and we did not record it for a
Yeah we could have though there's hilarity
Hilarities
God why don't we monetize social interaction we haven't really
We hung out too much
Yeah it was really good because we start maybe we started this whole thing as
Is just really good friends
And now we're back
Situation professionally or more professional
I enjoyed it. I had a great time as well good time
Masks
Theater mask
Yeah I know you got a mask
It's great
In Chicago a mask
Can you play everybody's always like I got a beard
Doesn't do that much between the hair does
My friend
American Septic
I would like to be around upon to wear a balaclava all the
Previously it was just to burden
Summer whatever scarf around your face or nothing not the past I've had some
Scarves but they've been tough to keep on the head of course
It's great even if there wasn't a virus I'd be wearing a man. I don't know what these happy Masters are all going on about it very comfortable
Socially acceptable out of hell
Anyway this leads me to opening of the mailbag disease
Typically we have been doing some mailbag stuff on our bonus episodes
Would you can find even if you're not asleep
Subscriber over on patreon are patreon page
Go to the page
Amore of the Vizio
Like this was important
To go ahead and toss over your way
Yes we got to a couple of hats
From Christina
Yeah
They say policy walk
A raptor princess winter hats
Jordan I hope he's had to keep your heads warm during the coming
Uchicago winter
Making them was a pain in the ass but you guys are worth it because no Jordan the has eight garbage opinion on schitt's Creek
I got a PostScript to your we harvested 11 butternut squash is off one plant this year
Really good had to brag to my plant guy
I applaud you although I'm not a squash guy I'm not a gorgeous guy
I don't hoard to go
I don't know
Giving squash a bad rap I think I think it's something that's worth Explorer
In the future
If you are a
A giant robot
End
Power Rangers
Given
Title
And I know where I know where you're going with it like
Lexi
Taking a large number of pumps
Skin landed
What would you be
No you would be
A Lord's sword hoarding courts
Oh
I didn't realize I was going to have
Power Rangers hat on a hat
The sword is all you needed that is fair
Anyway
Episode to go over I'm going to say that this is part 1 of 2
Because
Stay here then can be next Monday
It will be the second part of this
Day before the 2020
Kind of fitting
Because what we're doing
Is weird looking at these days
Prior to the 20s
16 election on the Alex Jones Show
Little blind
Spa in our history of covering Alex
A bit of a new understanding of what was going on
Okay I think I have a working theory that I have
Google out of Coke
Just know
There is
A feeling that a lot of people have suggested
Floated that I've been resistant to
But looking at this time frame
Makes me a little bit more
Open-minded I think I will bear that out
But like I said
We're going to be looking at 2 November 4th
4th 5th and 6th
Today which is Friday Saturday Sunday night so we're not going to look at Saturday because it's mostly Owen Shroyer Joe Biggs
Right but Alex did a very special Saturday broadcast
Mostly in Friday and Sunday
And then part 2
Is
Monday and Alex was doing a
52 hour marathon on Monday
Porta culminated in the election looking at the beginning stages of that autumn day
I meant okay
But before we get to business on this
Stick little moments
Say thank you
You're signed up north
That's great idea do first Marc with a c on Gagnon last initial L thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Rabies thank you so much and I apologize
Text Ryan W thank you so much
I know that.
Wankel you pulse okay
Text Melissa
Text Rebecca
Donated on elevator
What's the first Indiana bees thank you so much you are now.
Technocrats and
Benghazi and the butter emails thank you so much
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
Gianna and think as much of Benghazi in the butter emails
Sportage
Website.com
We'd appreciate it or
What you could do is rekindle your friendship with generosity invite
Generosity over to your place
Eat some pizza play some party games together
And then send that generosity back out into the world to a local charity or Bell funded your arrow
Fair enough thank you
So Jordan
Are toes in the water here on the 4th
November 4th 26
Alex SB
How did it go
Four things that we would have wanted to have it
Alex is a big news
Headline
About the FBI
Alright
Quote
We believe she's the Antichrist
And we'll destroy the world go further what they said
But they believe
Michelle wants to destroy the Earth
Obama and Hillary are devil work
Worshippers
The secret service has told me
Members of the military have told me
That
Obama seems really nice and all suddenly walking down the hall and it's like
I didn't tell you half of
Okay just gets
We people are scared they don't want to be there
It's very dark
Easier
The words I was told
And Hillary's even worse folks okay
So we were looking at earlier in 2016 and noting how little demon there was
0d Now by November 4th
Immediate review hard already
SBI
Apocalypse on us
That Hillary Clinton was going to end the world that were there were documents there was a guardian
And I believe
Guardian headline
Maybe put some Anonymous FBI person
Came out and said that
Hey there's a lot of people who take the cheese
Satan incarnate alright metaphorically of course
She is basically
Beelzebub walking the Earth investigation going to be the moment that we went
From metaphorical devil to literal devil
I hope not
But it is interesting
Seems to me they within the span of this year
That tone does
Seem to have shifted
Quite a bit
This episode is
Sure there's nobody at least November 4th 2016
Shift
Is notable
Yeah that
Makes sense though like this is backed
Two are the worst
Trump is
The worst
They have to portray the enemy
And we're already at the point now where Trump is so bad
The only thing worse
Is the literal Chris
Some Subway
I think the other thing is
The popularity of the online pizza
Dipped into the occult
And I sent through yeah I think that that is a large portion of it because
It's kind of like
Hey get there get there how you get there
Where you're going jump on that train
Prince to be talkin about the devil all the time
The train you're going to be on that train wheel jump
Talks-a-lot
A lot
About podesta's email
This issue podesta and Hillary run with
That's a ghost
Is Dennis email
Good evening
Discuss
What's on the menu
Placenta
Flashpaq
Blood clots of blood mainly blood
100 talk in clear code
About what else is on the menu
What's in the menu
Lumo pack
It shows up child severed head
Appears to be an effigy
With the blood
Bring dump
On top
Leave the blood and other
Tsheets
Ceremonial
Look like a child
That is black
Blood
That is enjoy
Aleister Crowley
Instantly this morning
I thought Paul
Drudgereport.com
I knew what it was
Alright
Now we're bringing Crowley
Is
Right
Into our mythology
Crowley knew what was going on Crowley was not a
Charlatan welder Liars thread that needle
I'm not saying he's right. They think he's right
And therefore we turn right
Crowley's in play
What we're doing
I went ahead and search through all the podesta emails that Wikileaks release that included the word menu and I'm not sure I came to similar
Conclusions italics
Resume contacts the word appears 211 times in the release mess
The first email that comes up is between the podesta's and a shock and a Mitre
Mahbubani
Big strangers by planning a dinner party when the bahubali knees
Are they return from Morocco
And the dishes suggested were mixed grill of tandoori chicken lamin Lahori fish
Garlic naan
Greek yogurt with try to cucumber and a lentil
Yeah but they put children
The next visit you Georgetown alumni association association message which includes a bunch of different events
Including a cooking class quote
With the menu Florentine favorite soda
Just asking country soup
And ravioli with shrimp and scallop
Shrimp and children
The next is an email that was a Briefing app for Hillary about participants in an upcoming technology
Discussion
One of them was the founder of a startup called munchery
Order delivery from
Changing
Children
There's one email from Kristen gillibrand inviting podesta to a Labor Day barbecue at our house with these Sinister line
Quote will be serving all locally sourced foods from the Hudson
Sun Valley
Children are welcome we have a bounce house for them
Two-player games
Code for bounce
News about
Sounds on the route number of these emails in the body of them
To those
Hyperlinks includes the word menu
Describing Nori menu
Pictures of this menu that
Has codeword uneasy stalking
Just about Marina
You just talkin about the art
That email
Tony and John podesta inviting them to a dinner party
Taking all of her art as if it's so literal
Variegated
How do you get there
How do you get their into believing that
People
Just drink blood
Dial
Have you ever drink blood
I have had like I bit my lip
Before it tasted
Is blood a cat
Blood there's got to be a better way to say that than irony
Iron
Yeah I don't know I don't put it past there being some people who do like
Because there's people who like to do everything
Lot of different
Interest on people
Be into it for a shock value car
Some people
You know there's
Put
Alex
Discussing or in the context videos
Wisconsin I do not believe
There are demonic
Performance artist go round it invites a heads of state
Crowley's in Plano everything everything is up
For grabs
Alex
You should look
Do about this stuff because he's not he's not just a dumb dumb is actually someone
As we
Heard many times
Who they tried to get him
Personally experienced this
When I was growing up in the richest county in Tech
Because
Billionaires in mansions all over the place
Countryside
And it really got to be a bummer
Or I wouldn't get
Girlfriends
Anymore
Because
But I just thought I was super handsome getting the senior
Super beetle beetle beautiful girl
Are Buell fancy Bentley or Jaguar
Learn after I was dating her a week or so that that really love the
I was being recruited into
Satanism
Duane's right the way he's talked about me I know you've heard this this sort of Taylor number of times but
In the past I've always heard
The story more as like it happened
Wants
Maybe the cat fishing with the hot cheerleader with something that Satanist ride one
Other things to get him into the ground
I didn't realize.
Did the way he seems to be describing it now it's like
He's dating some young lady and then
Not again not as far as the satanism
Because we've heard multiple iteration many
Buy the one that I remember is that this happened when he was like
15 or so
He's dating this girl for about a week and then she invited him to her house
Giant mansion
All satan is over there in the basement
People are chopping up
Whatever yeah right Alex talks about it in another occasion
That like
There were police there any other runaway through the woods and then police stopped him as he was leaving
Stop stop
Shots.
But I also remember that I think he said that this happened
Also when he was like 8
Even goes
They caught me again I got
Drug back into it again like
He's the idiot here
Childish story that's like
Just cribbing from a movie
But when you're in Blake sort of express the idea that
Kept happening to it make
Me
Think more about how like we might
KT Tape
A fool
Perspective
Of how
Stream
Alex's religion might have been
As a child he might have
Experience
Do not let say dating a woman
And them having liberal values to seduce them to the dark side
It could have been the way Alex process
Shame for having sexual urges towards these women
Sure somehow evil
Or something
I don't know I don't know if any of that is
Is accurate at all but when I hear somebody say like
Just kept happening to me
Girls that were dating
Recruit me into Satanism right it makes me think that there's some sort of like
Mean to him
Something
Ryouri there's something he kept experience yeah yeah I'm not sure what it is but it doesn't seem
What's the
Alex actually drink blood
At a satanic
I think low
Uniqlo
Yeah you don't think he actually drink blood like an open one says add are at 1 if he's taking his
Bears happen all the time I'm going to say I think the odds are low that he's been to a Satanism party
Now I've been to
Is a party it's a truth or dare there like what's your deepest Secret
Then I'm going to ask you this
If your sew-in with a Satanist you know everything about it I literally was my grandfather
The pecking order
Who's higher on the org chart
Luciferians
Spur Satanist
Luciferians are satanists
Right now satanists are a little bit of head butt
Kind of a horse race scenario you know one every 10 years the luciferians
Iron Man
The competition
Well
Luciferian the way I do
I know okay
I know I reverse engineered it
My whole life's been basically brushing up against it over and over again
Stephen King novel
Okay
Gunslinger all right
And you need to understand
This stuff real
This stuff's going on
You'll understand that we're in deep
And the people
Realize
Hillary gets and she wants definition
She basically Linda Blair's folks
She rolled around the carpet
Snapping
Music
Flips out
He goes into transfer
Chosen to transfer transfer Linda Blair's everyone
Time to duel
Seems very busy busy
Freak-outs
Public appearances
People are following her all day everyday in the last time just secretly do this
Need some self-care to Astro and for some people it's a bath for some people it's Linda Blair
I enjoy that it appears that this is
These demons and what have you been brushing up against Alex or his whole life is
Because he's had his brain
For his whole life
Any experience as a lot of things as satanic nonsense
Yeah I've 1 out of 100 people
I'm going even further
1 out of 100 million people
Experiences demons on a daily basis
Maybe it's
Smallest 100 million people who run Baby It's You
But this also raises the question of like
Why wasn't his show always
Is more
Like this
That's fair
Why why is there so much more.
Demon talk now why is that
Floodgate open
Like was he just holding that back
Write for years because he knew people would look at him like you
Now it's now it's something
Thing that he can piggyback on or was it something that he's been hiding the whole
Right right I have no idea
Know his character
Seems to be
One that
Would support
Because he's an extremist and he does seem a little bit unstable in terms of their belief
The influences that Alex says were around in his younger days
So I could see there being like a
Complete religious zealotry
He was hiding
Because he knew it wouldn't
Be profitable
But then at the same time he's also a complete liar and a fraud
So
Makes sense that he could have added that to his character
It's some point
It's it's three it's very difficult to tell what sincere and what's not
Chinese knot
Kicked off of
Social media
Like he's still
Because
When he's kicked off social media
You go too deep
Men's why not your
Nobody
You still on social and he's already
Demon so that kind of gets rid of that
Theory of like 120 got kicked off social media all of the stuff that he has been hiding
I think I think it's
Probably related
WikiLeaks
I am the pizzagate nonsense
The theory that whether it's
Organic
Or
The organic version will be that he'd been holding this back and visit normalizes that kind of conversate we're sure she's doing jumps into the water
Coronavirus
Or if he's like okay this is a great way to go yours always
Sensationalizing
This is the new editorial line
I'm here I think that the
The normalization that came
From
The way the internet went nuts
I think that's
That's probably what allowed him
Do the demons
Disconnect Clips on 4th
For Alex
Traffic is worse by the day
We're now four days out
3in changed
Technically
The hammer
Drip now is getting stronger
Bowling
Thunder cracks now
What are they going to do
A false flag
I knew Sandy Hook
Launch a new war
What are they going to do to stop
So
I would say nothing of the weather going to do in New Sandy Hook replies that they did the old Sandy Hook yeah
Alright Alex
I'd learned the truth apologize for all the
Pain you caused people
Only just I think I don't think he was being very sincere and I'd say that was a lie
It's almost
Wall-to-wall carpeting
Hillary Clinton
Is it God damn
Expect us a few days out you got a hammer surprised about is how thick
The argument is
One of the big things is just
Podesta's email to
Being used
Yeah and then this is the other one
Bill Clinton says I practice voodoo
I think this is wonderful
Who wrote a book
Bill Clinton's book
Where he talks
About it
How great it is
Add another copy
Print it up
It's My Life the earlier
Here's the passage from Bill Clinton's book my life
I was pretty
Particularly intrigued by the voodoo religion and culture to which I had some limited exposure in New Orleans
And that existed alongside Catholicism in Haiti
The name of the traditional Haitian religion comes from the Fawn language of
Banana in West Africa where Voodoo originated
It means god or Spirit without the connotations of black magic and Witchcraft attached to it in so many movies
Voodoo Central ritual is a dance during which Spirits possess believers
On the most
Interesting day of the
The trip I got a chance to observe Voodoo in practice
David Citibank
Contact in Port-au-Prince
I offered to take him Hilary and me to a nearby Village
To meet an unusual voodoo priest
Max Beauvoir had spent 15 years outside Haiti's studying at the sorbonne in Paris
And working in New York
He had a beautiful blonde French wife into bright young daughter
He been practicing chemical engineering until he's Voodoo priests
Grandfather on his deathbed chose Max to succeed him
Max was a Believer and he did
It must have been a pro
Approved
A challenge
Bruce ranch wife
And westernized
Kids
We arrived in the late afternoon an hour or so before the dance ceremony which
Which Max open to pay interest as a way of covering some of the cost of his operation
He explained it in Voodoo God is Manifest to humans through spirits that represent forces of light and darkness
Good and Evil
Which are more or less
Imbalance
After Hillary David and I finished our brief course in Voodoo theology
We were escorted back to an open area and seeded with other guests
Who would come to witness
Miss the ceremony
In which Spirits are called forth
And enter into the bodies of Dance
Believers
After several minutes of rhythmic dance
Pounding drums
The spirits arrived
Season the woman and a man
The man proceeded to rub a burning torch all over his body and walk on hot coals without being burned
The woman in a frenzy screams repeatedly then grabbed a live chicken and bit his head off
Then the spirits left and those that have been possessed Felder
To the ground
I described my brief foray into the world of voodoo because I've always been fascinated by the way different cultures try to make sense
Life nature
And the virtually Universal belief that there is a non-physical Spirit Force
At work in the world that existed before Humanity
And we'll be here when we're all long gone
Haitians understanding of how God is Manifest in our lives is very different
Automatic most Christians Jews or Muslims
But they're documented experiences certainly proves the old adage
That the Lord works
Mysterious ways
Silence is taking this passage of a interesting
For inexperienced
Yeah I had turned it into
Billy Mitchell
He loves Voodoo he does it all the time him and Hillary SP
It's his business bad
So flimsy
It does
Surprise me that a benign
Admiration for another culture
Would be misinterpreted as joining the literal Christian devil
But what does
Surprise me
Is that nobody has written
A roach
Trip movie
About a guy
Who is a chemical engineer
All the sudden his grandfather's like guess what you're the priest now
Is there any starts with him rubbing fire on himself in Hugo
I guess you're wondering how I got here and then we started all the ways easy
It wrote itself right now
Finish your book movie to work on this movie I just found this to be like
Wow you're making an
Our out of this
Yeah this is
This is
Ready
Software
I don't know man I just think
If you're in Haiti
And someone is like hey do you want to come
I don't know why you would ever say no do your very interesting experience
I don't know that's all I see in that Clinton book give you the opportunity
Opportunities
You f****** go
Yeah but why go other places if you don't
Experience
Things that are part of
Those places
That's why Alex doesn't really go other places
The hike-and-bike trails
So Alex Alakazam inside information about how all these these
Globalist
They're all Satanist
Chanel kill children who are
Anna's note
Just a little warning
This shows
Let's just say it didn't like in your Hollywood movie where they just got your little heart out
We have a lot of love
Until you
Aleister Crowley black magic house
Chile
The standard
Maybe I don't even want to talk
Yeah that's a great I do already just
Children are probably
This nonsense bulshit year olds out there you want to hear how Aleister Crowley says
To kill three-year-olds
Alright other round
So
This is an interesting clip
As we know Alex did not go to college
He does know that in
College
Sometimes
Secret societies
Still have you do things
Get you in little by little until you what you're going to find your in
Alright
To join his secret society kitten
We know that he is
Refuse to debate you absolutely
I would take Mike down for this cuz I'd like you to
Consider the order
Of things
Imaginary college student
What kind of like in college where
We have sex with a goat
And the next
You doing something
Next it
Sex
Again
You know what we're going to go
Okay so that is not the order
It shows Alex is mine though homosexual sex is an escalation
F*** this go
You did it while wouldn't expect that you don't have sex with me
All right now let's go kill a homeless person
I am really thrown off by you man
Sex with a code does not seem like it would be the entry point
Hey well if you f*** ago you f******
Is that what he's trying to say
You people in this cold must have such a low self-esteem I'm not ready to
You're not ready for me yet you got to f*** a goat
That just shows a bit of his homophobia and then also the quote
Homosexual
Ticket today
Yeah I found that to be interesting
Partially because I was just making everything up sure all it is is just a reflection
Tune of like
His own biases
Yeah he's revealing himself by
Before the election
Alex isn't
Fully on board
With the GOP because the GOP
Has not come on board with
Was Trump right
And the growing
Tide towards
White Christian heterosexual
Hegemony and authoritarianism
He thinks that the Republicans kind of Evil 2
The Democrats
Kendall
The Republicans are into Germanic
Versions of this is like a Germanic
Mix
With the very same old mystery
Eastern mysticism
Mystery religion Babylon
Different churches
Of the same religion
Different flavors of the same
Garbage
Rich and
So much about this
30 years later
Burgers Lake
I know that they tried to recruit me basically into three different branches of the scrap
It's the real big religion of America
The real religion of America
The Democrats are into Aleister Crowley nagaland
Guns are not
Enter into Germanic mysticism
Yeah I would say this is stupid
Everything about it
It really becomes
That much more stupid when you hear him try to talk
Specific
Why use number
And by the way
The Democrat
Far worse number
They are basically 90%
Taking over at the highest levels
Fat people doing the worst of you could imagine
Republicans is about 30%
50%
A few years ago
Politically
Has really brought the pain
I know
That good
Percent
Doing what more do you want
We're working on our Delaware's for numbers
We've initiated some rules and regulations in place to an hour down
Board meeting somewhere where they're like all our Satanism numbers are down what are we what are we doing
Like what are we what are we doing I would like to know how Alex I'd like to know
I want to know I want to know about your methodology definition
Terms
How does one become
Part of this twenty-five 30%
See now I'm just now I'm back
Madmen and Don Draper is giving an amazing beautiful speech about how we should all become Satanist pedophile
Sounds like that's what I'm seeing
Know what this is is Alex's way to support
Brightwing
Conservative
Republican
Bulshit
But at the same time pretend that he's like
Above The Fray
Here's my
Strongman and then I'm going to call my guys
Strawman and then I will never be anywhere
Yep interesting Poppin
From someone who I haven't I heard
For a long time he's not on the show anymore
Basically there's lots of different celebrities that are you know talk about the Illuminati like Jay-Z
And
Some of the other celebrities that sort of hand at it with the imagery inside of their videos
Etc and the question is is this always just some sort of
Playful take
On
On spiritualism and it just kind of let you know
Spooky like Halloween
Or is it real
You think that's real
It's real now
Do you know who that was
Play with my friends back in high school with the Wu-Tang Clan
Cuz they didn't know
Sure I know that you got is that
What are we doing with the Kraken
I don't know who it is
Buckley
What are the Illuminati celebrities are real serious
That does make sense that Buckley is
Is like Jay-Z talks about the Illuminati
He thought he was
Is joking
Yeah
Sick beat
Jay-Z I would like you to wrap over one of these tracks
Baobab
Zoom out pretty fast
A couple minutes
Then Alex drawers
What is top researcher
Alright
Okay
Got really strange
Because
My cup should have runneth over
Because then what should happen
But Alex has
F****** John Rappaport, in
Yeah Batman's in studio
Tumi
Very honorable
He's in studio yeah he only does the fourth hour
Very rare that unless Alex needs a very serious pep talk
It's a terrible interview it's pointless I couldn't even find anything that Rose to the level of Interest wow
It's just kind of like
Yeah they're demon called
Alright great
And then there's a pointless interview with William Binney
All that doesn't lie forever technical head of the NSA
Not nothing in
Interested banana
It's just
Wikileaks got stuff from the good guys in the government is supposed to hacker
I don't suppose that at
It surprises me much though since we are so close to the election I imagine nobody's
Is coming up with too many big
Big swings other than like
We got to do everything we can to stop Hillary from being present
You no like
He's coming up with Eric
They're really good.
There is
Steaming
Focused
Maybe that's more what I'm getting the gist of
I think I think
It's focused is fair but it's focused
Strangeway
And it doesn't feel ambitious
Listening to this
Spell Alot Like people treading water
Seemed weird to me
Nowadays
How Alex is screaming yeah
Bloody murder in lakes
Spitting
Out of his mouth while he yells
The behaviors
Very very
Very different
And no baby part of it is because I was
Just freaked out by the idea of people who drink
He's not going to drink blood
With John podesta
Billion dollars
I mean you could not
Amy
80 trillion-dollar
Words to be around these people
To be with them
To drink
Stop that I couldn't drink blood
What am I done the old Hunter ritual you know when you're ready to shoot your first beer to drink
Being a hunter
+ 1
Okay so you drink blood in a ritual
Almost almost
Ancient Pagan hunting ritual
That I don't understand proves that my
Anime
Demon blood rituals
I have engaged in a blood ritual when I was eight
So f****** RV
Obituary what's a good ritual in a bad ritual
Cuz this is a classic moment from The Alex Jones
Show that I did not realize
This is from this November 4th episode but this
This is a clip that will live in infamy
After this point
Resistance to tyrants is obedience
Alex I think about
Children Hillary Clinton is personally murdered
Lady Gaga
Personally murdered children
Is
What about the devil worship
Campaign chairman
Leave the menu of blood and semen and
Aleister Crowley
The private event
Talk about that
I mean 200,000-plus dead
Christian
Operation in Syria
Are operation in Libya and not let the crew
Christians get out and indirect
Al-Qaeda and Isis
To Target and murder
Children and put up their sex slavery
Priest off cliff
And kill people in masks and murder gays
And everything else you could imagine
Because I don't like
Peaceful people
That is a classic clip from Ali
He will later use
Is a ton
Because people in the news
I believe you may be the Megyn Kelly interview
Took the clip of him saying that Hillary Clinton
Personally has killed all of these children
Spoke to be there you spoke
Poorly
Your contacts
Text is
Is here within the
Consigns of a sentence
Well it's
Two different thoughts
Because if you want to
Hillary's foreign-policy and things
Decisions that were made while she was at the state department and how's that had
Ramifications that are not good
You deserve
Course
Fine yes
Now I understand that Alex thinks that he's just sensationalizing it by saying
What order or trying to get attention by saying she's
Personally killed all these
An incorrect state
Career over sensationalizing it in a way that is only men
Kind of debate people
Into
Pointing out that your
Those assholes Great Clips for him
Symbol for a bunch of that sir
Something like that you could you could get around
Did rhetorical move
He's trying to make sure just did a really poorly
I feel like
He did exactly what he wanted to do
Yes
But
If you are somebody who actually understands our language work
Right
He did he did this
Move portal
Oh oh yeah
If what he was
Trying to say if bouquet
If we are measuring the ability he
Hadwin
Saying what it was
Ostensibly tried to
He did a bad job
Yes if we look at
Somebody who
Realizes that nobody's going to come after him for it
And
It's to say whatever he wants you at hopefully will
Go viral with it
He did it
Exactly the best attention
Albuterol
I've heard this a bunch of times
Alex's mother Gaston
One of your favorite
He he's a guy who Alex
For a while
Doug Hagmann
I've been hearing for 15 years on Coast to Coast AM
I thought
That guy is
Is 2 radical
Why would he says I know is accurate
A lot of it
I just did too much
He said they were going to bring in mass of Muslims at some point
Caliphate
He said they were to use a strategy of tension
He said a lot of things and then about
Man
That'll
More of it what
When what my sources
Are we Cowboys
Secret Service
Did that already happen
NYPD
Now one of those dishes bongino butt
You just outed bongino
Like that yes shitbag
You guys are really fast and loose with your sources did not realize we were already a caliph
Yeah
Yep
So this
This has to do with
The weiners laptop
Yeah they're talking about how
The New York
FBI
Forced
Call me
To come out and reopen the investigation into Clinton's emails work because if they did
If you didn't do that
Then they were going to have a press conference where they're going to reveal everything that was on Weiner's laptop should I kill me
Later
When can we eat comes out and says
Deny everything yeah
Closed
The investigation closed
Alex is really have a great answer for that
But Doug Hagmann he had a source
But it said that they were going to
To do this but they were going to have a press conference
Gloats about being right
Before a Hagmann gets into the show proper
Alex has to do what he does best
And that is fake crying
Let me tell you some
Agents and their senior
Pretty tops
Uno
The shooting there
She's really really scared
Her children books
I thought he was doing an impression I give it to
I did not
Now that's
That's bad
I don't buy that for
Second
Snow fairies yeah I thought it was
Drake nope
It's it's not just purposefully not purposefully face because he starts talking more and
And it has the lingering of the the crying out
I know we've heard Alex talk a lot
Pretty regularly about the possibility that there we all deserve for the earth to be
Destroyed
Because we're bad
The globalist
Yeah it turns out this might be your four of him
Maybe we deserve a nuclear war
Maybe that's
We still be able to torture little kids to death anymore
Mom
Hillary Lane Andover
Your backyard
How's that sound
Not good
I do think that it's interesting that
You know Alex is a silver linings
He has a silver lining Sky maybe no one will let you know they won't
If everyone dies there will be no more
Great
D'Artagnan comes in
You want to talk about the codes
In the email I would like to talk about
There is a sub
Text or coating to some of the emails
Others have
Including Hillary
And who am I have been engaged in
For example
The party I'll just leave this out there
Pizza party that's not exactly what it means
Don't bring
Do you know don't bring your favorite video over for a
Pizza night
Pizza party to something else
Sexual connotations
IFly
They'll be semen they'll be
They'll be
They'll be blood lots of blood
Not exactly it does I mean you could go to
Yeah
Well I do
Yes
Why would you use blood is that why would blood be a code word
That's a terrible idea
Alright alright.
Ultimately the plan is
To drink blood blood
What's your safe word elsafe never catch on to the fact
Blood
Little boy
Okay
Bringing videos over for a pizza party
I mean
Screener
Can VHS
I think that the idea of some of these parties
Are like dinner parties with like a couple couple
So maybe you're coming over and someone has an actual like
Hot
Pizza oven
Rygar brick-oven get together and you make a pizza and then maybe Wildwood pizza cooking or some
Something you I have a video
Sure or maybe like I said maybe it's green or maybe you have an advance copy of something
Cuz your written exam a Hollywood party you're right that's what we're dealing with here
Shoe powerful you got it.
Bring over some dumb
Commoners can't watch Ironman
Is Doug Hagmann on that bringing videos over Iron Man 7
I don't know
Hilarious
Clearly I just wanted to make it clear that this
Thesaurus
Is within the orbit of the F4 the NYPD FBI investigation on the ground
In New York
New York City and Westchester
Chester County as well
Specifically New York City
I should have said that
There's an investigation going on
What are you doing
What is
What is happening
Well I should look at that
Whoops a doodle I'm a professional
Oh man
Accidentally
Possibly reveal too much information about your Source on 8-0 syndicated radio show
Should decide that
Yep
Rudy Giuliani should have said that whoops to doodle
My bad
He's most he's laundering bulshit towards me and now here we are
Oh what an ass off
I don't know anyway
Think of something that needs a citation
From
And by the way that there will be at least
6 if not 8
Or more verified
By Hillary
And by Houma on the Lolita Express
Course you talked about that Prince's saying that to
You know it's like the
Crossroads
What does information
You're supposed to hate him
Alright
Okay first
I understand
But there's only one per
All right you don't get to refer to Erik Prince by his last
There's one prints
If you say prince
You know who are talk
The mercenary formerly known as
Tell me about Erik Prince
Yeah. Information about these trip
Huma and Hillary Express
Provide documentation whenever you're ready where were they going
Of course he has a star-studded show on November 4th
Rapoport
Rapoport yet Buckley
William now you got Rodger
You supposed to have Steve but his phone didn't work
Call old man house phone I got very excited cuz I got teased with a Steve
Not materialized
You got Rodger
All right boring interview
Quite frankly that Rodger says
That I found very
Am I wrong and he's ahead and all the Battleground States even pulls oversampling looks like Landslide for Trump
Cautiously
Bigger women Reagan addirittura zor-el
I'm cautiously
Spirits
Happier
Alright Rogerstown will talk to you soon thank you my friend
Is very f****** different we're stealing this election
Cautiously optimistic about the theft
That is about
To take place
It's really it's really weird I do I don't know if I
I heard it the same way you're hearing at
I heard it as
We have no expectation that we're going to win
Voting
Machines in Georgia are definitely going to work this time
I get I get where you're coming from on that
I think it's the other way around
I think it's
We get to talk about the voting machines not working after we lose
To me it doesn't feel like any of them are really
Expectation
It really feels like they're all getting ready for Hillary
Yeah they are all that but yeah so is everybody we were all ready for it
Don't hear much talk about Trump
At all on this November 4th episode
The demons have they get in it's over
I guess electioneering for Trump giveaway Hillary is our kid
Her eyes upon it brought like
Still
There is not like
Merely the quantity of
Trump is our savior
There's little flickers of it now
Not nearly as much as you might expect these before the 20th
16 election
It's mostly about how bad Hillary is happened to me
It feels
Like
We're getting ready for next season
Right
Because it doesn't
Feel like the end of the world if Trump loses
Yeah
Talk of like
No it's not like well shrub loses its time to Gunn everyone down there still talk of like satanism
But it's almost in a way that's like
Productive for Alex
The yellow about later
It really I have had a very strong
Reluctance
I too agree with people who think like
Alex wanted Hillary to win
I don't know we'll see what happens on the the the
Later episodes
It does not feel like he's
Fully
Meeting
Trump to win the way he does now it is funny
That
Our
Situation is so warped
But Alex being like
Hillary Clinton is a pedophile murderers the devil and we're like
He's kind of ambivalent about
This election might notice he seems weirdly chill
Calling her a pedophile demon
Borderline nothing
Yeah it's it's it's the definition on that I had to look the background is it work for Trump as opposed to me
Like this is this is about building up a villain
For your neck
Pay-per-view or whatever like is not
I don't know it it it was definitely not what I
I expected I wonder if there's
Going to be I wouldn't be surprised if there was some like
Serious
Historical work that was like Hillary Clinton
Is literally the only politician that could have ever lost
Austin election to Donald
You do a really fascinating probably come up with a couple others
I imagine
McVay
I think you could probably come up with thousands of people that could
Lose
I agree that I think of leading let's say possible Democratic candidates
She would be probably of
Few
That that would
Who could be realistic
The candidates have lost
A lot of that is
Not necessarily her fault
A lot of it is just based on
You know
S*** Larry Nichols David
Dislike
It's
It's not that they just
Just got the propaganda train rolling on her in
In 2015
Or whatever
That's been going on
Years by that
Yeah
Longer if you lived in Arkansas
I think if your political strategy
Just you think like
Well
Yes there is that right
But
That's been going on forever over it
Most people know it's nonsense a lot of this is be bunked
Entirely totally
And unfortunately it is
It appears that might be a miscalculation
Democrat
Never fail to overestimates
These sorts of propaganda campaigns it existed over decade
Shiraz did they wouldn't be as potent
Or as
As mean
Painful but now it's very easy to look back
I can say now look at those
Is idiots making that choice
The time we were all like yeah there's no way Bernie's going to be there this year
And I would have said like
Nobody's going to care about like Vince Foster s*** notion
Turn down
So Steve was supposed to be on but he's not answer Alex's to Philz
Sometime
In front of a golf
Pizza okay
About two months ago I was on the hike-and-bike trail
Security reasons now always bring somebody with me and we're always
Locked and loaded as well
Quite frankly my hand inside baseball
Pappadeaux's on around here but
And I'm like 100 yards away and I saw the
He's really super white looking people in Black
And if I got up close to him they all had like pentagram necklaces there
Super white and leak
Do the old woman a younger woman in the manager either
There went the hell I was going down the hill
And I was like I sent them 100 yards away like I was at
They were so weak
They think they're powerful
Totally turned over to Eatonville
Thunder like
The most pathetic people
Remind just be some metal fan he's just ate did he just discovered golf's
Is that what just happened
Alex's life is so boring that two months ago he's awesome godson the hike-and-bike trail to
Jesus
I can feel I can feel pale people in the in the Wind
Jesus Christ
I would have preferred if he did
Pollo Tropical
Joke
Soggoth running and I leaned out the window of the car and went
Where's the
Funeral
Like that's that's all I want
That's as bad as
Is it could be well that's direct bullying this is just Alex bullying somebody on a
F****** show mother later or no
Earth and
Explaining
Why God allows us human
Exist
Interesting
Theological
Appointed
But I disagree with
And so that's why God allows us to exist
Murder Hornets
Bird's eye view
Do Souls do creatures new free entities Gods created
Just sit here and be told about him
You have to experience it
You have to live it
You have to be
Tortured by
You will always
Spiritual memory
Pascal nasty
This is
So that you've chosen
Which side you want to be on
Not with her
Never with this
Never
Never with these people
Harlan
Weather pain
What the failure
Ugliness
Weather weather weather
No. Would you ever
Alex is Hillary's slogan
I don't know I would say that if we are our ancestors than we should have all of their Spears
Virtual memory
He's too and I guess if evil has ever been experienced
In human history then we would all have our ancestors
Spiritual memories of that evil viscerally so we wouldn't need to re-experience it over and over again
Sure I don't know I think this is all stupid
And I disagree with
A lot of people say I know
Did I shouldn't jump off the the
But I'm telling you right now
You can't know that it's a bad idea unless you jump unless you breathe jumping off that bridge
How much you eat jumping off that bridge
Unless the Lord himself tells you that jumping off that bridge
Is it bad thing
And that's why you got to jump off the bridge
You can't know that
Evil is bad
Haha unless you jump off at
Okay
I make sense
I just I don't know what this is
That's very stupid
Like I said the 5th is not worthwhile
I got really excited cuz Alex said that he was doing the Saturday show
Just talking about how Bill Clinton
And said that he likes voodoo
Owen Shroyer
Pre-firing rainbow Joe big
Get together in magic
Complain about Stephanie
I don't know
Maybe I'll accept
I started working with her years
Is it go
Yeah I don't know I don't know if she was a big figure I know they likely Ann McAdoo is still there
Yeah I don't know there's a we'll see I mean
We on Monday next Monday 5 so it'll be about that Marathon
T2 hours we're going to see Rainbow snatch
Before those yet
And here is Alex
I really really basking and how much traffic
He's getting a lot of people are liking his s***
1 video
200,000 internal stream
Plus thousand people
How many millions is that
We have two and a half million viewers last night
RadioShack
If you got Hillary Facebook mention
Lonely quotes celebrities
The Facebook live
Celebrity Suite
When you go to hers right now just how many watts
Today live with LeBron James
Does it count
Live and then
The archive
As of
12 minutes ago before I went live
Don't care I don't I don't
I got more viewers than Hillary
Petty
Had a DS it is
Unprofessional
Perhaps
Rogers back
Sunday
He's on because he is gloating about winning a court
Alex
Telephone
Lawyers
Anyway
Picking nose is that they
Again
Donald Trump
Rodger Stone
National Committee
Campaign
Steel. Org
Was overturned
In Ohio
Late this afternoon
There is no evidence
Any plan on arm
Threaten or intimidate
Motors in anyway
This is a great example of how crazy the last 4 years
I'd completely forgotten that right before the election Rodger
Firestone was involved in a lawsuit where he was accused of engaging in voter intimidation
Due to his work with the
The Super PAC called
Stop the steel
Completely forgot that as well
On its own this story is Mass
The chaos that was going on at
Just faded into the background
Rodger was running stopped the steel is a nonprofit that was set up
To conduct exit polls
Some cities which had according to the Huffington Post quote
High minority population
Can you exit poll with extreme prejudice
The group was really nothing more than a website where people could register as a volunteer poll Watchers
Go to the polls
Presumably talk to voters and then enter the information they gathered on to this website
The argument was that any election that was more than 2% off from eggs
Bowling should be considered suspicious
So what
His group was intended to do is create
Completely nonsensical non-scientific exit poll data to yell about after Hillary won
That's what the scam was he
Create a narrative on the back of meaningless information that you
Who created yourself
Rodger even said that the plan was to gather information to use as a challenge to the election in the case that is data didn't
At what was Comic-Con
But that's nonsense
Even if his data wasn't
Completely unverifiable and wasn't biased as hell in
Complete trash
He couldn't use it as a basis to challenge the election
The only real outcome of this is
To create something to rile up your followers after you lose
This is a loser
Strategy not a path towards winning
The Huffington Post article on this is hilarious
And the part about
Stop the Steel's website is a personal favorite of mine
Quote any registered volunteer could sit at home and start entering
False information today
HuffPost entered by votes Wednesday for Green Party nominee Jill Stein
I vote
Search for Democratic nominee Hillary Clinton and libertarian nominee Gary Johnson
Had two votes
GOP nominee Trump
In looking into it they just entered. Kaiser Rogers in bulshit
Wow
Rodger was almost certainly using the Super PAC as way to move money around
As Mother Jones reported in 2018 that
Pitstop Bastille strangely paid approximately $5,000
Consulting fees
Do the mother of stone associate Kristin Davis the Manhattan madam
The mother has no experience
In politics or elections
I'm so this seems weird
According to Mother Jones
Quote in a text message
Stone said he was too busy to answer stupid questions like this
He did not respond to further question
All this is super weird because after he got sued over this group he claimed quote I did not establish Sophos Vito I do not
I control this bank account or It Anyway manages affairs
Hard to square that with payments to his friend's mom was no business
Consulting for the pack
And also payments. Over Rogers
It was people doing impressions of him online
Just before the election
Stop the steel spent it sent out new Direct
Consider volunteers that made it clear that they cannot do things that violate voting rights law
Princeton
You can't enter a polling place
Devote
You can't speak to anyone within 100 feet of the entrance to a polling place
You can't record anyone
You can't talk
To anyone about anything but
Before they vote
These rules are basically fly in the face of
To the Blustery talk it was coming out of the group before this
And it kind of feels like a cover-your-ass kind of thing
Did Ronald up everybody about the need to protect the pole so it doesn't matter if you send out an email that's all like
Control yourself that day before the election
The desired effect has
And then you can
Do that
You can say that tell you're trying
How to get everyone to follow voting laws
How can you possibly be held responsible for the action
Volunteers
You sent out an email telling them to follow the rules
We've spent two months
Describing all of the things that they shouldn't do
In repeated
Angry tones of voice
They misunderstood that
To mean those are the things that they shouldn't do
Going to do with that
It appears to me that this is
Like exactly what it appears
It looks like an entity that was used to direct money to Associates will also hopefully suppress
Open some of the vote
Possibly creating chaos
Fun places
The ultimate payoff whoever is just the creation of a meaningless data
So you can pretend if credible the proves that even though Hillary won the election your guys secretly want
It's a long con type of thing where you're protecting your grip
For the next stage
This is not the action of somebody whose intent
Going to win
Because even if Rodger was
I like using this as a strategy to help Trump
You couldn't
Lake
Even if he got the best
Best data pause
Possible sure this blog post
This would not
What's way anyone's
Opinion
In a legal framework about the validity of the election
Is useless
Except
Is it means
Making War propaganda narrative propaganda is only useful if Trump loses
Do you have to go through all this
Trouble unless you're looking for a way to after-the-fact
Dismiss
The claims that you're a loser
Sure I I mean I would also probably argue that
You know if you are setting up a super packed
To move money around
Hidden ways
That's just sort of a side
Suspicion I'm not entirely sure that okay
Alright 100% what was going on in the almost
Reverse
Baby sitting up a thing to move money around and he's like well we have to have a reason for the thing to a
Exist
So
This is fine
You know maybe the madam
Her mother was like stuffing on
Let me call the consul
Sure maybe it's not
I don't know
Sure anyone imagines
Was just really taken care of
You know you threw her that little bone she's on a fixed
The income music
Has nothing to do with that Manhattan Madam's
Well I mean Kristin Davis
A long time
But like
The thing that I just can't get around is like
Thinking of
How
This would be something you would do
If you were looking
Productive ways
Is to help Trump win
Or
Try to protect
The whale
Potentially
I contested
Do nothing
Pointless except as a PR kind of strategy
And to me that is an indication of something kind of strange
Also
He's not doing that this time
No Rogers not doing this time now they have regular illegal poll Watchers now Rodger thought there was some
I'm kind of like a real need for
This thing that he did last time
Like if there is a real concern about
About the polls
You think that you would be
Trying
Because
I think you
Wants Trump to win this time
I'm not positive these people actually even walked up to it
I'm starting to come around to the conclusion
That these people are expecting a loss
Yeah and they're bracing
Sing for a loss
Anyway for their business to move forward
After that
That's kind of the way all of this field that I believe that
I'm starting to feel that way
It's because Alex is declaring Victory no matter what happens in the twenties
16 election
He's doing now
But
In 2020
He's saying that
Either
Trump is going to win or Biden's going to win and it's going to be stolen and Trump actually watch
Alex is declaring Victory no matter what is
Is different in 26
Whether he wins or loses this election
Use a total winner he had courage
You had courage you've taken action
Globalism
He's on the table as a crony capitalist anti-free Market Mafia system
Screwing us over to use the fat
Our borders are being dissolved
Political correctness
This is a guy who's making the argument that even if Hillary ends up winning which of course it'll be shenanigans
Whatever
Even if she wins we win because of morals and some has been
Put on the table
Trump has been such a dick and so rude the political correctness is gone
Like this is someone who's like trying to look for the silver lining of the Trump losing
Yeah
It feels like that
Very strongly
As I go back and I look at this and maybe it's the
Position of how out of
Controller
Desperate
He seems for Trump to win now Shore
I don't know it it's it's
It's very different than I expect
Did I expect it
To hear a lot more like
Really desperate screaming a lot of like
Pleading almost
And I
Here
Barely covered resignation
The desperate attempt
To turn Hillary Clinton into the greatest villain
Which is pointless
If Hillary loses
Right
Yeah
All of this I mean we're seeing why we're seeing how pointless it is now seeing as how they're still trying to run against Hillary and
Behaviors that are going on
Total sense
If you're gearing up for the next election against Hillary
Again if you're over here looking
For four more years of fighting against Hillary washer doesn't make a ton of sense
If you think that you're going to have to deal with Trump for the long-term
Right
Trump works really well with the way that they're playing this as a prop that goes away
Like
A Ron Paul run
Or whatever
It doesn't it doesn't make sense to me and I know
I know that I'm jumping
To conclusions a little bit based on
Bali full data set
You know I'm I am just looking at a couple of days worth of his show sure but it is the overwhelming sense that I get
Bike
He doesn't
Yeah I mean I imagine that makes sense though because we
This time we spent six
Six months being repeatedly hammered with
Fivethirtyeight back when everybody thought that was a great thing that gave
Buying likes
And 85% Hillary like a 75% chance of winning
I feel like over and over again everyday there
Forced to like
There's only
The betting money says our guys going to lose
You know
And now even though we're dealing with the same type of care about that
Secret Pole
Secret polos
A call back whenever life was reasonable
Alex doesn't understand how pole is work
No that restrain statistic
Fix it all at sampling sizes.
Do you understand
Novi.
Sidestroke Barnes won a lot of money on the election
So
Rodger as a prediction that did not
I presumed
Between the election
I didn't happen
Imagine that
If Trump loses
Between now and the inauguration Trump
Full pardon
Everybody who's committed a crime ever
I think we might all get a clean fight
Officer Rodger has a little bit of a bone to pick
Here
What happened
Just before this episode was
Bat alley
Somebody else gun
In the audio
And Secret Service
Just came and then I was surrounded Trump
I want to watch that video Trump looks very good
Adidas Nazi
Stoic will say that he is very Story song
Now some people might have been
Suggesting at that point
That this was staged
In order to get
Get sympathy for Trump
Rodger does not care for this
Metropolis care last night briefly
Albion Nevada
Democratic party dog
What is the point of screaming Gunn Gunn and then running a truck just make him look weak or something
Joe Biggs
Flashlight on
Within seconds of this happening
Are we counted over 400
Screaming Mimi
Rodger Stone
Stage this
This is some serious
Ocean Wonderland
In the present-day you have
Gretchen Whitmer the governor of Michigan
Who is
Yuno gasai
The subject of a kidnapping plot that Alex says
Was done
Empathy for her which is Alice in Wonderland
According to Rodger
Also the other thing I find
Incredibly fascinating about this
Is that
When it's
Trump
The plot is Democrats doing it to make him look weak
African Spirits correct
When it's
Whitmer
It's
I don't know if
The intelligence
Agencies doing this to get her sympathy
Spell the word Democrats are really good at false flag
We can turn them into whatever we want I guess that's what we do right
Or it's
Just Alex makes all this s*** up
In slightly different way
I think Rodger
Kauai difficulty pointing out
That they were 400 tweets with insects
Makes me feel like
He did do a
Rodger feel like
Seconds after this happened 400 tweets came out
And they were the ones who knew what I did or I run 400 Twitter accounts and
Sympathy for myself
Apparently Trump is pretty
Fatalistic
This gets Alex really excited
But I wanted to get to this
Cuz he told me stop
Call come out
And the fact was
Couple years ago
Trump won going to run
He knew what would happen
But he just finally said okay I'll just found my life over
It doesn't matter in his wife back
Baby killed
And stone just let it slip so I brought it up
Of how committed
Trump is
So this is Steve stuff
This is all like Icees I recruited
Trump Quran with this group of
Of good guy is in the intelligence
Southside
Which is why when the reasons why I was excited to hear that Steve was going to be on and then when he didn't show up I got confused
I wanted to hear some more of that stuff
But yeah so
Rodger says the
The Trump has very fatalistic about this
Like Alex is a
Inside baseball
He doesn't even wear a bulletproof
Talk about you said fatalistic
Did they can't even make him wear a bulletproof vest he just doesn't even care
This is so presidential
So damn hot
Slowing down
His family has begged him to take more security
That is so manly
You calling fatalistic.
Fox
Another word
Have to do this
I have to do this
Is the opposite of a coward
I love
That
Alex is trying to do this like always so manly won't wear a bulletproof vest
Remove or add that I'm not flattering to his figures
To just wither under the
Keke Samantha
Alex is trying to
Push this now
Trump is ready to die for the country
Which is not
Foremost
It is not at the
The front of Alex
His reporting
And it's
It's coming in a tiny bit here but it's weird
It's not now
They're not fully committed to this as something that has being
Discuss the lot
You know
For somebody
Who believes
Pet
Hillary Clinton is working for the literal Christian
Devil
In 26
You would think he would be far more insistent that everyone get out and vote and not
Verite
Kind of like
He's probably not going to win
Christian devil
Kind of voting 1808
Almost
Entirely vote against Hillary
Like this little stretch with Rodger where Alex is excited about the idea that Trump doesn't wear a bulletproof vest and he's ready to die
Or whatever
And I think largely that's the
Just motivated by
The conversation about what happened at the rally tonight
It's very little positive about Trump
As much as it is
Supremely negative about Hillary
Man
How did we go from there
Trump is God King
Yeah it's weird to make the hard-right love you so much they want you to be
Peking
It's for you to piss off the live
Not bad
Rodger gone
And now Alex
Continues at a little bit more talking about how great Trump is
It's not
It's not the biggest deal
High-level groups who come to Trump and they know he's ahead
And I said just work with us
And we will let you in he said I
Serve the American people
This happened yesterday
Yesterday
Crapping your pants
They came to Trump May 7th
The Deep state
The older elements
Bush connect
And they said just
Say you'll work
So you listen.
Will
Let you win if you are the winner
Donald Trump told him no
American people
Grab side
And they said
Okay buddy
Okay
That was a warning last night
I got to go I got a gun
You just stood there and waited
Now you didn't he look
Pretty confused that's that's what I would say video
Justice like a woo
I don't know I mean like what now it's is trying to do here is just like a
Half-cooked version of
Like this
This doesn't
Sounds like he's even convinced
Have any of this
Grasping at straws like what kind of
Do it sometimes
Hey hey we're blackmailing you were going to install you in the office
75% of the time do whatever you want to get it out of there
Considered
Water be at we want to seat at the table
Of the office we're literally giving to you I don't always need my way I do know to know you
You heard me it is a very touchy
She feeling kind of overwhelming
Is viren pulling out these like
Your pants if you knew how real this was
Really
Yeah it is
To me just seems like Alex and
That isn't
He's not fully developed this ability to
Lionize Trump in the way that he
Become accustomed to now
IM and maybe it's a lack of development of the scale maybe it's an ambivalent to just seems very flat
So we have 11 morghast here on November 6th
And the guy who's very
Concerned
About widgets
LOL
Larry Nichols shows up here on November 6th
Something that this this is
The story that I've heard Larry Talib
Before and let's hear it again. It's a good one
I literally had to go to
Winter
TV local TV station
Church every Sunday
Who is Santa Cruz
Tony told me 20 years ago years ago
She got all that she turned away from me
Joker steps
She said
You know I can't do that
Andrea background
Walkaway
Love that story
Hillary Nichols just going to Hillary being like we just need you to pretend to be into Jesus
You know I
Why can't you that Noah
Why couldn't you
If you are like
The devil is the king of lies right
Not there are a lot of Arcane rules that make sense
Ewe
Contacts I don't know
I feel like if you are
I didn't
Who's trying to take over the country to somehow stop Alex from doing something
You'd be able to pretend that
MR2 had a good time
I cannot
Considering she's been to church
Plenty of time
I probably wouldn't play that clip again because he's told that story Bunch times but invented to Alex
Yeah half remembering sauce
It was in mainstream News Washington Post
As well
But she does he sounds for Dad and liberals will be there
If you can call it the dead Hillary's you just getting them broke down at the first level D called
Can we talk to Jesus and she says that's the one per
We don't talk to
You know I can't do that you told me that 20 years ago
Decade ago
The Washington Post
They were like
Oh she does stay on
Who was she talked to will not
Jesus
Talk to anybody but Jesus what is that mean he is a veritable
Hold on
I thought we'd be better if they could actually contact
Juve Isaiah throw everything that Alec beliefs into turmoil does sort of imply that a lie
Believe these seances work at Jesus's getting snow
Rude
Baby pigs that what it is
I guess
What their matter at all you're not going to talk to Jesus here
I'm too good for Jesus yes Alex's timelines a little bit off here he saying that Larry told him about this 20 years ago and then
10 years ago is in the news
And that's that's not true book written by Bob Woodward back in 1996 years ago
In the book it
It's claimed that Hillary would have quote imaginary conversations with Eleanor Roosevelt and Mahatma Gandhi
As a therapeutic release
In 2016 Bill Clinton gave a speech at the dedication of the Franklin Delano Roosevelt Four Freedoms
Park in which key you mentioned the exercises that Hillary did pretending
Speak to Eleanor
As a way of helping her cope with her new responsibilities as first lady
This video was taken and used to resurrect the talking point that Hillary speak
To the dad and engages in demonic rituals with Alex to again
As for the part about Hillary not talking
The Jesus
From a CNN article about Woodward's book
Quote the first lady declined a personal advisor
Suggestion that she address Jesus
Is Christ however
Because it would be quote
Too personal
According to Woodward's book
The choice
Is outrageously thin soup
This is just kind of like
I mean I don't know I've been in therapy and you talk
Do like your younger self or like
Dead relative
You do like a
Cathartic
Sure thing where you talk about some memory I don't know that you need to get out and you don't have the ability to it
It's something that people do
I can I find it
Completely plausible
Like
Hilary wood
Have a conversation am a giant with Eleanor Roosevelt and now he's in the same
Roll eyes
Right total census of b*******
I think what boggles my mind never boggles my
Because it's always out
Spud
Reagan
Literally made Polly just post
See decisions
Based on an astrology
Like a personal astrologer
Who they would ask
Policy Quest
And then make decisions based on that
Yes but like weave
Witches
Well you're prob
Jesus did they did they snub Jesus with the astrology
Linda bloodworth-thomason
Witches
So we won last clip here and keep this
As a nice way to push back against
What's the folks
I've gotten a little bit of feedback.
People were little soft on Larry
Because
Remembering
In him or whatever
The only thing that I want to be careful about
Is
I am fine with
Remembering his history and being like f*** you you sure
What did the occasion of his death to be the reason we would do some
And so
Yeah maybe
Maybe a little bit soft
If only two
Not be mans
Stress in in presentation
No interest in turning him into any figure whose
Not a complete
Creating a horrible Tok
Mexican fluent
On everything
That matters
It's weird for us
It like
We should probably be be
Graded on a
As far as
What's the same thing with reverence go like everybody we talked about would be fine if they all went into an incinerator like
They're all awful people with very few exceptions
Yeah exactly
What you talking about earlier the you like Hillary is demon in this is Alex's
Is kind of mild
Yeah there's there's
There's an understood these people suck
Just to be perfect
Quickly Fair
A whole lot
Okay
Last chance
The media has made it Rachel eBay
That's right he literally made it racially-based like that what do you mean
They'll never get to vote again
Conservative
All white people who are
Super invested in their whiteness you better because otherwise
Literally right now
Everybody was not awake conservative better f******
Vote
You're the new Larry Nichols
You hear stuff like that and it's like yeah okay Larry I got you
I hear what you're saying
Yeah put it down
Stretched be really interesting
Andrea Lee
Not what I expected at all
No I found it
Boobie Miles
From a desperation
Standpoint
But also not in the way of like we've got this in
In the bag
There's still a like it if we lose we still want to
Is globalism being
Disgusting
Frazee culture took a hit
It's kind of like a we're flying if we lose
Cuz our business is on the right direction
We've created the talking points that we need an order I abstain gears
Fighting a Hillary
We've talked about her being a demon we might have to deal with that but
We'll cross that bridge when we get to it
I'm coming around 2
The possibility that Alex did not want
Or expect
Which is not
The framework I have
Had for yourself
Yeah there is a little bit of
We had our
You know like we had our fun with Trump he got to be a dick to everybody got to make fun of all the
Non-white people
We got our message out
Which is f****** on white
People
And
Now it's like okay now we have to go back to the way we used to act
It's interesting to visit like you never really be able to really know what
That's why because
Alex will never be like
Hey
For Trump
Never you have to be encouraged
Using people to do the thing they will probably never work out
Yeah
Is not
Your preferred out
Company have to still
Pushing that direction like Alex
Never one
Ron Paul's actually win
You can never be like well it's time to give up on Ron Paul
Invoke
Mitt Romney's telesales
Then you know his consumers eat
You can't
Just force consumers to eat whatever it is you want them
Do you have to sell them automatically want
Young Voices
Regular global
That's the other thing too there was like really disappointing kind of is like looking back on like
This is just about Marina Abramovic
That's how you get to the demon stuff
You're just misrepresenting a couple passes
Stooges from Bill Clinton's book about him being into voodoo
Hillary's into seances because
She imagined talking to Eleanor Roosevelt
Against rust
It's just
So
Impotent
In terms of like
Having any legs to it there's no like
The propaganda is Sophie
Yep
And it worked
I mean
I'm just I'm looking for things
Games that are like
Deeper and it's like now you just saw painting the freak you out it should be harder to end of the world
I would suggest that you sure
Should have you should have to have some
Concrete
To end the world on but hopefully
Just do it with picture
And do whatever he wants
Amazing will be back
For another episode on Wednesday
Present-day stuff next Monday we will get back to the 26
16 election
Stop and break time for re-election Barracks we will see how Alex was behaving today
Yeah
I don't know if this is a good idea but
Oh well
Anyway I will be back but until then we website
Browser on
We are on Twitter that knowledge underscore fight not go to bed Jordan
Play iTunes and if you could please find a local charity or bail Fund in your area to help out those doing
But until then I'm Neo I'm Leo on dzx Clark
Daryl run
Time to Juicy
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work