Damned important swetik
I have great respect but knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
We are the bad guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Acknowledge
Joe
Jordan
What's up
My bright spot
Maybe a little meta
Struggling myself
I mean maybe we felt there was some inevitability to its butt
At least Spring Court confirmation of Barrett
Not good
Supreme Court
Decision Visa vie
Voting
Not good
No no no not not not not good
A lot of dark
Dark storm clouds hang hang overhead
I'd stuff I think sometimes you think about the these these bright spots
Send coming into an episode
You kind of think it was like well I'd like it
Get to be proportional to
To the dark spot
I sometimes have to recognize that
If this is about celebrating Little Things
But maybe you're not good enough
To make you feel good but
Celebrating
Little things in the face of
Escape and its back
In my
In my gardening
No experience with it at all
But
I just put some
Cloves of garlic Underground
Under some dirt going to work
But yesterday my bag of garlic in there
Yeah there's two little buds growing out of the soil
I really given up on it I thought I'd kiss him
I'm going to workout at night
But then little little protruding that stems
Was coming out of the ground
So I've got two garlic cloves growing the metaphor for hope
That's what that is
It gave me a little bit of Hope
My next crop of
Pease is coming along well
So I can take solace in some of that and I like
Some hope
Spots coming out of the other routine
That's all I got
How about you in that same boat
Proportional
The darkness
We've got really good at cooking one rep
Let me guess
What is it something to do with potatoes
Oh well
Yes I I make the
Different applications
I like embroiled samash
You do it all you do do well
We've got these
Okay baby Brock
So we can cook everything like
Have you ever successfully cooked everything so that it ended exactly the same time
No
Right
Like
It takes 40 minutes and it takes 20 minutes ago
The same time
Hot so that this meal that when we started cooking used
To take like 3 hours to like crap and all that stuff get it all done in one hour
Eat it's fantastic it's great it's a good accomplishment
Team up with
That's great we like to yell behind like they do in chop
Every time every time
That's awesome
Well Jordan what's not so awesome
Is today we were the present day
We got October 22nd and 23rd 2020
I deemed I started watching
Sunday's episodes is Thursday and Friday really bored
Monday Owen Shroyer hosted today we're recording this it's Tuesday and Alex was back in studio
There's just not enough time
To get that out for a Wednesday and then
As if the world wasn't to attract
Screw with me enough
Right before we started recording ilex is new episode on Roku
Start recording
Tweet like at a half hour ago
Yep great
Congratulations Universe you have got me to go back on my two episode of week promise
We will normally still only have two episode the week but this is an emergency
When there is a new Rogan episode
You released
Just now
Deliberately thinking of
Towards US Direct trying to screw with my schedule
Screwing with us
I've not actually had a chance to listen to that but we'll have that
For Friday
Very exciting
Forget that business on this October 22nd and 23rd episode
Jordan to some folks who signed up and are supporting Shirley
The first moose
Text moose I don't know if you know this but I used to work with a guy at Subway
They just got out of prison
Yeah I called me baby boy
Is very uncomfortable that's very nice guys oh cool cool dude
To the Revenge of the Nerds movie
Yeah
Panhandle antifa Admiral Todd
I'm a policy wonk
Are you very much
Sure
Text Kevin Adams
I'm a policy wonk
Eyes on the inside
Next
McDaniel
Another great name
This is a fun last name
Situation okay
I decided that I was going to give her
Try
They told me that I could say their last name but actually request
Did that
I did look up how to pronounce it so I can actually give you the what I thought it was okay and then what it actually is
Yeah okay
Guads
Banana actually
Agua
DJ
What is Lyme disease
Maybe one vowel
Depends on two things W's are vowels no
That's not
It's not even that sometimes
I think it is
I've got into argument about that
Aeiou sometimes Y and W
What about the word cwm
What about the word cwow functions as a vowel in it it means the hill
Anyway thank you Daniel watch we appreciate
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
The Bonsai wolves thank you so much
Next mr. Andy yug
Thank you so much you are now it's
Hey Brother Darkness thank you so much you are now it's
Heroin
Is freakishly large
Mister and eyu Jeep
And thank you so much
Greg laka brother Darkness
Wanted
Bring this up
Sure I think there might be a Mandela effect kind of thing go to your w
Two conversations with people about this people
Remember that rhyme with being a t i o u sometimes y
Get sometimes why I don't know what is reality anymore and I'm not looking forward to
To there being an argument among listeners
W's are sometimes about
There's no reason for it
If you was available then double that is two vowels that it's the only thing that makes sense
Done
Rules
Out the window
Raven is a verb
Before we get to today's episode of I wanted to take a little moment to open up the mail bags
The alright nice
Thing here from Miriam
Listen to Miriam
Sent us
This
Cool
Needle felted
Raptor princess did not quite know what
Call the design of it
It's very cute
So Miriam sent this to me
Because
I need a felted this little Raptor princess at the beginning of this long lonely weird-ass year
She's been gracing us with her benevolence but she belongs
With you I don't know her name but perhaps she will tell you so we've got to figure out a name for this Raptor
Princess
And then
Also Miriam sent and also
C'ville Charlottesville sticker
Sticker for the Blue Ridge abortion fund
And I wanted to take this opportunity to
I just
Reproductive health
Organizations 100% made a donation in the Raptor princesses name to the Blue Ridge
But in this in this trying time
I particularly uncertain
About where
Things are going
Those are organizations that are definitely going to
To need all of us
What's the Step Up
Support as best we can
I'm so
Thank you Miriam for the Raptor princess
It is on the Shelf
That's not going to be its permanent home we'll find a better place to put a
Put on one of the plants
To put it on one of the plants
Yeah
Two princesses don't ride play
Do not
Arabic lime quinoa
We start here on the 20
Second episode
Doctor / 22nd
Alex is swimming a good amount of time
On this episode
He's doing quite a bit of it but
Unfortunately none of it is to You Belong To The City
But he starts off the show with American band
Because we are an American band we are America
I should say that this ism
Minute into the rant
The first minute was not worth it
This just know that this is
If we're starting
Remind we're coming to your town or country
1776 worldwide
We want to see little stars with us
America Detroit
America
Really
God's plan America isn't in Revelations America's Adventure
Paralyzed
Oh boy okay
That took a turn
Seventh seal
Bald Eagle Road from the
Depths to bring Hell Fire upon the wicked
Interesting
Twist
Like just sort of
Yeah formulaic
Not saying anything meaningless Ranch over a dumb rock song
Into hey America is actually really in the Bible
Alright why don't you do an episode about that
Anyway Alex
Skip the talking about how like
Masks
Right
Sure
Bad
Of course
Alex knows this
Casinos the masks
Right and he knows that everyone else
Kind of knows that tooth they just need permission from someone else to be like and that someone is Alex of course it is
He convinces people
And gives them this permission
Should take off their masks
It seems from his neck
Text clip that mostly it's women
And mostly the technique that uses might be called sexual harassment
I'll be sitting there in a legal meaning
I'll be sitting there
Are at a store
And I'm like you don't need that mask
I know it's a fraud
The time
Particularly young attractive women
You
You mask
I get some form and I just so you know where those bad
Well they kind of make it still doesn't want you take them off
You know what's a frog you know what's a lie
We just have to do that
That didn't happen
Is imagining sexually harassed
Why is it
For somebody who won't shut up about God whenever he talks
Do other human beings in his own stories he sounds exactly like the devil
That mask you are very beautiful
He might as well be a serpent in his stories
It's strange it's strange
I take some solace in knowing that this didn't happen
Feels like a very weird
Gross
Yeah I'm still hurting for the fake women
Alex's on this tip talk about this a bit in the past
Confusing
He seems to be putting forth the idea that you can't get sick
Unless you have
Vitamin and mineral deficiencies which is not true
Fine with it is just
Science and medical advice
If it weren't for the fact that he specifically cells supplements
There is
Vitamin D zinc
And end as much
As he does sell those things
When part of his narrative is that
You can't get
Sick if you have these things
Yeah you should draw from those two
Ideas that he presents his products will keep you from getting sick
You can't go sick if you take the supplements that I have therefore it is a prevention for all sickness
Yeah basically
That's bad
Articles
I just want to say again
People don't get malnutrition
You're going to die of a cold
Pneumonia
Cheilosis
Homeless have Hollows door closest just cuz they
Almost
Drugs
Gas station food
I can draw that are sleeping outside
And their bodies are
Malnutrition can definitely be an aspect of what makes people experiencing homelessness more susceptible to catching TBH
But it's far from what experts believe is the largest factor that makes incidence of the condition much higher in that community
According to the World Health Organization quote
The majority of TB cases in urban homeless populations are attributable to ongoing Transmission in shelter
Do the factors that affect the community more than the house population is that they generally have less access to healthcare
Haley find themselves sheltered in Far More densely populated units
Beyond that because they have no permanent address and often no reliable way to
To find or contact them
When someone does test positive for TB it's
Incredibly challenging for healthcare workers
The trace their contacts
And get a jump on
Containment
Alex wants this to be a simple issue of the higher rate of TV being a result of simple choices these people make
Biggity B because they eat gas station food and do drugs that's kind of their fault
But that's nonsense
Through much of my early twenties I ate gas station Food and Drug
There are realities to the lives of people experiencing homelessness deal with are the result of our society choosing not to invest in making sure
I'm sure their lives are healthier or easier
The resource allocation issue that our leaders don't seem to want to fix
A people like Alex it's easier to blame the people who are struggling
Because to do anything else would require him
To give up on his childish opposition to anything
It sounds kind of like collectivism
That's just sad
I find it very interesting that you can have a state
Then
Like followed up
The results of that statement not like
What you think it's just because they're homeless
It's because they're eating gas station food it's because they're in the middle of the street is cuz they're doing drugs is cuz of all the
Things that you do as a result of being homeless
It's not like it's a
It's
Single has no effect on you just don't have a homie are you
Can still go to a restaurant right
That's no problem shirt and then I mean if
You think about it like what would his solution to tuberculosis among the people experiencing homelessness
Like what would what would the solution be get rid of gas
The only way to keep gas station food
Precinct Precinct 4 off
Right
So Alex has a big news
And as we know sometimes when he has big news
So he can't get on his show and do his show
He decided to do is show this
But he also has big nose that almost
Made it to eco.
Michelle
This is so big
Okay
Because of this
Looking fish
And I'm just like
Real journalists are like
Real journalist
Call Udo Udo I can replace you get the proof
You show it to people you document
I don't have the money
Something somebody said
Anime
They just ripped
Wow mascot to Alex complaining about Keith Olbermann
YouTube channel
To Alex saying something Bill Maher joke about 3 years ago
Goal of all left-wing people
I've got someone whose proof is always a lieutenant colonel
Or heard something that you literally what you just said
They hear something and then they repeat it
That's all you do
That's a slap
100 Verde
It's a little rude
It's a little road
Now if that was
Sort of Alex misrepresenting
Reality this next clip
Way worse
My biggest frustration
We have a small media organization
And as soon as I hire somebody in Training Day
No work somewhere else
Which is fine
Happens all the time
I mean this sincerely I can
Can't think of a single Infowars employee who's gone on to bigger and better things
Most of them just disappear into private life like Lee Ann McAdoo or
Jakari Jackson but the ones who try to keep going
Typically follow the path
Of getting poached Ramallah kill
Yeah Joe Biggs who Alex at the fire to save face but pizzagate who's now a high-profile member of The Proud boys
Which I would not consider an improvement
Probably
They're people like Rob Jacobson or Josh Owens and talked about how full of s*** Alex is an owl
Awful it is to work there
Millie Weaver got fired after she put out shadowgate which kind of insinuated that Rodger Stone was involved with the players that were created
Eating internet-based
False flag
Cousin Buckley is gone but he's not a big media figure that's probably
Doberman
Account because he used to work for Infowars but he work for like Newsmax before that
Get a big career in like he's at the Swift boat and a****** before that
And also he hates Alex now in Sudan
I don't know there's nobody
Here's what I do to ever worked it enforces been poached by anyone because literally everyone in the media understands that
Infowars is a stupid organization
And that anyone who would decide to work there
Sweetly unemployable
No one's getting poached
Yeah well here's my theory
On this
What he think
This is getting
Is all of the people who work in his audio and all of the
Cortical researches and all that
Stop right there
18 years old
They get about 8 months of experience and after f****** up everything that they can f****** on Alex
Yeah or they like they're behind the scenes
They they like they've never been
Publicly seen as an elderly knows right and they're like
I got to get out before someone knows I work here
Pixie look behind-the-scenes people but if you or if you take
Just be
In front of camera tablet
No.
Most of the people that work for Infowars Alex has to pretend he doesn't know
Never met him
Nevermind. Listen I don't get into I don't get into that stuff
I have no I've never even
Doug Biggs is one simple assault away from having never met Alex
That's what's going to happen a boy
Anyway this big news
I would say it's a dud
This is a source known directly
By individuals employed here
What you say different
Stratasys the security
Darren was a security guard for a week
Chilling in the nursing home
Multiple balance sometimes for a piece
Everybody's getting
Women are getting them
And almost all of them are
Registered what
Democrats
How's it going
Yeah how do you know that
Learned about this a week ago didn't talk about it on the show now you taking us because he's got another sore
I should have reported that last week
Then I can report it again now or something
Anyway Alex has another source on this
Means anything alright
I have a separate individual come here this morning
And he's showing me the evidence of this
This person you know works in the city of Austin they don't get in trouble
You're going to get more Travelers on a country song just like
Just get me copies of the ballet
Somebody else's ballot
What planets are on both of them
Eminem established stealing amount
It's open-and-shut it's going on
Guarantee I call the FBI knows going to
Yeah probably
You know I don't know just give me copies of ballots whenever you know it
Really serious federal crime when people are paying more attention than ever in the end of the world
I can understand Alex's desire to create fear in his audience of
Conspiracies about voting but this one is a bit offensive and honestly kind of ageist
Alex is trying to create the image that at these assisted living facilities the nefarious staff for stealing old folks pallets in prison
But using them to vote for Biden
Typically this is not how any of this works
According to a fact sheet released by equip for equality in many cases in-person absentee voting event
It's will be organized at Assisted Living Center
If that happens at least two election judges
One from each political party will come to the nursing home
The Friday Saturday Sunday or Monday before Alexa
Sunday and supervise the voting
When mrs. Your vote has to be collected by the election judge in order for it to be counted
Anyone who's an assisted-living can request an ABS
Santee palette
If you do that you can return it in person
And then obviously you're handing it over to the voting
Authorities or we can do it by mail
However if you get assistance in filling out that ballot which you can
From anybody who you decide
Is a qualified person to help you
The person helping you must sign the envelopes
Stating that they assisted you
Failure to do so would be a huge problem
Some states have laws that bar medical staff from assisting people with voting
That does present a challenge since visitation is limited in nursing homes due to
The Coronavirus
This is not an issue that no one is aware of
What's going on here is that Alex is creating conspiracy out of
Complaining about the wrong thing
The real issue that should be addressed as how even without a virus and play
There are hurdles
What's the defective voting access
For people who are in a c
Assisted Living
There are laws that require access to voting but
These are not perfectly followed
And some folks do end up getting disenfranchised
There's a definite problem that exists with propublica citing a Medicare receiving complaints
From 55 nursing homes between 2018 and 2019 where residence quote
Said they weren't given the opportunity to vote or we're unable to get help
Casting a ballot
This is real and it affects a real people have a right to vote
I don't want to be the message
To be that it's not fair for the elderly to vote if they vote Democrat because that must mean that someone's manipulate
That meant the voting that way
Let me go to the conclusion of his logic
Because that elderly people shouldn't have the right to vote because they're too impressionable or something
If you wants to make that argument he's welcome
Do but I would love to
To see how he would try and pull that off
As its band
He's ignoring the real issues surrounding voting rights and assisted living
While creating a fake version the benefits in politically
It's the same thing as with the TV nonsense
The answer is pretty clear when you consult people who understand the issues with the answer is something that
Compatible with Alex's worldview
Making progress in terms of TBH in the unhoused population requires investment and resource commit
Which either gets
Ensuring that everyone in Assisted Living has access to
Secure voting requires money resources
Probably some federal regulations analysis against
All of that
His world is no solution
Cancel B's actual problem
But you knows how to profit from the continuing of the
So that's what you do that's how this operates in
Got a boring yep
Yeah
It is very unproductive
It sucks
Making up
Terrible plans
That would never work
And getting people all scared of them
Will allow you to
Seedat very good plans
That have been in place to dissing
Enfranchise voters
Well this is the
It's a real bummer jangly key that
Amount of attention away from the real issues
Expect I should be addressed
No. I would say that the plans that Alex comes up with for his villains
Very bad blister always like
Very childish and dumb
Now the plans he comes up with for himself
Downright
Very illegal
And so I told these folks I said
Just go out
What you got to do
Go over there
Nursing home myself
The interview
Sneak into a nurse
You've seen me sneak into a secret billionaire
Buckfast
Sequel
30 years later nursing home
Imagine Alex biega like put down on wires
We need to whisper
Otherwise it will be why does everybody lies everybody here.
Is like
The king of
Self
Mike
I picture him basically being like someone in an assassin
The Watergate burglars wouldn't have gotten caught
The door open
I want to commit crimes
So Alex has a pretty
And here that's that's going to be named the winner of the election in the van
Stock market
Sure
The mediator
And this is a disaster by Design
During that they're going to plunge the stock market
Uncertainty about America
10000 blue drop that f******
What is 1020
He's going to be everybody lined up
Trump
Turn the stock market back on
. and they're going to kill the dollar
And then
A leftist won't remember they did this
Honestly Alex's just describing a funhouse mirror version of what could happen if
Biden win
Alex is creating false intentions and causation for things that could
Totally for instance no matter what there's a very good chance that we will not know on Election Day who is one
It's just the reality of how things work when there is such high levels of advanced and apps
Cindy voting which
Can't be counted until election day in many States including Ohio Pennsylvania
Which combine to represent 38 electoral votes
Some States live
Logistically could have difficulty having an accurate count by Tuesday evening
Probably many of them and that isn't suspicious
Alex has made its
Suspicious and by making the delay part of the globalist
Playing witch
Makes no sense
The next layer is the stock
It's very possible that the market could take a dip regardless of who's in the lead during the. Between the Alexa
Turn on the certification of the results
That stretch could be Rocky
Because of the uncertainty represents with investors not knowing which way to place
The Articles I've read it feels like investors are really aware of this Dynamic and many of hedged appropriately
So it's possible 2 p.m.
Ability won't be nearly as severe as it could be but there might be a dip
This is a natural market reaction
But Alex's preemptively characterize this as the globalist
Painting the stock market
Holding it hostage only to be let free if Biden is installed as president
Of course if there is a period of uncertainty and then Biden is declared the winner
That one of these stabilizing effect on the market which
Alex is trying
To get his audience to experience
As the globalists letting the market come back because they got their way
The elements of this narrative that Alex is building
Possible thing
Sensationalized quite a bit
And giving it
Completely fictional Conte
This is one of the big ways that Alex
Pretty good chance that there could be Market instability at the end of this year and it's likely that this instability could be worse
The longer the elect
Action is undecided
However as Jessica Rave the co-founder of datatrek research told
Cmpc quote
Long-lasting it's
Significant volatility usually stems from an economic shock as opposed to politically related issues
Experience of assure
Volatility can be exploited by people like Alex
If they're able to
Contextualize it ahead of time
And then he was being right about the
Prediction of that volatility
To pretend to be right about the context
They ascribe to it
Put simply Alex could be
Fairly accurate in his prediction that there might be Market
It drop so though obviously not as big as he saying
In the period when the election is undecided
And then when the winner is named things will settle down
He could be completely right about that and it would not prove that at all that he was right about the globalist holding the stock market Haas
Message in order to force Trump out and get Biden
That's just complete nonsense that he's imagining
But he's going to give himself the appearance of being right about
Should be
More basic
Prediction
Turn out to be correct
The Sun is going to go up tomorrow
And it's because you master
That's not the way it works
Very simple but essentially the same game
Yeah
If you kind of understand that trick a little bit and you listen to show
Critically
You'll see it come up quite a
Sirius B
You know being correct
What about something
That's
Trivial
Maybe even likely
Haha contact about a prediction that has been written about exhaustively for the patio
Year-and-a-half to the point where it's a notable phenomenon
The hedging and the protection
But investors are looking into for the end of this year
Yeah it's investing it's like a people say stuff
Politics influence investment choices now it's like
What are you doing everybody going to die
I think this is probably less of that amongst now I'm pretty sure
And they were all screaming
Look my friend
There's one thing that you will find at the New York Stock
But you won't find Alex's face
Another mask
I was thinking to wear that mask
Do Alex just wear the mask
You know it will be over soon it'll never be over
Bill Gates
Because the mass of the symbol of idiocy
Big studies
Bill Gates said that it may take a decade to get back to
To the point we reached in terms of economic development in the developing world
He wasn't saying that Alex would have to wear a mask for 10 years or even at the coronavirus pandemic last close to that long just a Thursday
Laxative happened is the world response to a crisis
And that realistically could take a long time to get back to where we were
Alex is just completely lying about what Bill Gates
Set
As for this idea that there were studies showing masks
Said spread disease
Don't let interest
I would be
In a very preliminary search
She can find a meta-analysis conducted back in May
That sound quote
Protective effect
Does wearing masks were
Do cluster-randomized trial
An observational
No studies
You can find a ton of studies that's set out to sea
See if there's an effectiveness
Difference between varying types of masks
So if you want
To make an argument that a cloth mask isn't as good as like a medical mask
Maybe you could do that but
I struggled to find the sort of thing that Alex
To be talkin about
As I always do the last resort I tried to find the article on Alex's on website
And those that web pages damn near unnavigable I was able to
To find what I think he's talking
There was a study that was released back on September 11th it's getting
Subtraction of the right-wing media right now and there was a recent story on Breitbart that Alex's reposted on his
The headline is quote CDC study 85% of coronavirus patients
Reported wearing masks
Always or off
Even this isn't a misinterpretation of a study it still isn't bombshell
As has been made clear over and over again wearing a mask is a less about protecting yourself and more about protecting those around you
In the case
If you are sick
Can possibly unaware
The article on Infowars is arguing against a straw man
They're claiming that the study shows that Max
Sirenis active in stopping the wearer from getting
King sake which is not the claim that anyone is making
I don't think most people would be as offended by antemasque people is wearing a mask was strictly about protecting oneself
It's the part about how wearing a mask is
To protect those around you that makes me whole I won't wear one thing
Kingsley really f***** up and child
Anyway
This study does show that you can catch the coronavirus even if you wear a mask
But I'm using the gotcha so I decided to look closer at the study to see what else
Set
The findings of this study was there
They were largely overlooked
Because what they said what
Just what you'd expect
For instance they found the quote quote close contact with one or more persons with known covid-19 was reported by 4
42% of case page
Compared with 14% of control protest
That's not shocking at all
They also found that these patients were more likely than
Control participants to have dined at a restaurant or gone to a bar in the previous two weeks
Oh yeah that would make
These were the two main findings and their data but the study itself makes clear their large.
Limitations to the day that they were able to gather
And it might not be a perfectly representative sample of the larger population for a number of reasons
This study or no way proves that wearing masks
Spreads disease
And if you're going to take anything from it it should be the dining venues are going to be
Particular challenge
What's the reopening
Ana contact tracing
Critical
You can do if you were exposed to someone who tests
The positive and then behave accordingly
Those things
Seem like productive ways to interpret this information making up b******* about mask spreading disease
What's up
I think there is something to be said for like wearing masks being like
Possibly harmful if you don't wash
Sure but that's the same as clothes
That's that already think it's a bad idea
Okay
How about this
How about that
Here's my picture
Alright we get a licensing system
For being allowed
To say
This is what a study
You know Alexa
16 you also have to take a critical thinking skills
And you get license and then you can but you have to wait till you're like
30 and you get license
And then you can talk about studies as if you know what they're talkin about ideally we should
Just incorporate that into education you would think but I want to go with us I want a license
I want another piece of government ID like conservatives are going to call this red tape
Bureaucracy study about
Hey man look bad
Doctors wear masks
Yeah but it's not fair that the symbol of idiocy idiocy
Pictures of stupid when they're doing surgeries
Not about like
Protecting
Patience from
Van with them from the page
Sure no no no
There's another reason they don't want to smell your blood
Throwing up
Okay
Let's just about smell is bad smell in your blood
Don't smell their blood
What's the point of having
History
What's the point of having science if Alex can say stuff like
Doctor sperm after they don't want to smell your blood
What are you
Talking about Borat
Is back
I have not yet seen Borat to I probably will watch it eventually
Borat
He hates us Baron Cohen Court believes that he works with the abl to control the world he's the closest thing to Hitler there is
What is particularly mad
Because
Rudy Giuliani
I got caught in a
And I'm not great
Situation
Perving on an underage girl thing to the point where Sacha Baron Cohen ran back in because he was like I don't want to actually
Delicia crime here
That's one way to look at it I haven't watched the whole movie but
I've seen the clip that was released
The argument that Alex is going to
To try to make
I bet he can sell me on it and they told her I Rudy was a break
Taking the filming in that they needed to take the Mike outs when he was going into his pants suit
Call boy choosing to ignore the part where the
Fake
15 year old girl invites Rudy into the bedroom for a drink
How do you say
It's clear with hacked that's what happened
I look
I can't say raw footage
B Sharp
Good
It doesn't look good no it looks very crying
So instead of dealing with this
Head on
Alex decide
Let's talk about the time that when Sacha Baron Cohen was making
Bruno
Ron Paul into a
Into a hotel room
And then took off his pants
And then especially the hotel
And Sao
The lights are broken
Please come in here and wait
There's no chairs
Are the bed
You sit on the bed
He comes
Lock the door
You know that was Louis c.k.
His
If he was lucky
Almost
Punchable face I'll talk
The point is is that
What's going on in a hotel room
How to do drop his drawers
A song
I'm out the door
Homophobic
Wow
I went back and I re-watched
That clip from Bruno because I didn't remember remember that
Those are not the words that Ron Paul uses
What is Alex's worth
Okay so Alec
Did Alex escalated from there
From Ron Paul's reaction to me Bruno taking off his pants
You know it's a just
Can't wait to show you how racist and homophobic and everything they are
It's interesting
It just can't wait
So yeah sure
Why Alex has a fake version here of what happened with Rudy
I miss it
Just sad
Rizzo Rizzo Kayleen
He goes to take the mic
Put your back
Parker your side
Do not pull your stuff.
How to get it
And the minute Giuliani goes to do that
Freeman
There's a criminal frama
Alex
Allen alright
Alex Rudy Giuliani is a f******
Terrifying
We all knew
I didn't mean
Sacha Baron Cohen said like it's f***** up that I see it
Like I needed
Like what what did you think was going to happen
It's questionable to agree to an interview with a fifth
18 year old in a hotel room
Like what I just bats
Decision
Alone
Iffy
If you're especially if you're Rudy Giuliani
That choice
Is something that I think
Is
Is dicey
And then to behave in the way that they've shown even before
Putting hand in pants
Paving the way that it appeared that he was behaving
Is another level of
Sounds good
Wow
That is pathetic
It is that's really sad
Is there what's not said though is Alex's initiative
Alex is a guy
Phuket
S***.
And you know that
Because he'll have
True
However
Infowars.com
Blocked on social media
Yorkie crates bad. Video
Panda video
Blocked on social media
Tenaya 2020 election
Consider
He's Bandit what does he know it's not like the name that's Bandit election center I think
Is getting
Block more so now
He has censored by Jack
Dot-com
Get a lot of URL
That are just to try and Dodge
I wish she would apply that same creativity and Ingenuity towards doing at his job
He has initiative
Actually creates a ton of URL
Strang keep traffic coming into his website
Also is creating new
Email addresses
Where people can send him
Information
About how
Maybe they're breaking into or sneaking into nursing home Drake
Cool
Police substation at 10 cops in it and there's like
But you know what somebody's got to do it
A new email
Boat
Ford.com
Cuz you know what's happening in Texas Houston
Michigan to
You know what's happening everywhere
And just go check on your parents
Or check on your sister or your brother
Just just
You know what if you've got a dog
Feel good
Companion Animal
My grandmother was in there
Popa.cr by real happy
Go visit the nursing home with your dog
No visitor and see if there's a
Then rub
Portage
Tumi
Like if you have business to be at Center like if you have a family member there
Go on an investigative Mission with your dog as cover
Yeah
Yeah yeah yeah yeah that's weird
Also what are we doing
Just call call and ask
It would be unfortunate if Alex like
I mean look
I don't think anybody to send bad tips
To that email address holy not need two tons of dumb s***
You guys would
Think that you are coming up with something that's so dumb there's no way and info Warrior would actually do it
And you are
Wrong you are wrong
You can't prank
The prank no matter what any of our listeners could come up with to send it
The f*** with him like
It won't be any sillier visit
Unreality
Reality is going to out surreal you
The Royal back Alex was feeling real bad money was tight
Hey
He thought like a man
Going down
Yes all over
View my last episode
But I'm not going to release
My last episode
I said it'll be there when I go off are whenever they come and get me I'll have my last episode
Was really hoping we we speculated that would be the way he ends his show forever secret last episode
Put on his actual last episode
That would be great
I thought about last week for our show on
This could be our last show
What would I say on my way
Show called my last show ever
That's election
? also next Tuesday next Tuesday on some whatever day is happening
I'm going to do my last show ever
What a f***
Can a soul
I hope he doesn't
I just want to throw tomatoes at it
I thought I would find that computer chip in a homeless man
I would find that
Tubi
Maybe kind of a fun kind of trolling on his partner on Election Day to do his fake
So Alex Goes to calls
The whole show is going to be all wall-to-wall calls
Does that gets calls
Quite a while
And this caller wants to pray
Unfortunately
And I'm going to piggyback off
The last color you had
And I'm going to pray
That's all right with you
Go brother
Lie with me
Lord. God creator and master of the universe
And your son's name is Sheila Emmanuelle
By the we pray that your will be done on Earth as it is in heaven
Your will include making your enemies your footstool
Leslie will surely face
So we got more callers calling in and praying for vengeance and punishment for their Earthly enemies
Remind me of the song
Surprisingly enough
Is really good whenever somebody in the year 2020 writes down us all
Alex f******
King Jones on the air here is much
Praying on the lake 2016 episode
Praying
Yeah
It is kind of an inch
Interesting thing considering you would expect them to
I hate Hillary Clinton so much
More
Than anything you can imagine the Benson praying out that the other whatever happened to another episode
Wade if
It's very strange
Fuct everybody's head up
The right-wing media has really
John the great job of
Destroying the brains of
Billions of people. Here's how you can tell that Alex still has some grass
Online
December
Yeah because this color starts breaking into
Prophecy immediately gets freaked out
God has given me a chance I have not been obedient about
One year ago
He gave me a vision in which told me that
Ezekiel 38
You do not warn them
Hang up I love you to death
I got to go man dude I had a vision you had a
Go listen to that a number of times I can't quite make out what he saying but I think he's
I think that's what he was saying
I think he said if you smoke hemp and Seed that's what it sounded like
That is what I
Gathered but I'm
I can't be certain
Yeah I don't know but whatever it is like yeah
Fine with some religious
Extremism we're cool with preying on erical
You're getting weird disease profitly is
I can't I have that we don't do future here if it's not the global is doing it out of control
Whatever the prophecy is I'm not dead yet
Wrinkly
I'm too into my libertarian weed is cool thing
Way too many of those people it would really bomb out a large section of my audience I went back on drugs
Go with you on if you
Smoke weed you die
You know not even even if you want to say that you're going to hell which is that's my love the herb
I don't understand dude come over to my side it's way more fun over here you're spouting prophecies and
Praying with Alex Jones
I'm smoking weed man come hang out with me
Gaston
Anything of his ghost
Who cares
You've got the floor
Project Veritas
What's happening what you broken what people should share and
Informed about what's coming next
Hey Alex great to be with you I just I don't care whatever is O'Keefe is the boy who cried
Don't care about what he has to say
But I do think it's interesting that Alex is having James O'Keefe on the same episode where he was complaining about boy
Borat
Yep
Yep can't handle those kind of got you prank
You-know-who reporter to a boat
That's that's investigative journalist you know what real journalist do there like FBI
Ditto fuckyourself Cheese's
Anyway we have one last year from the 22nd
I fell out of my chair metaphorically what I heard this
Tell me about the grand solar minimum age
And so why are they spraying on the oxide blocking solar radiation
They're trying to trigger an early
So 911
Returning in 2020
Before we go Interstellar
Have a good day
You're absolutely genius collar leather colors
Genius
Is that
Plan C
What the
F*** just
What happen if you if you're listening to this
You have to
Kind of think
Alex believes that the
The globalist
Yep they really like orderly thing
Yep so they want
To get everyone into camps
Sunforce vaccines imma kill everybody off slowly
I also because of Alex
Is machinations eSource they going to release a Superbowl
Everybody
Yes but also they're trying to
Start a new Ice Age early to kill people out
What what why
They already have the super bio-weapon with the why would they want it
Create a super Ice Age understand
Then there's a lot of different plans up in the air at a given point in time there's that many plans
Throw Alex office
The scent now
Obviously won't work because
Because Alex was up
God himself
All plans
Plantae
Through z
What if what if
Plan to create a new Ice Age
Makes it so the environment is inhospitable
To be super bio-weapon that they've created
Well then they cancel each other out and that's when you go to play in Peabody
I just
Bored bored
Okay alright
Everything that could be an apocalyptic playing
Is
Something to cover
None of these things are compatible or C4 complement each other but they're all there
Yep the other thing that I Come Away with two is like this this weird sense of like
Like I hate
Electoral Alex yeah
I that's the feeling that I have had a really difficult time putting my finger on for a while
Alex shouldn't care about electoral politics
It's really Unbecoming
Sing for him
If he believes that there's a super
A cabal of all this stuff and like
These globalized
They're all in control of
Soumyadeep blah blah blah the right and the left
After all an illusion
Shouldn't care at all
About
Votes you shouldn't get like the election shouldn't matter it should be like the Superbowl
Whatever like
I just feel like this is just a bunch of bulshit
The over-committing is
Is
Embarrassing
It is
I mean like
I just don't know how else to put it is it's like it's an invalidation of his character
He's just a hat
Yeah he doesn't have anything he used to have something to
To bring
That's why we got Where We Are
Now he's just a hack like everybody else
Do you like that's why the wrong Paul stuff works so well it's like yes this is never going to go anywhere
You can
You can sort of
Hang your hat on the what ifs
Like it's just
Great it's perfect for a guy like him
This just stinks
It stinks electoral Alex
Bomber bomber
So there was a debate on Thursday night
And on Friday really got into Studio
Here's how he interpreted the debate
President-trump
Devastation
Joe Biden
He has secured
That
I know I'm just going to call it
10 days out
He's going to win
In 2016
Electoral college
Thanks again so much election fraud
Going on
But just as sure as the sun came up this morning and we'll set this evening you can bet your bottom
Bottom
Benjamin Franklin
For your bottom George Washington
Bottom Thomas Jefferson
At your bottom
Just have the biggest Fiasco to ever seen they already said the last election was illegitimate
Hobo Jojo
But also states are going to secede
I can't think of anything I care about less right
Debate between
Joe Biden
Sure
Can you imagine
Giving a s*** about that
I don't think it's an environment where what you want in a debate
Can happen
I don't like the point of a debate
Would be to understand
Policy position
Understand differences
Between perspectives on issues that we're all facing
And I I don't think between those two
Primarily because he
The involvement of one of them
Yeah I don't think that's possible
No
So f*** it
We were talking about a little while back which is like
It's very hard to imagine that anybody is like
I just don't know
Yeah it doesn't 60 million votes have already been
Cast
That's not that's not
That's too many for anyone to
To genuinely consider that it matters
The people who are like
I better watch this debate
To figure out who I like
Like what the f*** are
I understand why you still do it
Door I guess anybody cheats the same reason reason reason that we're doing so much s*** right now that makes zero sense
That's which is just like
We're all pretty
Pending that the system is still work
Well I mean it's all imaginary lost sure we got it around so you can have it
I honestly think that
It makes perfect sense
Because
Like Trump was
Just like talking
Infowars man
Pointless
It's not based in reality
But it works for these right-wing media cycle
So basically they were seeing exactly the Trump that they need
Fair on that debate smile right
Think that you could easily see that is like yes this is good
But it's probably not good
Dialect orally I think most
People
First of all already made up their mind
And
Someone who's not already into Trump would look at that debate
Any of these debates
I just feel like
That guy's insane
Or just think I don't like what's going on I didn't watch a sec
Alex talks about China
Their relationship
With
This is
He tries to make a metaphor
Where China is like
A biker
Who's in an abusive relationship
Kinship with your mother
Normal situation that happened
Please try and
Trace this metaphor
It's all work on it
Pain
China
Is the big
That is give us an allergy that's having sex with your mom I guess you would say
You're five years old and there's this big mean motorcycle gang doodle a 4lb
Meet your mom and beat you and there's nothing you can really do she's scared
Power button
That's really where this country is
What
Your mom has Stockholm Syndrome
Cigarette
Yeah she's not eating upper ribs are showing
He broke her arm you know last year not summerteeth out last month
Trackmaster
If you don't do something about
Your mama
You can bail on a metaphor
Yeah going well just like
Just be like you know what that one got away from me
Yeah that happens
Live radio
So China is abusive boyfriend
The Democratic party their mother
Alright
You've already lost
The thread
Why is the Democratic party my mom I don't understand
Who is who in this scenario
Am I am I the Democrat
Why where where are the Republicans
There's a kids
Democratic party doesn't have
Any power right now
None
I don't understand
That's a horrifying sort of
Way to paint a picture
Yeah I was something but I don't understand the point I don't understand what
I mean obviously the point is Democrats Regina bad yeah
But also
This be making the Democrats
Incredibly sympathetic
Don't I think he know not for him because he believes that if you're getting hit by somebody
Then that's your fault I guess the Democrats are satanic
Did they kill kids
Yeah but the
China's the
Bigger
Killer of kids I don't know
It doesn't make any sense
None of it makes sense.
Metaphors Alex tries to get into it to get into
Minimizing climate change of carbon emission
Ricky trips over his own foot
Was one big volcano
Human carbon to the atmosphere
It happened in
Krakatoa
Look it up yourself
I'm not sure it's a winning strategy to say the carbon emissions aren't a big deal and your evidence is that every 10 years we do
Much damage is events
That are appointed to his historical disaster
The word that when you say it people don't think about how that's the name of the city
And the volcanoes actually Mount Vesuvius
The word Pompeii is shorthand for that disaster because it was
So bad it was shorthand for seeing people exploded
Good so fast they're f******
Ghosts on the wall
That was in 79 a.d.
Erupted in 1883 and these are still words that just mean volcano disaster because the effect
Those events were so serious
And let such an indelible impression on people psyche
If even if what I was saying we're true it would
Would still be strong argument for taking
Can human carbon emissions and climate change seriously
Does he think it's a convincing argument say that we're pointlessly creating a Krakatoa event every decade
That seems f****** stupid
You know what else created more CO2 emissions than we do that impact to kill off the dinosaurs
Everybody's always worried about volcanoes in meteors or whatever
Now to the larger Point Alex's just making up number
These incredibly violent eruptions are happening all the time where as our actions are
We may not have a Krakatoa type of volcano going off every year but there are volcanoes
The climate.gov
Human activities and mix
60 or more times the amount of carbon dioxide released by volcanoes
Each year
Large violent eruption
Maybacks the rate of human emission
It's for a few hours that they last
But they're too rare and fleeting to rival Humanity's annual admissions
In 2013 us
Geologic survey scientist Terry Gerlach published paper that estimated comparisons
Between emissions caused by volcanoes
His previous paper
In 2011 I had put the figure at humans releasing approximately 90 times as much as volcanoes
But this time the number was lower partially because quote
More data on carbon dioxide emissions
From subsurface magma had become available near set
Also
Even that 90 * figure is probably quite conserve
It is paper Gerlach looked at 4
Peculiarly large event
It's like the eruptions of Mount Saint Helens
Switching found quotes
Released carbon dioxide on a scale similar to
Human output
For about 9 hours
What is absolutely not true and even if it were true
Tell me a really stupid
You just making up numbers that aren't aren't real you know those things that Echo throughout human history
One of those every 10 years
In that in the sky you know that's right right
No-oooooo
What no
No it echoes throughout human history things that Echo throughout human history have to be good right now
These things are scars uncommon history
Like you think about it and you like
Gummy Bears the effects like
Changing Sunset shine
But some of them
Like they affect oral tradition throughout history
That has gone down the myth of the flood
Space
Everywhere for a reason
You know like it doesn't matter where but you got hit by that plug
You can't prove that
Literal flood
Alex says something that I needed citation
Any does not provide one
Numbers within five or ten thousand people the FBI tried to bribe posing as Russians
One conservative
One person
That you think
Long
You think about that hard
Why
A particularly proud
Patriots
Waffles
Grandma's with cancer the wife's got cancer
You got big
Sure whatever
And you're taking their money little info
But now
They cannot get one
Loyal good group of people
Sadlier
We're living right next
Pedophile self
You sound like a f******
Child yeah that's gross stupid
YouTube Rodger buddy it. If I'm tucking you sound like a f******
Doing a middle schooler telling a story about your dad being a corrupt
The debate
He wept
Oh
Why do I did part of the debate here live I went home
To watch it with my family
Standing up
Just what admiration really is
Because it's not jealousy it's stupid
Something example
Appreciating this is so
Dumb
I'm struggling forward
I just want to throw
I want I want to debate and I cried Trump is so great
To hire
10 people
To anywhere Alex Goes
Suddenly sometimes hit him with it
Like just always be around
Alex Jones
Never know when it's going to happen
But I wanted to be hit with the tomatoes semi-regularly
It get my doing some good I think it would be a good idea
Now Alex in this next clip speculates that
Probably
What's going to happen before the election
Is there going to false flag kill Joe Biden
They're going to false-flag kill Joe Biden I mean it made Celine more popular
I mean
Such a loser
Biden
A murder
I don't want to save a loser
Politically dad
Literally
Metaphysically
So
Assassinate Biden
Attack the power grid the internet
Killswitch
How to place selective
Temperature
Nothing
Sure
This is just all of this is every like I feel like every 1940s movie
We're at some point
Like somebody is acting crazy and then
Like f******
Dashiell Hammett
Slaps them in the face
Call it down
And everything's fine again
Go to bathroom splash some water on your face and get it together
Yeah I think what he's doing is
The Buckshot sort of strategy and everything is being touched.
Starship Killswitch by
He's going to get assassinated
Start a new Ice Age the pic go to release super bio weapon
Like all of the cheddar ones your flavor that's the one I'm talking about that going to happen
Anything close to any of them happens I'm going to pretend that's all I was talking about
Chicago got nuked and I still stand by that
Going to forget the 50 things he says
And folks
Guess on his interpretation of the one thing
That was close to what actually has to happen is Democrats don't have memory
And plus if one of
His
I don't know
Fringe weirdo
Community members does take a shot
Abidin
I told you this would happen
Play Alex improvises a little story here about them
Dim globalist
Stock market probably
You'll be fun
What is a did it like
Right around Bank
Thanksgiving soup
Go home
You talk with your parents and everyone here
Triple thing
Fusion
Sense of desperation
Then a bunch of stock market 10-15.
Flights
Before Thanksgiving
Or maybe right after sex
Because they're going to want you to
Yeah
Ryder Truck loading right now
We got a bunch of these little
Hamsters running around
Alex is just making all of that up when he's not he's not alone
Alone in the room
And what else are we going to do
Probably going to come find any that they're going to go through my window 8:30 to walk out my door
Easy I'm convinced of himself
Very troubling for other people
Can hear it before Thanksgiving
With your family
They're probably loading up Ryder trucks
F*** I too have had trouble going to sleep
At around 2 a.m. and you can't sleep for about two hours because everything is just going to
You got anxiety
But you're alone and you deal with
Yeah it's deeply deeply disturbing to hear this
So anyway
That it is next clip
Alex accuses liberals of
Thinking that the Smuggler coyotes tour
Actually coyote coyote
Infowars.com article Liberals are so stupid leftist are so disconnected from reality
Farm Ranch
They thought
The trumpet
Children riding on coyotes
I saw that last night
They said oh my God
Blue check marks are like he's crazy
Coyotes don't bring kids into the United States
That's what they're told you dumb bastards
I'm sure Alex would have the same response to Trump thinking a coyote's referred to the animal
Trump dating
2018 speech Saint Cloud
Without Borders we have the rain
Chaos crime and believe it or not
Coyotes
Because it is very clear instance of trump appearing
Do not know what coyote mad he went to use the word repeatedly in the most recent debate
People most likely making fun of that using those reference as a jumping-off point now because pretending that's not part of the contact
Get Trump's full response to
Coyotes you know the Smugglers
No sir that's stupid
Wow indeed
I agree with
Wow
Just wow
Trump obviously
Was saying that because
He said better 2018
The only reason that he would do that
Because that's how grown-up
Make it look
Two years later like he isn't as stupid as we all know him too
Bananas so Alex
Some calls and gets one
Let's never wants to know how we take our country back
And Alex's
Immediate responses of course
You already have
Because you support my shelf sure
But what if Trump do though how how do we
Before we reach
How long we're on air
We had a huge effect other independent
Not just sitting
What is the Uso
U-boat
They kill the president
God knows we're going to have to
So
We're not the ones who did this or the one started it I'm not looking for 5 believe me I don't want one
But they're looking for
Cuz we got tons of catchphrases Hublot of foods and not Sandman
Yeah I already supported you already saved the country because of you
Support and also maybe
Kill some people
Like remember when the government like I wish the government was like
Let's talk about what the best
Sure
Let's talk about how best to
To take care of rose
Garba
Pickup Man
Some slightly different ideas about local control versus
The federal state line should be supposed to be
Baby reborn
Is that how bored we are is that is if we're just like most because something has
To be interested creative
Fake
Factions
Everything is espionage and drama all the time
We used to have deep so used to show up once every couple of seasons
Do you know it's not a every episode things
And because
3rd hour Abba lot of it is Alex interview
Catherine Austin Fitts
Thought it incredibly boring
She's somebody who's
A frequent guest on Project Camelot and
Begin bring the hits no
Did not but we have one last clip
Explain American be a cop
And I agree with that I also agree with that
We had done a very
Familiar note
It's just it's a mess out there man you could not get me to be a police officer
Yes.
God almighty
Talk about cuz I mean now if you shoot somebody
You're going to prison
I got mad
And I kind of wasn't thinking once I punch the dog in the face few times
I want to do that
Because it was
I don't have those controls
And I just could not be
Outrageous hostility towards dogs with that with that kind of s*** you can't be out
Don't tell me I can't be a cop whenever you just said I saw a person and beat the s***
Service dog for a while you should be wearing a cone
F****** containment
Yeah it's
Adult
You didn't touch it one time
What time is the Heat of the Moment a couple of times as your f******
Crazy person needs to be in containment I feel like the strategy generally to with like a dog that's a little bit out of
Control as I get away from it
Yeah. Punch him if you could not be a f****** cop
Jesus Christ
Price also
Grosser also one of the reasons that people are up in arms and protesting as much as they are and
I have such a backlash
Yeah this conversation is happening
So affectionately
Is because when police
To people they do not
Typically end up
Galaxy
You're stupid everything is done
I can't tell you how different
This is from looking at
At the 2016
Completely
I mean still like
We got when we went and looked
November 4th
Insects
There is demon
You know all that
Always think so
F****** different
Like it's all I love Trump I cried watching the debate
Most you the first time around it's all Hillary's evil
It's very different
And
Equally
Annoying
I will I look forward to the election
Season kind of ending because like I said I do realize it
It's electoral politics does not mix
With crazy conspiracy
The 2-cycle oil and water and that's why this is so
Like just it doesn't make sense
Why is he seemed so desperate
Plenty of other reasons
Is really sad
When you get down to it it's disgraceful really disappointing
Even if you think that there's one good thing
You can say about Ali
What the hell
We do appreciate that
That is very nice of him not to eat as a
Acuvue
Four stars
Easy thing for him to say though because everybody already knows that
Could eat their goldfish so they keep their goldfish away for
Sure it is an opportunity
Automotive
Situation
Are Goldfish crackers Alex
3/12 crackers
They were clearly marked with my name on them
Anyway
We got interesting
Couple days ahead of us cuz now we have this emergency Joe Rogan episode up on Friday
2016 election on Monday
And I do know is that you're not sometime if you are concerned
If you can and it's safe
There are early voting
People should do a look into that
I don't know I always
I always try to
To be kind of
Respectful of
That being very personal
Thing and I I do believe that
A lot of a lot of
Vote bullying can be a real thing sure and I don't want any
Engaging that
Yeah but
You know
People search
I don't know what the back but until then Jordan wave website
Dot-com
Yes we're also on Twitter
We are on Twitter. And I was going to go fight not go to bed Jordan
If you could please find a local charity or bail Fund in your area to help out
Yes I will be back but until then I'm Nero I'm Leo I'm dzx Clark
I'm Daryl rundus I'm going to take my dog to an old folks home snooper ballot