Air Jordan X swetik
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge
Knowledge fight
Nike.com
The round-trip novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Jordan Jordan
My bright spot is a very rare possibly
On
Precedent
Advance
Okay
Episode is recorded
Recorded it hasn't happened
Pikmin 3 Deluxe
So this is supposed to be my day off we got called into duty
Because of world circumstances and Alex Jones going on Joe Rogan podcast
Dick and treat myself is playing Pikmin later just the image is that
Bright spot is enough for me it's it keeping you got love
Pigment you haven't slept for 2 days so you might as well play some picnic for you
Very much looking forward to it cuz there's a
Batman 3 but apparently there's new stuff added
New puzzles and things that I am very excited
Very well-made games
A lot of fun
Cute little alien
One problem solving got to fix your f******
Spaceship I find a bottle caps
A video game thing. I think that's pretty common
Coming up there's like Assassin's Creed Valhalla
I put well over
2:00 in Odyssey Calamity age of calamity
Man it's just like
By the end of the year they're just going to be a too much
Play
There's going to be not enough outside to go to
There's there's always a lot of video games is a lot that are actually in like
My wheelhouse
Alarm
At the end of this year is like just full of games that I want to play
We might take December off just to play video games
Optic December onward
Best Christmas gifts gifts that I like are coming out
Whenever they
My Cubs won the World Series we immediately got so there we go if they are but I cannot enjoy it
Like in the next
Month or so there's new.
King Kong Country game
Get a bunker
Azusa
I'm sorry I didn't
About
20 years ago
There is this like turn-based
A strategy game like a civilization called master of magic
Can I use
To play that with my childhood friend like
Obsessively
20 years ago
What I found out recently though
Is like 10 years ago
Somebody who also loved that game
Made a mod for civilization 4
So I got everything set up and it's f******
Perfect it is
Exactly the experiences that I wanted 20 years ago
And it is nailing it
This is all fifteen-year-old ship that's awesome I've got it on my old computer and it runs per
Perfectly and it makes me feel so good like a Nostalgia all the way I'm very happy for you
You like if I
Got
I don't know
Return to Zork
Rhythm Rhythm ribbon No One Beat rhythm
A mod for Fallout
Right now anyway Jordan today shortly have got a lot
To go over
I got to be honest jorja
Need to talk to you a little later
I'm going to go get some
Apple juice
I'm going to pray to Jesus
We got some in here
I need to talk
I need to talk to you
Alex Jones going on Joe Rogan
Lot of apple juice and scream and I need to talk to
I will say that Alex
Does
Drink about half a bottle of whiskey by the end of this
Yeah how many hours is it
3 hours and 11 minutes half a bottle in 3 hours and $11 of Alex's favorite
11 minutes
He their satanic baby peanut
3 hours
Drunkard like it's not
The end is really depressing the end of this episode is it
Incredibly f*****-up address
But there's some fun stuff along the way
Oh I'm going to Prescott
I killed those dogs
I'm going to say that I think that Joe Rogan
Prize
Sure however I don't think he's committed to what he's pretending to do just holding Alex Jones to account
For claims that he make sure
And I also would say that there is literally no way to do an interview like this response
You just can't do it and I think it's demonstrated by the fact
The Joe Rogan is
Presumably trying and it failed so miserably
Sucks
No he failed miserably and unforgivably when he booked Alex again
Didn't we didn't even need the show
True
The whole premise of like
You're my friend I think you're fun
This fun
I apologize I've been working around the clock to
This episode ready
Need to put out and
I forgot to grab some names for shout out so
Really appreciated
Everyone
Jordan
Today
It is what it is
Here's another context drop
From Jay Chou
You want to watch so crazy
No
I love that that's nice it's nice no no I do not
Not interested
If you start
You're not going to stop
Generally had watch
Rogan show on YouTube
Because it's there
Sure
I decided that this time I was going to download the audio
Podcast
Just have the audio version
In case anything happened to it like maybe it mysteriously disappear from Spotify
But apparently
Since that has happened it's gotten back up on Spotify
I don't know what's going on today
Don't care Vine
Glad you don't care
One thing I didn't realize is that Rogan does AD
Hello friends
The show this episode of the podcast
So whoop
Congratulations on being associated with this
I thought that was surprising
Because there's no
There's an ad the beginning of this episode
Going
We're also brought two
U-Box the motherfuking
Cash
This is funny there's a cash app add on this episode to the cash Episode by square which was co-founded and currently on
Don't by Jack Dorsey the head of Twitter
Who's Alex's mortal enemy
Even funnier when you realize that squares director and also co-founder is Jim McKelvey who is also on the board of directors
Actors for the Federal Reserve Bank in St Louis
Is Joe Rogan shows up to his eyeballs in global accounting
Corporate overlords
Do you buy Squarespace
Squarespace is the host of my website Joe Rogan.com
So whatever
Sheetz.com. Mattresses in boxes
You can get a mattress any podcast
Just say real quick
I love that we don't do that slimy too we're poor and we're going to stay that way but they're enough
Doing ads
And there's another ahead
We're also brought
Tushy is a bidet
That shoots water on your butt
Sweet potato
Attachment
Eclipse
Yeah I wasn't going to get it today but I have the Joe Rogan has said you attach it to yours
Water up your ass
I mean look
I think it's
Remarkable The Joe Rogan
Doing that
Like he's the biggest podcast in the world
He has all kinds of revenue streams he doesn't need to do this
I imagine maybe it's
Partially I don't know
It's so much money we live in the world you and I you and I
You and I live in a world where we did
You know if we had a hundred billion dollars we wouldn't
I don't know I don't think we do this yet
But it's just one of those things like there's no into Kapa
You know it's always
Hey
Just because you're making enough money doesn't mean you couldn't be me
Making more money
And I'm not I'm not criticizing I'm not hating the hustle narrator think it is what it is
This was surprising to me
Because I didn't think
That this was the way that his show a break cuz I'd only watched
Not on the YouTube versions
I thought that is a little bit
Strange and also
Tucci's Squarespace cash happened
Did you know that there are associated with everything that comes up later
I need to be proud of themselves
So here's the first clip that is not an ad and it's Joe Rogan welcoming his producer
Jamie's back to the show
Back in the saddle
How you feeling
Covid free 4 days in a row now
What
You still can't
You look at my battery
Really just
But you don't have any
No residual symptoms except for I can't taste the pickle juice man
People are crazy
F****** crazy didn't want to be too judgmental about the idea that this show is happening at all is nuts
On October 19th is reported in Forbes that quote popular podcast The Joe Rogan Experience has temporarily been struck down
Down by the coronavirus after a key member of Rogan's team test
The positive for covid-19
Obviously I can't possibly be privy to the kind of precautions and such that they take or whether or not the announcement on the 9th
People's delayed
From when Jamie got the positive diagnosis but it absolutely blows my mind that they would think it's a great idea to have people sitting in it
Confined space
4 hours talking and drinking when one of them recently had covid
I understand that the Rogan podcast is big business in these two she adds got to go somewhere
Episodes
Revenue stream biking little bit
This seems a little irresponsible if not for their own sake
Then for the message that it sent so the audience about how nuts
Seriously they're taking these things
You're four days free right that means that we're all safe and you kept it in a day
BJ's pickles
One of these stronger taste
I need to just start carrying around more
Routes to throw
That's if I saw Joe Rogan anywhere it's
A tomato
To the face
As soon as I can unleash I'm going to promise you this short I'm growing some tomato
Okay
You are growing tomatoes Farm to face
We're going to make this happen
Here Alex gets introduced
A nerve
Sales
Alex Jones
This is the most anticipated thing I ever did I probably had no exaggerated
When are you going back on Joe Rogan
I don't know I don't know
You're moving here
Months ago
Now we're here this
This is exciting
I don't get to a butterfly's anymore by taxi
The album here
This is great
It's good that a butterfly
Didn't get the last
Didn't get it when I interview Trump
I got butterflies there today
I got butterflies
Lying piece
Totally
You f****** like you even said to Trump I've got butterflies right now he's f*** you
You lying piece of s*** all these guys like one of the things that they are primary
Way they operate is to flatter each other ingratiate themselves
Like when we go on other people
Apple podcast
Podcast is 7 hours long there's no way I say so
Great but come on man I expect anybody to have time to listen to this
In the past
Whatever Alex has been on Rogan podcast
Has been accompanied by 180 Bravo
So is a goofy
Kind of funny bring some levity to things
Flat Earth charm to
Kind of
Soft the edges
Of whenever Alex and Joe Rogan are sitting here having a stupid conversation
This time Eddie is not there
However there is a third participant is comedian Tim Dillon
Who is comedian do we know him
We have some mutual friends I don't know if I've ever met him
Well I don't want to meet him anymore feel like we might have crossed paths as when I was in New York
Visiting but I'm not entirely sure I don't want to say that cuz it sounds like
I don't know I don't know I do know that
There are some circles that overlap
Yeah I think I remember the name and it's either because he was
At Jamie's one time whenever I was there too but maybe just hanging out or something
He's pretty good
I understand
Like
I think the only memories that I have of him is people I know telling me he's a nice guy
Yeah I don't know I don't know
I will say that
He is not as fun as Eddie Bravo
And
As a third wheel it's weird
I'm also there's another Dynamic it's going on and that is The Joe Rogan is currently doing sober October haha to drink
Lincoln quote on quote Apple Juice you are and Tim doesn't drink so he's high as hell okay alright
Sampling of it we might see it
Mixwell
You know it never works somebody whose only drunk hanging out with somebody who's only High
Didn't happen is in there cuz he wants to be funny
Okay
Yeah I got my free just lame shirt because I believe all women
Is that how you say it
I think so
I thought it was.
Is ghislaine
Do you know
Going
Because line
This is taking a while
Her father was a famous
Stop
Am I sick
Massage spa
Portal you sex operator
Yacht
Okay is that true
Oak Park
He has the confidence of the man whose wrong doesn't care that he's wrong and doesn't plan on carrying soon
Maxwell's father was named Robert Maxwell and I'd love for Alex to try to prove any of the things
But he saying about that dude
What we do know is that he died after falling off his yacht
In the Canary Islands back in 1991
However Alex is trying to imply that this was a murder and that
Not substantiated at all
The two leading theories are an accident or suicide
The rationale for the suicide theory is fairly
Convincing
Prior to his death Robert Maxwell was a huge name of the print industry
Publishing The Daily Mirror Sunday Mirror New York daily news just to name a few of his aunt
When he died it was a
The huge shock and people remember him fondly
With glowing obituaries
A month later a different story would come to the surface
As it turned out Maxwell was deeply in debt in order to keep his creditors at Bay while maintaining his luxurious lifestyle
He'd stolen from his employees pension fund
After his death it was
Discovered that 460 million lb of disappeared
And just like that the fond memories turned
Very sour the bit from The IT Crowd
That's where that bit originally from I guarantee it is
Is like the cops show up at his door
And it is secretary comes in and she's like
The cops are here they want to talk to you about the pension fund
Any just like
Okay that sounds good we walked over to the window opened it up
Just jumped out
I mean I think that might also just be like kind of thing you imagine people do it be the hudsucker proxy
T2
After his death various conspiracy theories have popped up at Alex couldn't prove any of the stuff that he suggesting on this episode
There's no evidence that he was murdered and there's good reason to suspect his death could have been due to his own actions or due to an accident
There's no evidence that he was a spy and the proof offered is
That he was an Israeli agent is
Pretty weak
Basically it's just the fact that his funeral took place in Israel and was attended by then prime minister and president
Santa by the country that's not too weird given that he was a Jewish man who'd escaped Nazi occupation as a youth and was a
Lifelong friend
Vince Porter the state of Israel
I've read some articles that try to make the argument that Maxwell was a spy but none of them are even close to
Conclusive
And even these post have to call him a quote alleged
Spy
There is a book called Robert Maxwell Israel's super-spy that claims that he was a
Super spy
But the reviews are this thing are not great
Ono intriguing if somewhat over-reaching
Quote
At times hard to believe that
What a very nice euphemism
A review by Michael pakenham and the Baltimore Sun puts things into somewhat of a perspective
The authors of the book are quote one man book factories
It's with 56 previous books released
Between the two of them
Your 55:5 apparel
Pakenham says quote
This is a big and ambitious book
Probably too big
I found it finally flawed by access
Exaggeration of narration and more fatally
Conclusions that are on
Drawn into fish
Elaborate aduriz
Substantiate
He later says quote
This amalgam of fact and insinuation converging without distinction suggest coining a new category of prose
How about infowindow
It can be totally possible that Robert Maxwell was secretly a spy but it's important to stress that Alex Jones absolutely cannot see
Substantiate or backup the two main claims
That he has here to open the show
The guylaine Maxwell's father was a spy and that he was murdered when he fell off that yaksh
If you were pushed on either of these going to it immediately have to retreat into saying things like come on and it's been to class
Classified
Making
Elaine's
Horrific
Crimes like
A family business like
Yeah her dad underage girls too it's just
The Maxwell's just do it
It is so f****** slow it's the sort of thing they like I think that if you want it introduced that as I thought
I'm not going
To like
I'm not going to
Tq4 spitballing like
Robert Maxwell
Really influential powerful person
But at the same time I'm going to demand that you have a certain amount of
Evidence to back up your claims you think it's important
And I just find the evidence
So I don't know I
Like I do think it's
A little bit dumb
That was like
I like a book
Reviewers just half
Let's I think we'll invent a new
Genre of literature
Info window supposed to just being like
Man this is
Bulshit
They have to be diplomatic to Grandma book reviewers and
Aspiring authors authors behind
Broken
Alex told him but Epstein like way back
And this is where like
Things
Kind of went off the rails for me in terms of like
Goddamn these episodes going to be so long
You were telling me
About Epstein and this
Island
Years ago
You were telling me long before anybody
I think you told me about him
Before his first
The rest
A long time ago they have these
Xylem
Florida
Children but I learned all this
Ted Gunn
Twenty-plus years ago
He wasn't lying to the FBI director
He was the head of the FBI
Los Angeles
Is a very famous chef
We apologize for
Died
Hi in the 2011
Vice
Good branch
Explain
CIA
Farted
Describes
Hollywood
We make people
Three part of these
Clubs
So I can do all this about Ted for Ted Gunderson
Sure with all due respect I kind of have to suspect The Joe Rogan the memories a little screwy here
Searches on Prison Planet Infowars don't really show much of an awareness of Epstein prior to the mainstream news covering the stories are kind of
I feel like Rogaine might be conflating things
Thinking of something else Alex ranted about to be like you talked about man any any of that I would almost guarantee with
Joe on the show it's like
Anything that sounds like it
Did eventually happen he's going to be like he probably told me before
Talking about like 20 year old conversations are you
Probably stoned out of your mind
Like I don't trust
I don't trust the recall there now absolute
Now as for Alexandra heard all this stuff from Ted Gunderson
I'm going to go ahead and say I believe that
Ted Gunderson was a long-serving FBI age
Retiring in 1979 after a 27-year career
During which time he actually wasn't charged in multiple cities offices
Including Los Angeles Alex is not making that up
After he retired he decided to
Continue with a freelance invest
Alligator and that's where things went
Completely off the rails for Android
In the 1980s the United States experienced its last
Completely out of control satanic panic
Had one of the more hysterical events and it was the McMartin preschool trial
I don't want to
Too much into detail about that but the broad outline is this
There was a preschool in California run by there was founded by Virginia McMartin
Run by some relative
Apparently one of the children who attended the school
Who is also a severe alcoholic
Paranoid skip
The phrenic
Some claims against teachers at the school which range from sexual abuse
Torture two things that border on Magic like one of them
Could fly
This mother quote wrote a letter admitting that she didn't know fantasy from reality
Which was
Weirdly hidden from the defendant's
So the eventual trial
In the process of investigating these allegations police sent out a letter to parents of other students at that school
There was incredibly poorly written and in hindsight
Almost design
The prop the panda
They said that this assistant at the school rate Buckley
Was under investigation for molestation and encouraged
Parents to question their children about sexual a
It's hard to imagine being a parent and reading the following line and not being terrified
Quote
Also photos may have been taken of children without their clothing
Any information from your child regarding having ever observe Ray Buckley to leave a classroom alone with a child during any
.
Or if they had ever observe Ray Buckley tie up a child is important
Naturally parental concern can go awry
A bunch of new claims were made
They'll ultimately no evidence of anything was ever found
There are many that believed that the case would never have made it to the headlines or even very far into the investigation
Were it not for timing
And Paula
A1984 La district attorney Robert
Filippou's Ian
Wasn't a very close race for re-election
Tune to a post he had not initially one
He been appointed District
Attorney after his predecessor had been elected attorney general general of the State of California
In the course of his campaign philibosian made a big deal of the McMartin case
1990 article in the LA Times quote
When the McMartin preschool indictments were first issued in March 1984 then-district attorney Robert for the Bossier
Facing a tough electoral Challenge from Reiner
Exploit the case
During pretrial hearings he sat beside of the prosecutors
In court a practice not seeing it in at least 50
Teen years
During recesses philipose Ian conducted hallway press conferences to grab some
Just before the primary philibosian added 92 counts on top of the already existing 115
Increase the number of alleged victims from 18 to 42
Robert Vela bozian lost
It is wrong for the DA office but the damage had been done
And by the time his successor I were reitner took over Ira Reiner
Make joke over
The case was too big for it to just go away
There were allegations of ritualistic abuse against
Katana kids which was now the biggest story in the country
Which is the problem
Seven people were ultimately arrested and indicted for these alleged
Crimes including Buckley his mother and his sister
As well as three teachers at the school
All charges were dropped against
Five of them before the case went
The trial leaving lonely Ray Buckley and his mother Peggy
As co-defendants
This was the longest and most
Expensive trial in US history ultimately ending up with almost
30 months
So testimony and over two months of jury deliberation
In the end Peggy was acquitted of all charges and the jury was deadlocked on 13 of the charges against Ray
With the foreperson of the jury explaining quote
The interview tapes were too biased
2 L
That's the main Crocs
Ray Buckley would go on to be retried coincidentally around the time when Ira Reiner was attempting to run for the office
California Attorney General
And again they would fail to reach a conviction
The state decided not to try Reagan and all charges were
You're dismissed
The entire Affair was a disgrace
And the pain it caused is almost unimaginable
From the employees of the school whose lives were ruined to the children were
Terrorized by the media attention and almost comically long trial
15 billion dollars in taxpayer money was spent
The ultimately achieve nothing
Other than leave emotional scars
Though it's easy to see some of the political motivations for the prosecution
The ability for it to get there only really happened because of a couple specific people
One of them was a therapist named
Kee MacFarlane
McFarland worked at the Children's Institute International and was in charge of questioning the children who responded to the sensationail LED
Letter from the police
This was not well.
Video tapes of the interviews also showed that McFarlane another therapist relied heavily on leading questions
And subtle pressure to persuade children to join the chorus of accuse
The defense play tapes that show therapist
Sean Connery telling child interviewees
That 183 kids had already revealed quote
Secrets
And that all the McMartin teachers were quote sick in the head
And deserve to be beaten up
The way she went about her work became an issue with the
The trial and quotes
Outside of the presence of the jury judge
Pounders declared quote
In my view her credibility is becoming more of an issue as
She testifies
She was not even called as a witness
As for the prosecution in the second trial
Great job
McFarland
InStyler Quest
Evening led to children making Sensational claims like ritualistic animal sacrifice
Secret torture rooms only accessible by tunnels
People flying
Somebody
Suggest that allegations of underground rooms were the results
Of being a
5 therapist
Using devil puppets quote if they find a secret room what do you think they'll find
That implies to a child that you're interviewing the existence of a secret room
Adjustable leading question
The insurance claim
Of underground rooms and tunnels would need to be investigated
You need to probably already guessed the independent investigator got called in for that job
Went underneath the Getty and found all the knots
Gunderson
That's how we get this back again
Likes all right
I can't say for certain
What he was up to or
Why any of this happened but by this point at Gunter
Completely lost his mind
He was an independent investigator but he wasn't the only one investigating
Understatement to say that his report on the matter doesn't
Match what anyone else is fast
41 claimed that he found a 40
35ft
Tunnel that it 9 ft wide entrances under a Buckley's classroom
It's pretty f******
And that's not the sort of thing that other people would miss you could see that you could knock on the
F****** floor in here a giant Hollow f****** room underneath it if it's that big
Strangely no one but Ted has evidence
7 tunnels that contains over 100 animal bones
Enclose a small white plastic
Plate with three pentagram hand-drawn on top
They're very easy to fight
Animal bones tunnel underneath the classroom
It'll be easy to find on this property that previously with a garbage
B****.
Whatever
Anyway it also in his report as a picture of this plate that has the pentagrams
Sturgis Stars I don't know if
They're not like
In a circle there's nothing overly
To Gundersen wasn't actually the only person
Who found
Disabled
Archaeologists named Jerry stickell
To do a very Rush archaeological assessment of the school
Looking for these fabled tunnel
This work took place in 1990 around when the second trial was going on but the DA's office told them
Even before they began their dig that they quote
Would not consider using any additional data from their work
It was legally pointless what I would do right
Great great great great
Straight
Did he find evidence of angels is that what he found
I read stickles archaeological report and it's very difficult to
Supertime this is a professional unbiased work
It's full of conjecture about cover-ups and
Conspiracy as well as many topics that are far outside the scope of archaeological evidence
By the time stickle went to work there at already been an official investigation
Navigation to buy March 1985 some of the parents have carried out
Unprofessional digging Expedition
If their own which it turned up nothing
The site that stickle had to work on was
Completely disrupted in
Contaminated
If you read his own report it's full of problem
Sounds like how earlier parents had dug up a 15-foot hole look
For an entrance to a tunnel which was
Told that they dug 15ft down was 3ft by 3ft and they ended up finding nothing
And that quote
This is from his report
Quote do to their our lack of qualifications and
Experienced any possible entrance to a tunnel could have been
Skewered by haphazard digging
What
The total is
2 bricks
Store with half our digging would probably reveal it faster than Goods
If it's reported fall down a hole at any point in time
If this report is anything wrong
Researchers who compared stickles report to the official investigation of noted a number of notable errors and omissions in stickles
Report
Like the fact that there is quote no mention of the fact that the
The areas of the side Lot was used as a trash
Job prior to 1942
Is it Go long way towards explaining somebody artifact
It's tickles report
Pretends are suspicious
Stickle claims that his use of ground-penetrating radar show the
The existence of a
Before tunnels or the company contracted to do the work
Which is called Spectrum say hi
No evidence was found to support the existence of filled-in underground
Hearthside below-ground tunnel so he basically did his own Ghost Hunter show where he's just walking around like
I feel it I feel this is where it's at
Yeah you might as well okay
Outrageous
They're clear instances of sickle fudging details to reach the conclusion that normal things he found while digging
Getting around the site already contaminated by previous amateur
It already investigated by professionals were intact
Secret underground tunnels
The torture room
He produced this report
Ted Gunderson used it to prove to the world
Although there was no evidence in the trials were embarrassing this wasn't actually site
The satanic abuse
Then I imagine you and I being back in the satanic
Panic would be experiencing almost
Exactly the same
Feeling that we are right now where it's at
Like you stick your head out and you look around
Everyone is in
Sane
And you're just like I don't
They're overlapping
The literal Christian devil isn't
There are overlaps
So from this point Ted Gunderson became an All-Star in the world of extreme right-wing conspiracy theorist spouting nonsense as a next
Bird on the Insidious World In Plain Sight
Puddle over there
Affected North was convicted and no one believed his supposed evidence is only further proof of just How Deeply rooted this satanic
Conspiracy is
This became Ted's Niche and he was the go-to expert for zealots to have around to life credibility to their nonsense demon claims
Based on the illusion that he's ever produced anything worthwhile
This is how Ted's path must have crossed with Alex's I guess at some point
Ted told Alex
Crazy stuff
Which I guess is now the basis for Alex's career
As opposed to him just being against the world government and private bank
To be perfectly blunt
His blood work on this case and has allowed it to not exist as a cautionary Tale
For some people
But as an actual proven satanic conspiracy
Hey many ways the satanic Panic that we're going through right now
And may not survive is in some part thanks
The Ted's b******* and Alex carrying on his legacy
Oh and is it that were message enough
It later came out the Ted Gunderson was involved
With Jackie Jackie McCullough
A parent of one of the students at McMartin
Preschool who was super involved in the amateur excavation efforts
Kind of biased
F****** God
The only time the FBI produces anything good is when it's in a movie
Real-life the FBI is wall-to-wall garbage
Always I would disagree with that because of
So much stuff that you
Christian ever hear about you are pretty decent record-keeping about like a lot like a lot of stuff
If you can find at the FBI V is shockingly
Well
Capture
Records of interviews and paperwork
Female that's where they hire good people
The problem is they hire bad people for all the other position I also believe it may have been defective FBI agent
At some point during those 27 years
I imagined Hoover might have been an effective FBI agent at one point in time or another
That's something it's kind of
Difficult exam people
Do not Thrive outside of supervision
Yeah like
Some people who could be a good Agent
With a boss or within a structure
Can't operate as independent
Because they get an idea and then they
Want to prove that idea
And they don't have the restraints of
Oversight
Shorts
Ted Gunderson that's kind of the way I feel about it like
Yeah he wasn't
Proving a satanic conspiracy when he was in the FBI because he had a boss
Yeah yeah and not because the boss was stopping him from finding the truth
But because those instinct
To allow
Proven shyt
To be felt as if it was proven
We're reindeer
Take this to the preds
I just need his sign off on this
I want to put all of the FBI's resources
Into investigating whether or not ghosted
Please tell the president that and then once he gives me that signature then I'll be able to get started
What he said no why I don't understand
Running is that what you want me to
Drug should be legal
Goes to be illegal
Pancoast
You're fired
Alright
Private investigation it is Sir
Just feels like Occam's razor makes that a simpler explanation to understand
The world is run
Bye
Satanic
Human trafficking groups
That all communicate with each other and there's no evidence of any of the ASN
I don't know it's just it's a bit much
So
Rogan
Starts complaining about 4 at
He does seem to like Sacha Baron Cohen butt
Problem he thinks they did Rudy dirty
Why
This the Borat movie
Were they
If you haven't seen it
Is very
Cuz I shut him up
Nothing happened
They made it look like
Giuliani
Jerking off
He would have to
Jerk-off
Inappropriate
Touch their back
Exaggerating
It was a couple of light Taps on the back
Well she was
Thank you very much dear yeah you might not want to like minimize that behavior because
Even that is a little it's dodgy
Don't touch a fifteen-year-old ever
Especially if you're rude
F****** Giuliani Rudy Giuliani
Unlock the doors
From the outside
It's a it's a little bit it seems like hey buddy this supposition you don't need to
What is necessary
It's okay for dudes to touch women
They just have to be like that you like part of their f****** life
I don't understand the impulse to defend Giuliani for being alone in a hotel room with someone
He thinks is 15 and touching her on the side like around the ribs
Not like that is not okay not least of which not least of which
Here's my other big problem
He didn't even do anything
Cuz they had to stop him because they had to stop him from doing so
Debatable but probable I don't know I think that that's a harder argument to have
Then one where it's like
Alright
Why is it such a hard thing to just say.
The circumstances that Rudy was in our circumstances you should never find yourself in
It's not like
Don't excuse the touching of this person you should not have been there to begin with
100% piss if this word
Traps that they set was the
Distance of this exactly what happened after that is gravy
He could have just
Giving an interview right now professional setting hold anything like that
You know I hate sometimes there are like
Somebody who's 15 and maybe
You want to help them out on their path of
Conservative pundit ship or whatever
There's an appropriate way to do that and there's an inappropriate way to do that
Everything I can tell about this
The joke
Or whatever the setup is
A completely
Inappropriate setting for this to happen
And then let's see what happens
Like I said man Rogan seems to want to be clear that he doesn't like Sacha Baron Cohen
But also it's totally
Cool what Rudy was do I need
I f****** love
I think he's brilliant
But his
Interpretation
Of what
In the room
Rudy Giuliani
It's not accurate
In my opinion
And who is America
Tapping her while she's
Touching him
Is Mikey does this little tap
On her waist
But it's not
Creepy
It's like an old man
Fly right in your opinion that's not creepy it mine it's supergroup
Here's where we found an impasse example
Especially when there's an intrinsic
Power imbalance America's mayor
Lawyer of the president and aspiring allegedly fifteen-year-old conservative journalist
Like there is a very serious responsibility
Of
Behavior that you have to uphold in this earth
Circumstances
F*** you man this is nonsense Lois Lane was already
Intrepid reporter as Lois Lane was 15 dating Superman that's
F***** up that's
Serious power imbalance specially if Superman used to be the mayor of New York
Celebrity was the lawyer to be current and then lost
Well it was like 7
Super creepy Cheese's
There's an elephant in the room
And it's not that
Scott
Instantly lashed out at Joe on his own show and snake and I've had other things.
Criticize
Joe for having Alex on his shoe
Logan's got a philosophy
People criticize me for being friends
With you and for talking to you and they also criticized
For not supporting
A lot of these people that got
Abandoned
Deplatform
My take on it has always
The best way
Data counter
Wrong
Is correct
When someone says something
That's wrong
Conspiracy theory that's not accurate
The best way to counter that
Is 2
To do better
People say the accurate information
I'm unequipped to debate the point of whether or not quote correct speech is the answer to bad speech
That could get a little philosophical and I don't really know what the answer is so for the purposes of what I'm about to say let's
Stipulate that Joe is right
People who are malicious con artist
Liars and frauds
I have them, you're very popular shows so you can engage in correct speech
Even if that
That's the case then I suggest The Joe Rogan is not ready or capable of having a correct speech
With Alex Jones
We're less than 10 minutes into this episode and already Joe has allowed Alex to assert that Robert Maxwell with a British and Israeli spy
Why was murdered on his got
And the Ted Gunderson revealed real proof and satanic pedophile cabal
Those are two massive instances of bad
Speech that Jose just allowed Alex 2%
Undisputed fact
With no attempts to bring up correct speech to correct it
There's no follow-up out of something like how do you know Maxwell was a spy or why don't you tell her audience more about who Ted
Gunderson is
The reality is the conversation like this
Where your new Japan have fun with your alleged friend Alex Jones
That's never going to be something you can engage in publicly responsive
Because he is a compulsive liar
And you don't want to grind the show to a halt
The fact check every piece of b******* that comes out of his mouth
It only makes matters worse when Rogan in that 10 minutes has also repeatedly asserted that it's no big deal that Rudy
Giuliani touched a waste of a girly believe me 50
Hotel robe
Wow are you trying to get her personal contact information
This is an outrageous kind of behavior where they're trying to argue that everything is fine because Rudy wasn't actually jerking off while they do
Just pretend that the entire context
Having a drink in a hotel room with the girls eat please B15
Whatever doesn't matter
Joe Rogan
Due to his own blind spots and is strange insistence on pretending Alex's actually his friend
Clearly not
Is
Joe's incapable
I've been gauging in this conversation
In a way that would effectively be the kind of corrective speech
He imagines that he's engaged again
You being used by our
And the more this happens the less I'm able to pretend that he's not a willing
Participant in it
The illusion is kind of
It's hard to swallow it
I would even I would even argue
Stipulating that he was right as a terrible idea like what we've covered the sake of the
It's just his taken
The f****** stupid
Even seen like okay
Here's what we've seen
When the left
Tolerance of the intolerant the intolerant take over and start killing people
And when we
Deplatform people
All the sudden they don't have as much
Power to take over and kill us
Yes that is true I'm not entirely sure that that entire Dynamic works the same way with speech
But you're sure
They are categories categories in his speech is
Insanely brought
The parts of the differences between like
Oh I disagree with you about something
Or
I'm lying
Yeah I'm intentionally trying to mislead people about things
For political gain
Those are both
Speech presumably but I think there's a way you would engage with them are deaf
Yeah now
But beyond that I don't know if his take is stupid because I don't know their
Maybe a way in which
Corrective types of speech
Maybe it is
I don't know I'm not convinced that it is
Even though I do a ship about it I'm not sure that our shows the answer to Alex at anyway
I don't know I think it's
A bigger Minds than mine
The only thing that I'm saying when I say I am stipulating that he's right is that otherwise I couldn't point out that
He still can't do that
Even if he's right
He can't do that
Circumstances he still fails
We said before he even had Alex on the show
Your plan sucks
Maybe
The hardest news reporter in the world
Could handle that kind of an interview responsibly with Alex
I'm not even I'm not even shooting on Joe in the scented like I could do it I could
Look before the 3-hour 11-minute Mark I mean Bob Woodward would have released
The tape six months after Alex it already killed a few hundred thousand people but
You know he's nice
Censoring
Slippery slope
When you start censoring
The problem is
The f****** slippery
Open is a reason why we've been so steadfast
In supporting the 1st Amendment
This country
And people think it's
Platatac
Aziz Tech Institute
Our private business
And they should be able to do whatever
Knowing
That f****** slippery slope has gone
From censoring u4ban out
Call Jones on Twitter a year-and-a-half ago
Whitehouse prep
Secretary
Bandar puteri
Because she post something from the New York Post
Crazy
A couple of quick points here White House Press Secretary Kayleigh mcenany
Better is still up and active
She's been treating quite a bit about Hunter Biden so I don't know Joe is trying to say about her getting banned
I'm guessing she posted a link to that New York Post story that was blocked and being exaggerated they're getting kicked off Twitter
I'd like to correct Jose wrong speech with some correct
Censoring things on Twitter has nothing to do with the First Amendment unless the government is doing
You don't have a right to say whatever you want wherever you want to particularly if you're on a platform that someone else runs
If you were a guest on my radio show it might be totally legal for you to be racist as hell but it would be my right to not allow you
You to do so on my show
I legitimately have no idea what people like Joe Rogan imagine the First Amendment to me
I guess the way I would approach this kind of conversation is I would ask him what scenarios exist where it would be okay to kick
Take someone off Twitter
And then try to go from there
Is it okay to kick someone off for threatening another user
If so
Why is that okay
If it's okay for Twitter to kick someone off for threatening an individual safety
Is there a possibility that there's a responsibility that the platform has to
To act when there are other threats
The people safe to you like when people are lying about a Public Health crisis for profit or they're spreading misinformation about an upcoming
Does is there a communal response
Possibility
And I can see a reasonable conversation between people who have different views on it but what I can't see being
Good use of time is a couple of idiots yelling about the First Amendment because weirdly all their bigoted friend
We're getting kicked off popular platforms for things like
Starting a violent Western chauvinist Street game
Sure those are bad
The only solution these Dum Dums ever put forth as repealing section 230 of the communications
Decency
Which makes these platforms like Twitter
Shot makes them platform
Publishers
Relinquish has them of legal responsibility for the things people post
If you were to repeal section 230 not only Whitaker
Completely destroy things like Facebook and Twitter
Make it so you could never run a social media site without
Incredibly intense moderation and censorship
Anytime anybody post
Copyright material Ukiah sued
Anytime anyone threatened another user you could be held responsible
If someone used your messenger service to organize a criminal acts you might find yourself being an accomplice
I think it's a great idea
I'm not sure what I think about Twitter blocking me Hunter Biden New York Post story but I know what Alex and Jo should think about it
HP f*****'-a
Excited
The back of the controversy broke out about it but blocking of the story
Attention
New York Post is not America's oldest new
Paper that's the Hartford Courant
Or if you're not only counting continuously published papers
You could go to the New Hampshire Gazette
If you allow papers
Is that sometimes take a little time off
You know what bums
About any argument about the first
It is not
Hmong
It is not a long amend
If you are going to have a discussion about the
The First Amendment
Someone should write it on the wall it should be
Be in front of you
You should be able to read the first amendment while we're discussing this and then tell me what backs up your b*******
Written within the amount that's what I need you to do you can't just tell me what you think
The First Amendment
22 Rogan
Discredit a little bit later he will make a point that he believes that
These companies have grown to the point where they're effectively should be
Considered utilities
Other governments
And hey
I'm not I don't think that that's the stupidest thing
It just requires a different solution
It requires 38
Treat them like utility move towards that
As opposed to like saying
Hey Alex Jones is a bad actor and he got kicked off
This person's platform
Like
Change the right
Thing
Have a conversation about the right thing first amendment
Reply in these circumstances
You want to talk about the other stuff go for it
Stopped
Confusing people
Are you
Slippery slope
Not interest
Not least of which because we are at the bottom of the
That slope underneath a giant rock
Trump rolled on top of Da baby
We're trying to go up that f***
Cancel the slope of decency goes a little further downward
His daughter
Daughters
Left her diarrhea
And the diary talks about all the
Same stuff go fuc yourself
Alcohol
Alex and Jo don't say anything or verifiable about Hunter Biden's laptop so I thought it'd be kind of fun intro leader
Just a band conversation of it
Like
Ally cast
That said I'm in touch on this really fast
Apparently Alex's buddy Tom paper over at Nationals
It was alleged to be Biden
Daughter Ashley's diary from 2019
If you read the article about it it's pretty disgusting and how it Rebels and Ashley supposed marital troubles and affairs
That story was published on October 26th
But that's another article was posted on National file
Patrick Howley
Here's the deal
These Ding Dongs have an uphill battle in terms of proving to me that this is actually Biden
Daughter's Journal
I don't trust them at all
Particularly someone like Patrick Howley
After reviewing the materials
I'm not convinced that it's definitely a real Journal
Even assuming that it is this is an outrage
Just leave disgusting move on their part
If it's real then it's the private Journal of someone struggling with addiction and mental health
But I find this kind of thing completely Unforgivable
I'm not going to discuss
The contents of the passages from the alleged Journal because nothing of it inside it rises to the level
A feeling like it's appropriate
To discuss
There's no allegations there's no claims in it that matter to people outside of the journal writers live
They're literally lives
It's their business
And if it's real
That is a horrific violation of their rights process their pain in the way they see
Fuc yourself
How dare you
At 1
I feel like this is like telling me that go ask Alice
This is a real die
You know it was like Go Ask Alice
Bulshit is like I just tried LSD yesterday and
Tomorrow
Correct this wrong speed
And to just
F******
Don't let this fly on your f****** platform that Frances kildare's diary was published 30 years after his death
That's the type of story is entirely true in the reporting on it is valid
Joe Rogan still apparently is of the mind that reporting on someone's diary
Is becoming use of his time I find that to be a little bit sad
Joe Rogan
Personal business
Will put out for everyone
To see he might
I appreciate it
I certainly think that is
If it were
Private
Messages to yourself about
Paying and how your processing things
Like I wouldn't
Want to read that from Joe even if I wanted to make fun of them
Like even if Alex is
Like I do so much private stuff about Alex that I don't want to know
I hate him but I still
Like I just can't imagine wanting to use that as ammunition against somebody
It just seems so.
Disgusting
About you than it does about anybody has a journal
So here's some more wrong speech
Trump doesn't
Have
Those outside connect
Because you can't buy him he doesn't have lobbyists
The problem
He then asked family of people around him
That Bass
Become lobbyist
For themselves
And Trump isn't real
And that's going on
You'll find out how
Give me the millions of dollars
You just to say something
The president is this
Standard ship
Real politics
I've always been.
Well it was Tanner does 600 years ago
The wife or the brother or some other words the White House
It got organized last hundred years
Trump Twitter
Everyone around him
How to make
Teacher stop meeting with him and stop
Briefings on what's going on I'll decide
Flashlight pistol Fishel Washington off
Nice spin for Alex to claim the trumps family at everyone around tomorrow lobbyist
Because you can't buy dropping will meet with lobbyists
That's some 2 plus 2 is 5 s***
About in the real world job has done literally everything he can to Buddy up with lobbyists and is running by far the
The most Lobby friendly Administration in recent history
In October 2019 propublica published a report identifying 281 lobbyists
The trumpet hired into his administration
Which is quote
80 times more than the Obama Administration
The Associated Press found a quote in less than three years Trump name more former lobbyist
The cabinet level post that his most recent predecessors did in 8 years
What are the things that scariest about how Trump is operated is that he's been willing to hire lobbyists
It's two positions that involve the fields they previously were lobbying in who knows better than the people who destroyed the entire
To protect the environment one example is a career in healthcare lobbying
Department of Health and Human Services in January 2019
Coincidental situation
Virginia Cantor the ethics Chief counsel
For responsibility and ethics in Washington told propublica that the number of lobbyists Trump was hiring quote
Suggest that lobbyists see themselves as more effective in furthering their clients special interests from
Inside the government
Rather than from outside
That's a shocking conclusion to make
And this phenomenon goes in both directions
In July Politico reported on 82 former Trump Administration officials who'd left their jobs and registered his
Lobbyist
Despite Trump's claim that he was gone
To put a 5-year ban on lobbying for people who left government employment
He's goddamn Chief of Staff ranked priebus is now the chairman of Michael best
The high-profile lobbying firm
Back in July there was plenty of reporting you can find about how Trump connected lobbyists to receiving billions of dollars from Corona
Coronavirus stimulus package packages while the businesses that were struggling we're less than
What does
Just weird
This whole thing is just a disgraceful lice old people who liked
Swap
Watchdog groups in journalists who've actually looked at the Staffing decisions are pretty Universal in their conclusion that
The most lobbyist infest
The presidency that anyone can remember in recent history
I think we've seen the results
Joe Rogan may not know
Research team is a guy with Google was working on the fly into
Getting over covid
Not okay to just let Alex pass off complete lies like this to aggrandize Trump when you're completely unprepared avycon
Conversation about the reality
It demonstrates to your impressionable audience of the man sitting in front of you
Who is your friend
Is a liar
You're not if you're not able to
Demonstrate that you can't have the conversation because then
The opposite
Conclusion will be reached by your audio
And even then Alex's argument is no no no it's not cronic capitalism
Nepotism
That's way better it's nepotism
Turns into a form of crony capitalism because the relatives and Friends
Defacto become exactly
So now they
That's not better so Alex just described a far worse system than what we had prior prior
And Joe's like
Yeah it's like a it's like before but you know the lobby is
Who used to just be professionals in and out related
Yeah that's great
So interesting Lee
They talked about this a little bit more and we get our first instance of Joe actually kind of pushing back
Which age
It was surprised by
Everyone around him and his cabinet and everyone that works there even down to mid-level people
Are now getting multimillion-dollar
Contracts
Four companies
AT&T and stuff
Just adjust
So just to even
Mentioned
That's bad
You said 18
Improving its 18t or you just
Just saying 80
Like
March 8th
Auntie doing something bad
No I just
I was mentioning that as a Fortune 500
Okay but
It's not 18
So we shouldn't say that
See this is why you know
I need someone.
A fact-checker right now to slow down the media will say I'm wrong
Right about that but okay
Put on a hold on a personal lawyer
The personal lawyer the one ended up going to jail
Actually Michael Cohen was getting money from
I was just trying to give you your stalled crying Oz
Before what you really need on your
You show is like
A legit journalist
She's right next to you with a laptop going to Alex hold on hold on
Joy the great idea there although he probably doesn't realize that Alex is entire style of conversation to broadcast his design soda
You can't fact check in without taking for a
There's a reason that our episodes are so long and I desperately need you to Yellow Box
Alex is basically the inverse show
Bizarro
Court ruling Alex will never have someone suggesting he stopped making s*** up
That was a nice attempt by Joe to push back on something Alex with your house slippery Alex Drive
To be how he needs to be seen as right
Even when it mitting
That he's wrong
Play the Trump campaign members are getting million-dollar deals
Some companies like AT&T and then when he's pressed on it
Yes it made you just using a TDS
An examples
When did have a million-dollar deal with AT&T
So I guess that's not true now what you was right to use AT&T as an example
You see how this is intentionally obtuse
Supposed to be confusing
So you'd have a difficult time nailing down exactly what Alex is even saying
An article in Reuters from 2018 discusses how Michael Cohen's consulting firm essential Consultants LLC
Was paid approximately $600,000 a 20-17 by AT&T to advise them on how to work with Trump
This is not illegal but it's shady as hell and guess what code was still working
A trumpet the time
If anything busy
Just an indication of the Shady sleazy behavior that was tolerated and totally normal in Trump Circle
The whole thing is tolerated
Like there was a huge merger on the table between AT&T and Time Warner which dropped been opposed
Do since it would it
As he said
Put quote
Too much concentration of power into the hands of too few
After the election quote Cohen approach ATM
Do you about working on their behalf at the post-election transition
He was given a one-year contract.
Did $50,000 per box
In fairness AT&T also donated $2000000 towards Trump's inauguration to it wasn't like going with the only person get
Everybody made their
We we got nope
The argument that to Alex seems to be making as the Trump hates lobbyists
Everyone around him is a lobbyist personal lawyer was engaged in a pretty clear case of influence peddling
Write this is a dumb argument
Push back on a little bit more but he doesn't
So you have this
And like
Band up
Finding that a story about Michael Cohen getting money from AT&T store now all of everything is true
Is it
Crazy for saying nothing
The problem becomes Alex make Sensational claims that he thinks are proven by a headline
And he's in a space with a guy who can have things proven to him by a headline
It's a real challenge here's what I did I'll have my guy Google it and he read me a headline so now it's true
A really difficult to ever get to anything Morrison
Substantial
So angry
Well I mean this is probably making more mad
Do you remember that Alex likes or dislikes Jared Kushner
Which day
Are you currently right now
You think that I think he's on the doesn't like Kushner tip right now
Now that's a
I can tell you that
I can tell you this
People were really pissed
Patriots game
And others
Enemies
Banana kush
Lot of respect
She got a lot of
Nobody else
Interesting how little press
I wonder why they're getting done
You never heard it
Like a month ago I was ranting on his show about how Jared was part of the deep state
So you are right
These allegiances just go back and forth with little meeting at all
Did they do something I can present is good to f****** Patriots
Daily do something I'm supposed to know what I just heard talk.
Soros gave him some money to secretly working together
Anthony's B steals they're getting a bunch of press coverage but it's not getting the kind of coverage these guys want
Which is people saying the Trump save the world then the reason
They are getting that coverage
Because he hasn't
To be clear Pieces good and I'll always be happy when people are work
Working towards it
I'm not going to bulk it
Peace just because it
Might involve Trump
Actions
But there are plenty of reasons
Today key issue with the story and expressed some reservations
The first is that the
The peace deals that have been struck don't involve any consideration of Palestinian
Which by definition is a problem
The second is that they don't involve Saudi Arabia
The third is that many experts do not believe these Agreements are the foundation of a lasting
Peace
Somerville noted that these deals with ag Bahrain and the United Arab Emirates recognizing and normalizing relations
Israel
They're less likely to create a real function
Peace but they are designed to expand regional trade by normalizing these relations
And to isolate a Ron
By normalizing relations with the UAE and Israel the possibility of using UAE as a place to
Launch from
For any possible attack on a run
Becomes a real issue that Iran has to deal
Ultimately this is not nothing
But it's also not a real peace plan if it doesn't include the Palestinian voice
And also a lot of groundwork for these deals
They weren't late by Trumpeter actually exact work
Should be done by the United Nation
We'll see what happens and how this situation develops
But it's nonsense to pretend that the media hasn't covered these deals
Overly
Deferential to Trump in there cover
Honestly
Deals that are going to lead to war
I mean that's what it
That's what they're creating they're creating a f****** stopgap in order to put their f******
Susan plate that's one perspective on it
Having the amount of information that I have in the abilities that I have I can't
Accurately
Assess
This until later
Water and the effects
Armoire
I can't say that I don't think this takes
Consideration
The Palestinian
It nearly the the except that they need to
And that's a problem
Which is going to lead to
Most likely
So this is still about Jared Kushner here they're talkin about kushner's dad right now I was a criminal
Criminal
Yeah unlike
Unlike Kushner
Sure
It's a Rogan find an article
About Chris Christie
Who was involved in
The prosecution of course
Where's father
And so they they talk about that and then Alex
Make s*** up
And so what am I supposed to do the process
I mean if a guy hires a process
Seduce
His brother-in-law was his brother-in-law
His brother-in-law brother-in-law
Okay
I like a complete
And then videotapes it
Send send the video.
To his sister
To attempt
Intimidate her
Testifying before grand jury
They're really need anymore
But but it wasn't his interpretation
All the time
People do videotaped other person cheating
That's why I went to prison
Because he wasn't doing if you was doing that the show that the person testifying was wrong
Of course you're trying to influence testimony
It's this idea that
Yes that they're cheating
I told you they were here's the proof how does that be
Become fraud
Okay I'm confused
So he set up his brother-in-law
With a
Attitude
What's been going on before what you do
Alex is having fun here making things up but I regret to inform you that Jared's father Charles Kushner plead guilty
To quote
16 counts of assisting in the filing a false tax return
One count of retaliating against a cooperating witness and one count of making
Making false statements to the federal election
Condition
Well he was running his business Kushner
Companies Charles had falsified charitable contributions in the excessive $1000000 to cheat on taxes
His sister was a witness to the crime and he didn't want her to testify so he attempted to hire sex worker to seduce her husband
Which you would record and use as blackmail
He pled guilty to all of this
And even coach told the court that he had paid a private investigator $25,000 to arrange for the seduction
And videotaping of the cooperating with
Husband
Kushner admitted to personally recruiting The Prostitute and instructing the videotape emailed
Do the cooperating Witness
Alex's pretending this is just a thing workers dad claimed that this dude was cheating but don't believe him so I guess he went and hired a sec
Sex workers who could videotape them having sex
I am right
Wow this is childish trying to pass off his truth
A lot of reasonable people try and prove themselves correct
By hiring a stalker in order to Blackmail their relation
Remind me to do with this has proven himself
Right and he knew he wasn't going to get a fair Shake in in court
Because Rich guys never get a fair Shake Dan the other 16 counts of fraud that he also touch
Those were fake
I want you to think about this
I was reflecting on as I was going through this episode
If Alex Jones
Wasn't the Trainwreck lightning-rod of attention The Joe Rogan
Can capitalize on platforming
Would you take any of this yet that he's saying seriously even for a second
Just imagine that in the context of this episode like all of the content is the same
But it's being said by a random person
You rightly ignore them
It assumed that they weren't well
Joe Rogan's only doing this because of the attention that he can get out of having Alex on his podcast
And possibly some imagining that their friends
I can't believe
Sounds like he does
Sounds like he still thinks their friends
Does he not listen to her show I have warned him many times that Alex
This is not his friend
I feel like his mom right
He's getting caught up in the wrong crack
Do you like it by the end of this
Joe doesn't realize that Alex is not his friend and he's being used
I just don't eat beyond that point ever reached
Because Alex
If Joe wants
To look more into this
This a story about kushner's Dad
And here's Alex's response
So he set up his brother-in-law
With a price
Destitute
To show that this was been going on before Wichita deal
Haida Prost
22 lure
Shoulder
Into having sex
In a Bridgewater
New Jersey motel in Frisco
You find yourself
Bridgewater New Jersey motel room
Camera roll
A tape of the encounter was then sent to Krishna
Builders warehouse
Distrust
We're Infowars
Just rustic
Now granted all the information you'll be able
Define does not
Support my version of things
How about no Alex have not learned that you like that is a new slogan for them
Just trust us look into it
Hey
The world is run by demon
Okay
So Alex he doesn't just rely on trust
He also has sources
And he's brought
We're going to get a lot of lieutenant-colonel.
Where they say
Jeezy pink mustache
Destroy Trump
To save America
He was our leader
I'm at the Davos group
He said three years ago I will
Will destroy Trump
I will work with Hollywood I got all his clothes right here
Ngcp said I want to overthrow American democracy
I want to repudiate it
How much is Credit in ggp
Admits he admires a dolphin
And Joseph Stalin
Isn't he doing that
Pull up
Adolf Hitler Joseph Stalin
Those are 2015
Always weirds me out whenever he specifically brings up Hitler and Stalin as being like
Look at the guys this idiot admires
Cody never never liked notes Hitler and Stalin
And I love those
Well he has at least that there studs
Joe again
He's trying
Part of my argument that this is just not a thing you can do responsibly tries to push back
On Alex's claim
That she had to come out and said
That he's going to destroy Trump or whatever
Handle
The Washington Post
The LA Times the New York Times I brought you the Arctic
Wilshere
Dreams of Red Emperor the Relentless rise
Image articles
He must destroy American West
Christian Valley
We love them
And we accept
China is our master
Who's this
Washington Post
Who sing that quote
The Washington Post
There's a huge article LA Times I understand but the
The quote that you just
Just like I said
AT&T gave money on the Pixley lobbying you pull it up
But what
Who you quoted song
Did you quote when you
I'm quoting
This morning before I came here
What I remember
David
Don
Curry
Burley
Nn
Chinese ladies white and yellow the prevailing sentiment of what they feel they must
Jumping in their articles
Destroyed
Save them
From weekend America
Look at the Chinese dictator
Do you think
That they're doing that
Happy cuz jump
Change the
The trade deal
Trump trade War he ended our sermons
Okay
You can see like Allegan camp
Answer direct questions
Think about what are you talkin about I remember from what I read this morning
That's not that is not a breath
Terrible
Is it longer than 4 Page
Probably
The towards the end of this episode I get I found one of these
Greatest
Exaggerations of length of everfree it's amazing
Okay
So are they going to talk about climate
Change a bit here
Alex is really into
Cole
Charcoal plant
That's really clean 104
How's that
Skype there two different types
The major play say when he says Clean Coal a roll my
What trumps like Queen Cole
Queen
Is it
Oh boy
So here we go Alex tries to explain his Clean Coal
This is amazing
Infuriate you
But please hold your fire for a moment
You'll notice in this clip
I believe what happened
Is that Alex realizes
You don't give her watches cartoons we're like Wile E coyote will run off of
The cliff and I'll make it a few staff and then he looks down and I believe
What happened
They had old-fashioned
Google Plants China doesn't have one scrubber or
Filter on there
Coal Power Plant
China doesn't have
There's one place United States
Major deposits
Occult
Such pure carb
Scrubbers
Nothing comes out the carbon dioxide water
Well they know we know water
Stop Ashley what's carbon
Dioxide
People think it's Monica side
Studies of you say
The scientific name of water most
Play band
You go out with Street jail Road
Monoxide is ever
Everywhere you get too much of either.
Background
So what I think is going on here is that Alex knows the word scrubber and that's about the dab
Of his understanding of this topic I looks like that's where we're at
He knows like as he's starting to talk is like
I don't really have much else to say on this so I'm going to just rest
How about I'll chemical names are weird and people don't know what they are
It's a lot of fun but it has nothing to do with the subject of clean call its
Leanne attempt to get Joe to forget the line of questioning he was going down
I get lost in this site Trail because Alex is a
Caught in a lie that he can't backup
There is no such thing as clean cold the way they
He is imagining it and he's lying to Joe's face way that he's talking about scrubbers almost like he thinks that there's like
Keep Century Japanese women with like little brushes just
Sonifi add Scrubbing Bubbles from the commercial that are running around and smiling
Piece of charcoal
Going to be so f****** pissed by the end of this section understand
How
Many people are listening to Joe Rogan
And Alex Jones talk about the
The climate
What me thank God the Joe's here to correct this a bad speech millions of people listen to
Magical great Cole out and west
There's a place in the United
States where carbon is just soap
You're right that's what is that what is that f****** carbon nanotubes
Diamond
It's cute pure carbon so clean
What is soclean
Same thing we do the scientific name of salt
Shoshone
Forgot that one
Monoxide
Dockside
That's a good one
That's
Wow light
Water
Oxygen
Carbon dioxide
You got to have fur
4life
Just say Cole his return
Quickshot carbon dioxide
And water vapor
Dirty Cole full
Bluemercury Oliver
Huge deposit
A clean-burning call
The whole world for a thousand
One Call
It showed a that's only on stage
That basically you don't even put scrubbers on
You need to scrubbers
This is Disturbed
How to fight somebody
I'm going to walk out of this
And I'm just going to fight the first f****** person I said about investing in like a heavy bag not for twerking
But just for like a road without another episode
Songs for me while I'm listening to these clips
Completely misleading Joe on the main issue which is that carbon dioxide is not just magically good
It's necessary for Life yes that is true but
In excess amounts it has a bad effect on the environment
Alex compared to water so I will too
You need water to live but too much of it will kill you it
It's the same thing with CO2
Is this conversation Alex's reframe the issue
Cuso the part that requires pushback isn't even being discussed
Depardieu needs to attack is the idea that CO2 emissions are always good but everyone thinks they're bad cuz they're actually
Carbon monoxide
That's what it is
In the world and Alex could never defend that position
But now Alex has introduced a completely new layer to this b*******
Which is that there's magical super pure cool at West is that I just
I just
The
Magical
Anyting Utah he's literally doing a f****** Brigham Young honest
We have to go to Utah to buy well Golden Plates is that what we're doing Dan
You can find a full report from the US Geological Survey of all the coal deposits in Utah play none of them seem to match with Alex's
Describing
You really think that they make note of this magic Cole that could power the entire world for a thousand years but I guess they somehow overlooked that
Globalist
Also Utah
Responsible for mining approximately
2%
Ethical let's use annually in the United States
Yeah but that's the match
Sure
A real and it's just a childish brain has come up with when he thinks about the word
Clean Coal
But his strategy is really good here
What he's done
Create a completely outrageous claim that's going to distract people from the farm or in
Insidious one that you've snuck through
There's no time to argue about CO2 if you're caught up with this magical Utah call
Yeah it doesn't
Really actually work
There is.
Because he has my document here's my argument to the magical Cole
No now let's talk about CO2
Well
Magical call is more fun
It is way more fun
You can't
You can't do that
Can't tell me that there's magical bird
Coldwell
Usher you should
Cuz it's not
It's not a good idea
But
Alex dozen
Succeed in wiggling loose
From this this trap
Or whatever not really in the Trap
You look mr. Magoo do you ran into like a coat rack
And
A coat fell on him and he thinks it's in that cell
And he's trying to get out of this metaphorical code by rambling of that has CO2 is great
This gets so weird
One call is so damn. It's only I've stated
Prescribers on it
Are scientists
In the 4050
70s
They realize that dirty call her
What's mercury in it
As always horrible toxic
Robert Sonic
20 Robert Culp
Wires
Hoses
That's because it's
And then take off all the cameras
Plastic
Chemicals
Pesticide
Make everything else
It comes out of that
And then out of the stack
Nothing but what if Center
Nothing but water
And carbon dioxide
Totally clean
Totally pure
Chow Chow
That's what's going on
Carbon monoxide
Why does everybody
Is worried about carbs
Urban dioxide
And the environment has
No negative
We'll talk about
Let's carbon monoxide is not
Something people are concerned about but it's a completely different issue has failed on many many levels but the fact
This one right I will give him props for that and it allows for the opportunity for Alex.
I have to say more and that in and of itself is kind of a good situation
If you handle it appropriately
An after-the-fact you say
That's stupid
Doesn't
He does allow for the opportunity for Alex
Carbon dioxide
Was over 500 times stronger
Ian the time
T-Rex
Okay
That's what plant
Krystal fast
So big
Just like Mars loss
U7 ocean
Lost
Smaller Planet couldn't hold
Is the earth losing its hat
Crazy is
What time pump up all
Of this juice and all this
Carbon
Was produced on the service
Ran down cracks
Went out pumping out all that
Carbon steel
Years ago
Terraforming
The planets carbon dioxide
Leave right this time like alien figure this out
Isn't carbon
But they said
That we would have a 7
Increase they said that my 2013 all that La would be flooded to Newark beatified all that slice
Forget about what they said in the past
They're saying now
Carbon dioxide
Responsible
4 in in
Which which which we hope
Pick-n-Pull opening
The last ice age
Hold a butthole.
Apparently
Temperature's going up is good or alright
We need a big
Big box like a packing box
Put some holes in it
When you put Alex in there and we need to feed him once
That's what I think we need to do
I don't even if I'd be safe I think it's a good idea so here we learned that there was way more CO2 in the atmosphere during the time
Do dinosaurs but since then CO2 levels have gone.
Accompanies of come-alongs
And figured out the perfect solution
Pollutant what happened
Baker billions of dollars
I leave I'm being
Charitable when I say air hose
It's fair enough that CO2 levels were much higher in the time of dinosaurs butt
So what
Those millions of years ago and to pretend that we're at all ready to face the kind of issues that would accompany the Earth changing to a climate unseen
For millions of years
Is comical dinosaurs record
Detailed notes and they left us solution
Unfortunately they didn't survive six
52 million year turned into a cockroach
There's normal variability in the levels of CO2 in the atmosphere over time that is
Fair enough
And you can see it roughly go up and down and waves for the past like 800,000 years
To the time posty dust real Revolution present
That wave get
With 2019 number representing a 33% increase over the previous highest CO2 concentration recorded
About 300,000 years ago
Alex does not understand the issues he's talking about and I will at least plug Joe for creating the situation where Alex sounds like
The idiot that he is but I resent
But he doesn't have the ability to
Call Alex
A liar and a fraud
Descent
Did this s*** is nonsense we have no idea what he's talking
I mean it's even worse it's
It's so much worse now than we could even
Like a bit the problem is we're so distracted by the rest of everything being the words
Like ice sheets are not even for me
Like this is not good
Yeah everything is really really bad with the climate more so than anything else
More f*****
What's up
It's hard to look at the
Why we're staying here
Nearest source of freshwater Dan Hotel over there we'll grab some buckets every morning will boil them and we'll have a great day
Joe does make another good play
Here on the same topic in that is that well
You know it's been shown that
Rising
Temperatures lead to hurricanes
Because of the Rising
Water temperature
Condition
Where is storms are stronger and there's more of them could play
Oh boy
The increase
Temperature of the earth is
Hurricanes
The frequency
In the power of the
If you look up the
The last hundred years Earth
That's all media hype
Chow Chow
I swear to God
Are you a carbon
Well said
Can I please tell you what's going on
You are a carbon-based life
Let me show you what I came here with my
Hellboy huracanes no matter how you want it
Determine the statistic
If you want to go by total number of named storms 2005 is a record holder with 28
But it probably won't
Before long
Since less than a week ago we saw tropical storm Zeta represent the 27th named storm of the season
Which won't be over
Until the end of November release
If you want to go by severity of storms that's been increasing as well if you want to go with frequency of stronger storms that setting records
Frequency of storms that Escalade very rapidly is also increasing
Three of the top five most costly storms in recorded history in the United
It states happened in the 2017
The other two were in 2012
You have to go 23 storms down that list
251 that happened before 1960
C5
It's not media hype that hurricanes are getting stronger and happening more frequently
Joking scoff italics
Deserve to be allowed to be scoffed at and then move along.
Dumbass distraction point but how were carbon-based life-form
He deserves to have this show grind to a halt
Until he can see that he's making this up
He should have to be forced
To either leave
Your admit I don't know what I'm talking about
I'm full of s***
Anything else is a wind
Anything else is a win like pivoting over to like
Oh we're carbon-based life-forms
Is exactly what Alex needs to do
And allowing him to do it
Is conceding this point essentially
And it's just a better move
Rogan
Having him walk off his show
It's just the best thing that Rogan
Well everybody would have non-stop talked about it instead of being the giant piece of s*** that would have been
Been one side of the argument in the other argument with a look at how it's essentially
Because if he eat
Gratwick believes he can have his
Come on Gallagher moment when you get the Trainwreck
Inevitably happens whenever Alex Goes anywhere in Idaho
He's guaranteed attention no matter what he does
Zip half that he's chosen
To take as the one
The county has the appearance of responsibility but isn't really all that responsible
Because
Alex Price
Do you know rant about carbon
Cuz you got some.
But he also realizes again much like Wile E coyote
He has run out of cliff
So he tries to transition
Into some transphobia
Sure and I'm too Jose credit
He tries to get him back on track
What are you what is what is what is what is Joe Rogan made of
Carpet
What we are literally
What are songwriters
Carb songs
Carbon-based life
Most
The dishes the carbon cycle
What's your sign
Search up so just like
They think they come out and assault reali now
A little boy is biologically
It girl
Let's not go down in capital
Two genders
Let's not go down that road
That road in the future
I don't want to get off track, because
Is there a delicate balance
The temperature on Earth
The rising
Sea levels in the melting the ice caps
This is all been
Bushfire
But very can
Environmental
Have said that an increase in
The temperature of the Earth
Disastrous
Are you sure it's a power grab
How do you know that it's not
How do you know
Because they're arrogant they've all written white papers on that I'd rather give you
Okay
Wow
U-cat
And you don't
Example even if it's a power Dynamic like with Rogan who is he
It's ya to stay on because this
His mrs. Outlet Rogan's the only one is willing to put a monkey butt
The face of Spotify.
And
Just
No matter what
If you just point out some
Power grab
But but the reason
But the reason that you descend to that is because Joe clearly wasn't taking the bait with going down the drain the hypocritical
Play I was hoping to
Pilot the conversation into that water can keep motormouth Highway through its impact
The fact that I could
Completely punted too far off carbon
Until you have to just be blocked no power grab a red light papers I could prove everything bother.
Ends up
At the bottom and it's sort of
Becomes like
Listen to this clip of Alex they're sort of like
Alright fine I'll just say all the words I know about climate change CO2 and stuff
There is
Contributing fact
Scientific
Proven that
Increase carbon dioxide
Has Anna
Effect on the
It depends on the models that you
Sometimes
More carbon dioxide
I can cause a cooling
Healing effect it depends
Apologize
Volcanic
The time also
Solar maximum and minimum
Alex's threw out that meaningless word salad of everything he can remember Lord monckton telling him in the past
Solar maximum
Potash
None of that is
Just Alex's weasel answer so he doesn't have to own the position of having that CO2 going up causes temperature to go
This is all just a function of him not wanting to get nailed down on a particular fact because if he does he has to only
Implications
Princeton
If Joe gets him to admit that Rising
CO2 levels result in higher temperatures
Justify why higher temp
Pictures are good
If Joe could demonstrate the negative effects of rising temperatures from the rising sea level
Do the relationship between water temperatures and hurricanes to the droughts around the world to the fact that many regions of the world could become
Uninhabitable
And caused massive dislocation of people then Alex would have to accept that he was in
Favor of those things
You can't do that
So that's why you always gives not answers which allowed to continue to operate in this deceptive space
Commit to anything except everything and everyone dropped
I don't understand the bottle
I just don't understand what it is
Really like deep down
That makes conservatives want to rub oil
Balls all over there
I just don't get it
Just like
I just love that s*** on their face and I just don't understand
Yeah I don't I don't know exactly either maybe that's the way we do
Okay we have to do something about climate change otherwise all those people are going to be at have to come here
That is not ecofascism
Totally know I'm just trying to trick them in
And doing it I'm not I do I did not come over here to an argument
I'll go over here and be like hey see if we do this then you won't have to deal with all these refugees
At the same time I'll be like come on in refugees just come around the back
Around the back entrance
So you're essentially appealing to an Eco fascist argument in order to sway their so
Support
For the opposite
Good luck
It is next Corp Rogan is trying to explain to Alex
That there are
Do you know if there are these
Environmentalists who have a point and then there are people in industry and they aren't the same people
Who knows they are working
Different
Alex does not agree
The environmentalist
Or not
In bed
Industrialist
Environmentalist
They're not in bed
With all these
Think that they can
Control the the worlds
Climate change
There's a bigot
Funders of it contrary to what you
Understand
You're smart.
Let's go hear what we have to
We have
Can't you understand that
The way you talk
And I enjoy the weight
Fast with the way you talk
His fast can you go on these
Long tan
And you go to frogs
Being gay
I wanted people control
But I want to do it
Step-by-step
But most people
The vast here we got here
PPK
100 million
The fun new admission
Productions project
Appreciate
That is why Joe is not equipped to handle the role he's given himself
That clip perfectly encapsulates visit
Entire dynamic
Joe thinks he can handle taking a mile-a-minute talkers liar like Alex Jones and slowing down
But they can take these claims piece-by-piece
And show what's really behind it all
He thinks because of the fake respecting imagines Alex has four and then Alex wouldn't just lie to his face and Dodge on to other topics
Instead of admit that he's lying to his fake friends
Which was wrong
Alex do not give a s*** about
Conversely Joe also really doesn't give as much of a s*** is pretending to
He knows that having Alex Auto be a huge attention-grabber as
I have the past two times he's been on the show
JoJo also knows that he can't really get away with just having Alex
On like he has in the past
There has to be the appearance of being a critical interview which is manifesting in his attempts
Alex and Roi
You can clearly see how rattled even just the performance of pushback
Just alyx
He's flopping all over the place and saying
Completely insane s***
Wiggle is way out of
Corner he accidentally backs himself into but we're Joe gives away his true intentions are moments like they're right at the
He's got Alex in a position where they refocus
He's supposed to get to his point about a CO2 emission
Conspiracy
Now it's improving and right is Alex is about to start talkin Joe pokes in with the gay frogs
If Joe wants the sideshow but he doesn't want to take responsibility for it
Honestly I kind of find this approach to be more distasteful than him and Eddie Bravo just laughing
Cuz because
It doesn't like that doesn't
Pretend to be something else now this is
This is to healthcare what the AC in this is to reality what the ACA
Day is to socialize
You know like I don't
Something is not
The whole thing sure and it's usually not as good
And
As we've seen with the ACA
It's caused a lot more problems in harm than everything else
I I don't I don't accept your analogy if only because I think it also helps helping a lot of people.
Tons of people I was being very very I don't know
Maybe there's a possibility that this interview could also help some people
Because I have forgotten some messages from a couple people just in my personal life who don't know Alex that
Well but like Rogan the interview they're like
What is this drunk
A****** like I
I feel like
Picked up some objective viewers could see
Rogan's pushback and Alex's inability to answer anything we like
It's full of s*** yeah I think there's a possibility that there is some benefit from it but I think the
What what Rogan is setting out to do eat does not achieve
And I think it does more harm
Good cuz you set up the
The impression that Alex is right about a lot of stuff
Demonstrate that he's wrong about everything and let him wiggle out of taking responsibility or owning
The fact that he's wrong about all these things
And that just makes him appear to be rubbing
York City
Stupid
Was it entertaining
Wow why do
There's one part that will get to that I found
Exciting
Okay almost like the end of a basketball
Cuz I like always
Jack is taking his last two freezer I didn't think it was that good
Warrior training and one of the reasons is that I mean they're all on different
Drugs or sober Shore Sean that is incompatible
Nothing against Tim Dillon but he's just not really even ineffective
Is third part in this bad Bravo at least will bring his own brand of personality and
Tim Dillon's just an Infowars fan likes Alex
And tries to reframe things Alex says
In ways that Joe might be more close to
Greenwood
It doesn't really make that many jokes
See Eddie Bravo adds that at that element that are
Factor
You know where it's like
Alex goes on a weird rent and then Eddie Bravo's like
You know I heard people were on the moon and they came down to my place
And telling you right now that's why Alex is right
Eddie Bravo
Your nuts
Thank you for smoothing the edges out on Alex saying some really transphobic
So Alex is still a be enforced
Discuss climate
You would rather have not stayed on this long should never remember everything is guidance
So happy we had this on his Wednesday episode from Wednesday
Volcanoes baby Ariel is one major volcano
Put out more dust
The decades
The Fuelman
Is what human cause nuclei deformity
Storm causes a nucleotide
What's the climatologists
They haven't broken down
The Sun by Mac
Is 98
Percent of
The driver
JoJo's is allowing him to to make this without any any cops
10 pushback
But Joe does have a good point
And that is that
Even if we allow that there are at
Ton of different influenza
Is that our cause
Climate change
CO2 emission is one thing that humans are capable of
Control a short the rest of the thing
Sunspots or whatever
We can't control those that do it
So it should be our
Google
To control the elements that could be destructive that are in our capacity could draw
And then Alex say something
Just batty
Isn't
CO2
The one thing
Human-created
Global warm
Common gases
If we can put a
Tap on that
Wouldn't you agree
Continue
Stuff in the atmosphere
And it continues
Get higher and higher and higher levels
Wouldn't make
Studies show
It's going to make deserts become green again
Plants are going to absorb the carbon
Look them up
Find out
I'm not argue
But you are
What's the tavern
Nothing to say
You should probably
Not to say
Look up
Something.
Do you have
Did you read that may
I actually know what
What would the plant study showare in greenhouses
They grow plants alive
Carbon dioxide
What a relief
If we burn tons of CO2 and put it in the atmosphere will just end up with deserts ahead foliage are plants
Sounds like win-win
I admire Jose attempt to get Alex to take responsibility for his claims but if this doesn't end with Joe telling Alex that he's full of s***
And then denouncing him in front of his audience
Then all these moments were Alex's clearly full of s*** don't
Mater like they don't mean anything unless they do apologize for having him on
You recognize that you had been
Trick by his Showmanship and he's a fun guy I bet he is I better yet I bet he is
Especially if he wants you to think that he's fun especially if you're at a Halloween party and he's dressed like a Nazi allegedly
True
I just like
If it if it is doesn't
It happened he's a really talented guy and he's really nice and we had a
Pretend friendship for 20 years or whatever but like
He just came on my program and he
Completely lied to you by audience
Yeah by presumably care about
He said that if you would burn CO2 deserts will have trees grow again them in
Pig
You know it is it is one of those things that makes you really think being a
Con man is so easy
Just because people will do everything possible to avoid admitting that they got Conte
Caught being a con man
Is probably good if you have
Good marks
Like if you like to go Rogue exactly like a guy with a hundred million dollars
Podcast in the world
Feeling like a guy with $5 month
Certainly not fair enough
So anyway this is because we're having so much excess CO2
Release of a sphere
Lavender Global greeting
Is this going to turn the everything wonderful
Global Greening happening
Countering us losing our Atmos
This point
The Earth has less atmosphere that did a million years
Or something we discovered all this oil
We are terraforming
The planet
Earlier healthier
States
Carbon
Was under the ground and putting it back
But isn't the problem that along the way we're also
The temperature of the planet and we are not
Aligned
With a higher 10
Urologic a week or no
T3
The club of Roundtable with a limits to growth
They had model Xanax
Actuaries I have copies of
Sinhala films free online
Bubble slime
Prediction virus released a lot
Things down everything
That was not what that movie was about
Yosemite
53 Leominster Girls Club of round plan they said we believe they'll be a global Ice Age
My2020
Because the last ice age ended about
Couple thousand years ago in
We're set for that
We're going to tell the public
Actually carbon-dioxide me a
Solar radiation off the Earth
Because we see volcanoes
Pause this.
Affected freezing
So we believe our scientist believe
The carbon dioxide to make
Earth freeze
My2020
I'm sure we've got it have a global regime to take control of all the factories all the energy
And put a tax
Stands for Global government
The name of stopping the Ice Age
Then by B 1987a
Heat up instead
Play flip the
Anybody you know
Nope
Anybody you
Alex is lying
Nobody's feel bad game and it's amazing for him to be such a dick as to call his own bulshit documentary Seminole
What a what an a****** roadman it was about a rose
Limits to growth came out 1972 not in 1963
The club of Rome didn't even exist
Until 1968
You can easily find a PDF of this document called limits
It's the growth and if you do go ahead and look through it there's no mention of an ice age or the year 2024
In the text the authors are very clear that they can
Simply demonstrations that the amount of CO2 in the atmosphere is rising
But it's unclear how much of that will be able to be sustained by the planet
Repeat 281
It's not known how much CO2 or thermal pollution
Can be released without causing irreversible damage in the earth's climate
How much radioactivity lead Mercury or pesticide can be absorbed by plants fish
We're human beings before the vital processes
Are severely interrupt
Did cut 250 years later
We know exactly how much it was a while back
Part of the despatches on board to part of the reason why you should act even though we aren't certain what the limits are its
At least spelled out in the text
Quote
This ignorance about the limits of Earth's ability to absorb pollutants should be reason enough for caution
In the release of polluting
The danger of reaching those limits is especially great
Because there is typically a long delay between the release of a pollutant into the environment
And the appearance of its negative effect
John the
Had spicy overly cautious
In a certain sense though Alex did say something
Incorrectly and he started it with
What we're doing is returning the Earth back to a healthier time
And
When he said a million years that makes sense to me because that was before we were here
Alex's 900,000
We will when we're gone
Be creating a much better healthier
Well I mean after we've killed if you're taking some kind of a weird geologic
Perspective and yes
And it's not what I recovered After The Dinosaurs right will be
It maybe we will
In the introduction to this text limits to growth on page 23 they lay out there
Conclusions the first of which is quote
If the present growth Trends in the world population industrialization food production and resource depletion
Continue unchanged
The limits to growth on this planet will be reached sometime within the next 100 years
That's the conclusion that they made based on their assumptions and estimation
At the time
In 1972
They've gone back and Revisited this multiple times
And some
Updating and some reflection online about a little bit of that whatever
Bye-bye
30 years
Alex's asserting that in this text they say that they are aware that an ice age is coming so they're going to pretend the carbon dioxide is
Bad and causing the Ice Age which I guess
Who's going to
Lead to them being able to take control of the population
Sick of all these is my plan is this playing the fio planaria hate to surprised none of that is in this book
What's a real shock
I have no idea of Alex's ever read limits to growth RVs just banking on the fact that the audience won't have but this s*** is Almeda
How long is
Longer than four pages for
This is not read it. Certainly.
What are the things that's interesting about this though is that this is a tax for 1972 and
You know
I think that you can go back and you can look at some of the stuff
Absolutely say like
Well they didn't know what we know now
And Joe tries to bring this up
It is
Don't you
Science facts
Didn't have it
So they're there model
And what they predict
C3
Faulty compare the in
They haven't
She said 2.5 million
Kobe dead
But yeah
But worldwide
A worldwide tuberculosis
Millionaire lifestyle
Kobe killed
Fart
Is that true
Come on
Boss
You see here how Alex tries to Pivot away from uncertain territory into more familiar and comfortable Water by taking
Joe's good point that old science didn't know what new science has discovered
Hitting his dog complaints about toci and covid
I'll explain goes out to make a sensational absurd claim back over it which will now distract conversation
And he will have escaped without having
Been held the claims that he made about the club of Rome
To grow or how excessive CO2 emissions are saving the world
Also again
TBH did not kill 1.4 million people in the United
Midstates in 29
That is a comical number that Alex's used before
And he just uses to minimize covid
Joe has no idea what the real number is which is what Alex
Is Batman when he just throws that out
Alex is being allowed to scatter bulshit all over
The place and these dudes are completely helpless to try to keep up
Or transform it into something that's responsible
2% to an audience who trust you it's not it's not good
Yeah you would think it about
And this is because I'm not very generous today
You think about 45
They would just start making fart
But
How how many hours are we into it now
I think is really really difficult is
Did like
If Ari shaffir or like Tom Segura had came on Joe Rogan show they had some weird ideas about
That's not good
But it's going to be a comedian expressing a stand for
Alex pretends to know like a ton of stuff so impressionable listeners will treat the things he says differently
Name something a comedian might say while they're sitting around talking s***
The potential for harm is significantly increased
And this is a show where the host seems
Unable or unwilling to do the work that's needed
Protect this audience from the brand of misinformation Alex cell
And the Harlot
I can come from it
He's treating it like it's just you know the same kind of steaks
Is Ari or Shrine in there and it's not
I mean he's unwilling to
Hold himself accountable and protect himself from Alex's
Narrative so
The hours of course he can
Johnny was rationalizing it's not it's not the best
Today we get our first
Point where I want to talk a little bit about
Tim Dillon
Back Alex
They're certainly
Contributing to man-made
Russo
What are you going to do
What are we going to do
Gradpoint
Perhaps the most disappointing sentence I've ever heard
What kind of Southpark a simpleton wearing apathy and defeatism is virtue bulshit is that
I tried to be kind to Tim Dillon in the past because like I said I meant I think we have some mutual friends and I don't care too much about that
Comedians who say things I disagree with even if they're Gaston Infowars
Because Tim has been
It's not really that interesting for me to get mad about something someone might have been joking about
It's often hard to tell the difference between a racist and an edgy comedian who swings and misses so typically
I tried to stay out of the criticizing comedians game
We all know how sad Alex sounds when he yells about Bill Maher or Michelle wolf
That is a joke
The Tim is saying though and it's
I just make me sad
Is the idea supposed to be that no one has any ideas about what can be done to limit the temperature
I mean
To be aware that people have some suggestions
A year ago he posted a comedy video on YouTube making fun of Greta thunberg
A person whose only famous because he's trying to propose solution
Yeah but what are we going to do
I don't care and I'm sure Tim's a good guy in a talented stand-up but I don't buy it
I don't buy this kind of edge
Am I supposed to believe that Tim thinks that even if all the scientist
Start making up climate change that there's nothing we should be doing
It really just feels like an attempt
Like
It too hard of an attempt to be right-wing edgy
I just don't buy it I just Rings Hollow to me
Oh yeah
We are contributing to climate change
What are you going to do about it
You know it bums me out
Is
No one
Funny
Yeah that's really bugging me out
Because the only reason you have Tim Dillon on there
As as a third party
Is 2
Kumon come with
The joke I think he likes Alex two more come with the Eddie Bravo swing
That's what you got to have you got to have that f****** element that you got to have me screaming. I don't disagree
No I just like he's just another differential a******
Like a slightly less
Pretending to know things out
Oh yeah it is
I think it's a
Mistake that will probably linger you should never break the format
And that is what if Alex is there so is Bravo yep
Like you you found a winning combination that allows you to pretend
We got Eddie Bravo here what are you going to take
You can't take any of this seriously funny Bravo stalking the kind of allowed you to dodge any kind of
And he added an element to
Some kind of unpredictability
For this I just don't I don't think it's a good idea to have anybody Plus
Alex plus Joe Rogan
Unless it's
Unless it's ready
Unless it's somebody who can temper the b******* that's
Flying low
It's a back-and-forth I mean conceivably
Kobe fun for me to be the third person put again I would never do that and I
No interest in it but
Does understand the things that Alex
Lying about what he's very helpful and it would create
I mean
Alex Wood
Believe that
You can't just have Tim Dillon
As an as as a third participant
It really the show suffers for it
And quite frankly I think
I don't think that anyone's going to enjoy this nearly as much as the other two
It's not it's not as good it's not as interesting
And it's not funny and a large portion of it is Alex talking about how he wants Rogan to drink with him
But it's sober October
So Rogan
Can't but Rogan says that he will drink on Election night cuz he's doing a livestream
It turns out
The announced on this
Episode
That Rogan and Kyle kulinski are doing a team up stream of the election
And Alex insinuates
Himself as a cast on that
And over and over again
Alex cubis
Being like I've about bully my way under your eye wear a drink together on the election night
Just looking at it on it
A personal level human level
Meowth it really it was desperate it was needy
It just it it's Unbecoming for a character who's supposed to be at strong
An alpha is alligator
For him to be so
Type of s*** that a baby comic does to somebody who's like 6 years in there like
Hey man your you run that really good show and we're good friends and you like and it's like
If you're a baby comic
Everybody tries it 16
That happens but if you're like a 10 years in guy doing this s*** or a in Alec 1826
You're not doing
Not so good we know though
Like I said
He comes off better than Alex
Just because I mean how could you fly
But
I don't know I don't I don't think he says all that much that's all that interesting he just sounds like a guy who likes out
Yeah we watch too much Infowars isn't really all that critical
But thanks adopting contrarian positions make
Up for light iron
Is like this is a purse
Personality
He's a guy who's wearing a free guylaine stroke
Metaphorical and literal
So in this next clip
You're really see like they're the two different
Kind of realities that are happening simultaneously in this episode
I'm sucking on a cigar
Like it's a jelly donut I'm hoping I get the weed on the inside outside
Piece of paper
What does it say
4 to the end of humanity
See
Okay but it's a person who wrote the
It's Adam Kirsch he's probably got a pistol in his mouth right now
Do people not realize that saying that Alex has documents is a joke
Like Tim is clearly making a joke when he says that they have documents
It is a bit at this point and the point of it is that Alex
Doesn't have any documents and he's making all this s*** up
The article titled looking forward to the end of humanity isn't about what Alex planes it is
It's just an opinion piece attacks
Actually it's pretty skeptical about the possibilities that many theorists believe could come with a transhumanist future
The headline Works rally
But because he lacks any depth any hopes
You just blow people's minds
Dixie doesn't go any
Further than that
The actual article is not about being eager for the end of humanity though it might be able to make it you might be able to make it
Sounds like
Alex says every responsibility to know what this article is about cuz he's brought it up a thousand times
In the past
He's got it because
Flat broke and doesn't have the time to read this entire op-ed
He doesn't have the ability to
To come in to be like that's not what that's about
This is actually really skeptical about
The widening gap between classes that could happen
With the implementation of
Of technological a supplementation
Flicka is a article uses as an example
How you could buy yourself out of War if you got drafted in the early days of our country
Skeptical
It's not pro the end of humanity
Even just the whole presentation of it like
Why are you acting like
It's not a joke
That Alex has document
You're making
That joke
You're laughing at that joke because it's funny because he does.
I think I think strategy
Should have tried
Right
Sure your live streaming
Or whatever Jamie's covid-19
So here's what you do
All right after the show you just go in and edit in all the things that you wish Joe it said you haven't
Voiceover later
Edit it all in and then it looks like Joe is a f******
Dynamite interviewer
And Alex just saying random ass things in response to drop
Alex you've no idea what you're talking about.
Talk to you
And Alex has a sex club they argue a little bit about driverless cars
And I'm just
But that display
Lot of iroh
Driverless cars don't know a wreck up ahead or what to do they have more Acts
Steve Wozniak
Earlier the founder of founder of Apple
The best AI
Is it a million
Close
How good
Stop stop stop stop
When they first
Develop cars they said why
Going to take a shower
Power needs
Cars now
Is not even understand the people running the AR predatory anti-human they want to get rid of us
He's working
Who said Beware those
The speak of a I got
People are worried
Did you want is more
Don't give me one of the
Keep that s*** away from me
Trying to give everyone Boos
Worried about the point where things start of like
I mean I would say is it for me intellectually the point where everything broke apart beginning
The part workout really dicey was the CO2
We're in trouble
Around here is kind of where you're in a place where it's like
He's he's starting
Yeah and I would say that driverless cars argument is trying to explain to a
Alex what these conversations to people who have concerns about air and the reality that future a I won't be
You know what we have now and
Alex just isn't there for that conversation
Nope he has
Documents
And sources that he needs to bring up about how evil these folks are
Look up calculator for great knowing as I do math now
Lookout phone to write no one knows her numbers anymore
All the statistics show
The scientific knowledge
And that's why they wrote the big article
The co-owner
Some micros
You 2000
Bill Joy Road
The top billionaires
And I made the decision
Surround play video games
Okay pull up why the future doesn't need us
But why why you think
Can we reverse intitle question Hilbert called useless Peters
I don't think damn you're doing great
Improve what a person
But I think we're doing it falls off
You going to go down another rabbit hole
Halibut
This is the distraction tactics that Alex
Excuses because he can't he can't
Stay on it
To keep moving or else he'll get round out like he's a shark of Lies
Leslie Prado truth on the shock of Lies this is the type of show
4 years ago before we have done
Before we get started
I could have been the third wheel on this
Instead of Tim Dillon maybe I would it would have been like me screaming and s*** but I wouldn't have the white
Hot Furious that I have now
Is a decent chance at 5 years ago if I'd seen this
Like knowing what I
I knew about Alex 5 years ago
But I could have got gotten some entertainment value out of it a little
Totally but I will also say that probably would have been a little bit
Depressed he does not come off
Well
Especially towards the end
And it's not it's not one of those like like
Ways to learn
Kind of
Sad
Really sad
Like deeply sad
I just don't even I don't I don't want to act like I'm teasing this or anything it's just
Bummer it it ends
Like a boss
Anyway that's all I want
Alex's life
I believe
That I've made the
Point a number of
Alex Jones
Pair for any
Fire
You wakes up at 6 every morning read
Hours of Articles until
I should say about that last time
Article for Bill Joy did not say anything
Any of the houses making it up completely
Admiral
There's a small passage inside that article where Bill Joyce quotient
The Unabomber and that's what Alex is talking about
I said Alex doesn't prepare and I need to
Correct the record
Call me David Brock's cuz I'm correct for the wreck
We did not
Crocodile
Talk about a lot of things
This what I wrote last night
For you I want
To take it down and not a silicon called
No I wrote
Define the enemy
But I'm not
Really a liberal or conservative
F*** off please listen to me and hear me out
Let's stop right
Let's stop right there that stop right there
Please announce up front
I am not liberal or conservative
Please listen to me I'm Rodeo Jesus this is when I turn to my like
It stopped recording
Stop recording
You don't get to
Daroga does a lot of work trying to help Alex
Push that idea that he's not left or right
You get right
Called a neoconservatives you get called all right
You get called a
A far-right person
When I first met you
You were protesting
George W
You bush
And you were saying
That what he was doing
And what he was trying to usher in
But what was it was essentially going to be the downfall West
Yes I remember that
So when people
Jose
Alex Jones
Far-right Dynamite
Complicated
He's really again
Corruption
More than he's against
The party kerbals hated corruption
The right
Was less
WhatsApp to send
Add more apps
Exactly
Election Audubon
What's good in the Bohemian
What
Alright love you
You know what
George W bush doesn't care about black people and now he supports Trump
B.j.
Dad threw and I think it's important to always recognize
What you're doing
Can be altered by why you're doing
So if you are protesting books
Because you're further right than bush
Protesting Obama it is unsurprising
If you are extreme right-wing of course
Someone like George W bush isn't going to be good for your business
Or at least complaining about him will be good for your business
I think needs to do a little bit of exploration about that
Consider why does Alex
Not like or like
The people that you does
You'll find a greater consistency there then oh he just hates corruption
Do you know what
Crazy though
What I think is the wildest part of
Is
That all of this stuff he's saying on here
You could have planned
You could have seen him saying this s***
If you would listen to his show for the past week and a
To the point where
You could literally have
Listen to a show and been like
I'm just going to grab a couple
Eclipse it random
And whenever I whenever Alex says something you just be like
Oh that's cool I get really kind of clip from your show if you sing deduct f****** opposite you moron
What kind of s*** is better for you if you want it
Exactly the same like talking about the volcanoes and that's because I think
He recorded this
Before
Almost one hundred percent guarantee it's so he might have done these on the same day that he did the volcano
Getting the same reps
Quit because that guy did more things
Cool
First I've heard about this
Investigate
Patricia
Which was the CIA was caught
Trafficking that you know the fighters are called
Caught trafficking children
And the CIA
Squasht
The Florida
Oci facility
With a snuff
Alex machine so he told me about all this
Crazy
You told us about it
And we actually
One of those stories
And I was correct
What
So we went we went into the finder situation and past episode
Children that were found with two guys
Anna in a van in Florida
And spice at the same either Alex or Kim could prove any of this stuff that they're talking about
First things first Defenders investigation did not begin until 1987 by which point Gunderson was retired from the FBI
It was ankle deep in the McMartin
Tunnel hysteria Scandal as Tim Dillon put in
On Ted Gunderson website you can find the 79-page report.
We filed on the finders case which is a chaotic mess
Another really proves that
The most interesting part of the report is part about murder hornets and know it's a report that was filed
Supposedly by Ramon Martinez who was a US Customs agent
For a rate of a warehouse in d.c.
Set an informant
It claimed was connected with a satanic cult called the
The Finders
Martinez right have seen proof of child exploitation and it almost
Astonishing level of criminals
Desiccation
What makes this report interesting is that it doesn't
Appear to be fake
Sent its referenced in the FBI Finders
Files that were released recently
However if you can sell the files the FBI released
There is reference to follow up
On the claims from Martinez's report that's not good for Martin how there was no evidence
Anything like what he describes that anyone else
Confirm
In fact the FBI v files include a report of a 1994 interview with the Washington
Metro field office agent who was present at the rated question
And it doesn't corroborate anything
Name redacted advised that during his review of both material from the computers and documents
Revealed nothing relating to any criminal activity
Further there's be logging of a 1993 interview with a representative of the Arlington Virginia National Center
Exploited
10 missing children
Who was present for the raid haven't formally been a detective with the Metro Police
Quote
He did not see any evidence of criminal activity
Because of the anomaly of this report for Martinez in other unsubstantiated gossip lingering conspiracy that the CIA
Hey was running the Finders
But again this is never been demonstrated or proven at all
Weirdly the FBI V includes a bunch of references to investigations into whether or not there was a connection between
The fighters at the CIA
It feels like if the CIA were running this group
The clandestine reasons they probably wouldn't cooperate with an FBI investigation
Into the cover-up They carried out surrounding it but maybe I'm a
Sheeple
I don't know
It's it's
It sucks the truth dies in obscurity and is lost but
Bulshit just lives forever
Because it's more interesting and usually people respond to shiny things
Reagan also ignored a message
2 pandemic and killed thousands upon thousands of
Here's a list of the claims that are being made by Tim and Alex that they absolutely could not prove Beyond saying something like that
1 the finders work
Trafficking killed
They can't prove that
To the CIA squash the Florida investigations group
Three Ted Gunderson got the DC Warehouse rated
Four said raid found a CIA facility
Please prove
Five the rating cover uncovered snuff film
Shepherd
There are at least five major claims these dudes are throwing out
Miss clip that they would never be able to
Come close to proving
And at the end cure Joe signing off on this s***
This is irresponsible coverage and honestly I hope to she is proud of what they're sponsoring
Yazoo doing great
Water up Alex Jones's ass
So I got really bored for a stretch here and maybe that's just because like
Is it exhausting to listen
I'm too fast pace Alex's all over the place
Trying to reel him in
It's it's
It's a mess because they're talking about Bohemian Grove and skull in Bones
And I just kind of was like
Pass
Alex
We can actually
Descendants
Sue Skull and Bones over geronimo's bone
George H bush
Grandfather Rob Geronimo
Grave member
Members of
Secret society
Leslie steal valuable thing
And put them in
Entomb
Great-grandson says Geronimo should be
Buried
Accordance with tradition
Federal law
Protects Native American
Kids rights to their
Your family member
That brought up that bush stole geronimo's skull
And then they pulled up this news article that says that geronimo's great-grandson
Is pursuing
This clip pretty neatly shows are you won't learn anything
Sing from the show
If you listen to this you'll think the Tim just claimed the bush stole Geronimo skull in that road
Pull up an article
Confirms it
In reality both proven nothing
This case with geronimo's great-grandson file to some 2009
And in August 2010 judge Richard Roberts
Drop the case we just missed it
The reason is actually kind of interesting
But you never know if you just listen to these dudes
The issue was the geronimos officially buried in a grave at Fort Sill which is on us
Property
In order to dig up bodies on federal property you need to get the permission of the government
And the plan of this suit was to sue the US government President Obama and the secretaries of
Defense of the army
To gain permission to dig up geronimo and bury him quote
Near his birthplace at the head of the Gila River in New Mexico
However in order for a lawsuit be filed
Against the US government first a judge has to decide whether or not the case justify suspending the government sovereign immunity
Judge Roberts found that this case did.
Have established
The caused wave this immunity
The case was dismissed
The plan was to transport the remains to The Gila River and in the process
Determine if as the legend has it
Geronimo's skull
Had been stolen
The great-grandsons lawyer said later that quote
He will eventually reopened his cases against
Galen Skull and Bones if need be but not until after the Fort Sill remains are exhume
They don't know what they have caused the Gaylord skull and bones
Until the bodies been exhumed and then they can see if there's a skull there
At that point I guess they have to build a case that it was more than just a ribbon Legend
Hearsay that would hold up in court
Remembering go ahead and
Successfully sued
I guess
Personally I think I should let the family dig up the remains
Because colonial-style your grandfather's bones doesn't mean that you have rights
To sue the government I'm not saying that that's a right decision
Personally but I'm just saying that is what they decide
The bottom line is that there's much more to this story and it's interesting to see how the world war
This is not a soup primarily targeting skull and bones or Yale or bush
It's about getting geronimo's remains from Fort Sill
And if the spell is gone then Crossing that bridge at that point
If you just listen to people like Alex or Timber Joe
You'll get a more fun kind of wacky version of the story that's really exciting but ultimately
They have no idea if anything they're saying is true or real
You get the impression that you're learning something but you're actually just listening to f***** up people ramble about something they read in a Blog
Horse Kim
Skimmed a better way
Man
So f***** up
It's not just keeping it fun keeping his bone
Why can't we just get
Like what the f*** are you talking about
You don't care you don't have to respond to people
Yeah I spent a while trying to
To figure out why the government didn't just say
Cool really get to the bottom of it and I was running
Low on time is like I am very curious about that but I can't figure this out
You make an interesting point and you could speculate
Late about that
Couldn't prove it
So if you use that as evidence that they're protecting
George W George h.w. Bush or Prescott
You're just as faulty
What's weird at buddy reminds me so much of like so many times if you go to a museum you see something like
This was
Taken by this Explorer in your life
No
He stole that
He stole it
Why are we keeping
B here
Indiana Jones Museum so it's okay that we stole it and now we get to keep it and show it to all the
The people and you don't get any
Beforeitsnews
Not an ideal way to operate it
A little bit about Epstein and Bill Clinton being all guilty
And
Tim
Describe it asks like a do you actually think the Trump
Cleaning all this Shore
Do you think Trump's cleaning everything
In Essex I mean
I'll give you
Here we go. My only superpower is that I really try to give you accurate take this mean I'm always right
Rabbit roll
Trump doesn't like Lobby
Is he fired a mollusk
Make the best decision
For everybody in the pragmatic
Pre-market
Don't have one side
Trade the old butt
His Blindside was by him not letting lobbies
Everyone around him
What do you what does that have to do with Trump and Epstein
Anyway I hope I hope that's not
I don't want to talk about him and UPS
Alex responded to Tim quested they're laughing at
They're they're laughing at
Performance he's not going to tell us anything that's why they're laughing if you want the skinny
Neon Trump They're laughing because like
Right before he doesn't tell again
I got a right
Anyway
This is the first point where I really got the
Besides
The Joe is trying to explain
2 hours
But Alex is annoying
But you said I'm hard to
Did Louisville because your taco
When their talk and you don't let him get
Don't let people
To get a full thawed out
Dura Nintendo
When he's
What I'm saying is he's talking
You jump in
And the problem is I know you have something
Things to say but
Then you f*** with
With the thing that's coming out the other person
They don't they
Do not look
Correctly
Because the way they're looking at it
I think they're doing a good
Good thing they're going to Usher
Utopian
World of
People always saying
They agree with
The problem with that is
You don't find out who
Who's right must get everybody talk
You can have an Echo chain
It's dangerous
Man it is hard to listen to this at Point
It's like this one
Like it pretty clear that Joe is fairly annoyed probably because he's never had to deal with Showtime Alex Wild
He himself had to be sober
Which must be the worst
I appreciate where Joe's going with this thought trying to find a motive for people wanting folks like Alex off social media that isn't there
They're demons and they want tyranny
But I also think the Jose wrong
I don't think that people want folks
Like Alex off social media sites because they want everyone to say the right same
I think they want him off because he can't control himself and he represents a danger to people so deciding that his behavior is not welcome on
Platform
Is actually an active customer service for your other users
I've never heard of anyone getting kicked off Twitter Forest
Suggesting a conservative tax plan or Express
Unconventional views in terms of foreign policy
In the case of the people that they try to rally around
They weren't punished for ideas
Pittsburgh Behavior
It's not welcome in various Blackfoot
Social media kicking people like that out is not saying that they want everyone to say all the same right things
It's saying that there are certain rules that people have to follow if they want to be treated like an adult
And if you refuse
To follow them
You can't be kicked out
In this sense Joe's argument is actually a straw man
But he's coming from a more open-minded less malicious place
Certain kind of appreciate that
I would just
Again respond to it disorder Thing by introducing a conversation about what sorts of behavior he would be okay with people getting
Kick-off a platform for
And then see where the conversation goes
From there
Is it people going like
Oh you're going to kick these raccoons out just cuz they have rabies
That's what you're going to do we're censoring raccoons for having a disease now
Now you just you guys are evil people
Wander around free biking people left and right
You're terrible sense
Yeah
You guys are think you're so great now I can't stab somebody with the samurai sword it's not a knife it's a sword
Haha
Different
So it is next cool if we get
Another
F****** Gundersen moments cheese
And it I didn't take the bait fully on this one because I just I was too tired I'd already done to Gundersen
But I do think of something is brought up
Here that I think is worthwhile to discuss
This is in relation to the Franklin
Scandal was
Involved
With that whole affair
Like blowing a whistle
And that one of his associates
Pickswise
William Colby
The former
Head of the CIA who died
And
This is
So illustrative
Of conspiracy thinking I think it's really important to look at things like this
William Colby what do in Colby and William Colby baseball
Blizzard
You're going to force
You're going up against forces that are way too powerful
You don't even know what you're you're you're knocking on here
To f*** it you know what
We should stop doing
Let's if we're going to fight this
And then a little while later William Colby
Who's in great health
Katja has accident in his canoe was found dead
In a river right by his house with his dinner still on the table so it's like nobody
Nobody gets up in the middle of the day
So this is been a,
Nobody
If you go against
These people
You find your dad
He was 70
Crown though
What do you want
Okay
William Colby Direct
Intelligence chose
Clothes from the name
Darkest
The Spy Service he loved
Drowned
27th and tributary thank God thanks guys
So honestly at this point I didn't have the patience to discuss another giant satanic cabal ring
Can claim that these dudes can't prove so I'm going to punt on that will do the
We'll talk about Franklin stuff later she wear I just pulled this clip because it demonstrates how Joe is trying to bring the slightest bit of rash
Conversation
But it just doesn't matter
These dudes have decided that this guy who dared to stand up against the man was killed because he did it
Problem here is it
Kind of Alex's whole explanation for why no one is killed him yet is that he's too high-profile but the person they're claiming they'd
Did kill with the farmer at
The CIA high-profile
Is there evidence that William Colby was murdered but
You see the p
Piece of evidence that Tim keeps pointing to dinner with still on the
Exactly do not go out
Canoeing while your dinner is still on the table I think is very
Never had a mid-meal knut
Sprite and if you had you would know
Once you do it
You never go back this is a misrepresentation of something from the original news article about the search
For Colby publishing the Associated Press on April 30th 1996
Investigators found dinner dishes on a table in clam shells in the kitchen sink
This would imply they possibly they'd already eaten or maybe
And not apply anything specific at all but the version that Tim is repeating is that dinner was on the table
Would be kind of weird
Why would a guy go canoeing in between serving and eating his dinner
That's the kind of question that gets
Conspiracy theorist
Aroused
But in this case it's actually in an accurate client based on initial reports which
She's really often the case
With these guys
Also Kobe's wife
Quote had spoken to her husband at about 7
P.m. Saturday
And you get said that
Even though he felt tired he was going canoeing
Anyway also from that article quote
Neighbor said the water was rough Saturday and not good for canoeing
According to those who knew him he was a creature of habit and that dude love canoeing
So is the mid-seventies old man on choppy Waters that are bad for canoeing any must have been murdered
About the clan
I've been murdered the only explanation I could say
You can easily find the medical examiner's report of his his death which determined that it was an accident
He was a little boozed-up with a .08 blood reading but the real important finding was that he had calcified
After Russell sclerosis
In his coronary arteries
Cancel possible heart trouble
According to the court the examiner's opinion quote
He had severe calcified
Asbury salerosa switch would predispose him to a stroke or heart attack
Decomposition however would dissolve
Clots on the fatty material and atheroma
You see it would
Ended up taking nine days for them to find
His body so in that time that he was in the water those signs of a stroke or heart attack would be gone
The underlying signs of him being a great
For those things
Would still be there
The medical examiner also reports quote the contents of his stomach are
Consistent with his last
Reported meal
And indicate his death was shortly after his dinner
I guess that would have to do with those clam shells that were in the sink that would make sense
But of course
Alex and Tim no better the man clearly killed why else would he go for dinner was Jerry Zelda terrible
So I made
You like that's really indicative
Tim has to hang his hat onto makes this
Do clearly a conspiracy has dinner was on the table he brings it up multiple times within a minute
Of trying to defend this claim
And it's not true and based on this misrepresentation of
Of early news reports
I would say that
The lesson here is
Yeah sometimes
They do conspiracy theorist will say something that's like yeah that is weird
Look into it
What does it mean misrepresent shouldn't say is yeah that is
Weird we should say
Yeah
That would be weird
I'm going to go look at and do it
Ml come back
Tell you that it is weird
But also not true
I feel like this is getting a little bit on
Comfortable
Tell you were great on Friends
I wasn't offering
Who do you think's right you think
Don't know you were friends characters
Jujubee Jeffrey Matt LeBlanc
Right leave me Jennifer
I don't
Hilarious
Who is Matt leblanc's a joke
Identify
I'm dumb
Jennifer Aniston Horrible Bosses
Good stuff
This is really uncomfortable
That is your boss at
6 after work
Bunch of people after work function your boss is like look at how funny I can be when I'm not in the office I'm Cutting Loose
And you're like
You are a deeply uncomfortable and sad person
So Alex gets to talking about how the Democrats have admitted
They're going
To crash the economy to get
The office sounds right to me
Ant-Man this is where I was like
Alright this is close to a basketball game
Because Joe is like
JoJo Nails this one has a dunk
They want to kill the US economy China has been open for 6 months
They admitted
It's leaked out
They're doing this to kill the US economy member week
Alice come out Democratic Party
Sports
Depression
Trump look bad
Who said this
Belmar
Yeah but Bill Maher is not a part of the day
Democratic Party
A comic
Around about that
Or Baptist
The New York trying to have an event
The police Shuffle
Orbea limits round burst
Again pivoting
I can't quite a handle the push back on.
Bill Maher is not a source
Use that as a source
Soju pushes back more on this idea of using Bill Maher as a
An example and I
You totally right
I want to bring you back
Animal crackers
Use Bill Mars
Example
What's a credible exam
Play said that
Yeah but he's a comic and he's always
Temperature cupboards the news people now
That's what Colbert and all them Post newspaper
Galaxy
You can't use him
An example
Of someone really politician
Who is calling for the economy to crash
Democrat get the f*** out
Tell Trump
China One China
Bioweapon
Give you an hour long
Before we do I love
I'd rather get drunk and have a good time
We know yeah
Yeah
I mean this is business
Really
I struggle
Watch this
And imagine how any kind of
Like
Respect
Or pretense
Can be maintained
By Joe and Tim
Yeah like how can they not if they entered this conversation with
Respecter
Admiration for what Alex does
How can it not be disappearing right in front of their eyes
Has nothing to do with him being drunk either it has everything to do with this means being like
You can't answer basic questions
And when you are asked
To give specifics about things like
The Democrats want to crash the economy to get rid of trump
You have a f****** comedian
Yep that's what you have
Speaking for the entire Democratic Party
I mean honestly personally
I really enjoy that because it's something I talked about
Reverse-engineered
From Alex's rhetoric to see him be forced to admit that and explain to his face
Stupid
But it doesn't matter unless Joe says
I can't believe I believe this guy is a piece of s*** sorry
Please
Don't trust
This stuff comes out of his mouth
He's not my friend
He's using me
You will not be on my election special
At least like that
Yeah but I don't foresee that coming so
Obviously
Example you can't use that
SoJO pushes a little bit more and tries to get Alex
Forgive another citation
Said something that I want you to back up
You said that
The Democrats are trying
Denying the possibility
But this seems like
Like if that was the case it would be
Grand conspiracy
Please have some evidence
They're trying or they
Economy
Because they
They want
To maintain power
The wave
Whitmer
Climb out exactly all say
The economy
Is it going to be
A bad job
We're not going to open
Till he's gone
Come out with its limit Newsome has opened
Emily said that
You sure
But what do you
Said I'm never
Abacus
Because of his
Nautica
Wineries open
A lot of issues
Right results there's a lot of
You plead they close so many
Jojo
Globalism was about selling America
Thundercloud
Change the subject
Specifically
Smith said he's really trying to change the subject
Yeah because not like that's up to
He knows that
Upon closer examination
He's going to be shown to have misrepresented these quotes
So he tries everything in his power to spin the conversation off into something I was hoping people will forget
Adidas
Strollers and Uptown Nevada covid
When when you say
The Depths increase
That is going to happen
The question is
By what rate
And how many
Write a check to normal flu and
Pneumonia morbidity like today
This year
Can you add that
It's whatever they don't count fluids of death
Or pneumonia anymore they only like they all kind of cover cuz I get remaining
50 plus thousand dollars
When they call it a covid deaths
Plus
When I say that again
Lucettes accommodation
And I got job
29000 wheeler wrecks
Madison walkthrough like
Medicare payments
Be that as it may I'm going to now introduce a new Sega
Call cheers
Very standard name for a second
Jeers
Yeah Joe Rogan for allowing Alex
Text to do that they get money for covid patients
Bulshit
CG deserve some pushback
Cheers aha Joe Rogan
For I think that he didn't push on that because he's still trying to focus on this new some copies giving it a shot
Be able to find
Proof of that he's trying to stay in the pocket
Getting done getting hit with a couple of things like
Yeah yeah yeah glanced off him goddamnit he's literally glass
What did Gavin Newsom
Some say though
You when you said
That he says not going to get better until
Top trumps out of all
Well it's
Said that specific
Ugly and he
Blacktube
I want be friends with Trump has been a bad response when does
Lockdown going and
Until Trump does this wrong until we have a chain
I'm just going to continue on
And it's always about
The power grab
So it's two years
15 days
The hospitals empty
And then it's
Then it's sorrow six months and I was two years legate said
Like a week ago
10 years
And now they've got the
People fauci
No it never ends
You never Shake hand enter the human rules they say
Don't look at someone
And turn your head
Inside the shin
Citizens of the UK told do not look at other people in
Turn your head
It's cold
Programming man he's a pretty common talking
Like a lot of Democrats
To take yeah it's not going to get better.
Until Trump is out because
Does Trump has made a mess of it
So Tim is
But this is
Was basically his purpose purpose cuz I don't know if it's intentional
The role that he feels
Throughout most of this is trying to restate
Insane things Alex says we contextualize ridiculous s*** Alex's to make it seem slightly more reasonable
Also not what I want to say
Because saying that you know predicting
But things aren't going to get better as long as Trump is in charge
It's not the same thing as threatening to keep everything closed until you get into power in fact I would say they're very very different
They are
That Tim is trying to muddy that water
Whether it's an intentional act or not I think it just might be
Based on his predisposition
Never be overstated
These are three very stupid p
All sitting around a table
Talkingshit
Maybe they're at least don't know what they're talkin about
I don't know if they're stupid in all facets of life
Joe Rogan
The pretty smart guy when he applies himself and and
Seems to want to keep he's not a dumb dumb idiot
308 complete
No no no
Have a lot of
But I'm at generously call blind-spot
I don't think Alex is stupid BS craft
What you doing honey sweetie I'm not trying to say
These are people who are like
IQ deprive nonsense like that kind of thing I'm just saying that these are people who are willfully committed
To not learning the answers to the questions that they are at
It does appear that way only explanation for this
Projo In This Moment
Okay cuz he wants to know about this
F****** quotes okay
I wonder if there's an actual
Statement
Or he said
Please
Then we'll open back up
He said some other things. It will it's fine it's not the news
Whitmer for sure
Dover to that make it
Different making find it this is all the more confusing been doing trying to Google things
Start over
Also Alex
Skip a little bit combative about outing
Interested Joe is in finding out what he's talking about
We ever find a quote for Whitmer
Do you want me to find it
Can you
Gretchen Whitmer they almost kidnapped
By the way
I know I don't have I'm just
Lake Merwin Trump
Office quote
She was almost there was a kidnapping
Plot against
No it's
Which 50 caliber long until Trump gone
Lockdowns won't end till
I'll try that
Whitmer
Whatever I know
You guys are great
Everyone here everyone in that room working together like a well-oiled machinery
Talking about Whitmer and Tim is brought up that there was that kidnapping attempt
Plan
That is a false flag although Alex would agree that it is a good idea as well
Forget into that a little bit and then two makes a joke
And then one of my favorite f****** moments in podcasts like this happen
It was weird but I
As it turned out the two leaders were FBI informant
What what's even crazier is 50
80%.
Citizens Michigan agreed with a
Take me to edit that part when you say that
Calls for kidnapping
Correction Hillary Clinton is not a topo did you guys see that
Bret Weinstein
Unity 20
Account was also banned from Twitter
Just told me that third-party
Was calling for Unity between
People on the right and left
Get together and have conversation
Perhaps even have an alternative
That's outrageous
I love how obsessed these dudes are with how fun it will be when the snowflake Libs take something they say out of context they are
That's with it
I think they should be way more worried about someone taking them in context and actually care about what they say
Because the picture looks
Are you worse than a couple of B- jokes
I'm going to go with you
As for unity2020 I don't know exactly why I told her kick the account off the platform put if I were a betting man I would say this
Probably because it's almost certainly a bad faith campaign to f*** with the election
And September like two months before an election.
That's when the brat f****** Weinstein is going to get a campaign rolling to field a candidate for president
That's f****** horseshit third-party and I think well after all the nominations are taken care of
How long after everybody knows exactly who the candidates are
Good time for summer to come in and shake things up.
16 ticket is Tulsi gabbard and Dan Crenshaw
Right now. Actually
What do we have
Water people presidents we haven't had any before that would also be a milestone
As far as I can tell they have not agreed to run on this ticket oh no
According to a video Weinstein posted on September 1st
He hadn't even collected signatures to get on ballot
Basically with Weinstein was pitching was for all the third parties to
Coalesce around his
Ticket green partying Libertarians even if they wanted to they could team up to be
If you actually watch Weinstein's video it's legitimately just him saying that he's not even going to try to get Battle attacks
Access for unity2020 as a
The party
Because he knows that's laughable
Instead his strategy is to Big the green or libertarian parties who already have candidate
Gates to abandon their candidates
And instead allow Bret Weinstein to choose their ticket
Which would be Tulsi gabbard Dan Crenshaw
Now I'm going to go out on a limb here
And say that
That might be an ovary
I meant look I like a big swing that's a big swing if I were Twitter I would kick this off too but life
Because I was worried about it affecting the election but because it's a very thinly veiled crap. f*** out of here
Two desperate even four words
Personal contacts deep video of
Feinstein's plant has been up for 2 months
Anime on YouTube has gotten
Not good
She might've
Bread sounds like I'll steal the presidency from her
Have you bility to go on like
Tucker Carlson and Joe Rogan's podcast and promote his unity2020 concept
Eddie's f****** video got 20 1000 views
Not a lot of excitement surrounding
Taxi app
The quote for a little while
Okay
The Trump virus
Response is the worst in the globe
She said if you're tired of the of lockdowns
Or you're tired of wearing masks or you wish you were in church
What's this morning or
Watching college
Or your kids were getting
In person
Instructions
It's time for a change in this country
And that's why we've got to look Joe Biden
Pretty
You can make that
Yeah
It's right pretty my problem is the problem is
If you just
If you're tired of locked
Hallelujah
YouTube
Interpretation of it but if
You back it up to the Trump virus
Response
Is the worst in
The globe
She said
If you're tired of locked
So what you saying you were here
Minion not necessarily
Because what she told please
What she's saying is we got it
What she saying is a trump is done
Such a shity job
That's the reason why we're locked down
The headline
Is true though
I think when you got to consider these you got people flying in
From Europe in China
And all these other countries
Expression
Yeah you're going to have
The f****** really contagious
When the light turns on
Let me ask you this
You're never wrong
On scale 1 to 10
Warrington numerology this is when it gets good
Great
So you can see here the decision tree of Alex's responses to being confronted with something
He can't really dispute
He's misrepresented reality in reality is looking
I'm back at him with the only possibility seems to be that he made up the Whitmer quote
Or he didn't understand this one and repeated a misleading version for his own purposes
His first attempt
Wiggle free is to claim that they're splitting hairs
And it's probably usually work
For whatever reason
Go doesn't accept
This and says it's not
So Alec
Excel has to try other things
Game 2
Right and game Tuesday School
Yeah they create false versions of What Joe is saying he on defend himself
From the fake version Joe just ignores that
Keep moving forward
And then we get to transitioning to
Something completely unrelated and possibly two interesting or confusing to resist following up on
In this case
Numerology
I just wish these dudes like Tim and Joe could see in the moment how much of a one-trick pony Alex's
I just disabuse themselves with the idea that he's worth listening to all he did
All he did
Was
Realize you can't plate
Realized you couldn't play offense we tried to change the field
He's a child singing I'm going to take my ball and go home you don't like the game
Being played so you distract people with numerology
John episode 911 meaning to the episode numbers
It's obviously just like an attempt to
Got to go to another conversation
You didn't even say that you're full of s*** yeah
Yep you can't defend this other than to be like yes I guess I took that out of context
And that now you have the responsibility to have that in your awareness that you took this out of context you can't use this argument
Anymore he's done with it I doubt we'll ever hear any problem.
This time right
Yeah probably half so they get to talk
Can some more
And Alex brings up
Operation lockstep
And now here is where Joe
Does his other bit of good
What about
The UN and
The Davis Group all say
This is the post-industrial world
The great reset a copy before right here
And I say
A lease document
We are going
Reorganize Society covid is good to shutdown the car
We're going to end
Success
In prosperity
Granite rack everybody works
Control their lives all under the name of
They said all that they said we're going to end
Successful
Oh yeah in the lockstep
Rockefeller
Viral lesueur
Simulator
The crates total funeral bring up
Police state
Martial law
Absolutely we talked about this a ton I'll read this document
Alex is completely lying about it
But it's interesting
That like I got
So excited
When Joe push back on that
Like if you are
Are successfully able to push back on Alex and demonstrate what
He's doing here game is over
Fully and very
Explicitly exposes him
Yeah once you're like
Actually there were four scenarios actually this wasn't a planned this was just a technological
Misrepresented as I plan
And then you say
And you f****** know it
Absolutely
Yep or did you not read the
Yeah exactly have you been talking about this for months
As a dystopian terrifying Planet you not even read this
What is it could at one of the two either you didn't read it or you're lying to me so you choose and get the f*** out of my
Exactly yeah I mean if you had any
Dignity. Any
Feeling of responsibility for your audience you have an obligation to do something like that yep and I got really excited
Because Jamie is
Able to Google it's not hard
If not it's very easy to find
And so I Jimmy Google's this and here's where I would end up happening
I was already looking
I'll Arkansas
Snopes
Green
Let's focus on the grain if everyone who says
The grain of Truth the kernel of Truth is in the document does exist
It's on all the Treasure Trove of life
Let's focus on the grain of Truth
Very small let's see what the big thing first
All the lies around it
They find a doctor
Rockefeller Foundation
An annual report
Look up a police state
What's up
Exact words
Ctrl f
Just one paper that's it
So when you control
Africa
20 States
What else
Before it says that so
Now you know
No not yet
Exact World cable let's look up pandemic
Alex has to feel his world and walls closing in on him at this point because like
Oh they're not going to find the things that I've said are here it's just not there
They're not in there no problem with the things that I say
Search for the word paint
All right with no network to
Critical infection
Nation without open minds
Thousands
Morfol 6th Avenue
Enclose disease
Becomes a nun
Check Pandora
Time
The right expert
Is brought to bear on the probable
Too late
The disease has spread around the globe
In a world of global trade and travel with traded faster and travel
Farthest
Are the microbes never
Southeast
What do they what is this
In reference
Okay it says
The few miles
Couldn't hold on.
Please go back to that
Yeah just
It's just a
It's just a escenario
Did their paint
Here's the exact moment that Joe need someone like me around I would never accept that position even if it were off
The first problem is that Joe has a wrong.
This is the Rockefeller annual report from 2010
Which is the link to where is the one Alex lies about and turned into the fictitious operation lockstep
He's called scenarios for the future of technology and International
They're both
Rockefeller Foundation documents from 2010 so it's an easy mistake to make
But the idea that there is such a thing as our operation lockstep
Just did something Alex took
From a meme
I applaud you for trying to find the document and I further applaud him for being able to discern that the text that he was reading was a
The scenario that was being described as opposed to the text being a nefarious plan
But he doesn't have the full picture
If he knew what he was talking about and knew what the conversation was
You know this wasn't the right document
You would know that the correct document is
Breakdown for Imaginary scenarios
Have ways in which technology and political situation
Developing world
The four scenarios depicts world where things develop differently onto axe
The first
Political and economic alignment can either be strong
Or week
The other adaptive capacity can either be low or high
This scenario Alex's pretending is the Rockefellers plan for the world is just the way that the authors of this exercise chose to
To characterize
At Emagine
Strong political and economic alignment and low adaptive
Capacity
And I know that we talked about this a bunch but
I figure there may be a chance that people haven't heard that because they're brought in by a rug in a bag
And this is an important point
Alex's
Complete fraud that he's pulling they were using Game Theory to figure out
What might
The
Well economic and political alignment
Has to do with the ways in which
The state does
Control of
Adaptive capacity in terms of technological advancement
Has another app
Accessbet important
Answer those are the
The two axies
That the the team of experts
Who prepared this report. Where the most
Import
In terms of
Deciding
What sort of challenges should be prepared for their a ton of other exies that they could have done a report on
And it would have been different than
Totally but what they're doing I mean what they're essentially doing is applying quick game theory to this
So you got four boxes
Top left is 11 top right is 10 bottom left her Hero 1
Bottom right of 00
Yeah like that's
That's what they're trying to do and extrapolate from there
That's the whole idea and
Come up with real
Realistic
Depictions of what that world could look like zactly
Depiction
They have
One in the lockstep one
There is a virus that is involved in the
Background of
The the scenario described
Announces taking that to pretend that there is such a thing as operation lockstep
That is run this 2010 Rockefeller document
It's just a complete lie
Because Joe doesn't know what Alex is talking about he's tried to find the thing he needs to Judge Alex his claim
Doesn't know it's not the right thing
So they're never going to get to any truth
Alex is wasted and he doesn't know which report is which
To begin with so he's do help me out
That's kind of what makes this show pointless
Unless there was an egg
Expected steak that is Alex
Cannot defend his claims are assumed to be wrong and he's full of s***
He's going to win every time because what do you do here
What do you what do you do is like I know it's in there
Yeah where do you go from there all right let's read this whole document or
Worse still
You got the wrong one
I'm criticizing for it the next day is like see they weren't even reading the right
Number one
Document though it is the wrong
By continuing our drive to invest
Systems that
Coordinated effort
And share information
The Rockefeller Foundation
To meet the health challenges
Of an intercom
Did world isn't a Perfect Analogy terrorism because it's
People wanted proof
How many rights do
Do you give up in order to do
Neither Joe nor Alex realize this isn't the document that Alex's entire conspiracy
Because surprise neither of them have actually read it
Surprisingly
Has red
What's going on
At the end because I think it's great stuff
I do think there's a productive conversation that could be had about the push-and-pull of personal freedoms and the responsibilities we have
Have to each other because we live in a world
Are the population over 1
People who prioritize individual freedoms could make that could be compelling and the same is true of people who believe that more aboard
An element is a communities around us
That's great
That's a conversation I encourage people to have because outside of the people on the fringes of either side
There's a lot of people with valuable things to say within that specter
However
One of those people is not Alex Jones
He is a liar and an idiot
Yeah I wouldn't want to have that conversation with anyone in that room except for maybe Jamie
And that's only because I don't know anything about him. Covid computer
At least you could look up the things that you're saying could have a conversation with him maybe
But only because
He hasn't disqualified yourself
So we're Tim saying something like yes
Why you bring that to this room you
Go sit around with your friends and talk about other people
Bulls live Swagger
Alex Manteca f****** prove lockstep stuff you can do it
I've got
Eurasian lockstep.
Where to bring in this
Global authoritarian
And you have to show us
I'm sitting here in
Studio
Talk to you about
But I understand
We want to try but you know everybody else watching
We could have found it right then
But it might be
Interpretation
What they're saying
So close
The criticism of trump
She's blaming all this lockdown Whitmer
By the Supreme Court
Who have seized all three branches of government
Martial law
Here's what I can understand
How can Joe Rogan so clearly understand that in the case of the Whitmer quote and most likely in the case of the flocks
That thing they can't find that Alex has taken something
Completely out of context
An interpreted it poorly he can't grasp but that's all Alex does
How can you be that close I'm not see Alex's act I'm just so surprised right now that I've caught you in this lie because I
I've never tried
The catch you before
Drunk with you always been telling me the truth and now I'm finally pushing back and it seems like you're lying to me yeah
So strange it's so weird cuz here again
I'll just cornered with Joe pointing out essentially his entire career sleight-of-hand
Intuit allowed Alex starts ranting about something unrelated
They were talking about Alex's interpretation of the Whitmer quote
He went off about the Michigan Supreme Court
This is to try to move the conversation into territory he can handle
Because he's being confronted about his willful misrepresentation or lies
About news item
That's not something he can deal with
Also the Michigan Supreme Court Judge ruled that the executive orders that Whitmer signed and try to extend cannot be extended
The court decided that the governor and legislature would need to work together to come up with the appropriate measures to deal with covid-19
Is a little bit shy
She's grasping all the power troll of Michigan herself
Yeah
Little bit different
Against Epson in his role
And that is to Tryon
You like guys
Close though
Tell you that quote
I want to
When you say if you are sick
Lockdown
Not being able to go to church
Joe Biden
Agree that is not a huge jump
But the problem is
The way
Being sad
She was talking about how bad
Trump handled
The the
Rate of infection
Of course
And that's on that
Like Mary Lou Dobbs like
15 years ago okay
Here's my response to that
I think they're in a different setting
You can see the conversation that's trying to be had
Yeah I'm at is okay let's look at this quote
Antsy
The way that Alex's interpretation you can understand why he's saying that sure it's not necessarily a fair
Interpretation of what her intention was
You can see
The path of this
Could go down if it wasn't a bunch
Two Dum Dums who are f***** up yelling
And Alex didn't have a vested interest in derailing the conversation little bit rambling about Lou Dobbs
It's just sad if it's point
Exercise in futility
And I think if Joe is just trying to do like some
Some kind of a metal art project where you shows that like
Talking to these people is not worth it then he succeeded but
Short of that doesn't failure
Anyway we get back to lockstep
And guess what
Jamie found the right document
They talk about in lockstep
Bring in a
Global authoritarian
Systematic about riots they talk about war
If you can find that article
Something but I don't
Scenario
I got 12 this
They found the right document and now Alex has got to be like
What because
He kind of wiggled out of the Yamaha that was a trap
You got out and then now like the Duke boys out he got cocky because he
He probably assumed like well James I can find anything else to look for anything else he's already
There's only one Rockefeller actually brings back up
And so they they start trying to read it and
I wish they understood what they were reading
Quite frankly because it could
I have actual conversation
But they do not
Like 20-25 people seem to be growing weary of so much
Top-down control and letting l
Send
Authorities
Make choices
For them
Whatever net wherever National interest
Clashed with individual in
Interested Wisconsin
Push back
Becomes
Increasingly organized and coordinated
Has this affected
Could use and people have seen their status number
Opportunity slip away
Largely in developing countries
Incited civil unrest
By 2026
Protesters in Nigeria
Down the government
Fed up with the
Entrenched cronyism and Corruption
Even though
YouTube like the greater
Stability and predictability
Of this world
Began to grow
Uncomfortable
And constrained by so many tight rules
And by the
Strictness of Nash
No Boundaries
The feeling lingard
But sooner or later something will inevitably upset
Bendy order
That the world's governments
Could work so hard to us
Establish okay I never read that but that's the other stuff
Spouses
To be clear the Rockefeller report
Scenarios for the future of technology and International
Kendall development is not thousands
How many pages
54 step that scenario is actually on the eight pages
No idea what is Grand lockstep conspiracy is based on and exactly what it's based on
She's never read the thing of the document super-long Zaki possibly know all of it
This is shameful s*** and honestly if Joe or Jamie understood the document they were reading or Alex's
Narratives around it
All the tools they would need to fully expose out to charade for Millions to see on their show
This would be a
Bubble puncturing moment
Like if they knew what they were had in their hands
That is
That is a real bummer
So Alex knows kind of I mean he has to know that like
I'm in trouble
Okay talk about global police
Police state and worldwide riots
I mean we're not that far away there's the writing it almost like
It's stuff like that
I don't seen that part it's
Says stuff like
Yes I do know what I honestly get the vibe of like I can't
I obviously can't prove this. I don't know but
It has the feeling of like
I think Tim recognizes that Alex is caught too and he's trying to save it does feel like that
Just be like Tim is making every possible excuse like
Know what he's actually I understand where you're coming from and I think that's a really good point that you
Held his feet to the fire instead of him saying the thing that he said
He said this thing would you more likely agree with
Seeming to indicate that this source that Alex is facing a conspiracy on his nothing like what he has described it as it was actually
Completely different but isn't it closed
What if I
Moved
These goalposts over here to a completely different spot in a different universe
It's very very Christ
So Alex he's up on the screen of the screen where Jamie project
The computer screen
And he thinks
Videos found the right word no miss lockstep talking to Alex
That he actually has already said I haven't seen there's a bike but now he sees the right word
There it is
For turning capitalism
I don't have it in front of me but I was reading
The lockstep Rock
Documents
Play predicted worldwide
Release date
Authoritarianism Civil War I mean you have them in front of you
18th Street
Will Africa
Embrace of
Terry and tap
And then via
Required solar panel every home and
It's weird the way they're riding
They're the writing this is us
Predicted
Yeah
They're talking about it like
We're not going to control the pandemic you don't
You get used to it
You get over it
You fought it was nutraceutical
She fight it with
You know wiswesser pewter
Bill Gates came out too it's going to go
Will be shut down
He said yeah no
Change the subject
Hit another talking point Move Along
Yeah now we have successfully moved on
And we can ignore the fact that you're
Complete lockstep b******* fell apart
Upon analysis
It it's just
Just jumped the General Lee over it again
Yeah I don't understand how you could be Joe Rogan be sober go through that and then move along to something else
I'll be like
That was
You just got
Destroyed yep
Your boat is sinking man
You just you have this giant conspiracy about the globalist
Call operation lockstep it's been in plans for 10 years and we pull up the document that you're like
IL Ira does it
So it's so
You're exposed
Alex Alex has officially made it so that he only gets two small air holes in his butt
Know if he continues. How many more Clips do we have
He's going to wind up with no air holes I hope not I'm telling you right now if he keeps going like this there going to be 08
Salvage at least 10K
We we transition
From bad to just being like
Can be done
Man all I know is I tried
Sitting here
Where are we
I gave that one
Worrying
All these
That's not what the Wall Street Journal articles about you just going based on
I would like to read a quote from that and see if it
It says what Alex lockstep treatment
So at this point the show descendants
Really boring stretch where Joe tells Alex about his feelings about UFOs and Alex does his best not to interrupt
And drink Saban
It's fine but I'm not particularly interested in Joe talked about aliens to Alex's barely paying attention
Honestly might as well not be there
Alex says this
Where little bit beyond juice
Clearly we're from
Outside the planet
Bigger going
Does life-forms have
Forecast
Just say a word
Stapes
What I mean by we
Is that income
Comparison
We could be eventually
Police Revolution
Look where a lot
Not smarter than
Sprite and regular tape store in system
In the zoo
Oh boy
This is this is where it's like
Alright
There's not nothing good is coming
Okay so
His
Bible includes humans not being from
Well there's prequels we just haven't found that could be
Joe is trying to explain to Alex
That you know his
His view of things involved
Humans
Just being monkeys that have evolved
Through our ability to manipulate
Technology door there's possibilities that we could find ways that we could Elevate ourselves even higher
IND
As he says
Free ourselves from our monkey
Peabody's
Alex should throw something at
You're sitting there saying this will
Frias
Walmart problems
But still humans it programming Nexus
Amplify
The problems that we worry about
It certainly could
Look you could go side
It could all go bad
But it also could
Could go to a point where
People don't seals indeed
Need to do that
And that we wreck
Is that a lot of what we have
We are asked
The shackles of our Monkey Ball is worth
Monkey bodies
Call Amma demon
Yep you're trying to merge with measuring exactly
Slippery slope trying to get rid of your monkey body
This is just like this section of the show is really kind of
What I would describe is Joe trying to have a trait conversation
With a
Uncooperative
Barely paying attention scene partner
Not interesting at all I don't get
Why you would think
That
Like they
They still persist in this idea of Alec
Alex being a manly man
And I'm having some kind of chauvinist like
Elevated toxic masculinity but that mascots good thing
You know
But at the same time
He's
Waffled on everything
He's hidden from everything
He interrupts you with
Diverge
This is a man who is
Completely incapable of acting like anything that you would consider a stereotypical
Male trait
If you will he lacks the assertiveness
Sore certainty yodeling
Conviction
Andy's looking Joe's boot
Navigate work
Dissection words are kind of like a dumb conversation
Joe does ask Alex what he thinks aliens are
What do you think
Murder Hornets
There are all sorts of interdimensional force
Killers like bad alien
Manipulator
Development
Gretchen Whitmer
Level
High-level would not try to manipulate our development
Right okay so
SoJO is like imprinting
Demon says he loves
It's all I'm saying is if we need to
2 billboards
What do you think about what do you think about myself
On the election
Publix
What you're drunk come on
What I want you're going to smoke weed with me what do you think about I will I will definitely
What do you think I'll pray.
They are out of the question was what do you think aliens are whole
Call Jordan you might want to give him back another airhole Maybe
Because I'm like
Ponce de Leon
Claimed to have found the Fountain of Youth
Alex actually does have the secret to immortality
God doesn't
Which of the
And we don't say where we came from
Definitely
Linus
Flowers
Whatever we are
Genetics
Experience
Wiercioch
Purchase individual
Forever
As long as
The Lively
The World's End
Eternal life
As long as we keep having kids I have kids we live forever
That's us
Will you get better
So if your kids are immortal
That sounds great
Good work dude so I think
Whoa sensibly
Joe hear that
Before this goes any further off the rails
Who's on it all you want to end this transmission
Do
I never got to all my notes
You got more s*** I got more
Let him
No Alex really wants
To break records
Break Elon Musk
Traffic record he wants to break his own record
Say come on let's do it
Say goodnight
This is an epic pod
Another hour
It is bigger
Then the Elon Musk
Compare every listener
Right now or I'm going to die
Well YouTube
Alex
JoJo about like whatever
Studio
You're getting a new one
Yeah we're bus
We're having problems finding
Good location
But yeah Will mobile
I got a huge Aaron
We going to fight
In the process
A good man
We're good no other two hours
Yeah
Alabama basketball
Do not come on then
I'm available later
Is there anything else you really
You want to discuss
No I mean
I'm glad the Jamie take no for an answer
I'm really good at it
He's better than
I'm really good at searching for things better
Alex does his his normal thing
King of like
Desmos
Is the most important
So then he goes anti-vax on
About
Been on the news that hundred percent of people
20%
Hospital
And so
They also have backs
Major
You can type it in
But let me pause worth
MRNA
You said a hundred percent of them
That they have to study
He wants to 100% got sick
Percent with Hospital understand
Jameson find
Bill Gates
Grilled
Over
Over vaccine
The point is they admit
Tabaxi
Keep moving forward
We don't get that we want a citation on this
Are we going
I just went out the window
How old is Erick Rowan
Mysterious
So they are talking about vaccines dangers and
Alex brings up
That like
There's polio that's caused by polio vaccine
I meant Joe Google's or Jamie does and they're shocked to find out that
UNC
New polio outbreak
Too damn was caused by Oral vaccine
Well you polio outbreak
Sudan is
Is caused by
Oral vac
Do you like kids
Oh my God is that
Terrifying image
The image of them
Distributing that looks like
Poor kids face
Imagine that kid getting polio
From that back
You look so terrified
Oh my God
This is Joe reading a headline that seems to validate Alex's anti-vax narrative
Only does so if you don't understand the context of what's being discussed
In the past but when they say there are vaccine-derived cases of polio they aren't saying that someone got the pill
Polio vaccine a gave them polio
That's how it sounds mean something
This generally refers to a phenomenon that occurs in under vaccinated community
If you get this vaccine that's derived from a live virus you may have a small chance of spreading that virus even though it's
Weekend and it won't get people sick or is badly sick
If everyone around you is vaccinated it's no big deal since they'll all be protected from the virus until just fizzle out
Problem comes in when there's a high percentage of unvaccinated in the community because these people can just pass the virus
Back and forth among each other and the longer the virus has to replicate
The higher the chance it could mutate into a version of The L Mystic
Really hurt people and get them sick
The conversation about vaccine-derived illness is actually one that support
What's the community immunization
But the words are easy to confuse if you just read something out of context like a headlight
For someone like Joe who's been hitting behold maybe this is out of context drum this whole episode you think baby and ask himself
What this headline he's reading means
Joe
Ya Coulda
Ended
Shut up
Shoulda ended.
So now Alex has
Seemingly wunjo over with the dangers of vaccine look at how it look at how awful that kid looks
That's such an emotional image
If it's an emotional m
So here's where it gets like really sad
Now I think I was feels like he has a win
I need to know the bad taste of that lockstep embarrassment is out of his mouth until now
Now we got a
Swing for the fences
I wish
I like to retire that she
To finish up my work
Mistakes I made
Other stuff
It's going to take more than a year to clean up the mistakes you tonight if you
At least
Alex's is like
This works at much
Stressed out
I know you are
I literally do this
Wisconsin
We thought
I'm not a victim
So I can't do this
And I want everybody to know I love my crew I told
Tell the truth
Get out the next
Does mean I won't go on your show on Sierra
Are you going to lie I try.
Go to a psychiatrist
This all makes me really sad
Like the ending the show Alex's drank half a bottle of whiskey
Amanda
Dewey tried to end it
It didn't work and now we're talking about Alec needing to get in shape
Going to die
Living the way he does on his show
This ism
Comfortable
Shoulda ended the show and then we get this
Joe has a revelation but Alex
Does not want to talk about
But it actually makes things make
A bit more
Talk to me about adderal
Well I'm not going to get any of that type of stuff
The point is it
Is the doctors play
The whole country
That makes a lot of sense
If you look at a lot of the
Behaviors that Alex manifest
The idea that he's abusing
Adderal
Or some kind of other stimulant
I mean it just a checks off a lot of boxes
I would never like speculate about that and I think it's
It's gotten a little bit weird
Leaving it might be a little bit across the line but
I need something Joe brought up and I honestly do agree with Joe that it is something that would be good
Talk about
A lot of people who have had trouble
Yeah I think that
Stimulant abuse might be very
It would make a lot of sense for how drastically it shows change
Over the couple of years like
Not
I mean there's there's
There's the influences that are sort of intellectual that are like these Insidious influences of
Steve pieczenik
Rodger Stone in a bunch of these weirdos and
Recognizing that Trump is an opportunity
I also probably not thinking the Trump is going to win and take you could
Ron Paul
Right right right I'll put a lot of the behavioral stuff really does
Does
CertiFit what you might expect with that Adderall abuse
And I mean
Jose talking about it that is a past thing
I should hope that I hope that.
Is the case
It's just a bummer
It's only drinks
Because he has to work so hard sure
But I'm not
I do caffeine
It gets the point where like
Exhausted
Sober October
Last October
Yeah
Do you think you
Totally
Rejected for
Do you think about if I wasn't doing a show ever
Everyday
I'm Alexander
Irene
50 article
Enslaving me
I don't want me around
It's not like I'm a scared of
Something else
B negative has NATO
Your help
Yasso
For me
Get away from all of us
What do you want to do
Relaxing
I love metal
What the f***
Is happening
This is just a
This is you do not
Get to do that no
You spent the last 30 years destroying the f****** world you don't get to just require different tire to a f***
Life of hunting and fishing and oil paintings of fuckyourself Hitler does not get to become a painter afterwards
Hitler just not I mean George W bush should be in the f****** haggai don't understand why he's allowed to paint
Alright f****** yeah it's just want to I just want to make sculptures of mother
Metal skull
I think that over the course of this episode is awesome
Really interesting attempt on Jose part 2
Call for citations you things entirely
Bottle of whiskey
I don't mean to discredit
He should be way drunk
A drink a lot
Have a bottle is a chunk
I usually don't want cookie usually don't walk after half
Sit around
He's a drinker drinker
Given given the
But then
I really think
The you can't use Bill Maher as an example
Step thing
Our complete puncturing of the illusion that Alex knows what he's talkin about or that he doesn't
Then at the end you getting really sad saying he wants to quit
Jose talking about like him being
Secretly taking adderal
And also I drink because I work too hard
I want to quit in like maybe hunt
And fish
Go fuc
It's very
Not great as a whole I think
Alex comes off very poorly
Yeah Joe Disick
But I appreciate you being here
This is a great way
Alex
See a side of you that
The movie Vendetta
And see the other two
You know I think
Degrade account
You really think so
I do not agree
That could you save that quote Forever This is Everything I hoped it would be
I would like that one to stay right there that would like Joe Rogan to have to live with
My Alex Jones podcast was everything I hoped it would be
If it was everything you hoped it would be very interesting set of hopes
Yeah it's not good I really hope
That I would come off okay
Yeah
To spread his b*******
2 million defeat I hope that I would come off as performatively curious at the same time
Also sandbagging of Alex totally
I I come off as like a pig who likes to roll around in the mud but doesn't actually want to
The top half of the pig doesn't get dirty by all these other pigs
They just roll around in it
My legs
Sure I covered in mud but I would never allow my face
If in his Cup Squad episodes he came out in
Said this was everything I wanted it to be because I believe that
Fully
Encapsulate if you have an understanding of what Alex believes what he puts into the world how he communicates
This episode is all you need
To decode that he doesn't know s*** 100 anything about these topics that he's talking about and all of this
Sources that he tries to rely on or misinterpretations
Or completely made up
He also is too much of a coward to ever admit any of this stuff yet so when confronted to
Buy a friend
He will lie to your friends and his friends face
In order to wiggle out of trouble
I think that if he said that and then said
F*** this dude I don't associate with them anymore
Congratulations you've pulled off
You did it something fantastic but
You continue to associate with them and there's no consequences for
Clear
Demonstrations of b******* that Alex did here then you're an active participant and
Sign off
With this clip
We did it
We did it all right
What would we do three and a half hours
Yes
A visit
Bye everybody thank you
Thank you friends
Tune into the show
Oh and thank you too
Sushi
I hope this was everything you hoped it would be
You guys congratulations on sponsoring this nonsense
Making making this possible
I think it's really interesting
That in the aftermath of this episode coming out there was a backlash and understandable
There's stuff that's just like
You know
Harmlessly dumbshit like William Colby was murdered show or Robert Maxwell was murder
True Crime
But there's damaging stuff anti-vax narratives is Joe Rogan
Does not do a responsible job of pushing back against
Climate change shirt that's huge
Could be useful in helping push back against the satanic panic
Absorbing people
Right now
I think that there is actually
Very good cause
For people to be like what the f*** are you doing
And the backyard.
I could I don't know I've seen headlines going around the people are wanting to cancel the Spotify account
Mehndi episode disappeared from Spotify
And then now today but just before we were recording
Cic another headline
They always attack glitch
And apparently the episode now on Spotify
So I don't know what's going on with this person lost those pages they were in the mail Dan and he just left
Where did they go anyway sure it was
Proof of everything but you can just trust
I'm not following that story I don't know what's going on with that I don't
Mugen to that later
I don't know what's going on with the status of this this episode but I don't know
I'd be really really hot
It'd be funny if he funny for Spotify to take it down
Nike Spotify to take
100 million
My mouth
Give us a
Hundred million dollars I need to find a way
Yeah you'll be number one I think we had a hundred million dollars I guarantee we'd be number one
Billboard
I'd be f****** going ape shitt with this
I don't I don't
No
Terrible idea when you give me 100 million I don't know any different than what we do
I guess we people smoke money instead maybe
I don't know I think I think that
I would
I would ask
If Joe were listening which is not know
I would ask that he engage in some reflection
How about some of the points that we've brought up
About
The tactics to try to get to the bottom of some of Alex's stuff
It makes sense
Those are the things that you were trying to figure out what someone Source on a certain thing what
Right
With Alex
There isn't anything there
And that's why you constantly end up with him
Trying to change the subject
Jangling keys in front of people
Obfuscating
Creating
False position
For you to have to own up to yep that's why he does those things because
Stanza possibility
Have you realizing
Did altimate lie there isn't a source yep there isn't anything behind
Anything that he's saying
And reflect on that
And reflect on how
You did the best you could maybe
Maybe
And it still won't
So don't do this again
Don't do it
Drift do a spectacle
Say really dumb yeah yeah
A pre-announced don't believe or care about anything that I say this is bananas fun
Seriously cuz you end up with
You have an intellectual conversation on s*** he made up
Between Joe Rogan
Tim Dillon and Alex
Jones
Great I'm most likely to believe Tim Dillon and again it's because I know the least about him
Anyway
We're done
And now I'm
I'm going to retire to my sit
Sleep for a week
I hope you all enjoyed will be back on Monday but until then Jordan Rave website
Also on Twitter
If you could please find a local charity or Bellefontaine area to help out people doing God's work
Indeed
Emilio
I'm Leo I'm dzx Clark
I'm Daryl rundus
I wrote operation lockstep
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color