Air Jordan 5 sweat it
I have great respect for knowledge babe I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
A little bit about
Alex Jones
Jordan Jordan
My bright spot
Continuation from last time the Brite Spot
So much better on the switch
Then it was on the Wii U I believe that it was the Wii U that they Pikmin 3 originally came out on
And you know what the
Controller for the Wii U was that like handheld thing
The only reason that I've never had a destroyed Mesa
Was not the best
Wait
Experience
Improve, switch
What's the
Lock on
Throw Pikmin.
It's better
It's much better I enjoy it
Good love it
Little Pikmin running around
There's little alien there's something to do with the yellow one
Can withstand electricity and they are lighter they have lighter bones or something I guess you can throw them farther
Way high up in the air
You can throw a yellow Pikmin
I get that one of your bones
Can't do it now
All the reservoir a beer
The blue ones
Can go in water
Okay the red ones are related to fire
And
The blind to see a pattern the black ones are made of Rock
So they can break
Glass smoking alright
Like Shack
Text through a backboard
Ones are really light
So they can fly
Sure
And then the yellow until I there also
I don't know
There's something about the white ones being able
Anyway what's your bright spot
There is one thing that Alex and I do share and that is
Blood hence love of Star War
And
Swell and blood
However you would like
The Mandalorian
Season 2
So I have
Return to my Star Wars Universe into memes we're desperately longed to be
Baby Yoda hell yeah baby Yoda
He is not aged today to Baby to Yoda
That sounds great I know maybe there was Bubba
OSHA I haven't seen any of that show but I've probably catch up
What's great at some point
Start with
Episode 1
Venus
I'll bet the other list of like
It's probably about a mile long by now never watch it
Space westerns are gray never want Cowboy Bebop written all over it I will never watch it until someone else
Suggested and then I'll be like it now
Stopwatch app
Tell me and media.
Jordan today we are coming off a bit of a hangover and high from the
Rogan Experience
Little too much
To Rogan to experience
Cindy and today what we're doing is we are back in the past looking at November
4/7 twenty-six
Alright I'm fine
The reason that I decided to do this was
Is that
You know we're recording this and you know there's going to be released on Monday the day before the election
Here in 2020
Okay I think that there is very little value to talk
Going about whatever Alex is talking about
Real people
We got it sure anything's
You know he's covering
Oscar every Gator talking about it would kind of be like playing in
Sensationalism
Even if we're pushing back on it and I just don't I don't have
Time or the energy or the stomach for it, and we'll get to what Alex was doing right before the 20th
20 election
Right after once it's happened and in in that spirit
I don't think that we can have an episode on Wednesday
That covers
This stuff
Now well pasa
No I just think because of the timing of everything and so our Wednesday episode will be on Friday this week or second episode of Beyond Friday week
I believe the plan eventually to go to
Maybe I'm not sure we'll see but be at the ability to put out a
Good middle of the week episode
How is light
What could
Possibly what could anybody want to listen to us talk about when the election hasn't happened at Alex
Monday
Day after the most
Day of maybe the world
We're like
Alex said this before the election
I'd like to be able to discuss it with a little bit of hindsight in a little bit of information so we will be doing that
And today like I said we're on November 7th we on our last episode from 26
16 we went looked at November 4th
Through 6 2016
And Alex was in a weird state where it was all pretty thin it was all
I hate Hillary
Hillary sucks
Despondent
Yeah yeah
It did not feel to me listening to it that he was planning
On Trump win
This was not a you did not scream 1776 2.0
Screaming
Trump was going to win I think you could just repeat like just Thomas Jefferson fake quotes for
4 hours straight
I would say that my assessment was that you know he didn't
The Trump couldn't
I Was preparing
For the most likely outcome would Hillary win
Like all of us yes
And then he came back
Back in the evening sure cuz they're in the middle of a 50
Due to our lives broadcast
Forget that business on that Jordan let's take a moment to say thank you
Some folks who signed up for himself
I'm off to meet Emmaus put moss in my mouth thank you so much you are now policy walk
I'm a policy wonk very much a moth made of mouse put moth in my mouth
Thank you so much next
Dan is there a war on Western Civilization
You are now a policy walk
I'm a policy wonk
That person requested that I
Thought I had a stroke
Is that very much
Next Erica's hunky husband Ian thank you so much right now if I was wrong
Husband
Milo B thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
They're listening everything and the childlike store
Or what you could do is take
That's generous.
Get it into a lovely little
Bishop
I put it in a little tiny egg
Maybe
If you are fighting a large
Beast you might need the assistance of that generous
Exit 88 might need to open up
Open needs to use some Force powers
And then once you've
Defeated the large Beast with in this metaphor I guess we're going to call selfishness
Then you've defeated it with the
The force powers of generosity and you take that to a local bail fund or charity Dan cuz this is spoiler for a Mandalorian
Okay
I got a message from Plantiva and
Enjoy plant update
So I wanted to actually use this as an opportunity
Need to give
AR partials
In the mailbag
Okay because we're going to talk about this person
Actual package
Later but I wanted to give a special shout-out to Duncan
Who along with
Also sent
Template
Is that Actuarial tables yeah it's like a template
For plant maintenance all you can keep track of like watering pass
Moisture pH
All kinds of things sure and so I have actually
Made pages
All of my plants
Bathroom and clock in and clock out
It was a little bit of disorder with how I've been treating the plan
I'm taking care of them for a little bit more organization could be good
Give me a wonderful template here so
Great America
Out of context
But I think you'll actually enjoy
Get ready
Because I mean
Michael Bloomberg
Yeah
Alright man
We like Star Wars and
F*** Michael Bloomberg
You always know some hot fires coming out says get ready to believe it's ready to believe
Alright thanks guys
The delivery on that's pretty good too I think I want to hear one more time
Get ready boy fish fry station, say it because I mean it
Michael Bloomberg
He hit that f****** real hard every time we heard him swear in the past I've always been like this
Do does not know how to swim
Weirdo
Is some top-quality
That was a that was a pro swearing good job
Good stuff here we start on the 7th is in Alex's actual show during the day and he's really
Excited about the
Well let's hear how I tell you to say that you could cut the
But it's absolutely true
I've never felt so
Such suspense
In my life
Quite frankly not even when I was about to see my wife have R4
Child
That's
Osun fortunate
Okay that's
Ugly
This 2016-elections boar exciting than Rex's birth of a man
Rex
Rex he is not your friend
Don't seem very good
For Family Values
So in this next whip Alex's talking about the state of election
As it turns out according to him
Trump's already won
Hillary win
She's cheating
Which is exactly what he said now
Yeah she has varied if
Trump has already won the election whether they steal it from him whether he wins in a landslide the other shows
That's where it's going
Because
He has introduced americanism not globalism
To the world
He has
Brought out 1776
This is a guy saying the Trump is already won
Because of the things that he's brought into
Conversation
This is a moral victory that we are speaking of
Not a literal
Let's and democracy forever victory that we're about to
Pictures of rationalization
It appears
So at this point
Anthony gucciardi comes into Studio
Cuz he doesn't work there anymore and I think he doesn't like Alec
Anymore
Sort of
Health blogger
Maybe
Mini Mike Adams but who actually worked at Infowars
You talk a lot about like these supplement line
However
He's on for a
Them today
Do Infowars now 172 rank 172 in the United States that means of all the billions of websites in the
World you can imagine all of them out there Infowars is 172
The 172nd
Google is only about twenty percent
Traffic
So just talkin about
To be a really important election I think there's somebody named Trump or is it somebody I think it's Bill running again
Can they do that anyways
We are
Doing
Great
It sucks it's a lot of that is a lot of that
This is pretty much all over the place in this interview part of it I think it's probably because Anthony gucciardi boring a s***
But
Give It Up
For the MVP
Of the season
Season's coming to a close
Was that another was the MVP in 45
50 okay well
That's fair that's fair
Everybody knows
But that is retrospectively that is decay
16 guy
Who will not be the MVP in 2020
Human Revolution
Against
What's the number one most valuable player isn't Nigel farage
Is it Donald Trump
It isn't Alex Jones
You're getting it
You showed up first unit the longest
You brought to the big story
You broke the mainstream media's control
I don't care Hadley steal it but that doesn't matter
I've looked at it that's even better
See
Wow tone very different than 20
Oh man let him see what I can profit off that
Yep
No man yeah
We were also bright-eyed and bushy-tailed back then thinking that Alex
Who's going to lose
He was going to lose
This is where you belong and then Alex winds and even he didn't know what to do with yeah it's a real tragedy it's almost
I meant like a Greek
Yes it is very much a illiterate illiterate or perspective
It's almost like the be careful what you wish for
Keep all over the play
Play the album the real polls
As we know which are very different than the poll polls
The pole that he has
3rd numbers for Trump
Internal
I don't want it I'll just tell you
And show him the entire time
30 points ahead of her in New York
Here's the problem
Republican
So if you keep like getting about he's a son of New York
New York
People
New York by 8
Large Marge
Yeah that was
Not good no he did not come close in New York even though he is a Native Son of New York
All of the stuff
I hated for the things
Not not super popular
But you know
Yahoo super popular
Volkswagen Jetta
Again we just showed you the Comcast number
They don't track everything
Play shows in 107
Show me something of the World Wide Web
Yeah that's okay it's about people understanding
What jokes they are
Are the big Ivory Towers
Mexican Kingpin
Chinese
The Chinese government
Announce their buying
All 6 Hollywood
And how do you cook you shut up you know you're covering up for blow up
Hollywood
Major producers
We're sitting there
Because I'm talk about the Real World MTV for idiots
When you know about this is when you go to the big dinner
If when you have dinner with 3-star General
What you literally
Conspiracy theorists
How the real world works
I told you ten years ago for the Chinese in the Muslims be
Now it's official
Now it's official.
You can tell Alex's little bit amped up
Little bit little bit all over the place all over the place little bit
He's f***** up
Here's what happens in his mind
The globalists go to somebody like Ron Howard and then I got to run
I know you don't want to do this
But you're going to have to have breakfast with Alex Jones in order to drink
Convince him to help
Let's kill everybody you're going to have to do it he's had
What's with everybody else
It's your turn Ron Howard Grazer had a dinner with him last week
Look I know you don't want to do it but he has dinner with 3-star generals he knows what the only person who won't ask
We talked with Nicolas Cage and that's cuz I don't know
He's too busy in his pyramid that he built or whatever
Mausoleum for when he
Excuse me
I don't know if you've heard
About this yet but Alex is traffic is way up I heard
We are
Okay
This first half-hour the show is almost entirely Alex and Anthony gucciardi bragging about how popular Infowars
8 bizarre it's
Completely out of place for how someone might want to spend their time on the day before the election
Alex sounds
F****** spawn
Honestly if I did
Know that this was the day before the election I would have turned this off
It's so master
Praetorian almost nothing to say about the beginning of this show
It's a desert it's a
Hazard of contact
Jesus
Ironic
He was doing so well when Trump
A campaign
From 172 in the US
To not allow
Allowed on the list
Yeah it's pretty it's pretty wild
Swing Flash
Hey
Alex
Is pretty
Peeved about that people
Hello Miss
Interpret Trump's comments
It's about next
African American
This one's where he wants them all day
Fiesta in Santa Maria
And
Alex
You know Keith Whitley
Trump because he said thing
The people have misinterpreted I don't think so
Nope
That's why I have such a
Donald Trump
You know Mexico
Let America great people who are working people
In a really good people but I'll tell you
A lot of criminals are coming across and they let him come across
And you know this
Yeah Mexico lot of bad people lot of criminals
What they do
Criminal down here we don't go home
Where you run
Around the Mexico tradition
That's not true
I was going to say that's a snow.
True
Mexico would not have a
The Mexico that allows Rd
It doesn't have
Extradition treaty that we do definitely have
Yeah that's
I wonder if Alex
For real or if you just lost track of ascend
I think that
That's probably
Yeah I might as well just end
Like that I think it's like I've seen movies little bit like that
Pig11 extradition
Previous listen to Outlaw country
All you have to do is get to the Border
Weight is Pancho and Lefty that's all Alex knows about laws
Anyway
Alex has done
A straw poll
Grassroots
98% in favor of trump it's a really wild number he's found all the Democrats
Don't like Hillary
Every Democrat
My mom has friends are Democrats last longer
Democrats
And I get like this
Play Thrice relations all rest of it in the bank
These women were just hugging me
My mom had a
The only party
Cookout
The same age as Hillary Clinton won up looks like Hillary Clinton
What up looks like her
I mean if you look like Hillary Clinton that you don't like Hillary Clinton
Clearly means that
Evereve
That's it obviously she's not a popular candidate people who look like her don't even want her that I'm not certain
No I think I think Alex might just be seeing Hillary Clinton
We already know that he thinks of it demons yell at him in the grocery store that's true he may be haunted by
Hillary Clinton by the
From The Ring I guess
So
Sing there though is that like
These people aren't so much saying the Trump is great they're saying that
Hillary is bad
It's still like the
There's some positive talk about Trump
Episode
Can't deny that at all but
The focus is
Very much still do
Just like she sucks
She looking
It's hard to remember but there was a time
Whenever people in
Coral Cove
Polite Society didn't
Actively an outwardly say
I would prefer non-white
People to be set
Second-class
Trump got elected
And we went from Alex and like
I hate Hillary and Donald Trump says some things that I've been misinterpreted
Beforeitsnews like
There are subtle differences
So
I don't know what do you think about the national
Racist
I was going to go with what is it 4th versus super race I was going to go with power
No I was not
Can I get a termite on the Star-Spangled Banner
During the Pledge of Allegiance
Extensive what people done for that
And why was under attack and why was still in Port
Now I know
Now I know why they want to pull America down with it
Testing ground of all the GMO in all the plays and all the garbage
Because they hate
His folks diplomas can't come
The system
We're announcing
Once
Once a year the total absolute biggest sale
Across-the-board
That is a nice
Nice Jones Ian.
I was pretty impressed
You know what we've been out of
2015 for so long
In our art
So I've kind of forgotten how good is that pivots used
To be or that one wasn't
Please tell surprising
That was just a smooth it was like it was meant to be there but instead it made my brain hurt
We have different opinions on it I don't think it was that smooth but I think we agree it was
Way out of nowhere
So Alex has a big narrative bushing
That is dated Barack Obama
Had told
Someone
Speech
Q&A session
About it
No snitch
Don't remember that
Gladwell Alex plays the clip of it here and I think you I think you can pretty easily sauce out what the
Here is Obama
Agreeing that we won't go after you illegals to vote
Dreamers undocumented
Are fearful
Immigration
Do they come for my family and Deportes
And the reason is
When you vote
And
It's not a situation where the hell are transferred over
And people started investigating a server
You can tell that he's responding to her
When you vote
You are
Because you can't you can't register
If you don't have the required that
Exactly equals Obama hearing request
About should everybody vote being like
Yeah come on
Yeah
Be concerned that this person was bringing up is that there are people who may have
Concerns about
Targeted
Oh no
No I would definitely trust the America
And that's one of the ways
Voter disenfranchisement
Immigration
Folks
People mites
Be intimidated away from Gone
It's the definition
Terrorism
I mean the idea is to go in
Terrify a popular
And then spread that
Terror throughout
Everybody in the entire
Country in order to influence people politically
Isis a terrorist organization
Alex
On a recent episode from 2020 that we heard we heard about him
Starting up a voter fraud
Email address okay
Infowars.com
Smart people
Send tips
Still yeah
Hey guess what he did that in 2016 to
Voted infowars.com report what's happening with the vote
It's flooding in
Dead people illegal
The presidents on TV Stanky Leg you can vote
So yeah
Email may have been active the whole time
Possibly
Deactivated then restarted them both
It's now I want to hear 2012
2208 fuckingo on back how long is that envelope if I email address been there probably just
Episode
Now he actually has an interview with Larry Nichols that I found no clips from work worthwhile it's so boring
Right before the election Larry David
Can't come up with s***
Which god dammit
Everybody
That's true
So another Gaston here
Probably doesn't want to be associated with now
Tutu Messi
Maybe but it's someone who he decided to have on on the day before the election in 2016
Will there be unrest are they going to steal at Disneyland side for Trump
I want to get his take on all of this Stefan molyneux
I mean can you feel the energy my friend
I got to tell you Alex that I've never been
Sports fans
Sports but getting pulled into this election cycle
And being so
Interested in the outcome
It's kind of like watching a football game
Where the winning team gets
Through Western Civilization for the neck
Next 1000 years so
Do you guys believe that since Trump won he gets to rule Western syphilis
A boy
Little boy I don't think I want a self-declared white nationalist. Yes
4000 years
The van is not self-declared that yet you haven't been to Portland
This point he was still just
Painfully obvious
Okay buddy
Cool
Stephon really does not waste any time
Getting pretty
Pretty crypto with his racism
If the if the Democrats
Let's get in there going to legalize across all the illegal immigrants
And they will be unbeatable
That's the test
Stickley 4
Pretty much ever
So you know this is all just the demographic replacement demographic shift
Kind of argument that says mint
Strike Up fear in the American
I like how normal code for white
Localized it is for people on the right to just be like
Yeah if everybody voted we lose every time
So we don't do that
And everybody just goes along with literally no chance that we could
Ever win over a voting Bloc
Not appeal
We've whipped
The media so bad
Did they just go and this is part of our system
Spell it's imagine that this large group of immigrants
That's at where to come in work
To be in franchise Bill. People are naturalized in Madison County
Why do you think that your side with
We better policies
We never said we have better power
What they do say that why do why would they think that these people would be in
Incapable of
You know what I think I would like to vote with Stephane his dumb ideas
Is Jared Kushner let us know it's because they don't want to
That's the problem with the rest of us
But we don't want it
I would say we were born with millions of dollars
Is that also help
Yeah I believe that
50 left
The Democrats are the ones who are really real
I like to hear
You know this as well as I do I'm sure but it may be new to your to recording sound
Don't care about minorities
They Don't Care About Women
People want
Equality for the races that can they're good people want equality for the
For the gender for this axis
I see what they do is they say what we care about black
How much do they care about Clarence Thomas or Herman Cain or other black
Are Republicans generally trying to destroy and Samir in Andorra
How much do they care about some of the amazing women
Who were on the right
Yeah it's not about it it's it's
It's trying to take our natural care and concern for
Equality between the races and the generous and turning it against us
That's so dumb
Like
Is argument is the real you say you like me but what about Clarence Thomas
Okay well then I'll just turn that around you say you like women what about Hillary Clinton like
I mean did you think that your aversion to Hillary Clinton might be based on a disagreement with her policy
Okay well I don't like Clarence Thomas's beliefs
I okay
Philosopher Kings I've got to that also proves how
Not right
Or misogyny
Honest I am
Damn I hate white nationalist
Of all Races
Genders
Creed's Orbach
Backgrounds you can make it simpler than that.
His is flawed reasoning is much simpler
He believes that
Democrats
Right
They're addicts
Power
Power off
Doesn't sound like
It seems like
I think the key thing to understand for me about the left Alex
Is that that it's impossible to really fandom
Their motives
And their imaginations without understanding
They're addicts to power
And if you've ever known somebody and I hope you haven't but if you have ever known somebody in your life
Who's the real addicts whether it's the sex
Gambling or drugs or alcohol
They will do anything
To get there drug
Have choice they will step over bodies they will destroy their lives they will lose their saving
Their marriage that relationship
The children
They steal everything
Cool
They are I will argue
Let those
2 will do everything possible
To keep people
That they want to be hold captive
From actually listening to anyone on the
No point in time are they like
Talk to them and listen to what they say
Doesn't matter
What's really going on is there a different Power
Sure it sounds nice to be a good person
Interview I would say but Alex is more regularly
Until now when
It's way too messy to have Stefan molyneux
Good idea
Start talk about phrenology or so
It's really racist
She's just gone.
Really racist races
Awesome
Bucket love
Alex and the two of them sort of having an agreement that this is a lichen
Exciting Sports
But they don't really like sports
Alex
Complaints about sports
Batman
Not watch Eyeworks
Lackadaisical not care
They want us
Politically and culturally involved
And put it on a prosthesis
Of Spore
That's like having sex with a blow-up doll folks getting real
Not against 439 but I played fourth but
You're not watching family-oriented yourself at the Joe
Roman do
Business in life in your family in
Your house in order that's where you have all this wargaming and
Knowing
Not you know what
Size jock
Some guy wears no that's in the NFL you like
You know men slapping each other on the bus and he's fine he won't do that no private time
That's not our religion is what I'm getting at
He's trying to make like liking Sports
It's kind of
Like
Something you can gay Bash
That's interesting that's very weird
But I find it so in
Interesting how many almost certainly
Roll tide
Listen to
I'm pretty sure the football Bixby
I don't think
Anybody who's into like sabermetrics
Statistics
Send Mike fantasy football I don't think that
Jockstrap size is a one of the things that they track
Foot size
I don't know if they've got
Contradicts yet but I think we're coming
I used to collect basketball cards and I don't feel like these are the sort of
Sports fans are into
What style are we all do how good big dick Johnson was complaining
Slapping asses in congratulations
Kind of happy you doing Hockey Night playlist
Did Tim Allen do that
So
Like I said the real tone here is very much like Hillary's probably
Steal the election but and what are you going to do
Point now
Where people are into politics they're awake they're involved
And Donald Trump was just that magic little
Little sprinkle
In this whole recipe that is just exploding
So don't freak out of a Steeler
Wentworth game that with some former Navy Seals other folks tomorrow
Don't freak out if they steal the election there's going to be more
Patriots
The globalist chicken
Sure sure you know if Hillary gets in rest easy my friend
The Fight Continues
Not she will open up a Chasm of hell and demons will spawn forthwith
It took so little time for everyone
I'm like Hey look
Sometimes the Democrats to Alexa
We're going to get through it till like
Biden's we're going to win by a mile no like
You know what's outrageous about it too is that like
He hates Hillary Clinton
Like for decades
Decades
Built-in mic
Real hatred of Joe Biden I know that he didn't like Obama
Super poke
Gaston by.
It'll be the end of the world when Biden is running and it's be like Hillary my twin what you going to do
When Hillary gets its Justin
I'm just so mad all the
Estranged
But I think I think again like if you look at it from a really cynical perspective it's because
At this point
I don't think
Did Alex's
Completely lost his mind
Prophet
If Hillary wins hika
Can profit off it and that's why I'm a maybe
Even better if they
They steal it
Cuz he can profit off that yep
I think that he thought
Pretty good profit off drop but I think he has but I think a T-Rex
Recognizes it
You can't go back now
If Biden wins
There's no way to keep
You Beautiful War going
You got to go to Walmart Infowars over that
So part of it is gone
Yeah
Trump winning is the only way that his racket
Joey is another guest
It's not Larry Nichols
But it is someone else
I don't know where I don't know where the f***
This dude is anymore
You certainly not around
The guy from fastball
No he's a hippie
He's a chiropractor
Oh boy.
Now remember we had in the past we had nasal mist vaccines but this year
They're recommending only injectable why is that
There's two different vaccines that hardly bypasses the immune system
Dangerous this year
A high-dose shot
For older people now remember
No special just
Kermit bad guy
Logan's Run carousel
The group
We are going to need those old
People to avoid getting flu shots so they can sacrifice themselves while going towards lighter
Yeah
This is all been going on during the election nobody even knows about this
I'm breaking this for the first time
Because I think it's so important
This is mark my words one of the worst
Lucy's in will create the most damage
Never in the history of the world and I'm not saying that to scare people it's definitely there but I mean
Take your shot at
According to the CDC the 2016 2017 flu season was slightly worse
Spend the 20
16 Season
But much milder than the two previous Seasons as well as
The 2017 to 2018
I have marked doctor groups words
And what do you know a chiropractor is Sensational prediction was inaccurate water shot
Wild wow he would have some sort of insight that other doctors who would maybe study these types of
Things for their entire lives are out
You know as an outsider could really shake things up but I think it's just
These Chiropractic
Some good advice for you
Don't get the flu shot do not do your research before you get the flu shot this year
Take it and get your coffin ready
Libra
Yep so don't
Get a flu shot
Trauma Chiropractic Group
That might be good advice strictly advise not to get a flu shot coming
From Doctor group
So ol all liberals
Against Hillary
Sure
According to Alex
Well that distinction wasn't really real to Alex at this point
Show all Liberals are against Hillary and did the reason that it be bad if
She got in his really interesting
Same here
Every real liberal like Julian Assange Bev Harris
You name it
Jill Stein is against Hillary and say
He wants World War 3 because she does
Terrible decisions
He cannot be challenged she must have her wait you can't do that with China and Russia
Weiwei isn't that wow plotting that offer literally 141
Exactly what your office around
Oh my God she wants to
What a terrible person
Grave
Wow
Wow this is hard to go into the past and hear the exact same s***
Wrong
It's really interesting
Superman
It's shocked
Blair
Vienna way
What what I could never have predicted based on the last
Last 4 years
Of this show
I'm listening to so much Alex
Is it you go back to the day before the election
Hey Alex would be like so lackadaisical just go to like B deal at what you going to do
Yeah
It isn't
It isn't it was screaming it's just not
It's another day for him
Infuriated
Isn't it amazing how
Spectrum me a f******
That's how stable Obama
The f****** country
That's how stable it was
It's not good
By no stretch
Stable is s*** to the point where Alex is like
You're focused a little action what I got to do Maryville
So at this point
Decided he's going to really swing and start fake cry
I can get lost hiking and kayaking and
Painting and cooking
IFit great cook-off man I love
Thanks for checking on her casseroles
I just so easily working hours days, cook food Hangout
My kids I want you so bad
There's bad people coming out to my kid
Computer laptop
Cuz I'm sad it's crying cuz I feel extremely vile
Alright
Annoy
Need him to backup
He keeps saying that he likes painting
Dino Alex on social media
No response
At press time we have no proof I think it's b*******
I think it's a thing that he thinks would make him sound so f******
Culture interesting
I have diverse interests
I'm sure you do
Rambling about how the man
Globalist
As Farmers ourselves
Yeah
They don't want what
Thomas Jefferson wrote about yeoman
Farmers
Hard-working smart
People that are confident and good
Farinelli read history the globalist are so scared of farmers
Poor farmers are family
Their men their women
Self-sufficient
Thomas
And called the little things
Strong
I don't want you to be a farmer they want you to be out of their control
Like Thomas Jeff
I'm not going to belabor this we're running specials right now
Sorry
A little boy
Real good
Out of nowhere
I don't want you to be farmers in South
Division 5 Mi whatever it was
That's what he just said I forgot where I was going
Sodus Point
Decides to get into his history with abortion
As we know we've heard him talk about the
And I probably would have just ignored it cuz it's rehashing a topic but
He spends quite a while on it
Salacious
I would say if it's
Stefan molyneux Zoe fancies himself a philosopher
Versailles
Basic reasoning and logic
Tissues cuz he's actually very stupid yes
Alex is getting into a very interesting
Ethical
Distinction
But I would like to talk about after this clip
Because what he proposes as an ethical system I believe is unsustainable in the real world
If you've paid for abortions you were lied to her to know what's happening
Cuz as long as you admit
I should have done that for birth control I was told I would lie
I forget myself I forgive
You know what I did say the baby please forgive me and him will God forgive me and just freeze
Not if it comes to human soccer
When you dip
Later when you learn about it your heart
By the Holy Spirit
And you don't do anything about it
Then you're committed that evil eye look
I'm somebody
Pedro Garcia born
My dad was like 16 he's i'll scrounge around here to get money and stuff he's like son you need to
If I want to get married if you want you to be you stop killing my grandkids
My resolve 16
Abortion
That's f***** up but like I don't think that getting reproductive
Healthcare is
I don't think there's any ethical problem with
With abortion or anything like that
All above board
Allowing
To just like
Play with the ideas Alex
If there is an act
That is
Totally fine to do
Then later can become
A human sacrifice
You have a very ethical dilemma because
The act itself can't be wrong if doing it
Is not wrong
You believe it to be wrong right only wrong once you have
Decided it's wrong
And
Deny that it's wrong that sounds like the system of
I think I would call it a malignant narcissistic psychopath
It's it's
It's nihilistic
Because we act itself
It has to be morally completely neutral
There can be no ethical implications to it
Wrong
Denny's your eventual feelings about it right
I would argue that it's actually a very normal thing for a religious people especially born-again ones
Partially harshly judge everyone who commits
It's the sins that they are
Absolutely free
Yeah and what about this what about the possibility that
I mean God forbid you die
Before
You make up your box
Ono then you're not from Africa me what is the What is the
Subway
Purgatory any put it in the Bible that we all know about
It's it's just strange it's strange to have this sort of ethical
Hunting
I guess you don't like I think that's a good way of putting it because it is literally going to ball down the road
Kill the person
I feel fine right now
I'll deal with this when it
I'll deal with this when the time is right
A bit much when the Holy Spirit
Alex's saying that like when he was 16 is Dad was
Confronting about this
My resolve 16 start looking at Mary payflex a divorce
So don't you stop killing the Grinch
I promised myself I would never do that again and I
That is not true
I know there were several more abortions between 16 and when you got married
Alex
He said he had
5e paperwise
That he's paid for
No that's not to shame or say anything wrong with
It's just Alex you're being mean
Consistent something is not right about these
Stories
And I care so deeply about the fact that he says everyone who has an abortion
I agree but also
Part of me wonders if it's all made up
Because it does
Really fit into that same sort of story is the youth pastor who wants to lie to you about that wild days stuff
I do kind of have that feeling
The way that everything is so inconsistent
The details are are just all over the place
I don't know if I even believed any of it
That's fair
It sounds like something like it the same way that I was like
I went to Satanic rituals
No you didn't
Yeah that's true it's more likely that he's like
There is something true
Brandi's riffing off of that there's a there's a kernel of something somewhere
Have the story down
It's delivered the same way every single time like a stand-up set
You know is there they know they're they
Travel around they do there
The youth pastor do you Pastor will have like
Taking a hit off a joint one time
And then turn that into
3 years old
Opium death anywhere right
Do anything I was just
So happy
Lay it on the
So there's a decent chance that like
The reality visit Alex
At 1
Not that he paid for it and now it's turned
But he feels around that is true
Didn't
Whatever it is it's
Just it just that it's Max
To me of life
Just unresolved
Feeling when I don't even think
I think it's just
Bulshit that possible
Anyway Alex leaves after rambling about to
Stouffer Wild
Very much not a show that I would have
Expected to be the day before the election
Pretty thin
How many abortions you pay for
David Knight takes over
52 hour live election broadcast that has begun we're now an hour number
Of that 52-hour broadcast
I just asked Leah guys the booth I said.
What time
Special right now because we have to find this operation post
Basically said pretty much everything
Keep on selling Grandpa
David Knight saying stick with me for 52 hours
Who's my true nightmare
Weather going to be
I'll be here with you 450
T2 hours
I will say that I could not listen to the toll fee
There was a part of me that felt like
I do it no you are not going to do it circumstances dictated that I could do it
Alex shows back up in the evening
He came in for one reason
Jessie J
A mother top
Reality TV stars ever with gun shows and car shows motorcycle shows
I don't James like 6
And
Been friends for a while
He's working
Like 5 years ago
The Patriot
Call Matt p
I'm ready to come on the show man
So let's do it okay
The evening of the day before the
Noted domestic abuser
Jesse James
Alex is on
Again
Mostly because Jesse James has
Agreed to be on the show and
So I got to interview this celebrity
But also
Rodger
Stone
W to call Lynn
Sure no
Jesse's not there yet he's on his way to that
Rodger calls in and
He has kind of a
Trump might win
Kind of feeling sure
Very much not like
What a f****** loser
Yeah
But you also
If you need evidence
It's that Rodger stone is on the payroll
On November 7th
I present you with this
What is the real state of this and now
Central Time
3 hours and 47 minutes out
Let me say that
And you just pay me to say this shooting
If it were not for brains
Horse right now
I would be completely.
Unfunctional it really use you
Mental Clarity in the Boost of energy when you just got
Evil little more
Amazing
Rodger you're on the team
You're either fishing for a job or you've already been hired
Add a little more
Boulger
So in this conversation with the two of them have I get a very strong sense
Alex
Preparing for a loss
Trump wins though as as as Macklemore mix
The biggest a Puget Sound
Shock
But regard
It looks like
Polly had to me
I want other folks
Regardless it's a huge victory that globalism
Is on its heels
Nationalism is rising
This whole movement
And taking us light
Ears
In the future in our fight against the NWA
So even if he loses we made so much progress
Girl feel good about that
We can take this as a win
We're light years ahead of where we were against the New World Order
In a way
Kind of does make sense though
Alex to be
Freaking out so hard now in
In comparison to 20
16 because this must
Like in 2016 this was like
Oh wow we got Trump but obviously Hillary's
Everybody
It was like obviously Hillary's
So now
It is kind of a situation where they like
Are insane I got in
There's no way this is ever going to happen again
Everybody saw what happens when insane guys in
We got to keep them in there or they're going to keep us away as
Fastest possible
What kind of makes sense in a way
It does seem like
We've got a
Keep the engineer's away or else they'll plug up the holes
Yeah
I don't I don't know how to make sense of it other than like
I just don't think that Alex
Easy guy not win
They love they love Ron Paul he never wins
You're not worried about that I assumed if Ron Paul a Dever one
And then it destroyed democracy he be like
We got to do everything we can
Rompope never winning again man
It would have played out way differently if Ron Paul had one
I guess we would have been baby
Cuba
Alex
Preoccupied with something
And that is Gary Johnson's running mate
Had some positive comments about Hillary
For sure and
So Alex now wants Rodger to denounce
Gary Johnson
Rodger
Rodger and Gary Johnson or past Associates
Donald Trump
The Liberals the Democrat
Sand
Weld openly doing
I think you said the name of the Republic
The human right classy
But I know you were the head of a campaign for a while
Last time Gary Johnson
Was wondering
Toy transporter libertarian
Maybe the man from civilization nuclear war made for the planet
Play the clip and ask you about Gary Johnson
Hey will you do now to
How did Gary Johnson will be proud to take credit like that so Alex keeps pushing on Rodger
Musically
F*** it did outside
This Rihanna
Don't want
I mean
About the
Silly to
I'm really glad you asked
For you
Perfection in Greek
Gary Johnson
Johnson's record as governor of New Mexico
Everybody
Okay
Germania
Alright
All right call it down
I'm Rodger goddamn Stone
Find me diplomatic before I say something awful
Do you understand I am going to s*** on him
Okay I am a s*** head in a top hat
I get away with the s*** had already because I wear a top at
I could sit on his face right now he'll hire me in 4 years
Some Rodger goddamn yeah that is the other thing I get the sense like Rodger thinks that he's going to be employable on the other side of this and
Yes Gary Johnson is a good man his record as a
Working I definitely don't plan on going to
Jail
They have this story that we heard on the
Last 22
16 episode The Anthony Weiner's laptop
Yeah man
It's remarkable to me how eggs
Exactly the same this is with Hunter Biden's laptop
To the point where even
The same person is pushing the story
I'm told
I have told
Former mayor Rudy Giuliani the thief
Files
Solid evidence
Security essentially in some cases
Blackmail files
There are government
Documents
Forwarded
There are all kinds of
Again the same words that I'd heard from other police sources
Cafeteria
Pay for play
Corruption
Sexual exploitation of children again
Extraordinary
Commence pertaining to the
Foundation
It's all just like rerun
Yeah it's just the it's just the same thing
How is that is that must be why Rudy was so mad when everybody was saw that story where like
We've done this before nobody really felt that they knew exactly when we've done this before but we are all like
We've seen this ship
Before this is exact
Believe it it's exactly
Rudy Giuliani has a little bit of
Livermore exciting backs
Yeah that's true
Yeah I mean it's it's
You know you forget about little
Details about
Everything is so crazy and there's so much
Spaghetti being thrown against the wall over and over and over again
Throughout
Do you know the 2016 election
No they said it never has that you forget like
I have Deja Vu always because we did this exact thing
She's a
So at this point Jesse James is still on his way to
Studio Springs in Lee Ann McAdoo
And Joby
Both you are not there anymore
Who have a really important
Purpose
Just thought of Facebook mention
Speaking of that
You know what
By the time I left
And if we did that
The topic was on
The Clinton Foundation because it's one of the top trending things on Facebook
Right now
Messy Leanne
Bragging about traffic
It's a preoccupation
Is such
A goddamn hubris
Schleich
Resignation
We're going to be on top forever
Now Trump's probably not going to win
It's outrageous
The level
Cut out
All the time
The day just
Ramble about there traffic
Assassin
Just like we've destroyed CNN
Droid the mainstream media wear on top
Yeah it is be like we're going to live forever that someone says right before they
Wow off of roof brutal
So in this next play I believe he's talkin
To Jesse James in the middle of introducing him
But Alex has his timeline
Just a tiny bit
I never liked
Like the Democrats
Republicans don't deliver on what
Trump
I mean I don't from like grudgingly
Supporting a meter and a half ago to like
Show route
That I supported this guy
The stamina the work
The attacks
A year-and-a-half prior to this
Would have been
May 2015
By that point
Alex did not say
Support him immediately
Nope little bit if he there he did not really
Support Trump until the end
Search Jesse James
You know I think this is a little bit
A little bit iffy
I think that he's very
Dumb
In terms of some of the things he
She says this might you might be able to take this is racist
Also
I grew up in the hood man I was born in Lynnwood and grew up in
Southgate Long Beach and I was like man to be cool to have a Brothers president you know that's what we need
You know we needed Billy Dee Williams to come in and Lex
This was going to be like you know we needed that
Instead we got
And then everybody realize like
Oh wait he's a
College professor
And it's like
College Prep
Super so great at what they do
How come they're not
Billionaire
Haha yeah man
Haha
Are you I think you can probably debate whether or not it's like a he's not the right kind of black person
The Urkel car
Remember Billy Pilgrim.
You need to watch Star Wars again
No he didn't
Although that would be great
I would say for me
I don't I don't
I don't think I could take anyone seriously
If they were like if teachers are so great why are they billionaires I would I would throw that I would throw that
I want to throw that I find that statement
To be a little bit.
I mean in credit
I mean I could answer him seriously it's like we can protect this is Siri
Please make sure
That would be a good person
Some people I have no desire to
To be billionaires
And some people instead of being validated
Strictly by the
Accumulation of money
Find that living the life where you and Rich other people's lives and
Caton
I helped a guy then
Next Generation
Through
Educational hurdles response
You're a dirty f******
Tommy
I want to be a billionaire but now you're good I've been chastised
That's all it takes so apparently I think Jesse doesn't like tea
Teachers teachers
Cuz they can't do it
Every every college professor when I was in college they're all disgruntled they all feel like everything stacked against them
I mean they're all like
I don't know
According to biography.com
Jesse graduated high school in 1987 and enrolled at Riverside Community College
Jori played on the football team and dreamed of somehow making the leap
From small school ball to NFL
However following two injury-plagued seasons
James quick
Demon dropped out of school
Swimming like look
There's no shame in going
Community colleges of June ologist but like
Attend
Don't pretend that you like
Have this
Broadview and you can sit on professors and disgruntled
Darryl matlick
Don't pretend that you have
Full view of the subject
Community college for
Two years probably mostly play football
Who didn't work out
When you dropped out
Like you didn't have
A full college experience
Do you know Jesus
Like
Alright
If your view of
College professor
At a community college
Spell community
Is that they are all
Everybody's against us and all that stuff
Did it ever occur to you
To stop for one second and think
I wonder if everyone's against
And the answer to that is he
Everyone is against them
And somehow they still go to work to teach your dumbass
Who doesn't care because you're playing Juco
So screw you I've met a lot more professors
Then Jessie had
You're my life
And I will give it to him the most pretty grumpy
But
If you know things you're grumpy
That's just the truth
Is there Grumpy in a fun way
Anyway
I would save this next clip of Jesse does not pass
The smell test
I'm like an aunt
Inure
Of humans and I have the best BS
Whatever I can do
Can I can I can meet someone and like
Know whether they're full of s*** or not
I don't know I don't know man
I don't know if that's
Exactly what you
You say right before you get
Conned by somebody named Alex
Jones
To the media and a lot of
Stuff that
The most notable for in the pub
Lead me to believe you may not have a good BS detector is off
The chart that that's why I trust Trump whenever he says literally everything
Maybe not
So you can tell Alex's voices a little bit weird there
There's a tone change
What it is I think you just
Crashed
Really tired
In the middle of the interview too weird
He almost has like the energy sucked out of him
Describe it but if you listen
Intuit
Entirety
At some point in the middle of it
Feels different yeah yeah that sounds like when the drugs run out
So anyway this is the this is a clip
Felt like kind of
Had that feeling of post
Crash
Low-tax
Prosperity
Great Medical Care on future
Not as coming up
Porto's
When I'm 60 Minutes a Vortec manifold app we've got a clubhouse
And is Leslie Stahl 1999 she goes
You help round up
More than 10,000
Jews in Romania hungry
Apologizing
No I do not
What I need to do
When is this guy is the biggest
Demon imagine
Yeah yeah
That's not true
Are there is that there's a deflation
Should not happen
Comes in
I takes over
And who cares
God
What an All-Star election Eve
However
So many people that are not allowed in
Polite Society anymore or don't work at Infowars anymore Rodger Stone
Yeah it's a wild row of
Of folks were like
Wow this is the faces of Infowars
Yeah and Owen is co-hosting with someone named Maggie who remember who this
Millie Weaver in a wig
It's not I have to look her up she used to work for The Young Turks
No s*** working it in forest
To the Daily. There was an article that was claiming that she was dating Jack burkman
The guy who will work
Jacob Wohl
Let's do it that's a fuk
In career path is what that is yeah
Yeah I don't even remember her she was
She was an enforcer for a cup of coffee out there very long anyway
Towards the end of the night
Late into the evening
This happen
And I wait I think that they probably are glad this happened at a point where to be
Be very hard for someone to
Find it
Or remember that this happened on the day before the election in 26
You get a story about a
The former Comet Pizza employee who is how we got to take okay
In the brainwashed
A fashion
Well folks we have found some
Really damning evidence of some pictures
Alleged
And some alleged pictures we have some strange artwork
I'm from Tony podesta we have some
Satanist to invite
The podesta's to a
Occult
Steak dinner
It appears though I'm we have some
Symbolism being used here with
Pizza and cheese
And it may be linked to a child pedophilia
It does look
Look as though
David Brock has a connection with this
To place owner and at the Obamas are well aware of it
Owens doing pizzagate
Late in the evening then whenever the pizzagate comes out
The pizza guy comes
You might have heard that
Producer is like we got a guy who's
Let's go to is that
Beards and who knows a former employee of kind of pizza
Yeah that's right
Quite a bit
And that we found that a.m.
Is a gentleman by the name of
Call Town
That was actually
Did he work there
That kind of pizza for about a year-and-a-half and he was going to
For pedophilia
What was his name again
Joe poletown is a prank name
That's how I was being used by posters on Fortune
Okay so you can find archived
Threads where people are laughing at Owen
As this episode is happening because
Poletown is a reference to pull
The pool board on 4chan
At least that is the sense that I got from looking through their comments
Hilarious
This is very clearly that guy
The Donald like you from the Donald subreddit
A guy f******
Ansel
Kind of gets
Sad
When Owen
Response to this guy giving him this Intel like this
How did you come across I'm like how did you encounter this person
So we've been we've been just basically going through
Different
Employee
Registration
Find online
Are we Crossing
Information with
Database
Call Town
As actually involved
Well I just want to I just want to
Give you a round of applause because
This is the time
Of effort it takes from We the People Folk
Okay again
I'm sorry I did the FBI call into that show and give us this Intel
Did the Washington Police Department call in and give us his until no
Owen is applauding this guy for pranking
I wonder if they had Jesse James there I'm sure he would have seen right through this prank
Bulshit
It's almost like he's stressing the name it's almost like he can't stop getting that name out
It's almost like a
Beginning every sentence with meow
And if I were
I don't know
Someone is working at an actual news Outlet I wouldn't let someone accuse now
No backup and he no follow-up Kia
Clap
Immediate Round of Applause standing ovation
Do any caller who says anything I want if you don't want to run the risk of somebody you know slandering
A private citizen on your show did you wouldn't
Owens instinct
They're so terrible
They're just the worst
I'll tell you why Maggie's not there any
She asked
Where did you get this information from
That is the end of her career
You are going to need 25
Yeah she she was cleaning out her desk when she
He finished that question
So I mean like look dude
The reality is ons getting pranked
By 4chan
Fine I mean I guess
It is what it is
It's Infowars
You know it's not like you told people to go to Comet Ping Pong
Has the New York Police Department raided this place
Has the FBI
Raider this place
Has anyone investigated, Pizza
Is there anybody planning on investigating, Pizza
Does anybody even know what time it is
On the American people
Don't do anything illegal
Don't break any laws
Tomorrow and start asking questions we like hey you know what this is a place in my neighborhood I like in pizza here
All the sudden I'm seeing this weird stuff going on
You know I'm not sure if I want to be buying pizza here anymore can you guys stand up for yourself what's your relation to David Brock you know the podesta's
Why do we have these emails why is that logo across the street
What's going on at, Pizza
All right I mean Owen told people should go to something with her
Don't do anything illegal today
Get to the bottom of it like the invest it like that
Good competent
Investigators in his audience
I am calling on the America
Can people get to the bottom of it
Questions in a row doing something we will later pretend
He did not do happened
At least you didn't like really stressed
I will give him that
This is how you
Get involved in this fight
This is how you change will think about that
Think about you
You're sitting at your couch
The Monday night its 1 here central time you're sitting on your couch you know
You watching Infowars maybe your
Enjoying
Corner something some chocolate you're just sitting down
Well maybe tomorrow you go to Comet Pizza
And you capture video footage
That changes the world
Okay
That
Is how
You make it impact folks
You get off your Duff
You go out
You make some
Action happen
It look for some answers
That's how you change the world
You
Get off your Duff
And go down
Comet Ping Pong Pizza
Change the world
I would not want that recording
On record the world you know that I said that that would be bad
So here's the thing
Games that tell you find by looking at the day before the election of 2016
I'm still not convinced
Alex was convinced
It's drop was going to wear through I don't think you wanted Trump to win
Did he was a violent it be aware of
The motto
Ization benefits
I'm possibilities if Hillary won
Freak out
It's going really well in that case
Mmm Yeah as the night wore on Owen Shroyer
Decided to get deep into pizzagate and tell everyone to
Why you don't do this
These marathons you can't
These guys
Have a completely controlled area of time that they will not say the worst
Thing that they can
Can say
Just once you let him go on past that
It gets wild early in his career at this point to
Need to get this f***** up this is the end
Infowars is
Maggie's
Fire
Because she obviously asked
The question
Hey
F******
Straight up go there and back
Number two
Alright think we can see how that works this is also something
You know it's kind of difficult to know
How much is real how much
The sense that I get sure but from listening to this
Feels like Alec
And Rodger
Are both
It's kind of like
And then like Joe Biggs
And Owen
Feel like real believe
Do you like Charlie actually convicted
On this path
I totally have no idea what's going on with very ambivalent about the whole
At all
Question which I'm proud of
For tonight's too boring to figure out what he's up to
Yeah this is weird
But I think it was much more productive and much more
More pleasant to look at then
Intuit Ryan
Get something about the present day
Yeah there's another out of context dropped
Just for fun
Walking the dogs around here and I'm like the son of a b****
What
This guy
It gets angry when he's walking the dog is getting a he is a real Dumber level got a relationship with.
He's got to yell at someone when he's out walking the dogs we didn't punch it
Unreal
Everyone out there I hope you're doing well and for our us walks
I hope you folks
Stay safe
Yeah this is your election
I will be back
At the end of the week
Bonus on Wednesday just to have some
To put out but
I just I really don't believe that we would have something productive
Worthwhile to add
By when
Wednesday
To hear about
The president doesn't
Exist until Wednesday
Play for me because
It's just like
So I will be back then
But
Until that point we have website
It's not right.
Yes we're also on Twitter
Find a local charity or bail Fund in your area to help at the zoo
Emilio Emilio
I'm dzx Clark
I'm Daryl rundus
I just want to hear this
And get ready boy fish fry station Simon say it because I mean it
Michael Bloomberg
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work