Soletic
I have great respect for its knowledge B
Knowledge fight
Nike.com
Hey everybody welcome back to
The fight knowledge I'm Jordan bombed
What is a podcast
Get together with my friends and we drink
Familiar Beverages and talk about anybody but Alex Jones
Too bad right now there's pretty all right
Doordash that worships water
Half half water only
Novelty 2A
That's how we all though it's not entirely sure he'll come up in some form or another
That sounds right yeah so Jordan congratulations
Taking the wheel brand of these episode
Probably thinking like
Hey dude when they're just an election what the hell is going on about that whole election deal
Set up front I want to say
Play I think that everybody would expect
Talk about Alex and the election that's why you got to go the entire
Directions
The reality is that
I realize it is that blue 499
So on Monday will be putting out episode 5
100 100
I thought it was only
I thought it was only appropriate
Spiritually that are
Podcast
Was born essentially out of
The election night on Infowars
Really kind of makes some sense that we would have episode 500 be this election
Some kind of a symbolic meaning if we did it
Today feels like we should both be like a bomb should land on us the moment after we
Put out the 500.
I'm trying to imagine like other people do
Who know what they're doing
Ed orgeron
Beige and they figure out what they're doing well before 500 episode yeah probably a lot of people there like we just did 50
Episode
Congratulate ourselves retire
We did it
That will be on Monday
I thought it'd be fun also
It's going to be 500 episodes now have
P-51 the chicken over
And I feel like that's appropriate 1 out of 100 accurate
Idea of our division
Glyburide
And in general
It's possible
Another factor is
Can suffice
No it's still a little bit a little bit
Unclear and I are covered people probably have a lot of better information
As a sorcerer
George Ryan I don't want to add to any confusion or risk
Getting something wrong in the middle of this
Some black sort of Middle Ground on clear kind of thing
Right and I feel like we could just do a much better job
Take a video how are you
To do that but I have a very simple and obvious bright spot
Or listen to it yet but we put out a bonus after
Episode where you did
Incredibly thoughtful and Incredibly nice things
And it was
It was a gentleman beautiful
Sing Anna
Really changed my my day in
The future
What is little less sentimental probably but things are going well with the worms
Bourne Farm is going but better than I thought it would
Actually got a little mini chopper
Do chop up food remain
For just for the worst
Chop up the worms
Two double no no no no no no
I think that's a name
I don't think that you can reliably do that never end
I just think you chop up
The food little smaller than they reproduce they'll they'll breed and then you'll have a large worm colony
And then I'll take over the world
Me and my worms
What is getting me through right now a little bit these nice worms
Exciting I'm not shiting on that I'm just saying that's an unusual thing to be like
That's what's really getting me through I mean pretty weird here
Words strange maybe Hobbies or interest
Anytime you can have a lot of people who were forced
Listen to like
Closer quarters
Are some things will go viral in terms of hobbies like everyone got it just a weirdo
Sometimes there are things that are a little bit less
Like Universal
I think worms are pretty cool
How do I put in bread
What time's right
Whataburger
Today the episode that I've
Prepared for you haha
Is personal it is
2 days
Before the election
Uncle decided
Text me
Clip
From the interweb
Okay all about how
Titled the real reason they want you to hate Donald
Now
Look
They sent that
Each other
Email James my family believes in all that b*******
Whatever go for
Don't send it to
I wanted Tunes like a mistake I wanted to reach through my phone and slap
And while I was thinking about
Reaching through my phone and slapping him I realized that we do what show
And that's maybe the best way to reach through your phone and slap someone right I think yeah
Yeah I think so he sends me a text of like a six-minute video and I do an hour
Hour-and-a-half explaining why he's wrong about every
Passive-aggressive
And that's
So that's what we are going to talk about and then we're
The same person
And also did a video just yesterday
Okay long little
Video about
How the hard-right feels
Right now so we're going to add a little bit of that into it as well
Do you know like his argument about why people want you to hate Trump
Should still stand up
It would
If it were real
I mean I think we'll get to the bottom of that
Being
The case
Before we get to add to that desert something else you need to do I was going to say thank you to some of our
I was about to get to that worried I'm sorry he's going to do the whole
First I'm sorry I was very excited cuz I was thinking about it while you were talking I was like
He's going to be blown away that I remembered to do this well I still haven't even though I even when I stepped on it
Alright billboard
F.e. up helders
You are now policy
We got Mike
You are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy 170
Trading has never been no one has ever accused me of getting an A in calligraphy
That's true
Well some people
Adam Beach
Unapologetically Adam
God dammit
Next we have Elizabeth wur now of Asia
Former presidential candidate Elizabeth Warren
Bet you would donate Morrison
Next we have Jason see you are now
Next we have lieutenant
Wiggles you are now a pollywog
I'm a policy wonk
And finally we have Thomas k
You are now a policy
I'm a policy wonk slept on
Soundbite absolutely and if you feel very very excited and very generous
I knew you would like to donate to our show please go ahead and go to our patreon page would be very happy if you did that
Or what
Could do is you could take this generosity that you feel right
I can put it in a little box
Senior living room
With a little bit of hummus and some coconut core and chop up a little food okay to feed that generosity bench
Shop that generosity in half and now it's to generosity
Give those generosity worms
To a charity in your area show up and ruin it like 30 times
You know what let's see how this plays out
Wrong move
Have you good clearly showed off
I am a failure
Episode
Go back to 500 episode the episode 500 I'm going to be replacing you Garden
With
I don't know if someone insults
And all I could come up with
I don't know why but the person I came up with was Jonny Fairplay hook Survivor
I think it was because I saw his face on Cameo I was scrolling through
I will not be replacing attorney
But yeah. Some people need that would be great
Be fantastic now we are going to talk about one fellow named Michael James
Matt have you ever heard of him
Annabelle
Matte
I don't know about people whose last names are first name
I don't know about that except for any of our listeners who that's the case
Michael Matt is tough
Study hard
But I mean I guess
His whole life
You know a lot of kids are probably
The cruel
I will tell you this I very much doubt that he interacted with too many
Kids outside of his feet
If you will
That'll be a surprise to
Michael J mats
Is the editor-in-chief
Of the I believe
It's called the Revenant
Okay
Christian identity stuff
Newspaper
And see the video that my uncle sent me
He was about the Davos
World economic forum
And he goes into this nonsense about how
Covid is all about how they're trying to do the Great
Reset
And he's doing the conspiracy theories about that
And I didn't want to rehash all of that stuff
Because that was the main thrust
So the little clips
That make you talked about that entire presentation
Find on their website already
Yeah
That nefarious
Normal reasonable
What I found out
In looking into
Was that it was not
The entire thing
Michael J Matt does a like weekly or bi-weekly show or whatever it is
Shocks for about a half hour
About whatever bulshit
He wants
Ramble on about
And whenever I went
Through and
Actually watched
The full clip
It was clear that they
Edited the entire 20 minutes
Down to the
The parts where he talks about Dave
And there's a whole bunch more
So I wanted to talk about why my uncle
Call sent me this
Dumb clip
Without all of the other problem at
And he didn't look into
Whether or not there was problematic Mountain
It's going okay so your position is
Okay alright
This is actually something that's probably
Maybe something we should do a little bit more of on the shopping site at that you came up with this idea
Because there is something to these
He's kind of things that get sent around
The people would like
I hate to say that you're lucky
Your uncle sent this to you but
And I think a lot of people are affected by those things and having a little bit of analysis
I might be something really productive for us
Hit episode 500 plus
But first let's hear a little out of context
It's all good ready to have bubbly person to draft
Michael Bloomberg
Haydn
Is not a serious candidate we can all agree on that right he's not serious
Not very serious enjoy
Enjoy having that little thing right there that was from the August
6 clip that my uncle
And just having that little pea
He's in there knowing what we know.
Is very
It warms my heart
Yeah this is a game like I think we talked about this every now and again took the pro wrestling strap
Energy of like
Building up your opponent while insulting them is important
Death because then if you win or lose you can still look good in Victory or defeat
If the person you're against is not a serious candidate and it doesn't matter and all this s*** like
Doesn't really matter if you win if you lose
It's very sad
And he he spent a long time and what's interesting about this guy
Is he is a far-right
Catholic and
He absolutely
He hates Joe Biden
For being calm
Okay but not the right time
Is he is he a bad guy
No
He's very much a knot
That's what I mean what I said
No that's super and that's where his whole thing comes
Did bold like originates from the schism
That happened because of the Vatican 2
Because they said that the Jews weren't evil
Run into a few of these cats
So the first thing in the in the clip that my uncle sent me I start there
And that 6 minutes is
Cut from
You know
The overall 25 minutes little bits here and there
Is it a presentation in front of people or is it a video he's recording for like a livestream okay
Made into the camera recorded video almost like sort of of
Almost
Exactly like that
He just opens up in this clip
With
Well you might guess it if you're talkin about Dave
Well almost
Just one guy who's got
The power to do something
Stop and you know exactly where I'm going
And I made a mistake
They tried to get Trump on there
Science we invited Donald's
The Davos
A couple of times
But in January when Donald Trump I take really began to see the Beast that he was up
Lexi went to Davos
That's in the world economic forum
And he
Stock a mega finger
In their eyes
Mega thing
A mega
Wow which seems like a terrible
You could have
Tossed Maga finger in there so he's oh wow yeah they could have
Also it makes me think of Dane Cook
Sydney have a mega finger or super finger or something I just remember him doing the leg
He got so many laughs from doing the leg
Alien
That was it
What I remember from Dane Cook some kind of an elevated version
Middle finger and mega finger makes me think of that
And I'm not I don't like either
Is upsetting about
Tossing the money changers
No
The reality is not that they asked him
He's been twice
The first time he went was in
It was
His f****** idea
Of course he just wanted to go
To the globalist headquarters and be like
Didn't kick 2017 Bass
Look at all you dumb dumbs going around there they did not invite him to like
Trick him into any kind of evil
They didn't invite him to be like
Wind when we're having
This conversation
Really be like stay
Globalism
Optical
Your balls a little bit Google
You know that kind of
Enzo
Was absolutely no one
Trying to get on his side
And then as far as
The Whispers
Speech was a
Received
Steve Howard co-chair of the we mean business
Coalition
I told Financial Times that
20 or 30%
Applauded at the
The end of trump
That's not bad. That's not bad
720 is alright there now he said a lot of evil s*** and I feel like at least 40% of them would be on board
Perhaps Perhaps
He's really interesting know you had these people who I was like
Forever demonize any kind of world government
Soar like governor
Body is the u.s.
The EU Davos
Got a particular
World economic forum
So whenever Trump went and was
Appearing to be
Engaging in that process there had to be such a like explanation
For it is going there to take them all down from the inside
Yeah that's always fun weird about it is
He kind of
Did exactly what they wanted him to do a huh
Explain it in a way that
Like they invited him
To trick him into doing the opposite
There needs to be more of a story
There's too much of like he was an ass holy crash their party if your
Enjoy that too
I love the fact that he's a dick just accept it
He's he's
Sticking the finger in the eye of Davos
And this is of course when we get it
Oh do it so let's
Surely after the speech
At the UN
Donald Trump delivered
Why you think happen
The Coronavirus
Was Unleashed on the world
And Trump's booming us
Economy
Went on life's
You think I was an accident
I'm guessing he doesn't
He does not say
Just a pause there is you got it
Speaks volumes after after listening to several of these episodes I've decided
I think it's called like the remnant hours
Like that I've decided to call it
Michael J Matt and the rhetorical
Does that sound right
Does it do you think that I think that
That is very such a soft
Strategy that is that is a very weak
Can you see it you see it around the tub
Could it possibly be
Yeah
Just make a conclusion and stand by it
Don't play this game
I will tell you about something
And this is what I found out
In in my Reese
Search do you know what else
What happened on the
The same day
That's Trump gave that
Let's see let me see if I can guess
The first trailer for 10
It came out no no no I believe that was already out in like 28 I don't know
Commercials
Tony Shalhoub won an Emmy over Stephen Roots hell yeah and that is why we have
I can tell you that right now what happened after that
Do you think that was an accident damn this is tough for me because I like both of those guys I like Stephen Root and I like
Shalhoub
Marvelous mrs. maisel over Stephen Root for anyting, I know man Shalhoub
Has Stephen Root ever won an Emmy
I don't know
He deserve at least one at least one a lot of good work in his career
Yeah that stuff needed for like man in the High Castle
I make more sense
Yeah that's probably that any decision was probably what they do
I think so covid
I think that's just what happened silly
So do you think that was an accident
Yeah
No
What
So it's such a b******* cop out
Hate that
Especially for people who purport
To be like I'm the mouthpiece
Piece of f***
But I don't have the balls to even say what I want to say
Well if you see out of a lot of people who don't want to be nailed down to specific
Like things because if they do then they have to own it they have to argue it they have to argue the implications of it
And that can be kind of tough they can be kind of unpleasant a lot of people don't like doing that
It hurts people's feelings
Wednesday app
And
So he starts off with the
Rhetorical question
He gets even f***
Hello again ladies and gentlemen Michael Matt coming to you once again for the offices of the run the newspaper
Here's something you're not at
To hear on mainstream media
Probably 18 million people in the world
Coronavirus
10 point
6 million
Have recovered
You feel hear numbers like that yeah I forgot
Those first two were from the 6-minute
Okay
They were the ones about
I was confused why is there a commercial break or something
That's the start of the actual show
Okay we start soda
This is August 6th
This year
So
That was back whenever the total number of
A cursory Google search
Would be like
How many cases
Does are there on August 7th
18 belly
How many people have recovered
10 points
What is that f******
What you know
Like
No you can see
Subtract those numbers
The other thing that you might as well say that
Here's what you want here in the heart rate m
Of the 18 million people who are infected with covid
7 point
4 million have not recovered
Yeah same thing
Said a cyst in the other direction
Yeah that's some
I always I always wonder about that they the impetus to insist everybody's covering up everything that is just readily of
Available information
Yep I don't know
It seems strange here's what it said the first thing he says is
This here's what you won't hear from the mainstream media
And you absolutely will can and are often hearing it from the main
All the
And then as of today
There's about 49 million
It's okay and it's only going to f****** go up
So you
Gives a s***
Are you a doctor well
Is there you go
If you are a doctor I'd listen to you over this guy but you're not so
Would you like to know more about this guy you think you should listen to this guy after what I tell you I mean it's not going to shake my trust and
Well I will tell you that he is the editor-in-chief of the remnant
A far-right
Catholic newspaper out of Minneapolis
Minnesota
Newspaper
Was
Created
When two brothers got into a fight
At The Wanderer
Wow those good things
Come out of that if everything
Is the United States oldest
Catholic news
It was started all the way back in like 18
And in 1899
A man named Joseph
Took over as editor-in-chief no relation
Dare Wonder
Wouldn't that be lovely if there was no relation
So
It was originally German language only
Hey it wasn't until 1931 that Joseph
If Matt made it in English
Newspaper
And the reasons are not Jose
It was his son
Walter
Who took over the editorship
In
And
Over over that time
It went from being this
Very small German Castle
What newspaper that
Maybe three thousand people of red
Do something that went
Worldwide
Mainly because of
Steve
Early
Hatred of the
So even in the 1930s
Joseph Matt
A a a
You know German
Was just out here telling people to avoid
He's a worst dude in the world
He was antifa
He was killing it to the point where f****** Mussolini had
Pravda really some like faith
These guys The Wanderer absolutely
Some serious s***
And then
Vatican 2
I am so
Walter
And his brother Alphonse
Who were both working
Walter being the editor-in-chief at
The time Alphonse working at
The Wanderer
Decided that
One of them
Really was fine with Jews and non-catholics
Extend the other one
Not fine with using not sure
And so
Walter Matthau
God created the
Which was a newspaper that basically exists only to tell you
Why the Jews and non-catholics a refund
Oh boy
The Pope
No one who is Catholic
Is Catholic to the red
The case with a lot of those
The folks who
Believe that they did the Vatican is now invalid
Except for
Our friends group
Everything we are the only ones keeping
In the fire
Isn't it I always find it amazing how
Solid a voting Bloc
Christians are
Quote unquote Christians are
When if you
Like get granular
They hate each other more than anyone else
There's a lot of infighting
Between sack
That is true
Because a lot of it for the people who get
Who does mortify tsp
Vivitar very apocalyptic
They're very into the fact
Or the idea that they have that it's going to come down to
Popular games
They they
Yeah it is very it's very much
Important that your groupie the one
It has the right idea.
And the tradition is
The traditionalist Catholic
Pixar
Nut bags
Walter Michael J map
Took over after Walter map
From the remnant
And of course
Michael Matt
What's first cousin
The Junior
Is editor of the Wonder
So these guys are third-generation
Catholic b******* newspaper
Editor but also vicious
Austin Minnesota
Oh wow
That states not big enough for these two newspapers I don't know
Has been labeled a hate Group by the splc
I think the smart money is on this guy to be correct
So
Keeps going on about covid
And this is all in the full video the stuff that
You know you don't get
Email address
Friends with Avatar
I mean let's be really clear right from the outset
Covid-19 is not a hoax
Okay
Worldwide over 650,000 people mostly elderly halves
Succumb to it
This is not a hoax
Even with skewed death reporting which we know is going on all over the
The place
This is a very serious virus
Okay
You got you got to give it up to him
Whatever is right now you do numbers look they're all going
To say that but at least he's on the
Take this season actual thing
This is a serious
It's not like
Applaudable that's just a demonstration of how
Far out like so many of the people that we talked about our
We're looking at him and he thinks it's a real virus is notable
Yeah the only thing
Credit where it's due for the harbor
Widow with the low bar that we're dealing with
Then how long do you think that credit
Maybe this next clip
But so was the H1 N1
The swine flu of 2009
Which claimed the lives of a
Half a million people
So was the Hong Kong flu of 1968
Which claimed the lives of up to
Million
People
Flu is a nasty business
Have you remember these
Previous epidemics pandemics probably not why because the media
Didn't freak us out over those
The Country Wasn't shut down
Healthy people were not quarantined
Schools weren't
Close
Church services
Weren't cancer
Sure
Sure it's a real
We've had viruses in the past
Remembers them
I think people do
I mean I'm sure if you related to one of those 500
Thousand people
Oh I remember that one
He just went through it that's not even get it I'm ever h191 I didn't
I don't know anybody
Off the top of my head
They got sick but
What is point
Exactly
His point is
The media it's nothing to worry about Serie media making everything right
So I looked into those and as far as H1
He
Kind of
He's misrepresenting things a little
The CDC total is in
Estimate that gives it
Between 140
N500,000
So
That's a pretty wide margin to just assume 500,000
Sure
Even more
Maybe to his
Beat United
How about 12,000
Nodal
From
H1n
So if you want to say why don't we remember those
Because it didn't lay waste
Why why didn't we respond the same way to those it's because different decision for event
Viruses exist and we did a much better job
Haha just frankly overall width
Contact tracing with
With every
Taken serious from
Within two weeks of the first H1 N1 case in the United States
It was being absolutely attacked
Now the 1968
Quote
Hong Kong
If he calls
Which is
Is racist then as it is now but you know
That one is actually kind of interesting and also
Instructor
In terms of this types of
So it was actually a strain of bird flu called h3n to
Two-story actually begins in nineteen
In
The southwestern province of Guangzhou
H2n to broke out
And by 1959 over a million people had died
Hey between Asia and
A vaccine was created
In just two years
And the outbreak was dimmed
But even in 19
Ireland had to close schools
Britain recommended quarantine
C8
Finally
The
H3n to
The h2n to
Created a new
It basically mutated it it reconstituted
Itself right into h3n
And this was
Maybe the first
Website that when
Global
Because of
Air travel
The first dryer is not website
I'm losing my mind it's alright I was
Is reading the the next note while I'm there I'm not I'm not good at reading notes while talking at the same time
Websites can go viral so I feel like I understand where the
So yeah that one
Went crazy
Now here is what happened
When h
3M
To hit the United
From the National Library of Medicine website
All 50 states experienced increased School abs
Absenteeism during the
Pandemic
Make sense 23 face school and college closures
31 saw elevated worker absenteeism
All of this stuff
Was
Chronicled
Tentatively
In every newspaper where their work
Obvious
Ali College closures
Business has slowed down
People were screaming about threats to Christmas mail people were screaming about the
Economy and how this is all going to happen
In December Apollo 8 astronauts in Apollo 8 astronauts were vac
Fascinated
From getting a space virus
The whole f****** thing
All of this
Even during that time
President Lyndon B Johnson
At one point he was hospitalized with a respiratory infection
That could be called
The flu
All of this stuff
As described by the New York Times
As one of the worst
Pandemics in the nation's history
And we responded in a lot of very similar ways it turns out
All of that stuff
Was was done and it was done in both kind of a half-assed way and in very serious
Say that the media did not freak out about
Would be
Wildly
Yeah yeah
This guy is bad point exactly
Furthermore
3 + 2
Was reported after multiple
Do you have a mortality rate of about
Half a percent
Covid
Overbuff
Average
Is about five times higher
And at high risk
Community category
10 times higher
There's so much
We know more now than we did six months ago or whatever but there's still a lot of unanswered
Questions about stuff that makes it much
More difficult than a lot of things that are much more closely related to a flu
That we have
A lot more history of
Of being able to
Have an event
Some treatments weather
But the things that I keep
Keep going back to
Is
And this is the thing that I
I just wish more people would understand
The quote
Hong Kong flu
Didn't start
Until 19th
But it mutated from it
A different virus
In night that started in night
1950s
So whenever people talk about immunity and all of this s***
All of that nonsense
It's like
This is not about just
Today how about just
Visvi
This
This is not something that we can allow to continue to prop
Navigate simply because it's
Going to adapt on its own
Exactly
How they survive longer you f****** allow it to roam what is now essentially on check
The more we
Almost certainly guarantee that
There's going to be another pandemic shortly
Yeah yeah
That's just how handling works
Give rise to higher in
Higher likelihood of
Pandemics if if not
Dealt with appropriately
I can't back that up with any any research because I'm just talking off the top of my head
Welcome to my job by Brent
But I really don't know if it's true
Conversely I don't like it
If you're very untethered
Despise having to know what I'm talking
Think about it's really freaking me I come if you a little bit more secured but
So yeah
Why don't we remember stuff like that
Because assholes like this dude just say
Why don't you remember instead of
Going back in talking
And talking about how they're these parallels
And things that we can learn
From Oliver
Coming to right now
The people don't remember these
Yeah yeah
There's a big difference between remembering
That something happened that actually understanding what happened
In a report like this
Little bit I remember the name
I don't remember what we did
But it seems like the media probably wasn't all that up in arms about it super freak out
Let's move on
Okay that's a good idea
Which case
This is something I would like to move on to Dan pika
In this situation I am going to need your help
Everyone with a pulse nose
Joe Biden can't do this job
What's he doing there
In my opinion he's
The personified Monument
To the US Presidency that the mob will
Tear down in January
They need to reset everything
Including the politics
Sub United States the governance of the United
Midstates
Besides that old
Joe the Catholic Bible
Is always been a new world order guy
The affirmative task we have now
Is is 2 actually
A creator
Anu
World Order
Oh boy
Oh no
So here's a here's the thing
Alright I understand what he's trying
He's trying to say biting is bad
Yeah
What is he actually trying to what is he actually saying
He's saying the Joe Biden
Sucks either bad kamp-rite is why they're running him as a sacrificial lamb
Once he becomes inaugurated to be taken down will take down with it
The entire
3-part
United
States government
Imbalances
Check up with words government create something better probably
Some kind of demonic socialist
Organization
12 workers
He is not
This is
Is completely out of left
This is in the middle of him talking about
All of the
Covid
Get your ready for Biden
To come in and then
Get him take
Can down
And then completely changed the United States
Send to
Helltown Venezuela or whatever the right-wing likes to yell about
I just don't
Is the statue that they're going to
To take down
And he's trying to say if you're if you're right he's saying that the mob
Yeah the left
Allah has chosen
Him
To then take him down
No
No their establishment
Has chosen him because he is vulnerable to being take
Down by the mob
Who the establishments order controls but maybe they don't sometimes if we need them to not
He'll be so weak
Take that the mob will take him down
And the establishment Will Forte
Okay so that's the real reason they want you to Hector's become
What are you f****** talking about
I don't know why would anyone run a candidate
Well I mean like I would also say
I'm sick and tired of hearing these people who have
Eclipse
Of them saying the words New World Order
I do not find this a compelling argument at all
Play New World Order it's all if any fee says that they're like it's the one that we want
Create they would make the argument that I would make
About everybody talk about a world order that is not
The same as the old
Way of
Things being organized alliances
Tension
Things like that pink disagreement
It's between country exactly new way of ordering
Bring the world
Collaboratively
Cooperatively that's what they would say if Trump saying
Passwords
Assertive benefits
No not very dumb always been New World Order
Totally as opposed to Trump who is never a new world order guy because he's always wanted things to stay
Exactly the same
I believe that Corn Pop
Actually got to abiding into the New World Order
Really that's what I understand that's his other got this guy's other speeches iHeart
Ducted him he did speak at a trump rally may have said that one that one.
Hellboy
So he tosses that out there and then almost immediately goes
Right back to
The great reset
Then politically economically it wants to implement massive
Socialist
Program so course global
Climate change
Along the lines of the green New Deal
The regulations
The unbelievable
And no one no country
Will be allowed to opt out of
What is why
William individual country
Apps out
The great reset
They're going to be endangering the whole world Community the whole world
Future pandemics it will be
Because by climate change
Al Gore says
Hanover population
Says Bill Gates you see how it works
No country
Will be allowed
To opt out
This is what we're facing in November
So this is what covid is
Creating
Cuz it's attacking
Every kind
Right every no country will be allowed to off
Right that's the idea behind all of this
And just because you say something with
The funny voice
Doesn't mean it's not still true
Like
There's no agreement and I'm sure that whatever agreement they do wind up working
Yeah but they
It's a terrible idea
Yeah
Because it's a global
The entire and this is something that we learn from 1968
Talking about air travel
It goes
Every
All of this stuff goes everywhere which means everywhere has to
To fight against
Yeah things that are human constructs
Can't fight things that are just real
Like a border can't fight
A disease
You know like even if you have
Even if you have a tightly-controlled wall and everything like that
Still vulnerabilities that you have you know you're never going to be able to
Completely
Insulate
Yeah totally
And there you are
Like whenever they talk about how we need to
Deal with climate change in order to keep all of these things
Taking care of that is also going to have to
Be a global effort
You nobody can opt out
Pollution here effect
Places that other than here
Absolutely
So
Just cuz you can't just be like
Oh yeah everybody has to stay in there and then be like okay well then
You got me
Yeah I mean I guess if what he was talking about was some kind of alike authoritarian rule of the planet
I guess I would probably be opposed to that
But if it yeah if it's just
Working
Together working together to fight climate change
I don't think that there's a real problem with centralization
Unified response
I don't see that being the same thing the wavy
These guys do
Absolute
And we're all we are
Climate change
Pandemics
All of the stuff
And I was going to ask I want to ask you a
Do you think
Think that the cats
Church is going to put
Me
Probably not
Anything the cat
Catholic Church
Is going to protect you from what
Coming from this globalist
Take over
Nightmare
Think again
We've been through all this
Leaving aside pachamama
Leaving aside laudato C
Which is the encyclical
The globalist
16 cyclical of the United
He's using the G word oh yeah
Yo we're talkin about globalists
Guess who's one of them
It's the pope buddy
As soon as soon as people started calling him Culpo
News 12
And if you
Do you know what pachamama is
I was a little bit lost
For a minute for the love. Tosi
Please
Explain so pachamama whenever he just tosses out pachamama I really
Struggled to figure out what it was that he was soaked
Concerned about
It seems my radar is up for something about
Here's what's going on
In 2019 in October
There was a
Indigenous prayer service
In the Vatican Gardens
Okay
And in that
Vatican guards
There was brought a an Amazonian female fraternity
Fertility
Names
Okay and it was just there
And that of course was the signal to everyone that the pope was actually a pagan
Andaz
Is been trying to destroy the church from the insides checks out
Yep yep I got to say they've done their homework.
And then the love. Tennessee
Was an encyclical from the Pope
In 25
And
An encyclical is something that's been
An added to the church
Executive order
Sickly yeah
Says it because
The pope is the mouthpiece
God if he's saying it
Well it turns out that believing that the pope is the mouthpiece of God is not something that Catholic
Looks really do
They're not really fans of that whenever the Pope
Disagrees with
So
Dlive. Tosi was essentially this
I'm going to sum it up for you very very
You know all those reasons that you and I think the world is f*****
Instead of having religion fights
Science over
What are widgets
Okay
How'd that go
I'm fine
With that
Michael J Matt and his friend
Instead heard that and went
Witches
Science witches
I'm so all of this stuff
Again
Not really in the video that
My uncle sends around
Through this guy that he's a weird Auntie papist Catholic
Who's been fighting against
Including Jews in like
Public
Spaces for his entire life
You would want to hide
Because you're trying to get this person the mess
Message out
About
Davos
A little bit different is
And so we continue on
Francis has already announced the global economic reset of his own last
You're I don't know what makes this man thinks it's Anthony's in a
Economist
I don't know where he learned all of this town and Argentina but he's an amazing guy he knows everything but
Theology
I didn't notice
All that close of attention so I hadn't notice
Well I will tell you one reason
That
Is knows a lot more about the
Michael J Matt
Princess back
Used to be cardinal bergoglio
All right before 8
And he was
The cardinal
And he was the Archbishop
Venezuela
During the
A f****** car
Collapse
Whenever inflation went in so he did it
I didn't do it okay
Venezuela
Is mentioned
I am sure he is
I wonder why
So the reason that I will trust him far more than
Michael J Matt
Is because when all of that one
Cardinal bergoglio
Oglio
Decided
F*** all of the Trap
I'm going to live in a small home
I'm going to walk to work
I'm not going to take a f****** limousine
When everyone around me is
So I will immediately trust somebody who is willing
To supper along
More than
Damn near anybody
It seems to be a good
Indicator of
Yeah it seems like
There was somebody really important
Into the Catholic Church who
Spoke almost exclusively about doing stuff like that
Yeah he's really important
Into I can't remember his name
Nobody took my tell somebody was like that's the only way to get to heaven
If you have all those trappings you're never going to heaven or whatever the f***
Who said that somebody really Thomas Jefferson Airplane
That's the end of that August show that's what I'm going to play from there obviously you can guess the Davos hits
Zoroaster
Go ahead with the great reset it's really interesting because you have this
Staying about the world economic forum
And a lot of like ideas about
New technologies in Waze
Is that they can be implemented to help with climate change and things like that
And meanwhile you have the people who are like the really
Paranoid conspiracy types
With d like a
The global economic reset nesselrode jasirah stuff
BBQ communities
And I don't think that they think that they're talking about the same thing
But they're playing with the same idea
They're playing their paranoia comes from a very similar place
I think that's really it
Wearing a suit
And the other has a sign it is yelling on the corner
And I bet it's pretty much the same
The same b*******
Just packaged in different ways for what audience that you're looking
This guy
There you go that's how it works
That's the end of that episode end this next one that I pulled clips from is from
What would that be Wednesday November
Number for hot off the press
Absolutely and I've watched a bunch of his
Is videos in
He operates very similarly to Alex
More boring
And what he does is
He just says a long series of like
Buzzwords
And then ask
The rhetorical question
Shannon that insinuates that you already know the answer
And then just moves on really really quickly
To the point where
Whenever I was cutting clips from this
If you look at the wave violin any player it's almost none
There are barely any brake
Where you can cut stuff out of there it's just almost like
Good cardio
F****** going
And so you get stuff like this
Actually there's a lot of good to consider
You know right now it's
Just seems so dark nobody wants tacos
About it but
You know over over the Long Haul to the Past
Couple years we've been
Spending a lot of time
Talking about this idea of
Gettel Chrysler
Society turns its back on Christ
Well chaos is an adverb
Understood thing my friend sent me right now we're seeing through Atwood living right through that
Is playing out in dramatic
Fashion in fact
With this election
And I'm not going to tell you that
Channel I can prove it
The Democrats are absolutely cheating their way into the White House and on the ground I don't have any inside dope anymore than you do
I can say this about the
He looks that way and at the very very least
You know we can say that we know
They came up with a mail-in ballots
Scheme that turn the election in Joe Biden's favorite right we can all agree on that has think about that for a minute
Let's think about it let's think about that for a minute
Dan
Haha all the things that he just
Just posted that
I think I got stuck on the chaos or Christ
Fairing
I think that's where I kind of
Remember
To remember every society and history
Whenever we go back to history every single one that's turned away from
Any society that sort of a different religion
Just character than Christian
Certainly
Always chaos
They were born turning away from Christ
Find me that kind of
That kind of
Mentality is pretty
Incompatible with
Cooperation
And it's definitely not something that you would
Icy ground
Alternative
To your religious belief
Being Universal is chaos absolutely
And then remember that his religious beliefs
Is
Hating everyone in
Including cat
That's true
It's going to be a problem
Then what's a mail-in ballot
What's game other than
People mailed in there
Ballad sound like
No it's just it's just
You can mail them in or you can walk
Yeah that's something that's always kind of like bum me out as I
You know that Republicans can vote by mail today
This isn't something that the left is doing
But nefariously to only benefit themselves
It's to help people vote in a difficult time you're the ones who made it a virtue signal to not vote
Blaming others
Foreboding
That's a little bit silly guy's
Absolutely not
And well you know
Making it more
Possible for people to vote
Is
Okay
All right of course
You know that whole like
It's obviously
They stole
I can't prove it I don't know
Of course the only evidence
But he provided was
Democrats allowed people
Do you watch them Infowars
Exactly
I halfway put this
Send here just
Just for pasta
Okay
How to things had to be done in other words in order for
Old Uncle Joe to win
And imagine if things were turned around and we were
Imagine if Donald Trump had devised
An eleventh-hour
Ballot harvesting skiing at suddenly put him in the lead
You think that maybe people deal with set about that in them in the media are they
EXO
It's fun to imagine
How do you think he will react
If that
Well guess what I would think it's like if like
But you know if everything has gone slightly differently
Trump
Even as a president that I thoroughly don't like and don't trust
We saying hey we got covid-19 going around this is really serious
Situation
We need to find ways to make voting more accessible and safer for people
To ensure that were able to carry out the election
I wouldn't think
He's trying to steal it by way of
Expanding access to ballots. Like I don't
I don't know Akiva I hate him
And I would still
Yes probably what you got to do you're just doing nothing that makes sense everything else you did was evil but
This one makes sense
People need to be protected as best as possible
Right hand
People need to vote
So if you're doing that
I still hate you
But that's cool keep doing that
No
Imagining that we are talking about Matt
Scenario wherein
He actually does
Find some
Scheme to steal the election at the eleventh hour
Do you think Michael mad is going to be like
Hey I don't like these schemes stealing votes and all that sex spec they won't be schemes at that point
W honest-to-god ballots I'm sure I'm sure
So
Real real organic folks
Coming out to
Protest the Democrats appeal
Mass last minute
All of that stuff
I just I just want that there just
Just for when it does happen
And I can just
Pull that up
Alright
And so he
He does his similar rhetorical question that assumes the answer and Brooks
All over it
And the other thing is I mean does anyone
Question
Let this
Party of death
The party that campaigns on the right
It's the fundamental right to
Terminate the lives of unborn babies anybody question that such a party would indeed cheat their way into the White House
If they thought they can get away with it
That makes no sense
Like
Just promised structural standpoint of an argument that makes no sense
I believe them to be evil because of Reproductive Rights
Therefore
They would steal in the like
They would do anything
His argument is
If you're fine with abortion
Then you are already
Free guilty
Of anything I suspect
I willing to make that argument based on nothing that you could do it
And then and now that's
And this is another one of those situations where Larry Nichols
I never said that Hillary killed anyone
But
Atlanta saying that she has the kind of personality where if someone did get killed should be upset of
About it no
Alright
I've decided that they would steal it
Okay cool
What else what else do you got
Hateful see what that would be more that's
Way more fun than
The way this dude is
True true true
That's it
So this clip is
A good example of like
One of those situations where he just Rambles along
Without stopping so there's no
Real place to like
Cut in cut out without
Losing a bunch
So I'll just say that after he says all the things
After he says that
Because Democrats are fine with abortion
They
They are
Willing to steal anything
And then he list
Several examples of other things
That they would be willing to do if you want including murder and yes Foster
The whole thing and it's so long and I just don't want to
Deal with it
So then he
Stop doing that and we get to his
Essentially what they're preaching
Is it doing whatever we want to do should be
Come the whole of the law
Oh
Which is the essence of satanism
So when you think about it in that
Play the big news
Today would be if the Democrats didn't cheat in these elect
They are baby killers
Of course they're cheap
So we've gone from
Of course they I believe they would
What would you say what would you assume I didn't do it
Oh yeah yeah their sickness to do what thou wilt
Some point there has to be a goddamn Crowley reference
Absolutely
Play Fool boy and that's just
It's just so like
They are baby killers
The end
Like you have no room for any
There's no like
Hey what's your tax policy
Nope you're a baby killer
So graduated income tax
Get the f*** out of here
It's just that simple
These people
And that is
Terrifying
Yeah yeah
I know it was
And as far as other things that terrify me
Try this
Can I try it on
Please do
But we still won
In the long-term the long run
Trump has remade that
Pathetic Republican party for which I refuse to vote when they were running
Romney and McCain
Tobacco back in the day
He's turned that Republican party into a pro-life
Proguides
Pro-family Pro Blue Collar working American party
They took the
Best shot now
From George Soros in his millions and his menu
Set the best shot these guys had to offer
Guess what
We're still standing
They're still debating this
After all of that
Evil laugh
The Adria League
Yeah it's upsetting
And furthermore
The things that he listed
He's turned the Republican Party into a pro-life pro-family right
Antivirus like that whole thing and I'm just go pro working class and I'm just sitting there going like
The party that
It sent in several hundred thousand people to death
Is pro-life
The party that separates
Children from their families
Is pro-family
And the party that is absolutely destroyed the working class
Within no interest in any kind of stimulus package
Anything along those lines no interest in doing anything good
Is the party of the working
In class pretty silly that's what these people think
I think they're what they think
Is that
Well I think what they don't
Nightcore they don't realize
Is that Trump has become
That to them because they did that
They created this projection that they've applied to him you got it and I think that Trump is such a like
A dick and a blank slate
In terms of any real
Seemingly any real care about anything able to do that whatever works the best
St Liams into whatever seems
Forget these damn dogs excited he's like make America great wasn't that fun
He doesn't realize that
Trump is his candidate because
He's so vapid and he is even able to mold him into what you wanted
It's one of the reasons why the last just disappointed with Viber
Is because he's not
Like an empty
That's a really good point that he has things that disagree with some of the political beliefs
Of people were more to the left
And that that's
That it if he was just an opportunist
Electron
He might
If one more handle it yeah that's probably true
That's a really good point
Man he should have just lied
Baby killer
Was killing a baby at the
That would be that would
Probably been assigned but
What are you
Damn
I think as we all know from listening to Alec
What's that if Biden
Officially takes
Texas election
God will have been
Correct
I mean I think it's gray but
Yeah it sort of
Plan will be put
Backward
Or something
Atleast defeated God in this bad
Be at the pole
Now
Do you think he's defeated God probably
So maybe we're going to lose this election
Chicks and cheating on the other side but that won't change the fact that we
Put the world on notice friends don't forget this
Just tell the spreader
Spread this around we put the world on notice
But God is not dead
But he lives in Ox that he lives in our families that he lives in our unborn children
That we will fight to the death
For him and
Brandy politician for anyone who's willing to
To call out his name
In the face of an eel
Pagan world
God's Not Dead was that movie right over the Kevin Sorbo
That sounds right
Absolutely
It's good to know that God is officially Not Dead
Put on notice by people like
Just got absolutely and I ate
It's freaking me out that
He's doing a little bit of what we
I have conjectured that Alex was doing at the end it was trying to pull off at the end of
16 election
It was a moral victory
Trump brought all of this to the Forefront and we got this moral Victory sure we didn't win this election but
You have to redefine things
Now I honestly don't think that is a uniquely like
Like these guys kind of
No no
There are
Piano
Electoral victories that don't go your way
Or electoral contest
Sometimes you do have to look down ballot
And see you later
Well yep
That didn't go our way but some other stuff cuz it's pretty interesting got through and
Some candidates to be excited about her there
I think that's a normal human thing doesn't work that well when it's the battle between good and
There is that kind of has a disconnect
When it's just an election
It's just like
Hey you know I don't like this candidate I'm more comfortable with this one
You can kind of
Take solace in some victories and they will get some more work done next time
Sure I don't think you should do that when it's
The devil
I mean when you say literally
My opponents are baby killers who will do anything because
If they're capable of that
Then you can't trust them
Ever
Anything
And you're willing to die for any politician who says the word Christ
Unless they're Democrat in which case they can't possibly believe how
Then they're lying absolutely
So it's difficult
It's difficult to like a play the
Do you like soda
Normal
Rational games when you elevate things to an irrational left
That's very strange to me
And I think you could pull that off
It is much better
If Trump had never won
Now that heat now that we are where we are
About how Trump is and isn't going anywhere
You know like this is a great example of that kind of
Thought process
That's because it's literally
It's not just
We lost this election
And we're going to
It together and take care of
It's
We're ready to kill for him and we are ready to
To die for him
Yeah but we're not going to
Probably going to
Psychic control of the insanity
We've completely lost it and it's time for a holy war
It's that that isn't effective
Tool that we can use
To further our political goals
And further whatever a business is at for like people like Alex totally
You know that season is over or whatever if Trump loses
Then you do have to go back to a more restrained like sure
Victories we've got destroyed political correctness or whatever
Do you have to do that and your total
It wouldn't be so much better for everyone
In that Griffey Community if trumpet never one
Because then they could
Keep playing
Like it made more sense
2016 reloading Alex play the sort of
You know hey you even if they steal it Trump's till 1 and you know it's great we can hang our head high
That made sense
Then it does not make sense
Yep it's going to be
Difficult move
When you
Basically said the West
Western Civilization is over
It's hard to go back
Okay it's over but not if we win
4 years
That's how it works
It's over by the midterms
What
Enter your boy let's start talking about moral victories Dan what do you
Do you think is the most
Impressive thing Trump has
That's interesting
I don't know myself in that
Mindset
I know for Alex but then he always goes to his he got out of the TPP
So I guess maybe that or the Paris
Record sure
I don't know something about
I think the answer will surprise you
Paula white-cain Maybe
Is he also showed
Christ wins elections
Music Christian
Can win elections in America
It's just amazing
Friends
Amazing day
Christian
In the United
That's amazing
Now admittedly
Literally every president
Has been a Christian
Sure
One of them was Catholic but he disagrees because he was fan of
Vatican 2 aha election
Recent
I heard a big the Christian voters can win the
Haha that's what I heard from
OKC straight up
Christians can win election
Okay did you talk about as a candidate
Yep not voting blocks
Oh yeah
Weird
Yeah that's even weirder than weird it was the way I heard it
Estranged
Strange things
Yeah I like literally
Most people in the United States
Have been Christian throughout our
That's a sizable voting Bloc
A very sizable
So
That's in
Same
That's insane
But
You know Dan
Because of trump
That you know Christians weren't afraid but now that might be president
Could be afraid then do you think
New to big
I don't know if you're doing this just to like intentionally asked me a bunch of rhetorical questions
Thank you for catching up with me
Stylistically
But it was the whole idea as annoying coming from you
That is if anybody can prove how annoying questions
Who could it be better than
I think you'll be scared
And being afraid is nothing new for us heck I grew up as a child of the
The Cold War
Were the Communists were putting millions of
People to death
In gulags all over the world we always thought they were going to come
You know
We're hiding out in the woods at the time you should preparing
You don't learn how to shoot
In Huntington
And defend ourselves worried about the communist
We grew up that way
You are still growing up that way I actually played this clip immediately
We just because I feel like this confirms or at least adds to the evidence
Inside of one of your main Theory
About all these right-wing dogs like sort of emotional
Scar ripples
Of the Cold War
Traumatic 2
These folks
I don't actually have a full theory on why that is
To what extent that explains a lot of this stuff
You know it's the same way that like every single person that is an expert on Alex's show or on one of these other shows
Will mixed up in a rom-com
Every single person
Is involved in Iran Contra
And it's
It's kind of the same you scratch any of these right-wing
Hard right guys
There is going to be Sonic
Extreme feelings about the Cold War
And
Very strong
Assistance
But it is still going on McCarthyism was cool it's great
Why shouldn't people be blacklisted for being Jewish that makes perfect sense to him
Yeah there is yeah it is
In end in much the same way that
Slavery and the
The aftermath is an untreated wound in the American psyche I think the cold war is another one
I think it's another one where
We lost our mind
Not everyone distrusted each other
Unsustainable
Like we never really dealt with it
I think that society would go a long way if week
You could figure out ways
To deal with these things as opposed
Repressing them and getting angry
And feeling guilty
I or projected guilt
Beginning of that stuff I think we'd be better off
Amber
Unfortunately I don't think we're going to do that I mean you see it you see exactly that
Kind of idea is
Because we haven't
Because it saves
Still open wound so many people are also susceptible
To the same anti-communist prop
Opaganda like what do you think this got do you think this guy is a Pez dispenser
Oh yeah
Of course he is
Like all of these guys
Just
Have that same
Propaganda
In their back pocket
Get it all time and it's always
Effective
So that's that's basically this is our last clip and I think I'll open it with
One more rhetoric
Flash mobile app
Should weirdo Chris
Jim's be discouraged
Don't be discouraged
Trump's not going away anyway
And neither I
The pickups
Trucks in the flags
And the boats
And the millions of Americans who are
Absolutely woke
To the New World Order
End of the Demons
Set want to build it
Thanks to what happened over the
Course of the past
4 years in God
Providence
Has a lot of words
Yep Providence
Beautiful boats
You got it
When when you said should weirdo Christians be discouraged I thought it was an interesting question
Because you know
The way I heard from you what should they be discouraged
From being
Weirdo Christian
Should I be discouraged in terms of
What's going on in the world
Today feel like
Yep I have completely
That's why they're so question too dangerous
Here's differ
It was a rhetorical
I think
Yeah it's probably going away
Everything's losses I don't think he has much relevance
He's just a prop
Do deer like
The people who
Support is movement anyway
It's just up to some more competent
Brightwing assholatu step-in
And take that mantle that's why I am
Because
He's right
Those trucks aren't going anywhere the
The boats aren't going anywhere you might be right in that Trump is
Trump personally is done
Because who gives a f***
But the movie
Those trucks are going away it's just going to be some other f****** s*** caught late
Temple are just now sitting ducks
For indoctrination to whatever the next
Person who
Scratches that itch yepiz
That'll probably be
Probably be a fairly familiar name
I don't know
Will safe Dinesh D'Souza will be the next right-wing cult leader I mean it should
It should have been
Should have gone better
Because
I don't know but
They're they're definitely not going anywhere
End it
Italy
Testament to this b******* that
My uncle
But so far as I know
Is absolutely
I don't remember him hurting recently
An interesting Lee enough
Because it's only be
Cousin Vatican 2
That he would even talk to my uncle
Because my uncle's a non-catholic
Do you know what I'm saying like what type of s*** we're somehow they create this
Nonsense Coalition of
Stupid beliefs
And they hate each other
Yeah yeah it's it's amazing to me
That is that is
Funny that I never even
Thought for a second that your uncle wasn't Catholic
But I think this happens
All the
I would guarantee this happens
All the time people are sending these things that
Agree with
Write short clips
And if you
Backup all the sudden you like
Oh s*** I didn't know I was being yours are some rumors were sending you this s*** I don't know the
Text of any of this stuff that I am passing along
I think that's one of the dangers of the social media age to like I think a lot of people are guilty of that
I think everybody can do a little bit of a better job booth
I hate to say this because
Become the thing where it's like well think before you retweet
Be better for everyone if people that that just retweet
I didn't make sense
Yeah about whether or not the teacher
Damn that is a do you have any closing
Thoughts on that
No other
I think that it's interesting whenever we go down one of these episodes that you take over
Today we get a glimpse of somebody that we've never heard before but is
Weirdly very familiar
And it also is like you know a we need more people
To talk about you know like we need more
I think they're all wisps
Yeah it's not your fault I don't want to go to no Charisma, disconnect Charisma vacuum
He's making weird mouth noises
Realgar
Is bad just not somebody that I could ever be interested in
More for not going to sustain this
Yeah but it does it does sort of depict
The sort of
The intended messages this video that got sets
To you and then what
Behind it is something
I bet
Is good to point out to be aware of
So thank you Jordan that you are very welcome
Remember
Uncle
Absolutely
Until I believe we're going to have an epic
Episode on Monday
Unimportant number I mean not really but pretend a little.
We do have a website it's not right. Calm we're also on
We aren't going to bed Jordan
Find a local charity or Bellefonte in your area to help out people doing
Emilio Emilio on dzx Clark on barrel rundus
I'm the juiciest Ice Cube
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color