Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
Hello everybody this is too much info
In particular
And I sit down and have a little chat about what I've learned with my friend
Who has
Has no goddamn idea what
What's going on with
It's a fun exploration
Over a glass of wine
So I think I'm just looking
Find out whether or not
He's stupid or
Yeah easy on everyone else is stupid
Bottle of wine and we talk about this stuff
It's kind of like
Insane book club
It's a lot like that it's a lot like
Relatively middle-aged women just a little bit
Except our version is a weird texting
Shouting
Borderline racist s*** all the
I hope you're ready for that I never would have guessed
Topics that are going to come up in weird ways
Rate
Sure.
But okay
So last we spoke
They're just
It's really looking
Ethiopians
Add to running the Boston Marathon
Against their will
Bespoke we've recorded a couple episodes over the weekend we're recording this on
Of the inauguration this will be out on Friday
And I want to fill everyone in on what the week has been like listening
Go to the Alex Jones program
You looking for
Well all at now all I'm thinking right now
This day will go down in
He says he said something exactly like that
ER
This day will be study
Beautiful generation
That is what he says
I didn't isolate cuz they're just little one off
Comment
Absolutely disagree about what you're talking about but yeah
Also on Monday
We all expected Alex will be back in studio
He was not you still on his work
Patience
But he's like I'll be back in on Tuesday
I'm working on the road
Work case
Studio
Cousins
What the f*** is going on
So David nights like hey guess what Alex
Who's going to be in later
With some breaking news of lethal consequences
Dammit
I love that show
I am a second put Alex's back
He hosted the last hour of the show
Well Rodger Stone came in and did a bit of it was talk about the second pick
But then Wednesday I'm like f****** Alex's back baby
I turn it on
It's night again
I guess what you like hey it's Thursday
Ethan
Literally
All right but still not enough to make David
Interesting I'm not listening.
Play turn it off on Wednesday
Next time travel boring
That is a good point
So Wednesday I checked out I didn't listen to
You can't pay me enough to listen to two hours of David Knight and his smug bulshit
I just can't do it
That is
Send an email
To knowledge
At gmail.com
With your offer to pay for
Enough money to do
Donate to my patreon
Freezing point if you want to donate to make me listen to David Knight
Lizabeth.
It's basically torture
If you are you like don't know I'll listen to it and I'll do on solo
With just talking about David Knight
That would be your drunken Alex Jones
From the road Motor Inn
I'm having a tough time
Thursday
When recording
Alex Jones
Broadcasting live from
In anticipation of the inauguration
When you're listening to this on Friday
They're starting a 14-hour live broadcast
At 8 a.m. I will be listening
Address
I'll give you as much of a report as I can
Back tattoos
Excellent Tuesday so Tuesday
Happened
Unfortunately
And what ended up happening was most
Camping
Some of these
He's been doing this
Just getting on his phone and recording
Special Report I have some special reports
Air before Alex makes it to the studio
Could we I got I want to get into his voicemail
See how many time
I'm keep try to record it and I made it
Can I make a prediction
Note 8
As you can hear I think you can hear from these clips
He's recording these on a plane
I think I cut it out but it won't point he's in the middle of a sentence like
How you doing man
Goddamn
In Trump's America
The babies won't be
Indeed
Studio
I don't have clips of this cuz I don't give a fuk
His big news
Was it Rodger Stone has been poisoned with polonium
Rodger Stone be consummate Trump Insider he works for a number to Missouri
Believe you worked like a Nixon Administration
Yeah he's been hosting the Alex Jones Show June 4th hour
Almost entirely the time that he claimed he was deadly sick pictures
Poisonous polonium I have not
Peony and Radioactive
Massively
You pick it up at
You can't get out of bed
That's working
Supposed to
Am I sick false flag
He wants to make Russia seem okay
I guess haha
If you just make sure it up you can
That's such a great move
Yeah
Outfit different wait no we have all this
No you don't fake nose ring
If you
Any doctor would be able to do
Test blood test
The half-life is not such that it would be out of your blood
Be traceable
Is about the size of a grain of salt
I did some research on this
How long before it kills you
It is kind of a gradual thing
Okay Goodberry's
Possible
Rodger Stone
It's entirely possible before have you ever seen him and radiation
Sabra
I think you nailed this one
So here's the best thing about lying about doctors
They can't
Say that you're lying
Cuz there's laws
About confidentiality
Yes if you lie
And say hey my doctors think it's at
They can't come out and say we never said that they can
It's perfect
You don't even have to
What about now probably have a stomach bug
Is dr. Wallach
Veterinary
As well I think there was a class at Mizzou about
Boner pills
Surprise
Cure radiation
Dogs Red Rock
F*** the radiation rated
I can't
Stand
Talking about that stuff so I don't
Valic that I think are worth covering
This is about this is
This is actually
For the deplorable with you're going to be speaking it
Will be the end of the world
No big deal
Because the cops aren't bad but the political
Nothing more
Call Jerry
Calling for gas
Yeah exactly
Project Veritas
They had one of their guys on in on the inside
Okay so they talked about
James O'Keefe
On from Project Veritas
Real quick
When he says they were plotting to guess us
Does he mean
People
People write so their story and these videos all going to be
Easily gases
Google place
The outdoor inauguration
Okay
Powerball is what they're talking about
Blossom
That's a solid
I like the repurposing negative things
As positively
Yeah
A video
Where they purported
Project
You that is
Cosplaying Lord of the Rings
While they're doing that
If you want me to call no
What they have done
Right I mean they did that bogus video about Acorn
Ended up having to issue a public apology and pay $100,000
And of course.
Because
He was shown to have manipulated videos to show people saying things they didn't
He reported to have worn a pimp costume into the acorn
Play
That would be
F****** Grace Slick couldn't commit
Okay
Is the selling fee.
Someone else
Really did the same thing
Yeah
Because they don't they're not journalists
Will ya
Also
In August
2010 James
Keep playing to staged encounter with CNN correspondent Abby Boudreau
Who is doing a documentary on the young conservatives
He set up an appointment at his office in Maryland
Video shoot
Easy Santa
Which is a crazy name
I could have swore that what you meant
Was like
Is James O'Keefe
The evidence isn't in yet they weren't in the same room if he has a hastily edited video
Is there an a
Executive director of project veritas
Warren Boudreaux that O'Keefe was planning to
Bunker on the boat
By trying to seduce her
Wychwood filmon hidden cameras
Buddha Board the boat
Soon left the area
CNN later published a 13-page plan written by O'Keefe Mentor Ben Wetmore
Hit List prop
Apps for the boats
Including pornography sexual AIDS
Condoms a blindfold and fuzzy handcuffs maybe the locker Apple
When questioned by CNN O'Keefe denied that he was going to follow the Wetmore plan has he found parts of it inappropriate
Boudreaux,
Heart
Pageland
Wetmore
So everyone's name is ridiculous, that does not appear to be true according to the series
Email to be obtained from Izzy Santa who says the emails revealed
James is true intent
Following the Boudreaux incident project Veritas pay 250 Santa Fe
Figure settlement
Which included a non-disclosure
So
You know we can we can
Baby is he was telling the truth on that one always have to have
The sign the
Disclosure agree
Cuz everybody's got
F****** high
Can't we just put somebody in jail
Can we put him in jail
Just like that
The crime
Let's just do that constantly also been caught trying
To get people to commit voter fraud and then they're on tape big like we're not going to do that illegal
Yeah that's
Bad in this case the most recent one
The devil
In the book of Joe
Make a Deal
Yeah but he's a really cheap
Yeah
I'll give you like 50 bucks
Your soul
There's not enough
Yeah I know but you can't commit in trap
Even if you're not part of the
Tape some people
Deplorable
Would you call the Stampede
His cohorts were all like
Becca Bernstein
How to make a
It's all this b*******
Gladware
Things of that with their usual
Clear-headed
Rational
Absolutely
It is it's a stink bomb but it's acid
So there's a group called undercurrent
Has other video
About this
And I think they might be a little more telling
We're more important than the truth
Project gravy mashed potatoes
Is it so they have video of one of James O'Keefe
Sort of Associates
One of his coordinators a project
Offering
Huge amounts of money
For these people to cause chaos
At the Trump inauguration
So basically they have
Part a
Where they follow through with
The plan that they established with one
I don't understand why I don't understand
Like do you not see how brilliant this plan is if you no one can trace it back to him
He didn't make the offer
It's it's it's
It's super crazy but it's
But run by idiots
Is it
Side of honey
Yeah
So stupid
So they're really up on this gas
Narrative
Except they do for a little bit
But here's one of Alex's
Special Report
That
Is weird
We are now about 3 days now from its historical then take
I should clear I should just save it
Look for contacts
He's going
To talk about the alleged
From the print
That are said to exist
Dad said to exist
And be horrible
Okay they allegedly exist of trump saying the n word
Arnold
Arbiter of our democracy
Play I always knew it would come down to that truly stupid
This is what I think
Is
Supposed to be pre-emptive damage control
But it spins out of control so f****** fat and it's hilarious
Play
Call Watson Auto big score yesterday
Eandc source
The source
Tape compilation
Whatever
With him sitting in the chair
Things like your son's retarded and
Dirty Jobs
And supposedly the n-word
Long time
Does white
Basically tell dirty jokes getting tingly comedian would do
Boston
Way to break the ice
Retarded
I never want the alarm on high powered people all the time
So
Absolutely not true
Well I mean we all do know how power people hookup you have to let us
But the part about Trump
Being self-deprecating
Air control
This is no longer really about the damage control
Okay
Play do it
It was a real
Previously
The word is he's so heavily edited with jump cuts
Contest
Like we doing
Ford
Even in any context it's not right because
If uses a proper word
Throwing up prior to use with Vine wax close
I was always offended by personally
Oh no
Call Alex I'm so sorry for you
So you eat that mean
You caught that right or reason you shouldn't say the n-word is because people can twist
I would hate for somebody to take the N word out of
So here's what our word
Also I like that he doesn't do it
You know he's a monster on weekend
Did the other part that I made that elicited a huge laugh
Is this like
When I heard that we're growing up is
Down
From black people so one that means it's okay for me to say it now forever
I'm also offended because I'm a way better person
Because I'm just like
I just like black people I'm offended by the use of that word
So
I'm going to say the N word a lot is really what he's trying
Laid out
Like all of that stuff
To me was exactly like the OJ book
Like if I'm done
Now that is all okay but my favorite my favorite
He opens it with
His famous we have a sword
Whip
We have lots of you would believe I'm not
But
The devaraj is a
It's credible source
No. We don't know the reports credible yet
You should probably know that
Exactly other contacts
The credible source
Maybe
Somebody
Yep may have something
That might be trustworthy
Benefits
If it is
If
It's not that true anyways
So that is that is like a
Spiraling out of control
Control like trying to hide everything
Amazing rationalization
Free excuses for things
It's it's
Have a scotch man like other rich people do
Assuming
Alex have a weird
Plan for what Trump should do
You know what I do
I wish
I wish you was in Barfly mode
Sauce
Right at my butthole
I shouldn't be getting into it I have sources
Are you sounding
Who's playing
I'm sorry for swearing
But I would never say
There's is playing for what Trump
If the tape is real
This
Open up this is
Is the craziest thing
This is the first time he's WarGames
Where are the ones always doing this
The first time
He's trying to think 10 moves ahead
And I'm going to go
He's not good at
He's not but he is way better than us
And you'll see by the time it gets to the end of it might be a little bit long but it is worth every penny
I just move on from
Trump
Is this compound and they Twisted order
Lisa
People sit around a joke around
Shocking
But he was already making up
What things like that and
Closest
Trulia Powerball this business country
Then he should come out
Talk about the fact that 51% of black
On average never get out of the woman's country and that we should work to make sure that genocide
Created by Margaret Sanger and push for the leftist
It stopped
Lanisha Cole
Monitor
Churches
Supposed to
Unova
Weather
Realized
So I wanted I wanted to stop here at this clip at all
For us to talk about
There we all know how well it went the last time Trump went to a black church when they told him to stop talk
Talking about Hillary from the pulpit
Almost at the light at a church
But I wanted to I wanted to cut in there
Compress cuz that's good advice
I have to assure you I did not do
Anything dishonest with this editing
This is exactly where the clip goes
So cute
Ladies and gentlemen
They are growing humans that are part animal
Charles and other large mammals there Artisan Rewards
Horrible experimentation
Public hunting 100,000 people of the Middle East and Africa
What about
Old Harbour
No no no
No
What what's the problem
Pick up from
O'Mara's are real
Islamic fundamentalist Jihadi
You missed the scepter
Not only are chimeras real
Who is talking about their rights huh
See both sides of it he's trying to both sides
Civil rights
Allegiant Air
Document
Growing
Human baby
Animal hybrid
What percent of African-Americans
Are dead in the womb
Which I feel like is in
Easy statistic
Take two
Proved wrong I don't know not how population number
It's definitely not I don't I don't know the numbers on it but I do know my BS detector went off
Percent of any population
Get the boarded
Yeah I would say probably a lot
I think he's probably including like
Contraception
For something like that
Morning-after pills or something like that
The Rhythm
More of this clip
Zoe
So Trump should tour black churches and hug people
Directly to Chimera right
Edible something about abortion and now
Things Obama done finding a Muslim Brotherhood
What about all the genetic engineering on the BMO and the glyphosate
Hundreds of millions of women worldwide
Leave her alone Cutler Illinois
Completely
I can say
Never done
Consciously
Racist
I am so sick and tired
Whispered in my ear Alex year
Tell me how he's never been race this year
Disinformation
Give me those words baby
Number one
And how dare you
I would argue this
Him saying that he was offended by black people saying the n word is
Probably the definition of but I don't think
People saying a word
I think though that his definition of consciously racist would be horribly Limited
Cuz he's black
Playdium
I don't know anyway
I took from Tuesday show
He also ships on
Why are we talkin
Turn up
Cancer because of
Glyphosate
But again that's probably part of his like enabling himself to make a sales pitch
Spinner
GMOs
The other stuff that he ranted on that I didn't take clips of his John Lewis is an a******
Never done a consciously race
Racist basically his point is like why can't Trump
John Lewis
Super
He's so race
Black chef
Racism turns you dark from within
So his argument
Alex is arguing that he makes
Is like Trump is an illegitimate president
And then Trump
His argument is that his
His tweets were really nice and trying to get John Lewis to work with him
Not true you were insulting as f***
Bass
Physically
Condescend upon him to an extent
Not seems
Since the early days
Did Alex
Yeah it's it was all like you're a man of
All talk
You would never
Mark Smith
King jr. like
But then late but the response to that by Alex and David night are like yeah
What has he done lately
Every becoming walk off
Becoming a congressman
Helps dangerous it into trying to get gun rights or get gun control test
Which they hate everything
Can possibly do being effective
At the vet you don't like
Just because
Just like
Wave his hand and gun control happen
Doesn't mean that
Being a giant pain in the ass for the
People who are fighting
Negative
No I know that
Cuz that's part takeaway Uganda
I mean
Regardless of what
But regardless of what side he's on you
Play he's all talk
Nope
Disagree with you
But you are acting
And you know what I didn't even think about that that's a really good point cuz she doesn't
Do you know a degree of respect for your position but
That you are doing
You're a man of action figure action
Your
Weak plaything
We have a lot of business
Yes
Thursday's show that
The rest of the clips today or going to be from January
2017 Alex broadcasting live
From Washington DC
I don't want to see this up top
This is one of the more unpleasant episodes
I've had to listen to to break down
Cuz it's one of the most
Full of beer
Episodes of the time that we've been covering
Really yeah
Yeah we're fine
Before
What will
Call trumpmas
I got to be honest I didn't catch it first
But you were being sarcastic
Surprise
He doesn't know how to
He doesn't know how to deal with being the winner
In response to that he's just going even more batch it out there
Rodger Stone has been poisoned with polonium
That's why you're going to hear what his new narrative is
Is here that
Wacky
I'm going to play as how he opened the show this
The beginning of the show
I am
It sort of is his prediction of what's going to happen
In the next 24 hours
From broadcast time
My phone
Will load
I bet
He believes
There will be an assassination
Not on
Interesting
But on pants
On no I mean you can kill pen today
Better
Brinkley that's what Pence
I was just like you
Let's go with
Hey
Democrat
So he predicts that there's an assassin
Destination
If not and it's Ash
But an attempt
Indigo
Exactly
That's not a prediction
I don't want to sit here on the show every segment Stacy i-told-you-so over and over again
GOG
And when we come back from break
Of course
Even though he doesn't really actually ever explain what that means but it means continuity-of-government
Okay so what's the plan in place
In case anything
Because in the past there have been issues
It's unclear so they had to put down
Debra Wilson was president
For two years because nobody else is allowed to
I didn't know that
We have had a woman president
But not elected
Not elected
The craziest thing about that story is
Is that Woodrow was sick
And so no one was allowed to
To visit him
For about a year-and-a-half while he was present
All of Congress just talked to Eve
This is a conspiracy theory
But if you look back at that time
Crazily enough a lot of
Pro-woman things got.
Interesting
Very strange to notes be out of place in time
Woodrow Wilson misogynist
Marriage human being that he was
You got Charlie Greenwoods earlier
No I did not I saw some pictures of the 3 Doors Down concert
Sparsely attended
3 Doors Down
They're my kryptonite
I just can't help my
If I could come up with another one of those
He never really explained
Cuz they're krog's
Listener Lyft promo
Assassinated
Because he's a ruski agent
Will appoint the new president
Selling that idea right now
Never heard that before mother tonight
Not show up
Show called improvised
Give a nuke goes off
You can't one
Hundred percent
100%
100 bucking percent
Be very well be an accurate statement
That's not a thing as possible it is like a hypothetical
If you make up something then you can say with 100% certainty
Impossible
CNN clip video eventually end up laying like an hour later
It's going to
Constitutional matters
That usually if
The president
Goes down
Takes over as president
The Secretary of State
Takes over
Succession for the president
Is that right well maybe the speaker goes down to
Well that's why whenever they do those
They always have some ran
Adam Congressman in like a
Anchor somewhere
Just in case so that
And they all take turns doing
A joke okay cuz your turn
What weird
Secretary of
Altra running the entire cut
The point of the Siena
Was that because we're in a weird place where
John Kerry will be gone as Secretary of State
Tillerson won't be
He confirmed that the time we don't have a secretary of state
I'm so it could go down all the way to the
Highest non political appointee
Down it right
Which is the
Purses
Presidency
To think it's basically a story about how weird it could be
American government has a weird system
Obama
That's not a thing
Nobody's ever said that was a thing
He's twisting words cuz
It's the idea that this guy was appointed by Obama
But in the story they make it very clear is the highest-ranking non political appointee
Rec Department
Obama
Just line
Politically app
But what if
As
Yep
Pitiful non-political where you appointed
Oh
Political appointee some thoughts about the shadow government
Keeps talking about
We set up a shadow government
Under mutually assured destruction
That is all Sarah's day
Distraction is
The term Mexican standoff I think
Cornwall
On one of the recent episodes
He did like a 3-minute breakdown of what am I
Standoff in
It's like when you're going to do and there's like a third-person view and like
Whatever
It's not even accurate
Throwing up
There would be an emergency
The problem is
4C OG they try to use
Interpret
He's not saying Hitler's good yet
We all need to clarify
I do like that we're at the place where if you doesn't clarify that plenty
About time somebody said hello
Yeah yeah
I love Alex Jones and I love Hitler
No it said do not want things I love about Alex
Those Shadow government baby
But what channel
Shadow Bank
But what's shadow
Isn't that just
The government played Sonic the Hedgehog
Some of the newer games that are dark
Character remember that was Shadow the Hedgehog
Okay well that's exactly like this
Metaphor
Shadow government
Succession
It's like the Deep State basically it's code it's like CIA
It's
Set it up
The moments that we got the nuclear bomb
Alright
Okay
I do believe
Hello
Get the utility of it in terms of people working behind the
I get that there are some people who do things
That is real
I think the idea that there is a functioning
Shadow government
I mean in the UK they just called the other side The Shadow
Yeah so whatever
F****** everybody over with their b*******
Please don't take offense but I might do an episode of someone else I hate for you to miss out on any of this
Can I send you a drunk missive from the road
But know this
No matter where you go no matter what country you're in
Alex Jones
Is never wrong
Here it is the day before
The inauguration
They're floating
Furr's Buffet directions
Then they'll say that we got to have a civil emergency
I want to point out that already happened also I want to point out that
Boom boom
What
What are you confused about
Yeah
Maybe
Okay
He's claiming that they tried all these things
That they know that the crg is the best way to overthrow
A president
How do we know this
Who knows this sources that may work
Everybody ever
But no that's not
No
He gets fed
Crazy wrong information by fake sources that are just his collars and he thinks
Like if I called him and I
I work for the FBI
I have some information
I almost guarantee
I feel like he would actually lead you on to be like
James O'Keefe
Basically if I called in
Just to be like
Now listen I got a source
My pillow just remind
Okay
No it has to do with dirty though
You know how we talk about these like a digital dropbox
At least they use
Every single time he talks about that BuzzFeed article and the thing that came from Russia
The dirty.
And I like that a lot
Ol Dirty Bastard
Would be the dirty.
The greatest thing you've ever read in your entire life
Together. I love that stuff
Childish
So Alex has more thoughts about how he's always right
Because most intelligent
Weather
Okay
The song about like if the globalist
Do Tryon.
Covid-19
Counter thought to Alex Jones
Oh boy
Is something that he truly believes
Right yeah
To really want this
Biscuit to go down
Just so a
He can see all the globalist
Junk
Yeah
All the crazy bullshittin he's been spouting for his entire 22 years
Is 100% accurate
The confirmation that he's right
No no no
He wouldn't
But you would think he would
Cuz it's someone I mean the greatest Coincidence of all time if all of this stuff
Completely different reason
I think it's more likely than his version
Quite frankly
Everything is more likely than his I look be clear
We have different political ideas we agree on a lot of stuff
Totally aligned
Neither of us want
Ill to happen to
We don't want him dead
Under
Law
What are I would be fine with that I don't want him
To be hurt by like assassinated
I want that would be a counterproductive
A caveat needs to be an actual
Full-on Revolution
Entire government of top-rated I want the entire country
The new Civil War well it may happen one way or another anyway
We reserve the right to strike
Vegeta
I'm going to walk myself back to my foot
What I mean is we don't support the things Alex thinks
We support no absolutely not
And almost everything else
Here's a little bit
Where
You know how I was
It's very worrisome
Tomorrow
People approved yet
People Obama appoint
Obama
Colorado
Space command
NORAD
Long time
And the people are in the bunkers
I'm just a little bit suspicious
Gog is the weather tomorrow
Annie's got f****** Wagner in the back
Are you like that like
At the end he's like I'm not going to think about it
Also they're openly talking about
Everybody's always openly talking about vet
To hear it man
Is it
Does he think it's cold or does he actually have Mike's everywhere
Is he always watching
I think he thinks
Is it
WWE Fastlane
Fiction is great cuz it's like
Obama has people at space command
Play Ora's outside of Washington DC apparently I do
Event
It has to be
What's 17
F****** amazing if you remember say too bad for that
God
So
He's in d.c.
He's hanging out waiting for the inauguration on the streets
You think that's everybody comes up to him and they were like
We're just really we're just really grateful for the job that you're done
You you are the only one telling the truth
We just really love you and we're grateful that you helped
Lorden
Savior hero
That might be the case some of the time but he has some other responses
Debating whether I should
I bet he does
Literally
Arrogant evil position
Evil people
Sit back
Car
They run this world
They are so mad
So this is this is great cuz I like people helping people I think that's great
I don't think we should bring back history
Accurately
Describes
Evil people
With all the words
He would use if he looked into
If you if you did mushrooms if you gave him an entire list of the things that he
He's done but put Obama's
Name on top of it
Those are all the things that evil people would do it
Slytherin
What's his name
Some sort of like a Christmas carol situation
Can you show up to show him the error of his
Breezeways that's what I'm saying
That's what I'm saying
Former White
No longer with us
When we needed him to do mushroom
Just do some mushrooms and like
Introspective and realize
Then being neck
Text to Alex
Yeah yeah
Cthulhu blade nightmare
I would sign up for it
The other day episode about whether or not we'd like to drink with Alex Jones
I realize that I got to I got to go full circle on myself
I'm in the unpleasant but
Could be fun
Such amazing things
Because
Because we wouldn't give it we don't give the reaction that he's looking for is either adoration or
We think it's
Hilarious
Still mad
Richard Edward territory in first four minutes and then we're off to the race
From there
Do you know where it is we would go after
I'll tell you this I bet we would be called
Aliens
Dallas
Tell me about these beings of light in about those beans
Play Aliens
Dirty Pleiadians
This clip is super f****** fun
It's awesome it shows a little bit
You're going to need
Microphone down
But
I want to set this up a little bit
He was ranting about how I
Putin gives him and Trump all of their marching orders
Like facetiously ranting about that
Depression and this is sort of the aftermath
They're so delusional
And so disconnected
Uninstalling
Other really good acting
Cookie Monster
Isn't that amazing
That might be one of my favorite moments ever he does this dumbass Cookie Monster B
But then he's like
My eight-year-old daughter loves when I do Cookie Monster
That's kind of beautiful
The real person now then not 20 seconds later
The nuclear weapons are all going to die
When I tell her about the
My daughter's age
She's two years away from being a correspondent on my traffic andesite
Oh my God
Cookie Monster
That's amazing
Drift
And that is
Ironic way
I thought that was pretty funny
Baby in terms of the context of every other horrifying thing that he
Eric Roberson on a sliding
Closest we're going to get to funny without like
Oh no a little bit of
Frank Caliendo
How is the egotistical also about impression
Can't do a Russian
That's kind of wanted
That is pretty easy
So this is
Less
Humane and
Alright
About 24 hours
This is a direct message
The globalist
Who do you think provide you your security
Quantifiable fact
That within 24 hours
Goodbye
Bluebird
Bye-bye
You think you're going to run a poison to Apollonia
Against a bunch of Americans that just want prosperity
I just want
Cocovan
Alicia
Rift
Trump
Perfect
But he's not out to get us
Is it good guy
The ones prosperity
4 supposed to be
Over
Because even if you kill me or Trump
What why do why would you go to the Liberty move my
Yeah but I mean you could let him go
Nature's going to get him
Some great ideas
He's crazy about some stuff but I do
Me too
I love it when Alex gets like
In this headspace where he's talking to Rick
Actually to the globalist
Mirror mirror on the wall
Literally like you talkin to
Yeah
He's like a
Do you know what you're going to try this and we're going to f****** get you
And he's just about to brush his teeth
Before that
He wipes the steam off of
His mirror
Looks directly into
The Marion ghost
Globalist
24-hour
There will be something long
The wrestler
Who do you think provides your security is my favorite part of that like
Patriots
Wait no
I mean they're the globalist I'm going to assume they've got their own security
Multinational corporation
But dude
Security we got a we got to Outsource
All the people who have guns
And I are behind this
Themes and s*** like that all of them are speaker
Currently on Maui
Okay people think it's going to be real fun when you do this
Just know that all the people protecting you are really on my side and they're going to get you
Fantastic
The most narcissistic thing I think I've ever heard in my
My tire light
Discuss a little bit hypothetical ideas about his financial structure
Yes and it's very nice conversation with the guy on Twitter
Kyoto
I really nice back-and-forth Tim about
You like advertising
On YouTube play what's going on
I think I actually found some new insight
One of the things is that the reason
B Alex
So is that real quick
Balance underscore 333
Big shout-out.
Kyoto
I realize that the reason that they can give away all the
The app time
Is it because they just do ads
On the Regular Show
They don't do and I also realize
I also realized that I've never played like one of their
Because
They're just doing their ad
So this is in the middle of the show not during commercial
This is a little bit long but I think it's worth it for a
A couple of
But this is just a commercial that's part of the show
This clip here and
Tell me if you want to pause and
The Clippers like three and a half
Engine is tone
Went from
Like there's just a subtle perception of like
This is Alex Jones salesman
Alex Jones fear monger
A hundred percent
Because they're selling bacteria out there
Active resistance
What's the crisis in the medical world crisis in the military
How to get a 20-plus antibiotics
U.s. Loan in newspaper
Get that he's personally been researching
Make sure you got that
Swastika
Dammit
I know it was my fault I caught it the wrong part
I've been researching
Important thing
Contract
Sends a big message
They are selling
Body armor
Yep
Like literal
Okay bulletproof for backpack
They are six months away from selling gun literally like any chance the Liberals
Other evolution
Done already
Any revolutionary thoughts I had before God
The people who take him seriously
It's not fair they don't deserve to die but no I don't mean that
They have body armor now
Which look anytime you are in people
Who are afraid
That really just me
They're looking for a reason
Going to use that arm
Undoubtedly so if you give them only do they have
But now that
Feel like they don't have to
You fear retaliation either
Whether or not that's actually how that works with
Here's the best news they don't make bulletproof vest in
XXX out
Call Jesus Christ I don't know if it's true but it seems like
A hurtful day on my part
And it means that we can
Helping Infowars product
Is that
Pittsburgh Avenue
System-wide the Department of Defense
Special Operations
The long-term
Kombat 1
And I got a whole lot of product
Twisted from
Combat armor brought up flesh eating bacteria
Yep.
Not be
Bodyarmor I feel like that's bad
Also shouldn't be spending 12 years researching baby wipes
And also why are you going Direct
Okay
Did you catch the part where he's not kill bacteria and lower your fertility
What do they do
Haven't you seen how low babies fertility's are these days
Every time I check a baby's fertility I'm like Jesus this fertility is everytime I try and get a baby to get me
Listen
If you ever f***** a baby
How to get pregnant
That's because you're
You're using the wrong baby
And here's where it gets in
Listen to like
If I were doing an ad
This is never what I would say
Territory
Everything Alex does is 99%
I would never do this
But even if you're just trying to be crass
Salesman I would never
I wouldn't get my thoughts organ
Okay
Also we go on a ramble
It's amazing you got to go research it for yourself
This is charged with
Call here's overall
With the Pentagon
In the field working with a developer
Battlefield 1
That's why
He was involved with DNA Force
You got to have doctors
New song about his dad I was involved
Dad was not involved
Nobody
Rhythm examples for evolve
His dad was a dentist who recently came out with a line of fluoride
Free toothpaste
Based on infowarsstore.com
I mean that's good synergy
But
Okay
He has more to say about it
Please let me know
Taking things process
Can't possibly be the same
No it is also just
Does the yard so to speak
All of our stuff is
FDA approved
Cuz it's on
It has to be like that's the one law
Did they do have
Like they don't say it on there
He said that like he's bragging
I guess cuz it's because the FDA is trying to get all the GMOs in the chimeras and earbuds
Blood screen
Shepherd
Not worth going public
Crushed pepper product
Kombat 1 skin protective life
Military-grade technology
Free preparedness and survival product
Everyone needs Kombat 1
100% quantifiable facts
That within 24 hours
You will never be cold again
Did you see what he did he started rambling
He keeps going
And here is where something awesome happens
He's doing this anymore. Just another awesome
Awesome thing number 544 and he gets interrupted by a commercial
Break
See what happens with that
Cases of the sphere office cases of the sphere family
Secret system
System-wide
In 2016-17 rolling out
As a thank-you for you being Patriots
You defeat them
Infowar
We just amazing product so we're launching
Also forces back in stock at 10% off
Amazing
He's 5 minutes into a commercial pitch
On his broadcast
Wow
What the f***
That makes no sense
No it's okay
But what is
Is it thank you
For the Patriots
They're going to give you some body armor that only the cops have you want that yeah you got it
Bakery
Do not like hearing
Do you want some boom boom boom unless unless the Black Eyed Peas
The Vengaboys
Boom boom boom boom
I want you in my room
To what I would call realtor
Are you ready
2/2 realtor
He was on the whole communist
By the Congressional
I just want to know that
Don't understand exactly
What a weird people
Went along with the system like the leftist of God
Donald Trump Americana Sleeper Cell
Inside
And that is why they are
Truly scared
This is crazy
Crazy
Just rotate
This is not a bad movie 60
Gilberto came over since Donald Trump was wanting
Well I mean yeah well but we'll use the CGI you know
Still alive
Okay
F****** Tatum
No Channing plays Alex Jones that's right that's right
Get the information
From
Congress
Secret globalist
Stop when he was 20
What is 20
He embarks Upon a
Sleeper Cell
See
Under all of his own idea
With no help from anybody else
And now
I love you struggling to come up with a thought
Why
That is actually the most insulting thing I think anybody's ever said about Trump
What did he was asleep herself
To me that is an insult to him because
Basically
Negate
All of the things that he really is good at
And says that he's good at something else
Interesting I think it's rather you'd rather someone celebrate his
Is bullying manipulative Market Act
Sure he is that is a more complimentary thing that saying you're a great spy
Going intertek
For 50 years
Get me on something that
What point is it like at Alki
Right and then I come up to you
I really love
The ghost riders
Who wrote all of your
Okay
Great job
Performing every
So he's taking
All of the stuff that you're good at
And complimenting somebody else
Person to
But
That's it that's offended
I wouldn't put it outside the round-the-clock
Says the n word
Hours in the back
I wouldn't be too surprised
If Trump
Cold out
Cuz the two of them
And Trump is a known liar
Kind of a social
PupilPath
Kind of is a very
He very easily could have told Alex these sorts of things
And Alex believes him
When I say
Full on
F****** rewriting
That
Would be
Funniest joke
You could play on Al
Alex Jones
Other than calling
50 years Sleeper Cell agent
To pull off one bit on ethics
I mean to be a rough 27 years before Alex got on the air
But if we're giving him that much forethought of knowing when the time would come
Strike
Why not why not
Knowing that Alex
Hilo and Alex
Would arise from the
If you are asleep or sell one of the things that you desperately need to do also is make yourself a laughing
In stock for you
Hide in plain sight
No
Ghibli for sale
He is the single greatest Sleeper Cell agent there is ever been in
In the history of the world and you know what is good at 3%
I mean
The day may not come that he has to go Ghost Protocol
16 oz
His daughter
My daughter
So Alex announces
Is big news
The Trump is a
Americana Sleeper Cell
That's some solid bulshit
He can't keep the thread
So how is that
How could you not keep please listen to what ends up coming out of his mouth
Immediately
Let's do this
But
Record numbers of minorities and women
Approved
Yeah
I'm done fact that gay men are gray
Casino Rose
That is a stereotype I've never heard before Goodfellas
Oldies bobmovies all the owners are stereotypically gay
Play Straight
What
Train stereotype to makeup
That's what they do
Oh man
I don't like
Have you in your life of Tolerance in
An acceptance ever felt you were Pandora
To gaze or minorities or anything
I would even know what is
What does pandering look
To you
To me in this
Catering really just means a lot
Because
Hindering
What he thinks that
Is him saying
I think
Instead of
You know
Say what he really feels
Which is that you should
Yeah I think I was just lying right I think in this case
His version of pandering would be active Lisa
Supporting
Oh
You know like
I think that's what he means by that
Odyssey here and actively support your day fine
Overtime
I super panda
All the time
I was more of like a
A silent partner
Just gave you the wink
Hey
Try saying the n word last but I like it
Edward
I don't have to sit here and explain
Everyone that wants low taxes really hate black people
I'm so sick of my whole life
I'm bad as I got the code
Okay
Me up
Because they were told I was my ancestors I did something to them
Post wife
Do you think of the lady doth protest too much
Okay
He did
Everything possible
How to say
He fought
Tooth and nail to keep that word from coming out of his mouth
They might have done something
Which is like
Know my ancestors were good Christian people trying to atone for it
Maybe they aren't
No big deal if they did on slaves even while they were owning slaves they were good Christians
Take a step back and I want to say one thing very clearly I don't think that it's a moral failure
On your part if your ancestors owned
But I think it's a moral failure on your part if you were aware of the history of slavery
And you think that is meaningless to our modern world
Well knock knock knock looks like to do that that's why I didn't go that far
Okay you think that's too far
Dude I mean
Okay how old is Alex Jones
He's probably pushing
Mid-to-late forties
So he was born in the late sixties
Now
Let me
Let me just
Bluesky think
He was born in Texas
I don't know if that's true
Well from his voice
Born somewhere around there
He's been there a long time
Sixties era he was born in Dallas
He's going doubts right
To Texas parrots
Beauty Tsum
During
The Civil Rights era
If I'm just going to
Go buy all of the history there is
You don't even have to go back to his grave
His parents were probably horrible races
Most likely means
Own up
You use that waterfowl
The worst thing you can do
Actually growing up everyday with black
Kids feeling like
Oh something is wrong because of the color of my skin
He just described
I think I just short skirt.
What was the I had a vein in my head but
People running around saying white people are bad
Is kind of newer than that era of
Maybe a little bit
They're bad
Northlake
RiverWatch
Fake idea that black people beat him up cuz they've been lied to that white people are bad
That's never happened
Maybe when you were a kid or something like that probably had nothing to do with your skin
0 chances that
Alex Jones
Does a speeding
Has ever been
Deserved
Weird
The
Wow
Here's the worst part about that
Is
Outside of that like the least conspiracy theories
Because I would guarantee that if
You really got
Most
White people
Like
Like most wifey
Explain to them
How whitefoord
Really happen
Their starting point is going to be
You know like
Well I mean
Sure
You know you know the idea of like
Moral development
Mint how it works
Do you start with the kernel of like Golden Rule
You work up to
New Concept
Principles
Is that Lawrence Kohlberg's theory of
Who cares
Good point basically you evolve to understand things
You end up at a place where you're at you thinking is much more evolved
If this is basically the low rung on
Of racial think
Cuz like I didn't do anything wrong
Great there's more that there's more work for you to do
Replace rear to get to in terms of understanding
It's not even that high
No it's not even that high it's just like
It's literally
Have you walked a mile in another man's shoes
Literally
Stephen Curry
Universal
Here's my answer
To Alex
Me with a weird thought about race
And I say
Can you do more for me out
He's like
Yeah
You are probably going to put my cardi b yellow
You're going to see Infowars
So this is Rob dude who's co-hosting for a little bit
Arab do
Where do all these names f******
Come from
Used to have a guy named
Jakari Jackson
Great Dane
Already left I wonder why
I don't know
Usually behind the camera
Sing a little bit
He's trying to explain
Stuff but
Can handle that he hijack
But
Cheetah
Your right finger know that's call what mammals do
Elizabeth Warren
What's great is it gets so much worse
Han
It's not possible
You could
Rob
If you which is better
If a woman is all over you and you kiss her
Well if that was just me too I was trying to hold in all the other stuff
Right you might think that's like he just said that
Nope
Purity goes developing that theme for about a minute
Is okay
If you want outside your parents
For the government
After that
But they were so happy that the war was over they both came
Corrupt
So funny that's so cute
It's a little child
It's so funny
Ranting about something that's not real
Amen
Actual sexual assault
Real is this b******* idea that anybody think
B kissing someone who is clearly into you
Helicopter
So
This is all about Trump
Sexual assault
This is like
Music waiting
His wife wanting a kiss
And Trump
Moving in on someone like a b****
Trying to finger bang them without permission
That's not equivalent that is not okay
No he's based
Sickly just described all of the things that are sexual assault and rape
And then said that because
No he just said it was okay to rape you
Most convoluted way when you unpack all of that
Is b*******
Basically
Do witches like
They want
Yeah they want it
They can signal it to you
Because then they are signaling
That's classic
Victim-blaming like
F*** you
If you believe any one of those words that he f****
Can said go f*** yourself
Yeah absolutely don't mean as an insult if you believe all that stuff in our lives
Sing this podcast please
Keep listening so I
Keep berating you
You dumb horrible person
We're winding down here in terms of
Dark lips
K2
But
We have a couple more of those I want
How to play
Where Alex
And robbed
To Trump's hotel
Post office
Yeah it's like
Claim that your journalist
Wow how can you f****** claim
Any right
Any sort of journalistic Integrity when you're just like
Yeah I mean it's crazy
So good it is incredible
Free
Free in the lobby
I can't even get myself to say
George Soros
Oh good I was I was worried we wouldn't hear about him nope those enough
Continuing X
There's a little narrative going on throughout the show about protesters being bussed in
Got it
Done
Addicott Universe Calvin
And Hobbes Calvin
Has anybody done a d
Decal with
Trump's face
Okay I haven't seen it but someone has
Right there
It's in the dirty.
That's all they needed
They just said Trump a picture of that
In the heavily classified
Procrastinate go to the inauguration
Saw the Calvin
Jesus hears about buses
Owen Shroyer
Soros group
Open Bing
He caught himself there with the
Owen Shroyer put out
They did catch people getting on buses
That's about it
I mean well
What about the Arkansas Department of Transportation
Are they still on the road
Also signal Alder videos literally proved is that people use buses
That's all
Conservative.
Any kind of responsibility for being called
Does George Soros and others
Could be anybody could be Greyhound
All the videos are are people being real
George Soros
This Global Hound of Owen Shroyer
Like watching people get on like in a line onto a bus
Advance
Them speculating
Reminder going to go get them
Some housing
Beat them up and then they'll be taking around to the protest
That's just
Racist
B******* right there I really the racist cuz it's
It's like all different races
Millennial
And we all know that
Yeah we are
But that's just what
F****** mean
M MS
You know what every morning I wake up and I'm like am I bad
Because I'm a millennial this really makes me
We feel bad and then
An old app
A baby boomer
Beat me up
You know I'm just trying to be a page
Crazy so that Owen Shroyer filed another report where he proved the protesters are idiots
If I going around during a
An active
That's where people are changing
I'm trying to ask them questions
Excellence
And no one's answering him
Because they're in the middle of a protest
You stop doing anything
So basically what he's doing is he's driving up in a motorcycle right now
Next to a moving car and knock
King on the window
Can you answer a three-point complicated math question for me real quick
Absolutely
How do you derivate calculus
Is motorist there also f******
Stupid
It seems it was invented in the 50s
Thinks he's being like Mike Wallace
But he's just like
All the footage they have the performance
To show anything
Doesn't
Say it does
Insinuates as long as
You put scary music
Around equation is about
I debated whether I would play this
Cuz it's
Disgusting
You just pulled the you just pulled the Alex Jones movie
I am going to play or not
No I I am I'm saying I'm Dubai debated whether to play it because it's actually
I mean are we going to be okay with us
I will find out answer
Horribly childish understanding of race and
Consent
But this is kind of on another level of like
Him a relishing
Things that are really uncomfortable
Anyway if you have any sort of sensitivity towards stuff about child abuse
Ferrari human being
If you want to turn it off go ahead but if not
Adjust email address
Overly dramatic but I just wanted to give people a little bit of a heads up at the
Gross it's a literal trigger
Yeah
Cam right now
Aristocratic
Boys and girls tortured killed
And forced to eat feces
Megan Baird
Softer soul
Meryl Streep
They want
This is on record
Drink supplies
Now I don't know
Entirely
Is Belgium story he's talkin
About is
But I do know that it's
Irresponsible
To claim that your political enemies
Are aligned with
Example of it possibly what he's talking about
Someone did
Like there's no.
Astros top of the world horrible
We have serial killers
They do a lot of weird
To take any likes to take things and be like
And that's who we're up against it's not fair
Like you didn't even
Couch at this time
In like some sort of plausible deniability
The globalist
Want to grab your kids
Rape them
Feed them crap
Damn
Probably not somebody that you can have an open and honest
Honest dialogue about afraid to mock
Not here a couple points that I want to make
As it relates
If you believe
That that's who you're up against
You obviously wouldn't listen to reason
If you truly believe that those are your enemies
It makes sense why you be passionately against
Yeah and you would be a hero
Yeah like if if you saw the if that was really true
And what he believed were
Was real
Then
I mean yeah all of us who are not fighting
Weird
The worst people alive in many ways complicit
Right
Because one thing
The same way that you know
However many years the Holocaust
What's going on
There's so many people
And let me take let me take a step back I do feel a certain amount of guilt
About the fact that sex trafficking
Best in the world
I could donate to organizations
But I'm living paycheck-to-paycheck
But this is so here's that here's the
I can't remember
But it is something along the lines of
The biggest difference
Liberals income
Always wins
Who wants to
But how they want to
On an individual level
You know you can go to a even the most conservative house Bowl
Household
And my parents live in one of those
Doesn't matter
Gender
Transvestite whatever
Thought you'll come in Delphia
Pjw
In terms of your overall rights
Not a chance
Now the argument then is that liberals you know like you and I
We're not going out and
Personally helping any sex traffic
We're not doing that
We're we're not
We're saying that it's a compliment
Complicated Global problem
That needs to be addressed
Buy an entire Federal
Right and that's where the disconnect
And that's why a lot of
PeopleNet
In order to make it through a dinner delivery
Will likely try and enact legislation
Enforcing plate
It's sincere
Some people f****** monster
There's no way in there
Sorkin
What
Globalist are all pedophiles
And that's who we're fighting again
And it's because not only pedophiles I hate prosperity and
Which is a remarkable 121
Comparison apparel
DIA
This on the bomber note
The other thing that I think
It is important
To remember
Along those lines
If you believe we are up against
You would be passionate
Italy
On that side
Consider that the person who's telling you that that's who you're up against
Also believes that they're making
Chimeras and
Cowbelly
Also consider all of his other b*******
Consider that he believed that not Y2K
Was going to be
B concentration
Hampton off
Yeah like it's so
Like
I'm at the I'm at the Pointe at
At the end of this episode where I this is about where I had
Turn off the episode today cuz I was like
No no more no more
Because it
It is
We can laugh
And we do
Clip there's parts that are pretty fairly laugh
But the reality is
Either using these tricks
22 full people into passion
Let me get him on his side
And that is
I believe in Act
After propaganda
What he just did is
Evil so we loop back to your
Yeah but if we come back to the beginning of the episode episode from that moment on
It's just a five-minute clip of Nubian
Check this clip app
January
2017 the wife of Alex Jones
Like I said you're listening to this on Friday is doing
In our live broadcast
I can't imagine
Repetitive
Spirit in the Sky
Darkest
I will be listening to that at work
Maybe we'll have an episode of early next week where I try and talk a little bit about
England by we should have at least one episode next week
Okay and then maybe some more
With filling gas
But it won't be
I am the Leann to your Mac
So we've already plugged we are on iTunes at knowledge fight Twitter
Knowledge underscore fights going to send us an email
Knowledge gmail.com these are the venues for
LazyTown
Good luck
And goodnight
Alexandra Thurston color with your trip and I love your work