Alex
Everybody welcome back to knowledge nighttime we're couple dudes like to sit around drink novelty Beverages and talk a little bit
3 hours that they generally loved
How to set the back with another episode I wanted to do a little bit of a special thing
A little bit of an Alex Jones
Your buster
So I don't know how much
Thank you I appreciate that
I don't know Jordan how much you know about Alex Jones is
I know that
He's been on
Set the very least
Y2K
Sure
And
Killed in the
Tampa Airport
Survive the killing
He was on Public Access TV
I've looked into up getting a Public Access TV show
I got to pay a lot for
Courses that make you pay like $100
TV
Production classes
Months
Complete the ones you need in order to
To get on TV
If we just shoot our own videos
Mike Play-Doh
So conceivably we're going to need that we're going to eat a better Studio that your bedroom if
Would like to donate to the show
That money may go towards us making it TV show
Public Access
Which would also be on YouTube
That's something we're considering
That would be
Fuckingawesome the spirit of Alex Jones is early career
We will do Public Access
I don't even care
I would love to
To do Public Access
TV and it I think everybody who has donated we really appreciate it but if people
Throw down a little
Something something
We are good we have two projects to work on
But anyway Alex started in public access
Then his dentist father
Talk to one of his patients
Who was a radio executive and got him a radio job
Paper is first ad
The American dream
Alex Jones is first Alex Jones is first ad
Closest dad's Dental
To the practice
He came in to be
But really make it big outside of the Austin Market
Where people thought she was kind of a crazy Yeller
Cuz he was so out at hasn't
She would go out in public with bullhorn
And make a big spectacle of himself and scream about thanks
And what have you
And because he was this crazy public figure that's why Richard linklater
Who wasn't Austin filmmaker
At the time ended up putting him in
And then Scanner Darkly
Very similar to himself
Crazy street fight
Creatures
Waking Life is a guy yelling at a bullhorn driving around in a car
Stuff like that
He's screaming about how the indomitable Spirit of humanity is great
He just leaves out all the globalist
Just going out on that
On Olympic
Chiropractic at that point
Also Feud I found a f****** episode where Anthony gucciardi and Alex Jones had a little bit of a rat
Obsession
How about doctor groups backstory f****** crazy
It's like a comic book
I'll give you
I'll give you the free version of it is a
Crazy Austin
Not real doctor doctor
Life is based out of Dallas
Text non-documentary has a place called the global healing in
Institute or whatever
Global Healing Center
My chiropractor
Preschool
Abby has a bunch of other b******* degree than homie
Homeopathic medicine
But
Anthony gucciardi
About how
Dr. group
Is trying to make up for the evils of his father
Apparently
Adductor groups dad
Created a bunch of these things that are talk
Toxify in the atmosphere
Doctor group doctor group finds out about this
Turns on his dad
Dedicates his life to creating product
Then undo the damage that his father
It's crazy
So crazy
Celtic dad was ostensibly a real ties
Probably
Porterville
The toxicity in the atmosphere created by
Evil scientist father
Hard to tell from watching the clip
If this is stuff that they're making up
Or if they were smoking weed with Doctor group
He was told them that they like
Cool cool also I found evidence
From 2015
That Alex Jones is not lying
About smoking weed once a year
What that came out in his divorce
Case customer care
Do you said in court during a custody case that he smoked weed once again
Singing 2015
That's crazy
He says he smokes weed wanted to check in on it
See what's going on with it see what it does to people
It's not
It's not something that just came out of his mouth
Point is he's not
He's not selling boner pills and Waking Life
So that's how he sort of
That's why he's in movie
What is a f****** lunatic and it's fun to listen to a f****** lunatic
But the reason that he ever broke
Through Inc
Conspiracy theory
And the reason that he got this elevated status
As
Be the champion of conspiracies
What made it really break
Was that
Put out a video
Where you showed breaking into and infiltrating Bohemian Grove
California
I believe it's in the North
North Coast
That wasn't 2000
Allegedly he infiltrated on July 15th
But he made the biggest f****** deal
You made a video
Started
This is sort of the beginning of his documentary Empire
Started getting a lot of
Engine for it because it was this
Mysterious place
Powerful people go
Alex Jones
Belle's himself is the only person who's been able to break in
Can you eat the whole part of it
The big
Coup de gras
Is
He got footage
Of The Cremation of
Pierce Arrow
Which is the most famous
Part of the video it's a fart
Everyone
Martha you remember cuz the rest of its
F****** b*******
It's a video of a giant
Stone owl
Where they burn figure in effigy
He portrays it is at
Pony where they're killing a baby
All this s*** yeah yeah
The realities of the actual ceremony
He presented it as
Like hey
I went in
Viper
InStyle I went in there with a
The camera
Got it
I got it
And they can't deny
Fret
Here's why he's bus
Oh no he's busted
There's a lot on the line
Yes
I've done a bit of looking into
The realities
Situation and I'm here to say
That I don't believe for a second
His version
End of the story
At all okay
So I have posted this I posted
Links to the videos
That are important to the evidence
Some people are some internet sleuths
Done some really good work on
But the more important
That he
Is it the one who exposed
Bohemian Grove
And before that no one knew about it was the shadowy place
We're really powerful Elites plan
And I would like to play this news report
From 1981
Now a question
What happened Herbert Hoover Jack London and Richard Nixon
Volleyball been members of the explosive all-male Bohemian Club
Open California
Where every year at this time the elite from around the country get together for two-and-a-half weeks of the finding game
Steve Guttenberg has this special
Telephone number for more than 2,000 members of San Francisco's exclusive an all-male bohemian
At once again descended on Northern California
When will spend some 2,700 Acres of pristine and privately owned Redwood
Woodforest
For 3 months like this
The place is called Bohemian Grove
That is located just 80 miles north of San Francisco
The Grove is the Bohemian Club summer retreat
And its facilities are hidden beneath left Forest canopy extending south from the banks of Sonoma County is Russian River
Century the camp has been a place where climbers and guests from all across America gather to relax
Yeah it is divided into
There is a reason that we don't watch it
Rockstar
Miles from overhead
Information
It goes into
There's footage
Inside the Bohemian Grove area
The people it's remained a Bohemian Grove
19 years before Alex Jones broken
Wow that's one piece
It's taken away from his I exposed
Bishop on the news talking about how the elites
From way back
Even when
F****** Richard Nixon in
Herbert Hoover
Yeah this is been going on for
It started a long time ago it started like 100
4 years ago I can't remember exactly
Also
The weird thing about 80s music
They can just say all mail
That's
Fine
Yeah
The Bohemian Grove
The all-male club and everybody's like
Good we have
Waterfall
So
Fascinating little pieces of Alex being
Completely wrong
Which
Years
For Alex Jones broken
A journalist named Philip
Reporting for spy magazine
Infiltrated Bohemian Grove for 6 days
No s***
6 days
A couple of excerpts from his column
Glad I quit
For me the trick was getting in
I guess card was out of the question
Club by-laws of State sponsors application
Quick shelter Shelby
And shall contain full information
The guidance of the board
In determining the merits and qualifications of the proposed
No Section 8 article
18 was to find a screen for me
Attempts to get a job as a waiter or a valet in one of the camps
Spell
In the end I entered myself
Some observers of the Grove warrants
Security was too good
Dick Smith me out immediately
I might last 3 hours before they put me in Santa Rosa jail for Trent
Lowell Burger
A producer with 60 Minutes who used to hunt rabbits in the nearby Hills
Remember to Fire Road leading into a site near the grahamsville way street
But sneaking in
Others mentioned barbed wire and electronic monitoring devices
The places where the Grove abuts Mount Rio
And helicopters patrolling The Ridge Road
Does the Traverse 3000 Foothills
Inform the Grove
Perimeter
Just f****** walk
One day
I drove up to the front gate and got a daunting glimpse of what look like the Grove Sheriff
A barrel like figure in a Smokey the bear hat
I set up checkpoints on the Berlin Wall seemed to stretch out behind
But
Myconnection
My driver was Mary Moore an Earth Mother type with long silver blonde hair who's the most active member of a distinctively
California left-wing group called The Bohemian Grove action
To network
More agreed to help me get in
Providing me with a sort of Underground Railroad
She put in my service a mountain guy who demanded only that I keep the methods he devised for me confidential
He had a keen geographical sense
Add a girlfriend to describe the plant
See magic crystals at the Grove gate
And make them open up of their own accord
Could walk in
We didn't do it that way
The great writer
We figure a punchline
The Grove security isn't quite what it's reputed to be
The sociologists to its
There was no real security
Yeah
There's that
So the real security is the ledge
That's what that's what the real security is probably a lot of security if you try and go into
But there's not like snipers posted
Therefore days
They just hung out and did all the stuff along with them
And one of the things that his disguise was always have a drink
Cuz everybody's drinking
Everyone just drunk bushes
Sprite
A crazy
Super powerful rich
People summertime
Yeah
When and we'll get back to that Maseca
But he had to have a reason to be there
My imposter included misrepresenting myself in conversation with other campers
And my story kept changing as I learned more about how license
I said it was a guest of Bromley
We run sortable visitors end up
A33 I was one of the youngest bohemian
Quote we looked around and saw we were becoming an old men
Men's club a member said
Explaining recent Everett
Efforts to recruit fresh blood
Being from New York was fine
The Grove limits
Retreat guest
Out-of-staters
No clamoring by well-connected Californians to visit the forest
Has resulted in the rise of the jeans
Jynx weak
I don't know what that means
I used miles
I used my real name
Noah
No one
No one inside Act
Suspicious
But paranoia about the Groves
Justified
And I brought along my own version of cyanide
Funeral
A tranquilizer used by actors to counteract stage
One day member asked if I was related to a bohemian
No but I've heard a lot about him and I'd like to meet him
You can't he said
He's dead
After that I began working a dead Westcoast relatives promise
To have me out to the Grove One Summer into my Shaggy Dog story about an invitation
Very nice so basically he's in the B
He's just hanging out with these people and
I'm hanging out drinking with these powerful people
He ends up bring the camera on the last days is that guys like I kicked out
What up whatever is my last day here
He goes to The Cremation of care ceremony that Alex
Videotape and misrepresent
That is some sort of a satanic thing
The reality of it is
Is that The Cremation of care ceremony is this thing
Where Uvalde super powerful people live crazy stressful live
It's much
The same as like
Really rich people often go to the dominatrix
To get the power taken away
Rubber Eva symbolic power
Exchange
In the same way
The super somebody who's in control all the time nothing is
Tantalizing
Exactly
And in this case these people have such scrutinize lies and such stress
The B go to this place where they can privately let loose
Maybe do some gay stuff
Get drunk all the time
That put on little musical numbers
Have people give speeches
Basically a lot of what goes on that there's a lot of
Politics
Discussion that goes on now too much more
That
It's a borg
Answer The Cremation of care ceremony is where you have a manifestation of care
Who comes in this is this this
What is
And it is this this
This idea of
The stresses and the cares of the outside world
They bring it in on a on a boat
A pontoon boat
Do this ritual space
In front of the giant owl is wisdom
The giant owl moloch
Is voiced by Walter Cronkite
And so they have this ritualistic
Play we're in all of the cares of the outside world
Only able to
To be burned by the
The Everlasting Flame
That never goes out throughout the
Entire weeks-long in a sex prop
Yeah and I think it's f****** awesome that sounds amazing
Stupid but I want I want to go and get chips I would go in a heartbeat
Yeah I could have gone
I don't care that it's quote the faggy is goddamn Nixon
Direct quote from Nixon
It's a good thing Alex Jones got in there to expose it
So those are
Two things that happened over a decade before Alex
Ostensibly allegedly
To the toilet
This guy Philip Weiss I really record
Is article here about his infiltration
Because it's
First of all he's a great writer
It's pithy
It's witty it really great and it's a really interesting window into sort of the reality of what believe mean
Club that Alex is satanic
It's like at Hunter S Thompson didn't
So the other problem
Who
Movie that he put out his documentary
About breaking
Bohemian Grove
Is that
A couple people have done some really good analysis on it
One question keeps jumping out and that is
Why do all of the
The craziest
Mangrove
Why is none of that on cam
Why is that just Alex's
Narration
Over
Shots of trees
And stuff like
He talks about how he sees
Surveillance
Equipment everywhere wires going all around the trees
None of that is on camera
He talks about
All sorts of things
And none of it is presented within the documentary
Further
He says that he gets
Accosted by Sheriff
On his way in
To try and break in
He just says that it happened
There's no reason to believe that it actually happened
What are you making a documentary you really got to show and prove
What you're doing
Instead.
The strong suit instead what they do have is shaky footage of trees
When he's allegedly
Hiking
To break into the
He made the Blair Witch Project
It's found footage
Yeah exactly
The other problem
Is
He's walking around in the
Trees
Santa's half-an-hour later
Create the illusion that he hiked around in the woods to find its way up
Like to hear on knowledge fight.com
This guy
Took Google Maps
And found the spot
Exactly where Alex was
Sometimes I love
It's so amazing
Basically what he ended up doing that
Is walked
About 50
He made almost like doodoo
Area that he would have to walk
To get to where he says he ends up
This parking
Parking area
And gets picked up five
What is so close
To the external Road
There's no way that it would take half an hour
Even with his bloated
Out of shape ass
Fresno
It's just literally impossible
The only explanation
He got it in
No
Conspiracy theorists
A lot of weirdos
Heart of the globalist
That makes perfect
Perfect right
The more likely reality
Is Alex Jones took a nap
It's Alex Jones
Psyching himself out in the middle of the Woods
He's afraid
That's possible and that's why
Possibility is
He wants to presented as it's super hard to get in but as Philip.
It's really not all that
Necessarily
Or whatever
I think that the shuttle that shows up
So if you're in the Bohemian Grove parking area which is clearly accessible
Really as we've not far from the road
If you're in
Cuz it's just a shuttle that runs
Consistently
So he gets it there
Airport shuttle
The problem is if you look at it
When you get picked up by the shuttle
MN
There's not a whole lot
The goes on
I meant he has footage
The Cremation of care ceremony
And its pitch black
It's just completely dark out
Right
He must
Footages
Hey Zach I went to this place this place in this place
Damn
It's super dark out
It's the dead of
They don't show how they leave
So
Higher career
Is built on something
People have already done
Yeah and he's clearly edited in a way that is
Manipulative
Play the most liked most likely
Didn't even really
The most likely scenario is that it
I imagine maybe Securities lease up now
Just because they're horrifying world religion for 1,000
Isabel
I think that they're like here's my
Real world scenario what I say
Think happened
He knew that this was a very opportunistic way he could make a name for himself
Cuz he wasn't cutting it
As a local conspiracy guy
He
Maybe red
Article
Baby he knew about
The Grove
From these news reports do exist from the back
California from
Texas it's a big trip
We have to get some
Of course so he knows he can sneak in pretty easily but he have to present it is really difficult cuz otherwise
Sacred Space that he's broken into it's just
You want these old dudes
Day Camp
Enjoy
So he kept in
And there's nothing nefarious happen
Globalist
Crazy
If you put that out
Problematic
Wendy's inside there's not all that crazy s*** happened
People drinking
He narrates
What size
Which is what
Even wanted around
People probably like it
Man tears
Don't f****** Alex
Zodiac
Blends in
Bunch of drunk people easy The Cremation of care ceremony
It does if you don't know what it is
It does look like
Weird
It's not like
Knowledge has changed my ability to be like f****** weird on the same level of taking communion
You're eating the body of
What are you doing
Anyway
I can't with this
To a f****** satanic
Never wrestled
The fact that
He's lying
Another subtitle to The Alex Jones
Biography
Never wrestled with the fact that he's lying it's perfect so cuz you have all these powerful people
It is a real social club that tons of
Elites in business and politics go to
And
If you can use that as a way to connect them all
In some sort of shadowy evil organization
Satanic
Exactly and unfortunately
Upon scrutiny none of it
Matches up
None of it is real Alex
You're busted
Man it makes
Oh give this caveat to the busting
Alex
You 90% but
He claims that a lot of the reason that there's not
Footage of a bunch of stuff
It's cuz he's using one hour
1 hour-long tape
But even if that's true
Bears
At least like there have to be 20-something hours of footage that wasn't
You can be on bus
If you really really really Seurat
And hopefully you did it on VHS
Is beta
I'm willing to believe you
I mean not about the stuff bike
The conclusions you draw about the satanism
The viewers before you going in it being out very public thing
But I'm willing to believe that you broken
If you will release
People types
Which you will do
Because you're a liar
And your propaganda
Cuz you don't listen to the
You faked the thing that made you
Adulation
Perfect
Origin story for this
Inveterate
Unending
Well you find out that this is probably a lie
Radio show
He find out that his mom kicked them off of her knee when he was six
Check
You are listening
I want to know
Alex would you like to be a policy wonk
Did you kill your dog
You got it
Yeah she got her now and release the tapes and release the tapes
You murdering your dog
Anyways I think that means
Hey what's going on
This is
What was Walter Cronkite
The full episode
We love you and join the policy wonk
Mallige underscore fight on Twitter
Look us up on iTunes libreview that way more people
Bookingfind us
If you met and please if you if you're considering donating we are
We're serious about trying to start a Public Access TV show
Funding for it cuz
Have a good camera
We need to set up this desk in Subway
Minimal expenses but this stuff I can't handle
Anyway
You know I know the Bohemian Grove really that kind of narrative
That's
Can I ask you a question
Is it about April
Central member of a human Brew I think it might be
Actually my real question is
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color