Damn important
I have great respect for this knowledge fight
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Jordan Jordan
What's up
My bright spot today Jordan
Is something that actually happened a little bit back but it's
Been reflecting on its
Appropriate for the 500th episode don't do it here
Suede is smooth in that little 500 Drive
Yeah for sure
Futsal betamerica
So I recently was
Did by listener Sarah back to give a little bit of a Q&A session discussion with
The college course
Such a rewarding interesting experience to be you know
Ask to talk to these college
It's about issues like researching
Topix
And
It was it was amazing
These kids were great all those scary I'm scared I'm scared of college kids
They look so young they are adults
It's technically that scares the s*** out of me
That is a problem and then also like I remember back when I was in college
I would just be disapproving by Nature sort of like the default look
On your way
I'm used to being a stand-up and and I want to
Elicit a response or positive
To imagine like
Leaving myself
Can College look at my face
Convey a message
Invoice from doing stand-up and teaching you know like they were teachers or how they were stand-ups in
It never occurred to me that you would have
Have to stand up in front of all the
The same types
The people
But they don't
Make a response at all
It's terrifying because of their
They're a crowd but they're not a crash
I can't do crowd work I'm not going to do a little 5 minutes up top every time
Thank you so much to sarabeth and those it was just a great experience
First really first
I think
I think I can put that in my title
Oh my bright spot Dan normally would be that assassin
Creed Valhalla is coming out
Not yet it's not here with me being able to do a preemptive one with Pikmin
But I won't be using that
Because Dan
My audiobook
Is finished and it is up on the website for everybody to download at
Their Ledger
School is really fun to do thank you very much for helping
Sing me producer made of tiny cameo
If you rated there are some Easter eggs and some weird things that are there on purpose I promise you to confuse you and kind of
Disorienting for a little lost.
That's where they can find it
I'm excited that it's how people can enjoy
The fruits of your labor with by which I mean screaming
Can my apartment
Go straight from listening 24 hours of us talk
Get rid of the best part of this haha
The great idea to listen to my audiobook get rid of me and replace it with you doing voices
Is despite what you say
I'm very happy
We got an interesting thing to do
A little bit
Election-time Infowars I've been hearing about
Might be a little bit different
Then what people could have
Expected
Last week Jordan we talked about how
Be too difficult to do an episode about the election to be released on that when
Wednesday and I remain true when it came time to record Friday's episode
At that point there was just
Too much uncertainty
I felt very difficult to discuss the whole thing with our kind of
Having any feelings of closure about the election itself
On Sunday as we record Monday show more of a sense of finality
All the networks have called the race for Biden and it looks
Looks like guy the basis for any kind of legal challenge Trump's campaign to make
Lb week
And it'll probably go nowhere
Everybody celebrating the Biden winnows
Huge raise a glass to the on-the-ground organizers and vote already
Extreme activist
In those Battleground States
The kitties of leave gone the other way
It's still mind-blowing anywhere near that close but
Country probably owes a deep debt of gratitude to a
Kana people
Whose names you'll likely never know
So now I'm more of a sense of what's going on I feel like I'm standing on more solid
It's time to get to Alex's election coverage what happened
Or maybe not
As I reflected over the weekend I had a bit of
Yeah that was what's up with you like a baby.
Qdel
I had a bit of a realization Jordan
A large part of motivation for me doing this podcast with my revulsion
And seeing Alex and his crew laughing
At the diverse crowds of Hillary supporters crying on Election night 2016
Mocking would what was for many of them a very real and just
Define existential fear
So now the tables are turned a little bit
And we have an opportunity to laugh at his behavior on the like
Tonight went things
Didn't go his way
Do we mock his
Appears comfortable in the knowledge that they're probably fake
And even if they are real the things he is afraid of aren't real
Is it just as bad for me to do a show where I relish
In his election night mode
Obviously the answer to that is no
It wouldn't be just
Is bad for me to do that would be totally cool
I'd love it
But also I'm not going to do that but for slightly different
What Alex Jones did on Election night literally doesn't matter
We can block his freaking out and yelling the same bulshit he yells everyday we can discuss his very dubious claim
You decided not to go on rugans Livestream Winona cord we can talk about his obvious intention
Incite violence but here's the thing
The most disrespectful
Roofing I think
You can do is it arms of Alex's election night coverage
Easter treated how deserves to be treated
And that's to say who gives a
Oh yeah
You a******
The lashing out the tears that yelling about demons
It's all meaningless
Some pills might have gotten sold but if I'm going for schadenfreude I'm not going halfway
And saying we'll talk about your election coverage sometime but it's
Totally not important now that's way harsher than playing clips of Alex yelling nonsense
And then say haha your guy lost
Yeah that's true
So we're good talk about the election coverage
Another time
Maybe a year from now who knows I don't know
It's not out of respect for Alex and his crew in this difficult time
Out of it deeper disrespect
I'd like it so
F*** all of you Infowars
Twist that you have right here
The reality is that Alex is now entering Uncharted Territory
His audience has been led to believe that any non Trump win would be the result of large-scale election
Thereby make
Any Biden presidency illegitimate
Further use
Extensively characterized
His opponents
From high-level politicians do street-level activistas pedophiles
In the employ of the literal Christian devil
Over and over again he said that Trump getting elected was the equivalent of the biblical story of God given the reprieve
Nineveh
And that story Jonah isn't listed by God to warn the people of Nineveh to repent of their evil ways
But he decides to go so
Somewhere else
He ends up getting swallowed by whale then realizes I got a job to do
It's a ghost gets out of the whale
I am then he convinces everyone there to repent
Thereby saving the city from God's judgment
According to the wake Alex characterizes
Is Trump's role as being reminiscent of this story
Combined with the people of the United States not deciding to repent by getting on board with Trump
Who's my pretty leads to a different conclusion
Jonah story
We're all going to get eaten by a bigger whale
This is kind of more like Sodom and Gomorrah
Anyways it Alex
Characterizing
If you take Alex seriously Alex's. His audience that his enemies are literal demons dead-set on the killing of the entire planet
Appease Lucifer and turn into robots or whatever
And that Trump was the US's only chance to repent and be saved
Now that that has been passed
It seems like it's time to become a full-on wrath-of-god doomsday preacher
That's one possible Avenue Alex could be going down
I honestly have no idea what Alex
David will be but I'm interested to see how much of the stuff you retains and how much you just pretend
I never said that s***
His audiences captured
So he could just start walking another Direction
As long as he talks
Fast enough and Jingles lose Keys around
Still retain some percentage of the auto
Some new Route 10
Colonel will tell Alex about some new piece of Intel that'll make everything make sense
Are there still good guys fighting off the devil inside the government
Or something
We'll see what he ends up doing but I've learned
Not just to assume that the boat is going to sink
Because it looks like boy that boat
Alex still has a few cards
The boat should
Have enough holes in it
And his box
Should have no air holes in it and that should be enough to
To take him down
But it doesn't seem to be
Asher
So I'm going to leave desperate an intensely boring electoral Alex to his game
He can try to whip up excitement about his attempt to Brandon Trump's lame-duck session is the 79 days of hell but I do
I don't think that's going to catch on
I wouldn't be surprised if Alex even loses interest in it before January comes around
But where does that leave us
What are we going to cover here for today's up
Episode 500
Well I found that the show works best when I follow my heart and my aunt
And there's only one thing that I want to talk about today
And that's how it
Infowars has been reeling
At the beginning
Are they 79 days of hell
We can talk about Alex going to Maricopa County on Thursday and using
An adult-sized bullhorn to yell about how they needed to stop counting ballots but
Honestly it just seems like a waste of time
The reason Arizona's been calls for Biden and honestly that wasn't much more than a sad and
An entirely predictable publicity stunt on Alex's party
No that would be a waste of time
What I want to discuss is something far more
Which is what happens to a propaganda Outlet
It's run by a tyrannical Central Authority
When they were anointed god-king is losing an election and their tyrannical Central Authority runs off to Arizona to do a poop
Bestop
How does the leaderless
And almost certainly confused underling who works there how did they keep the operation going how did they respond
How long has he been gone well he's back now but in the. He left on Thursday after his show
I think he got back on like Saturday for 2 days
He just wasn't there might have been back on Friday I'm not entirely sure work at covering Thursday evening
Okay into Friday morning
Watch a bunch of incompetent people scramble around and fantastic
On Thursday
I present to you George
Episode 5
For why Infowars doesn't work without Alex
Before we get down to business on that
Give a shout out to
To folks who was made
These past five hundred episode 40 nights
Likely done
So first Kev Kev please thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Whereabouts Cafe
Thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
It's just all the vowels
Taking out a demo house to prayer
Dr. Milton Wigglesworth
I'm a policy wonk Milton
Thank you very much Aunt Eva Boogeyman
And thank you next
Christopher
Thanks Christopher
Very much this person
Has a bone to pick with someone named Peter from Denver
Ruler of the walks
Attention
And Denmark Feud
Are you saying there's literally prevalent that there may be trouble ahead
We have a contender title of
Blank of Denmark
Peter from Denmark
Benda from Denmark
From Dad
From Denmark
Thank you so much
Heroin
Is freakishly large
Dying
Yes thank you very much dying that's from Denmark to stay out of this conflict
And see who comes out on top of that I was always on their side
Who sent us a wonderful care package
I thought that we'd done the whole technocrat Shadow but I believe we might have forgotten or maybe I'm not entirely sure what happened
We've already done it in the
The pass maybe that's awful if we did mess up or Miss
Current temperature
Strong
By declaring the becks
You're not a technic
No no no no
Your Raptor prints
And an order of that I've made a special drop
There was a request that we use the old techno
Minecraft drop because it included the daddy shark
They'll be better if I just made a new one
Which also included the daddy shark 1
The daddy shark 1 hour
So thank you so much packs also thank you we got a special pack of episode
500 package
They're going to be opening on a bonus episode they'll be out on Friday hahaha
Looks cool
Sweepstakes we appreciate you very much and my apologies that I'm absolutely terrible
It's social media correspondences
Raptor princess
I'm a policy wonk
Aaliyah baby shark dddd
Hillary Clinton
Mama shark eddp
Inside
The freeways were met before
Hate myself
I feel like a complete failure
Thank you very much Mac
Wonderful new job
Play It Again
Now let's jump into this episode
Cuz we are deep into the
We're going to start here on November 5th
We are past the election
Alex is reeling
You know think of the account is still going on bro
Call indication
I'm sorry that you know things are not looking at
That great for Trump
But they all involve Pennsylvania
And then some other things also
Is it
Conservatives are
Talkin Rebrand coyote and the roadrunner
Who painted The Way Forward on the wall and Alex is the one who crashes headfirst into reality
It's out where he's at
I want to give you the big announcement here
If Joe Biden gets in there never getting rid of the lock
It's a lot bigger than just kicking Trump out in
They want a bank rob
Dodge
And then have us have an app
Believe our front door and step one foot outside of our house
Admitted
Global strike on playing
So I guess that's now the angle is
If Biden gets in then the lockdown is never going to end
Covid-2 you're forever with something that one might even be hard for his followers
To buy
Really you're going to say that
Joe Biden is just going to say everyone stay inside
Also what do you want us to do now the elections over
The lockdown already happened and nobody listen to it anyways
What are what are we going to Viking going to change about that he's going to have even the Lesser
Evil
Probably less willing to use a lot of the forest Trump
It has been I mean except for against left
Well but look man
There is there was an election and it was
Trot
With a fraud
Yeah there's a lot of it
I don't remember the
Maybe you didn't hear about this
Okay
Videos of
Individuals in Michigan arriving with those ballots
At 4 a.m. illegally and going into the building
With ballot
Boxes
The Demerol for Biden
The arrogance level is
So
Atrocious
I don't even know
So is he in flag
Good China
Send people from
Michigan
With Mark Ballas for Biden ostensibly
Also coming from China
The Box itself is the only thing that you probably see in videos
Turn on the bus
There were a bunch of
These videos that were going around they were like
Drastic misrepresentation television
Pruitt was unloading gear pallets going in
And there was a video that went around that was actually from like
Years ago in Russia
People are just saying
Was that from one of these states
The idea that there was a suspicious
Possibly Chinese person
That's real
That's just
I just real sad on like a
Conspiracy level of just like
Man
Is it could have mailed them to San Francisco and had a white person Drive their why would you why would you fly
Directly from China to David
They land on top of the ballot-counting building
They're going to helicopter from like just of a real world perspective
You listen to it you can
Can kind of hear
What his
Like where he's coming from the story that he's telling
Alex
I would say
Lowe's
2 line
The Nightline is what I like to call the
Saying hey let's do some authentic violence Y close to that line
They are involved in a revolution
Fully
Conquering
The United
States
And killing
Republic
And they're hammering the last
Nails in
To the damn coffin to bury us
Alive as slaves of their sister
I'm not a macho guy I don't say things just to say I'm
But I'll tell you this
I'm not going to watch any offensive line
At this point
Because I've not
Think about
The right course it has
But I do this
If we let them steal this election and we let them put a Chinese Communist agents fully compromised with all the proof
That control the nuclear codes
All about
Are the destruction of our country and a Handover
Authoritarian Nation the world's ever seen
Communist China
And I will not be in accomplish
This type
I'm take over
So if I understand correctly what he saying first I have to take issue with the idea that you said I haven't
Time to think about
Yeah.
I would suggest that you've been thinking about this almost non-stop 495
Pretty much the only thing you've been talk of it any thought to when you
Start being violet
Wow the course of history blah blah blah
The course of history
Not if you understand what he's saying he's saying
Is
Controlled by China
So if we buy we aiming Alex on the paper
If we allow Joe Biden to take office with a nuclear codes and what have you
Uark
Complicit in aiding and abetting
The Chinese Communist takeover
I mean
That would be getting into office will be the condition
And then for offenses viola
Descendants all of this is simply
I am not
Counseling
Actual violence
Until
They're swearing him and I guess
But once they swear him in
Well yeah we got to blow it up because they're the most Authority
Thor if you could do something that you could
Conceivably like argue is going to
Stop him from being sworn in
Gradle MetLife limousine in front of the gate
To the White House
If you can't get anybody guess what
Never becomes president
Doing well
Yeah
Is just it it's bland
I would describe
This show
As Flash
There's there's very little going on that even Pete
Peaks my interest you at all
The hits
It just kind of like him saying the same thing
I got a hitting his base
Bieber criminals in a broker
The shadow out of America
And they want
Atomizer family and domestic
So we can never rise again and never resist
The nightmare future they've got
All of us
The chains are going on right now
You're being Des
Enfranchise all of us
Bolinao
So that Ward is not becoming
We are now entering the
Season of War
Our country is at War for its very life
You are under attack
You are being conquered
You are being taken over
We were in the midst of a chai combat
Cover of the country and we're losing right now
I just can't
Feel anything. Anymore
Personalized like I was thinking about it whenever we heard the first clip of him talking
King and then I realize that right now the only thing I'm
I'm interested in
Really is
Is he going to take the plunge
You know what is he going to do what is he going to do are you going to take the leap or you're going to back off and if you back off
F*** you forever and if you take the leap alright now let's see what's happening
Do you change your whole brand to God
Like you are becoming televangelists Alex drawer whatever
That seems to be the way to make
Way better body than what he's doing and it seems like a place where he could
Play a lot more games about like
Stay depression an actual Church
Right
Becoming Scientology and then like just
Made it his
Entire life
Information to be a non-profit
For the government not to text him
See that working
Yeah that might be the next best thing
I agree I agree with you it's like I'm not I'm not really interested in
Yelling about
The Chinese
I
Really
You know
Maybe it's just a momentary thing but I'm a little bit bored
By the
Do you like
Waffle around
Offensive violence
We know what you're doing if yeah really
I'm not interested in his going to Phoenix into a bullhorn
I'm not that interested in it
I'm a little bit of
Was too big
For me to be bad interested
I agree I think he got two notes
Yeah
I mean
It's just as the most interesting is like what are you going
You have a problem
And I want to see how you fix it
Or at least I want to see how you deal with it cuz I
I don't think you're going to fix
That's a probably a good note
Correction
What are the things he's doing right now
Is
See him do a lot
At times when
I think people could probably
Predict
That there's going to be
A possibility for some viola
I think any
Thinking person
McKinney's
Specific predict
Anything but
But I do think that as we
We great closer to the inauguration
We do see
Probably an increase
Danger of
Some kind of
Right-wing violence
I don't know that it's going to happen and it very well may not but I think
The odds
I'm kind of a thing
Happening
Baby
It's impossible
Yeah
I think Alex recognizes that until he goes out of his way to
Two very consistently
I talked about how false flags are cops
I promise you I'm not giving up
Ever
Because I know
The more I bend over
The worst up yet
I will not
And be part of this
What up man I blow something up and say I did it I never do that
Okay
School
We see this all the time and it's of the times that I think that Alex is most keenly aware the people in his
Communities my bus company
This is a good strategy for him to preemptively characterize anything
Them false flagging in order to make us look fat
He doesn't he he goes on this tip quite a bit
And the enemy's next phase will be due
49ers
Or evil
And they will stay Terror attacks and blame it on us
Credit
We need to be ahead of that understand that
And their other forms of civil disobedience
Something in the threat
Continuum
Projection
Movies that point but it is alright
It is
Beauty
The resistance
Means necessary
And we are now at War for our very existence America is on the edge of death
So if you understand that what you saying is that the enemy is going to fall
Flag ya themselves in order to make Alex and his friends look bad and they got to be careful about that but also
I should tell you that there's something called the threat
Continuum projection and then also we have the right to
Terror attack
Yeah I'm confused as to
How old is you can play a game like this where it's like a we would never do those terror terror attacks its
False flag can but whatever if it does happen Bill and then the people are going to be like
Good job we do Terror attacks we loved Arabic with everybody
Alright is all of the
Bogalusa a f****** false flag
I think that might be true or something
Was that
Was Larry Nichols is
Act last act to false flag us with
The proud boys
Uno
Strategy might have I was going through like making that new drop
As I was going through like these old folders of episodes
I like whatever I do that I end up finding something that I completely forgotten about
Like did you remember that a year ago Alex was saying that the queen had joined the Patriots side
Do you remember that
Remember that
Picture of a completely forgotten there was like a two-day stretch where Alex thought that the queen had
I think that's going to be something but if we ever do look back on these four years
Like whatever it'll be funny again and in 50 will look like
At one point in time Alex said literally everyone he
You hated before was a patriot
I'm also that he hates them later it's in everyone
Is everyone a queen has with her dictator switch
Pope is evil but the public
A good today
But someone would never speak ill of
Steven or 500 years from now is it brother
I don't know who this dude it's okay brother-in-law
Okay
We have
Forget cats we have Alex's wife's tennis partner informing us about antifa tax course and Alex's brother in
Coming in
Prison big scoops
And then my own
Brother-in-law
Do I have never seen get mad in the many years I've done
Pause up shaking
Yesterday
I just
Got $50 you know down there Congress
Post office
Well I'm in the post office
Do that
Shaking with anger
Send me a voicemail
He did
They're f******
Give me a goddamn break
Forgetful
Committed voter fraud has like I follow the law
I would never as a far-right person I would never videotape a crime
My brother-in-law knows about all the time I have proof that can make it look nice
No
I can't pull up my phone don't you think there's any event really happened there's a moment in his head where he's like
Well here is his testimony recording audio
The post office
The drop offs
Packages with some products
And
Sky they're real sky
Any other grocery
Re-bag
Filled up with about
50 balance
And he was thinking
Themself in phone
Right there on the counter
And
I can only see the
The ballot
That he had in front of them on the counter
In the one on top of the
The back
But they have the same signatures
Same information on them
And he was just
Taking pictures
Doing one last check
Marking something
And then put them
Stream the back.
Ring for the baby one
On the counter
And no one did anything
And I think about doing some
Think about was
You know
Me getting some kind of federal charge for
You're interfering with the election
This guy
Naked palettes
That is what you would be doing
Late
Cuz I don't think this was a good
I mean if you have a lot of these people doing that
It's going to add up
And the only reason you would do it
To try to overturn
What
State has
Decided in Tech
Texas red
So one can only assume
That these boat
All 50 of them
Going to jail
This this
Sky
Chose
I mean he's the brother-in-law's he's not related by blood now that they're being close to the Jones family
It just makes you
Good at figuring things out
Good at investigating
There's like something in the in their in their family and their extended family that makes them not jump to conclusions about stuff
Nothing really just
Get to the bottom of it
I admire that if you need somebody to help you fill out your ballot does that person also need to
To sign the ballot they do yeah it could have been like a proxy
Siri or something
I've just gone to a nursing
That is a possibility
Or I mean if he's saying that this is like
After election day they might not have been balanced open anything I don't trust this guy
I have no idea what
Did or didn't see I don't even know if he's out with his brother-in-law quick question did he mail in his ballot
I doubt it
Does he know what a mail-in ballot would look like
No idea
I don't trust any of those and I love the part at the end there is like
The only reason you do this
Is to try and change things
And Texas went red so therefore already potoo
All these votes that I have just decided AR-15 I didn't count them I have no f****** idea
They must all be
Dumb dumb
Texas is already got right I suppose they hadn't called the other states with this time okay
They're being sent from Texas
The other state
NFL are you guys got you guys got to work on that if that's the case I mean it's 50 votes
What kind of
I don't know
I think it's a stupid
Texas by a million
There's only one solution
Fair enough
IQ
Think of anything everyone in the United States agrees is the worst idea that anyone could ever do
Let's do it again
The most stressful time it doesn't matter what
Siri robot
Don't do it again
Anything but that okay fine bye
Let's not do another election how about we know the five is one
The comeback
I'm going to say this right now
Whatever happens with Trump he's done the right thing fighting this but he didn't fight the central
We're in the bed we're in now
We're going to have to sleep in it
But if we get
Globalist takeover at the end of the country as we know it
And that it's illegal
Stealing the election
What's happened
And if we
Proof
We're going to nullify
Percent
Not have a fake investigation
Because we've got him red
Episode
Supercuts
Institutional
Where can I buy the legend of
McConnell do it without a trial
You know you if you're caught red-handed you still go to trial
If you get caught killing somebody they just hang you right then and there that simple
Call Dan alleged
Killer unless you're far-right murder in which case
You didn't actually do it was a false flag
I guess
Alex wants to know this this isn't going to work
I don't I don't think
Strange was this is like
Oh
Like I said flat
Feels like nothing
And then Alex as a guest on this guest
I don't know what the fuc
Fuckyous dude
So this person is named Amanda Milius
Haha she is the daughter of John Milius
He's the director of Conan the Barbarian Apocalypse Now and of course
Red Dawn
Alex's favorite documentary Red Dawn
I'll maybe producer
Okay I was going to tell you because there's a pretty famous guy who directed apocalypse
Directed any of those invited them over wrote them or something
Call Mick
Whatever
She's become a trump propaganda
Sure that you just released a film called
The plot against the president
And so
She is in
Interesting things to talk about
I love the smell of a huge part of why I left Hollywood I was listening to Infowars all the time
And I left and I went in a volunteering 2016 in Nevada
Which by the way Nevada is is it huge
Battleground for us right now Nevada's where everything's happening
And and I ended up leaving Hollywood completely joining the Trump Administration working at the state department
How's your family
Therefore they're pretty happy
Not to be a dick but Amanda Milius is not somebody who you would say walked away from a vibrant career in Hollywood
If you check out her IMDb page has two primary credits as a director one being this new Trump film
Show me other 18 2015 short called the Lotus Gun
Her only credit as a performer are as herself in a documentary about her dad
And appearances on Tucker
Carlson & Sebastian Gorka show
Most likely promoting Trump and her new propaganda film
It's all good to do this interview and be like hey look at this famous movie person's daughter who likes
It's entirely another thing to pretend that you would like an A or B or even
C-list
A person and then walked away from it to get on board with Trump
That's insulting to her and his listeners movie person of course his daughter
Tendons of his
Success has also become a massive sea
Success in the film industry what was that know of
Yeah and you were there she said she worked in the state department yeah
She apparently was involved in Trump's state
There is a feeling of her being here almost in a beneficial
Trump propaganda film that you just released
Wow she had
To get the state department
Is just a just a bizarre
Is it appropriate
Think someone with
Less than my resume should work
The state department
And I don't think I should work at
State Department
I'm going to get even worse cuz we introduced another weirdo head
Alright
I love Ali Alexander he's been on fire long time
You talk about how you just suddenly brought us together
Nnn reached out
Got a bunch of people together and now this is a super viral moment
So Allie Alexander is
This Zealot weirdo it's been coming on Alex's show a bit
Now he's involved in something called
Bastille
Which is the other doing the airliner update
It's maybe the catchphrase of a lot of these
Totally not AstroTurf 100%
Grass router
I don't care whatever I'm more interested in the fact
I only remember this because
We just talked about it
Stop the steel was the name of the things that Rodger Stone was involved in 2016
Jesus Christ
Rodger Stone
You got sued about how man
2016 is the year all their evil tricks worked in 2020 is the year they almost works
But everybody found them far more disappointing and sad
Social super weird
It's the same name is the same name
For your protest movement seems very strange to me
It makes me wonder if Rogers somehow involved
But I have no idea
He is nowhere to
Still have the email address
@yahoo probably
So Ali wants
Alex wants
The new election
Only in the states the Trump lost
Well because there's a recall
You know
Unfortunately even winning Nevada wouldn't put us over
That puts us at 26
55 or 2
Q66
We have to win
Pennsylvanian what Kine o it's not popular Republican party doesn't want me to say this
We need a Revo in Wisconsin and we need a revota Michigan
We are going to get a recount in in Wisconsin but here's what I'm afraid of Alex
I think the Democrats have baited us
Into a rig
Recount
God
Recap rap
Sky's classical
Guys
You just lost
We didn't
Paint you into a Rico
Trap no one wants a recount it's a classic recap track
It's not even if it's a setup
Every election since Hoover
This is what he thinks
The Democrats big prestiges at the end of the film they like
And we wanted you to do the recount the whole time we won the state and we want you to force a recall
Capsule weekend also with
More
So we can win more this time I can't imagine why the Republican Party
So he believes
Sally believes that trumps just got to seize power
But we certainly need to use the full weight of the federal government
And and and what we got to do is we the people have to say you have a mandate to do that
President Trump.
Any candidate in American history
The idea
Just visualize this go to your child and ask him
Do you think that Joe Biden would be the
Top vote-getter in American history
No nobody believes that
And so we know that it's rigged they just had a plus one system
Where did every Republican. They came in they found a dead person they found a covid ballot
Somebody did a mail-in ballot and then voted in
An election day 2
They rigged the election there's nobody who's going to believe that buying is most popular politician in American history
Do for me
So excuse me if we win by
66%
This is dumb
I would say
Don't ask your child
This question is a lot of surprises
Yeah yeah sometimes you'll be surprised
Act like a six-year-old with no prior actual experience
And really no understanding of the American system at all whether or not biting would be the most popular candidate
See that no one would think
In a bubble Biden would get the most votes
Has anybody ever
But I think if you look at the context that makes a little more sense if you consider
Haha a lot of that is
Is voting against
Trump
It makes sense
Yeah yeah yeah but he's like yeah
Because Yuki
Get a magic child couldn't imagine that someone likes by and more
That's not good thinking about a bill
That's real Bash
Sucks
Any leaves and Amanda and Alex
Start talkin about life
Drudge man
Grudges grudges gone
He doesn't like us anymore
What happened
I didn't you tell me you know I might everybody thinks he was kidnapped and there's somebody else
Someplace because this is very bizarre his behavior this year it's very weird
It's not helpful is what it is but whatever his
Game as I'm not super into it but
But anyway
What he blackmailed was he kidnapped
They're willing to do anything
I think
He was at the White House somebody to listen to him he's awesome Trails got really pissed
They were standing up against censorship
And
CNN
At least it
Seems like
Elise stefanik
I don't have five
I'm not trying to be a wash right I don't care
I don't know
CNN
And it's
Flavor it's their signature matches very very well
Finlayson MN
When we go back to the steaks
Words like
He said nothing
Drudgereport is leasing
Georgia's leasing The Drudge Report to CNN
Who's the contract like
Dogman
Contract to because you can't really run off to some extent is it
Hardin
Is everybody good
To share or is it like the
The Super Bowl thing where you can only buy a okay
If this does mean something that imagine
Did the hero of your media sphere the guy who has
Directed
The course of
Conservative talk radio for the last like 20 years
The guy who can make or break people
Therefore brought us Breitbart
The guy who's like
Responsible for so many s*******
Also someone who's site
You can lease
People that something that I think they would
But that would be like I'mma come with her he's a grifter prior
Prior
You working for
Murdock can't afford his prices anymore now it's just seeing it is that the implication
It's actually kind of touchdown what probably could be a reasonable explanation
And that is
The Drudge got LED in a little bit
Saw the disorder is although quote-unquote
Betrayal recognized the Trump wasn't taking the issues of like online censorship seriously
He would be super interested in giving
His brand
In his entire mark
Space you would think I'm so he followed his principle which is
Can support this anymore or whatever
How to get rid of 2:30
I act gay
Conservative media
So I am
If they do that
Cuz I'm now a single-issue voters and your guy
Kill my best bigstackd Lee
Recognize the game that he understands actually what's going on but you got to play some fun things
Family Style by CNN kidnapped or blackmailed whatever
Have a fun time with
Fat butt
Whatever dude
Another question
Not only what's up
With my drug
What's up with Trump
Where's he been
Let me ask you this question cuz you are an Insider
Patriot lemon
I was flipping out
The dancing lights
Was amazing
I want to see him Oval Office address of every fraud
Fireside chat
Shelly-Ann
No Gateway pain and I think she'll the best job overall Dallas and pores on video the best butt
I don't care I'm going to win
He should be up there showing it
But then he's been
Dead Silence
And then
Part of the crew
They all separately
Cuz I respect
Where is he
Ataxia
And he's going to see what we do
That is
A great leader
Our fearless leader he is
Decided to allow us
To choose what he will do
Based upon our
Disorganized action
I've kicked it away.
So if
It goes bad
It's kind of our fault
Ball in Ark
Just didn't
The building
Update
What you do whatever you got to do
What a leader
You know what
I'm almost
I'm almost like
Goddamnit America can't even get a good dick day
Good dictator like we're just shity people we're just shooting people got two other places know how to get a
Dictator you don't like it
30 dictators
They know what they're doing
It's a little
Strange
The position that Alex has put in his like he's he's he's presented this guy is like strong
Compass
A good leader
It in a position where you're like
Everything is
Is pretty
Uncertain
Things are tense
There's election
I'm counting going on
He's not assuming a leadership position all that's right
Though the thing he's supposed
Yeah you can do that without asserting power or claiming you won the election you can still be visible
Xavier
This is going along the processes move and we support the vote counter Zelda
There is a way to do that
And still like give the appearance
It's someone's here
Charge app
Instead do Alex even recognizes
I don't f****** know I don't know if I've seen Trump's intellect yeah and no one knows what to do
And if you look at all of the people on the bed like this is maybe another thing that we got lucky with
Because Trump such an
In actually shity leader
Everybody went ape shitt
In their own little pockets like
Throughout all of election night and as the votes of
Come in and they they
Declared it for Biden
You see more of those little pockets of everybody
Frantically
Disgusting with all their friends
But there's no unified yeah we're going to do this it's everybody's separate like
I don't know what to do
You hasn't said anything
I don't know what to do I don't know what to do I don't know
Lead us to our next clue
Because there's a phenomenon that Amanda
Discusses that I think is really interesting powervac
Got to Arizona
In like what
What couple hours like he was like I'm there I'm going and he gathered all those people and did I mean that's what's happening right now is
Is everybody's putting aside any kind of
You know critiques of the administration or whatever is happening in there just
They're just jumping in because this moment is everything
She repeats that a number of times about like people like Mike crnkovich inject
Osoba can all these people these influencers
Farallon
Presumably on the same page cuz you haven't like Ali Alexander on another one
Do they all put aside their differences
Any luck we got
How to do something right
Had no s*** they are
Their game is over
Recognize
The door is closing
On the scams they've been running
Is like Trump he's going to destroy my business
Assertive itches like
I think we should probably start a war because they're f****** up my business
We're just whatever like we are going to very quickly
Not have much rather
As the opposition right there is already
I guess I could just be an MRA guy again
Do my pickup artist thing again maybe just get your real estate license
Giselle
Yeah
That's when I was kind of interesting I don't experience it because I don't know what any of these damn dogs are up to
To privately play
It is it is
Hear her say like
All everyone putting their
Their heads together and figure out how to survive
The swamp
Congealed how do we how do we escape this
Let's claim Laura Loomer actually won
That is very good
Stupid
Because all man the here's the great thing about later on
And here's my here's my guess
We're going to see a very close parallel
Between what happens at Infowars whatever Alex is
God and what happens in the far-right when it
Hallandale be some
Some fractioning you know something
I think there'll be some splintering off but you'll see you'll see kind of
I think what's going to happen to everybody is basically what's happened to
People who've been kicked off Twitter
Sort of spiraled a little bit even if you had
A platform
This is worse than worse
Yeah
And I think
Did you know you're really see the difference
30 people who have
Something
And are safe
Yeah.
That people like Jack pasovic and Mike cernovich are not
Secure I don't think they're stable
A media position
People like Ben Shapiro
Or Alex
They are
There is like Alex Hudson
Issues to iron out and figure out what you're going to do
And a gigantic media operation
A bunch of his audience
But you'll figure out something
Ben Shapiro's probably going to be embarrassed
For a little bit
But he'll be fine
He'll be fine we'll figure out something to do
Check pasovic is going to keep working it like what these
Fringe oan type Outlets
Just know where there's no path forward there
Speaking of people who are going to be fun
Because they just have a big enough brand
James O'Keefe comes on
You think James will keep is going to be fine
Has enough of brand
And name recognition inside of like the larger
Conservative
So you're sure that he could sort of abandoned a lot of these like
Things that are tailored to the Trump base and he could be fine I think
He's if you're associated with Andrew Breitbart personally I don't think you're ever going
Going to be away for you to keep
Failing upwards yeah
And he's on with a
Arable phone connection
He's just talking about voter fraud it's really hard to listen to because the voter online is awful
Yeah there's also very sad
It honestly comes off last
About Alexa
He's trying to prove some kind of claim
It seems more like he has this narrative that he wants
To sell to people
He's trying to recruit other people to play the role of whistleblowers for him
Like to use them as props
Multi-level marketing
What we need today
Muller
People
Kohl's
People Whirlpool washers
Handlebars
Tupelo The Wiz
Reason Army opposed
Florida cannabis
Now is the time
Today tonight
I don't wait our destiny our future are are very Birthright been stolen
Unless people
Takamaki beard guest star in my next video the way he gets all of his quote whistleblowers
I found it very uninteresting
So Alex has now decided at this point in the show
I got to go somewhere
Cernovich went to Arizona and people seem to enjoy that
There's people yelling
In States
This is still wet concrete
Yeah he could still do something
Are still some attention
Arizona seems like it's getting
Closer so that might be one where we actually might
Maricopa County Ohio who I also love so much
Has Alex decides he's got to go somewhere but he does
Doesn't know where
Go to
Fitback what's going on
Arizona
Where should I go to Georgia
Should I go to Michigan
God almighty
You're try to fly direct from MOS eisley's Arizona
Analog clock
Do you have to take a couple of stops riches
You know we all know that he eventually ends up going to Arizona videos really
Difficult time
I'm figuring out where to go
The Show Goes On to like earlier
He was kind of just like puzzling over why Trump is
Not appearing right anywhere and he's kind of like guys just letting the people act
That was earlier
Every show goes on he starts to get a little bit
Mad about the fact that Trump is hiding
It begins Democrat lawmakers call on Twitter
Remove US president from the plateau
What's your 100 times more lateral
Where is the president
We haven't seen him unless I'm wrong crew your watch
As much as I do more
Two eyeballs to eyeball
Panera
Has Trump been saying
It's 3:30 in the morning on Wednesday
Just asking
36 hours ago as anybody seen the president
Did the Cookie Monster eating
Cookie
Where is the president
Where is the present
Defend the president
I love the president in the great job
But I mean
We're in the middle of
Alamo Warriors
And we ain't seen Colonel Travis today now
Huh
Just like the real Colonel Travis off drunk somewhere I mean like
I don't know I don't take fault with that thought
Devoid of anything else you saying it's like yeah you should be
You should be frustrated
Guy really guiding
The folks
Is that is that why it is
What have all of those predictions of like trumpism is never going to leave us rrall countered by the fact that we
And expect them to eventually be like
Hey Trump sucks
I think so you finally betrays them at the end
They're finally like all s*** we got caught
No I think a lot of the underlying things are we have to be more worried
And someone who isn't
As much of a very
Clear con man
Carrying out some of those political thing
The flaws in our system that Trump is
Is exploited the recognizing
But there is no reason
To not act like a dick hole
And there are no reason to follow Norm
Apparently because
Because
Some people do
Unwritten rules are just drifting
People generally been
Beholding to a lot of those things and I think Trump is really
I exposed that there's no reason there's no consequence
Baseball if you do a backflip too egregious
Hit in the back with him
We get to hit Trump in the back with a fastball
Over conman it somebody's a lot more capable and has the same sort of
Policies that appeal to people will recognize the ways in which they can
Break Unwritten rules and really worried about
And I think
Set those people will again fall for
For that
So Alex
I need to go somewhere
I haven't
Team Trump on TV in a long time
A motherfuking take a nap
Maybe I'm going to get a jet airplane fly Mia
DC
That's where I need to be
That I'm trying to like
I can't
I have to go to my sleepy
Place
A joke
Name of that
I literally I'll go take a 30-minute nap
Answer to something
I go to bed and I'll have a dream of what to do I got to
Dial in my subconscious
And I
Have the engine turn off
With in my mind what do I do and I'll wake up with the answer
Is it d.c.
Is it George
Is it
Arizona
Is it Detroit
Go to hell
But I mean I just can't sit with us
And do nothing
I got to take a shower
Oh my God
Country Club
I got to do something I just there's so much history going on at got to do something
I will take a nap
Dream by delish
The reason
Teresa
I do recognize that even with Trump not being in power
I'm still entirely fascinated by Alec
And the reason is
It's a compelling psychodrama
It is
Where in the where in the next season where he's just confused for the next year I think he'll be confused for a bit
But I think he'll land quicker than
Maybe he's
You should just go to Tibet
That's where people find themselves at know when takeover
Just become a f****** Buddhist out there just do it calm down relax live your life a little better blue be interested
But there's a 30% chance that he won't need to do
Okay
I give
Trump 30% chance
Pull this out
The broad
But now it's nobody came for those babies getting chopped
Kidnapped by the left
Porter Ranch
Good too long and God sick of us
Woohoo
You got to get a better got bad so I guess we've been judging will get a burn
Is really really returning on a hairpin these 30%
Trump somehow proves that the amount of fraud election fraud
That will stay.
Good God
What are we
Patriots are being cold from the internet
And Alex
Has a familiar thing happened to him as he's trying
They're going through everybody that's been identified
As a patriot for this coup
And they're blocking and freezing or Banning or
This is a takeover
When the lights go out
That's when the troops
Come down
This is
At least you're full-grown adults shot a baby in the womb got chopped
We deserve what's about to happen
Get close to Jesus and wake up
Get your head between your legs and kiss your ass goodbye
Go ahead and play that
Wonder Rob do gave us
Predict
All of a sudden happening that was when I talked about
We have that
We're going to have a Moment of clarity
About 2 hours ago
That's wonderful
Just tell him that
No problem
And
Federal meetings about it
But
Phones
Computers have a
Habituated
Amazing
They produce so much information
Better they don't face
Two-Face
That decision
It never happened so that's okay
Show
We're going
Tear that on air
So
Did you just tell me that is employees don't read emails
Maybe they don't do the same for me
They ignore me if I'm not yelling
I can't get tone and email
I tried all caps it doesn't work
I mean
I just thought I'd put that in there cuz I mean
That is what the
This is all about
I know that I've heard this feedback from the audio
If Biden wins
Alex's Tech problems will go away
He'll recognize that he's got to get his s*** together and they'll really clean up
And take care of business
No another storyline to follow a Alex into bet I'm going to call it that this
Sure
I'll go down with that
The show on November 5th
It off to Matt Bragg
Noted weirdo Matt Bracken
Fourth our host
And nothing else at bracket
Alex needs to go somewhere
Need to get some guidance about where to go
So you ask Matt Bracken
Where am I going
I'm planning to get on airplane antenna
Peter Gunn
Arizona
We're going to Georgia
Play the clip
Where do you think
People need to be the most on the ground is it
Detroit
Is it is it
Arizona is
Georgia
Detroit
The multi-front War I would probably
Google say Philadelphia
Because if
If it's if it doesn't happen in Pennsylvania
It doesn't matter the other ones are peripheral
All of the pathway
Toys for Trump require
Good point Matt I'm going to Arizona Donuts
That's creepy.
All right but that's a that's a very good point but I have friends in Arizona and Philly will be
Beat the s*** out of me
People dancing and they want to hurt me
Greedy
Alex
Ghost take a nap I guess
And then the spirits come to have a download to go to Arizona okay
Like that
Owen Shroyer comes in to host the War Room
And
Has a big guest
On the show
I get the sense that by this point
Alex Isley
I think he's already en route to Arizona because there is a sense of like
Which cadalack
Accident on this
She's either taking that nap or he's on
Arizona
Biggest
But dr. Steve pieczenik as we're in the middle of this selections over we're now in the stealing process of the election
What are you seeing what's going through your mind as you're witnessing this gigantic hoax
Happening now in the reason I couldn't come on the Alex
Jones
Show last night was
I was not given the permission that I needed to in order to say what I'm about to
So now
Do not work for the federal government
Make it clear I don't work for the government
Inside a bottle
Just a little bit so you can hear the doctor
Yeah you didn't have permission to
To say something
I didn't get the go-ahead
From Melania
And now we will be taking over everything I am
Concert to Melania
Can I be honest with you
I think that he knew that the shoot wouldn't fly without
I absolutely think how you think of that
Permission mean
That's exactly what I thought because here's what he's got two because I couldn't say this on Alex's show you would let me
Recently got permission guy that got you
Yes he's really a sting operation
Countrywood everybody else said
Trump
Knew this was happening Eric
Give me this was happening and
OneRepublic
I could not say any
What happened was
Weimar
Watermark
Andre ballad
Call the QFC
Ask
Block
Chain encryption
Another words we know pretty well
Wherever it is where it went
And who has
So this is not a
On the contrary
We were verse the entire game
Along the lines
Sun Tzu
The Art of War
And Trump was brilliant and
Is Steve claiming that the election was actually a sting operation
Voter fraud
Where is
The Department of Homeland Security has water marks all of these
Not explain what you mean by that
They can be traced
They know literally where every single ballot is at any point okay
Is Watermark they can
Can tell which ones are fake so there's a bunch of
The real bad reasons why
This is really
Particularly bad
What is
This is a narrative that
Is so provable
If you have this information
If Trump really does have this
First of all he needs to bring it out
This the only thing he needs to do don't want him to be president moral obligation
To tell the nation this is exactly what you would do like the day after they called everybody be like okay
Now we're going to reveal that this is all the sting operation
This backfires because no one cares and they all think I already lost the election
You have this hard evidence that's true hard evidence
Deer season non-falsifiable
They have to be like
They get about kuzin counter kouzan
Movies in the earthquake shadowy things
This
He's too concrete it's absolute
I have a I have another problem
Just one
Alright so he is saying we
I assume he can't
Mean he's not included
Set always talks like that he says that I have
I have 17,000
Send troops in Germany the first person about everything
We have work Bluewater Barclays ballad
But they don't work for the federal government
Do you work for the watermarking all these ballot he's a narcissist
And I visited qanon thing to this we're going around again.
Why is Steve into this
One I think it's cuz he's insecure
Sure
I was researching like Watermark ballots
What are the places that it comes up the most as like a very
Like, like I normally used thing
Hazen Condo Association elections in
Florida
Now Steve
Discussed on a number of websites your condo association elections
Keep them secure
Spencer Lake
I think maybe he has some experience
The idea from that that's very fun and maybe he's projecting that onto the world
Anyway this
Is silly
Yeah it's not good and it gets worse
Expected
All the rest
Is part of the
Sting operation with running
And let me tell you that
48 hours
Not only did we put markers on those
But I can
Say now
With the condition of people in the intelligence
Community in elsewhere
That we have sent out
Thousands and thousands of National Guards
Download
Taxes Arizona
Alabama
So now you have to
Considering rethink what is
Is really about
This is about the cons
Institution clearly
Governors of those
States
And all
States running their own elections
Agreed is watermarking of the ballot
Yeah okay whatever
Depleted
Anyway
Respond if you're Owen
Tara wearing a Hawaiian shirt
The goddamn Alliance
Why not
Here's how I would respond
Steve you've just broken certainly perhaps the biggest news
Since the election here on Earth
Have to play this out logically in my head
Okay
Basically
I keep if I kiss you on the lips right now if it wasn't digitally
Haha
So he's thrilled
Corsi is wants to make this even better
Of course
Come on
People will be arrested as a pet
Tonight
Tomorrow
And it will go on for
Quite a while
And this was
Set total sting operation
That I can say
Okay well
Red wedding will play itself out every night for years to come.
Blood in the streets until only Melania is left
Melania almost had to take the throne
Yeah alright okay just getting a little busy getting a little more to than
Usually
Like he's usually either like
Cranky
Racist
Anti-semitic homophobic
Usually have something going on or like wants to consult Alex
When did you have
Themed appearance
Strange
But I also think that he knows
On some level whether it
It's like rationally and consciously or just sort of
Best not to try that Alex wouldn't put up with this problem I don't know
This election was stolen
That's the business
That's where the money is
You
This is something that's going to be
Completely disproven or it'll be like never proven that why wasn't it
You could be a big problem for us we can't make money off his
It's in your trying to build a pay-per-view match with no one wants to see this is a day long
Story day long story at best and that's only on the War Room distraction for the junior varsity
Yeah
Steve talks a little bit more about this and I still don't
Really understand what
What he's describing really
I would love for him to actually say what all this technology is but
He doesn't do that right
So how is this
Watermark on the ballot
What is the significance of a tattoo
Is it going to stop from fake ballots being counted or or how is that going to be used
Where we use it in any way that we need to use it in terms of
Counting knowing which ones
We're not it's a very
Cicada
So if you just
Start on the way these are
Cyber communication
Locations that we have the code for we know exactly what we
Was thrown away
We know exactly what was played
We know exact
Actually who has it
We know exactly where
I can't do any
Any further than that
Wow this is huge news
Steve pieczenik is breaking on our show right now
Someone call it news
I mean
Yeah I'm going to go without it I don't I don't think I'm going to buy that one if I were having fun today
That Steve's dressed for the occasion
He showed up in his uniform for what this is just b******* the f****** phone
If you know where every ballad is right
Right now from The Fast and Furious movie
If they're fake widen
Can't you tell the people at the
Broward County place
Places that they were fake everywhere had people watching
Cuz you're not a Showman
You got
You don't understand the need for the reveal
This is all my fault I didn't realize that we have to have the procedure why do trick if there is no
You got to do this
I texted that part of its total
11:30 just stole money and then left
Explain a little bit more about what this Takkies describing is how is light so powerful
And then also
What it is a big problem
When nothing comes up
Yeah that's a real problem
Can I take Alex's in
Instincts even if he's desperate
To come up with a way to spend the election
He would know better than to take this on he's going to have
Deal with tomorrow
And the day after in the day
Someone who might have been Chinese who showed up at 4 in the morning
Try and disprove me
Care enough to disprove
But if you start saying some s*** like I know where every ballot is now we weren't rough
Now I got to deal with
S***
Like somebody saying stuff like
Why didn't you just use a barcode
I want to get the little boy
Hi Mom this is Steve inside
And he perhaps just broke the biggest news story of the day
He did it in a floral button-up shirt with a smile on his face from his kitchen
So I'll Fox News and then in mainstream news and all you with your
Billions of dollars in your big pharmaceutical contracts
I'll keep it PG rated you can go fug yourself
Okay
Gofugyourself
And enjoy it as well
Now I want to hone in on what documented broke again folks
Deacon reiterate this in his own words
The whole election theft was a setup
Triad that's my favorite thing
That is
That
What is
Is just the best
That is my
Like what I like to laugh at
Taunting the mainstream fake news
Fire
Defiant in the face of all reality
Listening to the doctors
Steve pieczenik Wallace masturbating looking at photos of Melania
Oh my God
Steve
He's a weirdo
Agree I agree he comes in with this guy
Choi he still go to say some things during the interview that are big
3 problems
And what are the what are the Cubs in
The sex club
Alex has been very
Very clear
That the Democrats are run by the Chinese
Intermediary between the devil of the Democrats
Job
Steve says
Who is running this Democrat Party right now I mean
Who is running who is the Brain Trust is obviously not biting
I don't think it's Obama is it the Chinese or the Chinese setting them up
Chinese on a parley with all due respect
Chinese communism
Chinese
The real issue we all know about Lau here in corruption
Democratic
Party and it's
Machinery
Involved
At all familiar with Chinese communism she and I hang out with
He's part of my condo
Before I leave I like to contradict entire world
That's why I live here there's no such thing as God
The Chinese Communists are not important
They're not a big deal
Operation
I got to go
You know who you got to worry about
Uruguay
They're big in the stealing election
Gay
Is throwing
Haymaker
Love it
Little bit about Obama
This is kind of funny
But I heard Obama two days ago against a
In this democracy we have the right
Morano
Obama is a CIA operative
Sing
Everything
Obama is
He knew already
Intelligence files 2
I can't say that but okay
Man
So funny
Yeah he knows it
All of this seems so much more fun and less serious when I don't have like four years of
Murder to look forward to
Yeah I mean there's four years of you know still trouble a lot of trouble but not like
Every minutes it's more it's more a situation of I think we're still in a little bit of like
Exhaling there is a big accident
You might be overselling like the feelings of relief
And I think it's a really tough thing because you don't discount the fact
Getting Trump
Out-of-office
Send him losing his
Very crucial
Yeah wow at the same time
Don't lose sight of the fact that
Even though
Biden gets it it doesn't mean anything
Yeah it's fix
By itself
They're still exactly the same amount of work then
Needs to be done
Same issues
Exist
Hyatt I've tweeted out
Oh f***
Famous present
And then
Oh f***
Fighting is
People were like don't run this for me I'm like that all you can hold these
These two thoughts simultaneously these are not dissonant
These are nuance
Yeah it could be it could be
The Matrix challenge
And now we just have to figure out
Done
Steve
We know from his time
With Alex over the years is a normal methodology
Who is Allah
Text is too flattered
And we see this exact same behavior being applied to Owen
Please
You know cell
Deprecation
It's not impressive
To talk a lot
And it takes a lot of cojones and it takes a lot of
Sense of self
Warriors and the
Would you and Alex have
And you got a great
Stafford area
And Scott and all of them
You were select
I do not only
I selected you
You guys but I personally selected
You and those who I
Work with ordeal Wilson friendly with Naomi
Understood that it would
For your
To me sounds like
Alex wouldn't buy this year
I was like
Who could I go on
Real deluge
Regional here this is gone pass
That's like fun
Conspiracy theories to him being like
I control the universe
Well and like I have this
Big breaking news in
You're no you're so wonderful oh and that I chose you to break the story
It's nonsensical.
It really
I know Elsa
Go now it is absolute
You are as good as I could do
Yeah bro I'm going to butter you up really hard
Yeah
Alex we need to get Alex in on this
Cuz this is big
Like for them and you are
So-so
Holdover Alex Jones as soon as he heard Steve pieczenik break the huge news about the Trump staying
Alex Jones hopped in his race car
He's probably going about 160 mph right now
You probably on the phone with engineer's trying to rig up like a car helicopter
Get here faster and avoid traffic
Alex does not show up
Jesse Lee Peterson
After Steve
I don't know I don't I think I feel like Alex
Would be like
Shut it down
But only
I want has that feel of like a literal Apprentice situation where it's like
The master is out of the room
And I found something that I think is really exciting and it takes the world one and this one's mine
I discovered this was going to take it to the master and he's going to be so proud of me and then they
No this is f****** see
Disney movie
Fantasia accidentally made the mop Stan surrounded
Making a mess
Exactly right
Still alive
This is what I want plugged into my voice of course
We're back in the Infowars war room
The fake news media today with dr. Steve pieczenik
Giving us the inside scoop of President Trump sting operation that is ongoing right now the traps have been
Sprung sprung
There's a
Completely
Two different feet
Right there's the feeling of being proud of yourself
And then having that Pride punctured
By someone else and realized
Sing of fail
And then there's the feeling of hoping someone else will be proud of you
And when that
Punctured
That's devastating
I'm looking forward to hearing that from LA
I want to hear that devastation
He thinks somebody's going to be so proud of her
Yeah yeah
Got it
Just
It is a complex
Feeling that is like
I've done it
I have figured out how to save the world or something
We're going to make a lot of money Oculus
Picture show something else
I've saved Infowars
And you can see it in the moment like
No
Hilarious
This is a screw and I would never laugh at conservative tears
Conservative
Hubris is the funniest thing in the world and that's really what I was feeling
When it was like what's the reverse
Yeah that I can feel good about
Of election night 2016 Alex laughing at people Cryer's it's this
It is always be like we're taking down the
Your
George
Unable or incapable of seeing through Steve
Botanics bulshit
Transparently stupid b*******
Bugatti
Qci dozark
We're past the emperor has no clothes be a walk
Walking down the street without
What's skin ever
Owen is like
A baby love that guy
Sorry one last clip here Steve
It's just the buttering up
Yeah
I was given the privilege
Yes but I don't know who else knows it I don't know
What else will happen
The truth
Your show was
You have the good
Are the benefits
And I hope
And of a problem
I
Wish you
Godspeed
Yep
High hopes
This wind up with a lot of arrest
Like I said interview Jesse Lee Peterson
Then everyone went to sleep
How we wake up
And David Knight show from November 6th
He realizes
Owen got these brooms and mops dancing all over the place I got to clean up
No I know there's a
A theory that's come out
Penguin have watermark
And this is all just a big
Sing
And we should
The plant
I'm telling you right now
Total
Gaslighting
Pharmacy Aiea
Still working today
And we'll talk about that coming up that is
Is absolute nonsense
The kids off the show forever so David Knight comes in and he's like
I first heard that this has gone down the David Knight was pushing
Back on this.
Fires his f******
Fire
Thought about it a little bit more and recognize like what are the Dynamics here
I think David Knight
Fine
And I think I'll just pretend I went didn't do that
I think Owen made
A bad move but it's like that's an Infowars mistake
Christmas Day
I forgive you friend
How you learn it's an Infowars mistake
What world event
You know like
Nine times out of ten baby it doesn't work that tenth time maybe we make $1000000
So we'll let you do that
It's embarrassing
Pretend you didn't do it
Move Along
Put Stephen time out we won't have him on for a little bit
You give me gone for a little bit
When I listen to this David first of all I was like wow
He is as boring as I remember
But then
I doubt he's doing what Daddy needs
He's doing the work of
Cleaning up this because the narrative needs to be that the
Operation
Beautiful Park
Real quick
Call boy
Looks like
You're f****** charge
Steven got to be on the outs he's got to have like at least a talkin to or something
Yeah yeah that what that must have been a phone call as liked
You can't be swinging that hard
So they would make that before it gets out of business on on Steve's nonsense
Kia
40 play couple clips
The tones of these things are so f***
Indifferent
Twitter permanently banned
Cbennett
Because he called for
Bailey
Mark of the beast
He called for the beheading
Dr. fauci
An FBI director
Christopher Wray
Well here's what he actually had to say
Go back to the old times
Put that their heads on
Pikes right
Corners of the White House as a warning to Federal.
Medicine
What's known as a metaphor
I believe I always get back
Computers assembly
Cuz it needs to work like
I think that is
Wow what is
Exactly I'm like this is
Is for grandparents or something for people who need a little bit of a
And the rationalizations of of people say I'm f***** up things
Also
I will say the David Knight
Likes to make jokes
All right Nancy Pelosi has announced a big expansion of
Covid testing for lawmaker
Testing
I knew it wasn't to be polygraph
Wow that was actually almost Charming
I was almost a little child by that what that was that was
GoPro
Structure of a
Like maybe something that's off color or a pensive
Thanksgiving any like that was great you didn't say anything about black lives matter are having a great time didn't bring up how much you love
Song of the South this time David
I thought that was so bizarre like
I was looking at
Infowars
You just made a joke and laughed at it
And that lasted not seem fake
And did not use any old timey slurs in the process area Bazaar
Took awhile and a lot of boring
S*** to get through
We get to
David Tucker
Can about Steve pieczenik
But
You'll notice that the way he's talking about it
He's very careful
To talk about it as a story that he posted on reason.com as opposed to an interview
You his coworker had done
Find me delivery
Likeliest path appears to be there or he needs to hang onto
Pennsylvania and Georgia
Overtake Biden
And either Nevada or Arizona
So that's where we are at the MoMA
But of course you know that this was all
Rigged
We know that it was all
Which is why
I just about
Fell out of my chair when I saw this headline from reason Maga
Not when you were watching the War Room the day before
I wouldn't
So one thing I think is really interesting
Is the David Knight
His approach on hat
Is very much alike
This makes no sense
Well I appreciate it
Tell me if this was a sting
It doesn't even make any sense it's another one of these deals like the lap
Top 100
Very last minute
Put that thing out thinking is going to be at
Surprise
And everybody just said well
It's not credible but media is going to
Put out the
Narrative is not
Credible
Photographic evidence
Beginning of all the documentation that you wanted the world and they're not going to believe it because the mainstream media social media are going to censor you and they're going to put
About their narrative
I don't see that's going to do anything other than
Create
Forest fire
Soju
Did but the point he's trying to make
Pikachu with one little tweak I make one little
But
Like it doesn't make sense cuz no one would believe this anyway so there is that make sense
Yeah he's version of it is known to believe because the media would put out their own version I don't really I don't agree with that
I would say that ever want to be like go f*** yourself
Probably that story came out
People would just
Yeah and I believe it
Wait so he's saying that
Is true but they don't
They would that the media wouldn't
Believe it anyways he's saying that they wouldn't do it because no one would believe it even if they did it okay
He saying that they would have seen that happening
Ahead of time
F***** by no one believing it. So they wouldn't have gone down that road again
Sure I guess however you get there so you get there I don't know
It doesn't make sense
Your reason why it doesn't make sense
You work at Infowars whatever
Now it just last clip
You don't talk about it that much
What Steve does say something that I think is great
Yes
So David says this thing that's like
I think it's great
But also it's a
The classic Infowars thing
Where
You're right
But you're wrong
But you are still the paradox
But I didn't jump it
Pizzagate
Idlewild pechenik
Come on the show because last time he came on their show with right after the shooting in Vegas
He came on the show
The salvalai
That nobody died in Vegas
Because you trying to trap me
This guy is a CIA shill
And he comes on to
Grappa's
That's one of the ways that they disc
Credit you
I'm not have anything to do with that
We'll be right back
Baxley weather
So
David
Steve is a f****** liar any fux with Infowars
To be able to get away with it then
Because it's a lot of chaos has great time I do believe that is correct I remember that episode where is
He was on the David Knight and he was talking about the Las Vegas shooting being fake
David nights reaction
Into that was
I agree with you that Sandy Hook was fake
Somewhere somewhere
But
I do agree with him
Don't have Steve on breathing
He's not a CIA Shelton he's a board man
In a condo in Florida you got it
I don't understand how one out of
3 Infowars house
Closest just like
This guy's a CIA she'll who's trying to destroy our entire business and the other two are like
Acoma
Not only is he
If he's a CIA shell
He's tricked me
Oh
Here's here's where this
Becomes a little bit last like
Ava severe problem
Cuz I do seem like a problem
We're like David Knight
Tavion are being like Steve pieczenik is a CIA shows trying to trap me with these bulshit story
And that's how they get you going all the way back to Las Vegas
You been on Alex's your since then saying a bunch of nonsense
By that token
David would have to think that
He's trying to trap Alex it would only somehow that's fine
Do still work at the same place where is that is going on
Trap David David Knight is the white whale
Even trying to get fries
I don't think that's the case anybody is particularly focused on David Knight
But here's the thing
Alex has done this to
Like what after the Las Vegas shooting
Alex did turn on Steve for a little while I think Steve is still working for the sea
CIA
And then they made their peace after a couple Bond
Steve being on timeout
So that probably wouldn't happen again
Most likely
Although
Free funny
Very funny
It's B
Really funny
I think that the image of Owen being like
F*** you mainstream media destroying you
That's the image of an Infowars 2020 election that I want to hold on to
I want that to be
Took the spiritual energy that we're coming with
As opposed to
No laughing at all you lost I don't want to laugh at you for losing and I want I want to be
Glad that your candidate lost cuz I hate to policy
But I want to laugh at you for taunting the mainstream media because you got tricked by Steve pieczenik
So good
You said you will get tricks to give you think
You're so smart
And you think that Steve gave you a scoop
If you got it it's not a school
Back I work for the CIA killed everybody if you haven't
What he got that party telling you that he chose yourself
Even smiled at me I'm throwing a fastball that okay
Yeah if you want
To talk to you
He wants to use you
Right
If Steve was coming with big
Stuff
This close to the election
This important a time. For
I guess
Overthrowing the government
Alex isn't giving it
I mean it's not relative audience size is huge difference
Yeah okay
I'm Steve
I got this big in
Information
That the election was actually secretly a sting operation
I can't get permission
Talk about it an hour early
I'm sorry they had it on a clock that at 9 p.m.
Eastern time should I could have done it at 3
I think that you're like
Relevant
Children good work
Sure
Every now and again you got to go yell at Congress and he walked out or something like that you got to get to get high
And I guess if
No it's believe in Steve is what does it for you sometimes it
It's going to do everybody needs a little juice from here
From time to take yourself back up Owen
Get back on track
Don't
This is so embarrassing you should quit
You should quit you said
Fudge You mainstream media
Because Steve pieczenik told you that the entire election
Was a sting operation was an elaborate ruse Hellboy
Oh yeah so this is episode 500 Jordan
Then
Quite a few
That's weird
Haha
This is how we celebrate
Celebrate
Infowars war room
The fake news media today with dr. Steve pieczenik
I want to talk more about that clip I love it for so many reasons
First of all you've got that sort of new metal base going behind it which is great
That's a 6-string bass
Devastating
The fake
News media
Big news media
Is what's being devastated with Steve
Does Owen work for the CIA
My eyes are really wide broken some serious news to your dad you know where the CIA is based
St.Louis
Alright I don't think it is because we're from
Episode 501 website
Dot-com
Review and if you could please find a local charity or bail Fund in your area the fight's not over
Emilio Emilio
Dzx Clark
I am Darrell rundus I'm
Devastating
Fake news media with Steve
Vagina
Alexandra Thurston color