Jordan
I have great respect for Tenaya Lodge like I'm sick of them posing as if through the good guy
Monica
What's fight.com
Acknowledge
About Alex
Fitzgerald
Jordan Jordan
Brick by today
We just recorded our bright spot inside realize that it was not recorded
It's Crusade
I hit the button to start recording not saying cuz I did I would not say that I just believe
Cheryl bright spots with each other for a second time so if any of this sounds insincere
Yeah
Great rip
Totally you guys missed out on going to feel like I can't bring anything
I know it's tough
How to bring the same energy know anyway by bright spot is world music
I'm just worried like I told you earlier on the first time
I'm worried that I'm becoming my parents
Because they used to have a lot of interest in a lot of music from around the world
Particularly this disband you through gindi which is a lot of
Since and also tribal
Sounds Oceania
And
I was on Spotify for the episode
What to put on music in the background while I'm like researching and reading up on stuff
IND
See what you got
You didn't know what I've listened to
Let's see if you can hit a homerun
And there was some music from Malawi
That ended up coming up
And I really really enjoyed it and I'm worried is going to set me off
Our path
Of just like
You getting into all sorts of stuff from around the world
Never nothing
You should try them out there fantastic
Miss down there's all kinds of great music
I think it's a little bit
Cliche to referee
Prince them because they're probably
Probably
Or maybe not maybe no one has any idea about that except for in the weird circles that I live in that might be
It's so cliche to reference Orchestra Baobab you know the thing everyone remain on one of our bonus episodes
Talk about your love of really obscure music you can't tell who knows what
This might be a new little bit of an auditory adventure for me I'm excited to embark on it and
And I'll find out what the rest of the world has to offer at
Awesome
Creed Valhalla
It's
The game I enjoyed it
I want to say that I already knew that the first time around but now it's the second time
Really not twice
Just did that surprised even already know the story that I hit my bright spot is so it's not even do that cuz you texted me
About it before the PlayStore you recorded
The video game is that what you wanted to hear dance for you cuz it's been a long time coming you're very excited about this game been
Favorite series in originally ordered a found out on the nights that my copy wooden
12 +
I have reached that time
Console
Cartridges ink cartridges
Yeah I know and it wasn't going to show up in
Until the 17th so
On the 9th I was like
F*** this
Is 7
It wasn't it was going to be available at 11
Spice scrambled and got the
The download copy as soon as I possibly could you go
Another week
Flights
Yeah and I'm like that
Experience
I must be part of the zeitgeist
So I've been busy cuz you know
The show and what have you and other related projects
It so I haven't had a lot of time to play it but I did preorder a digital copy myself
Play a little bit
Play the little bit the other night I'm not going very far into it and I'm concerned
Now here's why okay
Know a lot about Norse and Vikings stuff sure is other.
Oceans of the game where like sodas mythologies cultural histories that I know a little bit more about
Does your wheelhouse early before it was Egypt yeah yeah I know that about you.
Egyptian history
I know very little
And I realized why
It's those letters
It's the letter U the ruins
No I just can't handle
The weird combination of letters
Eminem's and stuff
Intimidates me and I don't know what to do with those V's
Why is Jesus everywhere
It scares me
I realize that so conscious bias
Has kept me away embarked on a little bit
Find out some stuff that I can then maybe read up on the real version
And then I also really funny about that is
Having played just a little bit further into you
Into the game than you
After the title card which is going to like
4 hours 5 hours a night
Even come close to that I'm sure
Where is wheelers
3 hours from now
But the other thing
Actually kind of puts to bed my other worried about game
I'm having again played very little up
I'm worried it's
But not in with white
People wave to I mean no
There's so much goddamn snow around individually
Monochromatic
To a level that if it were the entire game
I would have a problem with that I think I would have it would be a difficulty
Because of the open-world exploration has back if you just running around everywhere snow-covered
Even with Witcher 3 it wasn't gloomy all the
Yeah it was gloomy
Most of the
And they were sort of variation
Since to the Gloom
Yeah there's like Gloom
You got them well I'm glad to know that some of these
Concerns that I have whether it be letter or snow base
The developers of those games enough
Not make
A game that's all Snow Elementary
Peppa Pig but I did not know that was mainly snow so
Skip that one for good
Skip it
Out of here a little snow
Pennywise you don't mind
A little snowpocalypse
Jordan
Today the present going to be talking about November 7th
We're entering that interesting. Where we find out what Alex does during the 79 days of hell
We experience
What happened to Alex left
Steve pieczenik
Today we jump I guess we're just pretending none of this s*** happen
I was bored at 7
My father was a Highlander and so am I
I had to kill him that can be only one I don't know exactly how we're doing it but
I guess we're just pretending
That never happened on Saturday
Alex is doing a broadcast on Saturday the 7th
And then his show on Sunday the 8th
And yeah I will see
We'll see what you see what's going on I like it
Supposed to have signed up North Garden Show
So first
Knox worth
I'm a policy wonk Xbox Revenge
G thank you so much you're now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk Dexter
I'm a policy wonk about to Jared next
Thank you so much
Give a shout out to hook to donate it on elevator
Appreciate that very much
The first of all H-E-B thank you so much you're now a technocrat
Fernando F thank you so much you are now technocrat
Don't go into the forest thank you so much
Money off that heroin
Is freakishly large
Into the forest
I would like to first of all encourage anybody do you have a donor name that is an ominous
Warning
Enjoy that which one
To Sporty's Gents
Oh okay
What else could people
Well you know what Dan some people could absolutely be filled with that generous spirit
Want to give or donate to someone but then realize that they would have to wait a week
Deal with that
You just can't wait a week because the generous spirit is so strong within you
Find a way to get that money out now then
I was worried it was going to end or silver some some nonsense
Whatever
You know what I'm saying
Today Show
Dancing with the Stars
In the final episode or whatever
Cuz I'm a big TV guy that I do like watching
Good looking women
Let's go to see celebrities
You don't need to justify why you watching TV show
Look I got tricks to Sean Spicer was on and I watched it
Whatever
Actually I don't even like the dancing at all the way that they couldn't pick at pirouette and throws and then
It seems unmanly for me to enjoy what I'm able.
So sad
Secure about what
Enjoy what you enjoy
Anyway here we go quit jumping in on the seven
What's Saturday Alex's day off
He's in any way back from his trip
To Phoenix
Swear yelled into adult-sized bullhorn
And
Is Biden's really present
It looks like he is
Saturday
November 7th the year of 2020
We accept
False claims of Joe Biden
Chinese deep State handlers that he is
President probably just Witness
Then you could
Really see this as a
Good day
To put on the Republic
Austin Stone
Born
July 4th
Died November 7th
That's what this is
How is it called it
Death of America November 7th
As as a millionaire I can tell you that the
The tragedy of the Biden
Administration will be that they raise the marginal income tax on
Individuals making over 500,000
$1 a year to above
But that is the end of the reports that I hear
I think that's
The end of the Republic funeral of America
Imagine how angry
2 Chainz is going to be then so so mad he's still mad
In this next clip
Will you learn
Look at this is the problem that I have to show talking about put this date on America's Tombstone 2
Like this
About the failures of trump and in
And why this was able to happen
Talk about
What Trump should have done better
Where to do that sweet leaf
What next time
Wonder what the f*** next time
According to Alex there is no next time
This isn't just a political party that you disagree with it now has control of the executive branch of the government
This is the f****** devil taking over
Without Trump there to stop them the story supposed to be that there's nothing to protect the Patriots from getting rounded up in the entire world being
Killed off with the super bioweapon
A false-flag ice age
With Alex's feeling bad guys gone for sure
It's downright insulting for Alex Devin nerve
To act like a political commentator right now
When is candidate has been projected to lose
Do you have this tantrum about the death of the Republic being on November 7th and immediately gets into the mode expectancy on regular outlet
They're doing a post-mortem on the campaign where were the flaws in the strategy where is there room for improvement
We can do better next time let's talk midterms
Normal people get to do that
Because they don't live in artificial reality that used to abused their audiences where if their guy loses the election
Pedophile demons will run the street the gods Firefield judgment will be upon us
Alex don't get to war game but the midterms he lost that right when he made
The terms of this election
Supernatural
Yeah I believe it was
If Biden wins
Is there going to switch
To plan B
Kill all of us a media
It wasn't even conditional on the election that was just something Alex that they decided to do
Because Alex is too effective in a bad mood
All the Infowars too strong so they're going to just kill a dog
They like to do because the devil
Love plan I don't even think that you know what there's nothing to be ashamed about losing to the devil you're supposed
Salute to the devil the only person who wins against The Travelers Jesus man
I was Johnny rising up that bow and play cards
Johnny was really a Christ metaphor
The whole world
It's really just about fiddle flakes
The devil acted with honor and Fiddle like the other rip-off songs of the Devil Went Down
Georgia I bet I think some other people might have
There is at least one juggler Who Went Down to Georgia
Inform me of the song Like The Devil Went Down to Detroit rap version
Heavy like a DJ contest with the devil I think they win
Okay I don't know if look a lot of people may have
Fictitious Libby the devil's butt
Look there's no shame in that you're not supposed to beat the devil why are you beating yourself up over
He's beating himself up
I want to stress one of the compelling reasons not to respect Alex Jones
He's an intellectual coward
He can't stand to be wrong to such a ridiculous
Except that he set up this election as a battle between good and evil which evil could not possibly win and even if they did
Good secretly actually won because evil cheated in a way that's never going to be proven
Now that the supposedly evil side is one
Alex won't even stick to his own parameters and act like a literal devil
This beat is gyro
I was going to leave it at the Integrity to present for a minute to any of the stuff you screaming about
Fake crying about on-air means anything
Because it's time to move on and learn the lessons of the last election and apply them to whatever white supremacist he supports next time
Because they insist they're just a national
He's a child
This more than
Any other moment
Is it very clear and unmistakable in
Instance of
Treat
Get the f*** out of here that learning lessons for next time sheet
Nope other people get
To do I resent that are very few situations where I don't
Now that many of these people are private cities
We should spit on them every
Single time they go outside
Like there's no way Alex should not be spit on regularly
There's no way that
Like f******
If Trump walks down f****** A Street in Manhattan
He should be Spit On by thousands of people on a cont
Yeah I think that you could make an argument that spitting is a form of assault
And maybe I'm not into that fair
Yelling is better
I'll go with you as far as yelling you're alright
Anytime Alex leaves his house people
Surrounded with
I think is a little bit gross
Express support
Through your mask
Perfectly
Yeah I think I think that's a middle ground should be hounded to the ends of the Earth
Barkat people through bullhorn
Alex
Concerned that a lot of his everyone
Never was getting kicked off how the
I mean taking off
Social media platforms
You see the mass censorship now
Predicted almost total censorship
No media that I saw Carrington
Thank God it right side Broadcasting
Thank God you're out there a
This is a serious
War
Everyone's getting taken out
Infowars and right side broadcasting the stand-up
Hover Rudy giuliani's wonderful press conference but he's got to
I would expect the most media Outlets if they didn't
They didn't cover Rudy giuliani's press conference out of respect for him
That s*** was super embarrassed
Also it wasn't censored people were making fun of it all over the place
This was of course the Four Seasons press conference
As best as anyone can tell someone in the campaign may have thought that they booked
The Four Seasons hotel conference room for the Presser
But it actually set up a event in front of a small Landscaping
When company called for season
Total Landscaping
I have no idea what actually happened here if they intended it to be there or someone screwed up
What is pretty hilarious
Giuliani gabri rambling nonsense Beach
Right at the moment when the Network's called the racer Vidant it was a total mess
Also during the event
One of giuliani's guest wasn't a legend
Pull Watcher name Darrell Brooks
Who turned out to also have been quote
Incarcerated in the 1990s on charges of sexual assault lewdness
And endangering the welfare of a minor by exposing a
Himself to two girls ages 7 and 11 it's a false flag Democrat if I ever heard one according to the NRA
The Cut quote Brooks denied the charges and said his arrest was a police set up
So it's a double false flag
Perhaps
He was false Flags into becoming the false flag that's what happened I don't know
You know who this guy is somebody whose identifiable it makes things a little bit more confusing for the claims that were being made
Apparently was being alleged that Brooks was a poll Watcher in Philadelphia
And you know like not being allowed into check the check the rolls and everything
He lives in New Jersey
And it's not like he's a low-profile New Jersey resident
An article in Politico quoted read escoria the mayor of Trenton New Jersey Asda
Describing Brooks as quote
New Jersey's perennial candidate
Because Brooks
Did run from many different offices in New Jersey including the Senate and House
The state of Pennsylvania requires poll Watchers to be registered voters in the County's they wished
Apple watch
So he couldn't actually been in a position
To actually
Make the claim that he was living
Disaster for Giuliani location to the almost comical
Bad timing to the pool water
Alleged who I had as a witness
Possibly be a poll watcher
Abbott is actually a convicted child abuser
If anything I would
Alex
Coverage of this everything is bad
Every element of that press conference was bad I mean
A perfect
Example of how we are held hostage
By their own reality
Should be a criminal offense
All the stuff that happened at that press
I know they're not illegal but if you do that
You can't be near other people bohorse we need Crews of people with tiny bullhorn
On the ready
That's what Arkham Asylum is for people who acts
Dental
Play escaping
That's not it's not a
Crime it's something that people need to be kept there
Pizza Hut
Killer Croc
Got Rudy Giuliani
Why why are you here
I set up a weird Prescott
They would all be like yeah I know you're the only one we're not let it go
Whatever the Riddler comes unless I believe Rudy
At least we get the place we're going to hoist
Right because we got to the wrong place okay
They are there like the whole no no no really you got to take me to give a message to to the back for us
God
What'd
A******
Jesus
So Alex gets to talk in about
The China
Has this interesting idea that you know isn't based in
And really anything
But
I got really lost him
Thought after listen
This Cliff because I think it's really
Really good example of why
It is really frustrating to take things that Alex says
Seriously
So instead of making
China Cafe
Criminal elements
Rockefeller combine
Go back to the
The real world
George Herbert Walker Bush in there
James Baker
To make a deal to Tommy's Chinese after they spent
25-years enslaving
Killing
89 other people
Behave
Every follower every directive
One child policy
She's a horrible thing
The Rockefellers told to do
I said yeah kill about 89 your people
One child policy will make you
The global superpower of
Economics but you're not allowed to have a big military
Course
Winter globalist
They were
Obama
Because China weather
The following its
Expansionist
Minerals
Call economic power
Economically span
But America would
Economically close
But then
So that's how you divide power
Rollerball
Allegory
Or whatever it is
Of course
It's always
Always a f****** movie
That's why I like
It's so frustrating to listen to I'm like it starts with that clip their it starts something really absurd
The decision was made by people like the Rockefellers
Deb trying to not be capitalist at the end of WWII
They're going to think it's me kinda interested
Well at least it would have surely wrongdoing the show
It's a laughable and nonsensical claim
You know that even without doing any reason
I would ask Alex to explain What mechanisms were used by the Rockefellers to keep China from being a capitalist
If I were to do this
Because of doing Michelle
I know that Alex would just point to John Birch
Society talk
Complaints about how the US didn't do enough to help Shane Kai-shek in the Chinese Civil War
Which is the claim it's been exaggerated into the Rockefellers installed Mouse
I like this absurd claim
It's stupid but probably sounds smart to his audience and I can kind of appreciate that
Kind of the sort of thing that
I did my my my teeth into
He claims that David Rockefeller wrote a book into articles in the times about this whole China stuff and that's just not true
The op-ed Rockefeller wrote don't look great with the hind side of history on our side but they're nothing like Alex is claiming them
He also wrote a book called memoirs
Which is an autobiography but if that admission is in there
Really simple for Alex
Reproduce which weirdly never does
When everything falls apart with the rambling about the imaginary deal where China gets to have the economy and us gets to have the middle
Military which incidentally is something
Similar to like
Something Alex might be cribbing from the piece of dystopian sci-fi from the time when he was a child
Seems to be a pattern does seem like that is
Often the case
The original movie Rollerball
Logan
The original movie rollerball was based on a short story called rollerball Murder By William Neil Harrison published in
Esquire in September 1973
It's a little bit different than what the movie ended up being as
It's far more to statement about the rising brutality
Publix taste in entertainment
They're also similarities to the movie version no like it's
The kind of clunky
And not
Not super
Short story itself
This Bears a lot of mention of
Various women's
Shay pleiness
Great in the movie
Sure
I-Ready
God was talking about like
Love doing those rollerball scene
I had to go Act
That was about as processed for thief
Too I think I love those rollerball C
In the short
Story it's not so much like differ
Countries do different things
It's fit within the United States different corporations run six different
Concerns of life
Energy transport Food House
Services and Lux
You just a super powerful Corporation in the main character Jonathan he plays for the roller ball team run by energy
B company based in Hughes
The actual story is about a guy who's the best roller ball player in the world struggling with his sense of self
Finding himself unsatisfied while living the life filled with money power sex and celebrity
The brutality of the sport has been increasing with new rules being added to satisfy the Public's lust for violence
Gradually things get more vile
With rules added to penalize players who aren't trying hard enough
By having their helmets confiscated
This all culminates in the All-Star Game
The end of the season
Where there's a new rule that's added where there's no time limit for the game
Essentially making a gladiatorial contest we're pretty much everyone is guaranteed to die
Johnson wants something more out of his life but he doesn't know what
But as the All-Star Game gets
Closer his only request is that he'll be able to see his estranged wife
She comes to him and they f*** for a few days and then they remember their shared love that they had
Jonathan had convinced himself that in the past
Been taken from him by the evil Corporation
But he realizes that wasn't
The case
It would be nice I think wants to imagine that she was taken away from me by some malevolent force and they soften
Age but I know the truth of that
She went away
Simply because I wasn't enough back
Because those were the days when I urine
Before I urine for anything
When I was beginning to leave to play the game
But no matter
For a few days she sits on my bed and I touch her skin like a blind
It's implied that they both realize they can't go back to their younger lives even if there is love
Between them and Jonathan nose
He has to play the All-Star Game
Even if it means almost certain death
The story concludes quote
Before the game begins I stand with my team as a corporation him plays
I'm brutespeed today I tell myself trying to rest myself up yet
I dream in my thoughts
I'm a bit
I'm convinced
A Chorus of voices joins the band now is the music swells
The game the game all glory to at the music rings
And I can feel my lips
Smooth with the words
Singing
William Harrison fleshed-out the story into a screenplay that no longer really resembles the point of this original work
Some parts of it that are still carried over
Actually directly contradicted
Certain points
The director of the movie It
Explain why they made the movie
Tell him to Guardian quote
I thought that violence for the entertainment of the masses was an obscene idea
This is what I saw coming and that's why I made
The film
The original in the movie or both commentaries on the idea of brutality as entertainment but in order to make the movie out of 8
10-page story
We needed to add a whole plot about the corporations fearing the Jonathan was becoming too much of
An individual and corporate world built on
Conformity or Logan's Run to just come out recently
The game and the people's reaction to it
As well as the violence depicted in the movie itself and the people's reaction to that
Where the point of the movie Rollerball
If it has any artistic
Text Mary it's that attempt for a state
The dystopian sci-fi future backdrop
Absolutely unnoticed
And the only really exist as a way of justifying why the game exist
Yeah yeah
Alex doesn't know how to wrestle with or analyze works of art
He refuses to understand subtext or deeper meaning makes perfect sense
He'd think that all this
Dystopian fiction from his youth to secretly about the
The Communist conspiracy
But no one will admit it's right in front of their face
Here's an example
There is a phenomenon
You could point
Which is that a lot of movies
He's particularly dystopian action movies seem to exist in a world ruled by Ridgid authoritarian to have molded Society into
Estate of uniformity
You could point this out and provide a number of examples
And that's fair
Alex might see this phenomenon and argue that this is because the globalist through using Purdue
Addictive programming to tell the world about what they're going to do to that
There's a cosmic
Contract law Clause that states
Unless we all consent to them so they put the stuff in movies
To get us to accept it
That is the theory
For why there's such a consistent feature like this
In this genre
I would argue that it's
Because the setting of a rigid uniform world is 1 worth in
Incredibly easy
The differentiated hero character from the rest of the world
Even an antihero or a flawed person could easily be cheer for when they're the only person
With any modicum of individuality in a city full of facelessness
Putting your character in their story into that setting
It's kind of a genre based shortcut
A plot where the tension is about individualism vs
Conformity
And gave him a text and art with even just a baseline of critical ability allows you to see authorial intent
I do understand the more complicated things that are being said by artists
And it brings a richness to your life
It's a critically important exercise now more than ever and honestly
It's one of the things I find Most Fascinating but out
I do believe that most of the stuff he says is embellishment
He doesn't actually believe we're kind of believed
But his inability to grasp the point of literature and movies
Is something soak
Consistent in his career that I find it difficult to accept that it's not a genuine
Future of his brain
It's annoying
To do this show because I end up thinking
Think about Rollerball
There was an attempted statement that they were making there in the desert of the corporations and ship
In the movie and all that
Is really just
Make it so you're watching this movie really exist
Would never exist in our world
The commentary is about
People's taste
Sports
And entertained becoming more and more violent
And The Logical extension of that
Is
A game where
Killing each other
That itself
Could not exist
In our reality
So the commentary couldn't be made
By plugging it into the present day
Is there any things like hey why is no one getting sued for this never fly
Plug it into this dystopian authoritarian world in the shooter
Yeah
And it makes it so much easier to cheer on your hero Jonathan M
Even if you
Rhino not a great person
I wonder I wonder what it would have been like if Alex would instead of being into hard sci-fi
And gotten watching rollerball at that age and it said watch
Like They Shoot Horses Don't They
Watching Everybody she's in that f****** exploitative destructive dance contest
Realize and get a real.
Dystopia is where we live now
I just
I don't know
I do wish
He was better
Yeah that would be
I wish a lot of food
Almost everyone was better
Activate a difficult skill
It is it seems like it should be easy considering we talk to each other
But then you think about and you realize most people don't even talk to me
Which other honestly
It's really hard to understand what people are saying cuz their brains don't
Speak the word
Their brains think
One of the more interesting things that is like an alien right now
They act so strange
So weird
What are the things I found what I was looking at
Is reading about Rollerball
Was beta the writer William Harrison
He was like
I want
More violent
This movie
But not because like he wants a movie to be super violent
To make the point
That the violence is supposed to be repulsive
So brutal that when you watch it you go you know and then when people watch
And then the director of it was talking about how I
Most of the most of the European audiences that we do no talk
To understand that is disgusting
We should start a rollerball League
Frankly what
DTE what's the difference between CTE rollerball we might as well get rollerball while we're at it anyways
Vince McMahon get the ex-nfl the f*** out of here get the rfl right in here babe
That's what I'm talking about so anyway that there was that
It's sort of sidetracked by the roller ball off today
We get two more complaints about China
We live on earth
It's all been one-sided
It's not about
Kumbaya.
Brake stop
Competition was allowed to buy a park that
Hollywood
The crusher
So I've been thinking about this for a while
I think this is one of the newer formulations of like the Jews around all the bank
Yeah that kind of bigger than the Chinese
The new one of those
Sounds like something they heard someone say before
Intimidating thing where you like
Why would you buy debt
Yeah just complete bulshit
According to MarketWatch the US government itself owns
27% of the US debt with us investors own in the further 32.5%
The Federal Reserve owns 11.2% which is just a slightly more complicated
Was the government owning it
So all that added up is 70.9% of the US national debt that's owned essentially by USA
Sure
Compared to that the amount owned by China is not that much
As of 2018 they held about 5.6% of our national debt in the form of
Like treasury bonds
But Japan also at 4.9%
The dreaded Japanese threat Olive a Makar
These countries have bought these bonds
Because generally speaking they're considered good investment
Since most world currency is tied to the dollar
Also in 2020 Japan overtook China is the largest foreign investor in our debts the dynamic that Alex
Describing
Is even more
What you're getting wrong there is China on
99% of
Pan's death
So they secretly owned
All of the other 4.4%
Do people date did they want to spread this fear and what is based on is the idea of the China owns our debt and what they
Can do is they can
Can call in that debt that you repay your debt
Like a landlord who's giving you a slide exactly
It's based on
More less nothing
Alex wants to create that image because it means the China rules
They can say the word Indus
Destroying our economy a10e
They don't own enough of our debt to really
Matter that much
In that in that term
And also investing in our debt doesn't work like
Our national debt is a super complicated thing
Isn't the same as your personal debt that you might have if you're like a late on a gas bill
They're too many real-world factors to make it sensible discusses like a one factor thing like
Bigger number that equals worse or whatever
But that's basically what Alex is doing and then adding on a layer of
Conspiracy China baiting for fun
Jonathan by up all are dead they don't own Hollywood and they didn't buy all our info
Talking point Alex repeats over and over again
Until his audience accepts them as being fat
But it's all just
Warmed-over Bircher nonsense
It's very interesting to me that
Like
One of the ways that the
Conservative
Propaganda
Just get normal people
To believe their bulshit
Is because they try and make it that micro-level of like
You have
If someone calls in that debt
That'll suck
The same thing is true for the United States but what they don't realize is that when you get
Get to the United States
Money is imaginary is it called in our debt what happens
We print more and then inflation goes up and
Their money's worth
You know there is a
Serious
Incentive for them not
To do that
Based on their own economy
That's fine
You're just inflation goes up and all other kinds
The b******* happens there's a hundred different after effects of that
Do magic
Magic
Even that
Being understood
What Alex is saying is
It sounds compelling
It's very simple that like get across
I want to ask you a question here Jordan Shore
I think that you've done Elena we've we've been at this for a while you understand Alex pretty well
In this Mexico power to discuss it with his greatest
Sadness is
Do you think that you could guess what his greatest sadness is
On the ending SWAT
Lots of dead dogs in his wake
I would assume that that guilt would weigh heavily upon
Money talks about it
It seems like as dogs had it coming
I know you're incorrect
Here's my greatest sadness
The average person that's a leftist
Positive
They do when they get one degree
3 degrees
Or they get some little government
Bureaucracy
Once we overthrow America
Afraid of socialist Utopia
You're all going to be in charge and have mansion
And I believe this
Brought into the
The power structure
Absolute
They're vicious and they're hateful
So Alex is greatest sadness is over educated liberals leftist to Ensign jobs
So
At the Socialist Utopia is a capitalist Utopia where we switch who lives in mansions
Is that what he thinks is going on
Yeah probably assume so real
He doesn't understand socialism at all
And it's next clip
Alex
Is recognize that there are people showing up
Maybe it's State Capitol
No I mean they're there their they're
Oh I wouldn't admit that right now
They're good Bakery what's going on
You know and stuff sure and because of this there's also a lot of people are showing up at the Y
Let you know there's a few people now
But soon
Lb million
So obvious
By the weekend
Pick a Saturday
People on at work
Until they can use social media to say
People around the White House
Won't be a million today
It'll be a hundred thousand today
Won't be annoying today
Rihanna.
But by the time Trump isn't leaving in a week or two
They'll be a million 2 million
And they will
Pair
Those barricades up
The plant
Democrats
Your plan
Hey
The Goblins have never gotten in trouble for
Anything they've done
Hawaii
Wouldn't they
Do that
Because they're never
Elder County
I mean if Trump black
Directly is like I don't respect the results of an election
I'm not leaving
I wouldn't be surprised if tons of people shelter
Four numbers
But I will admit a million people showing up outside the White House doesn't seem
Impossible to me
Pretty
That might happen if a leader refuses to step down
I think we could we could
To go real high
We could go real high there
Not good not good
Definitely not good
There were tense standoff
Outside the White House
A couple months
Over the George Floyd
Protest
I don't
I don't know if people would
Storm the White House
But
People will be shaking fences you think we're going to get a moat around the White House I don't know if you want to go with a moat
I don't I don't know I don't know
I don't know
You don't know
And I think it's I'm fine with that limb have the house
Pizza House
Modern Warfare
Lachemann there give him a moat put alligators on their I was just thinking about if they do emotes
IV solution
Tons of Jell-O
Bunch of Jell-O powder in there
System may be outdated and tears of defensive effect
Anyway situation
I just really can't stand this waffly back-and-forth nonsense of
The f****** Devil's coming for next time
Or this
Apparently
Maybe maybe maybe everything will be alright
Election fraud
How there's a very narrow way out of this
A very narrow way out of this
And then I'm going to
Explain
Is another path
And that path Act
Orchestra
And very horrible
Bubble actually hasten the destruction of the global order
And they have stepped in
Now I have no
I will go down
And don't worry
You're going to go down that path to
Because there's no getting out of this now
Everyone is going to SeaWorld government manifest
You're going to see everything I told you come true
Everything
So that's violence
Oh that's
Street violence
That's a murder of your your neighbors and Lawrence doubt that's the other path
What does a narrow path
Which is Trump
Seizing power basically
You could kind of get the Santa like
Okay now the conversation is B
Become Trump is got to become king
Or else
Bucking
Yeah totally
And that's not
Encouraging no no no
Pursuit of a Baseline
Just where we're at
I don't know if I enjoy that no I mean right now I enjoyed the election results coming in
And Biden winning
Outright that's good stuff
What's the amount of overconfidence
Gloating
What's going on before
Trump has
Entirely left the White House
Google nerve-racking for me
I don't like it when people who I've seen before and
All of our lives
Destroyed
Because of it
Goat again
I don't like it I don't like seeing it
Yeah
I think because of
This kind of contest
The territory really don't know
How much of the stuff that goes on
Between an election
And an inauguration
He's a normie
We're going to turn out to be a lot
Save-A-Lot in Newark
I heard no longer on the on Cheers
So in his neck
Clip
Alex is very
Few friends left
In the media
Do people even just doesn't
Yeah yeah one of them
Lou Dobbs short hair like Lou Dobbs alright
Fursona play
Sidney Powell Lou Dobbs
Ameresco card
And this is very very poor
Michigan place to start
We're going to play this clip and we'll be right back
So the long and short of this is that there's a
Conspiracy going around there's a super-secret overpowered computer called hammer
They can run a program called
Scorecard
Which was used to manipulate and change the results of this Alexa
This desperate and absurd conspiracies being sold by people like Gaston
Steve Bannon show Mike Flynn's attorney Sidney Powell and Lou.
Either high-profile people in right-wing Spears this just isn't like some Fringe completely online nonsense I was wondering
Where did this come from
Luckily I did not
Have to look too far
Will summer Over The Daily Beast it already put together a great piece about how all the claims about the supercomputer and the program come for me
Single source
And someone who I have a special bond with
This all comes from Dennis Montgomery dammit
Talking damn I was amazed
Call back in the reality his name come up again
It would take far too long to get into this right now but back on March 2017 on the 25th episode of Art
Podcast we dedicated
Two and a half hours to Dennis Montgomery and his various frauds
Why you don't need to take anything that raises back to him seriously
Go ahead and check that episode at my God so Wills article on it is a really good break down to
This is how these dicks work
Supposedly respectable outlets on the right or so desperate for a big overarching explanation for how they were screwed in the election
They're willing to amplify and give credibility to claims being made by a career con man
Who's the lawyer is Larry f****** claiming you can't do it
How is it that
Even in this way
People don't
Oh it's Larry klayman
The fuckout
Like Larry klayman Larry claim with coming for you eventually
Like it doesn't matter what if you're on the hard right it doesn't matter sooner or later lyric luminous Larry claim is going to sue you
Everywhere
Don't listen to him now
You didn't need to worry about the lawsuits just look at em look at look at those
Yeah
Pass
You could have the biggest scoop in the world
I'm going to take the hit if you're right this time
I'm going to just bite the bullet and say I don't trust anything you say and if that bites me in the ass
I still did the right thing
The idea that you might like
James O'Keefe video pop up in
Well maybe you got it right this time
No no
That's bad that's bad thing
So it is next Alex like I said he's kind of interested in these ideas about to
Millions of people showing up at the White House truck
Also he doesn't like that the media is downplaying the number of people that are coming to Owen Shroyer's rally
In Austin is very preoccupied
A lot of time over. Crowd sizes in Austin
Studio for a while
Notice that there are thousands
Rally's
Capital Round Rock
I was down there
A few hours ago at the Texas Capitol
DPSS Pandora.
2000 people thousands more
Are showing up right
Fry
The
Southside
Add
Photoshoot
It's actually on
Hernandez Twitter
From a building
Bob actually shows
Mike Ross
But
The local news
You'll notice is not
Showing
Is local news
Do not want you to know
What is unfolding
What's happening
And that's
That's how they operate you do it we're not going to show
The Kebab shop
I just have to have
Okay and then I'm going to read to you
Breakdown
On the president
That has come out
And I'm going to go through
Everything else
This year
Right now let's go ahead and play
Ali Alexander
The capital
And then I want to show
Veritas
Fairness
I'm not throwing a fit
I need to see this
Yeah I don't know
I don't know
He doesn't go to rebroadcast whoever he's at whatever intern he's hired was able to pull that up before
The pot bubbled over
Do spend a lot more time than this even on just like the crowd size
Pictures inside
Exactly the same as
After the 2016 election
Is just
Just a
The funhouse mirror version of
We did the election we talked about fraud we talked about complaining about
Different claims about
Crowd sizes
Just did
Guy lost this time exactly almost beat for be just with a different angle
Can't believe that they're going
Like it's not going to
Every other year during election season
Alex is going to scream about how it's
The devil
And then every other year he's going to be like
Well
I know we lost but
We got a path through this
And it's never going to
To stop they were always be convinced that it's the devil will always be convinced that it
It's fine that the devil 12
It is keep going
It does seem like that would be just how things
Yeah that's just how it operates
Yeah and then just come up with fun interesting stuff to say about whatever headlines
Auntie didn't read the articles of
How disappointing would have disappointed you think God is that they're like
We only fight against
The devil in an
Sitting here come on until we fight against the devil's assistant during the midterm
Yeah yeah exactly
Later otherwise you burn yourself out and if
Supernanny
Preoccupied at these crowd pictures and
Could not
Find myself
Giving a s*** out
And I understand
Turning off this episode
This Saturday episode
Boring
It is so much just like
Over and over again Ramblin repetitious the election was stolen
But it also was really
Uninspired like here's a little clip that just sort of sums up
Kind of how I feel that way
They just stole this bigger Dallas
Right out the oven
About stealing stuff
Tanaka cat
We're going to get the tools
There was no cat
Burglar and going on here ladies and gentlemen
This was
Done
I'll be open
There's a feeling of resignation almost
To the fact that I stole it we've proven it
When are you going to do
And I don't understand that
No no no I mean I
Standard if you don't actually believe any of it
Beyond perfect
Especially if
You've made your last entire year-and-a-half
Referendum on whether or not the tree of Liberty does
To be watered with the blood of tyrants from time to time
Apparently
I guess not this
Year it's been
Abundantly clear what his position on that is
Drink that you don't go back from that so
We have this situation where where you know in this. After the election where it's the 79 days of hell
Call Aaron Biden is the president election
Alex sitting Trump hasn't
Conceited and Alex doesn't know what
He's going to
I find it to be like
What are the most
Important
It's for us to be like really tracking
What are the moves
What are the things he does and I found this Saturday to be just
Almost done listenable
It's just
Banging the gong over and over again Alexa
She was stolen treading water
Yeah but putting water
Boring yeah yeah
And so I needed
Jump into Sunday
I like you to sense
Something
I really feel like Alex
Didn't do it for me at the beginning of the show
I can tell you as bad as it is we're going to come through this stronger
The other side no matter what
The devil is killing us all
I wish we could bypass was coming
Wish we could have gone around this
Which could have an easy Landing
Michelle
20%
Action
20% chance
Winning I guess I got an election and then 100% chance of everything going cool if Trump seizes power
But that would be a hundred percent chance
I don't know
2020 Acura 50/50
A hundred percent chances of Alex getting ready watch
He wants in the form of trump staying in power and then Trump.
Not being in office worker up to
Unilaterally declare itself a dictator
Yeah
But that is only 79 more days ahead
A lot of
Preparation
No sitting around thing like what is he trying to say here yours a lot of that
It's all right I'm accustomed to stretches of
Intense
Mental exertion
Alex
PS2
I brainstorm so hard this morning
For about 6 a.m. to about
12:00 noon. The office
That
Completely exhausted
Okay
Alright thinking is hard that's fair
I left and I told everybody to kill everybody but now
I think that's a bad idea so what's my next move power nap
Power nap
Seized power nap alright I know what to talk about
About today you know I think there's a new thread that I hope will go on throughout the podcast is Alex
Reverting to dream space for his
Define bee answers
Yeah Alex becoming sort of like the shaman of the the right-wing extremist world
Jared Daniel who's going to interpret his dreams more of and then we've got this all couches
I was not going to do s*** but
About his family's breakfast time
This morning
Disturbing
Well this morning I talked to my oldest daughter and my wife at breakfast with my three-year-old daughter played
Toy cars in blocks on the floor both what was happening
Well if my oldest daughter
Finish my sentences before I
Already we understand
It was a very good feeling a feeling of strength
I never went a bottom
They've been listening and they've been showing
My oldest daughter Charlotte to me she said
Almost always right
Voltaire cannot ride
So much to be
Animus speech
Twilight out the future
Stop
Coming back today I understood
You just imagine like he's sitting around with like some granola
This is a dinner conversation
These kids are too young for coffee you can't handle Alex Jones predict
In the future without a little caffeine
Yeah that's not fair
Let him get through the more DeGraw I got to deal with the Apocalypse
In the morning
I definitely not I don't know why but that mental image
Used to bees in the real world disturbing hilarious
Funny so funny man and the worst part is you're the worst
For me
The kids
Don't know
Something that's
Fundamentally true that would change everything about their outlook on life
Meister dad is Alex Jones
They're going to be
They're going to
Continue to be rich
They're going to continue to be taken care of
They're going to continue doing everything
With
No changes at all
Well none
Yeah
I mean I guess
I would say they're going to be fine in many material ways
They're not going to be fine with that emotionally
It's if you just sat him down a bit like listen
I am
Always lying
We're going to be fine
Don't worry why are you crying there's no need to cry where riches s*** we don't actually get the tear in her eye
You're almost always right doesn't sound like something and someone else says it sounds like
Alex writing dialogue for Imaginary characters
But seem like that
Anyway
I would be
More upset with him telling a story about preparing his
Children and his wife for the coming
Tribulation or whatever the f***
If he didn't
Have really good reason
Disrespect
That there
Is
Corruption
Sure in the election sure and one of the pieces of evidence he brings to the table is I mean
I'm convinced
Google.com
Google
FedEx
Record search in the days before the election
And the days after the election
No one ever searches
What is the penalty
The one of the searches and what is the consequences
And what is the
Prison time and what is the jail time
Peter searches no one's ever done
Pushpay
In Pennsylvania
In Georgia
In Minnesota
In Wisconsin
In Michigan
The search was
What is the consequences what is the penalty
What is the prison
Sometime
For election fraud
Wow that's election officials in fraud
Not Butter
Scroll up Google Trends searches for Aladdin fries
In the key Battleground States
Morton
Fattest people
Checking to see
What's going to happen to them
What a conclusion he's a big jump
So you're saying that people are Googling a crime there about
To commit
Oh my God
You don't think it might have something to do with maybe right-wing people constantly hoping retribution will come to their and amazing
That there's some sort of punishment
Discover that will be War
Open death silly friend this is a forensic fingerprint that proves
Election officials are
What up what a good thinker
I think I'm impressed by him
If that's the result of is brainstorming
For 6 hours take a nap cuz you probably have
Analytical abilities
So Alex is something in this next clip that I
I found really interesting answer
Example of like how
There's sort of a dark mirror
Version of real world
Things that are often times behind his rhetoric
Come back from break I'm going to
What they're saying the president inside the house right now
Concede
I blame him for the covid-19 deaths
Therma set up a Truth and Reconciliation Commission supporters
And they're going to make the lockdown
Economy Tent
Obiden
So I find this kind of Interest
I don't know if I disagree too much with Alex's assessment of things that could happen if Trump concedes inviting because
Comes president
I just think that he's
Portraying these things false light
Percy says that they'll blame Trump for the covid-19 deaths and to the extent that anyone should be blamed
It probably should be the executive officer the country was in a position
To make decisions that he failed to make
Obviously no one would say that it's
All Trump's fault but the conversation about policy failures
Hindu information about what was known when and what was ignored
Would almost certainly paint Trump
But a terrible light
Especially if he's staked his entire repartee
Reputation on being
A perfect
Chief executive officer
You could easily see someone like Alex experiencing a harsh sober look at Trump's virus response as the
The globalist blaming him for all the deaths
So that might
Actually be a fair assessment
Just the requested mirror
I mean you don't get to take
Credit for the things
That they end then not take blame for the
Apparently you do
Oh okay nevermind I forgot about that second thing Alex says is that there will be Truth and Reconciliation committee
To demonize Trump supporters
This is obviously Alex's way of spinning the inevitable necessity of trying to bring humans in this country back to a place where we can
Even communicate with each other
The fracturing of shared reality is something that needs to be addressed
Any attempt to do that is a threat to someone like Alex
Whose entire business relies on the perpetuation of that false reality
Attempts by people who aren't in his fantasy world to humbly reach out and reintegrate people who got sucked
Into the Trump call
Q ship is obviously going to be painted as communist indoctrination by Alex
Reconciliation
His business cannot afford for him to present it any other way. But
Veep
Attempt
Reaching out and in
Having like okay look
That s*** was really bad
But we need to cut Whitney
Need to figure out a way to move forward
That will be what this is
The third thing he says that there will be even
Harsher lockdown
Now I'm not sure if that's actually the case or Howitzer Define any of those terms
But I do think that if Biden were to get into office
Amora.
Reasonable approach
Do a Public Health crisis would be enacted it'll be easy for Alex to paint that as
These harsh Crackdown
All of the things that he's describing is
Trump concede
Are things that are based on kernels of things that could be real right
It's just preemptively painting them as these evil nefarious plans
Sugar globalist
It's how he
That's how he gives himself
The credibility of having like all these
That good prediction of the hell
Which I will come upon us in this case because we already have been told
Bad Ad nauseam what a reasonable response
What's would be
Then we've already not
Seen it then taking a reasonable response
Is already in baked into their proper
You know like
The fact that we
We didn't take a reasonable response makes a super-smart for killing 200,000 people
And if they do take a reasonable response
Then it's because
Is there trying to hurt our economy
It's just
Yeah they've already already one that messaging
On this Sunday I kind of
Do you know I felt
I felt a little bit
Still want tethered
Liquor wasn't much going on the election was stolen
Sure sure
We are desk
Ant-Man
Owen Shroyer
It's super Sonic on an eight-day sort of
Drop the ball
He's about to make up for it
Okay
Let's go ahead and lay it out right now
Starting tomorrow
If you don't watch it Caravan
Bmpro location rentals
Mexico border
Louisiana
Mississippi
Florida or North into Georgia
Then we'll go up
To the Carolinas in Virginia or I will need it in d.c.
On
How to make a bed all day
I would like to bet on this one billion dollars
In the midwest in the south
I'll take over DC this next weekend
Cavalry's coming
Now I f****** excited wow
Wow now we are in business
New segment on knowledge base
Countdown to the Caravan putting
Well I mean Caravan is also an unfortunate term for them to use cuz the right-wing was all obsessed with the Caravans coming from south
Porter shorts
He's like a weird turd picture
But
Are you guys are southern dumb dummy W McCall would let you want to eat
Hey there rubber duck we got some smoke he's on his
Caravan
Get the f*** out of here turning into a convoy have a little excited
Caravans are just plodding along destination
Convoys
What were the running moonshine
You're right it should be it should be a cowboy
And they could
That's why the hard-right sucks at everything they could even get Convoy
If Alex really wanted to put some money into this
He could hire kellyanne Conway to run the kellyanne Conway Kansai
It could work I I like it
Alliteration
You should guide all choices
Yes
So I got
Very very very very very excited
Soap opera
Stussy
Like what a great punished
Metro infusion wow
I don't know if this early punishment but like no one else could probably do this true
Really came into Infowars by yelling at people on the street
Micro whose only real value to the organization isn't as somebody who can
Tell whether Steves full of s*** or not at all
Just send him on a f****** tour
Convoy
And I have people yell at him him yell at other people
Play people took their string exactly you did the pieczenik s*** you f***** up how we're going to get back
Basic me to focus on what you do well and then maybe you'll get your shot again he got knocked down a peg
Yeah you wanted to play out of position
You blew it
Now get back
Apprentice
Go back to where you began absolutely
The potential for like
Hilarity
Unresolved High
For this is this documented
I want the raw footage of this road trip is going to produce a channel
Video right now for the Caravan
I can edit I think beautiful
I can't tell you like
I have not I've not been this excited for some dumb idea
Stop
It's something that's supposed to happen over the course of this week
Owen Shroyer is already
Somewhere yes close location
This is not good I want to bet money on whether or not this makes it
I will bet you
Money right now okay
Alex does not make it
He's going to cancel it
Charity box
I'm going to win this bet going to be
Alright
I feel like
The better bat
Is whether or not Owen make
That's a good question cuz he's actually got a challenge in front of that stripping at all of these
Alex is just going to fly him saying is if Owen doesn't make it there's no way Alex
Can save face on that right
It would be tough to beat
It's available whether or not the the presentation be better if Helen doesn't think that's true
That is true
I don't know
Steps to make up some story about him beads
Stopped
Listen to be good and you look at me well alright now
If
There were any way for this
To have been possible
I would
Almost do anything
Beyond that
Like to be a Hunter S Thompson.
Like a look I don't like you guys
But I want to do some Gonzo journalism alright I'm on this bus with Owen I'll stay out of your way I'm not going to f*** with anything
Just to be able to record this for history should be filmed
Time this should be a road trip documentary and we should have the final
This should be the new Cannonball Run
Now
Jordan
Norcold open I have to I have to I have to punch this up
Owen
Is down there he's got to get to the DC through all these stops
Antifa
Is rare and they have to get to The Oregon Territory
Of course he's going on
There's got to be somebody who's Dastardly and a dog that laughs these are the things I know about the wacky race
Ants and one car that's like
They're drunk
We're not going to show their drinking characters who are drunks
We're not showing this for legal reasons
So anyway you can tell I'm very excited about this exciting new development
Is the first time I've been really excited about something if it was done as a little while I do think there is the potential for this to go real
Really bad
Because I think a lot of
The people who might be drawn to that wedding philant and certainly I hope that's not the case
I'm excited
I'm excited for Owen tripping over his own foot all the way up the Eastern seaboard
Imagine if Paul Revere had like a two-legged horse
That's what we're dealing with here
So Alex gets to talk
Alexander
He comes on
And they're just trying to get Trump not to concede
It's so proud
Qawwali
Tonight
Get the
To concede because the cavalry's coming
Evidence of fraud is mounting massive
We know that the Press
Resident is watching these broadcast and so I want to see mr.
President
The calvary is
Coming
Calvary and Cavalry coming
Gray Cavalry for the guys who like
The Bible figure it out
We have seen Alexander really coming
Into his own as a real
Feel like Hardline real religious Traditions la
So maybe he is actually saying caliper
Put you up there
So if
The election
Is to be believed
By that you know
All the source
Reality
And even if that's the case Trump should still
Kobe Bryant that's great
We have a right to not let him be president
We've got incredible evidence
We've got
Damning evidence we've got him dead
How to write
I mean like why even do the election that based on what you're saying pretty much
You're saying that the person is disqualified so I guess
Why was
Your argument I mean why wasn't there a position of
F*** this election we shouldn't even do it
Instead of
Let's do the election the Democrats are going to try and steal it and Trump will win by a landslide
I don't understand
The cell that with the only way that it's
The fair election is if Trump wins so what are the election because if he doesn't
Let's just not do the
I didn't expect that
I think that's another thing that they're they're not able to comprehend
How stupid it makes them look right
Okay so you're saying
Trump had no like it's all
Fake evidence
None of it's real bad no evidence for the Russian
We saw a lot of
Yeah and for very
Sources all over
But you're right
So if that's manufactured
That's well
Quite
Currently
Trump is
Proving that bite
Install the election
We have very little evidence while we have Rudy Giuliani Etta landscaping place
Cecil they're even admitting that they're taking evidence
Dennis Montgomery
Alright
Hold your horses
Google Google
I bet you that's true true
Please get one person like a like a Michael Flynn or Michael Cohen to like
Flipped Forum just for a little
Pumping out the dentist Montgomery GI but from the other side you know they got to get a Bugatti in trap
Someone
I have them like turn Rogue or whatever
I think it would they really want though
We've been
Kind of aware of Shar-Peis
Forgot to seize power and is to be Christian theocracy
And always a little bit too open about
Pervert and they're seeking to you and I have talked
Invert
All of these holy orders that we have
Christianity stabilize this
Of of what Rome had no after it burned in all this
Christian be injected
Into
Western Civilization
Stabilizing formula for workout
Exactly so
The basis of what we call Western Civilization now is Chris
Christianity because
Prior Western Civilization didn't work
Oh so whenever you talk about like Western Civilization being what you're all about your actually just talking about like
I don't know a Christian
Religious state
I'm glad we can have that in the clear now
It is kind of see it is kind of out being mean again
That's really their only option
If they guess they can't even really lie about the
Open results
Cuz nobody's buying it
Except for everybody that they like
Your only option
And then just an out-and-out be like
Well in order to save the Republic we have to
Become a Christian theocracy
Yeah I think that that's sort of the the underlying Trend that you see from
People like Ali obviously
And a little bit on Infowars
Actually the sense that I got from this Sunday episode was
Very much not
That interested in the election fraud stuff anymore
Like
Kind of it it seems like we proved it and he has stuff like this that happened but
Is focus seems to be elsewhere
2 months ago saying
We got the most people ever for election fraud
Pelosi we can have enough saying I don't care what happens to this thing coming up
He'll be inaugurated after
There was one thing criminals do they love to brag
Anthony over here
Secondly
We're in a situation where we have put
Together
And you'd guys did did it did it for our administrative President Obama's administration
Before this
We put together
I think
The most
Extensions
And inclusive
Voter fraud
Organization
In history of American pilot
But we are ready
I feel very confident that Joe Biden will be elected president
On Tuesday
Forever
End
Count is
But
On the election that occurs on Tuesday he will be elected on January 20th he will be
Inaugurated president of the United States
She's the one that does the salon that's going bankrupt
Damascus
I find that like
Clip was
Useless I don't think I didn't hear anything in there that was even like
Suspicious
No I think he's just trying to pass off
Confidence as
Knowledge
Perhaps but I think even he recognized I was so weak that he had to complain about the
Salon
Anything that's in the club
Sounds a little worse
And if you think that he was just speaking a man accidentally said that they put together a voter fraud organization
The conclusion that Alex is presenting
However that's not Biden misspeaking
It's a clip taken from an interview on pod save America for back in October
In reality if the person who found that clip it allowed it to play in full movie pain Play album
Was talking about organizing to stop and avoid
Instances of voter fraud
But honestly that's not the best word that he could have used
What he was referring to as more of a broad-spectrum voter disa
Enfranchise
Immediately after the clip stops by and goes on to
Discuss be calling line that have been set up to connect people with lawyers who can help if they have trouble voting or face intimidation at the polls
These are the sorts of specific talents has because it's about appearances
It's not reality
Eclipse sounds really bad like buying was accidentally admitting to setting up a
Voter fraud organization
But it only does if you only listen to that little snippet
Facade doesn't Publix
What you doing Matt restorative
Not talk about it that much
I think he wants to talk about that
What's dark but this goddamn
He also has an emergency message
Emergency message
Coming out the bottom of the hour
Who got that message coming up and I think that's really where you want
This do you wants to put his Focus
Sure sure sure we'll get to that in a minute
Because his Focus
Is never far
From one person
One person in this world
Hans
Alex like a wheel
Showmars
Preparing to remove
Kamala Harris will probably bring Hillary Clinton
What a time to be alive
I mean if you want
Millions of people outside the White House
Trick everyone into getting Hillary Clinton become president now be vice-president then and then
Kamala Harris
Xeno constitutional Steph
So this is where I got
You know I've already I think I think based on our Behavior so far you can already tell I'm super
Excited about this complex
Now here's where I got real excited
You're coming in here lied
Live
Strong
4 day trip to DC
Send a message to the globalist that they are in deep trouble
March on DC it's here when the chips are down
You going to do now State weather
I felt challenged
And I realized
We're going to join that Caravan 00
We have to do an episode on Friday
At this is if there ever was an emergency episode necessary
The Caravans the only thing I care about now it's the only thing I can
Because Gina what
I think that's going to be fun
Yeah I think that's going to be fun for us I even think it's going to be fun for Owen and all the people in the Caravan
Temporarily forgotten about Assassin's Creed
Because this Caravan is accepted
Now I kind of want to do a caravan
Yeah you almost like you can just Envision in your head like
Sad moments of funny music behind it
It's great so it's not going to be a normal regular thing
But Caravan necessitates
We got to do an episode on Friday about the Caravan
That will have to be decided on Friday
20 of Caravan nonsense
I2 to get it when he too
God it's just going to be a series of banana peels
I can't imagine being
Alex Diaz videos is emergent
MC message coming up
Heera he throws to
Okay the videos abandon videos infowars.com Alex Jones does emergency measures of President Trump
Do not conceive
I love you I
Appreciate your amazing
Appreciate those that brought you here
If you decide to spread this video
Presently
Here is the report
I bet if you spread it if
It still isn't going to
Now
I don't know if Trump's going to
See eye-to-eye a lot of shares on that Infowars video I better wake up
Snap out of it
Oh man that Infowars video has almost as many likes
Is that dumb
Tweet I just posted
Did 5 seconds ago I better change all of my thing this is where I got to go
Do I spell cheated
Buy this because the emergency message that he was teasing I didn't realize it was a pre-recorded video
You just did this week and leave half an hour early
He just lets
Yeah
But you know
He has an emergency message
So we better find out what it is
President-trump
The approach
Joe Biden and his new
King Commission
They're going to tell
You're going to be blamed
How's the death
How much do you sign onto a new lockdown
Contact tracing
But even people being
From their homes and forced inoculate
When you sign on
Covid-19
Legitimizing
The martial law
This country
I'm a complete shutdown
Will be
You sir
You're going to be approached by
At midnight you will be visited by
Team Ghost
The 4th will give you an envelope as the location
Come on man
What are we doing
Alright this is kind of what I think Alex wants to turn this into a as opposed to worrying too much about like
Voter fraud or whatever it's feels just dead
Deflated even on Alex's show
What do you wants to talk about is
During the 79 days of hell
Bright Biden and his transition team
We're going to have some ideas about better ways to address
Covid-19 situation sure the real conspiracy is
Is there going to make
Bucking demand
Bored with their globalist plant
If they if he doesn't
Then they're going to blame the deaths on him
He does
Then are going to blame the damage
The economy that their evil plans do during play baton Trump
He has that situation except to come out
Say go fuc
Yourselves globalist but then even if they do that they're going to try and use the 25th Amendment to take him out of office
Sure really much more exciting then yeah
Very very boring voter fraud claims that Dennis Montgomery's pedaling
You think that
That press conference
Should taken in
Higher party down
That's how sad that was yeah wanted to laugh at it because it's may be objectively the funnies
This thing I've ever heard
Yeah it was
Using Leaf everything about it I thought about it is everybody who
Who is like oh, he's going to be good under the Trump Administration
And I'm like
Every single thing I've seen of people trying to dunk on this
Is not as funny
And never will be
As if mirax
Like you're never going to win there's no
Point in trying, d.c. standing next to a pawn shop
With a f******
Pedophile right next to a
It just doesn't get better than that
There's no joke
That is better than that
And landscaping place also called Four Seasons
Self is it implied
Pedophile after the fifteen-year-old girl thing
Like the whole thing is off the rails
Joq I have
None
So Alex's message to Trump
Is largely like you got to talk more s*** man
So essential
For you now
The election
Come out with your beliefs
All the Oval Office
Layout
The news
Articles
And the new science
Call the doctor
Under Obama's
Command
Before you ever got into office
For running
The very
Exact
Covid-19
Weaponized virus test
Drop you got to use our talking points
You got to get in the Oval Office in
Say Infowars s*** that'll really help me out
Well Alex
Just talkin those articles flash up on screen one of them is that article from the scientist
Oh no
Right under the headline
When is an editor's note
About Heather
Conspiracy theories
Crack a
Connecting this article to covid-19 for in the coronavirus and now this is all on
Substantiate even is Alex is trying to show this evidence
Did he just doesn't work
Accidentally
Checking himself
So they're going to try and remove Trump
Is that
That's what this emergency messages all the time
Sure
Irish to know
What they're planning
Office
Before
20th
Planet
Brick Oven
It's been their plan all along
Then your legacy
Supporters
Will be a revocable econnect
The covid-19
People will be perfect
Computed
Americanism itself
Will be demonized
Wuhan virus
Which of the Chinese,
I would say that history is not going to be super kind
Stu Trump's fans
No. About their response
Wants to
Do probably not go
Going to go well
Don't Trump leaving early no more staying until January
Imaginary
Saginaw
Just going to look back.
Weird how
Responding poorly to a Public Health crisis
Seem to be
Policy plank
Weird seemed like a good idea
It's very strange new policy is murder
They're going to try and use that 25th
Amendment
Sure
You who is still present
Election of the Constitution
Implementing
If you do not
Mediately agreed
They're going to say the 206
Teapot styles
You died from something else
Ronnie
Your
Watch
Your head
You are
Guilty of this
The 25th of May
I do not
President of the United States
Discredit you
Election
Put the certified that Frozen election
By having your own tablet remove you
Under the 25th Amendment
Because you don't follow
The recommendations
Orders
Abigail B
Do Global Discovery
I mean what's the point
I don't I don't understand
Why
I think what's funny about this is that
He's
Okay
In his world
We live in a
This is what they would do so we do it
But they would do what our plans are that we're doing right now
So
I think Alex is actually saying that one he knows
All of this stuff is
This is all transfer
And
That's the only way is the best way for us to go about this
Is to use the 25th Amendment to remove him from office
To do all this stuff early like he's saying that the best plan
Well that's what he would do
In our situation
Right but that's not always still even the best thing to do
Does this weekend
Movies like here is what I would
And that's what they're trying to do already
Yeah I hear it more like
Yeah it's going to look
Real bad
If competent leadership comes in
And people like oh this is what we've been missing
Like all the Deep State all these weird
Weird things that have been going on over the past couple years
Weird excuses
Are all just going to look
Kind of dumb
And I think Alex recognizes that
And you know
Abstract people
Create
Do something funny
79 days of hell
I have to leave
Anyway I mean something that scares me
Is there's only two ways
And that is to
Step down early
And have
Pence right
The most
Broad pardon
In the history of the United States
That somehow also supersedes any and all State Crime
When's the Trump is coming
Or
Not leave
Because anything other than those
2nd going to J
So
I think he knows that until proven guilty first of all
I don't I don't know
I don't I don't know if that's the case but
I could easily see some kind of
Brokered immunity I don't know nothing to to say if
He leaves office
He's going to lose all of her
Shmoney
Like it's going to be a bloodbath
For him personally
Because he's bad at everything
And I think what's going to save us is he's too incompetent
To do either of the only two things that he
Then maybe I don't know I think
I think we'll see
I'm not entirely sure
Alex is presenting
Drop with this position we're like if
You're going to be approached
Show me is going to tell you Biden secret plan
Should you
So you know to this plan they would blame you for all that right
However if you say yes to it
Here
Is what you got to do
Are you looking to have
If you follow the law.
Your name
Homecoming depression in the United States
Blame you
All the previous deaths staying later
You actually a
But you were the one
You did we have tape
Scion
You got come out exposed fauci
Bill Gates
Galbi
All of them
Oval Office
Only
Stop them
So this is the 20% he was talking about earlier I think
Is Trump giving
Oval Office addresses where he spouts Infowars
Conspiracies
I think 20% is a
Embarrassingly
Hi
Chance to give that if successful
I think
As far as Alex Goes
This is a great
The Great
What does good as he can do because
Trump has nothing left to lose
And this would be great for Alex's business
So why not see if trouble do some s*** form now
I think even Alex has to recognize that that that
I think fruit list
Publix
I do think that this is better
For Alex
Then getting too hung up on the election stuff to hung up on
F****** like
Even addressing Steve's nonsense like
It's a better game to play that like
It's really about because then
Kind of
Has a stage remove
From be like
Strict electoral stuff at parties outside of Paula
This is about the globalist evil plan
You know it and I think that is
Good
For him so I think that's why he's Focus
And this message to the president
Supposed
Is not about
Fight in Michigan fight in Pennsylvania
Y'all get there to counterbalance right
Get to Steve pieczenik on the phone he's at the sting operation
Or whatever you know like not doing that
Because
Sure that you live in the background
But it's proven already yeah yeah we have to go
Because there's more pressing information exactly
Did Biden's covid response team is really
A trojan horse
To get Trump out with the 25th Amendment
Or
Sure
That's pretty good on his part in terms of spin
He's playing thing
Flat night handle Steve pieczenik
Get Owen out of the studio for a while I let me try and f****** thread whatever needle that I need to
To try and keep us in business after next week
I think that's about as good as you can get any better
Who is the Beast Aunt out of this camera
Totally
Now this is a far better plan than I ever would expect
I don't even know if it's a
Plan I wonder if it's
It's just kind of like alright
What can we do
Alright
This could work
Yeah I don't know if it's a grand machination or apart or anything
Number of the requirement
B get around some of
The problem
Still not a good play because it's still like
I mean
What happens when the 25th Amendment isn't
Invoke
What happens when
Do you know these votes are certified and and Biden
Is they do need to have the transition team's takeover
What happens in January
These are only
Like
Little Band-Aids you can put on gas there's still a much larger problem isn't being addressed by it right but
In terms of being like Alex Jones or you got to keep moving the shock of Lies
Toronto truth shock of light
In terms of being that guy
It is good at
You could do right now
I wouldn't be surprised if they half-assed their way into an accidental
Competent
Move I don't know if it's
Albertsons wear green on a curve
Fetster
I keep reminding myself
Eating parts of his
Best Buy
Survival food
It looks like it's made of glass
It's actually Sugar
New Cal on my last episode I fall into the desk from
20 ft above given
Throwing an elbow drop
Alex is talking
Background dressing that Trump won the election and it was stolen
President-trump
Choreograph
The approximately blamed
Covid-19
The American people not believe it they know the truth
Feel like you over woman
Snooze
Election fraud is designed to take you out
If you comply
Give you
Take the Olive Branch the neocon
Mitt Romney and George W bush
Say okay I'll
I'll follow the recommendations
The president-elect
Showbox
The lock things down
The wear the mask
Inoculation
Contact tracers
Turn around later in
Admits that you will repudiate
Your fault
Gentamicin
The kitchen of your supporters
So basically Alex is being like for our sake please cease power
I find most interesting about that is that Alex called Biden president-elect
Yeah I know
I feel like you would be more Patty than they all know
I feel like you would be
That's really weird
Really strange
I feel like do a second tank I know he's the one take also their cuts
Mispronounce the word
That's not great
But
Even in this message
That is
And I like I said
There's there's this
It is supposed to be like a message
Directly to Trump
There's an elephant in the room that Alex can't even ignore in this message
And that is the Trump is not being a leader
Waiting for leadership
We need the address
From the Oval Office
When you get a reconfirm
In the face of Fox News never sell out Traders
That you are
Going to concede
The fraud and fell out
Election system in this country
We know you're our camping
So even that it's kind of like a call-out
A little bit
Man I feel so
Like Joe Rogan and Alex
Like so many of these people
AR
Sitting here being like
Where's Q
Where's trout
Where is all this stuff and it's like guys
They weren't your friend
Yeah they
You've been using you
You're the fool here I know you can't admit it but that's what
Got to get you just brought up Joe Rogan's I need to say two things real quick
Someone sent me a message
About Tim Dillon on Joe Rogan show sure they pointed out to me that Tim Dillon is
Sober
First recovery or whatever Goshen
Or smoke we were saying that he was high
It was because
He kept saying he was high
Yeah but I realize it was probably saying is he high like because he's around.
And I misspoke and I apologize about that I didn't mean to imply
Tim was high when he wasn't made that mistake
Easy easy to make
Second letter is an a****** without p
Second
I think I had this fantasy
Rogan
Ikea and Isaac
I just rationalize having Alex on my show
I just started thinking about how fun it would be if you was like
Forced to have Alex's friends on the show
Alright
Okay you want Alex on there you got to bring a picture anaconda
Keep chatting with you for a little while if you want to say that this guy sources and s*** are backed up and we got a fact check
Let's bring
Pieczenik right next
Next episode
Dance that dance
I want to do this do it next time
Today
And now Florida congresswoman elect Laura Loomer
I don't think it's outside possibility to lose my husband on drugs because that doesn't think she has but so either
If you want to have Alex back again
Is that
Is that Batman appeared from the bushes
What's brings up a headline in his address to
This is one of his at current talking
Had
UK
Their secretary
Their chairman
Are there Joint Chiefs
Other defects.
General Sir Nick Carter
Coming out and saying
Lockdown
The trigger World War 3
Another lockdown
So I said line of an article that Alex didn't read about an interview with General Sir Nick Carter on Sky News
Where he discussed how they continuing covid-19 situation and
Economic ramifications of it
Around the world has the potential to exacerbate Regional conflicts that already
Exist
Many people don't feel like Regional conflicts are too relevant to their lives but Carter was trying to point out the
The quote rhythms of History show to that localized tensions
Can easily ratchet up and drag Nations
Store
What are you saying is that regional conflict can off an Escalade when it's miscalculated
And ignore
He said quote
If you look back at the last century before both world wars
I think it was an arguable that there was escalating which led to the miscalculated miscalculation
Which ultimately led to war descale we hope
We never see again
His comments weren't meant to imply that dealing with covid-19
To cause a third world war
And you never said that measure is that Alex
Exaggerated unnecessary
That's Oz imagination about what an article he hasn't read
Says based on his impression of headlight
The interview was given to celebrate remembrance
Sunday ruk day of commemoration for the service person
Another country who participated in the two World Wars
Given this context
The General's comments on the interview made a lot more sense
But it's exactly
This context that Alex makes it his job.
Deprive his audience of
It's bad enough when the intended audience is some listener who might buy dumb pills
It's another thing when he's imagining that he's calling the
What does bulshit
It makes total sense this is a remembrance Sunday interview about these world wars
And the concerned it regional conflict
Grow in and and golf
Other p
Yeah I mean
World War 1 was
Rich guy got killed men a bunch of cows
You know
Do we have one last clip here Jordan sure
This is
Saatchi a metaphor this is a audio metaphor
More Alex Jones is
Dumdum message
The trop
Mike down for this because I want you to experience this and it's full.
We're still on air
Infowars.com
Video
Announcements later this evening
Caravans
Alcorn State
Descending on Washington DC
In the next few days
Infowars.com
Attention business owners Bodyslam by overwhelming debt
Just
Just amazing
I can't even I can't say enough about that
This is this is this
Can be amazing beautiful video that I was pre-recorded so he could lie
Leave work early so you can give a message of desperation to the president and first of all ends with a plug for
Infowars.com
Directly to the I mean if I was going to plug his book
Send a message to me what a dick what is
What does imply like okay
The message to Trump part is kind of part of the performance to her
A painfully obvious
I meant it's just a Larry Miss timed it and he got cut off by the brake how long
You do
To the second yes
It is recorded numbers on Mario
Call Lynn
Don't
Romans 8:28
54 reason that you need to be getting cut off by the break-in
The recognition that this is performed
It's art for the audience as it's also an admission that like
It's not as important as
We don't really care about getting the whole messaging
The fact that we did it we like
And hate Trump get excited
The Caravans are coming
Great thing to say we've got your back
Are you heading the overwhelming. Just so good because
In the statement of we've got your back and then you literally dis
Imagine if your Trump listening to what else
Not only do I have the cold out
Message pills I've got pills I got your back and I got pills
Dino
Rare
I need for Friday episode but this Caravan demands it
I'm excited to follow the adventures of Owen Shroyer
Across these United States
I'm excited to see what kind of goose
I wish I was there
This Caravan Hasbro has breathed New Life in
This is very exciting
And I
Just
Whoever they hired I know they've got somebody
Video that somebody with cameras
You got to give a
What's the raw footage yeah yeah
It should be 24/7 filming this should be a f****** David at
Bro documentary-like that's what we're dealing
Whatever they're using
To go down there should be like hardwired
Video audio at all times
Verner hertzog is there has to be there
The potential for this just to be an amazing story that might never get told
It's too high it's too high
I know
Do our best
We got this
And we'll see you then
Go to bed Jordan net worth
Charity or bail Fund in your area to help out people
Text Clark I'm Daryl rundus I think it's totally fine
Are free watch Dancing with the Stars
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work