Damn important
Pray I have great respect for this knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Sit around drink novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex
Emmerich June
Jordan
What's up
Now it is my turn to say that my bright spot is Assassin's Creed Valhalla
The game and I'm very dizzy
Excited first of all to be out of the snow now I've gotten to the point where I'm not
Does rediger free for free
But also that like they brought back
The homestead
Aspects of
I love so much
Love the idea of just building up a little settlement and all that
Some of those really missing
From the last two games
I do enjoy that quite a bit
Obviously not played nearly as much as you but I've been quite a bit
Of the things that they
I think they fixed a lot of things
That we're kind of little
Hurdles
Play in the past ones
It's very very good
I look forward
Do a dabbling around
Playing
For the next very long time
Problem
There's because I finish the audiobook invented came out I'm like
Out of of all other work
Like this is my reward
So I'm just putting
Hours upon hours
Intuit
Island
I swear to you I
Don't think I've gotten out of the
I still think the title card is coming like
Good.
What the genre in the style of
You came there for
Totally my bright spot Dan is it is one
Leslie Jones
On the reboot of Supermarket Sweep
It is
Fant
It is first I'm hearing about this
This to know it's so great like the old guy was fantastic turnout he was just he was just that white guy who
Was 5 ft
And Leslie Jones
Host of the show a
Exactly how I would host the
The show and watches the sweep exactly how I watch it
Incredibly serious
Oh okay
Yeah Bandits
Perfect that is great
To go with it one is like that the better option totally
Incredibly serious just
Straight face
You've got the cup of coffee that's $300 already you're going to go back again to take the I think you could get I could do that
That really well
It would be much more.
Difficult to pull off in an entertaining funny way
Supermarket Sweep when I would stay home sick
Every part of the show is
Is better than what you remember and Leslie is
Credibly good
Congratulations congratulations
So you people off the cats
We are on our day off and we're coming in
What's a convoy Duty called
And if I hadn't had to pour over as much
Stuff is I have to get this episode ready
I was going
What does a prize You by putting on a truck
A cab
Pics of the open with Eastbound & Down
Say something
Eastbound & Down is for like people who wish
Stay were truck
C.w. McCall
Pittsburgh real
3 year old
I didn't realize we had hip
Webster truckers now to
So we have
Quite a bit of
Nonsense to go over over the
November 9th
And yeah this is
I'm excited
And I
Decided that this series is going to have a name because Monday is the conclusion of it
Because we don't know what happened
Alex hasn't gotten down to DC not there yet for me to cover everything
Broken it up into
The two chunks
And we're calling this
Cara vanity project
I'm going to have
To take words away from you
If you want to use them you can ask
Wealthy I was thinking about it I was like a written request
I was sitting there like this is kind of a vanity project
Dick from a Caravan Grand Caravan project kisses amazing Jordan's going to hate it
Even worse because I know how long it took you
Second thought after coming up with a detector
Furious
Down to my Caravan Tree project
Resigned up a recording show
The first ominous warning thank you so much you are now policy walk
Omnicef
They called her ominous warning
Jessie G
Fealty
I'm a policy wonk you very much
That is about to an apology Wong
Next
!
Obviously
Next Elizabeth
I'm a policy wonk
Text Joshua
I think it's about two and a half hours
Next
Thank you so much
Chris welcome to the club
Appreciate that very much so
Sailor Moon Spirit sister Stephanie be thank you so much you are now attacking
Are you pimp
Sailor Moon Spirit sister Stephanie
Is it going to rain
Agoda website
What you can do is
Get yourself a big old cart
Run it up and down the metaphorical
Grocery aisle
Do not forget the turkey those are $100 balls
Make sure that you get what's on the shopping list this week that the next
Tu250.
Are you going to want to get the triple bonus that's $300
Down to your local charity or Belvoir
And donate
Not bad not bad
The same bonuses as the old one or did they
A flip-up what I do
You need to get
Coffee
Jerky Leroy
Thermoses and chitlins
Just myself
Wonderful I'm about to get on this immediately
Episode
Caravan
So Jordan our Wednesday episode we learned the new Infowars plan to run a caravan from
Austin Texas
Then upward along the east coast arriving on Friday and washing
Then d.c.
The idea
I guess is that
The Cavalry is coming
The drop these fight off the globalist Menace
Prudential Reality is a little less noble than
On an Optics level
The goal is very obviously meant to provide Trump Within
An appearance that he could use to make claims that the people are demanding that he fight back against the Alexa
The result
Because he lost
This Caravan is an attempt of the people's
Start to turn themselves into human prop
Which Trump can use to justify an authoritarian power grab
On a deeper level this is Alex attempting to pull off an outstanding
Overly ambitious and protect protracted publicity
Please.
He's hoping that sending dum dum Owen Shroyer at the Barn store in the Eastern side of the country
Will force the media to pay attention to
And his mind Owens going to
Pick up a couple hundred Patriots in Austin and by the time he reaches Houston the number will be in the
Thousand
By the time they hit d.c.
It'll be a massive people it'll be impossible to ignore
This is not what's going to happen
I'm so feeling that
He's hoping the people with big social media reaches
We unable to resist meme in the f*** out of clips
On the road
And he'll be able to drive some trap
The final thing that this done accomplishes
Is it provide something with a
Drastic immediacy
They can distract the audience for realizing that if anything Alex says means anything
No number of people showing up in DC is going to mean
A damn thing
Because I was already said that the globalists are going to kill everyone no matter what and they even if Trump is
Successful there's a plan B
That the Patriots
Can't Stop
In this sense the Caravan serves as the shity
Shiny set of keys that Alec
Mexican jingle around to keep people
Cancel an auto-ship
Biting his one we need to kill everyone and overthrow the United States government
Biden
We're going to go on a road trip they got 79 days of hell
I bought a URL literal devil has one
Let's get on the road
We're already just bullshiting about the
The apocalypse on the devil why not create our own tribulation it's fantastic
All that being said I love this
It's my favorite thing to divorce is done in a long time
Partially because it's
No naked and tramps
Parenteral
If this ends up being anything notable Italy a collection of people whose various scams are endangered
If Trump is out of office
He could easily end up being like the Rocky Mountain Rendezvous but you replace the Nazis and white power groups
With pill salesman
And YouTube commentators who just now realized
Overplayed their hand
Canarian way too deep
On another level this also scratches a very pretty
Particular itch for me
And that's what I f****** love Road
I love road trip so much that I
Kind of fond memories of Tom Green's movie wrote
Back when I was younger me and my friends would often just embarked on random trips for the sake of driving a couple hours or a day
Hey way to see what was there
Sometimes there was a destination but other times it was just the experience of being out on the road
Seeing things that weren't part of our normal routine which was the
Actual reward itself
I love that
And it's one of the
Things that I feel is most missing
For my adult life
You're probably a big part of why I dream of getting an RV in wandering the country
Caravan
He's been branded these stop the steel Caravan and I cannot
Not pay
All the attention in the world
What's a better name and stop this
Steel
Harold trying to piggyback this stop this
Steel momentum that people like Ali Alexander have been pushing for a little while
Choosing that name as well go all the way back
We got to go all the way back
226 to UB election and you think
Hangouts
All the way there's a connection there but I'm not sure what it is
And I
Because it's
It's frustrating
An article from the Southern Poverty Law Center Trace be
The current pushers of the term stop this
Bastille number of new far-right folks
Who are connected to Rodger
People like Jack
So big Mike cernovich and Ali
They're amplification of it reached other Fringe figures like
Michelle Malkin
Faith Goldy
And then even
Trump son Eric
Who pushed the term onto a larger audience
It's hard not to feel like all of this somehow
Back to Stone but
Improve it
It drives me nuts
It's important to recognize before we get too far into any of this there two threads
To keep the stick
Both of them which are branded stop
Bastille
The first of the series of depressing protests are being organized around the
Some of them may be organically started and organized
And some of maybe AstroTurf by tea party groups and write
When money they wants the result of
The protest but definitely doesn't want to be associated with
That's really a smaller issue to me what's
Organic and what
It's not investigate or probably publish
He's about in about a year
What's definitely true about the
These protests is it they're being Amplified and pushed by this network
Desperate Trump scam
The second thread is Alex's Caravan
Would you spiritually connected
Bellevue protest
Results
Trying to selfishly profit off them as well
How it's supposed to be stuck is not about bringing more attention to these protests
Take whatever energy
My generator
And steal it
Increase the spotlight
On his tank with a huge Infowars logo on it
Almost like
This is a
A conference of scammers
And Alex
It is it is lonely
It's totally like baby
Maybe you have to scam them to get into the scam conference you know it's like an entry
Alex tuch on man Island
Exactly
Zambo as it relates to protest
For most of his career he just uses them to self aggrandize himself
Make the protest about
This is no.
Course
That's why I'm treating Alex's Caravan stunt as a separate thing from the protest even though they're technically both
Part of the same desperation strategy
It's being used by these Doom
It simultaneously more simple and more complicated than the sad protest
I will save it as I'm preparing this episode it does not look good like we're like the Caravan is really set the world
World on fire
If you judge by the number of views that the videos on banned. Video have
The kick-off video and Austin has about 130 set
7000 views but
But the drop-off
From there is quite
Noticed
Yes
It doesn't feel like this is working out so
So far and that being said
I still
I would give anything to have been able to go along for the ride
I feel like I could have written my own fear and loathing long after the campaign Trail 2020
If I would have been allowed to go
It sadly that will never be
For now the best I can do is
This two-part series on art
About the Tor Owen Shroyer is taking
From Austin UPS
To d.c.
On the information available to me from
How far
Since the timing is what it is this going to be part one where and we'll discuss what happened on the Caravan tour
Between its launch on November 9th
And then
To the end of Alex's show on Wednesday November
After that we'll pick up on Mondays episode
So we'll wrap things up
With the Wednesday Thursday
And then the event in d.c.
There stood
Is very very stupid
I fucken love
I love it
So much
I can't
I can't believe
The main reason that you do a caravan is
I believe wholeheartedly
You're going to pick up
Momentum along
The way
You know it's going to start as a small thing and then it's going to snow
And you know
The premise for you even to get the moment they said Caravan
I knew it was going to fizzle out
In the way that are
Firework
Should feel like an inverse firework
You know it's going to
Explode
Physically
Yeah I don't know I'm don't get ahead of yourself with predictions alcohol but
I mean we'll see we'll see what all this
What goes down alright
Today Show
I am a president I am the President
I am 46
Alex has declared himself president
Elaboration
Bowling night
I'm not positive if David Knight had any Caravan business
On November 9th
And hopefully never know because I didn't listen to what I'm not going
November 9th
On Alex
Show
And
He's tried to keep Spirits High
There is still
To win the election
Fairly and squarely
That was sitting in
What are the offices this morning
12 ft away from a trash can
I should watch this and I threw a little
Turn off the wall
File cabinet and into the trash
Getaround
Around is the law
We're going to build a wall
Alright
And I will
If everyone bullhorn to the White House
Call the White House
The bullhorn the White House
The bullhorn marlago comes back and forth
Pointy ears
Him know what's happening with the unfolding and I can tell you
On the phone with
Salisbury close to president or the president if I need to
I don't have a day or two.
Telephone
Many times they call that missed the call
I miss some of the calls are in the last few days I cannot
By the telephone
I cannot sit
It makes me sick
Bomb here phone
I missed the phone call
Calls
But when I map
You know what happens every time I go to call him and he's in the middle of calling me and then the line is busy
Yeah man
I don't think this is a good angle beak
Because Alex is already said multiple times that he and Trump are literally Psych
Seafood Connection
I really don't think they understand that his advice is essentially
Bully your fearless leader into taking over as a dick
I mean that's really what it seems like
The whole thing is
Be a bully
To a guy that we think is unbelievable
Even though we obviously know if we just
Which Adam apparently he'll do whatever we want
Caravan as a whole is like
That is
Directed at
Trump
Exactly it's not really for us
Support
It's the yell at Rebellion
To give him already
Kind of the idea
You've always been conception and execution it's very bad
I love that Alex is saying like I take this nap and then I miss Trump calling it recently we've seen that Alex
Did you get the prophetic visions
The other get the call in the nap
He might have that would explain everything
Everyone else in the world is
Too dumb
To see what Alex
Everything is so clear to him
And you
F****** idiot
Just won't get
Get it together
It's all America will probably
That sounds right
Thursday while he's president-elect
Running is fake task force
Truck cannot assault
Fraud of the scam and lay it all out
House addresses and it's over
Enchilada of the in
It's like
Soviet Union
Instead of
That's fine
Sounds like a great Patriot
Lotto America no matter what
And you can all burn if I can't pay rent on my gigantic Studio
Patriotic and if you cannot
Help me
Lifan billion-dollar home
Yeah
I just hope you all burn to death
Republic
Is based on the blood
Patriot
And I'll stand up for it as long as I'm making a dollar off.
You guys can all burn to hell
So Alex has this strange thing going on about like how he can't get ahold of
Trump in like
Text today
Because
I'm officially choking on air
I love my crew
All stressed out
And
Over the edge
Professional I am some of the Caribbean
Knox
Bag and then get ahold of Don Jr and then get the present on the phone
And that hope he listens to me about this stuff
And there's nothing more frustrating
Been missing phone calls from the president
Wow
Seems like
Describing isn't anybody
Have to beg somebody to get a hold of John Jr does seem like that
That's the only way to get
Get there
That's not gray.
Jr's handlers are doing a lot
To keep Alex Jones
Don Jr will believe any old b******* Alex please don't get him anywhere near there
It's going to get a blowback on a
He's an idiot
All right there's a there's a Feeling
Of that Alex is really mad
He's very
Corsi is
Terry's got to get away
Owens got to come into
The discuss the launchers
The Caribbean islands already on the Caribbean
Evening of the night
Stop is Austin at 5
Right on the night he still he still there to be in studio
And what they do is basically what we were already talking about about this
This whole idea of going to Washington
It's a threat
To Trump
They're saying basically
We will
Stop
Supporting you and we are the only people who support
Paramore behind truck now that ever what about you owing
Yeah and I'm going to be more behind him for the next I guess 72 days
And he better he better rise to the occasion in the next 72 days
And save this route
Public or his name is going to is going to be
You know
Emblem on the side of his building airplane
Savage
Shi
Wow we will abandon you and basically
You see these scam dudes
Who are going to show up in d.c.
Brandon straka jaspas obok
We're the only people who give a s*** anymore it's where the Ocean's Eleven taken down
We were overdoing
Arguing with everybody who's accurately describing your actions
Yeah yeah
Why in God's name
Would you think
He's going to step up
Be the leader now
Did you really convinced yourself that all you need to do to step up and be a leader is be a belligerent a****** on TV
That
I think they know what they think
Yeah I think that is what Alex thinks he's done very little ass
Alex has a little bit of an inch
Slated sin
What could come from this Caravan
Isaiah
You might be a little
Might be a little bit I got to reveal that the whole thing was actually a sting operation through this guy or not
Okay
Cowboys
To stop a few times a day so you can
You don't meet up with it
Join us
And we use the phone
Caravans going
Tri-C the Saturday
I didn't the Friday's going to change the world
So now the time to take action ladies and gentlemen
5:30 today
I don't know if you're going to get hundreds
The vows of cars
Truckers to shut down DC but
Good luck
From what I see that might be a little higher
Do a little bit huh
Unless
A person can drive
A couple thousand cars themselves really feel like what's going to change the world is that Mass
Scoop Owen has right about how this is
Tire election has been a sting out of a scoop
He's got a huge scoop of this he recanted this to feel like he needs to just really Hammer this home because it's
Obviously the biggest story of you
It would be he said it was the biggest news since the election
You know he's got to pay the bills
Courtney's just straight-up reading ad copy like
Pivots or anything huh
Riding shotgun
American Patriot
Are you and your family again for coming down
Please support us
Praises to you right now because I'm pouring out all the money we got to run these operations
American crisis emergency
Lockdown to is coming
Support Infowars in the fight against totally canonical apps
Martial law
Besides lockdown to
Up 60% off
Plus free shipping
Point on
Has big say oh yeah it's a real great
Great read
He talks about
I need to get rid of everything you got to get rid of everything
Now he's at least two vehicles out there that act looks like
God I can't even imagine
Yeah he's running the sale where everything 60% off free shipping triple Patriot Point you are
Pretty similarly extreme sales
And talked about how he needs
To sell everything pretty regularly
Internet
Panasonic
Call headlight
Timeco
Is it true you're going bankrupt
No
Family business
Play while you're out of business, don't work for the Blazer whenever
Fine
I love you
So I mean like Alex is the one who keeps actor
Sing like he's going out of business saying we can't afford to stay in business
People get that idea
That was two years ago so who knows alot and then
Terms of employees like going and working somewhere else I would to constantly set on are these not the
Fire people it again
If I heard her I wouldn't risk it
I wouldn't hurt it one time even if I knew on-air he's a lying piece of s*** I be like
Just it's still in there
He's not full of s*** this time
Leaving you like
Without a job out of nowhere
I'll go find someplace
Buckling back
But I bet he has a better like workouts
Have to assume
Yelled at every time because I'm
14 and I don't know how to pull up a
Clip goddamn 14
So Alex believes
Releases pretending to believe
That he is actually respond
Possible for Trump knocking
And he wants to see if the American people really ready to fight
Fight for this country and have it back to I think there's an element of that
Cuz if he sees
Millions in d.c.
As soon as I saw us
As soon as I saw everybody around
They specifically mentioned
Getting together in Austin and I like
Conceited
That's all people
Get together in Austin haha
Yeah alright
Trump has lied guy if eyes are come up to his
Mr. president
Protectionism play
Is been Unleashed
So they talked a little bit about what people are afraid of
Then I kind of agree
Fraud
What's a jail with nobody have Jose a try, agent
Illegitimate
Calling us out to action
I don't agree with anything that he said except for yes I think he's very much afraid
People like you
Crazy friend
Because that would
Very much cos
People to die
On TV I'm calling on
Patriots to
Take over this country action
Yeah we're going to die like a green light
Totally
Straight up Non-Stop
Mass murder
Anyway Alex gives you a reason to think he's going out of business which
I don't know why you was confused about it earlier
Play responsibilities
Shorty need but it takes money to do it
I'm watching what I did two months ago.
The capital
Last time we didn't have enough Capital to keep going
Wow
That's that's why that's almost like he's like why would you leave
I've been in this situation so many times I'll figure out a way to pay you eventually come on it did strike
Makes me as like
I'm guilty of this to like being like that maybe this is the time that he's actually
Completely f***** on the money order
Totally
I'm so
Assertive
The distance desensitized to it now that like
The time that he is
Actually Fox
Yeah I probably will just make a guy got sure yard
We get to the actual bit of information here and this is about
The vaccine
Advisor short has a released information about
I bet it's true
Boy Alex isn't it about
Covid-19
Klepto
Governor Cuomo cannot said I don't care what he says it's not safe
Because I want the lockdown to continue
I'm not endorsing the vaccine
Real
Attenuated version of the virus. An mRNA vaccine
Control the fear
Data solution
This vaccine was created by Pfizer was not done because Trump wanted to undercut Bill Gates and all that s***
That's silly and Gates Foundation is given vaccine-related grants to Pfizer in Spanish
Whatever good working
Also when the news about the vaccine broke
Whine like a baby
Can claim that the vaccine was withheld so he wouldn't have a wind during his term
They waited until after the election to bring out this news
Yeah I'm kind of f******
Stupid cuz he
Still president
Until January
Nonsense
Pfizer released
Scathing statement about how they don't care about politics in their bark
Concerned with the global emergency
Don't think of the release of his vaccines made to him and make him look bad so I think maybe he and Alex have different talking
Pinpoints on this one
Further Alex has no idea what he's talking
The vaccine being announced by Pfizer is an mRNA vaccine
Who's playing against the alternative the Gaithers
Is evil mRNA vaccine is the exact
Same type of virus vaccine
He's literally no grass for the subject he's covering and you just makes
This s*** up as it goes along
It's embarrassing I'm just more interested in what does he want
What do you mean what you're off to see the
Trump created this vaccine in order to
Control fear and they
They don't want to give you the vaccine because they want the lockdown to continue now I don't want to give you the vaccine because I think vaccines are Eve
But they are doing this to me
What are you
Positively what would you prefer happen
No unvax
See you never
And then what
Crush doctors
Kill scientist
Okay well that actually does sound right
I forgot I should have started from the assumption that it's always
Chris Cuomo doesn't want people taking
This vaccine
I guess
Flip a coin
Beer to keep going
You get their mRNA vaccine
Big shot by a BB gun
Versus big shot by
12-gauge shotgun
I'm not saying take
Vaccine
I'm not saying
Check the regular
Pfizer
Attenuated
Coronavirus
See this is where it would help Alex
To know what he's talking about
He's saying the Governor Cuomo doesn't want people to take the Pfizer vaccine because what he really wants is for everyone
It is much more dangerous and deadly mRNA vaccine it'll come out later
Thanks Bill Gates
The normal attenuated vaccine is bad but
Equipment wants to hurt people more so you insist they wait until an mRNA one is ready
Great play
That's a fun story to tell dumb dumb
But it really does
Doesn't make sense when you realize at the Pfizer vaccine is an mRNA vaccine
If you know that then Alex
Cuz you're saying the Cuomo doesn't want you to take an mRNA vaccine because he wants you to wait until there's an mRNA vaccine ready
Nonsense
Alex needs to try harder
Because this is just embarrassing Lee sloppy
There's not even a conspiracy to unravel lyrics
An instance where he clearly is making up details about this Pfizer vaccine
Beauty knows nothing about it
And it would severely hurt his ability to support Trump
If you had to explain why Trump was trying to take credit for an mRNA vaccine something that he specifically and repeatedly is
Said he's going to kill everyone
This is the time for him to stand up and really be the leader
Right now yeah
Also let's remember that this vaccine that's being touted by Pfizer they're saying that has 90%
Set success rate
But that's not been validated by peer reviewed study scream from the rooftops
Does the answer to the prayer
Promising
And I do hope that things
Continue to look good
It's kind of a sticky situation and someone like Cuomo is in an unfortunate position to have to be
Now you know the person who
Have some picture
To say about this
Special vaccine
Yeah
Not even available and he's already being
Called out for like not wanting to give it to people yet
You know
This is really just the way that people flip a narrative when they know that they can't really argue the vax
Scene anymore
Their game of being staunchly opposed to any and all that scene is great when there isn't an actual vaccine Canada
Once there is they know that opposing the release and distribution of That vaccine is tantamount to them saying
That they are supported
Continuing deaths of thousands
From covid-19 it's really hard
How to defend that one in
And most of them particular
Lee the ones Work Media
To publicly argue that position
And it will hurt their bottom line
So you see what someone like Alex does
He lies about how this vaccine from Pfizer
Is one of the less Dangerous Ones
And pretend that there's a
Conspiracy against Trump
Among anyone
Who would say like 8 maybe it's premature to widely released as one
Still need some more tests.
It's all garbled
The point isn't the
Yeah yeah
You if you think that there's something about this
That's like the vaccine
Is actually relevant to the argument that
That's why you gay
Can pigs Act
That's the issue
It's just
A bunch of s***
Spinning around in the f****** toilet
Spirals down into our collect
Active sadness
Yeah that's a poetic word
We're done with a knife
So can you show is not good
It's it's
It is what it is
Is not nearly enough Caravan for me the only thing I'm
Interested in
We get into now the videos that Owen has released
Okay for the Caravan
I'm sorry on the 9th
Anna Anna Anna
Owen sits down
Any breaks down with the
The trip is going to look like
Here is the itinerary can't wait
This is a map
And on this map
I got to see
Little Road
Okay so
We are launching
Stop the
Caravan
And it is going to be launching
At 5 p.m.
And what we're going to do is
Going to drive right down here
And a huge
We're going to have our first stop tonight
8 p.m.
Then we got a long drive ahead of us
To go all the way here
Through Louisiana we make
Make It Stop maybe in
Theater something
Parsippany
All the way through here down to Florida and
Tallahassee
This is where we will be
Tuesday
First of all this is a severe schedule
Alex up there going to go slow you heard that isn't as brutal
Austin to Tallahassee and basically a day's time
If they're leaving Austin at 5 p.m. they should have no problem getting to Houston by
It's about a two-and-a-half-hour drive so I guess that shouldn't be an issue
The next leg of the trip is a
Concern
Owen seems to be a little loose on the details but according to his itinerary would say post
Online
They're set to be in Baton Rouge Louisiana by 11 a.m. on Tuesday
It's good they didn't choose New Orlean
Extra hours add-on
How to drive
Still this is
24-hour Drive
Assuming that they get to Houston on time then they ever rally
Are they going to stay the night in Houston
We could probably pull that off
2 hour rally
Then go to bed
Get up and get on the road by 7
Then they could make it to Baton Rouge by 11
Then they got to have a Louisiana rally and then get to Tallahassee by
BPM for another rally
That's an approximately 7 hour drive
Forgiveness of 2 hours in Baton Rouge for the rally and everything that they're doing
It could work out
That's f****** tight battle
It's almost like they're expecting everything to either be nothing
Or that everyone will plan things
For them
Ready
To go ahead of time when they get there
It's it's sloppy from a production
Anything goes wrong
Anything anything goes wrong
They're inside
Higher trip is behind
Hounded
What does it matter
No course they get to Tallahassee at 9
If the stakes are low but also the setup is terrible
The next day's a little bit better paste
On Wednesday but this is a very very poorly time brute has not suggest that they had a lot of time
Compliant
Here's what happens on Wednesday
Then on Wednesday
We're going to head north
Do here
Wake up in
Atlanta
Friends
That'll be
Wednesday
I'm in Thursday
We're going to head out to
North Carolina
Charlotte
Heading to
Virginia
This is a little better spaced-out
The first stop of the day there on Wednesday is 3 p.m. in Atlanta which is only 4 hours
Tallahassee
To be totally fine
The next stop of the rally is in
Columbia South Carolina at 8
Yeah that's another 3 hours on the road so as long as they limit their
Thursday in Atlanta 22 hours this should be possible
That seems like what they did they gave themselves
2 hours a day
Then on Thursday they do not go to Charlotte
In fact they don't go to Charlotte at all
The next step is Raleigh and then there's another three-and-a-half-hour upside that he's another three and a half hours in the car
At 3 p.m. so they should be able
Go to make that 15
After that it's on to Richmond Virginia for an 8 p.m. rally which again should be no problem
I'm in the next phase in DC so they can get there whenever they f****** want
Really this is a horribly designed trip
First day out
Must have been brutal
Yeah like I've been on the road
When I look at it that like
Wuuno yeah yeah
No I've been in 7 hours in like you're adding on time to get meals
Listen to go to the bathroom and unexpected
Did things just always happen
Yep
So it just seems like I would not want I want to go along with
But I wouldn't want to be the ones doing it out
I wouldn't want to be like
Responsible
No and it was clearly planned in a in about 45 minutes
I wouldn't be surprised if they didn't
Account for
Time zones and all of this
Oh I didn't
What I was planning at like how many hours apart they are about that
I think we might find out if they did too
So
Alex
His giving his his little like YouTube
Quite abruptly
Do not more coming there infowars.com I want Royale lead the attack
Very important people.
11 punch
We get to turn the other cheek right into their f******
Faceit
We get to 5 p.m. Owen Shroyer goes down to the
State capitol Court
He's got to pay
Patriots there
InStyle
All right ladies and gentlemen
Owen Shroyer here live
Owen Shroyer
Cameron I looking at
Alright
Owen Shroyer hear Lively
We are at the
We got a lot of
Peace out here that
Tonight
I want is a great group of Patriots they are sending him off in Austin
Can clearly hear the excitement
Rousing cheer in the background how many people are there for Owen send-off and I will give you a
Okay I do have it
An exact number
I think we are
I'm going to go with 13 peep
9 people in their hometown
If you send off a vent for their cross-country barnstorming
And you're being sent off by all the
Look drunk people in the bleary-eyed morning absolutely picture you can imagine it
Admire Owen
Attempt
To keep a stiff upper lip to pretend that this is a great turnout
He's doing great I'm pretty sure that's everyone who is there too because when the livestream starts there's actually only six people behind
Going
I'm at the Corral the other three to get into the shop to make it look like there's more people there
Old people out of a Denny's
Sadman but it's amazing it's my favorite genre of entertainment
This is like this I could watch
B forever
Do it try to stay Brave
Completely obvious sadness
Just it's just
It couldn't be more Blackadder
Like it is just
Cure
Your
Stupid it's amazing
So here's here's a little bit of Owen talking about where they're about to head off to
Hermann Park
Miller Hill
We want to try to be there by 8
We may be running a
But we should be there by 9
Name of the latest it's your first leg of the Yard-Man
And especially with that
Free simple language in Austin
I mean if you're worried if you're worried about that
That's a good Park in Houston
Who donated a bunch of land to the city
Abbott also fought for the king
Confederacy
Yeah you think
So are we get
201 talking about
Unit B this seems like a comedy show guy I like a promoter
Maybe a local show guy who booked
Tomorrow we're going to
Going through hopefully we'll have a stop
Open Baton Rouge
In Tallahassee
The Florida
Tomorrow night
Turn out there
Should be a big turnout in Tallahassee
I know there's people there
You should have been here an hour before you thousands
Last week was Pac-Man
Sorry I don't know what happened
Sewing doesn't really have much to say
People
The first fella
So we got a lot of people out here
You people why it's so important
Come here
Okay give me a Richard
Richard Reeves Infowars
Gold friend of Alex's this is not
Someone high-profile maybe an employee profile
They have a big media presence
What's 2
I'm surprised Joe isn't
Are you know Rogan should be right there exactly
Globalist
Well you know
Rogan's out there that would
Definitely giving them quite a spotlight
They do have a lot of media there though
Multiple news
Media
Out here course the local
Front door
As long as
You make it pork
As long as you realize
The final level
Well I don't I don't know if there's multiple media Outlets
Depends on what you can
Consider a media Outlet
14 people exist in space
There might be a blogger there
Richard Reid might have a website
You could say Infowars is there
Innocence the internet is National
The interviews are what they are. They're pretty boring
Going to leave
But youth interrupted
We got to get to Houston
We're going to take off
We still alive
What's up
What is it called when a radical
Feminist
Star God
Facial hair
After protests
President
Impeachment
Hahaha
Didn't even get good laughs there from that crowd
So this is a guy who got interviewed by Owen earlier who
A response from the gathered
Is it kills just kills my clan meetings was it was everybody loving this
So
What's good
Ruby driving
Lodging
You just stay the course with us
On Friday
Saturday's a big
Big Daddy
Trump
DC
To stop
This deal so
Are you guys ready
How to make history
Are we ready to make history and save this country
God bless the Patriots.
Cookout
Possible
Hit the road will see you at
Still Caravan
F****** William Wallace chick right there man
Wow
We declare
Our independence day
The Optics of this are very very depressing. Good
Stop
You would expect
Is going
Awesome
Zagg.com
Absolutely you might be surprised to find out on the way from Austin to Houston
Call into Infowars
I had to come on here and do this update
Because we're having a mass
Problem
With communication and this is because of the censorship
Pontificate on the Mass
Not allowed to promote our events
On mainstream news they'll never talk about our events on TV news
We're not allowed to exist on Twitter or Facebook or Instagram
That's all we have so
Had to call in and interrupt your broadcast night cuz
This is the only place I can
Remote viewing
Bestop distill Caravan
I hate to risk sounding uncaring about Owens problems
Describing a challenge that they had to be aware of well in advance
Spanning half the nation that you need to get people to a very tightly Time series
Events in various cities
Is a coordination in messaging your number one concern to do a direct mail campaign but we realize there is a
Misuse their to refuse to believe that I wouldn't got out on the road and only then it hit him but he's been banned
From Twitter's we can't read about their next stop and it turns out parlor isn't that great
Really on the road for like an hour and he's calling in complaining about not having it
Twitter account
This is absurd
I love it
Mom
I'm running away
Did you notice I don't have any money to get a bus ticket
So turns out that I mean like they did know that they weren't on the social media sites
Kind of over
Baton parlor being good
Surprised maybe it's not
I guess parlor
Is becoming so popular right now that it's just being overwhelmed
Andover inundated
With people on it and it's just failing miserably
I can't put out any updates on parlor
Quite frankly it's extremely frustrating cuz that's what we were going to use to promote this thing but it looks like we're just going to
The call-in here and give people updates
And of course were banned everywhere else
Soy
Promote and give updates via Gab
You're not on Tab why aren't you on cab why aren't you do you realize that
Cabins to toxic In-N-Out fun
Even you realize that but then I got hounded by all these hooking Nazis
Calling me like a
Because she'll for Israel
I don't like it when you get abused online also has anybody ever noticed that there's a lot
Reviews online somebody should do something
We might go back to get it resolved they still posted
Updates on parlor
An account with like fake information that they need an actual phone number of course
I'm not doing anything I don't know
It look like things were
Regret
The only thing he can do is plug
On Infowars
And then Wednesday Atlanta
Greenville
South Carolina and then Thursday Raleigh North Carolina and Richmond Virginia and enforce Friday and Saturday Indy
DC so this is the latest now again
I want to plug the rally in Greenville South Carolina that's not on any of their Caravan itinerary
This is weird Monday There's a map that says they have stops
Atlanta and Columbia South Carolina on Wednesday but then
On Tuesday
I posted a map that omits
The Columbia stop
It's very confusing
With or without parlor problems and Greenville isn't helping
It kind of makes sense for the tour to go to Colombia though because that's the state capital
And the rest of these stops
Except for Houston are all state capitals
It's obviously Colombia
You just keep sucking up he said Greenville
Charleston
Part of me thinks
But maybe that's
Just because all these rallies are really
Up in the air out of moment
The moment baser they could be
Oh it's on this map this time and then we got a phone call and it's like
We can only get four people to go to the VFW you still want to come and then I got don't think we can do that
Ronaldo
It's called in to complain about how he can't promote things to Deanna Lorraine
At this point I was really needing some contacts
Text some additional footage or information
Adjust the Infowars content and luckily
They're actually was
Was a self-styled journalist decided to come along
Document they're fresh
Eugenius not granted this person wasn't Infowars fan
Like it's still edited Down video
But it's something
And you end up with interviews like this
Don't drive and Ryan I'm here adrenaline faith in God and love 0
Fear and we're on a mission at the pub
Divine proportions
Shell art
Will never ever submit
Will never submit to the commons
In case you're curious why you just heard is the same guy who told the anti-feminist Joe Paterno and send off
Wild
From a channel called
Just another Channel and the guy who runs it is a dude who's called into Alex's show in the past
I forgot his name but he's a dude basically calling Infowars employee except they don't have to pay
Tractor videos from the tour that I was able to consult
For contacts
From his video of the Austin send-off I was able to
See Owens video from another angle and it's
Just as depressing from any angle as it was from straight on
I'm not fully convinced that some of the people in the video weren't they're explicitly with Owen
So same thing in organic turnout of 9 people might have been an exaggeration
This dude
Is
Following
Their Caravan
This guy from the just another Channel
And
This weird dude has joke
Hide his communist
He's also he might as well be alright
Isaiah
Oh my God
I guess just happened too fast
I feel like if they'd actually plan this would like a tour manager and stuff
Somebody would have been able to pitch to like
Boxer something like we're going to embed with this whole thing
If there had been enough lead time I might have
Risk blowing cover or whatever
Please give me you know that I'm good at yeah yeah yeah like I could write an amazing thing
About going
You know I'd be fair yeah
Tufan
I'm a Cohen look
Fine
So where in Houston
We've got now to streams
Of information the Infowars stream
And this other weird Dude shows going along with him
And here is
When is arrived in
Stephanie says the turnout
Is bigger than expect
Things are little bit more difficult to assess interns the turnout in Houston but that's just because it's nighttime
There's no doubt that it's more people than were in Austin
But it still looks pretty sad lullaby
Guess the number I would feel fairly comfortable in the 100 to 150 territory
That's more than I would have got that stretches my beliefs
You just another Channel video kind of
Cheats to make the turnout look a lot bigger by recording the walk from a parking lot to Owens location in fast motion
Making it appear the all the people
Play Pastor their 40s
It's shaking all over the place
I don't know if those people were there for Owen or not but
It's a public
Even if I give Owen the benefit of the doubt and go with the high estimate of the turnout
It's still an embarrassing failure for info
If they presented themselves as Scrappy upstarts
People showing up to a rally is great
That's not their brain
Alex insist
Millions upon Millions listen to him world leaders listen
Domestic and international election
Jill million-dollar high-tech Studio
He should not be drawing this poorly yeah
If you're a talented but relatively unknown, can you can draw a quarter of a house
That is nothing
Ashamed
If you're a headliner who's been in the business
For 26 years and you can't fill a room
You should stop looking
Gigs
Yeah that you're going to wind up with
The comedy Shrine in Aurora
With me
So it's got some good news to give this collection
The Patriots in Houston
Nice-looking armored vehicle
The armored truck right there's no way
Jomashop
I know when I have some good news to give an eager
Your crowd of speaking to through a megaphone I'm really quick
Distracted at the Trump impressions
And rambling about multiple
What car is in the Caravan
It's amazing how the instinct
IPad for time and
Panties things out for no reason
It's just the Style style guide
Reminded me so much
Do You Remember Have You Ever Seen The Kurt Russell
Full speech in Miracle
That is a
Exactly how motivating that was
That Owen just taught not very
No it's okay
Yeah
A working theory that if you work
Infowars for long enough you lose the
The ability to
Emmaus
Can truly in
Affect you with some
Something that you like
Can't get out you know like there's a serious virus that he can
Can break into you
We get to the good news
Stop
Transylvania online
Lost Pennsylvania
That's a great thing to say to get a crowd to cheer for you say that every time
You get a big cheer
It's not true but you get a big cheer you know the good news is teasing out is that Beau Biden had lost
The electoral votes
It's in Pennsylvania
This is not true nor was it true that
So this is sad
I was curious what the deal was here and where this news is coming from and thankfully I didn't have to look far
Because a source is provided in the video from just another chance
Here again
Was that weird dude who told that anti-feminist joke
Tom
What's the news that just broke what's going on with the state some real clear politics announce that they
They took the electoral votes away from Pennsylvania and then immediately takes him away from
Having you both that claimed him as the winner Joe Biden oplinger
Actually Trump is winning
And he is going to
So this is
The issue here is that there's a
Confusion inter
What these guys are presenting is it RealClearPolitics is reporting a Pennsylvania has taken away the electoral votes from Biden
That's putting the election back into play
What they're actually claiming whether it's
True or not is that real clear politics
Is withdrawing their projects
That Biden had won Pennsylvania's electoral votes
Which is a
There's a bit of a misunderstanding going on here that was exacerbated by social media
And of course Rudy Giuliani
Rudy tweeted out the RealClearPolitics
To take away their predict
Kitchen of Biden winning Pennsylvania on November 9th
Which is the news that all these people are responding
However in the real world RealClearPolitics that never called the winter in Pennsylvania to begin with
Their president Tom Bevin tweeted out on November this is false
We never called Pennsylvania and nothing has
The idea here is to pretend
That sucks there's some PD Outlet in this case RealClearPolitics
That is one of the things away from Biden and towards
Because this creates the illusion of momentum
Simple victories and no real hope.
Important
These assholes in the right-wing propaganda
Create their own fuel
And this is one of the ways they do that
You can see how even went on the road when doing something that's supposed to
To be fun
Help but spread false and misleading information
All these people are equipped to do that's a real bummer
I mean if you want to get a cheer that's a great way to do it
It's like if you're a stand-up
Yeah and you're like let's give it up for the truth
Through this point I started to get a little bit lost
10 Flights of Fancy
I felt like Tom had really given me an assist with that one
Thorson
Yet I had no idea
Who Tom was
I'm getting information from Tom
He was just a weirdo in this guy's videos clearly along for the Long Haul
Essentially he was doing exactly what I wish I was doing documenting this other nonsense except he believes all of it
He's actually Zack
I bet this is my deep throat revealed
Back from space
Tom was going to be doing
All these things that I wish I was doing
Like I should get a better sense of who this guy is
Figure it out figure it out
Luckily they just another Channel videos use his full name and I was easily able to find his YouTube channel
The Tom is basically an open-mic stand-up comic and his bits and what they are
Haven't been through it and got hundreds and hundreds of open mics and live through the process of trying to write and work on jokes
I really don't have an interest
Shooting on Comics who are on their path
I will say however that I don't
Especially
I'm not going to take up her time making fun of his dude stand-up but I can
Can't not mentioned
On October 20th
This year
He posted a video of himself doing stand-up is Shao Kahn from Mortal Kombat
That was like
2 weeks ago
He's on stage
I'm using the term very generous
Who costume
And here is one of the B
That's really not good
Mailed it
Spell landed
It's a lot of costume
Yeah he got the whole costume for one shall combo video
Pinterest that joke
I do care
Now you got the custody of all right buddy because I can
See myself in I can see myself
A bar
It like the hidden Shamrock or something
Drinking at the at the the bar and a couple of the comments
I don't know but my
And he comes up and shout, then we alternate look at him
I would like
And then turn back to Arch that's exactly
Doing that huh
Probably should have worked on the writing
Tended you have a shout-out
Now here's a really a joke
If you have a good joke you don't need to Costco you don't need a car if you don't have a great joke you do need a costume
And this still is iffy
Anyway that's the guy who's along for the Long Haul
At The Shrine
So I hear back to in Houston
And he tells
He tells them this
To give them
The real sense of meaning
And what they're doing
Can you look in the mirror
America right now
Nationwide
They would not have callback Pennsylvania and they already would have called Georgia and North Carolina Arizona and Nevada
So you heard Alex
Guys claim they like
Trump fighting is because he saw them at Austin and
When is
To give the audience
Same grandiose
100 people showing up at a park in Houston
Is the reason
That the globalists
Cook-Out electoral votes in Pennsylvania away from fighting
These men
Later in their life Shelf
Sleep wondering what will become of a shame that they were not here with us on this st. crispin's day
I want protect
Zen d.c.
Good luck
I know that there's about to be over
American Standard
When when
Hellboy
Surprisingly large percentage of Ellen speech
When is the crab breaking into usa-chan
Honestly I thought were kind of satirical than I was young
You know I felt like a high number of the people who doing USA chance were mocking like making fun of the people who
Stupidly yellow USA
Inexplicably like
I feel like they've reclaimed it
An inspiring speech Owen doesn't really have much gas left in the tank
Just trying to pry
Chance and talk about
Very not true news from Pennsylvania that's basically at
Here's a little taste of him from about minutes
Just seems like he's falling back on like
Platitudes whatever
Starbucks
Are we going to be free to let him know.
Steve Madden will deny the Cox
Pro 3 tides
So at this point
The rally and
And I start to realize first of all these turnouts
They were the first two
You're not good
No better
Cookie batter
Are you
Realize that I had really over thought things when I was talking with her itinerary
We can do this
Stop all right we're going to get out of here you got to keep on fighting the good fight
I was thinking it was actually like
You're not working to coordinate we're going to meet up with stealing
If it's nothing
Just show up
This just another Channel guy will go around a videotape
Some people
It's following them called the hippies4trump
Of course
White dudes with dreadlocks
I hastily slept together
And I'm just starting
Love it
And we wake up
And again
I will never know if David Nye cover this on his show
Episode of The Alex Jones program
Or he's bent out of shape
About our globalist named Klaus Schwab
Klaus Schwab
World
No more police no more meat no more travel
We'll be lucky if you're alive wait till
And you're going to do about it
Les Schwab is the head of the world economic Forum that erode book earlier this year called the Great reset
Some of the ideas in night were further explored in that online presentation that we discussed on the past episodes of Beyond need to get to deepen
That's what we talked about
Video that I did
With that dumb
This book is not Schwab saying that you can't have meat anymore or any of that b*******
It's a complex
Examination of interconnected forces that have been disrupted or altered by the Coronavirus
Ameritemps
Define possible solution
Some trends that might be expected to BC
I just don't care about Alex's inability to read anymore
He's someone who can't be trusted to get the
The point of a young adult
Sci-fi novel so it's
Really crucial
To understand that when it comes
To Something Like A Book Like This
He truly can't handle the material doesn't realize that
His teacher was not actually an alien
In the book
Caesar was an alien but I all teachers were
Goosebumps
When Schwab
Discusses how things are never going back to normal again he's saying that the state we were in early 2020 is not a state that we're working
To return to
We can't be
Because that's
Impossible
The idea that we have some kind of quote-unquote normal is
Isn't a real thing
You know it and when we end up wherever we end up
That will be the result of decision
We're making now
How we respond to the challenges
The pandemic
As well as various aspects
Of life that it affect
Honestly from what I've read about the book it seems like one of the largest points he has it about
I think about how things will be different in the future
Is it there's going to be a trend away from globalization
The thinking
Is that what
That makes the virus response
So difficult
Is it everything is interconnect
So it's very hard to slow things down in one area of life
Without affecting every other one in this
You would expect
Toledo
Towards a less connect
Did world
Because
It would
More
I don't know bility to have one thing Fall Apart
I think the one thing that
Conservatives have absolutely
Dominated as far as messaging goes is like
This idea that
Even acceptable to talk
Talk about
An older
Time as being normal or or status
Like at no point like
Oh let's go back to when America was great or or anything like that the 1950s regret
It wasn't
Find it was constantly in flux
Then and then
Change Dylan's going to
Keep changing
But that's just how it is
Yeah how can you even have a conversation where people are like
Let's live like we did back then
So you can take like this guy saying we're never going back to quote unquote
Mexican pretend that that means that
There's no police on me while traveling more
You really means is
Something that
The future is unpredictable
Pitbull and we have the ability to
Make better decisions now
Although this is terrible what's happening right now
Disruption
Are there are there occasions and opportunities for us
To do
Things
Better better
Dum Dums
Tired of saying I told you so listen
Listen to us before you do the dump
Again I stress Alex Jones is unable or unwilling to wrestle with complex ideas
So what he does instead
Is that he takes his fantasies and bizarre notion
How many presents them has researched
Studied facts
He's dumb
But being dumb isn't something to shame someone
He makes
Is living through the weaponization of his ignorant to something that is just repulsive
And I cannot forget
NSX brake really weirdly
Elizabeth might down for this cuz I want you to pay attention
Temperature I am
Dead certain that he met
To plug and I think you'll agree with me
Is it absolutely supposed to be a butthead.
Why do you got to stay on there now more than ever
I hope Trump
But we've got a build and be faithful
Impossible
It's so bad that even those are delusional
Euthanize
And they'll just finally go home and we grown army robots
I got a mop up plan
The biotech
And then
Real weapons
I will be so absolutely
Humans are very strong
Reply back
And I said
Most people nurse will be.
Hope you all enjoy it
How to kill you and your fam
Running around screaming nightwatch Dayton
God is going to hurt them so
Damn that
Paul Joseph Watson on the other side infowars.com
100%
A couple points during that
He had met to jump to an a******
Bramble about everyone
Going to die at least
Four times where I guarantee I was supposed to hear and that's why we need your help
That's why we need your support that was supposed to be
The further reinforces that is
As soon as he comes back from break
Taquitos applaud
I'm pretty sure that you would like
Buckeye blue
Alex talks to a Paul Joseph Watson
And I don't care
I only have the
This clip in because it demonstrates
This is Vanessa
And Alex
Still doesn't know that Pfizer vaccine is a mRNA vaccine
Waldo in Olivehurst
It's excuse to end the Great reset
But they're saying no don't take it now you got to take
100 times more dangerous next year so there
Completely transparent
Another difference either
Who cares
Why would they look it up
They look it up
Alex made it up on the spot he was just guessing there's a 50-50 chance maybe he was right or not right with it
Serena's next clip Alex discusses lying to a woman that he saw in public about mass at the receipts
Gaslight the s*** out of her
By the way people are in such fear
A few weeks ago that I know now
And I said
Has Bill Gates said he wants you to work
She started crying
And she said don't be mean to me
I just parked
People are so emotional about this
Man
You are an a******
It's because everyone is so emotional that's why everyone always says you're attacking me and then starts crying
It's because of them every time it has something to do with me in this like sort of mental
To be heroic story of Alex's game
Giant
People who suck
Rodger Stone shows up
I will say I'm pretty sure he's drunk
I think he's doing he has a giant cigar
Halfway through the interview he puts on a big pair of glasses
Sunglasses inside
Job he's not getting a new one from anybody who got it fired and Trump's going to lose
Rodger stone is a smartplug library
The stop this feel
He joins us from Florida Rodger thank you so much for taking time out to answer
So he has his plan for how this could
Could still work out using operation
Hasn't won yet
People who say that he has
Right
Similar to another group that's in denial about something
Deeper you dig you know that they do they like Holocaust
Despicable
He kept insisting no no there is no evidence of
He's going to be
So
People who are not buying your arguments about election fraud are similar to Holocaust deniers which are repulsed
Tell Alex about that a lot of people who deny the Holocaust
9 in a good way
I like this election
I don't know if there's any
Single
Source of entertainment that I viewed in my life
It had more Holocaust deniers on it then Infowars
If cheers
Not sure about the
The percentage
I would say if you exclude the History Channel
That's so dumb does like their languages
Is always the
The f****** both disgust
Make impossibly
Like I said it goes both ways to it's like Mitch
McConnell likes with reference Martin Luther King jr.
Speech about how
Is unveiling a bill to bring back slavery
That's how awful they really are
You're not wrong
So in the next Clipper Rodger kind of rewrites
The party swap
From the 6
I don't think he's making a whole lot of sun
The South and the Deep South have been a
Christian conservative values
They used to be Democratic in the old days until
Conservative Democrats saw the error of the left-wing
Now communist infiltration
And there are there
Blursed
And they had already moved around Reagan Richard Nixon
Southern military tradition here
It goes all the way but we have a Great Southern military tradition to goes all the way back
Beginning of the United
Military people here in the south
No idea why I'm bringing that up I know that out there
Just indicative of that very standard
Sort of belief
In the anti-communist wings of the right way
Sweeter
That is easy
These civil rights
Its movements were really
Communist
I mean
Rodger Stone one
The people who helped
Create
The southern strategy built entirely on whipping people up about race
Compare to be like they saw the error of their ways
F*** you Rodger
Narrow Victory to Victory any hints that has something to do
Do with electors or something
Patriots understand that the last
In this process is the
Legislature certifying
Who is the elect
Who will go to the Electoral College
Under Jus cause
I'll bet they are in fact
They are who are shooting for
If you understand
Yes sir not interrupting cuz I want you to get all out
Idem in yes
The electors are
What his his argument is I think
Is
We can use these legislators to force
Electors
Is that will vote for Trump even when they're supposed to be pledged B
Furiously disgusting
Did with this
You cannot spend a year telling me that this
This is life-or-death
And we're fighting the devil
And then be like
Well if we can use the vagaries of the f****** concert
Institution Dave
Trick our way into the presidency
No no you can't like then
You didn't read us his rights before he got elected president
12 hour booking
Cinderella solution to this f****** problem
Okay the devil
Rodger
I will say
There's reasons not to take him too seriously to definitely
Sidney Powell
Correctly
A very invasive
Droll
Essentially surveillance
Abuse
Which had
Corrupted
Has been able to manipulate
True a
Who is scorecard
Program that was specifically designed to work
To the back doors of the
Rogers on nasm Dennis Montgomery
I think the worst part of that is he's telling it like he
He half remembers what it's supposed to be about
F***** up yeah and then he's just filling in the blanks where he doesn't remember the yeah he doesn't know what it even is out of
Getzen Ethan vicious it's an invasion
He's promoting the stop the steal stuff
You're involved
I know you're involved
I don't know what's going on
Somehow I'm sure that
Totally
This is my favorite
Is there such good comedy
I could not have written
This myself
The universe had to create
Is 4 MI
This is Alex
Cuz last question
Temperature
I have one more question
What does Trump need to do
If you're drowning in debt you can't afford
I got one last question for you
Is Trump getting the light I'm sorry we're going to have to go
Every time magic metallics
Imagine that what he's saying is true
And that world leaders listen to his show
Alex is talking to Rodger Stone
Trump is watching
What's what's the last thing I need to know what is he have to
Call in to the show to get there
Analysis to be taking a nap
So it's not going to be able to do if that's why he always misses the part that he wants to hear and Alex's just done with the show
Oh man that's brutal
The Rogers gone
View
Jordan
I mean you're not in the city where you
You could
If you were in one of the cities along the Route Seattle near the karazhan on if you don't join
You're crazy
Tallahassee tonight about 8
Florida
Florida loves
Liberty
Gas up the car drive up the next few days with us
Stay in DC for this event
Baby don't you're crazy
Because this is all about visuals and it's all about going up there and it's all about standing
CC in d.c.
We are running
The emergency sale
It's all about visual sure
That's very clear we know
When is back on now
And a little interview from the road
Moving van
He describes
Kind of what's going on and I don't understand how
This is any different than a
Who what you're describing is a coup
So you had Donald Trump
President of the United States
You've now had essentially for all intensive
Purposes
Mike Pompeo the Secretary of
Penn State playing
He's one
And you have about 70 million Americans
I think millions of which could be in d.c. this weekend
Flaming Trump
Queer eye
So you have Trump
Declaring himself the winner of an election that the
13 sentences with
Ensure
You have a secretary of state
Lackey
Saying A1 right
And then you also have
Large groups of supporters who are very angry
Who are saying
None of that proves that he won
Exactly what you would have
Expect in the case of like
Someone who lost
Usher claiming that they want
Right
But
Spot
Hey
It might be
It might be in my nappy
Literally ate forgotten about that now literally a group of people getting in the car trying to grab more
Read more supporters in order
Where to
Essentially put Siege to the White House
Until until they take over the country
Yes with bull horns
Now Jordan
My favorite
Thing
I know that I said that last clip with Rodger where it cut. Cut off short favorite thing sure
Probably the finest moment episode it's possible
When is just complaining about voter fraud and what have you
And then this happen
They see them counting in Pennsylvania in
Well we lost Owen
What's this
Easy hamburger
Hamburger place
So good
What is this happens a lot
This happens a lot but this is I think the first time or maybe it's one of the few times that I was has been forced to like
Actually real
I'm sorry
A Cheesy hamburger
Cheeseburger
Basically like your hamburgers
Cheesy
Goes out
I got to own up to this cheeseburger
His defense
Honestly this is the best cheeseburger I've ever eaten so frankly I'll dude you guys
The favored by
Eating a cheeseburger
It's too good now
Shows up what needs to happen
Is declassify everything
I think he's on the verge of doing what Ivan
What is the class
Vermont
Hepatitis C before the election
Declassify destroy Brennan is a foreign agent
Destroyer Destroyer
And that's why they're now calling for a
So I guess the idea is that what they now W is for Trump to prove all there
Conspiracy
I'm sure he's going to do
Personally
Would love it
If you just be classified Alki
Of all the things that he could do as a spite move on his way out of office
That's the one I'm most in favor of
As long as it was
Like really very strong
Strategically targeted like alien ship or whatever
Just something that like
You're going down the hill Kennedy
The whole thing
Absolute let the chips fall where they may
Exactly
They're going to probably not coming out
Store Road says this and I feel like
I like it the motor responses
That's not cool
Secure
And we're starting out we're going to be
And we'll be there I'll be inside BC
Prepare to go in
History
Cool boy
Yeah that's not
No that's really f***** up
Yeah Stewart Road leader of The Oath Keepers have an army
Of armed man ready
Yeah I'm going to be honest it sounds sounds real blustery yeah a little bit ago and he's playing on this one
Most likely but
Such a scary Prospect yet I still feel the need to take him a little seriously
No cuss people the cosplayers with
Giant heavy swords
Even if they're
They're heavy
They can still hurt somebody makes me a compass
They don't have
Guns guns are worse
These guys do that
The thing I think is really funny about this interview is that Owen earlier said
Bowser mayor Bowser we have to keep him out of BC apparently that was in reference to like covid
Restrictions
Yeah you have to quarantine me
Stewart roses interviews
Narrative
So now we're done with
The show itself again not very good so is not satisfying and in many ways
The little things come up Alex eating a cheeseburger registering probably drunk doing an interview when he was eating
Geez ring got caught did he like make a face to the camera didn't bug you or would like a little unfortunately there isn't video
Video of a meeting the cheeseburgers
Disappoint
Just like
It's Owen's shot and then the camera goes out and then a big Sony logo
It's
The three-dimensional
Yeah we pick up
With Owen on the road
He's on his way to Baton Rouge
Stick in French
Rouge Louisiana
All right ladies and gentlemen Owen Shroyer here from infowars.com stop the steel Caravan in
Baton Rouge Louisiana
Car
Of the day
Before we get to
Tallahassee
Florida this evening
So I'm not sure where
Our people may be out here because there is no real parking
And they have kind of
Capitol grounds shut down
Drive around
See if we've got a caravan
Otherwise
Pick a parking lot
Oh and can't find his people
Which is a bad sign
Because we were very confident
That we had planned everything but we realized
Just now
Oh that's right we're very.
Part of meetups is where
Where is the first question usually that you want to take care of
Text 31 Brazil Google Maps
The folks
I would say that his response is
Tepid
Hello Baton Rouge
Infowars
Are the solid clock
I can tell there's a turnout of about twenty-five and Baton Rouge for Owens arrival at only one of them had hands with wings
The other ones were holding like Gadsden flags and s***
Owen's Beach in a Baton Rouge is incredibly boring so I checked
Just another channel that was useless to Cajun impression
I would say that this stop on the Convoy was even waste of time for both of us
And Owen
It was a zero
Is the Kong
Is labeled B and lost
Pennsylvania
I think we've got enough
This is probably not a good question
And ask
All the time
Dumb
Democrats
They celebrated
They find one
And now he
How dumb do you
Make a filbert how dumb
Do they feel they probably
So yeah so I'm not sure if they can
I like the feeling you said this was a
Sting operation that I should feel dumb just a couple days ago people reported this
Huh
Strange how I feel stupid about that to the people over there and
And one guy comes up and he says
We had a million people in
DC and a million people all across this country
Getting up on freeways
Putting the Bears over having 10,000
Every hour
We don't need a media
Social media weekend
Do-it-yourself
Is a multi-front battle of
You're not going to.
Can you pick a bridge
Did you get on it you do it you do whatever
Everyday
Got2b
Are you go
We are the media now
We are the media now we are the media now we've taking the bridges
They can they put
Like a little paper cups
Inside of the fence on Bridges took how to spell out a message to wait wait for them to learn about
Pamphlets
They're the media now they got bridge in all right
Alex
I can get this would write something something
Biden
Victory is brutal
But the turnout at these rallies is a brutality
As as good as that other dude is acting like he just had a Babality
That was a joke
This is a statement
Is Baton Rouge rally in
Play audience for a message
Stalex
Just say something
Send Alex Jones because
Because I'll tell you you know I work for Dallas
For a long time
And
Play tied into this
It's hard even under
So just give him a little word
Encouragement
PC
America
Tell Alex
So there's a hippies for Trump event along this whole tour
Your words are going on too long
Here's another this was a fun little Mexican Alex from the audience
Joe Rogan dead
John the Baptist
You're you're laughing over another guy thing you're the John the Baptist of this movement
Oh boy there's nothing funnier than you like Joe Rogan be like Joe Rogan
The harsh fact checker
And that's kind of the problem with like doing it halfway
Yeah it's because then you have the appearance of Alex
Coming out of that on
Scabies
Gave you through everything against the wall and Alex
States that is a really bad Optical thing
Give out
Now I hate to say that
Piss you off
This is probably a me because you're a lid
You know this is really probably going to be like
No but it's going to be like you're going to just
The hair on the back of your neck is going to stand up your punching my wall broken
I pledge allegiance
Recite the pledge
Another step to Anchor
Guys guys
It's funny when they don't actually know or meet any live
I'm sure so they get this weird like
Created version of the liver
Is being like terrified of the Pledge of Allegiance they respond to the pledge like of vampires do to garlic
Where is like
Repeat that you can't get this like that we're just like
But you man nobody's nobody's
Mad
At the Pledge of Allegiance stop
Probably unsurprisingly though that has ended
We pray right now.
Pray that you hear this
Raise up
Donald Trump
Continue
Be your king
We're standing in unity right now we come together in the name
Well then we pray that you
All demonic
Sebring for a trip to Romania
King
Good good
This is me God
I would choose someone who can stand better
So the turnout in Tallahassee that which is the next stop I'll go to her
It doesn't appear to be much better than the previous event
But again it's night time so be pretty difficult to gauge the exact number
Could be absolutely I would be shocked
If there were 200
Kind of the ceiling I would go to
Needtobreathe turn out for an indie band
But it's a terrible turnout for Infowars
Somebody individual close-up shots don't look too bad but the people are packed in
Pretty close
Also if you watch the video you're going to notice
Glaring and that is
Literally no one's wearing a mask
That's something that our friend Tom
What is actually pretty stoked about
Distance from here to come to Florida no mask mandate one of that
Feels like freedom is a totally change of energy
Amazing
That's right completely unrelated Florida state with the third highest number of covid-19 cases
Steph
It's like if Typhoid Mary was actually a political movement
If you're Owen you can probably feel a little bit better
About your arrival in Tallahassee
But not because it's amazing but because the other events were so bad
They're so damned
This is kind of like okay
You have you have some
Stuff you can work with your
Payless
Then it should be if all the other things about what you do you say about what you do are accurate
But fine
I'm not I'm not too mad it look like
Get people having a good time
In Tallahassee
So they go to
And we wake up
And
November 11th
Again I don't know if David night covered any of this
I'll never know how okay
Be at the Alex's show and I was expecting like
Some big news
From the road
Instead we get something altogether different
He's coming on
Get the f*** out of the show they were going to fire
And I have the CIA and others
Did you hear that
Steve is coming on 2 days ago it was an operation
Baby got something right 2 days ago
Are you people do you talk
This is
Outrageous send a text message
I'm out
Turns out you can f*** over Owen it's not that big of a deal anything on war room
Because Noah
Yeah I think it's a small audience
If there aren't really any steaks to it
Can choose to have Steve on or not
She has a tiny audience even better
You can sit all over because
Give the s*** anyway
Caught up talking about how black lives matter are Aunt Jemima
Vans
Well you're not
DC black lives matter
I'll look like Aunt Jemima they are folks they are literally
Marxist-leninist Satan worshipers who follow me
I'll say tongue
And said they hate men's very existence
The only good man is a castrated man
And their main Sacrament is no family
He doesn't doesn't break
The syrup was
Pro that we weren't aware of
I don't know okay I think this is all just
Weird weird weird races
Alex
I got to say in terms of
Satire
He's not good at it
Set pieces that he does
Not good no this is about as well done
As a joke
Is ever been on his show this is where he declares himself bread
He declares himself president
Like I think
I feel like this is all right
Really freaked out
Self-esteem
President-elect
Fraud but that's what
Scammers
Or trying to do because her past hoaxes
FL
I got some good news for you
The United States
Here we are ladies and gentlemen thank you
You got to do
He was the 44th president
Miss
History
Chinese Communist globalization
No all you got to do is
You are a
Allowed to announce the winner
But no one else is
The president
And so
The presidential seal on it and you are
The president
45th president stays Alexander Emery
Jones
Texas
Before you say anything as time
Went to Long
Over explain the joke totally as usual made me think it was good
Yeah yeah it was alright
Slips to being a joke
Music you with at the right time
That that was what tricked me into forgetting that it went to fucanglong
Gives you a little but
Subway
Search
Terrible
Okay we've announced it on the president and
You know that because I've simulated what a normal news Outlet would look like you know that you can do the
This because there's a
The blue background
And on top of the blue background there's a logo and I'm front of the logo there's a flag
Get in front of the flag
There's an eagle
I know the music guys like
This joke really working for you
This is SNL right
Yeah I would say that it's a rare
Day in Austin
When
Acuzat Infowars work
That might have blinded extra
Astro so Alex has some problems with
The voter fraud people not believing
Their story
USPS
Post-dating
Balance
After the election
Saying that they were
Before the election
Brother-in-law
Commercial
Working with the post office
I don't care about Alex's dumb brother-in-law however I do want to touch on this whistleblower from the USPS but Alex is referring to
This is the subject of project Veritas is latest polish APO guy named Richard Hopkins
Hopkins claim that he was instructed by his postmaster in Pennsylvania to backdate pallets
The came in after the election
His death has been used by many
And far more official Avenue
Claims they're solid evidence that illegal ballots
Come again
However
The Inspector General of the US
PS spoke to her
And Hopkins told them that quote
The allegations were not true any signed affidavit
Camping his claim
Started to GoFundMe and quickly raised over $130,000 for Hopkins
Even though he's clearly making s*** up to be used as a basis for right-wing dictatorship enabling propaganda
Of course Veritas
Can claim that he was coerced into recanting his story and he said that he
He didn't
This could just be another one of those
Things that's totally believe by the Dum Dum
But there's no real evidence
Only acting in ways
Exactly what you would do if you want to keep a grip going but also want to cover your ass
Prime leaf
Exposure
Sad stuff all around
Can you come on in here I
Just want to talk to you about the
Voter fraud in the alleged abuse that
Why didn't you say s*** is because you could be hit with a federal crime for like to I'd like to
We can't avoid
Flash forward to a little later
I didn't work and everything remember recanting anything--but give me my GoFundMe money no kid
I would not be surprised if that's a GoFundMe get
It's frozen
Anyway Steve Channel comes in
And he's there too
Complain about
John
Brennan
What do you want
It was one of the stupidest
He's ever done
Did he claim that the election was a thing
I would feel real stupid if I gave an interview where I said that
I didn't say that
Brandon was talking about how like
You got to get Trump out of there like
He's a caged lion
You don't know what he's going to do during
Lame duck.
So he was just sort of
Close to anything
That Alex says
That is
Encouraging the 25th Amendment review
No elaborate conspiracy
Trump into
Getting hit
With the 25th Amendment
Public television
Hey
Tops f****** dude earned
He's f***** up there
Hey guys I don't know if you've been alive for the past four years or if you have ever read any history but
You realize that wannabe dictator is don't leave on their own accord right now to leave the room at
Themes
Even assuming
Everything goes fine in January
Like there's a lot of damage
He's got it I'm not saying that I'm a hundred percent
Agree with that just
Based on like
How much more trouble that cost
And the fact that January is
Coming
I understand
Brandon
Perspectives like
I don't know
Anyway Steve somebody who Alex says has been in the CIA
Steve Wood back today
I was accused of being a shill for the CIA
Accused by who
Maybe an important party and David Knight
Alex's said many many times
It seems in the CIA
Stop.
If I were Alex and I were interviewing him I'd be like what you've told me that you were
A lot for years
Steve was on the war room with Owen on the fair
And he said that the whole election was a staying they water is balanced yes
And it's all like haha They played into our hands to claim and would later discover was
Was completely false dumb
Information
It would haunt
You for the rest of your career and you would never be able to get a job
Atlanta lone be some sort of presenter on the show
Again so soon
Is this technique called hand-waving
Trump is very much in control
This is what I said
Before this is Sun Tzu
He's watching the game
Manipulating
Tony we set it up
It is not relevant
It's not really important
Minor detail
Election was a setup operation minor detail
Whatever
Bucking
What a dick pretty amazing
That's unfair to Steve has a belief that Trump is going to win the electoral college
What sure
What I said years ago on your show
We did a sting operation on Hillary Clinton she didn't say
Exceed
We are allowing buying to
To be president
And it's over
What
It will be over
The electric
College will be
Planet Trump want Rumple come back
Looters
Well
Cheese's
We got a pretty solid prediction there we connect on that about a month
Sorry about that
I do like that I think they're very kind
I think that's like is that their version of a Make-a-Wish like
We're going to let it be president of 40 to 60 days and then obviously we're going to do a coup in
But he's going to have a really good night
He's making some specific predictions and also handle nonsense that he said
About the watermark
Text to Heidi ritza minority
I will say that this makes
I've never agreed with him more
Totally agree
Totally 100% agree there is no reason for anyone to believe you
Reasons for the opposite
I would say that didn't fit in the procon call them you got
0 Bros
So this interview end
Pretty uneventful
Which I was kind of disappointed by
And
I feel very
Confused
Betrayed
Flummoxed yeah
Animal with more words
If you like but I don't have
Mysore is Handy maybe that's a more fitting pun
Steve is to take away his
Dick's Wings
Well I mean this is a pretty small swing except for him
I'm saying that
If you know like
We are allowing by U2
Boring middle of Infowars
And I got kind of excited when this happen
See we really appreciate you thinking for all the time
Thank you and God bless
You know what I just
I called it a fall start
Call Cindy
Come back I got one more question
Important phone calls
Cuz everybody's talking about
Election fraud watermarks I know those existed Secret Service
30 years ago
Printer ink
I don't know all that stuff that's a real thing I'm going to get your take on that
Fred Hamilton County
He does not bottom of the ninth
Two outs
Is Steve pieczenik going to get one more chance to swing the bat dad
He does not know damn it I thought he had one big Swig left it doesn't even really ask the question
Turn directly at all
Just want to talk about how great it is the Trump's firing people even though he just lost shipping
Sure sure sure
All these people
And bring it all these war heroes right
Can I see the pucker Factor
Visibly scared
I got videos of them learning the Trump winning States
Custom iron
Panicking
Country
Watch for military doing
Military
I just melted
No
What year did bloodhound
I mean you're Sherlock Holmes in that way I don't need it
Facetiously holyshit
No this is
I will.
Guarantee
My career my future
Trump will be the next president of the United States
8 years
Not only four years it will be eight
Alright dude
Alright
He hit a line drive single guaranteed
On his career
Trample serpent
8 years
Correct
Cool
Alright
Well I'm not a fan of authoritarianism but I do have a guest on who saying that Trump is going to destroy term limits
I just want you guys to know and I've lost
This election
Or something
This brings us to the end of our episode and
Things up on Monday with what happened
The evening
I know
I got to know we'll find out what happened in
South Carolina
I guess North Carolina after that
Virginia need somebody
Like this is me
To be documented 24 hours because we've already seen so many stupid things that you know
Very interesting
Angry conversation I almost guarantee
I bet it was incredibly boring
Really there's no way that they were like oh we can't do this
We can't do this rally here and they got them they had a furious argument together though I'm sure own be like okay sir and then
I would bet if you wired their car
And like you had the actual footage
It would just be hours of them singing 99 bottles of beer on the wall
Alright who else has a shell called Joker and Paul's Twitter
Do
No one can get in this bus
Downtown
World
That guy was another bus he was along with the other end
But
Yeah cuz I do think there's a tiny bit of
If you look
Do you like Tallahassee
Turn out it was definitely better
Yeah
But I think they do better at night
Also so I think
Lesson from that building
I'm excited
See like if it keeps growing a little bit I will I hope it doesn't
That could be a half done too many tours where it's like
You have a
Couple first bad shows and then your third show you're like oh s*** there's 70 people there this good turnout
Everybody was great we parted afterwards
This whole thing is turning around and then your next show there's two people
In Finland
Send Dan Midland
They were from Finland how am I supposed to do skinny jokes to two people for
Define common
It wasn't good I don't know I'm interested to see I would like to I'd like to
I don't know what I would like to end without any violence
Particularly invest
Like if this story ends up in his being a
Complete dud Adam like
Embarrassing awful
That'll be pretty f***** up growing and growing to the point where they get to
There's a lot of people
Hey it's still just as a rally
That's fine story story short
They did
Couple people in Oz
Almost almost make me believe that Owens speeches did inspire people
Certainly not very much maybe other people social media post
But I I you know I could see that as a story and I'd be fine with that too
Keeper shooting some people is not the story that I want to see as long as we can avoid that
I think we can have a lot of fun
The Danza
Cara vanity project
Fairy Tail ending
Alright
We have every policy wonk and DC show up
And Surround their rally
All of them holding their phones
And when the rally is sad and everybody
Kind of slinks away they also
Simultaneously press the button on their phone
And 200 phone scream out
Wow
Just like that that's what I want at all play I'm Apollo
Do do
Yes I will see what happens I'm thrilled that we were able to do this because
This this could not wait
Is just too much material for one episode
Leave it all for
Maybe we wouldn't have gotten that weird appearance from here on there
Unfair that that's how you can operate in the real world
But
We will be back
Jordan
Indy we will until then we have website
We are inviting I go to Jordan
We are on Facebook
That was iTunes Ruby real and if you could please find a local charity
Or bail Fund in your area
Do I help out
Emilio Emilio
Dzx Clark
I'm Daryl rundus
I only do stand up and shout
Or Goro
Or maybe by Rock
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work