Air Jordan
Knowledge party.com
Pray I have a great respect for this knowledge B. I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Buzzfile.com
Acknowledge
Call Wendy
Jordan Jordan
What's up
My bright spot today Jordan symbol
Vinegar
Moving on
And if I
I believe it explain your voice box
I am
I've been looking for salad dressing replace
A little bit better and I accidentally stumbled upon some
Some interesting vinegars
Lincoln strawberry rose a vinegar
Chris and
Fantastic I had it on
Some chicken and now I've decided that I'm going to explore the wonderful world
Why not
I didn't realize there was
Such a
Diverse
World
Of weird vinegar products
I thought it was just
Yeah that makes
Vinegar is it like ketchup
It's not just like a thing
No but there are also a bunch of different ketchup
Right you know
Sure you know what I'm saying
Not really
Okay fair enough
I have a champagne vinegar in the
Olympics
And then what did I order I ordered some
Blonde one online
Is a chamomile tea
Vinegar never never not going to enjoy your you're
Willingness to put both feet in the pond
Before you have any idea how
Is Bulova
Yeah I enjoy it we'll see what happens
But vinegar week
Do the filters hirsutum house
My bright spot theater is unfortunately also food-related
It but it is also a
Gratitude towards our listeners related
500th episode the The Fog something
Nickelodeon
Informatics
And
It is
Spectacular
It is and it's also Lex tacular
Oh s***
Forgot what it take
He's like when it's made out of real things
GIF here like this is
Borderline all sugar and fake peanuts
Nicely done
Probably a hockey joke
No it's pronounced
Play whatever people say it's
Like a lot of grocery stores they have the things you can put the
Peanut sitting grinded up
Grocery store because I don't have a Peanut Farm not because I want to talk to my boy 2
I don't want to Moonlight as a Peanut Farm
I'm glad you're enjoying that peanut butter
So Jordan today
We are having
A very exciting time here
It is time for the thrilling conclusion conclusion
Today we're going to be talking about November 11th
The evening
Of Wednesday until
Whenever
This weekend's nonsense
So we'll see what happens
Owen Shroyer continues on his great big Convoy
Down along
Cowboy South up the Easter
Keyboard
Okay
Joe
John M thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Kara m
Send me your namma thank you so much here and I'll probably walk
Y'all related
Gutter deed
I'm a policy wonk
McDonald's
Chris D thank you so much
Chris Kresser
Think no no last name
Biggest apology walk
I'm a policy wonk
Party in 2016 never again
Like very much that stuff
Soak it in Laura from Cincinnati thank you so much you are now a technocrat
Bianca see her cousin what you earn our technocrat
And Eminem
Jordan Howard
Money off at heroin
Freakishly large
Thank you so much kitten Laura out in Cincy
You Evan
These gents do you can do that
Bonjour website knowledge
That we would love it
What you could do is you could
Superknife
Into a big old
Jar of generosity
Crunchy jizz creamy generosity
Spread it all over the bagel of a local
Call Charity or bail Fund in your air
On top of a really weird vinegar
So Jordan to out-of-context drops
Today Show
So we'll do one little bit
Because I'm a Christian
Cannot kill you
Just because you're stupid
They're enough
Feeling good
Galaxy
People were killed because they were stupid and
And it's a lot but I don't know if it's
Post-crisis
I don't know if it was specifically only be
Because they were stupid
George when we last left off on our our previous episode Shroyer in his merry band of
Impersonators and hippies4trump we're about to roll into Atlanta Georgia
That was Wednesday the 11th
I was just wrapped up his show where Steve pieczenik came in to claim that whether or not you believe the 20th
20 election was a massive sting operation
Planned in advance
It's a small detail what you believe that or not
What is important is the Trump is going to win and then apparently he's going to get a third term because these dudes love
America
One thing is crucially important to understand as we continue exploring this Caravan
And is that a certain point
It stopped being an Infowars Caravan
And it starts being Infowars With Envy larger space
I'm comfortable judging Owen and Infowars for their crowds
In places like Tallahassee in Baton Rouge
Because those are specifically Infowars Caravan events
At least appear to be
Once they reach Washington DC
They are now becoming part of something
Open larger
Which is the combined work of a network of loosely affiliated
Plan for the weekend has been for everyone to show up in d.c. informed be million Maga March
Iconography
Did spare
This effort combines the Infowars Caravan with a lie Alexander stop the steel campaign
As well as Brandon straka walkaway nonsense and whatever the f*** Mike cernovich is doing these days
Beyond that it's attracted the legions
Both Keepers proud boys
And members of many right-wing gangs who are less interested in talking
The spotlight
According to an article from Friday and USA Today the only group that had a permit for the event is a group called women
America first
Amy Kremer
Care for Women for America first
Not coordinating with any of the other groups planning simultaneous events
This is really interesting because according to a recent article in Mother Jones women for America first run one of the main websites for stop this
Steel www. Stolen election.
What US
Donations that people made on these
Bastille through that website
End up going to women for America first
Stand the sight was used to promote Rally's branded as. The steel
Great Apocalypse these people are coordinating
But that's not even
An argument it's really worth having I think
The point is that the end result of these rallies will be the combined efforts of a whole Cadre of weirdos
And it's so even if we get to the end of this
And there is
Big turnout in d.c.
We'll keep our eyes on the ball
And remember that had nothing to do with this stupid road trip
Not at all
None at all
It's because I've again
Evil Steve Bannon
Furious into the other
More or less
We've never lived in more historical times
This is one of the most historical
Jesus Christ
Okay
Let's see if we can name under his other historical figures who
Jesus
1776 with no big deal
Smallville call trailer
But it look
Exactly like
Hundreds of thousands of Mongols riding horseback with their
Amazing that s*** was nothing
Fair enough
11th November
Arrive
And Atlanta
Atlanta Georgia
Play right now
Building
Stop the steel Caravan
There was no reason for me to pull this clip nothing happens in it
I only decided to
To start with this
Because the opening of the video in Atlanta is so real
You have Owen Shroyer poking his little head out of the sunroof of the Infowars tank with a handheld mic
Talking about how they're heading to the Capitol while driving down an empty Street
There's no reason for them
Tuesday's presentation all it does is make me audio terrible
Even if I went as a windscreen on his Mikey still using a regular microphone to hang out of a moving vehicle
Just very bizarre is really easy to understand what he was saying.
This videos real bad
Not a pop out of their tablet
Stop the hill Caravan and right now it is very successful it looks like we may
There's one thing that's
Suspicious and its absence from the shot of Owen hang out the top of the tank
And that's any indication that there are any cars
Behind him
You would think that if the Caravan is that successful as I want his claiming they pan around to show the giant Convoy but no
Just Owen talking to no one
I'm driving down an empty Street
Great metaphor you know that I'm Mister Caravan fan Mister Carol saying if you will but I found it incredibly chal
Challenging to jump back into this stuff
Entirely because I
Who are the produce this Infowars video is
I want doesn't arrive at the Atlanta rally until eight minutes into the video and the entire time up to that point is just hit with
What is head out the sunroof repeatedly saying
Atlanta wherein you make sounds it sounds more like
That like
After the end of a week at Camp they always have the
The slideshow with of the there's always a clip of somebody being like
That's why we love camping when they're swelling music around it everybody's like
That's great but it was just him
Silent
The Emptiness you feel like this is a bad guy
If I went to that camp
I probably I probably be into a well-made version of memories from cats
Sure
I still wouldn't be into it if it was poorly made
And that's how I feel about this like even if I were into Infowars and I thought
I've got to do better than that minutes ago and saying nothing
Sucks
Toys R Us version of Mission Impossible I don't understand
Keep it for time or anyting
There's no reason for this to be in there it's so distracting
I think it's just hubris they just think any idea is the best idea at the time
Their attention span
Well I would argue that it's more likely that they think
There's something badass about him driving around out the sunroof
Kind of looks
Just like
I mean it looks
What's fun
The wind in your hair MythBusters one-time is great
Sure
I don't know it it was
Made this
On his way
Whether or not he's back or not leaving out the roof of this year
Your tank
He does
End up at a stoplight
There's a guy at the stoplight
Up and like
Immediately deflating
About a tank at a stoplight
It's pretty sad
Ifucking tank
Leading a convoy traffic laws
And a little bit of
Does Doolittle card work with a guy who's standing waiting to cross the street
I know that's our plan and that's why I rented landed here today how are you doing sir
Me too
Me to Atlanta
We are here
Stop The Shield Caravan has arrived
How far Auto Repair
They are out of gas
There is no enthusiasm left in this f****** thing at all
I'm trying really hard to stay excited about this and they're not doing it
They realized a couple of days and it was a terrible idea
We went to bed Andrews we drove 7 hours and they were 10 people there what are we doing
Starbucks
Oh man this is what you want to be on the
Rb21 be getting the conversations and bird's eye view just right there beautiful
He's funny and so he tries
What's to do
And this is this
I mean I guess this is exactly how comedians do it you know you polish things up at open mics before you tried on a real house
The open-mic is
Sticking his head out the top of a car while no one's list
I think the Democrats are actually still voting guide
Democrats still voting in Georgia or have they stopped yet
Duino
I think they're still voting
Is not a head yet
There's no one there wow he's just talking to nobody
Now hold on now I want s'more schalke
Well maybe your maybe your mood will change okay
What's you hear the crowd with it within the background
Try this on an actual Act
I think the Democrats are still voting guys
I think the Democrats are voting
Georgia
What does Joe Biden hasn't been put in the lead
But I don't think it's going to work
Good stuff but I don't think it's going to work
Alright that sounds too much shade at the turnout of the
Lancer rally
It's still south of 200 people but that's really good printer Wars event is taking place during the day
So far their daytime rallies have been very very sad at least looks like you might call a group
People
There were some strange signs in the crowd
Why was this a big
You with a where we go one we go all slogan
Another was quote Trump's coup d'etat is already underway with kind of applies the Trump is leading and overthrow the government
Really don't think they get how that
That sound that seems to either be
Counter-protester or the opposite of where the messaging is supposed to be I don't know what's going on
Overall I would give this a final rally
A solid
Decent turnout when we grade on a curve but full of suspect weirdos and nothing really enter
Nothing at all
It kind of feels like this was an event that might have been planned already and OMG
Just crashed it
Since there's definitely some people there who seem to be
Confused by his arrival
The video on Infowars is titled quote
Democrats and operatives to start violence at rally in Atlanta which
I don't see in the video itself
And even if there were violence in the video their claim that they were
Operative sent in by anyone
Completely manufactured
And not substantiated in anyway
I think the title is in reference to a young woman who drives by and yells the Trump isn't President anymore
The closest I could see the scary stuff
Yeah I just certain point another guy with a bullhorn threatens Owens dominance with a we don't want pedo zhuocheng at
Badal results
I would hate to see in fighting at the
I imagine their Democratic operatives if that's that's got to be somebody in the movie who's like
Their green is our first operation in the field you know they've been on the death
Few years
Somebody else got injured so now it's their chance to shine and they like we're sending you to a rally with 200 people
To cause problems
Oh no going to go send you to agent provocateur
Out-of-control terrorism or something
Next time
Alright
Video from just another Channel also doesn't really show any violence
There's a little bit of yelling between a few people at one point but it's unclear where the context is
And then there's a long segment where the video maker and his friend Tom
Who's that
Friend Tom to I complain about how someone is flipping them off from a nearby window
It's pretty sad
Wrong with these people
It's very
Adele just like making heart shapes with their hand
The Atlanta rally was at 3 p.m. and unlike past stops this one included
An actual March
I have no idea where they were going or why they were parading but
It seems like a new development
Compared to previous cities
From there
Because he had to arrive in Columbia South Carolina for an 8 p.m. rally
Infowars only posted a 1-minute video about South Carolina but she's weird
Because from they just another Channel footage it seems like that would be the most useful for them optically sure it was nighttime
That was pretty good
There were some college students yelling at the
Creating the sort of tension and victimhood they desire in their optic operatives
Go to college spend 40 to $60,000 and then they're undercover enough
In the video on Infowars we get a shot of the Caravan itself
It's really hard to tell how many of these cars are actually along with them
Or if it's just breath
Assuming that all these cars are part of the Convoy it's like maybe 4:50
15 cars
There's nothing to sneeze at if you're a ninja or something but it's really sad for Dave free when you're Infowars
Turnout was alright
In Columbia South Carolina
Easy to overestimate because it was nighttime
They ended up taking a big group picture in front of the Capitol building
And I think it's about 150 people properly
Sure that's nice
The in the evening of the 11th
Things took a turn for the ugly
As the Infowars Caravan came under attack
According to a video posted on parlor
We're throwing milkshakes
Convoy
And here is the report
I still think we're like 20 cars strong 31st
Five cars back behind the info
Ford's right wagon
Throw something at the nasty milkshake or something
Heard through something so I'm getting attacked because other people
Caravan driving well
And traveling back and forth across this country that I've never had a trucker throne
So that's definitely a new one
We're on our way to DC have to get a car wash
Several of our guys up here ahead of us
Driving this Caravan stuff is pretty crazy because
Slowing and speeding up and slowing and speeding up
Hope you're all dramas
People were pretty quick to
To point out that the reason for all the things this guy is
Describing is because they were basically
Logging the interstate
20 cars in a row in the passing Lane which is it that's dumb and selfish and where
Passing Lane they were on the left side of the road as a chicagoan
Sets me more than what they stand for
When you do a convoy like this there's no reason that the car is all need to actually travel down the highway on a line
But that's what they seemed insistent on doing what
Courseplus at night for no reason
This was the leg between Columbia South Carolina and Raleigh North Carolina which is about three and a half hours drive
Elmendorf
Carolina rally was
Is at 3 p.m. on Thursday
There's no reason tonight drive that one in a convoy 20 cars deep
That's just a****** Behavior
Luckily
Everyone survived
Car Wash you're a rugged individualist you have to
To find a f****** Hozier you don't get to use all of his Creature Comforts if you're trying to sell yourself as the
Revolutionary that you are I would like
To wash it another f****** flashlight
To shift
Your criticism
I don't care whether they use car washes or not
I would like to say
You don't get to complain about someone throwing the belt
Thoroughly agree with
Yeah
Now we jump in on the 12th
On Alex Jones
Ashoka might have had full coverage of the Caravan
And it'll be a mystery lost to time much like who built the pyramids was at the aliens
Iliad
Non-white
People can also build things turned out what is the equivalent of David Knight covered like ancient mystery
Yeah that's possible
If you wanted to hide
True information
Can you give it to David night and no one will ever know
Yeah and if you want to have a really fun interesting fake information give it to him and the s*** out of me
Does normally would happen
Here is Alec
Attempting to make some analogies
And I apologize in advance for the audio quality on the
Alex Wireless
California
Vote for Biden
Wednesday
What
Stop
I thought it was
35%
Donald Trump
Oh Peter so that coming up
Why would they treat California
It's like saying
You're a Cheney
Remarried
Your new wife pregnant
What
Yes please
Okay
Correct
We can defeat the bubble cuz there
Sports Authority
I do I do
So I listen to Alex a bunch so I can help you out here cuz that was a garbled mess
I got the point
Really well let's see if you did trying to make as the truck basically one almost
Every state but there was fraud all over the
There was even massive voter fraud in California which people he talks to
Can't understand
They don't understand why the globalist
Steal votes in California when California consistently votes Democrat
How does explanation is a California doesn't actually consistently vote Democrat in the appearance that they do
He's only there because the voting fraud that's already and always going on there
They were stealing quotes
Open California because they're only in power in California due to all the vote they always feel
This is not that complicated of a concept that he's trying to
Describe and yet Alex strugglers
To come up with two really bad analogy
The first is getting married and your new wife is pregnant but you have an 18 year old child
From a previous marriage
This analogy doesn't make sense
It's because each Prague
Nancy would be an unrelated event where is the imaginary voting fraud probably
Homie be able to be pulled off by the people in California because the people committed all the fraud or in power and covering it up
Now they're having kids because they've already always been having kids
We'll get to that previous frog facilitate
It's the current fraud
Linda California
Example
LG actually work would be to imagine a scenario where the new wife allows Alex to impregnate her because she's
So impressed that he has an 18 year old son
That would make sense something about his son needs to implicate
Current situation in the existing analogy that's not the case
With the California stuff the ideas that they're stealing the election because they always do so
It's possible that another way to make this analogy work is for Alex's response to this person
To be that his new wife is pregnant because he only gets romantically involved with women he's gotten pregnant
That would make
The second Melody Alex is trying is that he's slaughtering a cowlick keeping what's left of his previous calendar.
Is also doesn't make sense based on what he's trying to
This would be a good analogy if you were trying to argue the Democrats kept
Frozen votes
From the last election
To use on this one because they want
One by such a wide margin last time
So they have leftovers or something like that
I mean in terms of the keeping cows in the deep freezer
That's that's how that might work I would put the votes
In a plastic bag
Tornado game
M these analogies help clarify his point but Alex insist this is somehow third-dimensional thinking whatever the f*** that
Really the only thing that these two analogies have in common is a sense of time
That's whoever Alex is talking to seems unaware of
The previous marriage analogy involves a person who doesn't realize you could have had a child with someone else in the past
DeKalb butchering example involves a person who doesn't realize that the cow in the freezer will eventually be eating in the future
The only thing I come away from this convinced of is that Alex is really bad analogies and people to talk to you on a regular basis must have a
Guilty with really Elementary concept
Maybe even object permanence
Tested Alex on object permanence
We could play Peek-a-boo I wouldn't I would be interested to know exactly
Still
Assume it's more than peekaboo
Okay what is it like
Anybody who's involved with the Sandy Hook trial is listen
On the stand
Cast his object
Here's what you do
On the first day
Hold up a sign
And then see if he remembers that there was a
The side of the road
Sew-ins next clip
Alex
Discusses the cycle of History
Interesting theories about this
Pretty simple
Based on his assessment
What happens throughout history
Power
Whether it be
Brian Chapman
Capitalization
Just suddenly there's no one left
Everywhere
Everybody dead
Dollface
Populator
Is the cycle of History
Wow
I wish I wish there was some way that every archaeological dig throughout history found like some sort of recording
Or like a
Tablet or something and it's all just
The same Alex Jones ideas
Like every civilization has been ultimately destroyed
By somebody like Alex Jones
Somebody thinks that all history is a cycle of decadent leading to the priest
Everyone
Somebody in ancient Rome just running around screaming
There was a priest types of eating people
I would I would I would say that
Maybe in Cruller times they had less of an influence
Sherpani cuz they couldn't ever so they could never get to a point where they would have a radio show
That's fair you know people would just
Like hell
I think that's the ideal solution no I don't think so
I do
Guarantee that this this sort of
Mentality of probably exist
Throughout all cultures
Paranoia
Sort of imaginative creative paranoia
Yeah I mean
I I suppose you could
Probably make a very good argument that every civilization ultimately
Collapses
When the perceived Corruption of the government
Equals they actual corruption
Do you know what I'm saying I hear what you're saying I don't know how I could
Protest that
In the moment
Yep
Alright boo boo
Depriest
I understand what you're saying
It's an interesting thought but I don't know if I fully agree with
I don't know if it's
Accurate
What was well said it sounds really great sounds almost like an aphorism
Society collapses let me perceived corruption matches the actual cup
Nevermind I take back my comment because now it's
Pillow where they die
Probably economic
I worry about it being b******* because it sounds good so good
Speaking of things that are b*******
North Carolina
There's absolutely zero chance there been 400 cars in the Caravan at any point and I would be comfortable
Wasn't even a total of 400 cars throughout the entire thing
I would go so far as to bet that the combined turnout for the events that have happened up to this point on November 12th
Are barely more than 400 total people I would agree
This is
Same levels of hubris
Enough
People in the cars
I'm so it's not like there's four people to a car where if you guys could all afford your own individual cars
Derby 200 car
Offended that there probably are 10 cars
That is to be as shocking and scary
Probably Infowars employees
Another one is the guy from just another Channel
Another color is the hippies
For Trump
So like
They're not busy
No this is
We want to live the hippie lifestyle also support a couple a man
That is trying to actively kill it my Grandpa father The Grateful Dead around I'm following Owen Shroyer
That's
That's real bad
You know what you know where the best place to get drugs is
The parking lot
Who's my real dad mom
Well back in the 2020s
South Carolina
Here you are
70 year old people with Infowars Caravan tattoos where were you made
There were upwards of 50 people
If you can remember the Infowars Caravan that means you weren't there
Bastard
Anyway
Pidf
All right we got we can't we can't live in
Different versions of that exact same job.
I will say that there's one thing that I like
It's pretty consistent.
Exaggerate
A little bit here
I thought about doing this broadcast
Plus years you know
Broadcast
What's my last broadcast
I need to just let you know and explain something to you
I don't exaggerate any of this
This could be our last
We could be
RhymeZone
Set a new coffee
Good thing you don't exaggerate ever feel safe
I don't exaggerate things but if you spend one single moment and safety
Does this mean that this is the actual last
Broadcast that he's been
Teasing doing
Play after he's done if he is out already
Yeah yeah
I don't know what's going on
He's talking about this sort of like I could be his last where I guess it's obvious but like
I want I want him to
To do that
Good Mythical Last Broadcast already
How can you say I don't exaggerate things and then say This Could Be Our Last Broadcast knowing full well
That you've got it
Least several more months
In the
Do you know
Like you're bigger than assholes everybody isn't it of itself an exaggeration
This disorder
Stream this is really escalating here in this
Distraction
I guess maybe I was disappointed in the Caravan cuz he's talking about like you know a nuke is going to go off Trump to get his ass
Fascinated
Turn off the internet why not
Text with dresses
Head to the hills guys
It's over
Express
The Press has been on me that I
Howard Stern Lake Joseph
Last last 2 months
Maybe it's those f****** pills
Absolutely lashing out
God
Last Knights
I listen to Just the Way
Peopleready
It's all over
Cuz it's all just going to
Holyshit
The only thing that differentiates Alex from someone like Jim Jones is that Jim Jones
With specific
Yeah
Also not for nothing
Like
Responded to this
Being passionate doesn't result in grinding your teeth to the point they fall out of your head
However that's one of the most common symptoms of
Stimulant abuse
Between that pretty much everything about how Alex acts in the fact
The Joe Rogan tried to get Alex to talk about his problem with adderal on their last episode
How to make the picture come into Focus
Alex might as well be like a high-functioning cocaine
Yeah
This is
Take it all
Makes a bit more sense
When you imagine that I owe ya
He's on
Stimulants
That this is disappointingly simple answer
But
Probably the correct one
Explain
Is everything there still a whole bunch of ideas that are bad
And if it certainly doesn't let him off the hook
For his behavior
It does make it like
The weather things that don't make sense
Do make sense
When you consider like a
He's just
On drugs
Billions are going to die and you got to head to the Hills
Alex
Need you to know
Billions are going
Doesn't exaggerate
Just say that you will watch
Williams died
Bloodborne authorize their ears about
Cool are you going to watch
Absolutely
And we were coming into the Earth
Negative
All you can do
Holding back
Silverdale
But we've seen a model of the devil's attack
Revelation
He'll keep going
Going and going
It overcomes
Really difficult to go back to normal
After that we're living in the biblical end times
Stories are like oh really
Easy
Waiter
Walk-back
Where in Revelation
Doesn't include like.
Gyno
I got some good news for you
They closed the third seal
They closed the Third Wheel backup guys we've only got to deal with seals one and two let's get to work on
A lockdown to deal with all these goddamn place
We have a special on steel ceiling
In the
Get the f*** out of here yeah
Troubling
It's troubling because like
It feels like the only move after this
Is go away or become a doomsday like full-on
Religious preacher
I don't think it's all that stuff when Obama was elected to those the biblical end times
I kept that
That's true but I heard about the biblical end-times probably from Biblical end-times preacher
A bunch of times
Do something less
Extreme
You know like they can say we were wrong in the ER or whatever am I
Hey man I can be
Become a hot dog
These are the blood moon real last time we
We thought we knew was up at this time blood moon
You do that
But you can't be like
The world is going to end I know it's coming
And then be wrong and then be like
Who would you really need to do is focus on your Alderman race
Or or whatever or like it
2D sensationalized
From the point of of end times
5 minutes
Again like the idea of of like
Alright
We lost this one
Devil's going to win
But we got to focus on the midterms
In order to defeat the Devil again like right
And the other problem too is if you are in m x type
Enzymes always got to become
The end times cannot be here
That's what the money is in end times being
Coming down the road somewhere
It really screw things up when it's here I think Alex is going to
I don't know I see this is a bad
So Alex
Scripture talking about Galactic laws
Contract law for aliens
Sure
This is released
5th dimensional chess
All the timeline for the globalist always tell us what to do
All documents that are public
Wyoroads
What are some down
Give you notice cuz you have metaphysical spiritual rice
Common law
This is a comically childish and stupid view of morality and I would just like to take everyone who claims the Altis smart
He has good point
What they think of that
Because that moral system and Alex's presenting
He's really hard to
To defend if you want to look at
Human history
It's simple enough to say that everyone
Deprive people of their alienable rights went to hell after they died
Yeah that's kind of a problem Alex would have to either save it slavery doesn't
Violate inalienable rights for a bunch of his Heroes and ancestors are in hell
But leaving that aside looking at the actions that are ascribed to the devil in traditional Christian
I don't see where he's warning people what he's going to do before he does it
In the Garden of Eden
It's God who tells them not to eat from the Tree of knowledge
If God hadn't done that then the serpent would presumably have done the exact same thing it did in the story and convince Adam and Eve to eat the
Fruit
The serpent didn't do anything except a manipulative evil Act
The part where there was a warning came from someone else
Entirely
Do in order for this make any sense and how it's his moral conception
The morality or immorality of your actions can be determined by other
People's actions
This would imply that it would be very wrong
For me to punch you randomly
And without Warren
However
If someone were to tell you Dan is going to punch you when you go to his house
Then my Poncho be completely fine
Because someone else let you know that it was coming and you chose to come here anyway
In fact
In this conception
It could be argued that me punching you is never immoral in and of itself
If my punch is morally correct when someone else warns you
And Morley
Incorrect when they do not
The actual distinction is the warning itself
That's where the moral weight loss
So it becomes a matter of the other person doing something
The emerald by not warning you my punch doesn't matter at all
So then
What if no one else knows that I'm going to punch
Then apparently I have to tell you ahead of time that I plan to punch you had that if you come over anyway
You consented to being punched
This is stupid for a number of reasons
To what extent do I need to make
Make sure that you're aware that I'm going to punch
Don't you have to serve people before you
Is it enough that I bumble it to you as you leave knowing they go probably not
Hear me or fur
Forget by the time we end up getting together to record again
How to make put it in a movie
Is it enough for me to write I'm going to punch
Jordan the next time he comes over on a piece of paper that I taped to a Lamppost 2 miles north of my house
Knowing that you'll never pass that Lamppost
I thought Arthur got that bike
Satisfy the metaphysical condition even though there's literally no way it could ever a
Pack your behavior
Ask the Vogons
You could say that the warning was that there if you wanted to look
Look for it and it's really your fault that you didn't find that lamp post
Stood right there on the old
Open for everyone to see
That does
The person that thing is being done to need to be aware of the thing that's going
Going to be done to them
This is a question that Alex cannot answer because no matter what
The answer is
It doesn't make sense
If the standard is informed consent
You need to be doing
Way more warning than they're doing right now
And honestly would probably need to get literally everyone to sign off on their plan
Knowing the implications of what they were agreeing to
So it obviously can't be
That
If the standard is that person needs to believe the Warren
Is that possible sure you need to believe it
Because even if that's the standard I still don't think you deserve to be punched for coming over whether or not you believe the warning
You might not believe it someone could say damn going to punch you to come over and I can have f*** you
Sure but you understand that this line of thinking makes perfect sense because of the way that the all of these people
The deal with hell
Like okay
If everybody that doesn't accept Jesus Christ into their heart is going to hell
Jesus didn't get his message out for a good long while
To the rest of the world
So all of those people despite never having heard of Jesus Christ spend eternity in hell
Just because God was like
Geographical product placement
You know like that's
So your argument that has to be well there's evidence
God all around you so you should have known that God was real and Ava
Christ if there's a God
Stood Still your phone
And that's why he'll is justifiable
Two people who've never heard of Christianity
B b
I I think
You're trying to bring
Too much sense
Stewart and I'm trying to Deacon
Struck this from an ethical perspective
Wealthy here's what I think that Alex would say the standard is
He would say that the standard that you need to achieve is that you need to publicly admit this somewhere
So even if you do it in code that's only decipherable to a genius like Alex Jones
That's still good enough
I struggled
See how this qualifies as warning people in an ethically meaningful way for the same reason that by message tape to Lamppost doesn't seem like
You could reasonably be seen
Possibly impact
Acting your behavior
I mean you know
And we're dealing with Satan
Name God there's obviously a lot of wiggle room in the rules those two guys aren't human behavior
What we're f***** in order to make this morality work it must not be the wood
Be victims of
The crime that are required to be warned about what they're going
Into this person's going
He must be a thing where the act of writing it down and put it out there is to serve as a notice
The god of their intentions but what kind of sense does that make
Also what are the
Consequences for breaking these supposed
Galactic laws
And why should the devil be concerned with any
He's already the
The f****** devil
Disintegration
Punishment he fears most
Okay so you do
The devil anymore but otherwise who's
Probably wouldn't come
See you again
Here's where I'm really struggling with Alex and all this b******* you understand that for your
Actual religion
Do not be both
B******* you have to have the entire time
You can't
Stop them
You can't delay them
It's God's moment
He chooses
There's no way that bite
Is going to affect
God's plan
Otherwise your entire religion is nonsense
Yeah and you can't
Vote on the devil
Assuming Joe would have had a different voice
This'll be moral system of a child and honestly it's embarrassing to hear and try to explain
His beliefs
How small his vision of the Divine is
Same kind of bummer I get whenever I hear people on Project Camelot talking about like a lien contract
Psycho
Yeah are you
Who sang to me
Even if we
Beyond the stars we're never going to get
Point where at
Materias going to
Hold the entire universe
Together
It's still just going to be a signature
And God is trying
To get the devil on technicalities or something
All right we have them on a RICO case
Yeah
At this point Alex does something
Incredibly familiar
Ladies and gentlemen we are back live broadcasting worldwide again we are Night live broadcasting worldwide Miami
Alex Jones
To be here with you today
Cuz I got to reset
I got some really important news released over here and hit reset
And so the
What what
He's an important announcement
I was thinking about
Is going on
Yeah Alex isn't DC now you lost the bet
So he's freaking out trying to do this show remotely sounds like s*** like that a lot of audio
Crackly nurses terrible and honestly even beyond that his heart is not in it
Sweet freaks out a little bit and he goes to rebroadcast it
Honestly wasn't surprising
To me at all but it never honestly seems like a
Prootest
Decision
The only real question to me is why is he hosts
Nothing at all
Then it dawned on me there's probably no one else
Who can host
Shroyer's on the Caravan
David Knight is
Definitely not a prime-time candidate I think David Knight he has his own show right and he had a heart attack like a
You're a go
This workload
I think it's great that he's not taking on unnecessary probably not be the person who
He's not going to move product
And Millie Weaver is gone forever Diablo
Terrible 22 Green happily for The Man Show
Same problem with Harrison
Smith Galaxy can fill in on the war room cuz no one's watching
Actual Owen show
Seems like it's probably
Probably no good Mike Adams is gone like you can't talk to Mike Adams the 4th hour fill-in host
Sorry Heather
Like
They wouldn't do it or
Are we going to have
Three-and-a-half 4 hours of Gerald Celente
Are those the funeral Bells
Because I can hear Rodger Stones name cover
Coming right down 3 hours of rambling
I do not
I listen to it
I do not want him
There may literally be no one left it enforces able to fill in for Alex
It's interesting in a way
He's kind of reached
The Pinnacle of success
But at the same time he's right where he started
He's got a giant business with a ton of employees but he still needs to do everything himself cuz everyone sucks
He's the president's biggest cheerleader but
Are you still ignored in cast
Decide in favor of more seemingly acceptable right
When commentators
Same as it ever was
I feel like you should realize that
Patxi's on lead to Nowhere it never has
It started with him being alone is going to end with him being alone
And I good luck to you buddy
Except
There's some good
Was that
Affair and comes back and then
Sports talk about having cancer
I was like wait to actually have cancer
Just the only way I can talk to
It's hard where I'm at
Snooze
Devastator
It's not just that I've learned that I have
Cancer
My God
Alright you didn't even need that
No just say I don't have cancer
They're not weirded me out cuz I kind of felt like
Oh that makes sense answer
Spaghetti I would believe it if I have terminal cancer
S*** well no wonder you went the world
Yeah I got your nose
This is amazing.
Well
No unfortunately that is not how I would put it
He just thinks that I was going to die
You should know he's not happy to report
Joshua
I'm sitting here last night and this morning
Thinking about what I'm going to say today on here because of all the announcements and all the statements have been made
I don't feel good coming on air
Telling you
Dad
I want explain
Sound like
Yeah
Ceremony
Alright I don't want to
Man I know I just
Now that we kind of get more of the gist of what he told his kids at The Breakfast Table
You're going to watch
Millions died
Is like not a good morning
Kids got to head to the Hills
Hey we can do remote learning
As far remote As we need to be looked I got some John Birch Society books that's all the Buckle I need
Siri I mean we're all going to die
Reporting that if Trump had won the election which is weird
The election stolen
Stole this wigger
In Dallas in front of everybody
House with a safe
Bring your house with it
Computers
Bring your house with a silverware
Family heirloom
Damn right you do
So they are
Person have a coup against Trump all over the news
He's insane he's crazy
He's not going to let them have this
Infowarsstore.com
Brandon Caravan up here is a shockingly pointless
Spent a lot on gas for no reason
Owen the bomber
I I do I do appreciate the the if
You know if
You catch the robber in your house
That's that's good
If
You catch
You know you have a right to
To defend yourself
Etcetera
But if instead of doing that you're you lose something and then you drive to DC and murder
For someone who has you've never met before and who's never been to
No similar tablet
Cuz of metaphysical laws were
Also from that clip at the audio is not gotten better hell
Answer Alex
It's really mad again
I'm on the road I'm here in Washington d.c. not a lot of technical
Salty's Redondo
Stay on here is best
As I can
Muddy signal I'm getting blessed in my ear
Broadcast
But it's okay
I'm trying about scanner
By the whole country is going to hell in a handbasket
Jumpman
My feelings of course the entire country is falling apart naturally isn't my
City set up Jodi cattive of the state of the world
Alex Jones Infowars would have issues with my phone can
I constantly have these techies shoes to plague me in studio and out
And everytime I try and take a phone call from somebody and broadcast from DC and I'm having problems
Somehow I'm
Surprised
Shock in the world
Is clearly going to hell totally interesting
Did this happen
Twice
I don't recall the last time he's done this twice
Probably end up vamping
Until the commercial breaks it doesn't actually have to storm out
Second time
But
Leaving early
Of course
Yeah yeah definitely
Totally
Lorraine
Williams Junior
Horseshoe
Country Boys work is never done
The Lord has certainly made a lot of beautiful woman
Wow
Hanover
Snooze
That was just on
Remember
So this is a great add for brain Force
You have these sort of nootropics these supplements that give you
Focus and Clarity and the ability to really stay on task
Yaya bility to disintegrate in gotland also real eye-opener
Mental fog versus Clarity you're talking about the ability to do a radio show and a hotel room
There are other people present
God.
Anyway
Takes over for like the last half-hour
He's terrible but I'm a little tired
Give him 5 minutes up top he won't hurt the show
Yeah it's alright I want you to get some
Best spotahome product
You have to keep the audience happy Alex
Most of it although he's not going to do much
That night
Or that day in
Caravan
Activity
It was really stormy
That day
Proin
So why you talked to an underwhelming group of people in the rain
I'm in in North Carolina but how the election was stolen
And honestly by this point the charm of the Caribbean
Caravan it worn off for me
It's redundant
It's unimpressive and ultimately
Too obvious with
This is all about creating the Optics
Taking your dumb show on the road
Arriving at a much larger event
And then giving yourself credit for the turnout at the largest
It's honestly
Pretty disappointing
There's such great
Potential for this road trip in the end it's really forgettable
I tried to find an angle of something interesting
We talked about the open my comic did the shellcon impression
I tried to see if there was a human-interest angle in here somewhere but there just isn't
They have the opportunity to do something really interesting and compelling
Instead they did exactly what Infowars always does
They produced a cookie-cutter performance that was meant to create profit
And gather attention
Well funneling support to larger fashion
Movements
I'm really disappointed in them but I also know there's
It's not really anything else they can do
The only thing that's even close to interesting in this stretch
Is they did a damaged
Control video in Raleigh where gris-gris
And some other employees
Discuss how someone gave them a book with a Nazi bookmark in it
Their angle naturally is that this was an agent provocateur like that who is that
Trump look bad natural although I would argue it's equally possible it was just
Justify a bookmark in our yoga book
After the rally stop ended on to Richmond Virginia and honestly it's a fine turnout but it's more of the same
My highlight is that a guy playing the trumpet there while the crowd sings the national anthem
And a shot of the trumpet player happens to include a historical marker in the background
This was actually shot on the site of the 1863 rich
Red Riot
Cool kind of fit
The Union forces at her
Supply lines for the
Confederacy
The prices of food at increased in Richmond
Considerably
From history.com
On April 1st the group of poor working women held a meeting in a Baptist Church to organize a demonstration against the rising
Acosta food
Mary Jackson a 34 year-old mother and Martha Ferguson riled up the audience
The tales of Rapids
Speculation
And price gouging happening in the market
Soon the mob was angry enough to agree to meet
The very next day outside the Capitol building
An extract bread and just
Stats from the men in charge
The governor initially refused to meet with them but then then when he
Daddy was Unser
Sympathetic to the mob went on a tear and started writing
They stole food but also luxury goods until the riot police arrived and we're prepared to fire
The reason that I think this is
Spitting it is
Ridiculous display was on the same side of the bread riot
Is because the aftermath of that Riot was it
The Confederacy tried really hard
To keep it quiet
Since I knew that word of this
Internal chaos would raise the morale of the Union Army
These videos are really things that I want in Infowars
Try to keep quiet
They're out there yelling about how does the end of the country and
This Caravan the last battle in these of the crowds they can draw
I don't know that raises my morale but I think it should hurt tears
They looked at it honestly this is not this is not impressive
I wouldn't
If I was doing that in any capacity
Like even
Play tours
Where I made
Negative
Exclusively. Math
I think I broke even once maybe maybe maybe for me
But yeah if I was doing
Vicinity
Like this would be bad for me on an amateur tour
Like that
The level of
The bad this is
Yeah
You might be able to get like a little bit of b-roll from there she asked for a larger thing yet
Camp video the wrap-up has Maybe.
Susan good
It it seem it seems to me like
This is them throwing
Everything they've got
The most
Extreme language the most immediacy possible
And it's still
Ratably underwhelming
And I I would be embarrassed to that if I work until Warriors
And if I were Ellen
I would treat this like the
The Confederacy treated the bread riot
And I would not to have
You're standing right in front of the memorial of that
So we jumped
To the 13th
Friday and Alex's back Hosta
Singing Shower
Prophesied
I've been really funny if he
But we can't I can't do it from here and nobody is home
I dropped called yesterday but I was napping
Call him back
Drove by the hotel in Vienna
Classic Hotel staff
Yeah it would be fun if you left
But instead he stayed and then just
Did nothing
Except for y'all to a bullhorn
But you're here he is talking about what has happened
On the the Caravan
You know that this wasn't
True if you were keeping up with the cameras at
On the way here
Posing as
Patriots
Premise literature
Tomorrow
Video red-handed
Station Subs
Thrift stores
Tears are not
Tomorrow
Boring
Berrington
Haha
I was just making all that up shirt
The only thing that's real is that book
Did someone gave that with a Nazi book Market
And they have a bowl and antifa follow them broke
Florida up through the the whole Convoy
All the way up and there's plans
Paradisi
They're going to show up
With backwards
Maga hat
A camouflage pants sure they're going to hand out dirty literature
Do you ever want to make a Patriots look bad
So dumb
I can think of a few things
Is that
Would do more for the cause
Then antifa
Joining that Infowars Caravan as agent prop
Because yours I did I just don't think there's anything else that could be done for the movement
Don't have that much effect
Stop
I don't think I've heard anybody but
Me talk about this
I really care about it just for that one.
A+ daddy like Angry tweets about it or even I think I saw a couple
People posting about the milkshake
From the trucker is a little bit of jokes about that
I don't think anybody gives a s*** except for them and me
I don't think anybody
It's really it's really
Annoying
That you spend all of your time whipping up whites
Two promises to fight
For you
And then you like
I don't know where all these white supremacist come from
Must Be Love
Man you don't so much time loving me
Too little it's a little much
It's not going to end it's not going to alienate 48% of the country
It's not going to alienate the people who are still listening to you at this point
If you can ramble about the literal devil all the f****** time and say all this nonsense b******* and people don't leave
Just mask off man
So even if he does do that these listeners
Nazi or otherwise need to recognize that their lives are over
And so because their lives are over
Time to go yell at the governor
Your life is over
We need people everyday surrounding
Pizza restaurant
Threatening you go up in the spacer
We know you're being black
We know the lockdowns permanent Bo lyrics
Smash got to Alex complaining about people yelling at Trump officials a restaurant
Also there are 20 states in the United States where Governor can be recalled in Texas is not one of them
In order for Alex to do his plan about recalling Governor Abbott he would first need to find to just
Application for a new law in context
The Constitution
And then get a law passed by the state legislature
To be a cumbersome process
He's not up for it honestly will probably just be easier to wait until he's up for re-election
And then filled a fringe as candidate to lose to him and probably split the vote to a Democrat ends up winning
Also Governor Abbott's not being blackmailed you still living
Credibly far-right politician
I'm just not far right enough for Alex
He's failed Alex's purity test
It's not illegal to write a law that just says
Is Governor Abbott
Can never be governor
Wright Abbott out
Abbotsford
I might be a ninja
Challenge
Someone filed a lawsuit
I'm not a lawyer
Little bit long but I kept it in because it begins with Alex
Talkin about
How he's not into offensive violence
Sure and then it
Wider ramble about a bunch of nonsense
But I think I needed to play it
It's two-and-a-half minutes long but the recent want to play this whole chunk is like if you listen to this
It's sort of an ABA kind of
Structure you have the a theme of offensive violence sure he's kind of just
Random talking points spaghetti up against the wall
And then you return to what the thesis
Of the initial thought was
But by that point
Your brain will ask if you're not paying attention you'll kind of already you've forgotten that that's what he was talking about
And if this happens quite a bit but I rarely play full clip
Just because it's
Plumbing floor
I don't want the offensive line with but I see a lot of talk online dual saying time to dust off the market
Is eclipse
Under common law under comments
You cannot talk
Experimental dangerous facts
Will they be safe or not they're not there
People have
Long history
Assistant
Billions of dollars he got four big foundation
Robber barons
The most anxious teksystems
He's a friend of R22
Thrown out of 20 gauge
When you got something
Through plate glass window
Says he's wants to do this
Coming
Bollywood Geneva Convention
International law
Give you a deadly shot or take your kids away
You don't just have a right you have a duty to fight him
You're a in this round
California and in New York
Holmes beating people up
Take away the UN said that was a goal
Australian Spain
They're just normal
Come
You disappear
They say you have covid
And now you're going to see people taking the tablets are this already having Australia
They go all he got sick we had to intubate
Kind of Chinese food
Lungs
In the blue study area for the doctor
Copilot
White girl
Dyersburg
Bigger Psycho Killer
Run Road
What's the pressure you're supposed to
There's like
Because I got to get kill numbers
Coming to kill
They're coming to kill you
Kind of you kind of get
What I'm saying
He starts with the Press
Temptation of like there's a lot of people were saying clean off your rifles
Amen
He gives the appearance of saying that no you shouldn't
That is good for him because he can sort of point to that
Yeah that's being like
This is me pushing back against the idea of offensive violin now the next 2 minutes as him saying
F****** different things
Right you can't keep track of all these
Various little
Bulshit
Leftist doctors
Killers
Colts creep bioethics boards
Increase
Goddamn Temple
And then it gets to the end
And the messages he's trying to drive home if they're coming
To kill you they're coming
The kill you they're coming to kill you
This
Is the answer to the
Beginning of
This is him saying
There is no such
Being as offensive it's not a question of that
Existentially this isn't even a question we need to worry about yet all violence is defensive
But he doesn't need to actually say that if he structures be argument this way
Anybody tries to say like Alex you're advocating for people to dust off their rifles and
Fire at people if they feel like they're
New vaccine evolution is coming for that
Anything you do to that person is anybody
He tries to say that Alex this is what you're saying
2.2 like
I said that there's a lot of people were saying clean off the rifles and I was pushing
Back against that idea
You are one of them
The coward's way of saying exactly that just shoot people there's no such
Such thing as offensive Ila
That one of those crimes
I will say that it's a leftist student
F****** book with the Nazis bookmark
Cheese's
So I can slide clip Alex talks about
Conspiracy that I'd like to see him
Substantiate at all
And the police come and say you're not allowed to criticize a lockdown
By the way all these people leave them on Daria
Remember that job
What's Swedish couples
He was organizing a demonstration they arrested her
Hyundai in Australia they disappeared
Members of City Council
What
There's a big difference between you not checking this is object permanence
Existed we would have heard of him about them in the news again yeah we haven't heard about them in the middle never been seen there
You killed they've been disappeared
That's really sloppy
That's all
That's all it takes I have not seen my delivery driver
For the Chinese food that I got last
For 24 hours and I'm thinking about filing
I would assume that if city council members
Schreiber being pissy
Appeared
Continue Council they were very suspicious
We never run off why we have we elected somebody
A don't worry about
Okay
PDF
1 things that would happen there is paperwork short
Conspicuous in its absence for many others
Does any proof and when Alex
Swedish couple
They've never been
Again we should look into them
Like I told me you'd have it and you're making that off so why would you say
Alex Costa calls
You take some calls
And one of them I offer the job to
And this guy
Is somebody who had previously offered a job too
And he's he's okay give me a half hour show or something and then Alex's
Start that up soon
You still planning on starting that show with callers up soon
But here's what this caller is theory is
It's about what the Dems are up to
The left is winding up there people
Ejected this win
Does win on the day of the eclipse
December 14th
Sorted out
Is it going to rain
Bedlam Industries
News now
Create a lockdown
Scenario and all those people down to supper
Present even more
They go crazy when Trump wins
The released
That's really what they set up
I totally agree with you start what else you think
You were saying about the
Rio taxi
I feel like
You're going with God here and looking at the alignment and God
Annie work here just look there's a great conjunction on December
21st
I'm sick of conjunction years later
Matic a conjunction
So that Eclipse that's happening on December 14th is it going to be visible in any part of North America but they will be able to
It's only going to be seen in South America parts of Northern Antarctica and some of
Southwest Africa
I have no idea why that would be sitting
Navigate to the United
Midstates bud
Go off whatever
It's an eclipse
Eclipses are Global events
It's the sun in the moon and they're doing the whole thing they're spinning all the time I grow weary
These sorts of ideas being brought to Alex's attention hibiya
Getting my fist down to whip them up into a frenzy so whatever Trump death
Probably doesn't steal the election wins it outright sale be whipped
Savers and start the Civil War and they knew that they had to do all of this
Is right now because the stars are aligning it other than eclipse
So does that report
It's eclipse
Anybody who dares take this s*** seriously has the pretense of like
He's right about more than he's wrong about f*** yourself
Fuckyour soon never listen to this show you listen to this God damn it
Anybody I challenge them if they think
But Alex has more right than he's wrong
No kidding
Explain away tell me tell me about
How eclipses are part of the fuc
Plan every civilization ended because of
Priest eating people only 100 years
Sometimes it's like
Okay where is different time frame is it always ends up with a human barbecue
Never wanted Spectre
Christ and totally falls apart
Instead of just handing off the Baton to Harrison Smith this episode
And that is he has Ezra Levant from Rebel media come on
Two Hosts for a couple segments
And then Harrison takes over a nice Alex still gets to leave early
Is coming up
Very excited I'm interviewing a segment
These great talk to us is alright
And then
Coronavirus methadone Shroyer
Housing for d.c.
Austin Texas
The interview is not very interesting at all and the only other clip Alex has on the show before he leaves I think his interests
And anyway is this
But man
Landslide
Everyone I know
Believe
Hispanic gold Young
It's like 60%
No one builds for that
Dead zombie
Is there such
Papa
Controller
So I think we have 60%
If it's we have to convince ourselves we are the majority
This is in reference to a caller who is like
3% in polls believe Trump won the election
It's a hundred percent
Hachi
You talk to Ezra Levant
On consequential event
The show wraps up
I think
Frustrates me the most
Principal reason that Alex in the conservatives like
Is because he's a dick
2 Libs
Liberty Road
Never occur to you
That would motivate
Right
Say okay fine say that nobody is voting for Biden
Principal factor of your guy is making a lot of people hate him
Yeah yeah that's motivating
I better when you add on like
The existential danger that he presents to vulnerable populations
Probably galvanized quite a bit of support that way as well
Oh yeah it's all just
Job
Anyway on Friday the Convoy
Arrived
In d.c.
At that point really kind of pointless to discuss it is it being its own thing anymore
From that point on the Caravan just became another group of participants in the larger very sad
Display in d.c.
Here's a little clip of Owen
I guess this is their point now
I don't
Know what they're doing
Man
God
Yes we've been
Wildly obsessed with electoral politics with the last
A little while and
Yet here we are trying to overturn an election
While yelling
Government sucks
I just
You guys
Don't understand
Anything you want to be anarchists
God I hate
These people
Government that is not fully in line with exactly what we want in his way that represses
The people we don't like
Sucks that's the real
The Nazi suck
She suck on the one hand
It's only fair that I congratulate Owen for being able to get to d.c.
Theoretically on time
50 bucks in hindsight this was a miscalculation on my part because I thought they were actually planning to do things in
In the cities that they went to not just drop in and ongoing rallies for about 15 minutes before leaving
They were able to achieve their goals on their trip
Because he had no goals
So I guess I just overestimated the
You put together that
Time
Schedule where I was like yeah
I would say two hours is about right for a rally
Awesome to go around America maybe you good
And I know from the times that I've been on the road like there's just unexpected
The s*** like invite hat
Take a shet
You might have to
Pull over at a rest stop
For a couple minutes
How many times have you been on the road and been like I weird
10 minutes
We're 15 minutes of track exit
Yeah it's the best
You might even stop and see the world's largest
Blank
I think that they probably weren't on time for most of it but they did end up pulling it off in the
The trip ended up
So like
Congratulate
I mean what they said
Barzola
Success I had more ambition for them but they did
Kind of course it's kind of sad
With that congratulation out-of-the-way I have to say that this is one of the most
Pathetic dismal embarrassing and childish weekends I've ever seen in this country
The Prelude of Alex's
Completely pointless and poorly attended Caravan tour is what made me pay closer attention
But if not for that aspect I think I might have given this entire million Maga March nonsense a Passenger Terminal invention
The turnout on Saturday was in the tens of
But nowhere near their goal of a million people
And well below the 400,000 + who came to DC for the 2017 women's March
It doesn't even come close to the turnout for John
Stewart and Stephen Colbert's rally to restore sanity and or fear back in 20
They're two pieces of the puzzle here
The reporting to recognize are both true
And seemed at odds with each other but aren't
The first is that this rally was a horrible fails
The turnout wasn't even closed with the organizers and propagandists
Like Alex would have wanted
Haven't built this up as their last fight
For the country
The fact that you did a poorly attended Caravan leading up to the March only serves to highlight how thin the support for their causes and others
Cities around the country
Even the board
Conservative-leaning South
Their attempt at creating optic
Pics of the country speaking out in
In support of trump is really only proven that their best shot isn't even a fraction of the people
Cucarachas
Support reproductive
Rights are civil rights
Who's going to be excuses for the small turnout and there'll be pictures that do look
Like million
Are people but they're far less
There are a ton of attempts to use pictures from the women's March or the March for our lives protest
Of course been around easily claim to have been
For this weekend
Videos
The Trump supporters being attacked where the context of them initiating the violence
Was left out
These will be the attempts to salvage what the trumps
Scammers cam
From this utter failure of a rally
The second piece of
The puzzle is that the
The turnout was still way too hot
And that's because this rally was
Explicitly radical
This was not a political rally in the sense that like a March
Supporting the Second Amendment or March protesting attacks like might be
The only reason Israeli was happening is that these people decided to show up to say they don't want to follow the rules of the country anymore
Whenever the news there's a new president elected
I'm sorry but doesn't win will often hold them
Inspirations and you're likely to hear people chanting stuff like notmypresident
I bet you can find small pockets of people in those protests to insist the election itself with invalid and the right
The results are real
This weekend's rally was an entire rally that
Just consisted of that smallpox
Which is now
Yes the right way
Collection of really f***** up weirdo
Alex Jones had the proud boys giving him
Security Apparently one of them at a Pinochet did nothing wrong shirt on
The old neighbors may or may not have had men stationed around the city in case it got hot
Great Nick Fuentes and his groper gripers walked around as completely normal participants in the affair
Qanon weirdos are all around
The seeming contradiction is
Same thing
Haunted every stop on the
Caravan
In every city the turned out they got was miniscule
Compared to the way they present the rowdy
Every event they held would be considered a flop by anyone who seriously had the self-image
That they do
But they don't mean it when they describe how popular they are
Kind of a joke
They know they're lying
Just like Alex does when he says there were 400 cars in the Caravan
That's a lie for the benefit of The Listener in the middle of nowhere who thinks they're hearing dispatches from the Frontline
Not realizing that they're being deceived to sell them pills
They don't care if there's no one at the actual rally because on some level ever wanted in Forza has to know
Did insane world no one would show up at their rally
9 people showing up to send them off in Austin is more than they deserve based on their credibility
Work ethic
And Integra
Indeed
This is the same Dynamic at the DC rally
Butternut is a disaster
If you're looking at it as a
Sincere attempt at a political rally
If you're looking at it for what it is
Which is a collection of people living in a
Completely fractured reality that's at odds with our reality
And sees all reality as hostile
Turn out to be terrified and a wake-up call
Any event that would allowed people like Nick Fuentes and Alex
Put Jones to speak on their stages is not a political event
And I worry that some people there
Or some people who I've seen cover to the rally
He might not understand that dynamic
And how extreme the stuff they're seeing actually is
I don't know what to think about what the future holds but I do have a couple of main thought
The came up
The first is that Alex is messaging to his audience is completely out of sync with his public
Behavior
It is. Where he's going to DC and join again this rally that's trying to reinstall Trump as the president of the country
He simultaneously telling his audience that there is no hope and everyone's going to die so everyone needs to head to the Hills
This messaging is discordant
And it kind of gives you the impression that his primary focus is attention-seeking behavior
And selling survival food.
The second is that we're about to be entering a period where fantasies and alternative realities on the extreme right
Are going to be coming into large-scale conflict
With what I'm going to
Call reality
As more and more excuses for why these fantasies are coming
True become unconvincing
The need to escalate will be ever-present
Where is before in his earlier career Alex could justify his conspiracies by pointing to
The Federal Reserve
Now in the era of
Trump in order to make anything you saying makes sense
He needs to evoke the literal devil end time prophecies outrageously complicated and nonsensical conspiracies
An insistence is that everybody doesn't like
Is a pedophile
Without strong forces pushing in the opposite direction
This road only leads
2D / extreme
There's no point where someone like Alex will be like all right good job
If you ever reached is impossible to attain goal of eliminating all the globalist
I would bet everything that I own that he'd magically find a new sect of Neo globalist
Then just knock me down with a feather they all happened to not be white
What I'm saying is
I'm worried
What was
I mean
Extremism in on the right has always been there
Obviously there's a right
Give their position
In electoral politics
Used to be able to give them a bone
You know like
Oh George W bush lowered the marginal tax rate
That's all that's like a little like pressure valve
You know we got to win
You know the president gave us something we elected him and we got the win that we were looking
Now all of the winds that they want
Are either imaginary
And so cannot be
Right or impossible
And so also cannot be at
Or will kill everyone
So hopefully will not be
Even the imaginary
Pressure valve you know other than
The imaginary in the impossible 1
The Practical real-world versions of them are
Exactly what it would look like
If someone were taking authoritarian rule
Exactly you know it would be like
Like the
Execution targeted prosecution of
The leadership of the opposition party we want Hillary to go to prison
And that's not going to happen
The real the real world version of any kind of thing that would be like
Oh yes
We've gotten what we want
That would be
Public execution
So it's like there's no
Pressure release
And
If the if
Trump if they it's the right handed
Weaponized
Imagination
Then they could have been like
Oh well Trump
Put up
F****** he dropped Environmental Protection so we went but nobody gives a s*** about that on the right if
If Alex wants to drink continue his break and he should just be focusing on the fact that Trump got out of the TPP or whatever
They all met talking point and be like
Khmer
And your new life
Was never economic anxiety
It used to come off that way but now it's just full-on racism so you can't even be like oh well we got out of the TPP because of
Economic anxiety or anything like that it's like you might want to tell the times that
I think that it's really worrisome
The
Just the
Did the rally itself
Send DC quiz Warriors
This is an attempt to take over fully
The gop's
With these scam artist
These Trump scam Folk
I think it's probably wise of them
I think it's the only thing they can
Yeah
Although they'll end up in a turf war with qanon soon enough
Sure and then they'll fracture the party and
Democrats or whenever election
That's probably our
Do the most
It's likely out
Of that in the long-term is they will eventually kill each
Build destroy the world according with or at least diminish their own electrical power
Metaphysics
Play not you know
But
That's
Like the long-term
The short-term is
Fuckedupshit
Very scary
Oh well
Anyway that's like everything on knowledge fights
Just Kara project
Sober
The good news is though in South Carolina they did find a homeless
Computer chip in
But they
Couldn't get footage of Eddie gave him that Nazi broccoli there's the problem that's what happen
This so much ruin my fun
Just Want to Have Fun they just don't understand how to do anything
Yeah
How much fun would it be if one of the videos does just like
Owen being like all right we're going to go to this North Carolina where they look this Raleigh
Event but you know what while we're in town
I'm going to try and find the best hot dog
So personality other than were angry
Angry Edward sensitive
Angry and we're like please don't hit us with milk
God dammit you got to the carwash
On this Caravan body project
That's indeed I think I need a day off
So I think we will be back at the end of the week
Week 11 episode on Friday this week
Because
I also just don't take that
Alex is going to be like back
Putting out some
Some content that I can cover but a Time
For Wednesday's episode or anyting
Sorry guys
Everybody out there sorry
I don't want to cover Alex going out Tim pool I don't care
I don't respect him pool enough to deconstruct an episode
Of his squirrely ass people told me that Alex was on Tim pool and I was like who the f*** is Tim
Kool-Aid why would I give a s***
He is somewhat relevant to the world
That we cover but
I just
I find him so
Insufferable
And also he seems like somebody who might bother me what type of guy who might email
I don't want to wake up someday and see a notification to who wants to debate
I just don't want to do it
So yeah I don't know I don't think I'm going to do that sometime in the future may be assertive they look
Back then I have no interested
Finding covering at the subway we might cover Rogue
By the way what the back at the end of the week
But until then we website
Twitter we are on Twitter at that knowledge underscore
We are Facebook and revives uses and if you could please find a local charity or bail Fund in your area.
Emilio on dzx
I am that trucker who threw a milkshake at the due to the Caravan
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color