Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for its knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Need
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Alex
June
What's up
My bright spot today is
Ian
It is nice out
So it wasn't just the words.
Whatever the f***
Because I stuff earlier this week
What do I know about myself I like spicy stuff
A spice challenge
Sitting around that we were going to camera
No what's the nuts
It was the chocolate bar
I believe
This white chocolate bar that has bunch of Chili's at at you cuz I was like
That sounds interesting
They were given
Meals to charity for every bar that they soldiers Charity Drive
I will try it we'll have some fun
It was sitting on my counter
I thought to myself
Would I enjoy this
Without an audience
That's a good question would I in
Enjoy this spice
The crazy hot thing with
Without the added element of people watching me eat it sure can I enjoy this without it being
Contact and now we get to know the
Exactly
I don't like spicy stuff that much
What half of it alone
I thought
Terrible
I don't know if I'm getting older or what it but like it was
Unpleasant
I found it to be too much
It hurt
It's a tall punctured you don't like f****** the spicy things you don't like
Seltzer's you're not going to like myself anymore
Fake smile
Is this just you and me I have all these sock puppet account
Address isn't sending buttons to yes that is a what's going on
I still really like spicy stuff but I don't like
Really spicy
You know I don't know maybe it was late 20s early 30s I was in a realex
Stream spice kind of
Place and now I got your picture
Cheap company
I think that maybe it's just over for me for the extreme spicy
So I will be
Beginning
A hot
As opposed to an extra hot
At the Thai place in the future
And I think that's okay
That is okay is accepted
How about you by Brightspot dead is a piano solos
Okay
Well actually this is a mix of a grape bright spot
B of A
The outro to Layla.
I was listening to Yoko
Econo play the piano solo on I do from the Cowboy Bebop soundtrack
Really good pianos
Solo I can delete the outro from Layla
It's very salonius Monk and it's syncopation it's really really good
And then I was thinking about my favorite pianist
List of all-time Keith Jarrett
Okay keep Jared I do not
He is a jazz pianist
Who will give these like
Literally hour-and-a-half-long
Improvise piano Khan
It's basically just him
For an hour and a half
His music is beautiful and he is in
Incredible he's a dynamite
Performer
And I just found out
That he had a stroke
Oh no
Yeah and he's lost the ability to use his right hand or his I can't remember it's one of his hands though so we'll probably never
Never play live again
I'm telling you he was he is
Incredible
So I am pouring one out for for Keith Jarrett hantu
Recover that's that
It's very sentimental
Time. We're wishing the past
Snout into one of his live album I want to transition into a less
Rain is bad
I was thinking the whole time you were talking
We've had pianos for a very long time now
I can't imagine anyone doing anything new with them
I don't think you're telling me about how great he is
Ghetto self
How many keys does a piano have
Simple combinations of 88
Over any number of measures are they
I mean some of those sound good
For the good place
We got a lot of time
Today's you say that
Yeah I think I might be done with all music
Wrap it up we got all the musically dude
Now see here but my brain doesn't work again you're like
Let's talk numbers I like ya wait we've done everything we can with numbers.
I'm in a wiener
Headspace
Whole numbers is infinite
Today
16th and 17th 2020 of Dance
Sounds good
That's right
Holyshit
This is Ben
What 100 episode
I got accepted Suitor later
That's just how it got to go X
Sometimes you need to submit to the universe
Insist on saying this thing
I'm going to be honest I have to accept a little bit like the end of 1984 with
I just love the government now dance right
I'm bad to the government
So
This is a stretch of time
I think it's a little bit of a stop
We're talking about
Week Monday and Tuesday sure and there's a reason
Al Bundy episode will pick up on Wednesday
And go through the rest of the week
Everybody who's listen to this probably already knows Alex has gone down to Atlanta
Because there's a protest in to do and he's got to try and stop the Steal
He's on his
And I kind of feel like that's an extension of the Caravan Alex Went Down to Georgia looking for an election to seal
What's Happening Here
I just
Hold on tonight
Okay
Alex is going to Georgia and
Doing all this stuff and I kind of it's not obviously part of the Caravan had to go through Atlanta
But
It's kind of a kind of has the same spiritual energy is like Infowars on-the-road IRA
Will have the sequel of Alex's Adventure in Atlanta.
Texas back in Austin in studio
And
Complaining a whole bunch
It's kind of like Steve Coogan and Rob brydon in the trip
Sure
Business on this episode
So first gap-tooth killer thank you so much you're now probably walk
Gtk
Were you about to say Andrew Dice Clay iwk
Another
Virginia
Creator and it's spelled
Cre8
H e r
I'm a policy wonk much greater
Usher
Had nothing to say
Next
The tiger High eats license plates inch Ikon globalist thank you so much you're now if I was you want
I'm a policy wonk
Are you very much
People donate Donuts
Chrissy thank you so much juvenile technocrat
Thank you so much
You are now attacking
Money off that heroin
Yub
Thank you so much Sarah
Website
I'm sure we would reach
Or what you could do if you find yourself filled with a generous spirit and you need to ask
Express that
Find your way over to a little device that has 88 keys on it
I play one of the 10 approved
The songs that Dan allows
And then
Use that generous Spirit text
Breast
Music in a way that gets lost it a little bit at the end because of your
You bet
God
Through
Cheated
This is just logic
This makes sense
You can't refute that
Real done with God
A real dumbass
Is Emma's first clip where we start off the show at
Alexa
Last episode he had to go off air threat to go off air twice
Cindy he's now switching it up and just going off air as soon as
The show began
We have massive breaking news
A few minutes
To some insiders Hollywood
Stealing Georgia
Serious this situation is
We have a path forward
First I want to play a little bit my speech
Yesterday Dallas Jones
Myspace from Saturday
Million
Trump March
After I had close to a million people attitude no no they're not
Estimated game
He's getting his information on that they're trying to steal Georgia and so as we know by the end of this Alex Wilhite
Atlanta to meet up with Alexander who's going to be
Stop & steal thing great stuff
I wanted to stop you before you started talking about Alex without Georgia
Because I've written the song
I'm sorry for stepping on
You're one of six.
I do think that this episode is not as good as I want
There's not as much happening
Alex is kind of
Just talking about how Georgia needs
What's on his mind
Take it over
And what have you
That's all I thought as a bonus
To the audience appeal to people
I would write my own version of The Devil Went Down to Georgia but that Alec
Saint Alexander
Do you have a company
No
How do I get a piano
Certainly.
Do the mouth sounds
Alright I'll take that
Alex Went Down to Georgia he was looking to stop the steal his sales are down
We came across this young man
Spinning a yarn and
Malik's jumped
Tell you what
I guess you didn't know it but I'm a bulshit all this to
And if you care to DARE I'd like to work with you
Now you spend the money you owe her boy but give the texting this dude
I need your skills to sell my pills but I'm still better than you
My name's Ally and it might be unwise
Don't join your scam to make some clamps cuz I only have shameful allies
Peter was a little office.
Perfect so far just keep on rolling
Ali Robin up your threesome push-ups aquitard
Google profit to Macon Georgia and Alex's of blowhard
If this works of money and Renown are all yours
But if you don't
Dope dope
Go to
Alex and mumbled about his obsession with The Unborn
My pickup.
I've got to be out of system
You just do get this from other political podcast
You just out
Alex mumbled about his obsession with v on board
And fire flew from his fingertips when equipped
Any push the talk button and it was a static hiss
Replace the battery
Has Alex fumbled
I know you have a million-dollar Studio B
Go to the boat run boys run
Alex got abused
Conclusion
Charles here
Alex got a misty look in his eye because he knew he met a friend
Any offered Ally of tiny bullhorn handing it by the speaker end
Can you call Larry Nichols about that Congressional blackmail
And I don't told you want to son-of-a-b**** stop extending Easter sale
So
That's
Bethel Music
Real hard to do any kind of think you were Cupid struggling I realized
It's just business
It took me maybe half an hour
Music
Stop the stereo
Bastille dad election
Georgia
There better be
This Thursday apparently is the deadline
We're recording this on Thursday
And I have been on the phone with
With a lot of different
And
Purposes
This election could be over for
President-trump
Thursday
Last
Still not leave office
There's a fraud is real
Perception of the election has been certified
Make the road towards
Put a second
Trump
Taking our country back
Very hard
Yeah I know s*** that will that will make things more challenging
The process continuing to move along as it's supposed to
Make
Derailing
The process more
My car being turned into a cube will make it difficult to
To drive from here on
That is that is trapped having your wheels taken
Yeah absolutely having my feet
Cut off
Will really make it harder to
Play
Yes yes
Alex is not the only one is heading down to Georgia
Of course Ali Alexander
Is going down there
Some other noted weirdos
Everybody needs
To go to Georgia I would like to just
Point out
Again
I don't I don't want to keep
Beating a dead horse and I love that Caravan
Caravan
To Georgia
It did
And it was wildly successful
Successful in so they need
To do it again here
Better
You're in the car
Heading to the Capitol
Cambodia
Unfolding right now
Give me black people
Legislature
The force the governor
Emergency station
Certified
Legislature must stand up
You work for the clintons
Staff
Is the problem
We need funding
Yeah I don't know I find this unconvincing
Uninteresting
Yeah I'm a little bit Blown Away by
The level to which
They're willing to embarrass themselves
Without dragging my route
I'm talking about the whole the whole
The Hulk
Are all teaming up
To make everything sick
Joke
And it's weird me out
Because
That suggests to me that we're going to have to escalate
From sick joke to
Full-on military takeover or they're just good I don't know you know didn't you notice how I asked
It's
Here we go
Let's ride this
I don't know why everyone's acting like we can just wait and he'll just go
Well I think that's one of the good reasons why I'm really glad that our show is about Alice
Alex Jones
Because at least I know he
Peaceful looks
I don't know what's going on
In terms of other places and not very scary
So I'd rather not have
You know an opinion the people take you seriously on it sure is I could be wrong
Right I could misinterpret something
Italics
Totally fine saying he is
And push
Extremist
I thought along the way sometimes there's something really fun
Like
It's always fun to write a parody song of The Devil Went Down to Georgia
A lot a lot
Great
Another thing that's fun is when Alex says things like this
The Dollar Tree rolling around like
Exterminator
Hello my friend
You got to go away
No be very different villain
Japan and Europe have Daleks
Doctor Who
Copy.
Sure
Gundam
I want one of those
Right now I want a
Suavity
Gun transfer
God of War 1
Barrel
I love that so much
Alright Google
Alright it's programmed
I guess because he's not saying it's someone's
Captaining is robot eyasu
The robot comes up to you
I'd somehow it's in its programming that if you refuse
It Shakes You Down
Weatherguard retina
Presumably not shooting you if you then agree to get
Schwab
Alright
Here's your swab
Or here's your gun
Turns out you're going to choose this one
Carrot stick swab gun
I think why would you even
I would prefer a knife
If you switch from a slob to a knife and it's like
One of these is going up your nose today made by doctors
Do I assume we're not prioritize
Alright the head of a
The head of the Mayo Clinic is a real gun nut alright so we're developing this
Robot that specifically to text people for covid-19
Make it so people don't have to risk getting exposed to run tests
I feel like you didn't answer my only question
Of course it has. I will
Greenlight
Anything
Is amazing news
I'm going to need a citation.
Source
Information on it
Although I think what he's referring to is that there are robots that are used for like covid testing
We're countries they've rolled out
How do you combining that with
If there was a crowd control robot
In China
From like maybe last
Gear 2 after they were working on that would like give little shocks
Different directions
The mental images so funny
No I will not
What about now
Read the most
This is what ticks
So f****** funny
Shootout with a cartoon
Got a robot hand
Pick them up
Annette it takes your wallet
Alright stop here for a showdown
Has been the fun part of the show at
Alex gets into like what sort of Georgia
Storyline
This is a big story
Georgia Secretary of State
Signed
Legal deal
Democrats
Challenging how bad
Alice
Lottery process
Mail-in ballot
This is another classic case of Alex getting a trump talking point it's factually incorrect and then
Spiraling out of
Control when he's recovering it in
To something else
In this case Trump tweeted about how the Georgia was stealing the election in the third been they
A consent decree by the secretary of state that quote
Makes it impossible to
Checking match signatures on ballots and envelopes
Etc
To say quote
They know what they knew they were going to cheat must
Expose real signatures
This dude speeding like a detective in a shity Noir film who's just been shot
Rolling on a piece of paper
Suppose real signature
Anyway I have no idea how a consent decree would make it impossible for people to
Compare signatures but I guess that's the best drops people can
Can come up with
Do people like Alex busy and keep people funneling money
Ended up stopping the Steelers or
In reality according to the Associated Press the state absolutely requires
The match
The issue comes down to this
Cook a lawsuit by the Democratic party which led to the agreement argue that minorities were disproportionately affected when they have
Heather ballots rejected
Among other things
Sings the settlement
Set steps for local election officials to notify a voter
IPhone mail or email in a timely fashion about problem
Bums with a signature
Are they really trying to tell me
That a state
Governed
By Kemp
Has not done enough
Voter suppression
It's an interesting
Angle
Yeah I feel like he didn't win the election because it was
Was free and fair
Summer said that
Like maybe if they were paper ballots we might find out that the results might have been different
It could be
And this is just another legal challenge
The Trump's Camp is making trying
Block the finalization of the election but it's going to get thrown out just like all the others
The only thing I find really interesting here is the dynamic where Alex can't even really understand what the
Issue is
Alex thinks it has to do with deadlines and post that signatures
The legal challenge has to do with whether or not the secretary of state had the authority to make
The changes that were made
Which word designs
To create more oversight and better handling of signature matches
The suit doesn't seem to even take issue with the actual change that was made
Just it was allegedly made unilaterally and without proper approval
Which is pretty deep in the weeds in terms of legal challenges to an election
I'm not surprised Alex doesn't know the details on this I wouldn't make
Expect them to
It's being aware of how much of a Hail Mary this is
Would probably be bad for business
Can you imagine
I believe that right before we started recording this challenge got thrown out
I believe if I if I understand the headline is just saw
Correctly I believe this cases
Just died got thrown out the moment
The judge realized that it was written in color
Can you imagine if that's what if they've all the sudden they were like all the Secretary of State didn't do it right so Trump is president again
That's that's
How it goes. That's how it's going to work for anyone I wouldn't assume it would
Obviously knowing this is week
Alex
Recommend
Course of a door
Is investing in Conroe box
I lied
Everyone must go
To the capital of Georgia now
Round the governor's mansion
Rodger Stone
Other people
Call the White House
To go
Get on a freaking airplane
Capital Georgia ago
End of the governor's mansion
Stop
To see people power and this will do it
Yeah it's a great idea live Trump storm the
Governor's Mansion the great idea idea
The only thing that would be
Better episode that one is a great idea he should do that everybody in the Senate
Stabbed him once
I do love the idea that he's like
I'm coming
Georgia and I'm f****** bring it Rodger stone with me
I want I want him to be like
And we're going to settle this election
Buy single comment combat 204 we have Rodger Stone in this card
The camera pans over
Play Glenn Elliott
Girl fight whoever you f****** world
I will only fight if Eliot Spitzer's dad
Come again
Gina
Security in DC for a job
Gyros
Having proud boys
Launch
I see this is the thing that I'm talking about how is it that we have
The juxtaposition of Rudy Giuliani melting like a f******
Candle in front of us with
Enrico Tauriel being like what if we killed all the left
Enrique tarrio is clearly trying to learn a little bit about
PR
Because he's doing some heavy lifting on this appearance
Trying to give the okay we just like to hang out
You know the boys were just like a drinking Club
We'll just let anybody in
Stickman
Extensive background searches
Whatever the case
He's trying to make it look much more respectable
And Alex is actually the one who
Kind of ruining
When somebody when a man's down I don't want to keep it
Women and children
So Alex seems to be the one who's
Who sings this towards even more
Street seems like a nerd
Talking to a bully
How you kick their ass
Good thing you're not blowing me
Do you know what IUD people up I kind of know what's the job it's got it that's the end of the site.
Cheese's
You know what we're trying to do is just show that we're we're a group of normal people like everyone else I mean we have our own political
Local beliefs
We do is we get together and we just share Community just like we do
I think you should kill people
Delhi okay
So much bad press
A lot of our members
Turn out to be real crazy
We do a lot of background checks but apparently not on that kind of
Kind of cereals
Exactly
The deal
We're trying not to do all that s*** publicly all this stuff about kicking people when they're down
Look different
I know The Oath Keepers
And your buddy still roads kind of lead into that we're going to kill you stuff
That's great where different
Alex Alex
Text Buddy
There two ways
We're going
Underground my
We're going to survive and then we'll kill people again in 10 years or for whatever will be will make it through this
We're not going to go out to guns blazing today
This is like
What if we're not
I think if I had to guess
I think it's
Just like
Glass half-full half-empty in terms of the DC rally
I think that Alex is trying to play it like
Half full
Like we are going to take over the world that you almost there
What's weather like
Yeah it was a lot of people but it wasn't that money and we can't take over the world of this many people had enough
Yeah not enough to maybe
Brian put on a face of respect
Stability
Or invite General
Patras and see if he'll do us a solid
Boom so Alex is impressed that I don't
Know if this is actually true I think it's
It's not but Alex
Thinks that no one is ever going to
Filtrate of The Proud boys
I don't think that's
True but he has a theory as to why
And I think it's pretty fun
How you guys accept organization infiltration free
How do people get involved with boys and
Operation Freedom
You looking at me for the devil worshiping vampires
Canterbury School
Yeah too Macho to infiltrate you know
Yeah leftist we just can't look Macho enough.
That's worth something
So I think that Alex is a pretty consistent
Thread going over
Just like really gaslighting as audiences
Crowd size
He's talking about like it's
Straight up maybe even a million people they're tough to sell
Event incredible getting Gavin again is lined up dealing with
Appreciation
First of all Skype issues not a surprise
We're we're really trying to infiltrate the
I have this I had this interesting experience while I was
Episode
Largely
Okay
We're just going to interview bunch of people with proud Boys in
Extremist
I'm not interested
Who else wants
Start a war
You want to start a war yeah
Okay yeah I'm not super interested except for just to say like yeah okay
Having the whole conversation is largely about everyone's
Got to go to Georgia
I think this is bad but I also don't respect
Gavin at all
I don't I don't not refuse not interesting he's not funny he doesn't say anything
So are they trying to drum up likes
Support from the proud boys like Hey we're focusing on the Proud boys the proud boys need to go to it
Anna is that like there
The idea here no I think they're just trying to show a stiff upper lip
Insertive like you can come to Atlanta because the proud boys will be there to fight with you
Short case s*** goes bad or something
I think that's kind of a lot of them
Stop being a coward
You'll have don't have your back
I'm so Alex
Enrique 2
Define the MoMA
Keep doing this
He asked
Define the moment
And then something very
Very familiar happen
Taking over probably if you haven't started as an idea to promote family and man and
Attorney in area
Kellogg
Hundreds of antifa
You call
Enrique tarrio this just right now
Sorry that was my fault
Cool that happens multiple times I think there's some issues
Gavin shows up
I find him
Insufferable
Yes
I just wanted to
Say that I'm thrilled that he's decided
To give up
We proved it this weekend
The we are on the side
That's right
And they are on the side of what's wrong
And if you can't see that now
I give up
Congratulations
Good good
Please
Please give up didn't didn't Kevin come on Alex's show like a year ago saying
F*** this
The point
Nothing nothing expresses
You know just like
Leader
More than any time you lose Hootie deciding
To quit Moody lash out
Absolutely
A lot of people with
Listen to that
And say I would die for that
Anyway
Tucker Gavin
Owen Shroyer
Leader of the Caravan comes in
And they talk about their
Huge crowd
Daddy
Doan you did the Carolinas for the South
DC
The police that we talked to estimated cuz I was a 200,000 that Days please listen to Adele Someone spot
Going back to the beginning of it
Three-and-a-half miles
Annoying people
What would you describe
Images I've seen sad
Morphe
People in attendance Andy million
March
From the images
I've seen of your
Caravan
I've done
Stand up for large crowd
Was a failure
Oh yeah
You
I don't know
I don't care but relative size of the Million Man March either
They seem really hung up on that really want to make sure that this March
Which is better than other black people's March
It seemed it seemed like a perfect
Seems like a sticking point they brought it up a couple time
I would ask you Jordan how do you
How do you define the
How do I de
Define the time this moment
I would say pathetic
It is sad pathetic
That's what I would say that the
The human race
Has
Responded brilliantly
Terribly
At the same time
To the point where
Man I'm really hoping
We lose 98% of people and get the reefs
Do you know what I'm saying the 98% of reefs lost
That's a tragic
That's not great
Owen has had a revelation
This doesn't seem like a revelation
Seems like very similar to
Catchphrase of Ben Shapiro's kind of
He Democrat
Body politic
Emotional
Live in reality million people out there nobody got covid nobody got sick I'm riding back in the air
Define laughing about the dumbass thing
Don't kick me off of
Flats
So it's far too soon to know what kind of effect that DC rally is going to have on covid rates
But it's not discuss broader trends that we seen from past event
If Trump's rallies throughout 2020 or any indication
Eat those words
It's in the future once
Data is available
Purple released in October by the center for American progress said quote
Analysis by the center for American progress find said about half of the president's 22 campaign rallies held between June and said
September 4th followed by county-level increase in covid-19 cases
Suggesting the events May have life
Community spread
I don't have data on the recent rally nor does anyone yet but I mostly cut out that clip cuz I have a hunch
Watch that Owens going to look pretty bad in hindsight
As well.
Crazy from from like
I blocked up to the Supreme Court
You're here packed in like sardines I mean it neither
You can barely even breathe
Poor choice of words I would say
Shall we end the 16th
And this is a business
This is really strange.
Beginning
First of all
Screws up his
His whole thing
This whole time. Between the election in the inauguration what are you what it what is it
79 days of hell
79 days in hell
The countdown
Day after the election
78 days I have left
Alex Cruz
Goes backwards
64 other 79 days in hell, does China and its dual
War allies are desperately trying to overthrow the election
President Trump I understand that it's an easy mistake to make
No one cares about the
Has accepted you caught on it's not it's not
No one's going to remember 10 years from now all your member the 79 days of how you're the one who's pushing is really hard
Do you have to actually get it right you can't say where updates
64 valve there is a little bit left
Little bit
End on the 30th
It is fine but it's not
No
Pennywise
There was a weird sound
I mean like poor quality sound or anything like I really felt like Alex's
It sounded like he was reading a commercial
Beginning of this episode
The mainline Republican party is the truth of the New World Order and world government
Tucker Carlson
DJ
Opportunist
Persian
Copying
Your truly
As
Macon
The Mac Ranch
When it comes to culture War
We are winning
Cidnet
Yeah take a promo trailer
Those LaFontaine all the way and I was really thrown by it cuz it just seems like what is going
Going on and goes to couple Lake pre-recorded report
Realized
Heated wasn't there
That was pretty important
Alex
18 minutes into the episode
Thank you so much for joining us
Plenty of
Broadcast
Was 6:05 Minnesota Carlson but he knocked it out of the
I guess he was getting more in
Information about Georgia
Or something
There's an interesting dynamic
What's going on
Alex is crazy
And all this stuff is nonsense
I think he's benefiting
From qanon
Quite a bit
Cuz you know you remember
The day that Dynamic that existed
You know it is
Previous time
Between people like Fox News and Glenn Beck
Alex Jones Justified Glenn Beck being crazy I'm not Alex Jones
You hear about you was able to sanitize himself and make
Himself seem more palatable
To a wider audience bulshit launderer
Because there was somebody could be like I'm not that guy exact I'm stepping on that guy in order to make myself look respectable
I think Alex now has qanon to be like I'm not qanon
That's a fair point and because everything has just gotten
So much worse
In terms of public discourse
Filtering information
Like I think
I think he's able to like
Take advantage of people thinking they like there's only one person who's wrong time
Whatever not realizing qanon and Alexandra
You think you think
Qanon selfie
Who's going to
Become leaderless
And they're going to be like
Hey baby will go back to
Alex Jones
No
I don't I don't know I don't know what the predictive it but I think
Make that most of those people are two pills
Seattle back to Alec to go back to the lights
Yeah I think they would find it a little bit
Point actually find it on gratifying
You know Alex is late
Yeah starting to show 14 minutes
Or whatever he did say videos of Newport
Tough talk about
Now generally when is important things to talk about
Bizarre fantasies
Notions
Things he's misremembering
Half-baked anything
Am I one of my favorite things
Is reporting Twitter comments as if their new desk
P.m. at the future had upstate
Country
Have been openly promoting the global economic forum
Initiative for months already
Mentioned or disgusting
Cuz you're a slave you're not supposed to see all that info
Supposed to be
Before
Never consciously
Understand
So this is really standard bulshit but I think it highlights something that's really interesting within like Alex and his resurrection
You can easily find articles discussing the ideas presented by Klaus Schwab and references by name to quote the
The great reset
Immediate going back to early this year after his book
Was published
Just a simple Google search shows that before July there were articles in
Forbes and plenty of international Outlet
This is the same thing
As why aren't there any Muslim voices denouncing terrorism
You didn't look
For it you assume it's not there
And now you're making out
Conspiracy out of the idea that you haven't found anywhere
There plenty of people talking about these ideas they were just not places you were interested in
They weren't in Publications that you
Maybe normally read the hill is publicly available to their the articles are there
If you wanted to if you had any interest
That discussions there
No one's hiding anything from you you can
Type questions into the Google
Search bar true
So if he's like
Giving you one of those rhetoric
Questions like
How come no one's talking
Think about this
You could type in like
How come no one's talking about this
And you would have to fill in
I think that what's going on is a Miss phrasing of what they believe or what they
Experience as the
Sure
They want these ideas
To be yelled on the front page of every paper
That is what they
Think
They Merit
It's so important
Exactly
In the same way that all of Alex's
Conspiracies never take the media is not covering XYZ like there's an article about why you're wrong about this everywhere
You can find it if you want
They just want
This like the coverage
The same thing with like no and no one covers
The truck being good at finding
Articles and Publications about good things
Did no-one is bowing down back
They're covering these ideas in a real-world way as opposed to your way
Because that isn't your view isn't being
Shouted from the rooftops
Experience as a cover-up and that's just not
That's not accurate
They're not saying what I want them to say so they're not covering it all
Exactly
And I'm not going to look for the articles that would
Prove my point wrong
And it depends
For business
Phenomenon right now because
Alex is reading someone
Tweet yeah
That's
Is there any bad take you can
Find
On Twitter
Like you can find
The Scituate that's the corollary to your lies about
The piano
Bees are too good
Resorts
Yeah for the environment
Exactly
There's no oil executive someone who hasn't tweeted out like let's kill all the bees so I don't
I have to be with flowers anymore
Trying to think of a take that isn't on their candy sucks
Snow someone doesn't like
Nope definitely there it's all there man
It's all there if you want to find a bad take you just search it into Twitter it was somebody's bad
Of course
Do you know where are comes from
Busch Gardens
Stardew Valley Alexander shows up
And this is actually really interesting to like that last clip
Really Devon
Once traded this sort of phenomenon of like not look
Looking for evidence and then claiming there's apps
Evidence of something
This is another really in
Interesting thing that Alex and his people do quite a bit
Really
Appreciative of all the Grassroots work out there
Teachers are Coalition partners are always willing to work with anyone
More than people go get
Right
We care about winning the Electoral College and getting Donald Trump above 270
We secured the permit and then decided
Alex can't speak
This person can speak in that person can't speak
Come out later
But you know we're not going to tolerate our movement behind the White House
That's the reason these ladies are
Georgia featuring is a blue state
Any misspelled Georgia
You and I were first to announce on our independent channels
Casting freaks
You really want
What's going on
It is that women for America first group got the
Petitioner got the department
Yeah and they organized the actual event and had a list of speakers that shouldn't include
People like Alex
Well they organized
Well there were a lot of people who also
Decided to descend on Washington at the same time
Party crashers are actually more integral to the party by Diplo willing to
There is no party without the crash Iraq that doesn't sound true but I guess I have to believe you I don't have any evidence
Why isn't anybody talking about this
Are you find this fast
Because it's the same thing with like OK freedomworks America
For prosperity
Coke money Coke funds
Astroturfed a ton of
The tea party ended early days
Amanda Alex
Glommed onto it and then
Accuse them of taking his move
I meant exactly what he's doing here
Ezz and they won't let them hijack their height
He's crashed this thing
In d.c.
They rightfully probably like this is going to be tough to deal with
I understand maybe Alex speaking
But Alex is Buddy
I don't know about this
And then they have the temerity
To get on this show and accused the people who are the actual organizers
Stealing varuven
To be like they do present well
Like Alex
Do they really want to like
I have these clips available just whenever I'm
I'm just like
Women for Trump and it's like man
You guys don't get it
The moment you say
Step out of line
You're no longer
For Trump
Just women to them and you know how they treat
Blanket chest with
It's
It is
Kind of kind of shocking
He like
So fast you could
Not have organized
That event
Alex
You could not have
We saw the Caravan
Exactly
Saw what you were capable of
The combined work of a ton of grifters
Added to the
Population
They came to DC
The actual
Avent
And people having a reason to be there
Was done by the work of the
The people who you are
Computer
And that's why
Diaper if you're on the right
Stop crying
Stop it
Stop organizing these things
The people who want to come and get up there and yell and make you look bad
And steal all your thunder
Are going to s*** on you later
Yeah you're being used
Party time
Oh well
Anyway Alex's friend
Alex is talking to Allie and he wants to know why
Is Georgia so important
Why Georgia Stokes
Gorgeous
How you doing there buddy
3 long pods
Alex
Alex we lost you
Alex is Misha
In command
Control
Weird
Alright
Commercial
I thought that was really strange oven if he just went out
Yeah and I don't know what happened when they come back
But here's the thing
I know that probably online that didn't happen
Sure but I'm listening to it through
The feed that goes to all of the radio station that play Alex around the country
This is what syndicated to shortwave to
Whoever's listening it just cut out
What is
I'm a psycho
If that's an audience you care about that
Certainly
Not great
Could
Really fit
Dixie's Brown
Maybe not
It's doable
I don't know
Why let's go
Alex wants to know where
Hiding I like Howard he always was Alexander
Blanca's question from
Because that's his bully pulpit power he still has why has he been so
I won the election yesterday
So the rallies were going to come and then there was a cop
Compromise reached
Inside the White House so I'm just
That is my first time talking about it
I start making their way through the
Trump is not want to
Position himself
What can hold a tweet against him
Or a rally against him
And so
Hey sweetie
Concentrate
Counterpoint Alex just said that he tweeted the other day that I won the election
Victory fraudulently
Calling him a dictator but he's afraid
Ridiculous
Held during the
The band The terrorism Bandit was described as the
Muslim ban
Kinston
Cachapa trying to play
Play the legal strategies tomorrow
Counterpoint
Trump tweeted
I want really smart strategy iPhone
Antifa scum
Your story doesn't hold water Ali
You can make up all the fantasy
Fiction that you want
But Trump has a giant
Cowardly loser
And I holding
He does now he wasn't
Want to get out there
He wants to do his rallies
There's plans to do rallies
Anytime stop Bastille. Us
Opposing rallies
Capital
Full-time
Until the Electoral College meet to maybe after that maybe after that
Maybe
We never get this
Country back to them
If it's calling at the Electoral College
Is fun but
I don't care
What are you doing is
Trump wants to come out and say hi to the people you lost
To be the figurehead but he can't be he's got to play it smart cuz record
So for now it's just me
But here's my website so we can have demonstrations
Capital
And never give the country back whatever that mean
She idolized I get it and I understand why everybody is like
Mocking this
Dislike
This is just a griffin
Turn all that stuff
What it's like
This script is going to run out
Fatal just stop it when the grift runs out they create a new Griff and whatever they need to do
Whatever they need to do they will do to
Continue that
Not a joke
Right right right
It is primarily
A scam people like Alex
Somalia running
B
The scam
If taken seriously
It's super
Verify
In the past when it's been a scam
Civilians
And normal people
You know it
It's awful and it is what it is
It's a game where you get hurt
The world
Yeah yeah yeah
That's too much
Now I've had a theory
This whole time
But Alexander was working with Rodger Stone
Stop a steel because it is the same name as Rodger Stone
Alleged
Pool watching organization from 2016
And I didn't actually do any further research on if they just told me he was
Olly Alexander a great political analyst
The publisher
Is here with us he's been a tireless fighter
Was Rodger Stone starting
I don't understand
Okay
So I was right
Is all connected
If Alex has to be believed which
She's usually not
But this seems like something that makes total sense
How does Rodger
There's domain
He registered it now he's
He's taking his cut
No doubt he
He's taking a cut
I'm here here's the
Nothing if if this is a conspiracy
Conspirators can be charged with every aspect
Active a crime Rico
Exactly
So
Is Ali follow through with his plan Rodger might be in trouble
Tweak out our plan Alex
We're going to
Virtual
Alex and I will feel the street
Million Patriots
Insurrectionist
We know how to deal with that
We will bring trucks
Now is the time
A Georgia
Occupied
DC.
So apparently
The plan
Is occupying DC what you're going to get bored very quickly Alex
You have no
Ability to run anything like this no interest in anything that
Especially once
The cameras stop
It does kind of occupations is that
I get boring after awhile
People make coverage broke up and then there's a long periods where there are cameras
Sending you don't have you're not built for that
So now you're not going to do that
But assuming that you do
You're not going to get 5 million people to come to DC
That is not going to happen
Let's imagine what's going to happen
If you try and inaugurate a second
President now that'll work
Dark pope
We'll have to poke somebody will dig up Biden's remains and put them on trial of the
Remember my middle evil medieval warfare history I don't remember
People like
Writing down
CJ's where our favorite pie
You know
4 months of waiting for supply lines to catch up
Sitting there going hungry
Not fighting anybody. I think I think Alex wants his listeners
To do that
While buying survival food from him
Of course and then Alex will show up with a bullhorn every now and again and take credit for everything
Like medieval kings fighting a washer
I just try and think
Think about like
What in the real world would that look
Is Alex
First of all
It's a leap to imagine 5 million people show up
So let them add let's stipulate that 5 million do show up
Now they decide they're going to inaugurate Trump is no he lost the election
I guess we divided up
Territories
I don't know
The Mind reels
Guess Steve pieczenik might get a job I'm telling you I
I just telling you we just got to isolate him
We just got into isolated we give them we give them all Alaska it's
The biggest stadiums old werewolf treatments take all of these take all of them and say you know what
We agree with everything you're
We love what's
Going on going to say we're starting a pilot
We want to put your ideas into action but we're not sure cuz they're not
Tried-and-tested
We want to move all conservatives to Alaska
And you guys just
Work it out there and then bring it back to us whenever you're ready I feel like this is not fair to the people who live in Alaska
No that's true
Oh well
The moon will give will give alaskans Hawaii
Who
To Japan
Book everything
It's trouble so let's leave that aside for another day
Alex
Gets if he's been doing that on this episode to his Brian stelter impression
Oh that's just great
Not a good impression
Now it's really funny because apparently it's not his
Hours and hours of evidence today it's ridiculous
Hokkaido
I don't either
Alex told Brian
Makes me feel like an
These people is what
Play laugh at
Yeah like
Was that that
Funny
What did you laugh at all
What did you laugh
Was it just that he did a voice
I think so
And if so
Yeah well I mean I think is that that was one of the challenges of
Doing stand-up
Was
First of all not
Thinking the things that I said we're that funny
That's the audience agreeing
And then you know things that I eat saw other people say that weren't all that funny
And audiences thinking they were hilarious
People have different
Sense of humor there's no accounting for that and it's bewildering
I do agree with you that the stuff on Infowars
State is humorous
Like a folks were on as guest
It's worse than anyting
Most things that I've seen at comedy shows
Really does because
Comedy
You know you've seen every
Kind of obscene the gamut of
People trying to be funny
All lacrosse
Keyboard
And even they
I have nothing
There's nothing like
This is just a series of people who only understand each other and laugh at
These weird things
Divorce
From
Real
Yeah so much of comedy and so much of what you find funny is the ability to
Shared
Perceptions
Ideas
And I think once people have
Such fractured
The reality is that they live in it make sense that you were wouldn't translate at all
At sad how did you make a joke about the sun rising if they're like weird
It's dark all the time and then I got to be tough there's no SharePoint
Commonality
I'm sorry this expert Valley yells that he signing his death warrant
He's going to fight this thing all the way to his grave
And show all of these guys on soap
Proud to be working with you Alex and you add
Got to rush the gate
The Barbarians that rushed the gates in the castle
It's really that simple
It's liberty oryx death
I think you're in the same boat
Well I'm like that I'm total commitment every cell in my body is Tamanna music
I just remembered
Money got sued by Chobani and Alex said I will fight that are backed I will
Woodwind or I will die I will win at other week later
That I did
I will win or die
That's a you-know-what
Error
Look
Hamdullah Kaya I am so sorry
That I said those things about you please don't
Okay I'll
Alex whatever
Ali leaves
He's got a head down to Georgia
Alex
To meet him down there
And Alex pics
Some calls
This is
Ifucking performa
It's on Alex's Park
I believe that what's going on here is that
Alex thing
Fix that this caller is nuts
And he doesn't want to talk to him
So he decides to
To pretend to be mad about something else
On the Air day
Mass ejection
British accent
I love you Dad
Other talk shows
Want to have your clean phone
You're calling about
Once you get on air
You tell us what you want to cover you don't have to ask permission sir
He wasn't he was telling you what his topic was around
His phone sounded fine compared to
The colors that you generally have on this show but he said he wants a predicted Corona
Brain-chip
Alex is like I want to fuc
Talkin talk to this dude I want to get mad at him for no reason
Continue
Once you get on here
You tell us what you want to cover you don't have to ask permission sir
Hang up on you
And no screening
Dragon Dave I love you still had your free man brother glad
Did not ask for permission again he's he was given a caveat that this is going to sound like numerology
How's more Preamble than
Numerology
This is going to sound like numerology maybe you'll think it is more of a rational actor in this whole thing
Yeah alright
I don't want to do this
I don't want to take whatever this guy saying seriously but
Yeah whatever I'll just get mad about my weird ideas about anti-censorship of phone calls
Very strange
Yeah everybody
A very strange
Don't think another call and this guy wants you to not take of that
And then thankfully
Alex starts talking about his idea of this Karma
Indeed
That's what the whole thing about like you need
Utica Obits need to trick you into doing things to her moral reasons Galactic law sure
And you might get a little
Confused
Could using
Is perhaps the only thing that like really fascinates me about Alex anymore
This idea of his bizarre ethical
And all up the radiation they can inject you with anything they want to
You got to make sure that
You don't take anything that that
Get their push it out
They need you to agree
I need you to agree
At least
I do understand it all they know it's a loss that a lie
You make somebody do something get Instant Karma
Interdimensional, when you die
For sins even if you manipulated the
The field how it works
They need to trick us to go along with it
Emily
Their satanic operation
They need
Garden
No
Not not not one bit
Nope
So
If I understand
Correctly
Instant
Karma
Isn't after you die
Right
Witches real
I don't think the history backs that up
No.
All the monsters who died in their beds
Do that but you missed out all the Instant Karma
If it did happen though
I don't think that this works
I think you're going to really tough time explaining how this system has
Ever operated
Especially if you go back to like
Times when
Like feudal time
I'm sure how did how did Instant Karma work back then
Well okay in the Dark Ages
I can't remember but it was I can't remember if it was Roman
If it was not but I feel like in my head it's Roman
The the
Metal Bowl
Do you remember the metal Bowl The Golden Bowl and they would put a human being inside the bullying light
The fire underneath it
Making that person burn alive inside of the bowl
Kings last talked about Game of Thrones
And that guy
Absolutely
Had diarrhea
And that's what happened
Instant Karma
Tough
Yeah
Tough for me to wrap my head around this
Now Alex
Seems to also be saying that even if you manipulate the system and get people
To do things up their own
Volition
You'll still have
Bad seem Karma or you die
What haven't you seen the scoreboards that
What's the vet follow us around everywhere and sit on top of our left shoulder am I the only person who can see the scoreboard
I think so
This makes perfect sense to me and Alex scoreboard
I'm
A little bit I'm a little bit worried
About the
Real world application of this moral system
I'm a little bit worried about it
If you believe this moral system
And then
Light say
You violate someone's free will
And then there's no answer
Instant Karma
Oh my God
I must not have violated their free will go there we go
Bentley car mode so
Furthermore furthermore here's the biggest hit
You know what that kind of implied
Is there anything that you do if God doesn't strike you down for doing it it must be okay
Until after when you find out
It's not like
Whatever you did to somebody they must have been fine
So the fact that you're still standing and don't have
What the f***
I think my biggest
Is that they can
Quote
Pressure you
Now
What does that mean
Wow what are the limits of
They can presser
Are you into agreeing with them still be in trouble after they die so just have Instant Karma if they pressure
Just figured just
Torture you endlessly until you agree what if they send my profile
If I would say that it's not
Baloch Baloch pressure
Installing pressure I think that's the question that it is
Globalist
Have to get you to agree to do things you sure
Daleks with guns is not
Pressure
If the guy that killed the person
That's insta
But as long as our director of the government is not
Appropriate level of pressure
I think it is debatable you know the whole idea of like
Did I make you do something cuz I pointed a gun at you
Morally culpable or should you have gotten shot instead of sure
Stupid conversation of course
You got a gun
This portal system makes no sense but I I want Alex to talk about it for an hour
Robot with a swab is baby
The robot.
That's a little bit intimidating
I mean it's weird
If there's no Garden it's not walk away from the robot
For the jet
But if you could outrun it
Close
Not feasible
Not real well right now
I like to call Matt Smith and see what he can do about
Anyway I just want Alex
To do a socket
Whole special episode about this weird moral system
The call-in show
Where people can ask him questions help refine some of these ideas
I wanted to have it
So far I really want him to try and explain it I really do because
Is it is
But Uncle yeah
So now Alex another call and
What happened
When's that happens more than I would like
To admit
And that is this caller tells Alex about a dream he had
Discern
I just wanted to
To reiterate a dream I had approximately
16 years ago
Gringo's like today
Red Cross.
Waycross
I didn't know where to go
I lay down my back
I looked up to heaven
And I saw a
Blue spiraling light in this blue spiraling light turned into like a
A tornado
And out of that Blues
Spiraling light
A dove
The blue dove
And
Liquid Love raindrop
Entirely through me
A moment is only for a moment
But a moment last forever
Alex
This is America's moment
Stand up
If this moment dismiss
This moment will pass
Forever
There's a shelf life on it
And I
Kudos for you for going to Georgia today
What a liquefied the energy field
The future and we have to remold things now
What are those words
People liquefied the jump
What are you talkin about
Course
Yep liquefied the junkie dream that I was skateboarding last night
Anyway this guy I got to tell you about a dream I had
At 6
So I was
I was 17 years old
I love you and you're my best friend. Don't want to hang out do you want to hear this
Really incredible
I had this dream and there was this
Is cat and it was
Was climbing a tree you know like
And then I saw this blinding light
And so did the cat
And you know the cats.
Because that's the light blinded the cat so much that it fell
And it was holding onto the tree
And a booming voice said it was like a trumpet in there Kitty
And I just always hung onto that Dad
Well it's a meaningful thing
I like the idea that some people are like in a maybe
Like protest outside capitalism be like the time is now
I mean or else why would that guy who caught Alex Jones Show
I've had that dream 16 years ago
That's ludicrous
I just want to reiterate add riwayat
16 years ago
Is the last sentence I want to hear anyone say ever have to assume Alex and that bubbles like I'm so mad I freaked
The Freak Out
Anyway we have one last clip
It's sort of an intro
To our Monday up
Well I'm on my way I'm not the devil little bit but I love Jesus
So I'm on my way to Georgia
Rodger Stone Ali Alexander so many others
Very exciting
Join us Monday on knowledge fight is no way a project part 3
The Texan Went Down to Georgia
Yeah so I'm excited about that kind of
I'm excited
About the idea of
Like I'm playing by my own rules
Likes to wear to cover the show but
I think a bottle episode we talked about his time in Georgia makes more sense than discovering Wednesday at the end of
This episode
Agreed
Like the Caravan
Perfect two-parter
Mexico recently and let me tell you something I've done a little bit
But I was very well
Well-written Perry
Thank you that is very well-written is a good parody song I will be genuine for this one is very nice of you to say
I will admit
In hindsight
2 m problem
That's a problem whenever you write it out
And you don't sing it in a you know
I might have reread it
Anyway
I think that this was a little bit of a
Preamble episode
In some ways
I feel like this
Was getting ready to go to Georgia
And it's this
Just got back from DC and now he's about to leave again there's this weird middle play swords like
Buck I don't know I'm going to hang out with Allie Alexander and all the proud boys at the layover in the airport
He is he is a nomad
For the 79 days of hell
He is a manager if
Running around the country hit already on trying
To find attention wherever it might be
He is going to have to do that
I guess yeah
That seems like what he's got to do I will see
On the one hand
I'm glad it doesn't
Come off as desperate
As being pissy
Website
Girls want to go to bed
Facebook we are visiting a local charity or Bellefonte in your area to help out
How people do
Doing God's work right now
Will be back until the enemy oh I'm Leo I'm dcx clerk I'm Terrell run this week except
All colors except
Censored
I don't know how to do this one I f***** up sorry
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work