Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for Tenaya Lodge like I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
We're going to do but sit around
Technology Beverages and talked a little bit about Alex
Giordano Giordano Giordano
What's up
My bright spot today
Paradox
Sickly very strange the thing that you
Left soon as you've probably realized after eight months that you should have been gone from it
Mutations
Because I find
But it's just us
Match with
It's the way my brain works
Not no shade on people who do enjoy it or or like Twitter and Facebook
Can stuff I I just did it
It's not for me
I've gotten older Iraq
Recognize that it's
It's confusing
I don't like
I was running the knowledge fight Twitter account
And it became a thing where it's like I know I'm using
This
Everybody listens to the show knows I'm using this Shore
So if I post
Promo stuff
It feels dirty
Yeah
I don't know
Reversion to self-promotion
Anyway the reason that I
Turn on the bright spots
What are ways that social media can be used
In ways that are fun
And not
Dumb
Everyone keeps asking for pictures of my plants
Started an Instagram account
Caldera plant underscore fight
Forever post pictures of plant
I like it so like
I like periodically feature different plants
Dan's Wild
Kingdom
It's not connect
Did the show he's not
Do intrusive on my personal life
Nice sweet spot and some of the people enjoy people like seeing
I think so maybe this is a function that social media cancer
I still think most
Here's what we'll do I'll make an
Instagram account
Parts for my two dogs
People have asked
Pictures of Bulldogs I'll go with Westies underscore fight
Will compete to see who's
I guess
Growing things are better
I'm afraid that your dogs are
Cuter than most of my plants
I think I probably was
That is true underscore fight
Popular
I don't know about that
About how it but it is
What specific reference
In Valhalla that I particularly enjoyed
That came out of nowhere
Which was a reference to one punch man do you know about one punch man
Vaguely yeah about a
Very depressed guy who can defeat anything and anyone in one
You told me about that
Essentially destroyed by that
Like how bored and awful it is to to be the
Ultimate power in the universe
That he's just a real bummer all the time and there's a perfect referee
Prince2 that
In Valhalla where you have to fight a girl
Spoilers
Okay the real bummer about it could guess that was going to be more alert
So it's very very very funny
I have a great
I don't know what the deal is
But I lost a bunch of
Time
Corrupted save
But I ran into problems that happens when you play games when they first come out
Not really used to
But I I had there's a mission at a certain point
Spoilers
You talked to a guy and then you've got to get
To another city
You got to take a boat to
To get to the other City
Every single time after I talk to this guy the boat would spawn
Like in the middle of land
As if it were a horse
So I had to go back
To buy most
Resent
Auto save file
Anahit autosaved
So many times
Wow that boat was chill there you restarted like 50 times in all your auto-saves
Back to where the boat was last saved before that was
Great Towers
Is very frustrating but it is what it is
The same thing happened One mission all the sudden every time I load
To save the entire screen would just start shaking and veggies and then
My character would just fall directly through and then
Fall Forever Until It
Until she died
Even even great games sometimes are a little problem release bugs
It's really exciting for me to is that like
I have I know that
Age of calamity
The Zelda game
Hyrule Warriors
I haven't even
Touched it
Oh got it I haven't even thought about it
No and that's a
Nice feeling
To know that that's there
If I ever ever
We may not ever happen
Are you got another 80 to 100 hours later
Calamities they're working for
That's a nice
Comforting feeling
How do I add second bright spot back
I was one down to Georgia
People
Made audio version
My parodies on which is level of
Oh yeah
Quite frankly uncomfortable with but I think his delightful that's a lot of people
Put put my music
I don't know if
Is there a sequel to The Devil Went Down to Georgia
Charlie Daniels version
But there's a million
Mine was a sequel that's true that's true
I know there is nosql
I figured they know it can't force it
But Alex said he went down to Georgia.
Kids was
Knox
What I wanted
It lacks a lot of the charm
And the fun of the Caravan
Because the Caravan allowed me to
To paint a picture
As in this case it's kind of Alec
The pictures
You realize every time we get excited for something we're talkin about
People who turn every good thing into s*** yeah yeah we're at we're getting excited about the potential
But never gets realized
F****** Lucy
Charlie Brown
Every time they set up that football more like
We're going to f***
Can do it this time
It's going to be a caravan field goal
Going to be amazing and then they slide it out from under as a guy
It is
Some fun to be had along with a number of interesting things that I want to bring up and discuss it.
The course of this
But we're just going to be talking about November 18th 2020
Is 120
Oh you're still told you we're still alright with it
Accepted I also want to say that when I discuss this on the last
Episode
I was actually the stuck in my craw a little bit
I said that you were
Submitting
To the B
And I don't actually that was not the right choice award I meant surrender
Surrender is that was the word I was wondering
You come up with that work
In your crawl
I was laying in bed with a
Surrendered
The real name of this one
Because I am I take the
Trip to George's pretty unimpact
Actual I think that
It's it's repetitive
In nature what Alex does when he's on the road
And at the same time
There's enough stuff that happened during this episode
That's worth
Talkin about that
Headed to try and force it and do like
The whole rest of the week
6 hour episode computer chip out of that Homeless
Still has not where I'm at 8 months of not pulling the computer chip out of
Yeah I'd like to either somebody running
Sally's has refused your challenge
Close to 150
We are currently on day 4 of The Scourge
Gun-toting Daleks running around the streets
To keep an eye on
Keep an eye on my gratitude in our gratitude for the folks suicide
Cayden thank you so much you are now policy walk
The 4th
Roman initials
Ivy
The ivy
Darren Emma Darin
I think it's about your nail polish
Text Taylor D thinking about you and how about you want
Taylor Taylor Dayne
Leisure
Zoe
Godzilla never ever get into a zoo Zoe argument
No good
Next fella asked
Give me to say how I thought his last name was pronounced
I know this was just because it
Looks like weiner sure
Maybe maybe
His weiner
It's I think it's rarely
I mean like a Matt Winer is new the guy who made Adventure
The first name wrong
Song like that
Yeah it's anyway Jason siwa
Jason weiner weiner argument down
Next to Queens are the Corgi star they
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks qticles
Are they finally like to thank you to come people donated on an elevated level from abroad
I'm so first
From Denmark thank you so much you are now a technocrat
Emmy Rossum from
This is a name that I'm knock
Going to be able to handle
Hammond Malena thank you so much
What's your now a technic
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
Thank you so much to our Representatives
News from Denmark
Hammond Louisiana
Thank you very much to the both of you
It's pronounced quokka
I probably
So if you're out there listening to take a nap
Website
If you are experienced any kind of malaise or perhaps existential
Prices
What do
You should do is fill yourself with
The generous spirit
Channel that Chi energy all the way up into your fist
And punch
Local charity or bail fund but metaphorically
Alright that works
Jordan
This is the reverse
The Caravan
This is and I don't know why I didn't
Didn't see the novel Rock
I don't know why I didn't see this in advance
I'm so blind
I'm Snowblind to like
What actually going to happen
Because like Alex going down to Georgia
But I forgot that that means that I wouldn't
Is going to be hosting the show
Anna and like yep
I forgot
The flip of the dynamic from the Caravan wear Owens out on the road and Alex's
Throwing to him in the field now he's got it
God
And I was just like
As soon as you get into it you're like oh no
How does a how does Owen try and really pull off 3
Lazy does it is he mostly plays a live feed of Alex
And Ally Alexander yelling in Atlanta on this episode
Hopefully there's
And the episode starts with Alex doing a little bit of a mess
This is the mark of the beast of Revelation
Which is not coming this year
Can you show me the
Baptist churches and Catholic
Directions to plug in the QR codes
So Alex is God
Fear of QR codes QR codes are
15 years
It's been around for awhile
Advancement of the same idea behind
Which is used by many retail outlet
I say many
Because if you don't want to use barcodes and UPC scanners to ring up products
You don't have to
No you do it compelled by the mark of the beast
Compelled by the market
Efficient
The main reason I pulled this Clippers to illustrate how deep into the nonsense Alex's
Start the show off
The second reason I glued this live is probably boring for
It's to use this as an opportunity to explain how people like Alex or broken records trying to make everyone afraid of everything foreign
No reason
QR codes or something that Alex is trying
Pescaraz audio
It's about an interesting Lee if you look into the history of the thing I proceeded QR codes
The UPC barcode
You'll find a sterical people doing the exact same thing
50 years of
According to an article about you PC history and wired quote
When the first UPC scanner has arrived in the early 1970s
According to various IB Evers who worked on the
The project
There were protests at grocery stores
Even though the codes appeared on Coke cans and jars of applesauce
That's not right
4 heads
I love
End-of-the-year that followed
An urban legend a rose Ward
Gullible types of the number 666
It was hidden in each barcode
Some of these paranoid types noted that there were often
10 sixes in the barcode which were in fact Arabic
But it doesn't matter
Again from the article quote
Early test films of the scanners were labeled with the letters f g and H
And some saw this is proof that the code would wind up on more than just Coke
Assisting the eighth stood forehead
And the app
Her forearm
Sure people do this
It's inevitable because James at the future are both scary things
The more complex the system is the greater possibility it has
In terms of productivity and Effectiveness inability to help people live Better Lives
But as that
Complexity increases the theoretical damage that
Make a calls go up to
A simple example is just the internet
The ability for people to
Communicative digitally interact over great distances its revolution
Canary in terms of information
Inflow directing
Charitable assistance
Places that need it
But it's created a gigantic Tinderbox they could
Exploded anytime
For instance back in 2013 the Associated Press has Twitter account got hacked
And a fake tweet was posted about two explosions going off at the White House
That injured President Obama
This wasn't
True but the effect on the stock market was
Is real and it's the byproduct of evolve
Volatility that would not exist
Without the ability for information to travel
Almost every technology could imagine could be slotted into this kind of ballet
Having a centralized Power Company in your town relieves you of
The burden of having to run a generator yourself
But also if there's like a bad storm in your area in your whole block might end up losing power for a while
The complexity of emerging Technologies provide
B benefits but also increases the problems when something goes wrong
Alex is just one in a long long chain of hysterical idiots yelling about how some new ish
Not even that new
Is the end of the world
Rambling about QR codes
Just like his forefathers
You protested barcodes outside grocery
It's a real bummer that
John of Patmos
Really maligned more efficient
Consistent like maybe if Satan were less of it like God is kind of a Luddite in this scenario right so the Antichrist
Hey let's give everybody a mark so we can do the whole thing
You can do Commerce
You can do all this stuff
Yeah I get that can be abused
Splitsvilla boruff
Alright
God is out here like look everybody free will f*** that
That gets everybody complicated see what we're talking about what Twitter people are jumping out there lying
In the stock market in 2 seconds
What the mark of the beast on everybody forehead
Call it a day
Right
I lost myself entirely the message
All right let's do that
You have a hypnotic power today Georgia that worried about it
So
Alex's on
The seeing in Atlanta with Allie and
The beginning of the show is
What appears to be a pre-recorded or I could have been live I'm not entirely sure thing of them
Disorder yelling
An ally has
Some big news to break
Just one example of Georgia radar
Morning Georgia Republican party chair please pick one of our monitors
9626 are in DeKalb County that is in Atlanta
And 13 for trunk
Biden would have gained enough votes from this one back to loan to cancel out
Vulcan we have to audit the vote
That's why Alex Jones and I are here
So Allie is reporting based on a tweet that was posted by David Shaffer they had to
The GOP in Georgia
But it's a very misleading
Think we've designed to be used by bad faith actors like Alex
Some alley to fuel their machines that they're trying to use overturn this election
Basically what happened was this
They're conducting his recount in Georgia and during the recount someone made a recording
That is the same thing mistakenly put down over 10,000 votes for Biden
When in reality the total was just over 1,000
Providing at 13
Never Trump
His mistake was caught in the recount
That's what Shaffer is yelling at
Discounting error was not made in the initial automated count
So it does not actually affect the total for the state at all
But that's the impression that Schaeffer's and Alex's coverage resigned to leave the audience
Sure
The ideas supposed to be there sleuths uncovered 9000 votes from the actual election for Biden that were erroneous
When reality someone involved with the recount made a mistake and
In the process caught it
Before it actually was a big mistake
Yeah that'll happen
The DeKalb County CEO released
The statement the basically said that they were unable to verify the
The claims of this error
But to put it in my words
Even if everything Schaefer said is true
It doesn't matter
Quote Twitter storm
A little surprised by the tone of this week
It was more about
A Twitter storm the alleged
Discovered reported
DeKalb elections officials and correct
Did prior to the transmission
How the official audit report to the Georgia
Georgia Secretary of State's office
If the scenario occurred is Jeremy Shafer Legends
This is evidence
Subutex imbalances established by Georgia Secretary of State Brad raffensperger to ensure the accuracy of the election results
Performed as designed
As is always the case with Alex and Ali this is a dud but
It's a dud that they're probably going to use as a piece of evidence of fraud
Yep
It's not
Somebody during the recount accidentally put an extra zero
And then they found it
And now it's all over
More or less
Stop yeah
Okay cool
But it's not just Georgia
Thanks America
Delton Michigan
Breaking news on the situation that is just explosive kind of Hollywood gangster movie
Wayne County Michigan that Detroit other Republicans to Republicans
Did you Democrats it on the board
Republicans decided not to certify the election but under duress and threat from hundred
Get the secretary of state would do an audit we are in legal and cost
What all you saying is inaccurate but let's pretend for a moment
That would mean that the Republicans on this Council he's talking about we're willing to certify an election that they felt was fraudulent
Because people were mean to them on
On Twitter
Alex Haley is saying that like it's an understandable thing like the leftist
Just to meet on Twitter they had to certify the results
Will when you see mean things that's how it does that's how the
American Revolution started
Sure there's the taxation thing but George's like these guys are a bunch of
The Dixon
Yeah yeah
It's like
In the Declaration of Independence cyberbullying comes up a lot
Ellie singer
The people
Tweeting the stuff this mean stuff is like the equivalent of having a gun to your
Ridiculous
If it's your job to make sure the election is fair and your decision-making process is in any way affected by would someone on Twitter
You proven
Exactly one thing and that is that you're not qualified for your position
The Wayne County Board of canvassers met
To certify the election results broke down on a party-line
With the two Republicans William Hartman and Monica Palmer voting against certification
Have the Democrats voting
For
At issue was the number there's a number of Precinct ahead and onyx
Explain discrepancy
The info total
According to the Detroit Free Press
Quote most of them recorded discrepancies of
3 votes or fewer
In 2016 there were similar discrepancies in voter totals in Jill Stein's campaign it pushed for a recount
This recap was ended by a court order before it could become
Completed but after the election was over
The state of Michigan did do an audit
Headed found that a vast majority of the
Explain discrepancies were easily explainable by human error
And the quote many of the problems encountered in
Detroit are attributable to a lack of proficiency
Using
Epi
Cpb software
Or the mishandling of provisional envelope ballot
They found their audit that votes were accurately counted but that there were mistakes made in terms of being able to correctly match
Devote with its pallet
Because of these various human error
It's incredibly likely
Almost to the point of certainty
The same phenomenon is present here in the
20 election
Ultimately Palmer and Hartman agreed to certified the Wayne County results with the Democrats on the board agreed to do an audit of the
The vote but apparently Palmer and Hartman didn't realize that the audit would
Be literally impossible to do prior to the certification of the election
Head so they tried to
To work a certain
Invocation witches
That's worth
I think Stan right now
The certification after the letter
The cynical minded fellow out there might to think that the real reason to Palmer and Hartman decided to recant their decision
The Trump called them personally but
What do I know
Not Ronald McDaniel V
Republican National committee chair is calling from Michigan to adjourn their board for 40
Teen Daze
The bottom of these very serious or possibly wildly overblown issues
At the point of us recording this episode we don't know how this is going to shake out
Because the board in Michigan is set to certify on Monday
Does in the future from us right now
All signs appear to indicate that like
Georgia they will certify the results
But this world
Who's f****** insane
So I'm not going to take
Anything for granted
Why not
Is there a word
Precinct Andrew Johnson in there to hell
Johnson to come back
Their issues of voting
Discrepancies that
AR
Norwalk
And that is something is being weaponized
Bialys
And one of the ways that he's doing it is just outright lying
They're still calling but they did go ahead and say they're going to certified because
That's just categorically not true
Alex and Allie are making this stuff up knowing that no one in their audience will question that Margo consult attorneys
16 audit which I would bet anything I own
Even these two dudes
Don't know exist
Be really hard to find you.
Google iHeart
This of The Unexplained discrepancies in Wayne County in the 20
20 election
Detroit's 503 election day Precinct
85 recorded on it
Explain discrepancies in the vote totals as did 94 of the city's 134
Absentee voting count
Counting board
Most of them recorded discrepancies of 3 votes
Interviewer
If you can salty 20
16 election audit conduct
Everybody Michigan
Interstate
You'll find it quote
The Wayne County Board of canvassers reported during the post-election
Canvas. That can
Concluded November twenty
Approximately 392 Precinct
Appear to be out of balance
If you combine the in-person and absent
Multi-county boards
You have a decrease of
Teen out-of-balance Precinct
In this election
Compared to 4 years ago not double but that's
By 10000
Each time
Sure every single one of those is
Is it an accidental adely adding of
Thousand
Stop these numbers probably sound high and they kind of are but these are almost
Entirely indicative of minor human errors that do not actually affect vote
But they do lead to accounting problem
Princeton
The audit report discusses the case
In 2016 a Precinct 15
Have to wear these sealed ballot
Container
50 volts and at the end of the night
But the rules indicated that the
306 votes
7 cast
This was because poll workers that accidentally left the rest of the ballots in the tabulator
Failed to put them then
Container Store
It's a problem and it will lead to a
Discrepancy but it doesn't actually have any bearing on the vote tallies are being there was any fraud
Most problems that you'll hear people like Alan
What's y'all about fall into this category and I would be willing to venture a guess
The in a few months
Whenever there is an audit of this election
Which Alex will ignore by that point
You'll find a lot of similar human
Have you ever
Counted to 1000
And then
Counting to 1000 with two people over your shoulder
6 ft away from you going like
No
That's one more for the other team
Lego course you're going to get
We're all I meant look in Mario Party 6
Thought there was a little mini game where you had to remember the order of fruit
Number for fruit and sometimes my friends got it wrong
We were high as hell when we were playing
But still
Sure
Untie my buddy Swearingen
Grapes to remember
I think it was great
A pluralized it
And I wrong
Is it 4 a.m.
It was that
Scattergories argument
Everybody got into weird. Where the I think it was the GameCube had a microphone
That you could have like
Couple voice command it would recognize you.
Banana
Break
You got it wrong even though you had the right
I think so yeah
Lives on in my memory
Forever
Anyway my point is
The people can make
Mistake people make
The larger Point here though is that Ally and Alex are completely wrong and absolutely just making up but there's record levels apriso
Since being out of balance
They have no idea what they're talking
About the actual numbers are the exact
Consider their narrative
There wasn't record discrepancy
If you go by the
District numbers there was a
54%
Decrease in precincts reporting unexplained to scrap
Is this Alexa
Incycle
Seems like a progress
Yeah that would make sense considering up for the like 3 months up to
To the election everybody Wisconsin
Silly screaming about how there's no possible way that this would be a fair counted election so everybody wet
Overboard
Because of those
Discrepancies that happened in the 2016 election there were probably a lot of conversations about
Little things that could be done to limit
I mean obviously you'd like to see that number even lower but
Stop much of a decrease
From one
Presidential election to another
Seems like
Pretty good
I don't know
I mean it let's say we've got
What is it
Almost 150 million votes Caster over 160 million now something along those
And we have
It's
50% of the County's and wash in Michigan
In 2016
Reported
Fewer than
3 or fewer
Like that
That's a boat
Tally of discrepancy less than 1000
Well Michigan
Yeah reading over this audit they were discussing that like the really bad
R1 Fathead / 3
And that
You know
It leaves you to recognize that these ones that are out of balance aren't out of balance by like 1,000
That would be egregious
Yeah that would be like National alarms
Yeah yeah it's
Severe when there's three or four
Piano in a recount and it got caught before anything
Have any impact on anything
These are kind of a big
Sort of election fraud narratives that they got and both are just like the real story I understand
Flies are coming from
This pain you're putting on but it's
It's flimsy
As is this
Ali is a
Complain about the
Pennsylvania Supreme Court
Pennsylvania Supreme Court decision it doesn't matter that there were no Republicans
It's fine
That is not
True well that's
Here's what's going on here
Trump's legal team had argued that their pool Watchers in Pennsylvania we're not allowed to close enough access
The voters Evoque counters excuse me in the Philadelphia
Ocean Center
Because of many factors perhaps
Most important
Play covid-19 related social distancing
The poll Watchers were kept behind a barrier approximately 15 to 18 ft away from
On the first row of camp
So the workers would have a safe area too,
Mango is needed to go to the bathroom or whatever
The Trump campaign argued that this was not appropriate
Lower judge
The compromise where they can sit the barrier at
Then Trump's campaign filed a lawsuit claiming that the votes that were counted before the barrier were moved where I they shouldn't
The Watchers didn't have appropriate access
The matter reached the Pennsylvania Supreme Court ruled that the initial distance was appropriate for the requirements of the election
And to mandate that the disc
Since was too great would be the
State encroaching on the County's right
Run selection
Through the
Philadelphia County Board of Elections
I don't sound right
Vacated any previous order and denied the Trump campaign there were
This is not what a lie is
Report it
He's saying that the court decided that it was fine that the Republicans had no poll Watchers which is not at all the issue those before the court
He's lying about it because it sounds better for his side
Cuz he's a liar employed by Trump's legal team
Included
Including noted weirdo Jenna Ellis who said quote
It's inexplicable than five justices on the Pennsylvania Supreme Court would conclude that Watchers observing from distances
Up to 100 ft away is reasonable
And then she pulled out her
Slide whistling
No downward
There's no evidence that this is gate at all in the only reference to 100 ft of the Court decision is quote
The campaign contends that
Keyboard setup and Posen
In the barrier
And having some tables in the area over 100 feet away from the edge of the sea
Security Fence
Effectively deprived it's representative of the ability to be truly present and effectively eliminates the representatives ability
Perform his or her role in ensuring open this
Transparent
And the electoral process
That idea only existed a thing of the Trump legal team
Claim but isn't
Substantiate
I like that the Trump legal team
Could just be like
Yeah we're claiming that 30 Different Drum bombs kill all the Republican in the United States and nobody is talking
Think about that nobody said in the Pennsylvania Supreme Court isn't even going to certify that the election was stolen
Since all Republicans are dead now
Sure
If you look at
The findings of the suit
You can find out what the max
Strawberries in the Watchers
There was a 15 to 18 ft divided between the Watchers
The first row
Do tables
A designated area of the convention center was divided into discrete sex
Each of the various aspects of
Dupree canvassing in campus
Process
Each section contain three rows of folding tables
Each table separated by 52
Even if you assume that like
Each table takes up sick
Sweet on its own and use the high-end of 18ft for the initial barrier
You still having it end up only with the distance
54 ft
For the barrier to be for this table
But of course
And I also people could observe
From different angles
Anyway my point here is that you can easily see how talking point
Landscape created out of this
For someone like Jenna Ellis she can claim in a suit the people are 100 ft away
And then when the suit gets thrown out you can claim that the court determined the people on her feet away is totally fine
And that's not nice
Now they can make any claim they were
Now you can
Spin this case
Rightly being reject
That's for someone like Allie
No
He doesn't have to worry about things like getting disbarred or anything so use free to just make up anything
Yeah why not
What he's doing
Great
Google
There's just no way
I'm a blown away that at no point in time do any of these courts
It's just be like
We're holding you in
In contempt for this dumb argue
One time
Copa America
It's pathetic
Shameful thing to have. I can't imagine being a judge
Reading one of these things and being like
My job is valuable
How could you possibly feel
It took two like this bar Larry klayman though
Suspended do anything to avoid telling each other that they're doing a bad job
Plan
In Georgia
But Ali is this plan
I'm going to lay out all right
He's one of these guys who really like
I think he fancies himself a bond villain sure really likes
To lay out his plan
Here in Georgia
High noon at the Georgia state capitol Alex Jones myself another Patriot
These are here and we are Marching and we're telling the Secretary of State
Don't certify the chances of that happening are zero but we might stop the deadline
24-hours after that and that's what Governor Brian Kemp
Certify the election from his office
So
Various
The other times.
There's no chance but maybe we won't fail later
Even though it seems like planning to fail from the beginning with suggest that we are going to
Continued
Everyday at noon we're going to be Marching for something that is not going to work
You have then
Maybe after that
The governor will do some
And by the way
Kappa
Did certified
Sucks that also at 0%
F****** LARPing pieces at work going
Guns-blazing
F****** job you might have to because
Even Ali recognizes hear that
Is Brian Kemp
He's certified even Brian Kemp isn't on our team
When he signed a piece of paper through find the election they put they Democrats place of electors to the Electoral College
Well that's where we are now
Therapy is lost Georgia
Move Along Philadelphia or something
Getting in a fight with Grady
Yeah
These f****** guy
I wonder what the next day will be Alex went to Arizona
You went to Georgia
This isn't going to work in Georgia now what's next
What's the next state you going to do another one
I don't know with the with the weakness of all of these
Legal
Colleges
Lego
They're not going to get less desperate
Like these are already incredibly pathetic
What happens when all of these
They have to do something they have to do something and it's going to be even more desperate than got to be GoDaddy
You see again or something
Yeah
Or maybe like a Lexington in
Concorde lie cuz you know how much they love the
Maybe maybe try and recreate that good out of Boston and I'm waiting for them to be like okay
We're going to have to South Carolina
There's a couple for
We'll just I got I got a crazy idea Alex is going to occupy the Alamo
I don't think that's a bad idea is my destiny leave them there
You to leave
I am Colonel Travis
Great I would
Be great lake career change for Alex
Living Museum display
Instead of going around with his Mark Twain show
Yeah you just drink
Navigate to Owen
Helming the show
In-studio and
Giving a little talk over the the footage
Sure he gets
Surprise
Buy a little
Someone he see is hanging out with Alex
Alex Jones is
Right there on the screen
Horning the state
Capitol building in Atlanta Georgia
Can I have Alex
A Nazi standing next to him so
How old is
Video as much as he can
Urban cart
Football 44
People know
Electrical
While
Oh yes such a great Khan's
Institutional plan
Call for new elections
Is in the states that your hero lost
It is really stupid but for the first time in a long time Alex makes sense
He's back
Opposition role to the rest of reality
Appeals
Yeah
They just they just know they want fashion
Your son had to be blunt about it
Election results in Michigan like okay okay
I got you
What if we just
Throw out all black
How about that does that count would we still have an election there
Good so good
Alex seems right
Out on the street
What I'm talking about
I compare things to wrestling a lot but that's because there's a lot of similarity to the
Distorted reality that exists on Infowars and in the WWE
Did you really basic with things there are good guys and bad guys in wrestling
The good guy is the face
Bad guys
The ultimate goal of a few days to have the bad guy anger the audience Weatherby B
Cheating and matches Oregon
Machete personality or whatever
To the point where the audience wants to pay to see the face
Kick his ass
There variations in some middlegrounds but this is the bass
Dynamic
Their character types
Only work as a heel or a face
And trying to make them work in an opposite of lineman
Does not
Play
Ithaki Showboat who thinks they're too hot works as a heel but not as if
Because the things that they have to do to play their character are inherently annoying
The exceptions Bisbee Shawn Michaels but he was a once-in-a-generation talent rules don't apply to people like a stone-cold to the Undertaker
We can move on
Similarly
The scrappy try-hard wrestler who refuses to
Quit does not work as a heel
The audience watching a person take
The horrible beating and still kicking out of pins
Makes them cheer for the underdog Who Won't Give Up
The giant there fighting
Throwing everything they have against them and they just won't stay down
People love that s***
To the point where it's such a powerful thing that it was used to Turnstone
Coldface
In his match against Bret Hart WrestleMania 13
Brett went into that matches the face
And the two had a brutal
That resulted in Breton Stone Cold submission hold
The Sharpshooter
Stone cold is bleeding profusely from the face and he refused to tap out
To the Sharpshooter
With Brett ending up winning
When Stone Cold
Passed out
In the hole
He left an iconic image
And that performance where he refused to give it made it impossible for crowds.
To cheer for Stone Cold and nuts
He had to be a fake
Consider the previous to this is giving it been that he was a homicidal redneck that was inspired by the emotionless
Serial killer
Richard Kuklinski
Less than a year prior
He'd broken his former tag team partner Brian pillman's ankle and then was trying to invade his home to
Are you attacking him
Would you let the pool man pulling out a gun on television to protect itself
Which was super f***** up and really scare people
Appetite because
Well
The feed cut out right is pillman with pulling his gun
No it's still cold was rushing into the house
That's not good
Anyway the point here is that there are characterizations that only working certain
Contacts
And Alex Jones only works
Outside any connection
Power
Everything becomes incoherent once he's trying to make it
Excuses for the president who supports but everything is still look
Conspiracy
Jessica
Involve the president in emerado blindly
Sportsaid president
It's nonsensical like trying to boo a wrestler was too much heart
To give up U2
It doesn't make sense
This I think more than anything else has made me feel substantially better ascend
When's the election
And I wanted to take a moment to address that levity that we probably have them
This life couple episodes
He'll be easy to get the impression that I don't think that Alex has a series of problem anymore
Or that I feel like the work is done now that Trump is out of office
Make sure no one
Strongly disagree
I want to make sure no one thinks that that's where I'm coming from
It's my job to watch Alex Jones
And critique event for a long time he's not made actual sense
From the standpoint of what his
Character is supposed to be
Which is infuriating
He's supposed to be the only person who can see through the elaborate communist plot to take over the country but he's apparently also supposed to
Be the guy that has a president's ear but he's also the guy was mad that
The president isn't doing everything he says
Convoluted
The truth-teller Persona needs to be someone who is they
Signor
Or is Liz
Listen to by people who are perennial losers like Ron Paul
If you don't do it that way
Too many unanswerable
Has come up that penetrate the
Passat
I'm grateful to be able to study Alex Jones raspberry words Persona was completely out of sync
With the reality
He's trying to present but I'm also incredibly relieved to re-enter a world where
He's back where he belongs
Time will tell if he's able to pull off the transition back to that place
Where he gets
Yellow on the street and everyone
El Chapo
And stuff
Tattletale
I have a hunch there's a lot of money to be made off semi redpilled folks
Who find themselves unsatisfied by Fox News but
Thank you and Aunt
I think that Alex could have a
Brady
F****** profitable time he's able to thread the needle back
I can't believe that we're positioned in a place where it seems like all of these right-wing people are just
Just going to slide back
Into their
Positions butt
With a we're going to have a higher tolerance
You know what I'm saying yeah it could be a situation where some people are going to come out of this more sanitized to Norm
Reality
Yeah people like Mitt Romney Barco Rubio might come off with Certo
I sure she knows
Sensibility
Because they're not saying Trump
Should
I meant
Other people might think there's going to be a drastic reorganization in terms of like
MediaFire
I think I've
I think of that
I think it's so much radicalization and so much
You know
Nonsense
Has happened in the last 4 years that
I don't
I don't think most people are going to be satisfied by Fox
Snooze the audience that they have catered to
I think I might have
Progressed past
The point of what they're able to
Yeah they radicalize them beyond the point where they
Control4 satisfy it feels like that's a real possibility could be an amazingly huge
Market
More people like Alex
If they're able like I said it
And I think he wants to I think he would love to cuz he loves money
Yeah and also seems to be having just a blast
Yeah
You this is his this is Alex like
You know I don't remember
How Free Willy end
But I imagine that it ends
With that whale getting to swim in the ocean
2 cm like a universe which is kind of like
We love you
Excited
He never gets to hear cheers whenever he's on the
Michelle do any good just yell catch phrases people get excited
I don't want to salute all your
Alex Jones
Aspen lights
About everything
Ahmad Ali
You don't need a job right now
Even Alex doesn't want to hear that
Ninety-nine percent of the time
He says that you don't tell him that
These catchphrases people get really excited and then when he runs out of breath
He'll have someone like Allie there to tag team the bike with them
Alex swimming
Free in the ocean
It's a little you know I can understand that it's a little bit the difference now between like doing an online comedy show
People watching a screen versus
He's going into a locked and upset
You're not going to get those same laughs man
That's the juice that's the way it feels good
Yeah perhaps
What's perhaps
So Nick Fuentes is there that's the downside of that is a huge problem daddy alive comedy
I think he's there and he seems like this
This dude scary as hell because
I can kind of see what his program is right now and that is
Earlier he did his thing where you brought like his his groyper movement sure and they started trying to embarrass
Charlie Kirk
Turning Point USA at all these
Live event
I mean
I don't know I feel like
I don't know how how effective
Turning Point USA
And also another point of that is also that like Charlie Kirk
Just getting older
And his hole
Appeal as a
College Ambassador should rephrase maybe a little bit less sensible at this point
Whatever the case
I do think that you know he set his sights
On demand weather
He's responsible for them having the waning influence
He's now I think moving on to the other GOP
Sure I think that there's a
Target on like the actual
Republican
Compartir
And I know that a lot of people there mentality would be like let him fight
Stand that
But also I think if you let them fight
You run the risk
Of like
Okay
Well any games made by people like Nick
Yeah make this a even more
Nazi party
Anyway he's not happy
Republican Party
Spell.
We know there was
Reach Out election day
There is no question about it
Election day
We have heard from our Republican rep
Sedative
Nikki Haley
Cartoon
Exact
Oregon
Feeling this election
You have here is more or less
Getting ready for Biden to win the election
And then their focus will turn to
Interred
GOP conference
Like right this is sort of the model of the
Booty party
Y'all with it where the
Fringe inside taking over the party
Seems like there's doing it again but
Start even more t.i.
And great I look forward to that
Because this cycle doesn't seem to
Just repeat itself
Get worse as it goes a lot
It's a testament I think two
True level of can
Apps that the GOP party
Operatives have towards
Their voters
Is just like
We're going to lie to them
Essentially
Take them captive to are b*******
And then we'll be able to control them forever
And then we'll leave them sitting ducks
To demagogues like these assholes
To you and you're like no we don't even need to worry about them the mob is
So stupid
You know Nick Fuentes is going to remain On The Fringe
Never going to come in here
And in 20 years ago
Supreme leader Nick Fuentes is going to be great for us
I'm worried about Nick Fuentes in the sent that like
This guy's a real s*** head
Used
Young
Clearly
His box has fewer are holes in it than Alex's Alex got rid of all of his plan
You know that's
But that's what makes him
Worrying to me
Though I will say that sometimes he has ideas that just don't make
I'm not sure if Nick understands his political
Very well but he should realize that it makes absolutely no sense for him to be calling for a strike of any
He's either rub paleo
Conservative or a Libertarian depending on when he's answering the question
Philosophies are super anti-union and super anti-strike
We hate unions and we want every trucker in United 541
They're horrible oppressors
Typically Libertarians reunions is an extortion racket
Trying to get in the way of the freedom opening
Employer and employee freely agree to terms
Trading money for labor
They would likely support to workers right to withhold their labor if the
The terms were unfair but they would definitely
And I mean definitely
Be way more passionate about supporting a business's right to replace that worker with someone who would accept unfair terms
That's what freedom is about
After all according to libertarian
Acknowledging that in the face of an overwhelming governing but government entity the only method of
Fighting
To unite together at all of us utilize our power to neutralize
Is there power
And that's what we call
Libertarianism
Great
I don't see any possible way for Nick Winchester
Coherently call for a trucker strike in order to force
Trump into office
If the truckers were to strike over their disapproval that an election Nicks political beliefs that should
Require that he support
Trucking companies
Breathing in
Scabs to do the work these truckers refuse
It doesn't matter
Because this isn't the state but that's bad to make political sense
Nor is it even something you can pretend would be effect
This is a line he's throwing out in hopes of insight
He's trying to pump up the crowd and piping images in their head of their side throwing the country into
The chaos with truckers refusing to work unless trumpism
Installed as president
Sure is exciting
It's exciting
So
The classic
F****** takeover
Play book though is today to utilize all the
The power of
The stuff that you hate
To get yourself into power and then close the door behind you as fast as
Could you possibly can so other people can
You sure
Like that's that's
How you do it
Yeah that's a gay man out there and it's fun enough but there's also Lowe's
Lowe's Owens got to talk
I already said something very on
Surprising
Looking at the crowd here as they begin to March into the building
People who were on the Caravan with me last week who are still
Part of this
Americans are ready to go
Not going to let this election be stolen from them
They're people you recognize when the Caravan cuz you were in Atlanta
I don't understand
They were in the cars the whole way
People who are info Warrior types
Atlanta are very likely to come to both of these
I don't know if they have that
Rescheduling
Most of them are unemployed
That's not fair
Get stuck in a bathtub
Dominion
Conspiracy
Bad here he believes
Just the dumbest version
There's no record
It can all be done off location
It can all be done remotely
That's why they run with these system that's why they tested it with Hugo Chavez
In Venezuela and then went at work to steal elections for the
Communist
In Venezuela it with Nationwide
You don't think that had some
To do with nevermind
For the record Hugo Chavez died in 2013 and won his last election of 2012 so I guess the theory here is it
This company stole the 2012 Venezuelan election is a test run than eight years later paid it all off
With the u.s. election
It's naturally raises the question of why the globalists didn't
Just use it at 26
16 but we're playing with
Conspiracy so let's not bring real questions
Chavez had just died in 2013 they weren't sure if it was going to work down in Pryor
Have you not read about Internationals and Intergalactic contract law
So the conspiracy that Owen is spinning
Is made out of combining details about to differ
Print companies in
Instead insisting you proving something
The two companies that issue are dominion and smartmatic
At Parkway this
Conspiracies presented as to claim that these are the same company or that Dominion own smartmatic
But that's not
Case they are unrelated
Smartmatic is a company that provided Alexa
Technology in Venezuela but they actually have a history of calling out
Problems like they did in August 2017
When they found that the results of the constituent Assembly Election had been altered
Which they do because their system is tamper-evident
Inset to quote self-report
Any attempt
Kefir with it
Dominion has nothing to do with Venezuela
Directly
Competitors
It's important to remember here that the game of these people are engaging in his not to make a coherent point
Their goal is to create a purse
Reception where they're right and everyone's out to
In this case the connection to Cuba Hugo Chavez is really
Telling
Because it's not about a connection that's real it's about time this whole thing to or right-wing Boogie
The anti-communist right wing
View Hugo Chavez's one of the world
Greatest evils
Call the name of this conspiracy is essentially
I don't know if a.m. service weird right-wingers
The different left-wing government America's tried to
Topple over the year
High profile
Either figure that most
Like Fox News Watchers or would be familiar with
Idris Elba
So it's almost the perfect person to use as as almost like a
The signifier
So it's not like he's going to come
Matcha
Sure
I don't know how you would sue anyway but I don't think he was interested
Ensuing Dan
This is where I just kind of lost my
My patients without
The livestream from the capital again in about a half an hour I got Avenue
Going to get you as well as
Video
Courts
In the meantime
I mean it's just so
Do I go down
Pandemic and everything they're doing
Torture
Psychological
Go torture
I'm speaking as a producer here
Infowars is currently in a no-win situation
You basically have to Main Event players in the entire come
Company with Alex and Owen
Owen sucks and all that but compared to rest
The recipe zeros he's basically Dominique Wilkins
Because I was in Atlanta
They are two roles that currently need to be filled
What is in studio and what is remote
And because they're only two people who can reasonably fill those roles
They have to do those jobs
With two rolls and two people there are only two possibilities of how to organize things
And they're both trash
In terms of
What option is having Alex and studio in Owen on the road
This is good because Alex is much much better is a broadcaster and he knows how to move the Prada
And he can say nothing passionately for an hour
The downside however is that Owen is not a draw
So you end up with really lackluster disappointing remote event
Even on his best day Owen can't get a crowd revved up like Alex
Alex is old-school on a bullhorn
And Alex
Pretender
The other option is what we have here where Owen isn't studio and Alex's on the road
The upshot here is that you probably get more compelling video from the rug
Cuz I was probably drunk
And he knows how to get People Pumped Up
More people are also gone
Show up
Naturally if Alex Jones is somewhere
Compared with Owen Shroyer is there
The large crowd you really need out
At the same time you run into problems with the show itself
Because I want
Just not that good at as a house
It's so goddamn boring
And I can't imagine he's moving
Any pills
He said something like we'll get back to the feeds of Alex & Allie in half an hour
And all I can think is wow here comes a shity half hour
This is a substitute teacher showing a movie
You know like is Alex
Yeah yelling into a bullhorn
And sometimes that movie stop
And you're like what do we do now that was play heads-up 7Up no
Let's listen to Owen talk forever
It's a tough situation if you're in charge of enforcing have to figure out how to assign roles
But if it were me
I would never have Alex out of Studio
He may draw a bigger crowd
But they're going to be a ton of people in Atlanta no matter what isn't as exciting as Alex
Combined with Allie Alexander and Nick Fuentes
End up not being as poorly attended as
The Caravan
You need Alex in studio for multiple reasons
The first is that he's the only person
An exciting enough to make this dumb show watchable and that's make people more likely to buy the pills
There's a financial reality that Alex is better for business
As the host
Then on top of that the whole point of Infowars right now is that shooting super dangerous
Antifa black lives matter or trying to kill all the
Conservative
Remember a few months ago Alex of the China and MS-13
15 duck with the Democrats
The takeout conservative talk show hosts
Legitimately
No
Narrative makes a lot more sense for me to imagine that Alex
Out-of-control stimuli data
To lean into this whole thing and make the studio feel like Alex's bunker
The whole point of his career supposed to be that he's the oracle
The only person in the world who can see directly through the globalist plan
But literal devil has been trying to enlist him since he was a child because the devil knew that Alex was special and he was a psychic
If you expect me to believe any of that
You have to
Check that person at all costs
The psychic who's the only person who knows what the globalist are going to do before they do is way too valuable to have out on the street yelling
Into a bullhorn with a couple of young enterprising bigots that's not the best military tax
No
Now that Infowars become something so comical and Hyper important
It's time for them to get right with the script
Alex is supposed to be this all import
Guru so you need to start acting like it
The Studio's already established as having guns everywhere and being super well-protected so Alex would only be making appearances
From there
When is the Young Gun the warrior in the fold
So he needs to be Alex's proxy on the streets
Willing to risk it all because he knows that his muscles and physical former all that he has to give to the infowar
Astro
I'm going to move on now because I'm getting lost in Flights of Fancy about the ideal directions reinforced to go in the future and again as we touch down at the beginning of the show
We keep coming up with better ideas for them and then they just don't do it I've got you
Beats by mile Harrison
Smith is like the
Smart research guy
F****** time you're on camera
You be peeking out from behind a comically large book
Really what are we doing here
Like why not
Bring Joe Biggs back in and I have him always have grease on him somewhere cuz he's like a mechanic time for something
I look like a monk
He's a monk in there
Fixing cars turn this into an episode of
That's what I want Danny DeVito should be hired
F****** like nothing that they say is real jet why not make all the characters actual fun characters
Christopher Lloyd could be involved
Alex
I know you're listening
I don't think you're listening
If you're listening
I will quit doing this show in order to
Produce
I've got you beat by tomorrow then and it's
I'll bring you in as a producer
It's easy
How
Can Alex
Be in both places at once
You ask yourself
Why are you wasting money on a f****** tank
When you could have a hologram
Yeah that's Harrison Smith comes with you
What's the little hologram Alex on the floor
He's got a fake bullhorn he does the whole thing remotely
Maybe just a little moonwalk
I assume that they're going to mix the Michael Jackson hologram with his to look a little bit but with a record you still need a record
Is time would still be strained that way for a while
IBEW.
About the 8th Friday
SoJO Spa
I could see it
Yeah I just think that there's intrinsic problems with people in the roles that they're in like they can do specific
6 things
To a certain level of competence
And unfortunately Alex can do multiple things
But the other people he had
Can't
Right
And the only way to really like
To maximize everybody
Skill sets
Is to have them all start playing
In order for this to Feel-Rite Alex can never be out of
Studio
I know that he wants to be and it is like I said is Free Willy natural environment to be up there yelling into a bullhorn
But that's not his
Is Play sign
I mean it's it is a little bit though that none of them really understand
Who they are because they all fit
Think that they're way better than who they are
You know like a reviewer associate
Is Lance Stephenson
They think
That they're f****** Kevin Durant
You're still late
San okay
You're going to blow
In LeBron's ear that's your job that's all you've got
You're not going to score 20 and night
It's just not going to happen
Batman
You're a dick
Play your role
It would be better I think for everybody
If they did play their roles
Totally
And
Thought it would be more funny
Play for me too
If everybody put it in that goes back
Everybody would have to have a base level of comp
What's that just simply does
Will it in Toto
Could if they focus
Everybody requires a base level of focus.
The reason that Owen probably hasn't gotten
Better at going out doing these Road thing is because he also has to do the Wardrobe
Yes do this against where these multiple hat
Obviously
If he spent all his time Focus
Sing on
Alright
How do we manipulate crowds
To the best of our belly
Is that shots work best in
Winfield pieces
He really studied his craft and really tried to hone that
He could be an amazing tool for Alex to use
While Alex is
The guru in studio
Doing what he does
If you had other employees
That he had just work
In specific areas
To be like
You are the person that I need
To cover text yet cuz I don't understand text stuff right
You Harris
If you have glasses you look like a dweeb
We need you to do that
Step into it to do with like Mike Adams whenever there's a health storywood
Ranger
You know this could be the reliable voice on that front
He needs that
He needs the people who fit
Cool are the tools
For the jobs that need to be done
Yeah but that would require Alec
What's to have any interest in in-house Talent Development which is
It seems he
Has strenuously avoided because I think he's trying to go for these cheap
Pops
Alexander Nix
Like all right you're trying
To capitalize on whatever audience
They already have
They're also using you
And it's not going to work out in any kind of long-run
Yeah it's it's
It's a bad strategy to keep giving him advice but yeah
You need to develop some Talent
It's too late probably has anybody he's had on camera in our entire time. Improve
Do you know what I'm saying like in terms of Isaac super greed
I mean other than other than a more increase
I suppose
Professionalism as opposed to be in like
Although at the same time he was like bucket and hammer and sickle or not
But I've been okay baby Millie Weaver but that's also
Just because the first time we saw her she was rainbow snatch and that's top
Yeah I know I don't think
There's a lot of proficiency in
Skill development going on
Add Infowars
Here's what I would say
Is one of the main problem
It's such a singular Alex Jones focused world that you have people like
Owen
Trying to host the show
And he's clearly trying to be Alex
I feel that
You got Democrats you know
I try not to yell
Screaming get f*****
Democrats are the most disingenuous
I've ever seen
And it's just so sad
That's just a bad Alex impression no kid one of his fake breakdowns with long pauses for dramatic effect
He's just doing the exact same thing that Alex does but
Come so far
Yeah it let way less believable
Needs to find his own lane his own voice
Like a comic doing someone else's delivery
Basically
Tragic because
You have stuff like that
And that just Falls
F****** flat
It goes to commercial
And Alex is back and he's doing s*** like this in your like Holy Chic you're running circles around people
Do you think something that flip over
Brian stelter
Working what are you going to do
What's everybody's
F****** dirigibles at Mama's watching everything whatever
You cut the Alexander
Disingenuous
God is in the blip shitted on all of his right now I mean what do you do with it like
Is like watching Michael Jordan.
Sit out here not your Horace Grant you're not even
Get the f*** out of here
Like kind of
Like I mean Alex is wrong and he's a monster but there is a part of me that like if he's frustrated with his staff
I get it
They're not good
He can do all of these things better than them
Hippie should be able to
It makes sense that he would be better but it's embarrassing the level is better
It is and he's doing a really bad job of fostering
The mentoring diabetic terms of
Whatever skills
They have
Not being a size
He told me it was created by the fact that I wanted
Just doing at Alex and pressure
Well I mean it's it's like a it's like Trump and his whole Administration
Enchanted psychic
I just
You bear the responsibility
For hiring
You do
That's part of your job
Yeah that's the administrative responsibilities
Not improving them or even seemingly attempted
Performance reviews in a lot of normal work environment
Buck stops there
In terms of
Pretending this is a chaotic environment
It's just
Just perform
Alex's
Just running circle
Just ate
Almost outrageous
Watching this episode
The diff
But you see
I want to give a round of applause
Remix Brian stelter is stalking a balloon
That's really funny
Not as good as a Dalek with a gun butt
No it's still good huh I do like the image though because I knock Euler
I see like the the Hindenburg level where it's a giant
When he's down in music
You f****** he's got a ships
Captain
Doing that whole thing looking out the window just leaning down to the like that motherfuker again he's bought the Hat
Alex wore on Halloween
Play Flight of the Valkyries while
Beside one of those
A sextant
I don't know
Well as we all do
Bread shelter only David
I mean like Alex is coming in with this
Like just
Dunking on ons
Brian stelter stalking me
And then
Like
He's so good at this that he's even doing commercials
From the road from god dammit
Georgia
Guidestone
Covering all this
Trying to stop
Cover all this
Is your financial support
T-shirt books
Film
Are these are the highest quality High
I really feel it
He just goes into a net
It's remarkable he even recognizes that probably Owens not doing a good enough job of pushing
Sing the product selling
Selling things to keep things afloat
So he knows that it's his job to not only
Go out there to draw a crowd to make the optic
Fix that they need
To push this argument that the people are demanding
Georgia flip
But he also needs to get on air and
Add pivot
To try and sell Palisade
It's
The weight of the weight of the Infowars is squarely on his shoulders I really don't understand
See that's the other thing that I do
How is Owen not-self inbred like
Just do you think he watches clips
Like what I was doing stand-up
Do you know I would listen to my sets over and over I would watch myself
Doucette's and I would critique my performance
You know he doesn't do any of that s***
Like what's the incentive
Exactly
I just I have
Good at your job I feel like that's a good
Incentive
I feel like I'm going to probably make a
A pretty decent argument that he's as good as he needs to be
He hasn't show on Infowars the top of the
Commercial
Conspiracy b*******
World like
In terms of that media sure it's a job
I'm get paid
You're on
Infowars about
But that's like somebody saying like a man
I have always dreamt of playing Triple-A ball and I made it and now I'm done
Why don't you want to don't you want to get to the show man come on
But the dark reality is for him this is the show
That's true
That is a
Cuz they like
For us we're looking at it so
You can work for a real outlet that would be like the equivalent to
The majors
But that's
That's not the way he looks at
Astro got the way the people in this room look at it
The only place to go up would maybe be Breitbart
Probably not even work for drugs but drugs is out-of-pocket now they can't do that
Play Anna maybe but that's kind of a lateral
Probably not
Their hosts are boring but in the
Different way they might want Owen but not Alex
Rebel media but then again that's another lateral though
Is about is bad
That's at the top of the mountain
That's really really really sad
Bunk'd
Yeah
I can't wait to have him
And to your question about like why doesn't Owen get better
One of the issues is whatever you accept becomes except
And if you can get away with just doing this
Why not always do this
I still sometimes like wake up in the middle of the night and I'm
Thinking about
It's that I've got
I've been like how can I improve those
I'm probably never going to do stand up again
There are stories
All across the nation
Including where I found this story today
Deep-diving this where the headline is
Black lady Goodwill Ambassador
Who hates white people with the headline
Should White Boys still be allowed to talk
That's in the
Dixon Dixon
Dicksonia
Addiction College
In Pennsylvania
Route to be racist against white people
Oh and did on this
This essay that Owen Sound
Today
Baby student newspaper at Dickens
Colleges with enrollment
Just over 2,400
It was written by a guest writer and it's obviously making the point that conversation and classes in the writers
Experience are dominated by white male voice
From yesterday
Quote in my time at Dickinson I've listen to probably hundreds of white boys talk
It feels incessant
From classes and lectures to the news and politics there's an endless line of white boys
Wait to share their opinions on the
The state of feminism in America
What does lgbtq plus population finally has an upright
The merits of capitalism Etc
The list of what white boys think they're qualified to talk about his endless
Something very few of them seem to understand is that informed uncritical opinions do not constitute
Truth
It's kind of funny actually because the essay itself
Explains why Owen being offended by this essay is nonsense
The second thing most white boys seem not to understand is that they do not exist separate from the rest of the world
You do not speak alone
You speak with the weight of every other white man who is spoken over a woman erased
Contributions of queer people from history
Or denigrated broken
English's
Know know when a black person does something all black people response
As we all know a white person is an individual and cannot be held against
Policies and laws meant to forever to find intelligence by how it measures
Is up to the Bros of America
As was made clear in the final paragraph of this essay this is about Black History Month
And how the writer doesn't approve of
Overvaluing
Particularly
22 the exclusion
Other quote
Buried or ignored voice
Speaking as a white boy I don't take any offense
At this perspective
The style of writing seems to me very intentionally to be confrontational because it's an opinion piece about how her perspective and
Her being relegated as being less important than others
The rhetorically at work
For the writing to be kind of brush
Stylistically sensible
Now that's somebody with a partner who teaches High School believe me
Boys talked
I don't I don't
Think like obviously this isn't
This person making the argument
Did white people
Should never be able to
The Talk
It's just that it's
The perspective of
Of
All this conversation on campus seems so much
About issues that are unrelated to their experience
To seem to
Take priority of president
About the other thing
I would say
Is that the
Headline of this
He's
Should white boys be allowed to
To talk and I know from my time
What I used to write for my campus paper
Generally
Editor's right the head
This person who wrote this article
Probably didn't write that
And she's being
Lambasted
The headline is more extreme than the actual
Article
I am trying to get more than you would make an extreme headline so people would grab them
Yeah yeah yeah
I don't know it so it's a willful misunderstanding of
The point that was being made in this student newspaper
Media did a cycle with this back in 2019 they already did that
Yearly thing
41 months
It wasn't last year who said it wasn't
It speaks volumes that Owen Shroyer decided to spend time on the show complaining about this
College Newspaper opinion
A form over a year-and-a-half ago
Cuz he wants to whine about how bad it is
Tough it's tough to be white just very sad
Just want to throw things
It's very
It's
It's remarkable
That length needs
To be gone to
Wood art
I bet the person who is
Furious
About
An op-ed piece in the student newspaper
That is
Thousands of miles away
Is the saddest
Very sad
Now we go back
Alex
Out there bullhorn
He's changed
Sure there's some stop the steel chance I'm going to do any Locker Outsider like lock her up never know I don't think there's any Locker ups that I heard
There's definitely some USA
If you agree
And then we get another surprise
Guest appearance
Let's go back to the state capitol in Atlanta he's outside now
With a big crowd bullhorn
Special session now
Enrique tarrio inter
The picture
With Alex and
Nick Fuentes
Real
Is the Washington generals
Conservative propagate
But so Alex is out there he's got this special session now champ going
And I've been pretty
Miano
A few sevigne my praise
For Alex out on the street and his ability to rile up a crowd
But here is the point where I have to point out that he is only
I need to not get any chance
Because things fizzle out a little bit
And so it goes back to him
And a little bit of a different
Let's go back live now Alex Jones on the
EPA
Who
Do you think he's trying to
I think he was
A long thing to chance
Well yeah yeah no it's not
Did I think he was
IPad
Like this Thursday
Did it's flat
Anymore
The rally is
Is over
It's true
Owen wants to make an analogy here you sit
Nice talking about these global
I don't like Bully
Steal your lunch
All right right
But they don't want you to talk about how they're bullying them because then people
Their analogies RC
Analogy
I try to make an allergy
You try
Can understand
Understand what I'm saying
I get it just in my head this makes sense or is this
Translating on air
If you're in the
High School
Lunch room
And there's a guy going around
Feeling everybody
This is weird
And then you're like hey
Steve over there
Has been going around stealing everybody's lunch money
I got to pause it real quick
Because
I didn't realize
The first time I listened through this
That he's imagining a scenario where this guy is stealthily
Steel
This is a high school Tik-Tok
High school bully cat burglar
Me
That can lead to violence against me
Well hold on a second
Back to the globalists are
That's the Democrats are
That's the mainstream media
They stole in your country they stolen your integrity
They stolen your reality they stolen
Everything
They stolen your future they stolen your children's future they stolen our education system
They have taken
Everything except the very breath
4 miles
And now they're coming for that too with a stupid
And so you just pulled that keep the breath in your mouth
You committed these crimes
You committed these atrocities
You're trying to make us a slave you were lying to us
You are dividing us
Doing it
You know what you deserve what's coming
Waiting for it
That's why they're so scared
Did you really think we wouldn't hate this on our fans
You really thought you could control the moms
No
That analogy that Owen used is not great but I think I get
The point
I want understands but his position in life and his career is to be a stochastic
Terrorist
And work really hard to inspire people to enact violence on his enemies
But he doesn't feel like he's wrong to do that
Because he's decided that is animes deserve it
Is imagined
That's not surprising
Here and honestly the thing the kind of runs underneath a lot of Infowars programming
But it's weird here Owen be so blunt about those feelings of wanting Bob viola
Yeah seems like a bad move
You guys stole everything and I want everybody to solve this problem and you deserve violence
I think we all know how it went
It seems like a really bad move particularly because we've done this enough times to know that
Should anything happen they'll call it a false flag
Also
It's almost impressive to me how much of that rant felt
Four star so bad
Ocean felt ungenuine but in a completely different way than
The falseness of Alex's outbursts
Alex's way over the
The top growling
Fake crying almost like a clowns take on
Performing an emotion
When Owen gets rolling
It feels way too much like he's thinking in his head
Alright now it's time to get intense
You could almost hear him trying to figure out what to talk about next
It's a really boring version of in
Sincerity and I just don't
Enjoy it that much as a style
I'm sorry to say this but his voice
Gets real whiny
Emma in the higher pitches he cracked
Texas voice gets real whiny and so his
He's in
Just doesn't sell it
I try not to be too critical on those kinds of
The fronts because I think the postman with a gold
Open Voice
Yeah but I also have you know.
Types
Emoting that I can do wear my voice
To folks as well
People don't hang out at
People don't have as much
Control over like
Tonal qualities of their voices they want
Understanding on that front
I mean
Just bored terms of be like
The things that are very easily
Controllable
You would think after four years you get a little bit better at fake
Getting an emotion
If your job is basically to
Create
And present emoji
But I mean if your job though as you see it is really just to do an Alex impression
You know that's
The problem
Fanfiction
About Trump
He's up to while he's hiding
Sure I just listened to this clip
Ask yourself how is this any different than what people online do with qanon
But you know what I think
What President Trump is doing right now is he's giving these people
The one last year
What he may have even given them
And just said you know what
I'm going to go away I'm going to be
Quiet
And you guys can
I can see this election
And
You can stop lying to the American people
And you can stop making deals with the Communist Chinese and stopped working for the UN in the World Health Organization
And let me be president
Or you can continue to take off the Americans
You can continue to
Take off the Republic
And all unleash this Beast
Island least it's cracking I'll let
This lion roar
And you can deal with that step
Cuz that's where this is going
Yeah it's a million Marchers in DC peacefully now
Yeah but
It's going to be thousands of people peacefully in Atlanta this weekend but let me
Me tell you
If you steal this election from us and you put in a u n
Communist
Corrupt criminal Joe Biden the White House it's not going to be a million piece will
Marchers in d.c.
Okay okay so if I'm is inaugurated we will kill
Fictitious imaginary scenario where Trump has given a deadline
For the globalist
Step back.
And stop pissing off the
The Patriots
Good guy
You have to give him that chance
To do the right
Thing
Oh this is where this idea
Bedouin is just creating out of his own
Stuff to do
Hey
Interesting
Thought because tails
In this next
Trump
And of course they're not
But she just like they have to have that
Metaphysical
Comfort
Just like they have to have that
Metaphysical comfort of
You accepting the Matthew accepting the vaccine
You accepting the Tyranny you inviting The Tyranny that gives them the metaphysical comfort knowing they didn't force it on you you accept
Trump
We have to have the same metaphysical
Comfort knowing that we
One last chance
DebtStoppers
Stop with the enslavement of mankind
Stop with the lies that you're telling mankind
Stop.
You can stop at all right now the censorship you're coming after all of us
And they won't do it
Even given the metaphysical opportunity now
Will be no excuses
Okay this is problem
Look for me on a couple levels
The preemptive justification
Asian / murder
Owen is telling the audience that wants Biden is president that means the audience's enemies have turned down this imaginary last
Chance the Trump is offering them
To give up their Wicked Ways
Can we talk to
To eat your neighbor but take comfort in the fact they deserve it
Cuz Trump
The function of the
Yep the second issue I have is with Owens understanding of Alex's bizarre moral system
Owen seems to think that it's about the globalist
Leading the field
Comfortable that they gave you a choice
But that's not what Alex believes
Alex believes there are literal Cosmic laws that even the devil cannot break that involve you not being able to act count
I heard someone else's free will
It's not that it's a comfort
To know you didn't force people to do something it's a belief system
Karma coming if you do
Chestatee
I worry that Alex
Mainata Feliz
Explain this whole system of how the cosmos work to Owen
Which is troubling
I get the sense that maybe what happened is that Alex got pretty drunk couple times and ramble did Owen about their sin
Elizabeth Comfort not be
The immutable laws of the universe
Why are you
Saying that you have to do the same thing as the Clone Wars
We'll see
Shouldn't you be like we don't have to do the globalist cuz we're not going was if you're saying we have to do the same thing as the globalist
You're actually Global it's not the same thing it just has sort of
Similarities
Like The Witcher
Globalist
Vert
Bear Lake
They have to
To trick you into doing something
That's
Deceitful
Trump this is straight-up
Cuz this isn't being like
Hey
Everybody knows everything
This is your last check
No he wouldn't
Be straight up if you sent that
He's doing these weird legal challenges to the globalist behind the scene
Oh okay
According to Owens imagination
Do you have a better chance you heard Owen
I did have you heard I would imagine this thing I apparently times to get it
I had my absolute acquiescence I guess
I think that this also highlights the other thing where Owen is doing a bad Alex impression like
Totally his version of Alex's stupid moral system isn't
Even more stupid and less
It's not interesting where is Malik
It seems like it's based on some kind of
Real f*****-up yeah
Belief system
I'm interested in unravel I'm not interested
Listening to Owen
Community
That nonsensical
Of course. He doesn't share it and I don't think he actually understand what Alex
Just trying to convey
But he is doing an hour to
Suppression and apparently
Mythology that
Nanavaty feels like he needs
Also included
It's just
Black tap
I was about ready to say f*** all this
But
Every time
I think I'm out
He pulls me back
Coming up in the next
Segment
We're going to be joined by Alex Jones and
Nick Fuentes
And apparently Alex has a big announcement that he is going to be making
And he really wants me to emphasize that so Alex is coming up
Huge announcement
Segment
I am not positive there is a huge announcement but when I hear that
That would be cool if he was like going to sacrifice Nick Fuentes 2
Did Trump in like eat his heart
Who's in public Alex has
Inclinations towards cannibalism
Alex eviscerated Nick Fuentes 1/8 his heart live on air
The only thing that I think is kind of
Live close to like maybe this is his huge announcement I don't know if I've heard
Birmingham before
Was he does
Say that the austro-hungarian empire did nothing wrong in the lead-up to World War 1
Issue for me it is about today
Cuz I don't think that and I got confused
Straight Talk
Braids on it
He said it's all the British
Sure that sounds right
Anyway
That's not his announcement
It could have been
Maybe it's that Nick Fuentes
The speech of the day
Best speech out there it in Atlanta
And I'm like I said he's
Just hits for 25 minutes but you hit
In the right direction and that is. Who are backing up drop
Again
Is
The guy who has a
The project is Project now seems to be focused
On being anti-gop
McConnell has said nothing
Nikki Haley said nothing
Print Shop Madison cawthorn
All the people hailed as the future of the GOP
Have remain silent
Well
People like myself
Open Alex
Patriots like you coming out
State capitals
A doing all the work
And fighting for this
Take the fight to them no matter what happens
And let's be clear
We know
China Joe's
The robot
When you got
Marco Rubio
A pirate
Crenshaw
Aldi's
Only fake pee
Julie Mall
Call Dish
They are literally worse
The man the enemy
Because they act like
Like they're with us
When they're really
Established
I mean it seems like this is the direction
That they will probably want to go next their targets
Like obviously you can always keep Soros and all that s*** in the back burner
But
Ineffective cowardly
Republicans in name only can be the new
Sue didn't support Trump in his hour of need
What guys
I agree with you they were lying to you the whole time
But in a different way than what you think
Relying differently than you
Like it would almost I wondered sometimes I wonder like what would happen if
The murdochs
Just like
One day we're like hey
We don't want everybody to be
So
We're just going to announce
Fox News has been lying to you this whole f****** time
It was alright DIA
We wanted to get you guys
To do the b******* that we wanted to
Now
We don't want you to K-Love
Someone would find some investor in new score
Conspiracy
I think that Alex is really into this too and I think
It's probably a really sound decision on his part
In terms of where to take
The rhetoric
Eyewear
To take the narratives
If you want to try and shift
Into some Direction
Going against
V
Ineffective
Turncoat Republican
Or whatever
He's probably going to be your best
Because then
You'll probably get a little bit of the slack
People on the road
Caring about what you're doing chores and you're attacking the people they don't like
You'll probably like less mean comments on Twitter or going
Be calm and
And you saw it exactly this model play out
With Nick Fuentes
That's when he started attacking
Turning Point
There was a lot of people who like a letter
Sunfire
Or there are a lot of people who are like haha look at this is Miss funny
And in the process
They passively or
Die amplifying and laughing
Them making
Funneh
Charlie Kirk
Eat it
Pushing and furthering Nick Fuentes
So I think
This is probably
If you were
Just trying to craft like what do we do next now that we know there's no chance shirt
This is going to work out it's probably a sound thing to do
Say going back to their terrible military strategy and then update it for for us here
When your enemies are in fighting
It is a bad idea to just let them
Watch or just watch it
That's when you destroyed both of
Can't allow them to regroup after
Defeating their inner power struggle in order to become even worse
Parts of it probably intren
During that inside
Then we saw that in
2009 onwards
The Tea Party
We are going to
To probably see that
I don't I don't know what you
You do like I don't know I don't like to talk about
Crushing
Because I think
But that's kind of
I don't know
Imagery and I'm not super into that
I don't know what you do to push back against
But I do agree with you like watching and laughing like haha they're destroying each other
Is not good
When one of the parties that is doing
The destroying is far more extreme
That's not to say hey we should defend him GOP
It's just that
Neither of those is a winning strategy
Do is what the right has always done so
Successfully to the left
In the center which is
Exacerbate whatever differ
Prince's they have
Force them to destroy each other instead of just
The right never sits back and watches us
Fight
Fair enough
The GOP
Which is what he said
Years ago
And then he said he had
And then
Trump dead
And now I guess they're doing
Sing it again
But
This is so lucky
Nick starts talking about is view of America
No
Cuts out
Exactly the right guy
We're taking over the party
We are the people we are the pop
Populist movement
Describe
The new Reich
Not well I call it America
Distinguishes us from
Is orange
Interpretation of what is America
America
Is the American people
It's not America as its economy it's not America
As its government
It's not going to talk
We are
Live right now we have Alex Jones and Nick
Wenches are
Transmission there are connection has been interrupted we will get
Imparted
If I were producer and I were watching this and I knew who Nick Fuentes what
Exactly
I'm not saying that's what happened it's not America the Republic
If you talk about what he believes the American people are
It's going
To become a little blunt what his beliefs are did hit the red button or anyting
Equally possible that their Tech issues just suck so much
If I were there I would have done exactly
Because I can't risk
Like
That game getting blown up
And a bridge waiting for them to be like
And we're going to
All the people with mental health issues and put them in the
Immigrants have to go
And okay
Well
Step
Anyway I thought that maybe that trucker strike
Nick was talking about was Joe
Just trying to rile up the
The crowd
It turns out he really
Is in support of this
Which is weird
It's weirder that Alex is to
Okay fuckout tell you I really like what I'm seeing with this trucker strike
If they're planning later this month
For a week
If the trucker strike
Especially on the East Coast shutdown
Thanks for shutting
You shut
You down and I should come to Georgia another state
I just drive around
The whole time
I'm calling for you
On Thursday Friday and Saturday here
At noon everyday
Drive
Around
The
Honking your
Horn
Nick is a child so I'm less interested in his political philosophy make
Incoherent sentence
Alex on the other hand should definitely not be in favor of a strike just
Because he likes
The goal of it
The means that's being used to achieve the goal is the withholding of Labor in an organized fashion
Which he totally hates
It's interesting and kind of ironic why this plan that Nick is so keen on would never work
The biggest reason is deregulation and Union Bus
Thing in the shipping and trucking
According to Snopes there used to be two million Truckers
Members of the teamster
So now there are only seven
Great the institutional power the trucker's had in the 70s from Banda
Getting together and keeping those Union strong has disappeared
Largely due to political influence
Hope people who naked Alex would be largely in agreement with
At least as far as labor issues go
There is often Big Talk
About truckers strike
Because it brings to mind
Complete shutdown of food
Distribution in the Myriad issues that come along with it
But the sad reality is that these strikes don't really end up having
Any real impact because they can
If you're a trucker and you want to strike are you going to get the
Teamsters to strike to install Trump as president
You really think that's going to work
That's probably never going
To happen so if you're working in a union shop
That's not going to be a strike that's going to be you quitting
If you're an independent
Penda truck or maybe you work for a smaller outfit
It's theoretically on board at this strike
You probably can't afford to do it
Because there's no protection
For you
You have no wait to throw around by withholding your labor
Since whoever is hiring
Could just hire somebody else
Does tomatoes need to get to Kansas
And you're on strike to install your fantasy
Great good for you
You're fired
And this other truck is going to get paid to haul those tomato
The only way this kind of strategy could work is ironically
If the world was exactly how Alex and Nick
Don't want it to
If the truckers union was strong and everyone in it could vote to stop work because they felt the elect
Action was stolen
You be super f***** up but they could make a pretty huge statement
The political movement
The Alex and Nick are apart of his actually insured
That this can never really happen
It is because it's clearly them being like well we would love unions if they agreed with us and for some reason week
Can't get unions to agree that we should destroy Union
Then I just don't get it
Honestly even if it did
Could possibly happen this idea
It doesn't matter on this day when this episode recorded November 18th
The guy who organized this strike
Called it off
Cool probably because it was an absurd idea that would only hurt the participants
Send a cheese literally nothing
Yeah I'm fascinated by this like
Application of their political beliefs though
Like I don't understand it believes are we will do anything to get what we want
So if that's
That's why it always
It gets to me whenever somebody's like
Mitch McConnell's hypocrite or any of that b*******
They're only political belief
Is here is the thing that I want
And I will do anything to get it
So there's no possible way for them to be hypocritical in this
I understand that you know I understand that
People like Mitch
McConnell
I know that Alex isn't any better but his brand is supposed to be that he's
And that
Just kind of weird to me that like
I get it
I don't get how you don't
I know right away Alex's traffic is way up
Because of course it because of course during these sorts of. Alex ends up getting
Much more traffic I think a lot of the time people want to see him drunk
Crying or something
There's a lot of potential for
Something a couple times
In the last
Last couple weeks
The traffic is way up and no one's buying it
Total characteristic of either artificial traffic
Or people tuning in to beat like
Aziz like traffic is so it would
Triple the size but people are buying anything and I just don't
We are seeing 45 times
Homicide
The Bible say don't know what
Sad
FBI
Restaurants sit down
They put CIA sticker
And I just want to know they're watching
Course we know
That you're helping
Died in the end of America
History peaceful
I'm good but it's not
Sterilizer
Are coming with 5G
I just remember
Unicron
Into the wind
You're destroying
You're destroying everything so I feel good about what I'm doing and I'm
You are
You don't stay
Campbell.
Two-faced God real
Wow
Wawa
That's antenna
Alex is traffic is way up and
The feds are following in the pudding
CIA
Stickers on his car and I'm confused as to why they would do
Is that a just a like
Gentle remote hey guys we're watching
Just to let you know
We can put a cigarette in your car anytime we want
I don't
Know if
The CIA isn't
Pranks
Kids
It certainly could be I mean I think or I could be people who used to like Alex and now decided he's a shill or
During the CIA we're going to label your car
I ain't worried didn't happen at all and Alex's imagine
These things are possible if what I think is not possible
Is the defect
The following him around Atlanta
To be going around and putting CIA stickers on Alexander
I don't know if they exist
So Alex gets in this next clip to what I
Pinkbike
Maybe possibly his big news but it just makes no sense that this would be the big news
We're here I've got
Big news I said the austro-hungarian empire
The freedom screen
Of those of us that were
Will go away justifications washer
Fighting
The fraudulent election
Deposition
Trump
Put a big
We're just getting started
So I guess
These big news is that
Trump isn't the
Which is not
Doesn't sound like news at all big hit in 2016 before Trump won the election
I was like listen here's the major victory for us
Step along the way
Yeah I don't know
If there was some sort of actual big news
It's not gotten
M2 at all
It's just that we'd keep on fighting
And what have you
Weird way but it's actually not that weird
Really revealing
What they've done is they've disenfranchise 70
3 million Trump
The president gained 10 million voters but
Between 2016 and
There's more Trump supporters than ever
Is more patriots than ever
Dinnerware of globalism
The idea that stealing the election
From us
Canceling our vote
In disenfranchising 70 some million people
There we go away after all of that if they just
Through you know they speed through the process they see Joe Biden
We just disappear Into Thin Air
Losing an election is not the same thing as being just
Franchise
But this is actually a really neat Moment of clarity for Nick
Because it is the same thing to him
He believes that he's entitled to win everything
Dang Weatherby do to the color of his
Scanner is radical
Catholicism
This is the same mentality
You hear in that tape of Richard Spencer Milo
In his rant
Spencer said quote
Like this is never over
I win they f****** lose that's how the world f****** work
Little f******
Kay's
Weed
They get Rules by people like me
My ancestors f****** in
Enslave those little pieces of f******
I Ruled the f****** world
Those pieces of f***
Kinship get ruled over ruled by people like me
They look up and see a face like mine looking down at them
Who's audio was allegedly recorded the day after the unite the right rally in 2017
Teen witch
Nick Fuentes
Pardon
It's not hard to understand that underneath whatever slick presentation
Kinfolks like Nick have that Rage of entitlement
Is just below the surface
It makes total sense for him to claim that losing an election is disenfranchising his side because he's entitled to
What do you ever think that all the people who voted for Hillary and 20
SeaWorld disenfranchised
No course
Cuz they're entitled to lose to someone like him there globally
And they're evil and they should be the lie I know it's very very f*****-up
Exactly what they
Yeah they want a while I mean if you want a homogenous Nation
The idea that
Losing an election is false
Possible is kind of silly
True
And I mean like
He's not going to be pressed on this on Infowars cuz Alex doesn't want to open up this box of worms butt
I mean he believes that people who have like immigrated
Here
Shouldn't vote
And stop knick-knack I have a couple of quick questions for you
Do you want a white Nation
Wow okay
Follow-up question
Have you ever heard of what happens to people who don't have quote
Pureblood
In a white Nation
I've heard
I've heard you are heard what happens to people who do not have
Sore blood
That's a point that comes up in a number of discussion
That he's had that
I'm seeing the point about his last name being Fuentes
I don't know I don't really deal with that
Now anyway
I think it's interesting
This is all very revealing
This the conversation that they're having
Whether it be
Owen being like
Yeah my violin
Okay
Trump gave them an ephemeral chance that they had no idea what's happening
Because he put it in a quart
Filing Fleury said that
Demons were flying in from Stargates to s*** on our shoes
All of their specific point
It's the third making about
These are the various States
Nonsense
Nick is just
Talking about
Taking over the GOP
Probably is the most singular Focus
And I don't know if he actually believes this or he knows that Alex
It's believed that
And therefore it's best
Play into Alex's believes that he's presenting himself as also
Fighting the literal devil
Spiritual war
You know don't forget it's not about
On some level even
Looking to Democrats
Globalism people although it is in some sense
It is about
The rulers and the principal
Of other Realm
Evil vs. good
So I don't know if Nick actually believes that if he's doing the
This to manipulate Alex either is possible
But also use the Republicans Or democrats
Globalist
Scorpio
Economy there
Stream he's genuinely one of those
Truly terrifying cycle
You know
Like he's he's a guy who provides you
I would say that ninety-nine percent of the people
In the world you can act
The reason
But guys like nipple
Hazard that argument for like
You can't talk to this
Either terrifying psychopath
What can only be handled by a larger power
Federal
Obviously a level of something
Somebody needs to step in because this isn't a like one-on-one
Conversation that you can have with Nick later if you were someone in his life you might want to try and let get him help
Get me like a couple months ago he got he posted a video of him going to lie
Electro love black lives matter protest
Larry like I had one of his friends had assignments
But I can't read
Yeah like parroting I can't breathe these the type of person who does s*** like
It's just like you take the political stuff out of it take the
Take anything out of it
It's just
Antisocial
Disgusting Behavior
And
I don't know
Anyway
I think it we saw a little bit if that's seapak
Appearance
Is sort of
Continuing
It's not been as
Consistent or direct
As it appeared it might be
I was kind of trying to
Usurping a little bit a little bit
He's taking up a mantle
Call here as more of a
Actual leader
Malik
And that's kind of scary but also like what are you going to lead
Alex's
Kingdom is a loser
Really exist
The thing that I was
Wondering what you want to be the next Owen Shroyer good luck I mean we saw this on his ambition is clearly
Fallout pie
Yahweh way higher than being a second-in-command
Kind of why I receive project involves
Using Infowars
Not being a part of it is almost even embarrassed that they are
The sort of people he has to
As soon as he gets outside of their level he's not
He's not a ladder up guy
What was the what was the name of the event that they wanted the RNC
Remember
Went out got super drunk and couldn't
Yeah
Really drunk and peed on a tree
Spell good time
No it back whenever Fuentes
Showed up and
And clearly stole the show from him
Like even then my first thought is like
Alex Bisson
Not somebody that you can
Use
This is somebody you should watch out
This is somebody who's gunning
For you and
And if you can't see that
You're insane.
You know
Yeah but Alex and him can co-exist as long as he follows Nick
Yeah like I said
It's big next season
The next project
Is destroying the GOP
Do you want then
Extremist tea party will
Then the two of them couldn't have,
Macaws and coexist perfectly fine
It's just
Wants
Nick when Tyson is like larger project
Leaning towards Catholic fascism
It becomes more apparent that's where he metallic
What's my come to loggerheads
Yes but that's
See that's the thing though if you're Alex
You have to see Nick Fuentes and realize tooth
It's it
He's never going to bend to you
That's never going to have
And two there's only two ways that go
You been to him
Or he
Those are the only option
And when he's gone
But he disappears haha
He's planning something against you what don't you understand about who
People who their friends are
Everybody who's run afoul of Rodger Stone Rodger stone is tried to destroy
You don't think you sent me that you think he's going to be like well I have some sentimental
Metallic friends with Larry klayman
We saw that
Exactly it's not don't
Don't
Get involved
Seems like
I mean like just
Quite frankly
Switch
IntelliJ
Able to
Guess yes razor Focus
Nazi General Lee with people who are in the Infowars here
Like obviously I agree with you if I were Alex I would be terrified of him
And work
Trying to destroy
Either that or pretend he doesn't
Toto
Because
Knickers
Fairly popular in these right-wing worlds he has
I do know whatever amount of juice that he doesn't grow pers
And stuff and Alex wants a piece
It's just so weird to be watching a
Greek tragedy happen and not have them
Like
If you're watching a play and you're watching a Greek tragedy or like man those characters have no idea what's coming
Well here's where I would take issue with that
It's the same thing with me saying that like Alex should only be in studio in owensby is proxy
Is what they should do and what it could play out
Can be disappointing when it doesn't
You looking at this as a Greek tragedy
Is also probably not how it's
Going to play out it'll probably drink
Interesting
Then it is
Cuz people develop
Open people change over time
And honestly I think the most likely thing
What's going to happen
Is
That
Alex
And Nick
Will have
Some sort of in a lion
And be able to work together
Attacking the GOP
And then
I don't know
Nick can't help himself
He's also a f****** extreme Troll he's alone is going to do something that ends up
Getting him
Kicked off whatever streaming platform he's been relegated to now
Or whatever
You can't not push the envelope
Estrella
Be some sort of
An extremist voice
Next next
George Lincoln Rockwell or some s***
Yeah probably
I just he's just one of those guys who it seems like
Speakeasies that like
Dark
Candidate in the GOP that they
Cannot see,
You know that we just don't see him coming
Completely different people now and then Nick tortoises are they realize their Nick Fuentes
I don't I don't think I do I do that
Writing a supervillain story
We're only a s*** hat
Like a really dangerous s*** head
We have a couple last Clips here
And just a little little chicken on how Alex's operation
Is going
He did a money bomb a little while ago
You made a lot of money from that
But then he also decided to send
The tank across the
East Coast
So that was a bad idea from
And then he's been flying all over the place and he goes like a large security detail
And then also has two
The broadcast remotely
Apparently this hasn't been a great idea
Break
Growth
Madonna
What we caulk Snow crew
Like why bother products
Infowarsstore.com
Are more cruel to be able to
The Beyond
He can't afford to do the nightly show now
Just canceled it for a week
He'll be back
In Austin
Like Manpower
Will be able to be moved that that's it
Then
Operation there is like no
If there's no one else to run the board
You can't afford to pay someone I don't know 20 bucks an hour or something
That you can't get someone on it like some freelance person
Wow guess not if that is the difference
It's between like
I like
We have the money for it we don't
That's a
That is a razor real bad
That's real bad I don't know if that's
Actually true or not
Assume that it's just
It's not worth it
I would oigi that would probably make
The most sense to
And it turns out it was between that cancel the nightly show
Get rid of David
I just we don't
The forces
Run the show
Infowars my shoulder
The day the War Room
Which was it
Tacos way
Force.com is it real
12 round
Infowarsstore.com
Great products big syllabi
Jon rappoport no more fake news
I'm taking over
God bless you all see it in Georgia
State Capitol
Oh
Watch out
It takes zero for us to suddenly just
Start jamming a little bit
Totally that is total
I have no problem
Confident to the staying power of my organization and I had to
Fire someone
Weatherby the nightly show or beloved David Knight hey you know what we don't get money by be gone
The f*** out of here
Anyway here's
The show
Very very
They just heard us maybe I should have learned long ago and learned fairly read
At face value with Alex's Financial
Financial talks
Meme something about everybody
I don't know but
If the nightly shows canceled for a week because Alex is in Georgia
That does not itch
Byron cop
Put into terms of
Mini trampoline just sucks
I mean she does
Yeah they like Deanna
You suck
Yeah we need to find a character for her I'm not sure what I haven't watched enough of her to really know what character she would show
Giant ad
Anyway that Owen as
The proxy on the street
The mechanic monochromatic snack
I see what you did there
Thank you know
No there's nothing better
When making a little joke and having somebody say
I see what you did there
I just don't think that that conception of a character was any good
The parody of the social justice Warrior
Archetype or whatever
They had no legs
Even a good performer couldn't
Nepal that off
Such a bad idea
I don't know
Whatever we'll see what happens anyway I was a little disappointed by Alex in Georgia
Just as a whole I think
It was refreshing
To hear him yelling in a bullhorn and people yelling back
Getting people excited
But you also notice once
You watch enough of it that it's like this is really OneNote
It's just that over and over again yelling the same catchphrases the same sort of
A little blurb
You want to fight you better get her done
Where is on it away that like you shouldn't be in Georgia for multiple days
You should just be there
Frosting
And then get back to
To the f****** Studio where you're needed
You know
It didn't work out
No Georgia
And this is coming out on Monday
So we'll know for sure near the surface
Application status
But
Oh I'm sorry I mean with Misha
Earlier
And I don't know I just
I think this is going to fizzle
And they're going to need
Define themselves on more solid ground
It appears to me that's all that ground if they're smart
Is
A new Tea Party
Attacking the GOP
Yeah
CC
What's up
We're also on
We are on Twitter is at knowledge underscore fight it at go to bed Jordan
We are on Facebook
People doing God's
But until then
Clerk
Find the juiciest ice
Alex
Birthstone colors