Damn important
I have great respect for its knowledge B
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Alex Jones
From The Grapes areas of the world that are
Not America
Yeah I got a nice package Z in the mail bag from Over the UK
Oh my God
What so much candy
I don't see a goddamn.
Because I tried to the last one but came in another package to someone overseas and they were so terrible
Your form of Sharon Kennedy
Candy is literally like
I picked out all the jellybeans I don't like it I gave the detective all the licorice one
The problem is I see a Jordan is that I go pick up the mail sure if there's candy in it you're not
Not here when I open it up block
Would you open the candy
Between you and me you getting together that's 72 hours yeah I'm not going to survive that candy like and I I'm ready to
Really close to ready to say that the UK might have some of the best chocolates
And candies
All of the things that have been sent for sure Canada's pretty strong to
But in terms of the ones that I've had I've I think I act like I got to move to London
Oh well reconstruct allowed to do different ship to American chocolate
Can we have some good day
Good chocolate options weird but put option
Superman
Some of these
God just a crunch
Cheese so good
Nothing will ever beat the reefs
Reese's peanut butter eggs
It's simply impossible to get food ratio Perfect Day Out
So do we got that
And I I'm sorry that I ate all the candy that is what it is
Wine gums
You and your partner in July
Also got to this nice package from employment list Eddie and government goat
Gotay
Gia ute
Norway out of the Socialist Democratic monarchy of Norway
Got to go do a couple novelty beverages
Currently drinking a Nordic raspberry hard seltzer
Yeah yeah scream in Norwegian apparently it's very very good it's from eager Brewery or whatever
What's that letters that are connected to each other to do that
You know that letter
60 sounds like this
Brewery
I got a couple also if not alcoholic Seltzer's I've not had a chance
Have to dip into those
And then
So chocolate
Nosey
You know what's that
Bugle
Near the bugles
Did you put on your fingers to look like a witch
Yeah if you want
Got a bag of those covered in chocolate
Norwalk
Law here from this this note
Socialized Healthcare a functioning
Herman Tandoor
A secular society of Fairly decent-looking folks who spend their days eating babies worth
Incubating heinous atrocities against culinary science
Through their national dish
Alright
Maybe accurate based on the negative chocolate-covered bugles
Anyway I'm not trying to be great. Thank you to all our International
Sounds delicious
I really have a brain
Right spot so much as maybe a silver lining
As you know my aunt
Died earlier this year she did the the old Mortal coil
Sure if you recall
Perry and Walter Payton
Okay I know I know the Joker Megan Superbowl shuffle right
So
D-Day as I call it was
Was always her holiday like
Chico signed
But when I went to college the first time
Of my many John
My parents had terrible credit
The time
And she co-signed on my first student loan
And literally at that time she was like
And you're never going to miss
Today ever again are you
And yeah and the black male artist
That kind of thing is also deadly serious
The drawings of your hand as a turkey
Exactly exactly
So yeah so
This is a rough is the first
The first one without her so it's a little bit rough but
I was reflecting on it
And
I think my silver lining is that
I have no regret
Let's go there a lot of situations where you could lose a loved one and you regret something like I wish I had done this before
Before and all that stuff and I have no regrets
Whatsoever
Maya and I I just had a solid relationship and I
I'm terribly sad that it's over but
A lot of people don't get that luxury of like her everything went
Kum & Go I mean hey look
It's a bummer that you're talking about a loved one is no longer here
Pretty amazing thing to be able to feel that way
It really is that's about as uplifting as you can get when your tux
What's worse is oh because I didn't get to I didn't get the chance to say goodbye
Tonight I was going to go see her and
Do that whole stuff she she died
But
I was even thinking about that was like I said regret that I didn't get to say goodbye
And then I was remembering when my grandfather died her dad
We were at the nursing home as it was just watching him he took him like a year to die
And she literally turn to me and she's like
I would rather die than let people see me like this
What up man
Turn out the door.
Put on her head out to wet
She got her wish live the way she died
Great
Well I've been Silver Lining Happy Thanksgiving
Celebrate Thanksgiving
The imagery around it is nice tan assertive
Colonialist
Smith and all this complaints
About the holiday
But at the end of the day ultimately what it is about is if you wanted to be as about being grateful
I think that's certainly
If you take the time to reflect we have a lot to be grateful
Before
And not just
Weird
Things you can
Eat or drink from overseas
It's just great is his great-nephew a very wonderful
Not being able to reflect on those things everybody
Who is made
So many things for us to be grateful
Yes we are we are very very grateful
Fermenting
I am not grateful to
Alexander Emerick Joe motherfuker
Running things again
Took Jordan today we're going to talk about him
I know that's a shop
November 22nd
24th 2020
Dan this is 20/20
Back away from that I'm going to start saying god dammit again
View
I give it a shot bottle back and forth
Sorry there's a
We're reporting this a little later than we normally do any pushback recording
And there's a very specific reason
And I think that you will immediately
We know what it is
And I would like for you to yell bingo
Not now later
Whatever you think
You have discovered why we were reportedly
Alright okay
So we'll get down to business on this episode where before we do the take little moments say thank you some folks who signed up and exporting show
That's great idea first
Nicholas C
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Thank you so much you're now about his walk
I'm a policy wonk
Exegete
Thank you so much
Stan the Bold
Text daughter snow
Next moose work thank you so much you are now taking Jordan
I love you
Thank you very much
Do all of whatever that
Wiser
Lyrics thank you so much you are now
Thank you so much you are now attacking
Heroin
Freakishly large
Listen to thicken a outdoor the show
When you can do that by going to a website
60 day you know a kind of thing you need
To do Auntie day be generous and care for the
Need to get
Okay
I was going to start reciting the lyrics to all my rowdy friends are coming over tonight cuz there's a football holiday
Not really a football guy
No
Cold
Cold turkey
Okay turkey not good for
A couple of out of context drops
Which would you like to go for
Okay
Incorrect
I'll just start with this
Made flight
Okay that's how bad how bad that's good amount
Apropos of nothing
Thinking of people get confused that he was talking about the Smurfs to make sure
Now I hear this is actually very exciting just makes out of contacts drop does not make
They had no place in the episode but it's very exciting
Because it's something that I hope
So badly that Alex
Continues by Celtic
5 unit 5 Miller mustaches
Which Avenue
Who singer
Hitler mustache
I would love it
I think if you're on the scale at all
It's not great
Way2go
22nd and Alex is still the Kong
Voter fraud powerful people who are on his side
Ladies and gentlemen the head of the Federal Election Commission
Against President Trump head against the American people
Is
Coming
The current head of the Federal Election Commission is a fella by the name of James Trainor
And he's a bit of a kook
Busy Council for
2016 campaign and it is nomination hearing
Would not commit to a blanket recusal from matters involving the president if he's confirmed the federal election
Commission I imagine prior to that he was a used car salesman
Pretty cool stuff
Then you got to admire guy who says in their job interview they're straight-up not going to commit to doing their job
Excuse me what the Constitution know
He was confirmed in May of this year after his nomination stalled in Congress for a few years
49430 Don Street
Party lines
James Traynor is not a great dude
He made headlines earlier this year when he didn't interview with church millet
Compare the 2020
Listen to quotes spiritual warfare
He also claimed that religious leaders were tax
Exemption feel free to tell their congregants who to vote for since Trump release an executive order indicating that he wasn't interested in enforcing
Emily Johnson Amendment
Trainer said quote
The Bishops are using their nonprofit
Status as a shield to hide behind from having to make a decision about who to support
And to come out publicly
Bishop's we should have it
Inform conscious when we go vote
But they never really take that next step and say gears who's meets the criteria oh boy
In that interview he also made clear that he believes that the separation of church and state is a quote
Fallacy
He elaborated quote
It was John Adams it said the Constitution presupposes a Christian moral people
Which means you have to have that underlying principle in order for the Constitution
The function and work properly
What we see going on around the world is complete Anarchy in places where the rule of law has been completely abrogated
So it is a spiritual war that is striking at the underlying foundations of our constitutional republic
Getting rid of the Christian moral principles that are the basis
The foundation of a country
What important things
Point out is that John Adams and is 1798 letter said that quote our constitution
It was made only for a moral and religious
Just people
It's wholly inadequate
To the government of any other
Text James Traynor who's adding the word
Christian
John Adams wasn't saying that the constitution was only for Christians
You just had a philosophy that morality itself relied on religion because that's an appealing shortcut to A procession
This quote is used and misused by Christian zealot
To argue that this is a fundamentally Christian country
And even somebody go on to
This suggests that the Constitution and the rights protected by it
These people are f*****-up dangerous cultist
That's fun to realize that they had of the Federal Election Commission is one such person
Also two years prior to writing that letter
Adams have been part of signing the signing the Treaty of the AAA
Which was meant to establish commercial relations between the United States and Libya
Article 11 of that treaty presented by John Adams to be ratified by Congress begins quote
The government of the United States of America is not in any sense founded on the Christian religion
Weird
Trainers, the voter fraud came up in an interview with Newsmax
Where you was just complaining about the same stuff Trump's campaign is talking about in Pennsylvania
Where they believe that unless their pool water is get as close as possible to the vote counters
Then there must be fraud going on
He said quote
I do believe there is voter fraud taking place in these places
Otherwise they would allow observations to go in
This is a pretty standard bulshit artist act
They can all just lay this out for you how this works on a very basic
Sicklerville
Here's how it starts
You allege that there's some problem going on
And if gays vote
Speeding fraudulently count it
You have no proof that this is happening and it almost certainly is not happening but you need people to believe that it is
You insisted this is a major problem and then you propose a solution to this problem that you know will not be accepted
In this case it's the Supreme Court of Pennsylvania mandating howdy Philadelphia Board of Elections
Carries out there Alexa
You know that your demand is going to be thrown out because the complaint is frivolous and the remedy would require the infringing of elope
Kalady on its ability to run its own elect
It's certain to be reject
But that's good
You didn't want the complaint to be accepted anyway
If the complaint had been accepted them things don't change at all
The poll Watchers are a couple feet closer and you probably slow down the process or try to make a scene out of something
But it's not like you're going to find any actual fraud
What works so much better is it
The complaint being thrown out
Because then you get to go round it in system must be a cover-up going on or else your poll Watchers would be allowed to do basically the
Counting themselves
You don't actually want the poll Watchers to get closer you want that requested be rejected so your surrogate
You can then create the appearance of Suspicion
Everyone engaged in this knows exactly that this
This is the game
It's just outrageously tragic to see that someone
So transparently Craven
Could ever find themselves in the position of being the chair of Fe
DC is a real bummer
Yeah are you I mentioned it
At the very least some of these
I douchebag Republicans
In government must be like
You know when we hook
Our wagons
Insta Fox News 20 years ago
We thought we were going to be able to
The direct the mob
And we wouldn't allow them into power
But now the facc
Guy said we should start a holy war in the 15th century
I don't think that's okay
We got beat by Fox News
Even Charles Koch is going around saying who
Whoops my bad guys didn't mean to destroy democracy just
Wanted to make a s*** ton of money and kill people why is that wrong
Whoops
Anyway Alex's straight-up he's a real cool guy and he wants you to know that if
F****** tell you
Would you tell you upfront
Selection
Completely honest about it
Make stuff up
Hollister
The Sun the wrestler scumbags
Lakeshore
Sure it is
I would love to
CFA played out like
Months of him being like they're going to steal the election and then by Monday you know what I got to be honest I didn't steal this one
Can you imagine how long we spent listening to him safe
The only way is a fair election is if Trump wins for him to send me like guys
I got to be honest
This was a fair one I would be mad at him I got to be
I have nothing if I don't have my integrity
And I have to tell you I'm eating crow on this one.
Iris.
If Rodger Stone just comes out now and he's like guys I
I did my research
This is a fair election
Bikini block
That's what's so funny
Talking about that
But he did
Oh yeah
There is that you proved
The Supreme Court though
They may be making moves
Okay in order to make sure the Trump actually does get in
Unprecedented
Kman
Change
Key Battleground States
Supreme Court Justices were over what
Who will be ruling on
What cases to take from a circuit
You will have control of those ruling
The FasTrak
But Gorsuch
And they put
Thomas
Barrett
They put a towel
And they put cabin all over
Ford
So they are la
A major signal
They see the fraud
So there is a new Supreme Court justice so it's not at all surprising that there would be a new split of Circuit Court assignment
This is unprecedented
The f*** he's talking about
This is not
Some weird thing where they you know this
This brim Court Justice rules over all of their assigned circuit
And as far as I can tell this is just been really
Overblown by people in the nonsense Alex Jones kind of world did she weigh
Some kind of sign
There's an elaborate plan on folding a where it smells a lot like you and Archie
It's all very selective to like
You can say that Kavanaugh is over the six
Circuit which include
Michigan
Clarence Thomas's over the 11th
Which includes Georgia
But for this to make sense you have to ignore certain facts
Like for instance part of Alex's stopping the steel tour 2020 was going to Arizona which is in the 9th circuit on
Elena Kagan
Weird
That's not part of his
Block of trump lovers Arizona
So is the state that Alex really does need to
The flip in order to make his
Stuff work mathematically sure he pointed out
Listen to Samuel Alito
Right
Look I don't know this is just silly it it seems like someone grasping at straws and I'm just not so into it
Which is also literally how they could have picked these judicial
Circuit
I'm not interested in talking about this cuz there's bigger things
Sure to go on
Like to know what motivates
Joe Biden and Kamala Harris
Joe Biden
Because they want one thing status and money
I don't want to ride to thing
Joe Biden Kamala are known as
Put me on private jets
Give me money
Get me palaces
Give me caviar
Jimmy sax
Get drugs
Want
Annie
Mama Harris
And Joe Biden are about to release an album
Palliative
The Carter 3 what's happening right now
Step
Little Joe Biden on the streets he's always just like oh yeah you want something give me a pallet
2 Chainz is president now
Tax rate of people individuals making over $500,000 a year I am fascinated
The streets Joe Biden and Kamala Harris private jet
Really
That's pretty awesome
I do like I do like the just
That's just
Throwing that out there way.
Why not just throw that out there yeah vitamin, Kamala Harris looking rappers
Extravagant
Cartoonish pictures of
So Alex gets a talking about these are these Trump suits that have been thrown out in in Pennsylvania
Something to say about this judge
And
Money
Power Heaven are powerful
We're being lied to
Obama judge
That we knew
What's going
Without even looking
The evidence
In Pennsylvania
Lawyer said if what
I said
To be clear Alex and his audience may not know this but the president doesn't appoint state supreme court justices
38 states where is in 12 other states
Other methods are used epicly gubernatorial appointment or selection by the legislature
I guess the three states most relevant to Alex's hopes for a trump win our Pennsylvania Georgia and Michigan
And all three of them are states where the Supreme Court Justices are elect
There's no such thing as an Obama judge
Johnny Supreme Court
Unless you just Define anyone who disagrees with you is an Obama judge it seems to be what Alex is doing
Think about it
No s***
No not at all
Alex has also been using this visit Lestrange in
Between place
And he seems to be on this Sunday episode this this November 22nd
Seems to be really leaning pretty hard into doomsday preaching
You're going to be at a point where cast
The children you know
By Age 5
Dying
You're going to witness total extermination
Finally meet God
In your mind
Or you will get on your knees the state
Will go through the fire
No one will escape
Not me not you not anybody
It's pretty harsh
There's a lot of Doom talk
Half of the five-year-old's I know or half of all five year old
I think everyone
Yeah not just
You not just Jordan
Cuz if I got to
To pick we'll see
I don't know any five-year-olds
I don't think I know anybody roll.
You know we're not going to have to deal with it
The plague of the firstborn
Is not so bad if you don't have kids
Minute stuff cuz you still care about your neighbors or families short out
Oh yeah it's just very dark to be thinking that everybody's fuct
Bill Cooper's book was called behold apparel
Pale Horse
And he starts talking about that Bible verse
Looked and behold
Ashen horse
And who sat upon his name was death
Hades
A following with him
Kill the sword
Salmon
Horse
Who is the spiritual
Valentino
Now you see it
Theater Willmar
Used to have the G7 he is
The last
The Gate of gates
Executor
He will kill you and your family please.
You will die
Wow
Shadowgate
I want
A concrete
Job for Bill Gates I feel like either he's constantly jockeying for and winning / losing position
I think Alex might be making up a lot of making it up
Because you wouldn't have time to readjust to those shift in position like
How often
Has been in
Jobs I've had internal changes in position different department
Groupon I was into a couple of different places
You lose about a week of productivity hourly
Get reactivated the new workflow the new responsibilities moved our manager to this team and this team is
Run a different way using Salesforce a different way the f*** is going on
Yeah Bill Gates
Could never be like a middleman and then
One of the Council of twelve and now he's running the g702
Also rise upon the Pale Horse
This whole time has been like
Biding his time
Nino
No no
No no look
The Pale Horse has a few Riders
Amanda was like a buddy
Was up there before
Twilight Zone episode You Killed Jeff you become death
I got you
Alex is not only talking about heroin
And I am Bill Gates
Drive to tell her to tell you about how much
Everyone loves him and owl calls
The last 3 days
From
Major world leaders
The biggest people in Mania
All of the same thing they said Jones
We going to dinner parties are leaving Hollywood party
Everyone loves you now
Everyone's asking about you
It's not about me
The resistance
People are awake
I just been so right for so long without everyone loves me man I keep getting
Phone calls about how they talk about me wow
Wow
Alex it's the ghosts of Nelson Mandela
We love you in heaven going to be invited this sounds like a f****** bragging
15 being like man I just talked to somebody famous you like I'm 15 I don't care
My uncle knows Shaq
It doesn't raise your status
Tablet
Yes
I don't believe that anybody called Alex
I don't believe it
I don't believe that people are talking about about
Even if all of that was true it still wouldn't matter
Because I imagine the real world version of
I feel like we will be more popular and Famous
Sooner or later someone would be good be like
Hey did you know there's a podcast about him can you believe these two dick holding Chicago make this guy listenable
Oh okay
Hypethetic
Yes Brian stelter calls says everybody loves him @msnbc what hap
Think Alex
Critique his appearance on the phone Alex tell them he looks weird
Facebook
I got
Southern elevator that I love
Here
Likes we love you
You look like a pedophile
Tell the truth all right you're right like a clown demon
This is why we love you Alex your integrity shines through
Don Rickles
Yahoo
Soap
Is the globalist
Don't have children
And I haven't heard him bring that up in a while cuz excited for it to come back
Post
Human systems
I told somebody smokes after
All of them
Metaphysical
Ancestors of the future is just like
Alex loves this talking point which is nonsense sooner like that the idea that the globalists have children
Who's the lead globalist in the US right now and Alex knows better than anyone that has at least one son so don't Can't Stop
Complaining about it
The Pale Horse is the globalist the top of the rotation
Actually horse
To have more than one person inside the horse costume that he still has one extra kid
Horse costume
I don't know about that
Klaus Schwab the head of the world economic Forum in the author of The Great reset that's another guy that Alex is really
Going on and on about these days
He has to
This is so dumb and Alex says it all the time not because it's true but because it underscores an important piece of his cosmology
There's something inherently suspicious or wrong about people who don't view reproducing the most important
Piece of light
This isn't about the globalist
Having kids or not having kids
He's literally a talking point
Just to throw out
To make you feel like you need to have kids and there's nothing wrong if you don't
Probably like her
Part of the grape
Replacements
Bulshit that they all believe in where it's like
Hayward
White people have to have more kids
It could be that kind
And if you could be adjacent to that believe all that s*** you know
Might be
So Alex goes onto I talk about here how he's ready to die
Ready to die February 4th
The truth
I think it's a
I'll leave it up to you to decide whether
Ready to die
Imprisoned
Because I realized I
I can't sign on
I'm not in the persecution I'm not into
Much as I going to get me
Dip so short
Jesus Christ
I wish we could have stopped this
We can't
We're going to get hurt
Deserve
So again we're on this doom doom to appear on this this episode
I don't think I was sincere
Really
But here's my thought here's what I want to discuss sure
Alex says he's like persecution fantasy or he's like William Wallace
Like
Torture didn't like his last words afraid
I want to I want to ask you do you think of
He wants to make his I'd be willing to do anything for the
The truth
Would he be willing to live in obscurity and poverty
Oh absolutely for the truth
It's interesting to me to think about like well
Okay what if what if the truth
Required you to do a podcast out of your apartment
Would you do that Alex
All of this pretending about talking to world leaders in
Dinner party chatter about you
Would you give up
The pretense of being the leader
A video of the Patriot movement Texas royalty
You give up all that for the truth
I don't think you would
You probably get tortured though because then
You know that's part of the persecution fantasy if you get to go out of martyr
Well I mean it's
It's a lot more fun to think of
Dying
Instead of
Living with
Write it I would but I would much rather die for my beliefs than then
Live like
Really miserably forever
Yeah it's hard
It's a lot harder I don't think I'd be up for that
This thing you can do
It's not
So Alex talk to you about it's just like these are
Hugging scary times
God's going to judge
I just get scared
And the men will be measured
And measures
We're all that we measure
The fire
I want them to find out
Because it will cleanse.
Will do Annalise
Separate the metal
But in that far
We will find our descendants
405 Construction
Real test is now
From here on out
What the f***
Is he going on about
If it look if the culture at large it gave it 6 months with a new Trump Administration Alexandra
Yeah burning witches is totally fine again of course when did it ever go wrong I just like to imagine something
People like hey man
Yeah
I don't like
The Federal Reserve
Gradual weirdness intensifying you get to a point Relic
Yeah the cleansing fire tells me to come in fire
I'll be purifying and if you can't float well we know what's going on with you
That's like this
Trajectory Australian
Reasonable place
A little bit of a kudo
Tip of the cap okay
In that he does a show
More weird than threatening I think
I'll just go to little bit longer to about 2 minutes
This is just Alex
Begging leftists to accept Jesus
Alyssa
I got an open heart open mind
You know that was a globalist
I would see you in
Sea ocean animals with trash
Cool
God Spirit leads me
Start thinking like that
Easter sale
AutoZone on
Tell you straight up your face
If you are a Democrat
If you're allowed
If you are.
You're an idiot
Literal
Prince Philip
Charles Hua
The Dracula line
Hungarian Romanian
Sure
Thousand Years these are blood drinkers
You are literally on your knees
To the seed of State
Dragon
It's going to give you milk and
Cookies at night
You are
Pool
I'm begging you for your own soul
We will destroy you
Godzilla Destroyah
Opposite of Satan
I don't want to Detroit
Thanks
Pleasure in this
Destroy you
Pulga Destroyer I'm spanking
The place
Servicetitan
Now there's still time
Showtime
You can do it you can Run Oz
Bill Gates
You can renounce
Fauci
Ted Turner
What do
Yukon
Except
To do it
Much
This is such a serious
Situation
Please
Please turn back now
Detroit
He wrote a book about it
You have to reject Satan
We don't have any
You must reject your body
So let me ask you
Yasin open-hearted lifted heard Alex Jones is please
Write this is a business they can do haha
How do you feel
Are you ready are you ready
To renounce
Anthony fauci
I mean yeah
I really don't have a problem with that
I'll just pick somebody else who's very competent
I don't have any
Yeah I would like
It's certainly much less attachment then you have to someone like let's say print
Prince Philip
Desperately attached to I do find it I do find it hilarious
That he
Kind of correctly net he
Let me let me put it this way
He embodies the point of drag
Which is better
Foreigners are very weird and we should be terrified of that
Prince Philip
That's what he said that's what I'm saying he's not from America
And in the same way you know Dracula was written to terrify people about the Eastern Bloc of Europe turnover in
Into their home
Stealing their women and such
I guess I'm not that scared of her
Filipino
Will you do the 23rd now and this episode opens with Alex
I would say accepting the Biden is going to win
So how it is now
It's going to happen but it's the overthrow of the country or something
So we know that Alex has this thing that he talks about all the time which is operation lockstep
Which is what made up or
For the crib trauma meme or something about say 2010 document
Rockefeller Foundation
The what is a
Is it called the
The future of technology and internet National development document
Operation lockstep
It almost got
Deeply deeply Exposed on Rogan's podcast price
Him I intend Ellen and Jamie were just not able to
Synthesize the information take it in well enough
To Rabbit Alex's Boynton
In real time
Something that Alex benefits from
To do a s*** job in f*** over everybody
Yes but also I think I said this on the
It's a complex thing that it would be very difficult to know nothing about it
I did do a bad job but I don't know if they come
Exactly I know I know full well I just wanted I just want to make that clear
Except in the places where it's
Deserved
Villages at snot one
That's not a fair credit
Exactly
Play the biggest problem
Before they even began they were outgunned and had no chance
I'm so Alex is now turning this into something else
This is now like lockstep
Years ago
I put on Roblox jailbreak
It's since been taken off the internet
Airplane collapse
I plan to
Trigger
Collapse using virus
I knew that was and it just come out
In the
Haha
Operation lockstep is not a thing that is all just made up
Alex did not know about the term lockstep when he made the film and the game but it's a very recent element of his conspiracy theories
That he's been trying to
Being part of his work all along
It absolutely 100% not true
Alex started bring up the word lockstep immediately after people like Jim Fetzer started misrepresenting that Rockefeller document
Scenarios for the future of technology and International Development
And meme started spreading
About those Miss representation
That's the actual basis for Alex's reporting
But let's entertain Alex's lie here though
Tease this out
He's claiming it in the updated version of endgame he knew all this stuff that was going to happen because he's read this imaginary
Lockstep plant
That hadn't been written
That is a big bro
That is an issue
There's no such thing as a game 2.0 that's a bit of a problem
Alex's referring to endgame 1.5 which was this
Does the supplementary director's cut of endgame because 2007
The Rockefeller document that they luck
Except conspiracies based on wasn't written until 20
There's an issue
Was that we forgot that Alex's psychic
He can see the future
Dream
Keep forgetting about that timelines they'll be damned
You know it's really hard to fax them
Check somebody who can see into the future
That's an issue
Quite frankly
I'm going to the Second Sight I've been thinking about this for a while
I think I got a
Just come out with it
I don't believe you psychic
I don't I don't I don't know how that's going to go boy Jordan
Leaving
I don't
And I can't I can't believe he is because
Dennis becomes a silly exercise
Not that this isn't silly to begin with all the ones that I
Facetiously entertain
And even defense
That one I just never touch because
F****** I'm out
Yeah I'm out when you say you're psychic
Yeah it's fun to think that he thinks he is
The other thing too that I want to point out about this
Is this is such a really good example of these things that Alex does where he tries to insert current things
Into his past work
Like a lot of his work is so vague and so
You know it's in the documents in the white papers in all that I have the documents I can prove every
Nothing's ever proven
Everything is so hyper nonspecific that like he complains about the Rock
Rockefellers all the f****** time
And so yeah you can find tons of him talking with rocks I was trying to take over the world 10 years ago
Rockefeller evil
You did not know about a document that wouldn't
3 years later
When you made endgame
But it looks good now
It is it is unfortunate that part of the game
Of being so vague and tossing so much s*** at the wall
Is if you want to say like
Oh I knew about operation lockstep
11 years
And
And then tossed that s*** out you can be like
Okay well here's a clip of me saying that the Rockefellers are going to kill everybody and that it's in the white paper
The whitepaper I was referring to was the as heretofore yet Unwritten
You know that clip may exist and I found the like release
Article
On Prison Planet
About the
The endgame 1.5
No mention of the Rockefellers isn't match
Block step none of this s*** has a big row just like a man we're going to have more interviews with big
Jim Unger
And Daniel estulin
Bilderberg
Big Jim
Better
What is a giant panda or a really old chain-smoking anti-semite
Take the chimp I will I will also take
Take the chip Alex's to talk
Plus Schwab a whole bunch
That is one particular thing that he says about him that
Is this worth saying
Is not true
The populist movement across the world
Boris Johnson and he's got John Kerry
The covid-19 lockdown
Is a punishment
The populace to bring them under control and they admit
It's a social movement
Klaus Schwab says he's not a threat
Covid-19
All the all that's nonsense but it is worth pointing out also the Boris Johnson is now on the outs he is no longer the
Eroica populist today
Because I guess he's taking covid seriously eventually
You know
Now he's a globalist
Yeah unfortunately whenever you eventually like
Succumb to reality, everybody who's unreality does not like you anymore anybody who still committed to this
Yeah I will turn on you very attractive
Call Schwab thing in his book The Great reset the covid-19 is not a threat
Alex is doing this based on a cherry-picks quotation that reads quote
Unlike certain past pandemics covid-19 doesn't pose a new existential threat
This quote is taken out of context to imply that he's saying AB isn't really a threat and it's just being used take over Society Shore
You actually go to the text you'll find that the words quote
New existential threat
Have a
Specific meaning in the context of the writing
This was found after a discussion of the bubonic
Plague and the germs that were brought
To North America by the first European explorers
Which is why the word Anu is in that sense yeah there's that
Census of new X
Existential threat
What's the population
Covid-19 is dangerous and deadly but it's not the bubonic
Play again I don't think that's a controversial tape
Rob isn't saying the covid-19 not a threat
Just that quote
Unless the pandemic evolves in an unforeseen way
It's not going to be something that poses an existential threat to the world like
The plague
I want to take that quote out of context and giving it the context he wanted to have which isn't real
Alexandra read this book and I would go so far as to say that his researchers probably haven't either
I say this because of that quote is taken from the introduction to the text
So I can see them finding that being not good enough
Subway
I don't know if you've heard this
Jordan
I don't know if you heard this news
Did you hear that
People talk about Alex identified I did not hear
Actually
By the way
Yolanda calls but I've gotten calls
From some of the biggest people out there
Batman Alex
Incredible
When I go to these dinner parties in New York in LA
Only one talk about is you
What's it like to have everybody now accepting you a celebrating
No people
Finally understand
What's it like to have movies not a zero-sum your honor
Traitor to call you up man you remember when I was right
We really crusted in that movie
Anyways Alex
What is it like for James Woods to have commissioned a bronze sculpture of you and his front lawn
Alex what is it like
I got a call from the chair that Clint Eastwood talk to him talking to big people
SMS sent me a video of him
Saying that Alex is the leader of their movement
Well ad
4info Warriors fatality
Episode about that dude how many irrelevant
I think we have
Little punching laterally at the time that we did the coach
Text Dave though
I think I got tricked
By the fact that like rightwingwatch would that have post about himself
I thought for sure this is somebody who is much more relevant than they are
I don't understand why you were supposed to watch the right-wing use a right-wing voice
He was somebody who had a bit more of an audience
Expand
You just like that dog
Looks like his dog
Yeah I don't know I don't think that Alex is getting these calls like I said when he is very
Fixated on this end
Interesting Lee as he's being
People who are the most important
In society the heads of state
The media figures are
Celebrities everybody just so happens
That his every move is being watched
By the feds
You understand that
Followed home
Black SUVs
Eden restaurant
FBI and CIA
Papillon CIA
Next.
Have a good day mr. Jones
CPAP masks
Mission Impossible
Federal agents follow me
What
Wow
Wow we're going for it but I really do love the idea of like some guy being
Hey Alex
I'm CIA murder
I get like that I was I'm CIA my buddy here is as bi we are working on a joint test
Force about your diet
What the f*** is this
I think I could drive and got could legitimately drive a real person
And say it if so if
People were actually doing that
I think if people actually did that to Alex
He would feel so validated well I'd like it would make him feel good
I think if you're a paranoid narcissist who also has a modicum of celebrity
You might have people who interact with you
Who are like Sands
Sure or something sure I meant because your brain doesn't interpret information correctly like oh my God.
Privacy is URI cuz they're wearing a mask
It may be there in a suit yourself or a noticeable person yeah people turn and look whenever they
They're in a restaurant in there like maybe one time you was coming home from work and there was a black van that happened to be tonight
Black man is the
Grow up man
That would be that would be an easy I think that would be an easy situation that we should
Nobody who's not in law enforcement
Nobody was not a fed
Can have a black guy
I think that's a new rule that way we can all identify all the time
They would be against that
You have to okay fine
You have to pay me unicorn or a dragon
On the side of your black van
If you are not a fan
I think we could reach this compromise
This is real strange this is real
Like he had this
Doom and Gloom sort of like gods
Cleansing fire is going to purify the world on Sunday
Now on Monday with these fantasies about how all the celebrities love
Everybody is watching his every move at all of the alarm for Smith
And then
I got this news
When you decide to spread the word on when you decide to share the info download it
While
27 years on air
Oh really
How's the time
Zebras
Yes that is correct
Hypothetical last episode I was like
Alright
No matter what
The 24th
Is either going to be the day that he sets out to do his last episode
It will be yet another time
Your eyes
And your joy
Everytime it gets you up you have only to make you disappointed
It is
I will call after all these years
Steele Creek
Could not be more excited when I heard that
I thought
Hooray
Just turned off this episode I was like I'm surprised
Wow we've got to listen to some calls
Man
Not a great session
LMAO
I Do by Albanese and real
Question is I'm wondering
What
How are we supposed to get our information is
16in shutting down
I think they hung up on her
You got to have that cost button there for that assholes
Exhale
I will say this
I think Alex
And I both
Experience the same thing which is that I did not hear a single word
The chief said
I think for him it was because
He responded to her name was just like
Yeah he was
Steve was not happy about it
And for me it was because
I could not stop laughing is giving just hearing in May Van Gogh
He's very pissed off
He doesn't know or is it just that it's Andrea
I think with the
The problem is that he said the wrong name then she corrected the name gave to
Too much of a correction
And he doesn't care for this kind of thing
So did the thing where she
Asked if she was on the air which we all know
Sure yes
He has a hair-trigger with that
So you get another call and this person
Talk about hypothetical violence
Violence
But it could get to that point
They keep going down this road what are we going to do
What months they fix
The boss
Do what they did
And we just
I just can't go along with
Can't go along with
Alex's eating lunch
I did that because I have to always
You love catching him take a job there are recurring themes in the show
I think that's the most
Does that last call here on 23rd episode they're going to listen
Come to a little bit of is
Natural
Infowars
Kind of caller
This is
Not good
I didn't enjoy hearing this
I don't have anything against Jewish people like my wife
Children
What is fortissimo on what is
Jews behind it
What
Just ridiculous
So this color is trying to speculate that there are a cult
Jews who are behind stealing the election as well as the murder of the Tsar Allison
Responses
Dominion does Venezuela
Instead of being like
Haggai
How about how about you calm down with this
Cosmetic tropes
Bro I've been doing one thing
For twenty years
And that is telling people I'm not an anti-semite
And now you're making me say
Izaka-ya that caller was bad
So
We get to the 24th and
I was a little bit worried
Alex Warren
To do his last show I would you be worried about that is that a long long long long long track record of not follow
Ali doesn't do those things
So I was
Was very shocked
When he started the show
Head lineup
I thought about
Doing for a long time but haven't done yet for the live show
And it says it all it says this might be my last broadcast Alex Jones
I have that many points in my life where I'm almost at this on here because the situation was so serious
Last Broadcast
Every
Minute on air
As if it could be my last and I'm going to explain to you why
I really just tell you the truth
Duet
About how serious the situation isn't worth
Yeah so I think that this was the biggest
Cop out
It's like okay yeah this is going to be my last
But it is just saying like let's live each day like it's our last yeah weird mode
Motivational nonsense biblical on him and say this is lukewarm
And we all know how the Great
Feels about lukewarm
I kind of wanted a little more out of the idea of the last episode than just this
Conqueror
It seemed a little flat to me
I wanted a little bit more pageantry
A little dramatic
This is a little drummer
Maybe not as dramatic as I want it to be
Joe Biden's able to wiggle his way in the White House
The White House and get the nuclear codes
Then I will officially make the statement
McLaren United States
Creating a tombstone
Carbon Stone
Will in place
Here
In the TV radio
Lutheran and it'll be on sale at ShopRite
I can have a keychain of that
Pills shaped like tombstones
Honestly I think we should do that
First just to get out front
I think that be hilarious
Look I don't want to turn into kiss like when they're selling coffin
Too much plus I don't think teepublic sells tombstone
Now we might have to go to a boutique Redbubble
So I mean
Alright
I think that's a little dramatic but
Alex is being very serious
Let me get into it right now
Tell you what's coming up
Just getting into the basic news.
Square app
Do it
We're done
I'm turning around
She's very real
Okay
Alright
United States of America born
July 4th 1776
United States of America.
January 20th
B21
Because if we don't admit
How grave the situation is we don't have a shot
Stopping this is Devin like a giant sell that tombstone
How grave the situation now it's not bad not bad Alex
What I appreciate the most witches avoid saying pun not intended sure
Text administrate
Alex's never put out a headline like this
Like the maybe my last show ever
Any idea of doing that
And it turns out they f***** up the headline
I've been reading and studying the globalist
For 30-plus years
Digital screen
This could be my last broadcast TuneIn if you want to save yourself never put a head on out of
Have never
Engineer
Complete Global collapse
The ashes
A witch
What
But if you torture
Voice memo real quick
I can't talk about it
Text iPad line
Good last joke that's good stuff really
I got really fast cuz I had just done
Speed voice battle brothers
Eva comic
If a comic had a
Absurd intro
That day
Is it had to be part of the whole bit right they wrote it
You wrote it down for you
Say like
Repeat this after me
Hey I have a tongue twister that you need to memorize
You know I would say that like you
Talking about doing his last
Cheryl forever
He's
Decided
F*** I'm going to do it
Prepare
Because it's supposed to be a time capsule thing
Isn't it supposed to be like
Either be idea of his last episode to be like
In case I go off air this is like
A bottle
This is a bottle episode stand-up to Greatness
Going out like The Sopranos are right
He's who he is and then the lights go off Valley no wrapping up any
Anything does have a very serious message
And the biggest message I have before I give you my personal message here is
The people that serve the system the yuppies
You're the biggest jumps of them all
So delusional
You think you're part of the ruling class
You think you're part of the United States offer
You think you're part of the winning team you or anything
You are the week
Traders
Actually chose to join this evil
Because you were speaking out power
I think that Alex Wood
Good we're leftist enforcers
Guess I mean
If you had to wrestle with our existence
It would obviously say that we're trying to shut him down
We're like some Soros plan for some b*******
And I I can sing you fully up enough checked in on this a lot again really really thought about it I'm not
Thinking I'm part of the powers
No no I don't think I can think of very few times in all of
Cuban history when left us felt like they were on The Winning Side
Yeah I want even talk about you and me you're one of
Three or four people
My parents
Soros
That's it
Oh s***
Yeah that's all three
No I am
Yeah I just I find this to be a really bizarre
Thing for him to say he's like his big messages
You people are chumps
The last message is like
A playground insult based in vindictiveness and ambitious understanding the people you disagree with
Great scares
Your last message is a waste
Trivio annoying
Anyway remember how globalists don't have kids
100% of globalist don't have correct
And Bill Gates
None of them have to Rob at all of them
Nothing
Does not kids
Touche
Free market capitalist Society
They say the save-the-earth but really
When they live the most popular lifestyle to have all these children
Wait wait hold on there's all these children they don't have kids and Future
Oh maybe nothing you say means anything
Write 99% of
Alright 100%
There's a photo of fauci
15 years ago
Doesn't have kids
Spell Tom Brokaw George Soros
None of them have kids
Walters
Clippers
Lady
Anderson Cooper's mom is Gloria Vanderbilt know that because he keeps
Talk about how he's the last Vanderbilt not straight
Brooke Astor had one child who died in 2014 at the age of 90
Significantly older than
Going to soon
The batting average going down
Haha
So this is supposed to be as last episode
I've already brought this up
I'm really struggling with this
Because
It shouldn't
Be
Timestamp
It should be dated
If I were Alex
I would stay away from
Headlines
I would stay away from like
Things are going back out this is
This is November 2020 stuff right here if it's your last show
Victory lap you do like here all of our achievements do a f****** commentary for endgame anyting
This is your life
Although you wouldn't be able to get too many of his comeback
Instead what he does is like just headlines
New York City
Grab
Provide education and
So that's martial law
The secret police
Some reality covid-19 New York
To stop everyone like you might imagine
What Alex's
It specifically about people arriving in New York from out of state
Will be so much like they snatch people out there testing on site
There's no they want to advise people arriving to the city about quarantine requirements you could be hit with
Define if you don't follow
I don't like this much
Because
You know it's
Scary but also I don't like this pandemic
And people not taking it seriously so here we are
Also I'm much more interested in another part of the sheriff Joseph sushito his comment
About this stuff okay
Quote
Deputy sheriff's are investigating massive event that violate a panoply of criminal fire building
Help and other regulatory laws at locations
Such as illegal Fight Club
Underground raves in illegal gambling Den
These activities were illegal and sometimes deadly before covid-19 have a public safety hazards regarded them as
Amplified
Exponentially by the pandemic
I did not know that he legal fight clubs were a modern problem in New York
But I want Alex to talk more about that instead of a subtle bulshit
Deadly illegal fight the problem of the problem that we're seeing now is too many people in New York
Are cool
I should have known I mean I guess
Like I don't know I guess I should have assumed there would be
Fight Club
I just
I didn't ask
Well that there aren't fight clubs but it does look like it's not like Fight Club
The movie
I would assume it's a strange thing to read in that statement
Totally understand totally understand
Always going to
Even in Foods besides tore torn countries have underground raves in underground gambling
Fight clubs though bro
The first one on his list
Yeah
That makes me sound like fight clubs are real issue for now
Before rains on the list is even more like
What
Anyway I think Alex is burying the lead on this one
She doesn't live on his final episode and certain things will not look so good
Good lot of his covid feeling
In particular
And these centers
Hospital
Special
Execution Docs
Covid
Yeah Center
We're loving test
Sidra Cove in the put you in the hospital with covid
Leftists I got to kill you left this execution dock though does sound like
It could be a duck
Look for executing leftist
Sittin on the Electra sex
Dock of the Bay
Nice
Slick move this one on
So it won't just kill you
You didn't. Covid
Kill you
When you chained down
When your lungs
I get off on it
To walk over glass
They're going to kill you and your fam
We got a lot of
Reported reports
Reportedly doing a lot of work for one adverb
Yeah
I mean for the people who are First Responders and people who are in the medical field who are being
Deeply traumatized by virtue of the help
But they're providing and what they have to see
This is such a disgusting
Something to
To be putting out
Into the world
This disorder perspective is just shameful
On dead like
Bittrex
In terms of his career
Like you said a lot of really f***** up horrible things at this
Kind of thing
Hi continuously through this characterization of medical professionals
Dealing with this crisis like
It's
It's up there with Sandy Hook it's up there with the Boston bombing really
It's disgraceful
No we can we can talk about Italy actionable necessarily but it's as gross
Right no I mean it this is this goes back to our earlier conversation to you know we can
We can talk about all the hundreds of
Songs of deaths which are
Are f****** terrifying
Tragic
An awful but at the same time
There are millions of people
Millions of people who are going to live with the effects of this f******
Psychic Destruction for the rest of their life and not to mention people who don't.
Die but have
You know effect
Jackson lingering Health consequences that aren't captured by statistical out Untold
Story that people have to live with
And like
I mean just something small like hey guess what for the rest of your life you have shortness of breath forever
That's it
And you're like I understand that that you know
Yeah
Just f***** you
Runner before it now you're not
There are tons of things like that
And then the situation fits doctors and nurses
Irr put in
People who are medical professionals who have been infected themselves
It's just it's just
Disgusting I mean like
The evolution from there just f****** in the hospital and getting drunk
To take kill you and laugh at you
Just go f*** yourself at least people would have happily executed
Clinton
For Benghazi
She shop
You know
Like happily would have executed
Well they were strapped down
Charlie Daniels
Tweet about it anymore
Look
The shity and I think it's a board
To take those moments and be kind of serious about it because
But there's also time to laugh
Like when Alex talks
About Alex
With swabs and guns
Too good
WhatsApp
Are they back
The Daleks are back we have an update
Okay they have been disarmed
You deserve that I think we left I think
Laugh too much at it but now
The Daleks are not our
It rent-a-cars
Why do trains
Going to the police officers
Robots that come up with
Schwab
Bye-bye
Secret
Covid facility
Staffed by
FIFA.
Okay
Keto
It's the small things
That make me know
He's listening
Small things for your like
You knew
Guns in the Daleks is to buy a funny and 20
You found out and we all know like Icarus flew too close to the Sun
You're going to like the hilarious territory
That's why now it's a f****** Dalek with a swab and there's
Cops with guns behind them
That's somehow so that's fill your s*** to me cuz now
Now we're not just sending dog that we've increased our infrastructure cost
Now you're cops who were working with Dalek partners
So it raises the question why
You couldn't just have the cops swab
I got a new movie4u sequel the K-9 cop
Dollarconnect
Solving crime
I could see that I would watch that sort of
Really hyper focused on the Dalek and we're not talking about how there are antifa Berger Hospital
Sure
Barbie we always know those horses Dad we don't need to worry about that
Activa murder hospitals
I sometimes wish
We were at
Cool as they think we are I would love for that to be like the next blumhouse movie or something
What it could be like a real
Be kind of horror movie that caters to the
Conservative audience
Julie
It was a false flag by the Nazis in the antifa murder
I'm sorry
Bingo is
Justifiable pretty sure you can yell.
In a crowded theater that was never settled
I just don't want the neighbors to get
Some sort of very weird idea about what's going on like the idea that there
That we're suddenly screaming like
Call Chet.
New thing to complain about
A new primary source
And I will get into it a little bit after
You just saw Hugh in Rockefeller
Lockstep plan
10 years ago and they put lock stuff out
On paper
What you just saw
With the woman in charge
Your family
She can't travel she gets meet once a year
Cosmic look into a robot machine
Who did that tell you for them what they're going to be what they're going to do
That wasn't some
Cartoon made by George Orwell
Saying all this is terrible
They're saying this is good
Because they're showing children that
The Descent to ask the one-day years on her birthday
Planned opolis
Presenting this with no evidence
I'm saying that it
Something that was forcefully shown to kids show
Possible that it might have been shown in some classrooms an educational setting
But I'm certain he's making it up because it's a cartoon
It's believable
Be shown in classrooms
A kid as somebody who knows his Miyazaki history I'm pretty sure that Orwell worked on Spirited Away
Perhaps
It could have been nausicaa of the Valley of the wind but a pretty sure is.
I have to say
For Alex's
Sake
He did
Fairly accurately describe this
Kisscartoon
Alright
That's good
There is a woman
Who has their limited travel you can only have meat on your birthday for husband is hooked up to a machine at work
Right. In the way that maybe
Ueu my fantasize
That being butts
There's a video from a group called forum for the future
In 2011 they released
Series of videos that sought to depict what the potential cities of the future could look like given
Trends that were existing fan in the world
Habit
He's found one that he thinks he can claim is prosthetics
Eddie's choosing to ignore the fact that there were four scenarios
Status gruppe depict
The one how it's Joseph closest to the things that he makes his audience scared they strongly centralized government
Food rationing Etc
Scenario title
Planned opolis but there was also communis City
And renewable
These are each depictions of how City Planning could evolve in a scenario where alternative energy sources were made primary
And what life might look like depending on the strategies that are employed
None of this is my telestrator plan
It's an exploration exercise as the people who put the
This Together actually said explicitly
Quote for the future scenarios are not predictions or depictions of desirable Futures which we wished
To promote and they do not represent our vision of a sustainable future
They're pictures of different possible future is designed to help people understand the major trends that are shaping our world
The emperor challenge Inspire and excite so that people feel motivated to plan for a better
More sustainable
Yeah I mean this is almost exactly the same thing as the lockstep where he's taking that one
Plan
Scenario out of the 48 decided
Oh my God
Not going to talk about renewable
Although now that
The moment you said renew Abad
I got transported into the writers room with the Whiteboard and the million different city name puns
And it's just I that's where I would that's where I belong Dead coming up with
Renewable names for to print sidhe also renewable doesn't think what I'm doing sit ups
Sure
So this is this is a bunch of nonsense but I do think that it's probably going to be a very large
Piece of
Probably can be the next block
Planned opolis
Her mother
But the thing that's really weird when I was looking into this there like Reddit threads
From 2012
2015 about that around for a while.
New
So
Here's where things get weird
Does Alex's last show
This is last show
I am job
I thought she wants you to know that the the global
I believe it they're getting messages or mail
I'm sure we know this
That's what I believe that
He doesn't believe that
Yes
He's not crazy
This is what they believe exact
He's reporting on this as a scientist
Now wait till the end of this clip
The globalist follow this
Believe
Interdimensional
Information
It's like in the movie Buckaroo Banzai
A Grade B movie
Believe
Information
Bill dish
Transmission forever
You can go back to those ancient civilization 6000 years ago
Double helix
Preachers came from
The dog star
Sirius to tell them
We talked about that whole thing in a Project Camelot episode so yeah
That's something he should take
Think about if Alex believes
Flippy's aliens came down and told these poor thing
These people did get this information that I couldn't possibly have from any other source to FM that would
Imply that it isn't
Just
What the globalist believe if you
Call Donna
The movie
Alien movies all about it
They are. They knew all of this
They built it
Kill everybody and I'll give you the phone codes
You know Satan's Odyssey
Do you
And so
Obviously they're not going to be giving Jeff Bezos and Bill Gates or not
They're so
They're like ham radio operators you know transmission from
Japan or something
Just like the Bible says there is a fallen just like the vibe
Another dimension
Government
Embryonic stage
Alarm
Us to destroy ourselves
Will do it
Ausbuild
Okay
So the globalist believe that they're getting
Promises from Aliens Kill Everybody
And I'm look I know I sound crazy saying this but that's just what they believe now I should tell you
But they are getting
These messages from a transdimensional dependents Shore
Where in the Bible
And that's what's going on
Well that's up
Okay
Seems I hate
To be a dick
What about seems kind of like a technical
It does seem like what he say
What are you saying is they believe I'm not crazy
They believe that their King interdimensional messages
When we all know it's a demon
Devil from a different dimension sending the messages when I understand it's completely different
We might also be an alien
Sure
Yeah this is silly
And we all know safe
The fever
Rich
Okay so let's entertain this
For one sec
Alright
Bezos
Gates not getting Eternal Light
That suggest to them that they will receive eternal life yes
Now he's a real issue that they just
Haven't talked to Alex yet and had Alex be like
Nah nah nah nah that's
The devil you're not actually
Going to get a turn
They're lying
Is that all we need
We just need to get Bezos and Alex in a room together
I think we should
Nope I think that I think we should get them in a room together
Put a big dome over it
So it turns out
You can talk to aliens
Or the devil
Do you take drugs
Electrocute yourself
Could you stream
Alex later says you can just like
Do that thing where you choke yourself against a while
So they're even getting everyone ready
Okay and so it's on it's on
On
It's on you can electrocute yourself
You can have your heart stopped and do what you can take
Flatliners
Boy when they do it do they break through
Exactly what happened
He goes through the wall the other side
You don't come back the same day
Buckaroo Banzai predictive programming about how you could commune with the Devil
You know
I knew it was always going to come down to RoboCop
In one of his many roles
But I didn't expect it to be Buckaroo Banzai that was too happy and joyful film
Also was full of very very subtle messages about the
Now that'll happen
Open episode where Alex was incoherent f***** up on something and one of the questions from the Reddit ask
Anything was about Buckaroo Banzai Isaac Marisa
Public is being cagey he does not like revealing that he's a big nerd which is
Weird to me for the grace of God
I have been Alex Jones if I was just so insecure about my nerdiness when I was in like fourth grade
Probably were
I think it would also require an inability to understand the things you were reading
Essential piece of what makes Alex Alex
Like a lack of reading comprehension inability to comprehend what you read
Map mixed with
A pretty high functioning
Like a memory or we called and asked to recall
But just not a not a good understanding
Also being really insecure
That is well
Bob Bob
Do The Imperial March sorry
Just as bad as yelling
Neighbors travel
So Alex has a plug here
And
This made me pretty sad
I didn't plug last hour
I don't plug won't be
I am spending all the money we've got I have expended
Much of our reserves going to Georgia
I going to Arizona and going to be
What is series of great invest
Really got the achieve results out of
Georgia
Arizona DC Caravan
Really set the world on fire with that Caravan we're still hearing about it
The Ripple
The Caravan
The stop this steel Caravan
I mean it's changed the political landscape
I think pretty seriously
This will be
Maybe one of the few times Dan where
You have absolutely
8 likes
The caravana T project will live on forever
Long after the Caravan is
I don't believe that I didn't realize something
I got a phone call
I got lieutenant colonel
Gavin Newsom
Highly highly The Big E
Figures
Ghost politics sure they're terrified
That they're going to do another Carousel travel that's trouble
Out of trouble
I can see Feinstein's bones jigglin they're so afraid of
Crowds of tens of people
They'll get all the way to Nevada
I mean
I don't believe this is necessarily going to be what happened
But I do think that there would be a certain
Cosmic hilarity
If like Alex ends up going broke because of this bad
It'd be so great we could have another year but I thought it was a good idea to send Owen to bet
Baton Rouge
I want the armored car to take him down I want that severe
You could be living out of that armor
Such every bad boss that I've ever known I got a bunker
The Stag I got a bunch of beans
Every bad boss I've ever known has been just like that where it's like
Guys
Unfortunately we're only going to be able to do a small raise this year it's just going to be a 2%
Anyways
I bought an armored van
Like
F*** off
Yeah you guys are the worst
So answer the Gaston which I thought was weird okay it's your last show
Do your f****** last show
Don't have guests on
Unless it's Steve
Because he belongs on your last shower sure he has ruined your life, right
Wearing a black robe over
10 with a site
It's not it's not
Is Omnibus I'm not going to go over
This whole giant bio
A lot of big companies
Again list of all he was the CEO Overstock it started that
Ranchworld.com is the first major online site
Coin so yeah this Patrick Bernie was the CEOs Overstock
He had an intimate relationship with Maria butina
The Russian woman who played guilty to conspiracy to act as an unregistered foreign agent
I had to resign because of
Yeah he's mixed up in some s***
African Republic meltdown and said that the FBI forced him to have a relationship with her and you made it but
That's a good I like that
I don't care about Patrick Byrne
I'm just pushing the same sort of dominion can shore shore shore shore and also
First thing is that
If he's
To be believed
He's
Feeding information to Rudy Giuliani and Sidney Powell
The information that they're putting out he's taking credit
So you're telling me that somebody
Who lost
Is insanely perhaps obscenely high paying jobs
Yep
Because of having an illicit affair with a foreign agent
Is now telling me several years later
I'm feeding information to Rudy Giuliani
Someone who
Never ever had any connection to any sort of Russian intelligence
Whatsoever correct here's the problem is just full of s***
And so I don't know if I believe
That I don't believe him at all I'm going to say and then it has a pattern
True
Not great
Then it's not an interview either I don't really care
I'll be at alexcis
Another guest salon
Maybe this is somebody who should be on his last show but
Come the f*** on
Hour and 15 minutes
Don't kausen
Is the one thing only
David Icke
The turd in the punch bowl
The guy who earlier on in his career Alex would say is meant to make conspiracy thinkers and
Who asked question
Should give him a bad name because he talks about lizards and shape-shifted folks
Oh wait I'm that now
Is there something actually kind of spiritually appropriate I love the idea that on his last show
He's sitting here and just like
Kissing David Icke sent more of like a Reconciliation of reconciliation like a
Kind of music reconciliation at the end you know where they're both sitting there like
You know we disagreed about a lot of stuff but
Now I can see
I'm also full of s*** to
I I think there's two things one I would like to see
A bringing back
Of people like Jason bermas
Radowski these people from back
Wayback wijmenga seeing how they get along now that would be a good last year
But I also think that this is really good too because
Like Alex resented David Icke
For a long time
David Icke
Did not give a
Single flock
It just did his thing
Another. Technically that's a good thing
The David I did his thing
Beginning
To the end
I mean this isn't the last episode obviously Alex had a show on Wednesday
To the hypothetical last show
David Icke stands is a morsel
Successful
Yeah more popular
Better
Situated
Figure in the
Conspiracy world yeah then Alex could ever be
And Alex
Has now been brought low
Hogan had to been that's brewed I had to bend to me to someone like David Icke
Here's my pitch
On Alex's actual
We actually we full-on do a this is your life
Right shirt you have to hear the voice disembodied
Before you know who it is
This coming on there
I want
To get so many different voices just to see
How much he flinches
Like hearing his
Former friends boys just being like
I want to hear it's like you know those are always very positive oh my God
You know be great is
As if Rapaport
Was a master of impressions
I need to do like
The voices of people
Who hate Alex now like Webster
Guitar player something
Sure I bet he's like now Webster has working with you
We're on Voice number 15 Alex you should assume by now it's me oh God I love you Rappaport
Had me scared there
What Ike is here and basically what is big thing is is there's no covid
Even if you believe that
On the basis of
There is no deadly virus
The boss majority
Okay that's not the response you're supposed to have
Yeah I today but I coming on in
I am just saying that there is no virus have been convinced of this the whole time
But let's stipulate that there is just me
Just in case some of your listeners are ready for the
Proof that there is no virus
That's fitting
For the last year
For Alex to have a gas to saying things that directly contradict
Literally everything
I bet he believes him be like you're still on target you're the best
Should one last clip Heroes David Icke from the final app
Episode of the Alex.
Go fuc
Yourself David Icke
Best route through isolation
This is absolutely not true and David actually absolutely ashamed of himself for passing along
Bulshit
There's an article in the journal emerging infectious diseases from June 2020 with the title quotes severe acute
Respiratory Syndrome syndrome coronavirus 2
From patient with coronavirus disease United's
I'll redo this from the abstract
Quote we are isolated virus from nasal pharyngeal and oropharyngeal
Specimens from the patient and characterize the virus replication process
And cell culture trophy
Isolated
Even discusses how they were able to take us isolated virus and creative
Do you know I'm seeking
Which Bay made available to the domestic and international Public Health academic and pharmaceutical sectors
Her basic research diagnostic development antiviral testing
Development
Actually goes on to bring up this study which contradict this point there is no paper that shows this
It's not a problem for him though because he then claims this paper is bogus citing the expertise of a guy named Tom Cowan
Who's put out a video about how 5G is poisoning ourselves
Also
Calvin is a holistic medicine guy whose medical license is currently on probation because quote
Among other things he had offered an
Drug to a breast cancer patient without
It wasn't approved for use
He also never saw the patient in person or did he review her full medical file according to documents
From the medical board of California detailing why
He was to be disciplined
Listen to this dude anyway go f*** yourself David Icke
You're a real pile of s***
And it's fitting that I would have you
As a guest
On your last job
On a scale of 1 to 35 Hitler mustache
22 months that I think that's too probably yeah probably a lot of
Yeah but one Hitler mustache is still one
Too many
I mean by that it's really about how you look at the scale
You know I'd like
That's one of those things
There are limits
I don't see how saying on a show right now
That the virus isn't real is any
From from yelling fire in a
You know like that's just the reality of the situation
There's no difference you're killing me
I agree with you except
I don't know just be a bility to make direct line
You know.
If you yell fire in a crowded building obviously you see the effects
The immediate effects
Much harder to trace Direct
People who were affected and sure this is the reason that they behaved in the way they did all right
Trace bulshit
I agree
I don't know what the answer
That is I don't I don't
I hate it
I think it sucks
Murder Hornets
How about this
Stalker
Daleks
I like it
What would we put nardella compartments
Hornet
Okay take this mob released murder Hornets
He's so weird because just like all right take the swab
No I won't
What the f*** thank you Dallas
I got to say
I admire Alex
Thanks for doing his last
You know like
He said he was going to do it
Sure
I don't admire what he
He did though
Again
People running into this a lot
Yeah we could do this better than her
Internet if you have this opportunity to do your last show
Don't just do your show
Don't talk
Bird about Dominion conspiracies that'll be stale
Tomorrow
Don't do
Interview with David Icke where it just becomes trance
Apparently clear how
Munchies
Trade your own
Assertive beliefs in your career
Do something that is like
Retrospect I honestly think
Like just revisiting endgame
Would have been amazing probably
That would have been amazing
That really wasn't so confused by some of the theories that he had remembered
Prepared you would think that he knew everything about his phone
Biography on this
Billion later
Why didn't people fill this in
Pull up going on
Somebody get that in carded this from way back in my automated bibliography sucks always with me
Yeah I would I would be interested in something like that or no
Blowing hard for a couple hours just about like
Northern Lights three hours of esoteric
Alix Talton out all kinds of theories about all kinds of s*** needs
To be something that can live as a document clearly
Have
Talked about doing it as an idea for a long time before I'm finally going to do this thing
His last episode this hypothetical last episode
Got to be a concept episode
Flat
The guest
Terrible
This stuff's embarrassing like
Epiphany
To be remembered as his last episode
He's do no getting
Change it wrong all over the place he's big messages the the left there are chops
Sure every great dog talking about how
If you go to a hospital for covid
The mt4 will murder you and they're in their murder.
That's going to stand the test of time he's rambling about planned opolis Shores already again
It's a conspiracy that stale
Almost as soon as it comes out of his mouth obvious thing that his last show
What's up
Just a movie Roundup
All the movies
That he is based all of his b******* on
He just
Start playing clips
Man he does a full-on clip show of like
Hey you remember this conspiracy theory
This one's from Oblivion
Alright
Alright now let's move on to the next one
I remember this one logo
Run you guys ever see that that's my class like he does do that as he doesn't mean to hurt you or a crew bonsai
Comprehensive
Like do the whole filmography
AMC also let me just say
Dangerous message
Descend on your show
That you can talk to Demons or aliens if you electrocute yourself
What if somebody listening wants to talk to those alien well that's true
That I should try any of those things well now but now I obviously
We need to
Yeah
I give this to thumbs down
The Caravan
It's just another thing that gets me so f****** excited
And that is such a by such a let-down Alex cannot help but be disappointing
B
I should say
I'm back
To where I
Like to be
Which is I'm ready to be disappointed consistent there was a stretch where I was very much just like
It's getting tiresome that I'm being disappointed over and over again
Now there's a bit more charm
I can't help but think that it's all just
Because I'm building things up again
Some of that is about
Your excitement is both
Yours
And also anticipation
Of excitement of you telling it to
Thought ya even though I can see it in your eyes when you were getting excited about the
The feeling you had whenever you was like
I'm going to do my last show tomorrow
In the moment mostly mostly because
You immediately could tell that that was what I was asking about
I feel like yeah there is
Anticipation
Dialects with guns
Stillgoode
I mean I guess our show is over to now
Who's on his last show
You think those cop
Foxwood begin to view the Dalek as a partner
You know
I understand anything from globalist X
Stop
And by that I mean
Short Circuit
Sure yes
Okay
Yeah a lot of blatant racism
Walgreens globalux documentary
Yeah I don't know
Bulshit on his part
Pathetic
Coordinates on Wednesday because
Holiday Inn Express
I would love if today's show
On
I do know this
We did one but if it started
Yesterday I tried to do my last episode I really f*****
Good punted I screwed up
I will do my real life would be great I would give anything for him to do a whole week of
Each time I thought I did better but you know what
Third time's a charm
I realize in hindsight is embarrassing dope David icon for an hour and
Make his ass on the last show and I
By all accounts think he's a total weirdo
Hey where do this again
Also Steve Janik
Complained that he didn't get booked
I have like a like an aspiring comic
He got mad that he didn't get the call
So we're going to do it from the top
It is it is fitting if they also got to feel bad that he wasn't on the last year
You gotta you've been there forever
Indeed
The score fight
Map go to bed Jordan
30 or bail bond in your area help out people doing
We will be back but until they do I know you I'm dcx
I am a serf not a Smurf
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color