Damn important
I have great respect for its knowledge B I'm sick of imposing
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Alex
Joe
Jordan Jordan
What's up
Jordan is a nice sort of
Post-holiday
How we got to spend a little time
It's a great raise a lot of folks that's awesome congratulations
To chat with them
Into
Being overwhelmed quite frankly by the support
People donating to the the Senate
It's a campaign
We did a terrible job of
Promoting defense
We forgot to mention it on our last episode because we recorded in advance to earlier
But yeah I was it was nice to be invited it was nice to be along for the ride on that
How about you what's your lovely holiday together
Playing some board games in the
You are you introduce me to him
I did introduce you to have I cooked you a 10 lb ham DIY
The family and so I have not
Experienced really like a ham State like a slice of ham and I really ever
All kinds of fun
I'm not good at cooking ham but it was very nice
Very very
Delightful is great great holiday but in order to tell you but my actual bright spot is.
Have to open up my car
Correspondent cage we didn't have a big Gathering or anything
Thanksgiving party
Two of us
Very beautiful
It was very very small
I'm going to go ahead and open up my correspondence cage over here Dan
And
New rap
Princess crown
Created a cover for my book a graphic design
That is not just a great cover in a great design
But like really perfect
It's really really cool I did design it looks fantastic. I really
It's okay it's awesome
Cyberbully happy for you and that
So that's a really awesome
Piece of work
Been created
I have some issues with your correspondent
Its cage what about it
That's not a fan
This problem was to open the
I have another problem in that
You're naming someone a raptor princess
And you're not telling me in advance so I don't have the clicker
I can't just tell you to to play a Raptor
I feel like that's that's that's something that you have to also choose to do
We need to talk about
10 with v
Correspondence cage soundtrack
That's a good idea really want to annoy you really want to ask a late this arms race event
That is the way to go
That would be great
You have a great decision
Sure that is
It's tough to know how
Vowels are long or short
Well thank you end of this is a gift for George but I still thank you I think
It's pretty cool that exist Phantom
So over today
Lot of business to get into but before we get to do let's take a little
Pagan filth is Dustin
I'm a policy wonk
Dexter TW thank you so much
No last name the last initial
Simon experience
I'm a policy wonk Mister doodle I believe is what I reviewed yet
Libertarian
I'm a policy wonk
I hear you
A cat sleeve Journal
I'm a policy wonk
I dream about cats
Elevated level
At least middelfart
Thank you so much you are now a technocrat
Tough one here Donald Trump
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
Middle farts in the
Situation for him to be like well the only way to take down the GOP people who are betrayed is to donate to knowledge
That'll do it I'll get them
So Jordan today I found myself in a little bit of an interesting Piccoli conundrum
Sure and that is that
Thanksgiving happened and Alex Wassabi studio for the end of the week xuan so terms of us
Coming back with
With something
From Alex's seems like it's going to be
I guess we could have baby for something out of like Alex's little
You know hey how you doing videos where are showing in front of a lake yelling about something or other
I just wasn't interested now is the time
We got to get wacky
It's wacky Monday
It's been awhile
What we thankfully have
They like think that Kerry Cassidy carryover a Project Camelot has given up on her pay wall format
No that's because enough people or if
I don't know what the deal is but these videos are all very available and I have not had to log into anything
Isaac Carree Mystery episodes
Possible they're never going to do an episode on me again I better make me
She missed
Cheapest drifting we've got anybody
Take a break from Alex Jones we like to look into
How the world
The Project Camelot which is a YouTube channel
Run by lady we call scary Cary
Who interviews face weirdo
Super-Soldiers people have been
People who
Psychics psychics
But not a ton well maybe
If someone told her that
Who might be a racist alien
Abaddon
Her main source of information herbig whistleblowers this guy
Who is playing at the time
With his
Sentient spaceship Minerva
And his friends in the Raptor beings
Right right right
We didn't make this up
Nope to learn
We've observed this in the wild
Unfortunately over the time that we have looked
At this is supposed to be just a pressure release valve course come to realize that Carrie is also very insecure.
Our dovetailing together are two shows kind of took a little bit of the charm away from it
Butts
Sometimes you still just need a hit
We're going to be looking at a video that was released on Project Camelot on November 12th
Does a little bit of an election Q&A
Case collection
Hi everyone I'm Kerry Cassidy from prod Camelot
Hi Carrie so very happy to be here today but my
Didn't show up
So I guess you have some,
Reflector other and we'll have to
The reschedule
There
Anyway
So
I just thought I'd do a Q&A if that's
Useful
Now I want to say that I do not think
Anything is bad about a gas cancel
No no I only left that introduction in because
It is the
Set up
For a punchline later we're yelling Bingo all the time
You can figure out where the
The payoff to that joke okay
Alright
Canceled actually her
Nope it's a Fight Club scenario is definitely something
No way this guest shoot of ever cancel
You'll see once it happens
If you and I would be nice
Like I said you got Q's
Carrie's got at work
But it turns out this is even more than just a
Sakura name
What you started
Down this road
There's alot going on I can say that
In general
I did have a apricot dream last night finally about the outcome
Safari
Interesting
Dream that I had so maybe I'll just share that and then
You can go ahead and ask questions about whatever
So
I hear a caller on the Alex Jones Show talk about their dreams not interested
Cary open up the shows
I had a precognitive dream finally
Bury My Heart
Several days after
About what's going to happen here
Yes she gets into that right at the
Beginning right after
The top and it turns out that the she's a good storyteller
The seam
Before it was going on before the dream
Contacts
Happy Foods
Maybe
That might be the truth behind the word sheet music
The audience to know for sure
My dream basically was
And I had a very
They're shooting
5G at me last night so
I know Trump doesn't have what
Control
Over scalar weapons
Is that are being used
And so forth
So I was up most of the night
On and off
And then finally fell asleep
Am so I mean look
She was 75 G shot at her
Taylor laser vehicle
Instead she was saying that you and I get
Five you were having 5G shot at you that
That's enough
Aperture
How did she know
Cuz she didn't say what the
Effects of having 5G
No apparently
Not being able to fall asleep his sign of 5G attack
Well I mean I've certainly been someone who struggle with insomnia it. To my life
It takes me a long time to fall asleep it's frustrating
It sucks I have rented be like
I lay down and two minutes later I'm out and I get mad at me
It'll take me an hour and a half at least usually you're just laying there to fall asleep it sucks but if
If I could imagine that I was under 5G scalar attack
They probably be more excited I feel like it would make it impossible to sleep
Jonah
Instead of going to bed at midnight and falling asleep at 2 you fall asleep at 6
And you're worried about 5G attacks the whole time
Yeah maybe I'm glad I don't
Take the window with my phone
Having trouble sleeping does your phone have that app 25g shooting at
Actually
Emerges from a
That's that's important
Your Dalek phone
So this is the setting of The Dream
All night
Clyde and then
She gets to sleep at around 6 in the morning
And here is part of
The dream
And then I had this dream in which
I saw the television
And
Trump had taken it over
And was
Showing
Actually
Individual
And indict
And individuals that had Acts
Actually been killed
As part of their indictment
And I I guess a Military Tribunal
Situation
And
And it was all being announced
To the entire public
And I was very happy because
These individuals are
We're very dark
I'm involved
Hurting children in
You know the chill
Children in underground bases
Adrenochrome and all of that
So that was the dream
It was
Like a little movie
Play the dream
If I Were A Dream
She's dreaming about stuff he's read on blog
Well I think that she's tapping into the zeitgeist
A lot of the online extreme right
Disease
Get traffic tan message
Switchboards in
You know even people like Alex and Gage and half
This idea of
Righteously
Taking over
And killing their enemies
Yeah you know I can get
I get bloodthirsty to a point
You know somebody was whatever nonsense somebody wrote in like the Atlantic or something where it's like
But we don't want to see Trump dragged from the White House again
People don't want to see Trump taking away from the White House he needs to concede like an adult
And part of me is just sitting there going like
No I would like to see him dragged out by his hair I would like to see him dragged through the streets that would be great that's a little bloodthirsty I guess
I don't think it will I don't think
Good idea ask
I think the consequences of it are so much worse than whatever catharsis would get out of it
Second level of thought I don't have
The end bloodthirst that's all I need
Let's imagine a scenario where the does takeover broadcast television and announces like he's killed
What happens next
What kind of world are we living again
Just so you guys know and almost everybody
Horse
Pale for me guys
The IQ panel for my blood
So carries talking real
Specifically about upper
Who is been killed
The mystery Ensure
I'm not sure I'm I'm looking I'm scanning the chat
Right now and I'm not
Sure what some of these
Questions
Refer to if your friend
The details
We're very visual
So like I said
Television on
I was seeing it
It was
Literally
The pit part that it was on was a
Particular person who had been
Killed
As part of the
The cycle
Assertive
I don't know whatever you want to call it
Indictments and certainly
Payback
For his crimes against humanity
She doesn't say who she never says who know she had a dream it was visual so she saw the
Conceivably
I would say that it's either got to be Soros or Bill Gates Right
Sister is in the dreams of all right leading people that's
Two power demon clown power
I don't think it's still there on Elm Street
I don't know man
I don't know
Maybe it's not human
And maybe it's a Raptor
Could be
Whoa
What if what if it's an alien
Holyshit Alienware it has to be nailing wearing human face
Now that's a good point
Dad
Alabama reptiles
It's f***** up if all the sudden we hear that Trump killed all of his enemies
What if the same time
And he killed aliens David Icke
Train is going on David Icke is now my Surgeon General
What's nobody else can handle these Raptor surgeries
Anyway this person that use talking about has been killed already in the dream
But you won't say who it is
It's really frustrating
It was interesting
Because it was literally about
The fact that they already
So
That seems
Quiet
Adventurous
To come forward in that way
In theory is
Have said that they have
Certain people
Or it has
Put out there
Now
Trumpet courses
Said this yet
So this
This was an official
Report
And
It was clearly
Commandeered
A television
Station or maybe
And took the internet
Nobody was an official report in Madrid
In the dream it was official
How scary is this
How much does this fit all of your nightmare versions of What the Democrats are tripe
All of the internet right controls at least one TV stations
Communication ability to communicate with your audience community
So happy
So this might have been a vision this dream it might have been a dream
He says
Are they say
Qanon
And so and so forth
The philosophy behind it is
They want to show
So
My last
Video I said okay fine show us
You know in other words
Don't talk about showing us
Show us
I get the sense that there is a possibility that which he's trying to say is that her dream was a vision that was great
Answered by Q
Expecting something along those lines to be a little bit late is a belief
I can give you.
How long can you wait
On the whole revision from cute well I mean
Obviously you can wait a long time for a vision for
But
Like okay
She said last week
Banana thing to say about cute considering chirp
How are you still waiting
I think the dreams she thinks the dream as a response to her saying show me what's going on oh my God we're all going to die
This sucks
Because okay. You don't have to yell bingo
Cuz the Bingo is going to be in this clip
I got you
Afterwards I'd like you to explain to me why
This is the punchline to the joke of the guests canceling
My
Guess who is supposed to be here she is actually
The Gate of gay woman and
She
Considers herself
If something of a time traveler
She
Is also involved
And researching
I guess
CV
Say the name
And
Her book is going to be about
So
Hopefully we can get her back
She was on my show
A few years ago
So why is it really f***** up at the
This guest Miss
If you are a time traveler
It seems like you would
At the very least be able to make plenty of things on time
You would never miss an appointment if you're a time traveler
Happy maybe you can't use time travel for this kind of mundanity
You know, she had to go to
Get her hair appointment
I would suggest
That if you're somebody who has power over time
Manipulate it
For what
To whatever extent you can
To the point where people save if you fancy yourself a time traveler
Isaac but time is something that's on your mind
I think
Punctuality is probably a priority for you even if
Your talents are imaginary
I think I take issue
With something here I think I Let It Go by the first time but
Can you fancy yourself a time traveler
You see it seems like you either are or not myself a man about town
I also never leave the apartment so
No I just got out of you are neither a man nor a time traveler
Yeah I see
I think that your instinct to let that go is good because
I don't know if you're ever going to get any further truth on it
I like
Now I will say
That
With this person who takes their time travel who has a book coming out about covid
That book should come out three years ago
Did you bring the book to warn us about the show a couple years ago
Yeah that would be a good one to go back and check if she was like 3 years I'm going to write a book about this s*** just so you know
Plies I have some questions will check in on that and see you
To do
Fun that is good reason to time travel
The classic thing is I gamble on them but like
If you could go watch some like amazing moments
From likes
Dispute
Catharsis of this crowd
Just freaking out kind of fun
Mannitol
Watch Jesse Owens run
Hitler's f****** face
This guest didn't show up
And they shut up
Cuz they're talking about you
But Carrie mentions another guest
Someone asks
Ask question about Robert David Steele who is of course
A real weirdo
Is a lot of irons in many fires
True he does not however fancy himself time
No
However he was the guy who was on Alex Jones Show and talked about how the globalist
Kidnapping children and taking them two faces in space
And enslaving them
And then Alex got mad that everybody thought you believed it because you are he said
Yeah I believe you you are correct 100%
Project Camelot
This clip is very
Confusing I'd like you to listen to this
I think we have a little bit more
To this story
About Robert Davis
Very interested in what's going on in his life
Now I understand it
Benjamin fulford has come
Forward
Saying that Robert David Steele should be there
Candidate
You know I actually have
Seen the post
Kind of outrageous
She is
This always
Working under the orders
The Triad
Videos
Going back
First of all the original video I did we
With him where he
States what happen
12 Emerald
Which he was threatened
And so on
And had to base
Sickly
I think if he wants to stay in
Japan and stay alive
ISO
Now he's coming out against Trump
Strangely
Apparently Robert David Steele has turned on Trump which I didn't know about
Mostly cuz I don't care
And
To stay alive yes
To do the bidding of the Triad
Struggling to really comprehend this so if I understand correctly
Let me read exactly what I wrote down
Works for the Triad in Japan
Now that's
Robert David Steele David Steele CIA agent
Is that was actually the CIA they got just what he says
Probably I don't know it look dude here's the thing
I've listened to a lot of Project Camelot
I don't know who the f*** the Triad our president
Cucuzza but now there's a Triad
It's got to be pretty well I hope it's at least a trio
Otherwise our in real
Yeah this is confusing I don't like this sort of late
Reveal of Japan
Outlook
Every time I've ever seen he's been in the same study just inside he always has by Skype
Very nice looking study foot look wonderful wood shelves and tons of books
Baby just got one of those backgrounds is like a Shinto Temple
And she's like oh well he obviously lives in Japan
Now I'll maybe
I don't know cuz I've also listen to Robert David
Casteel's interview on like with Carrie
I don't remember the Triad
Coming up I don't remember Japan coming up
I remember any of this
I want to know who the Triad is
I want to know what they're doing with Robert
Think you can just toss that in there
Works
What's the Triad man in order to stay alive
The Illuminati
We know that
That there
Pretty involved in politics usually they like to Dabble
Yeah they're pushing back
About this election
Right now there's very
A great deal of
Evidence
Of Illuminati
Push back
I want to stop this really quick because one of the things that Carrie gets really upset about I really super upset
But not freaking out or anyting
She seems to be bummed out that people are not taking seriously the people who talk about
These allegations of wide
Spread fraud assure now
I would like to say that what
She does
In this clip
Is one of the reasons that no one takes these people seriously
Call this morning from someone one of my sources
Who said
Is that
I think it's Arizona.
The governor has come forward and said
Oh there's not enough
Boats to really cause a
Arica
And
So that Governor's Obby
We sleeping threatened
Obviously has gone on the side of the Illuminati even though
I think I have a
Arizona
Is the right person but I Arizona
Not sure
ISO
Dr. Eric
What I'm saying is that
Some governor and I heard it was a republican Governor I thought arras
Democrat
Anyone in the chat can
And let me know
Which it is
Do they have a gun
Cuz then I might
But this is what
Came out
This morning
Via source and it's out in the news
Details there. A lot a lot a lot of familiarity with
The topic I don't really know if it's a Republican or a Democrat or what they're talking about but I do know there's fraud
Like I I guess if you're mad that no one's taking that seriously I would suggest that you're not taking that
Seriously and that's why I asked to respond seriously to in Oman
Gets Arizona maybe somebody said something
Yeah the fuc
I'll do it
You can't care about recounts
Aliens that are real that is an issue for me to
Why do you care about electoral politics
Biden wins or Trump wins they're still
Extractor
Remaking them all day everyday what did I matter
Doesn't matter at all doesn't matter
Now that is true that is
Strange
These next two clips I think are really like
The balm
Little go on that
That to burn you're feeling this show is
Kind of nonsensical in the sense that it's somehow
Concerned with
Democratic politician
A tremendous amount of
Information and evidence out there the
The fighting is not all
One knows that
Watches my shows
That's just like all the other right-wing media outlets right
Just the same
Here is why Project Camelot is special
There's a
Tremendous amount of
Information and evidence out there the Biden is not
I was.
Is my show space
Case you don't know
There is reason to believe that he is a
Cyclone
Lyrica but I think
The clown he's also a walkie
The what
He's a walking that grow up man it's a walkie-talkie
Haircut
A gardener over here not knowing about what you want to come on man
I'd like you've been there know I did think it was a possibility but
Yes
We have a situation where you're talking about something very standard and right-wing is not all there
Explanation for it is why I'm single
He has he's a clone you and not only that
Walk-in
Come on man you're really embarrassing yourself
I'm willing to accept
You might be a Wocket
Well I can tell you that one of the things that might lead you to believe that he's a walk-in is
If he uses language weirdly
There's one particular
Clip
Actually
Quite funny
But also
Uncertain
Where he sang
I am going to
To be Joe Biden
That's what he says
And
He says quite a few others
Things that indicate to me
An alien who hasn't quite
Learn the English language
And so tense to put
Some words backwards or together that don't belong to go
But
My my instinct
Tends to say
This is kind of a man in Black
If you didn't know what Men in Black
We're supposed to be bodies
I know this going
Sound
What do you think these that have been dead and reanimate
And then
There's Bass
Physically a walk in and they get
They behave as if
They're alive
Apparently the dead body that an alien walks into
I mean I guess I can't really argue with any of it into a dead body
That is not what the movie Men in Black was about bettaway
Yeah
That's good!
The sound weird sometimes
I just Simone
Struggling struggling with their evidence
It said she ever hurt herself
Like you did she think that somebody
Could not possibly find
Misspoken it's because someone is shooting 5G at her
Spider attacks
Metronome that is like
Trump Miss speaks A Lot 24
This is where it comes to this where the rubber meets explains that I'm glad
Now I know that people used to
Criticize
Trump
Because Trump
Sort of uses language in a certain way but it
It's very unique
Him
And he's communicate
Show it
You have to have discernment and be able to
Totality of that word so much
Well do you hate it because it's the truth I hate it because they don't know what it means in the continue saying it over and over
And it's proof that there's an alien up in them
Corsage
Communicating and he's individualistic Ryan the only way to know the
Prince between the two is discernment my friend right now let me posit you this be real
Alright
Alien wise
Okay
Makes mistakes in the way that
We would consider Norm
Asian person who
Is talking in a very unique and individualistic way
Then that suggests that fighting is making mistakes in a way that is very common
Perhaps Perhaps
As if there's if that's your composure I'm in common for an alien who doesn't know in
What I would
Suggest though is that it is more likely the alien is somebody who is doing something different
From what we would consider to be relatively
Non-unique Behavior can I ask you a question sure
There's more than one alien right that you can walk in
Why would you choose one who doesn't know English
Like why would you ever choose
The alien for that assignment
Who is weird with the English got to cut its teeth on some assignment you know nobody starts out the most
Experience alien walk
We meet you to possess the f******
President of the United States
Make a lot of Publix
Know much English look at the Raptor being as a little bit iffy on verbs
Now I like that as a I think I like that isn't like relative place of earthlings in the universe
Is there like this is the guys
This is the guy starting out the new guy who's got to try and take over the president he's learning for a more
Fishing knot
At all not at all
This indicates to me either these aliens are
F****** in cop
They don't actually really want it there just f****** around Thursday to playful
That's not fair I mean I do know that English is one of those languages that's like notoriously difficult to learn
Later in life
Could this be something like that definitely be able to understand
I still say that if I'm an alien I'm not
Signing off on the walk-in who doesn't know English communicating
Probably job number one
For someone who's running for public office
I would say
Sorry you're a great walk Henry
Bad speaker lucky do a lot of good stuff we're going to keep you on here you're not
Man
I wonder
When did he become a walk-in
Going to walk in this entire time or recently become a
No idea
Alright
Etsy
I think maybe
That might be good for us
Because his previous policies
Not good
So now maybe he's an alien who's going to be a more Progressive politician I like it
Well
Is probably still in there
Recognize
Derek could still be
Joe Biden assault
Can still be in the body at the same time but they
The push to the
And they are not really able
Go to communicate
Variety
Is or they may actually be
Completely
Walled-off
And occupied else
I swear
Just trying to hang on to
Really being there
And this can happen with a lot of illnesses
People so it's not
Not that unusual
But what is unusual and what the Illuminati dark magicians must be
Laughing there
Their asses off
About
Is the fact
That the American people have actually voted for
So I know that hilarious
A sort of a slap in the face
Behind the scenes
Ministration who have
Plenty of magicians
You are going to see through these clothes and no
That's what they're doing
The slap-in-the-face for Trump's magician magician
So embarrassed that they lost to a walk-in
I see now I've got a whole new world that I would enjoy twice as much
Imagine if Rudy Giuliani was it
Exactly is incompetent in Marana
But could also fail at using Magic
That be great I love it
I love it much like the idea of Robert David Steele being in the employee of the Triad the walk-in is a new
Neutered
But I've not heard on other
Did this is really expanding
Can you reach that so using the power of love
They're really good
So recently election weird Steve pieczenik
Come on the Wardrobe with Owen Shroyer and talk about how the election was actually an elaborate set-up
Yep news blog
Chain technology and barcodes watermark
Then they immediately
30%
Didn't have that issue a retraction
Qanon
Carrie's into that
Obviously a lot more votes
Trump then went
For Biden
In truth
But
We it
It's a very good
This time at least
At the moment
To know exact
Play how many
You know for
So
I I think
Perhaps
The
The blockchain Estates
Is revealing some of this
But I'm actually
I'm sure
I'm curious
How the block
Watching with you
If it was used it was you
You know and
Thoughts
Sort of software
Yeah I'm curious
It's too but I also don't entertain any of these ideas
Cuz they're very
Stupid it's it's really unfortunate
To continue to hear well obviously this thing is true I'm curious
Sister how or why they did it but obviously there's massive amounts of fraud
But I don't
Cuz I just wanted play that clip just to illustrate that like out here's the connection with Steve
China King all that b*******
Should not send
Because I'm too excited
About this next Highway
This next clip oppa
Opens up all sorts of
Nuvista operas
I had
How did whistleblower
That was revealing
What is an essence
The fight in the Pacific
With our
Navy
And these myrrh
People
Thank you
Back in
Basically associated with
With movie underwater
I am
Sailors
So I had a whistleblower in this
Disregard an
I'd like that you were nodding aggressively through that
Totally the sailors
The Sailor
Associated with the kingdom of moves people
What are navy got mixed up at some point
Love it
Few more details on this massive do like trillion-dollar destroyers have
Issue with merpeople and Triton related back then
The holes are so reinforced trident
We've learned from the wooden Hulls
I just feel like these are issues we're like we need to
Saddle
Fundamental precept
Like we just need to like
I'm not going to believe you when you tell me that there was a battle with mu and be good merpeople at Harmony
Until you prove to me that merpeople
I can't go to the second
Sad because I'm not granted you the first one
People are taking his red
How many species continue to go undiscovered everyday
Raptors Mercantile dog
All the time you can buy
Merpeople
Big beetles in Vietnam
People are down there
Sure
So problem for the Illuminati and all them
Turns out they've tried a bunch but also if they do kill him it's mutually assured destruction so they
In
The chat is saying
She would have been killed Trump would have been
And killed by February if
If you want
Well
They've tried to
Kill him many
Palmetto
Important to realize that
It again is
Is it's kind of like a very
Stand
Be honest it's a lot like
You know the guy
Right showing
If you start feeling people on one side
By then the other side is
People on your side
And pretty soon they'll be no
Already left
So mute
Call Mutual
Destruction
And so this is not
And some people
The nuclear
Option
This is not really a notch
For the game being played
Today and
It doesn't mean they won't
Don't try doesn't mean
It couldn't have
I'm just saying that
I know they've
Try the number
X
I believe that
That Trump and team do have
And cool
Yai
To think that it should mean that they wouldn't try that they wouldn't try it
Direction and it's not the way the game is being played to or whatever that
It should not be a situation where they've tried and failed a bunch of time because they would know that if they succeeded they would
Destroy themselves in process but I mean you look at you look at Cold War history and I can actually see
See people deciding like
Well here's my problem with that
The Soviet Union existed
That is a good point
Stuff to get around that
So if he's got ET protection yes
Probably from Pleiadians by the way probably cuz there's a good ones
Well hold on I don't know if you know this
What they were actually
You don't almost every time we've ever heard Carrie talk about alien races they're always uniform
They're always like
These ones are good because like they are all like
Resonating with something or what if there's some sort of like
There's a magical element to it's like you cannot
Be bad if you are whatever that is unspoken
It turns out that might not be the case Okay so please radians are actually evil Ono
I believe that
Trump and team do have
Of
At least one race and I'm pretty sure it's
Pleiadians
But it's a certain division
Because there are some dark
And that was
Proven by my interview
With Eddie
Eddie
His name
I'm drawing a blank on
Hey
I love the idea
The words that was proven by my interviews
We can really good boy we can either decide from these interviews
Eddie Paige is a raven crazy person
The fact that he's an alien
We can believe that some idioms must be evil
Well there is that
That's where is that interesting
Decision-making tree
Bike
I can't not believe that he's a Pleiades
Must mean that there are evil. That's a good point or you could just say
Guys talkingshit he was talking s***
Only because he wasn't evil play 80 and it doesn't have to be an either-or C
Situation dance
I got to say it's a liberating to not believe any of this
It is nice it is nice
I feel less trapped in making up my own bulshit on a daily and concentrate
It's very simple to explain what's going on
Don't need to go further
Mercury can speak freely
All the s*** you want for CNN
One of the reasons I can speak
Speak so freely
Here is that unconsidered
Super friend
If I was mainstream they probably
Probably would have fired me or killed me
A long time
You know so
It's when
We're out on The Fringe that were allowed
How to get away with
Talking like this
I saw though I am
Under attack
And sometimes
It's very awesome
To strike
Call Aetna Point she can speak freely because
Is her boss
You know do one can
Can stop her from
But yeah if you had an employer you wouldn't fired long ago
Cuz you don't do good
Yeah sure we would have been fired long ago not this early because
You know terrible work with because why would anyone pay us to do this
It's inaccurate
There is a freedom that comes with
It's like not being attached to some kind of a big entity or or something
Inherently like
Integrity
Bearing about it
Strategist
Killed if you work for CNA had fired
You talkin about
F****** Murphy people battles
Interesting thing to hear on our Navy took out three or four people and broke a tree
Oh god dammit
Tradies Rogan
I like her version of the house we always live in the the enemies both
Ultra powered and Incredibly impossible to it can't win in what you know
Super Why
Purse feels more like
A game though because she's like
I'm allowed to do all this stuff cuz I'm On The Fringe
They're still attacking me though
So it's like a legitimate same thing for her is like why would you
Do an attack
Unless you
Kind of mean it to fail over and over and over again if you want do you want to inconvenience
The people like her where a truth-teller is but you don't want to make Martyrs of them I'm connected
Combining her and Alex's police about this the way they rationalize
Like hey I've existed
For a long time and no one seems to
Sicario
Kind of like yeah if you went
If you act too hard against me it would prove me right
Or that kind of but if you didn't go against me at all I would
Be too powerful
I would okay
Alright so it's sabotage
That's what they're more in
Disconnecting know I can see you have figured it out.
She's going to
Series on the same page is Steven terms of the like water marks on Fallas Sherlock change the whole thing
Seems to be on another sort of similar to a pin that is really thinking
Melania
Thoughts about
Well
I think Melania is
Let me just say that
Captain Mark
Says he believes Melania is it
With Annie.
And that she is a canoe it
Conduit
For Trump
To get
The download
And
And I think that's a very pie
Yeah
I got that
San Marco
She's not fully
And that's also
I think it was an interesting wave at people like hairy or trying to
Rationalize
Say at the sense that Melania doesn't seem to be doing anyting interested at all in this.
Trying to have this like alright Trump
Is a superhuman battling against
The forces of Darkness
Demonica child abusers who live under the Getty museum or whatever the
The f*** Indian like you have this heroic
Figure and then his wife is somebody who just
Seems to not give a s***
Buy anything
In order to make that make sense you have to create this elaborate backstory was I guess
Don't talk that much in public doesn't get involved with too much
A conduit for the
Spell Trump with his secret
Protection sure sure
So do the aliens
Get like upgrade
Okay
The aliens upgrade Trump with a new wife
And that's why he's had so many
Yeah I mean I guess I guess that's one way you could get around way you do it yeah
Trump with the help of his conduit wife
He's doing
Can't stress this enough
There's big adrenochrome
Out there
Okay you know how those big Pharma
Bigeloil
There's also a big
Adrenochrome manufacturing Industries publicly traded
On the black market
Secret market
Yes Market
And this is so crucial
And that's the same thing
Adrenochrome
And that whole
Manufacturing
Production line
Find that involves
You know
Taking a baby
You know from their parents
Whatever
Or even
Invade Iraq
Creating test tube baby
As product
And then
Adrenochrome
Rend
This is a very diabolic
Process
There's nothing they have
Control over
Disregard
Now they may be at
Get
And that has to involve
A battle
And you can
Nicely
So that means
A war
That means
The one with
The biggest gun
When
You know the best
Technology
And so on
So
This is what
We're dealing with
And what she's dealing with
That's what
Dealing with
He's dealing with a manufacturing industry and I'll trying to make this to babies to scare and then drink it
I got to be honest all too often I don't really think about what he has
Empathize a little bit more question though
So we can clone people
Right
Okay so
That means we can basically manufacturer
Bodies
Right-wing that suggest we could also manufacture just
The blood
And we can also synthesize adrenochrome
So
I don't understand it so I guess it has to be some like dark ritual thing that they're talking about
The game The Intergalactic strength
I guess
But in this cosmology it seems like you could just really easily manufacture Underworld movies
We ever talk about movies whenever we're talking about Carrie Carter
You can make your own talking blood and you move on everybody gets a good job yeah
Yeah
You know it's interesting that they do
Ever go down that road of of thought
It's to their detriment
Because it's a big gaping hole in tire
But
What I think is interesting about the way that Carrie is
Expressing this in presenting it is like this is not going to end without a war
So if
Award
Doesn't happen
Internally
Sure
Then that is evidence that this adrenochrome manufacturing is going all up and rougher
There must be a giant conflagration
Where else
There is no change in the status quo
That's f***** up what if we got Congress to regulate the industry
What is an electoral politics why isn't she campaigning for enough Senators income
Congressperson
To write a law regulating the use of adrenochrome
You broke my brain
I don't know why she's not trying to go to Civic route
I'm just saying if we got a participatory Republic I think she should start there instead of
The secret war that might be a good first step
At this point carries kind of running out of energy in like out of
You know petering out a little
Sticks couple Quest
Distance from the chat
I don't think that she actually reads the questions themselves
But response to them first one is about
The queen
Find out if there's anything else
Okay so somebody thing
Did the queen was
Beheaded
And we don't have the regular
Whatever
Is a lot of this is
Picture in my
These people
Put out the stuff
That doesn't mean
Everyone knows the queens of walk-in
Call man
Dum Dums think that the queen is a clone that's not true
Joe Biden's the Clone duh
So strange
To try and figure out like what
The difference between
Conjecture and conjecture
Sure. What completely different don't
It was proven in the interviews with Eddie Paige dance on play demons are evil
That's all you need to know
The call about whether or not Trump
Is an otaku
Oh that's good question
Anunnaki
No
The mountain.
Is not
Azaria
General Patton
She is
Commission
Is
Alien
Incarnation of a general
General the D General Patton that we are speaking of
Okay
When did he die
Actually
I did look this up he died
Just before Trump was really who maybe he is I think that's why I assumed that's why they
Otherwise they would feel real stupid
Buick 6-8 months off
Cartoon 64 60-month spiritually Lounge Lounge
Yeah you know you're right
I got you
At this point Carrie discusses
Israel and
Her feelings.
I'm going to say I don't respect her enough to even even
Like a joke
About
Terrible's is stupider ideas
Get into more interesting territory
Alex Jones believes
But there is a virus
Covid-19 is
But it's also a hoax even though he has David Icke on who says that it's not real at all
That's another version of this
Put also seems to believe in medical science
I guess Terry doesn't believe virus
Okay
My understanding of viruses
And I credit.
Actor Robert Young
Teach me about this
Is that
Actually they've never isolated
A real vibe
Viruses
Azar
Are not what you think
And that there
Simply poison
Ourselves
When were
When my face
A poison
An inner environment
Through food we
8 how you think she might be right A lot of the times I worry that my humors and eicher's are out of balance with each other and that
Going to happen and then you'll just start
Influencing a lot of people thought stuff like that but like you Murs
View
People thought about like
Jerbs
Yeah
But they were wrong
The viruses are
The part of what
Germs
And germ Theory
Burial
Please activate
Sure
And then that
Information
Was actually
As usual
Wrong
And doctor
I've been several
Dr. Robert Young
About all of this
Gone my way
Website search under his
And find those inner
Play recommend them
If you want to find out
History
And why germ Theory
At is no longer believe
By the most
Intelligent advance
Doctors
So that's
Important
You got to do a little better than Robert Young as your reference
Not we talked about him on another Project Camelot episode has the guy who like went to jail
You talk someone into
Not to getting treatment
For cancer
And like getting likes his like holistic approach
And then they got
Stage 4 incurable progression
I got sued for like
Millions of dollars
Isn't that like malpractice
Have a license
Enter.
Cuvee most
Advanced hippest coolest Doctor Who's telling you all about how germ theory is wrong
For doctors
Cuz this is silly
I'll agree I like her collar
It's very old-fashioned compared to obviously things Creator Insider
Your cells and then they explode out whenever it's poison that's
That's brand-new researched and nobody is ever thought hit that
Maybe spontaneous generation of poisons could explode through your body
That's a new one to look dude
It's all a plot by
The aliens
Maybe
So you think
Germs
Viruses that everything is contagious
It's not
But you know what are
Bad dreams memes
What is contagious
And can be
Taken in through osmosis
And in essence
Through mean
Is the mental
Thank you Cat
Because you are
Become
Eating my mind
40 become persuaded
Influence
Mental
So that means that when you
Are in a household
What is it called
You can easily
Catch
Through what
Empathy
And so
This is
It's all in the way you feel
That's first
First and foremost
Now interesting late this would be really easy or I mean there would be a way to scientifically Tryon
And I get to the bottom
To construct something
Knowing that someone you care about deeply is sick causes you to get sick
And I don't think that studies have borne that out
Oh yeah yeah yeah when you're in a house with someone who has a contagious
Yeah you get it because you
That would be indistinguishable from getting it because of germs
Attitude very easily if say you were
Long distance away from subject like that's what I'm saying very deeply but I don't know of any transmission of diseases
Is long distance
There's no morphic transmission of disease scary can
Established
There's no point me to some literature on it
I'd be interested
But I've had a doctor with your name on it
Robert Young
Not going to listen to him oh boy I got one last thing to say here she's talking to a lot of people all around the world
And they're all interested in the select
People all over the world
You know Anaconda
I travel so much
In the past
Traveling lately
And I
They are also a small
Realize that
In a certain sense this is all about
Who is going to run
Planet Earth
At least on the humans
So
Oki
Think I am
I am
So they've done for now
Epic 2
I don't know I think that it's such a gross
Perspective 3 like whoever wins this election is who's going to run the planet
Just because I mean first of all it's so america-centric so disrespectful to the other countries of the world
What's second
Like I don't
Sit like a horse
What everything to
Turn out that Biden
Becomes president
I don't want him running the world know very strange that these people people like carry people like Alex
They do want Trump running the world
100%
Defeat
It's just so weird like why would you want that even if you like this guy I liked Obama
Is President obviously had some problems in a lot of policies and decisions
But even as much as I supported
Hermes the president of United States that never would want him to be the head of the world
No
It's it's very silly it's childish
Yeah
I don't
Get how they can drive those two things
Together without just
Openly saying like
I want the end of all participatory governance
.
I mean if you have you can't vote
For aliens like if you believe that that
The real world
What's going on behind the scenes
What does it really matter if you give up the pretense of democracynow.org
Sure
Yeah you can feel good about casting a vote but that persons working for a lizard
So doesn't matter
Really
Like the thing that's interesting to me about how they always go about this
This is that
At no point in time is it like
Let's get enough people together
Because they know that they
Actually get paid
Anythink
Let's get a movement together there just like it has it all has to be in secret
Because if I try to get a bunch of people to know it they
Realize that I'm going to
Option option is someone else build something and then co-opted
Yeah
Yep but look
I just think like
You know I start to feel like
Spit really bad
For these people
Like this is this is sad
Like if you're somebody who's like
I'm all about the ins-and-outs of secret programs
And I'm all about the like
All these aliens have been visiting us forever and my friend is definitely not a murderer talks to Raptors in prison
He tells me all about these Great Space Adventures
Spaceships
You should not give a
S*** about a president
Degrading
For you too
Okay so
Business
Revealing anything about space
He's not you so I can approve you right
Do you know that
I think one of the hugest thing
That's been an issue for them
With Trump being president
Because we've heard this joke so many times or I at least I have this the the joke so many times like
When Obama was President I didn't have to care about politics that's why I liked him
Cuz I could
Could walk do my day and think that there's a reasonable person who's try
You know
Kind of think with Trump
Everyone has been paying attention
All the time
Yeah so all of that secret stuff all the stuff that's going on behind the scenes has to be so secret now
Either
You believe it to the point where you
Completely lost any sense of reality right you just have to go like now this
This is just too.
I just think you know what the history books are written
No no right about Project Camelot
It's just
It's just you should do
Everyone who
Made a decision to sign up with this is like
It did they made a bad move
Yeah
Strategically they made a bad move for their grip
It seemed like it was going to be really good in the shorter but it's just not going to pay off
There's going
To be too much that you're going to have to answer for later and explain away like
How do you get a
Explain Melania being a space conduit in 5 years
Like what
She still has space conduit why are they let her go
Okay sure whatever
Space spider
Okay and then you're like Biden is he still a walk-in
Yeah that's a good question
Well I think that's probably why it's so
They're also very desperate
For Trump to remain in office
Forever
Because
As long as he's in office forever you can make up all kinds of bulshit but after a while
You know everybody starts
Looking at reality again like a man
S*** that's crazy
Why did people believe that he was going to
How many hundred Biden is just gone
We just don't even talk about that s***
I'm sure some people still alive
Again
I don't know the alien angle on that is
It's interesting
I feel like
There there was a part of me that while I was listening to this episode as like
Where what is this have to do with space
And then it did come in
I was like oh that's
It's pretty funny people battles of merpeople battles walk-ins
And how did Robert David Steele's working for the Triad
But yeah
It's kind of I feel like a she's in a rut
2 yeah
How
Can't believe they're there
This committed to not admitting that they got caught
Rothschild
Because you know I made like that
The 22 people that we talked about
Maybe
Alex
Are both psychic
Can't get caught have built themselves up so much that to admit even the slightest bit of
Got Hoodwinked
Co-op is a real Hitta
To the branch they're both psychics would be validated if they were on the wrong path for 4 years at the same
Apologize
Oh boy I don't know anyway this little trip down here Road
Hopefully our beginning of this week and weekend.
And how that's going up shirts going great
Jordan we are at a local charity
Area to help out people doing gossip
Dzx Clark
I'm Daryl rundus I am truant time traveler
Alex
Birthstone colors