I have great respect for knowledge B. I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guy
Knowledge fight
Nike.com
Jews
What's up
What's
But my brakes but might be a little bit busy
Disappointing but it's again Assassin's Creed
LOL
I've been taking my time playing a casual laid
About the game is
Without giving any spoilers or anyting
I find myself playing this game and
Haven't
More moral
Choices
In a lot of other games at the past
And part of it
Is there are choices that you can make
I'm almost certain will not affect the game at all
But I feel bad about
I don't know if it's just that I have not been exposed to games than to do that well in the past
But I feel I feel a lot more like
These little things that you run into what your chores around the world today
The little thing I can rip somebody off if you want to and I don't know it'll ever know but
But you'll know you will know absolutely
I realize like later on I just finished requested later out I was playing otherwise like
I feel bad about what I did to that guy
I think it was the right thing to do but you know what
It doesn't make me feel good
I failed the test bro
Age of calamity
The Hyrule Warriors
But I just can't
You can
Disappointed I started dabbling in a little bit because you know it's a
Can't not
That's what happened it happened so quick
Novice Edward a Gators
A brush
I just
I guess but my feeling Andres it's fun
Calamity is fun
And if anybody enjoys that I don't think you're wrong
I just kind of had expectations of more of a Dynasty Warriors ask game
And I just did that are that it wasn't scratch it hasn't been
For what it is
So I can't give it right back got to keep it on the moral choices
How about you
I was looking for
We we played together
But I think I'm going to get into like Cooperative board games I'm going to find all those
We're going to play them together it's
Can be fantastic
So I went to a board game store
Guy who is very very helpful
Knew everything about board games and card games in the assorted like
And I was like hey
I need some help
Getting a board game
I'm just starting to get into this news like okay
This one is super accessible
I called Mansions of Madness
Brought it home
There's like 4,000 pieces
Companion app
For a goddamn iPad
Damage rolls and s*** there's a whole thing on it and I was like
This is very exciting
African people
Play that accessible is a different
Definition but you brought it up
Play it on it like a live stream or something
There's a lot of fun for sure
I'm so Jordan today I got something I'm looking forward to it Matt is
A Nutty Astro about from Alex
December 1st and 2nd 2020 of Danza
That is
Tuesday and Wednesday of this week and I was going to
Look here
What's the deal
As I was getting this episode ready we record on Thursdays and on Thursday
Alex
Dropped
A big episode with him and Joe Rogan
In the Infowars Studio hours
And of course
This is
Is Verizon at the bat signal
But
It doesn't quite realize it in the same way as Alex being on Rogan show
Cuz
Probably not going to be nearly as interesting no I don't care about Joe Rogan being interviewed
Does he have to say that I'm going to be interested in from from alligator View
Perspective Alex's interesting 100 million.
Alex is interesting on Rogan because he's desperately trying to steal Rogan's audience
Impress upon them that he knows things and yet
He is a guru they should follow one Holloway from Joe
Turn on Infowars is not that interesting Jose Roberts
Austin
What happened were such friends
Staff
I don't know
Where is Alex being on Rogan requires a emerge
Urgency episode
We got to get ahead of that thing
I don't fuk
No I don't know if anyone will care
I don't think this is a tree falling in a forest and no one's there I don't know I don't know if that makes me sound
I'm going to listen to it
And if it's worthwhile it'll be our episode for Monday
I know that by the time is episode is out people
Might be aware of the fact that Rogan did
Pocketnow or episodes
So we'll see on that but
Like I said
Lot of fun
I'm excited
Stupid I'm excited I'm excited
Go to I think
The first Jeff a thank you so much
I'm a good girl
Text Dexter K thank you so much
Jordan looks exactly like I imagined
But damn doesn't
Thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Very much
Thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Jusuf j.p. thank you so much during our policy want
Joseph
Text Emily w
Journal
Next time
Guess what
What your balls are walking
I think you took of people who donated on elevated level appreciate that very much
David M thank you so much
Your mother was a hamster and your father smelt of elderberries
Technocrat
Heroin
Freakishly large
Thanks so much Dave and thank you so much your mother was a hamster and your father smelt of elderberries
Both of you
What you could do is
You could gather 225 of your friends ages
3 and up put together a nice little night every week
To get together read the rulebook Maybe
Get the rulebook by which I mean find some local charities or bail funds in your area.
Help out and then get all your friends together and get it done
Thank you thank you
Eczema
Nice little thing
From Cassandra s Jordan you have a little box inside
Cassandra sent me a coloring book
Which Iowa
Pretend does not exist
It's right Right Alright terrifying adult coloring books
Cthulhu coloring books
For kids
More horrifying
Boring head
Wow this is
Is intense
Elliot's espresso nib
Peanut butter
Nut Butters grown up
This isn't at slow this is a DC the coloring and that everything is
It look at it like peanut butter chocolate
Nespresso
I don't know man I feel like you have some reticent
About
Assertive
Extravagant butter
Did you know I'm excited to try to get nut butter here's the problem that I'm seeing with this
It's it's not even distribution
I know I think you're right but it's looking like there's just weird
Black jumpsuit
I'm excited I'm going to try it looks like look forward to a full report looks delicious
Alright
We're jumping in
December 1st
Alex open
The show with a video
From the night before
Big breaking news
I had to get down
2 weeks
You are
With the documents
This is such a
Perfect way for Alex to do business
I love this so much
Watch because about painfully transparent
I don't need no I don't need to know what this is about or what does alleged whistleblower is claiming because I know
Oh how this is setup
Journalism
Know when it's being done
Sincerely
If there actually was a whistleblower and there actually were documented approved whatever it is they're claiming
It would be all really
The story
The document to be provided to help give credibility to
To the claims of The Whistleblower was making because
Otherwise it's
Just a person making claims that you aren't really able to fully assess
Think about it
In any conceivable world's can you imagine Glenn Greenwald meeting with Snowden
Been announcing that he has a whistleblower's ready to make a bunch of claim
And if anybody challenges them that's when the documents
I think it's a great idea how you keep it in your plus two bag of holding until you need it on set
Never would have acted like that because they had documents that didn't help them
Without knowing
Anything about this whistleblower or the claims I refuse to believe that anyone would behave this way unless this was an incredibly
Desperate block
If we are telling something
If we are challenged what does that even mean
Hey what are you talkin about that you have a story you'd never hold back the thing that Pro
Proves your story promising to release it only if you have to
Schoolyard bully or
Entry-level extortionist shitt
I will tell you guys about deepthroat the moment someone asks but until then you just got to believe it
Harley against Alex's entire career
Guiding principle
He's often told guests that if they have information they have to get it all out or else they're putting themselves at risk
Alex
Constantly says that his guests.
He doesn't want to have secret information that other people know he has
Since that's when things get dangerous
Exactly knowing Secrets is okay
And it's too late once you've already spilled a secret
But having people know that you know a secret and that you have
Said anything puts a Target on your back
Dangerous this is
The Gate of gates all over again
This is exactly what happened back in 2011 when Alex interviewed Bob Chapman
Bob implied that he had secret Intel on Ronald Reagan which Alex
Insisted he needed to stay on here now because
Said that he had
The secret and he was in danger if he didn't get it out in the open
Bob said that he'd seen a video of Reagan get
Pigs and Alex got weird out disappointed that it wasn't
Something more communists
Getting on are insanely as proof Hill produce is pushed
Connie's
Talk to Alex's entire careers methodology
It's not enough that much way really sadly broken idiot trying to Bluff it as a bombshell story that's actually a dud and
I could tell you that without knowing any other thing about where this this clip goes
Show me Reagan getting pegged and then I'll believe you
The end
I was like alright
Give a s*** like you could have said he could have said anything afterwards
And I would have been disappointed cuz
If you start by saying like we have all the proof and if the Brian stelter
Tries to get mouthy with me
At least the proof I'll do it
No will then why not release it now
Right
Dizzy your dress that at all
Why she's waiting for someone
He likes to set traps
This is about
You think you can guess
Do I think I can guess what
The Whistleblower have been Sunday night
Monday night
I want to say it's got something to do with Michigan
Okay
That's interesting
Executive
35 Hospital
Network
Western
Purple
Is exposing the fact
Covid-19
Grab
We receive this information
Yeah I was surprised too I really thought the
Russian religion
Kind of forgot that Alex is spinning multiple plates
See I was I was caught on my on the back
Keto as they say when is I go this is
The covid thing
It's almost kind of ridiculous that people are still denying covid
I mean it's almost convert it's insanely ridiculous ridiculous before but it seems like
This isn't what the season is on your show Alex
It seems like this is
How old were doing
He gets to talk about this with a blower here and this is
Kind of
I don't think I believe this
Hospital Network
UPMC
UPMC stands for the University of
Pittsburgh medical center and the network actually includes more than 35
Their website includes 36 Hospital campuses but they also have a satellite hospitals around that they manage but you know that
Included in the network
The bottom line about UPMC is it a giant entity
Their board of directors and executive team are all publicly listed and I would definitely try and track down who Alex is talking about but I
I'm sure it's not someone on that level and
I just
I started to listen to this unlike you got these documents you're never going to f****** produce you going to forget this even happened in a week
I'm not going to
Amplify the disappointment by trying to figure out which name on this
List you're trying to allude to
Not going to read the the chicken bones that I've thrown down on the ground I think you should have
To ignore that entirely
He has is before
For you to engage with it he must produce one
That you can research
Otherwise he's trying to get around you specifically
I've gone I've gone so far as to find a list of names of the people he's pretending this is and that's good enough
For me
Yeah that's it that's too much work your giving him too much credit
Well that's actually here with this
Almost certainly fake person
The latest so-called surge
Covid-19
Around 600
For covid-19 hospitals
Wide open
Most patients stayed overnight for observation because they tested positive
Media will say hospitalization patients have surged over 600%
Pasta spinach
It is a fake test
First of the time
Salik is reading also a bit of an Infowars article there but he's also just making up a lot of stuff and throwing it
Here are the parts of that clip that do not even appear in the Infowars article about this whistleblower
Resume Alex is just
Saying these things to try and apply your associate that with the Whistleblower
Just incredibly respond
This whistleblower article says nothing about anyone saying all the hospitals are overwhelmed
The circumstances would obviously be different to different areas where there are varying rates of infection that lead to hospitals
Canonbury mobiles of available medical resources
This article does not say that this
600 beds represent
What's 10% of the hospitals
Capacity
According to the American Hospital directory the hospitals that are listed as part of UPMC
7371 bed
But the number of excited in the blurbs that some that I can find about the network r8000 which
Think it's probably reasonable
Actually be less than 10% of their capacity but
It's kind of a meeting with statistic to discuss this way
As we don't really have any information about
The distribution
Gallup the needed bet ya don't know where the beds are
Mary's Hospital
Nor do we know how many of these bags are icub
Is there Airborne Airborne isolation pets
According to triblive as of November 20th there were 17% of a lability on the ladder bed type
Which is enough to worry
People
This is not something we could be easily captured by simple statistic
That's what I was just trying to do it just
Also
In addition to the article
Not in there the percent of there but I don't know if he's making that up
Or
I don't know it doesn't appear to be a blower
Ask for the no deaths
Spring among the 600 hospitalized individuals
I would be interested in seeing proof of that
Pittsburgh is in Allegheny County and on Tuesday
18 people died with covid-19 in the account
UPMC as hospitals and other counties to which
Also have
Stardust
I just don't know anything about this client and I just would need to see whatever documents Alex's with
Challenger the only thing you can do I'm not MSM but okay we
Challenge you to produce the documents
All I have
Stop
The stuff about the test being turned up 45 times does not appear in the article about this whistleblower
It seems to be at Alex's putting words in their mouth
Similar things I could say about the nonsense about the German
What Alex is boring supposed whistleblower claim and then ripping on it to make it
Etsy more bombs
If you read the actual article on this all the person appears to be claiming is that the hospitalization in the UPMC cyst
What up from 96 to 600 beds
They were occupied during this last. It's being characterized as a server
No specific data is given about these patients just that quote
Patients were kept in observation overnight and no deaths resulted
This is nonspecific to the point of being meaningless
Pennsylvania has a database where you can find all the information about county-level hospital bed availability
Give you a sense of the picture if you want
You're the last available report
In the entirety of the state
There are 4290 adult ICU beds
Total
Of those
695 are available
Which is 16 /
This is not to me there's other
At the other statistics to that you want but there's one
There's 16% of ICU beds
Are available
In
The entire State events
I can't stress this enough
This is not a whistleblower delivering meaningful information
And if you read on through the Infowars article about this
You can see what's going on
If you start with five patients
225 domini will say there's a 500% increase in cases
Sounds terrifying right
This article is essentially in force trying to explain how numbers work to Their audience
Suspicious about percentage sign
Sure a 600% increase sound scary but it couldn't be like 20 more people who cares
It's no big deal
But
This line of argumentation is really not good
Because I jumped from five cases somewhere 225 Wood
Definitely be a bad sign
Harborview remember with a numbers were like early on
In the car Coronavirus
Jump like that
In February
People with B would rightly have been worried about it
And if you're in a small-town let's say that has five cases right now
And tomorrow there's 25 that would be a big deal to real problem Community transmission
What else is attempting to do here is make this reality of rising covid cases and hospitalizations not worried his audience
By taking the numbers and shrinking them
It's baffling really because even for Alec
This is a little insulting to his audience is intelligence
This is him banging on them not
Feeling
To buy bringing a fake whistleblower
Explain how percentages work
It's really Elementary stuff and it's kind of degrading like it
Speak highly of his audience either
But this isn't hey if you only take the first like
Few little bits of a logarithmic
Scale it looks not scary at all it's the last part of the parabola if you just ignore the last part of the parabola where to go
Real fast
Yeah
Number to worry about 500% increase could be 125
A lot more
I do I don't even know what kind of like
Alright charade is beating
Alright let's start here
If you multiply 2 by 2
That's it that's so much
But that's only for an interview multiply that by 2 that seems like a lot but that's only if you multiply that by 2
That is quite a bit more then if you multiply that by 22 32
That its 64 and there's 128
So Alex keeps on going
Eisenhower gets attacked
The idea of
Testing
You see the big reports about the famous females
In your blood incredible in dollars
Call Campbell
What does PCR stand for
Instead
So a couple things real quick
Kary Mullis the inventor of the PCR test
Died on August 7th
He did not come out and say anything
About the PCR test
Covid-19 being a fraud
Pictures of Alex is trying to
Reply
So here is
The clip the Alex immediately after plays
ComEd
Gary Mullis Ismay
Find this virus in you at all
The PCR if you do it well you can talk
Find almost anything and anybody
Start making you believe in the assertive Buddhist notion that everything is contained and everything else right I mean
A play one single molecule
202 something that you can really measure
VCR can do then there's very few molecules that you don't have at least one thing
One of them in your body I'll get you
Clean that is Meaningful
The entire clip that Alex plays
This comment is out of contacts
It's from aquest
Question and answer session that Mullis did about using PCR test
Thing to detect HIV back in 1993
A lot of the stuff sounds applicable to the current pandemic
But it's really not
I got the most damning you can make this quote out to be is to understand maybe Malin
Mullis was expressing that this form of test is it good for determining
The quantity of something in somebody
Rather it detects the presence
Your absence
It's important to understand
In the context of these comment
So you was making though because
It sounds like what he's saying is that if you look at people you can find any disease on them
That's not
The case he's talking about HIV patients
Simply about how do you have that virus
There's a good chance
You may have others and maybe many other
He literally says that almost exactly after we're Alex
Cuts the clip off
Is that you don't need to test for HIV you don't need to test for the other 10,000 retroviruses that are unknown
Also in the subject
Somebody's got HIV
General is going to have almost anything that you can test for
Because they have definitely been hiv's a fairly rare
Virus
At the beginning of Alex's clip Mullis says if they find this virus in you at all with PCR if you do it well
You can find almost anything and anybody
It's selectively edited to make it sound like Melissa saying that using PCR doctor
Kristen find any virus in anyone
Contacts
Text which Alex
Deprives the audience of
Clear that the virus that he's referring to it so he says if they can find this virus in you at all
He's talking about HIV
Contention that if you can find Hy-Vee in a person
His contention is that you can find
Most viruses
Also not to get too far off track here but Kary Mullis
Do the inventor of PCR testing
He's not someone who's remembered super well in the field of HIV and AIDS
As he was a denial
Conclusion that the HIV
Causes AIDS
The point is relevant to our situation though today is that Alex's clip that he's using of Mullis to Tech the use of PCR
For covid-19 testing
He's completely out of context and doesn't
Don't mean anything
The complaint that Alex is making about PCR testing here isn't covid-19 specifically
Ucr's a testing method
And he's expecting the audience to believe that the
The inventor of PCR testing
Who won a Nobel prize for the discovery headset
Haha it's a little bit rich
He said that after he got the Nobel
I don't think I don't think part of your campaign for the Nobel is honestly this thing doesn't do s*** at all
I'd like to thank
The Nobel board for being so
He didn't tell me that the videos from 93
Why don't you tell me anything about any testing
Like
43 years old
Then I don't know if I can use I don't care yet
Yes and no
Perfect is not like the way anybody should live their lives but if you're talkin about PCR testing in 2020 versus
Something that I said it before the iPhone happened
I kind of think I don't care
Sure you know
Yeah
If you are using science from
Grunge was King
Since then
Yeah it's Counting Crows work
Cool what does science method around I'm not interested
It's a long November Alex's playing this is November
Thanks buddy
Alex is playing this special report
He just cuts off in the middle of it
Medical doctors
For what what do they want to use the hysteria for
I was overwhelmed
Because episode started with him talking about this giant whistleblower who has the documents of he'll be revealed
If anybody flexes and then just cuts off in the middle of like wait a second
Maybe that wasn't
Important
I guess that's a little bit like he didn't care about that
You got Nobel Prize my friend
All right for the show.
Bratayley supposed take that seriously
Sure there is whistleblower
In the middle because Alex finally showed up to the office
Sure he was busy
I have been preparing this broadcast since 6 a.m.
Damn this morning
The news is so massive so over-the-top so dangerous
Transmission
Yeah so okay Alex had to take the response minutes off because he was so busy work
Snooze 6 a.m.
You so busy distract me with another gigantica
We can't spend any time because this other stories the biggest news ever
Talked about
Things that project Veritas is broken
He talked about things
Carlton
All of which are the world
When they do big things to set a broken the biggest thing
Just about credit
But I have to tell you
We are breaking information on this show today
That is the biggest thing
Ever
Broken
Concerning this fraudulent election 1/2
Alex has the number one okay biggest
Go to bed James O'Keefe
But I really feel like the whole Germany's courts
Invalidating all testing
As 96
I think that's a boy bigger story than any Alexa
There are people dying around the world millions of them I mean Alex
Would make that argument on another day
But he was like
Everything is going
Really crazy
On the 1st
Stop
You know
Trump's attorney
Linwood is going
Baddie talking about. Trump going to declare martial law
Doing great lawyers that's what you want
Sidney Powell
And ends
Buckwild are fantastic I'm glad they're getting paid a lot of money
Stuff is happening
So I was
I'm sure what this big news Alex had to break was
This clip incredibly Charming
Let me just drop it on you right now
Dot-com live show feed headline
Must watch Tuesday live
Okay
Warriors
Declare martial law
I want just one
Typo
That's my point about that
But I appreciate it. That's that's how he knows that he did that
Yeah I know but that was his typo
Please
Makeup smile
If it was if it was someone else's fault
Kill Everybody
Not mad was
There's some kind of quaint about Justin being like
A typo there
Yeah that is a small refreshing human moments when you like you know what at least you got that
Get on Erin talk about how it actually is really
Cool that Trump is being told
Declare martial law
I should have typed matopos
It's like when a tweet goes viral in and out of typos in a blackout
Take it back
Been screenshotted that's interesting cuz you you're talkin about this human moment
One of the things that made this episode
And the content we were going to get into
Particularly like
I don't know
Elevated to me a little bit
Is there a little bit of pesos
In here there's a little bit like I don't I don't want to make you or the audience or anybody feel any kind of pain
Empathy for Alex
You know
As an actor in this world at all
I think that there's a there's a
The point in this
December 1st episode where are you
Book feel like
God damn this is sad
Hey we all still appreciate Macbeth he wasn't a good guy but we can feel the pesos of his choices
Sure Prejudice episode
And it all begins
And it's next
Then there's this story
Tired
Security firm
Another garage
When I was
Bye
The White House
Into Dominion
We checked it with the SEC confirmed it
2 days ago
Tom
Dominion voting systems
The Chinese government
Before election
Scandals there's a lot going on in there and I really enjoyed it cuz this
It's been awhile
Conspiracy I could dig into okay okay good
Apparently
The company that owns Dominion
A bunch of money
From the Chinese government
Or something
Resume
It kind of cases the first thing I like to do is I like to go to Infowars
And see what the Articles they're actually say
And actually this was an instance
Literally unlike any that I think I've ever encountered
And that's because this
Article includes links to 5 PDF documents
There are apparently used to prove their case
I've never seen one link
Two Zero Hedge
I've never seen embedded
Lights on.
Crazy
Four of them are apparently SEC documents that Evie following disclaimer on top of them in big letters
We we we we were recognized
The Securities and Exchange Commission has not necessarily review the information in this filing and is not determined if it's accurate income
Complete the reader should not assume that the information is accurate and complete
I don't hear any difference between what you read and what I said
Yeah they're very similar
So that's four of them
And the fifth
Is a link that goes to a Reuters article
Great terms of documents
But there was another problem that immediately jumped out at night
The article begins with this sentence
Quote
An investigation into SEC filings has revealed that the firm which owns Dominion voting systems
Received 400 million dollars from a Swiss bank with close links
Do the Chinese government less than a month
Before the election
And that clip we just heard Alex said that the White House had
Hume to look into this 3 weeks ago
How many hired a firm to do the research
Where'd all falls apart is there
There's an editor's note at the end of the article
The thing
A previous version of this article incorrectly credited
Particular research for a performing this investigation
Information was erroneous and this article has been updated to correct that
We apologize for the confusion research firm was not involved whatsoever
It definitely indicates
Problem
An archived copy of this article from before the correction credits the investigation to quote Austin security and
Navigation solution
This is a real company
Based on their website they don't appear to be
Research firm
They're more like
What kind of people you get to do an unofficial Steak-Out
Outdoor help you make court file day
Maybe like
When Alex had people following his wife around also sells Nanny cams if you're
Some stuff for him in like freelance investigation
Hard-boiled
The only thing I can conclude is that either Alex is making up
That some group did this research to make it seem more official
He needed this company's help to find SEC filings
Arrived at
Benny told him keep our name off this s***
I'm not going to dress
Be reality or falsity
Of any of the claims
About this conspiracy wildlife
Explain it to you for the sake of simplicity
According to Alex
Dominion is owned by a company called Staples Street
Capital
This group received 400 million dollars
From a company called UBS Sakura
UBS Securities is a Swiss invest
My back that also owns a company called UBS Securities Company Limited
Which is an investment Bank caters to the Chinese market
UBS owned approximately 25% of the
This Chinese Investment Bank
With the Chinese government being the other owner
Through
Number of other entity
Conspiracy here is that the
Parent company of
Dominion got some money from a Swiss Investment Bank which also owns a separate bank which the Chinese government is
We invested up even if every step of this is true and no one screwed up or fudge
Any of the details
It still doesn't prove any
This is not a meaningful connect
Between Dominion in China
Unfortunately
Someone screwed up or fudge
What's the details
This article on Infowars claims that Staple Street Capital quota choir Dominion voting systems in 2018
This is kind of a site
On July
16th 2018 it was announced that Dominion voting systems quote
Has been acquired by its management team and Staples Street Capital
This is partially an acquisition
But not in the same way as them like outright buying Dominion was more like a partnering in it
The merger + Capital kind of mix
Second
Second the article mentions
The quote on October 8th
2020 Staple Street Capital filed SEC form
D offering
And sales amount of 400 million dollars with the
Sales compensation recipients identified as
UBS securities
This is meant to imply that UBS Securities paid Staples Street 400 million dollars to use Dominion to steal the election
The reality
Is it form D with the SEC is used to report on the sale of security
I hate to sound like I don't think 400 million dollars is a lot of money but when you're in the investment Market it's not
Really that much to accompany
Like Staples Street
It's definitely not enough to pay them to rig
F****** election
That's a comically low amount for that kind of work
And also I would assume they do the payoff more than a month
Before the election
Teams teams wear timing I don't know about that these people get bribed I keep finding them
Taking so little amounts of money for like the most
I could actually buy somebody only getting four hundred million to steal and
20 trillion dollars everyday
See these people do while we stole 50 million dollars and I got paid 50
Grand to my re-election fund like that's what they do
Thursday
I think the way you're talkin about is sort of the you like
Boilerplate blase corruption
I'm not stealing election okay that might be a bigger thing that I'm really throwing it out as
Sometimes payoffs
For like corrupt
I doing business
Kind of thing
Might not be the size that you'd imagine a pretty big f****** height
More likely this was a payment from UBS securities
For purchase purchasing some equity
Of Investments that are held by Staples
This doesn't seem to be the case until the form that Alex likes to from the ICC it says that this is
Equity
Pooled investment
Van dinter
The third problem is probably the one that requires the least fact-checking but also is the biggest
Just problem
Alex Woods
It confuses audience and readers about the entities UPS
Securities and UBS Securities company limit
UBS Securities is the one that bought
Securities from Staples Street
And that's the Swiss invest
UBS Securities Company Limited is the Chinese Investment Bank co-owned by the Chinese government and UBS
Securities
UBS Securities Company Limited did not buy Securities from Staples street but because the names are so similar Alex wants the audience
To come away with that impression
That the entity that is the one that's giving the 400 million that's not the case at all
This is why
Conclusion to this article is
Just on Earth
The Revelation that Dominion voting systems has Financial ties to the Chinese government via UBS Securities will bolster claims
Trump supporters
Set up for and actors working on behalf of communist China may have sought to meddle in the presidential election
And help Joe Biden
None of that is demonstrated by the evidence provided
This is all just paper-thin b******* Alex is trying to pass off
As a Smoking Gun
Also
I hate
Crash Alex's parade here
Or rain on it
And crashes party simultaneously
But the story was not broken by Infowars
Did a post about it an article on December 1st and good for them
Unfortunately that's exact
Conspiracy using the exact same PDF files from the SEC that Alex
It's like two
Qanon Twitter
Where is early as November 29th there we go around like he's late for the show cuz of breaking news
The f****** basil qanon.pub
Alex is just taking bulshit qanon conspiracies one of his intern fines online
Emily's pretending that it's the product of an investigation
He hired a
Broom to do
Because the White House
Ask him to
This is a pathetic level of insincerity and Griff
When you actually realize what Alex is doing
Becomes really disgusting to think about
He as a person
Knows that the White House didn't
Ask him to do this investigation
He knows that he didn't pay Austin
Security and investigation Solutions
Define these.
That's the backstory that he needs
To create to make himself look like a big strong boy
For his audience
But you might as well just be reading your crazy uncle's Facebook pay
Like it's really
Gross to think about like he knows what he's doing yeah being in that moment where you're so sad
Do you have to take qanon posts
And pretended
The f****** White House
Peju
Corinne sister
Who's the bravest around you're the only person who can get this information out until we need you to do it
Deep in my pockets and I paid the best researchers to find these SEC filings
CVS phone number
Qanon
People f*** out of here
It's so sad
Halo that week
In that moment
It's amazing
He's a little bit like the America's Funniest Home Videos of
Wednesday
Q world now you know where like
He take
He takes stuff that you could find on the internet into second
Cancel it went around yesterday
And packages it in for people who only watch TV
I got these
From the f****** Chairman Mao himself
You stumbled onto actually a really good metaphor and it's why America's
America's Funniest Home Videos
Big
Is driver whatever
That wasn't that
Great because
They exist you could find those videos.
Aqua Net
America's Funniest Home Videos on
That was the only game just like Alex said yeah there was a time but then the internet there was a time when he was the only person
Could provide you with a hot shot
America's Funniest Home Videos falling over
Add place that Alex Jones exec
Brutal
That means qanon is
Just might actually be killed
So Alex
Secrets
Yeah they were
Describe the family
Cabal
What about Christopher
So Alex
Is
This story is not
Good
It doesn't work
The proof that he has doesn't backup
The claims like these documents don't
Chode nefariousness
To the level that he's
He's implying
And it's all just stuff used to cribbing from qanon
And he just
Won't Give Up This charade that he's on
This is so huge but let me give you the big Infowars exclusive
I'm too big Infowars inclusive
System is fighting in
It's hard to make sure it does not get out to anybody
Common owns Dominion voting systems received
400 million from Swiss bank
Wii connection to Chinese government
Before election
Samantha
Oviraptor
Is Infowars exclusives
Alex is going over the story is interesting cuz I guess he hasn't got
The memo
Investigation
Austin security and investigation Solutions centers on Staples Street
I hope you won't have to give an apology publicly to Atherton security
Solutions
Yeah I wonder if they have anything with your b*******
Wonder if they're thrilled about that
I wonder
I would do a half maybe checked in on it but I don't like
To stir the pot
Alex
He's going over the story to like you just
Like the story sucks
It doesn't work
It sucks even more cuz he just makes up
Conclusions
The real headline is
Chinese communist government caught laundering 400 million through Swiss bank
Month before election
You got me there I can't hear it any other way than it being out
The kind of being impressed with himself
Look at this s*** this sounds real we got 5 PDF
Don't believe anything in these but
And I went down a hill
I lost control of the bike
And
I was able to get a shoulder down on my way down and I ended up rolling
And I got like
It was one of the coolest things that no one else saw more or less like I had meant to do
Acrobatic moves
It was all just a landing exactly
Exactly how I needed
Rollover and then sort of be on my feet just woke up in the gymnast pose like bowing
To the judges that aren't there yeah
It does have a little bit of sap
I proved
A little bit like
The first time you throw a rolled-up
Piece of paper into a garbage can
In the office from a ways away and everybody's
Is it in your life
Wow this always happens when no one's looking holyshit I got this one
For Alex like
Everyone who's in the studio is like
Good
Anyways
This is so sad
To me like I understand
I can I can
See the audience
Our audience
Everyone's laughing at Alex
You for it because I'm
Overly invested
This sort of like this story I read
Just so sad to me to see this guy who knows that he's lying
About himself lying about why you should be in Prescott
This is so cool
Gross
Put on the lead of this
Buy a very high-level individual in the White House
Why me I said look we already know it's there
Detach be independent
You need to go find it
So I hired a security firm
I told him dig
Call confirm
Like he has to
Create this this
Cool spy novel where the White House
It's like you're there all that you're independent this got to come from the outside
What the f*** it sounds like
Road at 4
So the White House came to me and
And told me to investigate things
And this is what showed up I can tell you that Steve didn't
Okay because Steve does show up later and Alex
Bring some of this up to him and
Steve's really got it
But some
Steve's got his bags of Steve Ishq person perhaps
Meow meow
I don't know what
The deal is or like
Piano
Obviously
This came from like qanon posts
Online
Conspiracy
Nonsense
Galaxy
Is the basis for Tom Clancy's Jack Ryan character
Pathetic mess of coming up with how important
You are in and needing to project that to the audience
Does just like
God damn I don't I don't know how I
How you could live like that
Just so.
Totally
Anyway in the sex clip Alex
Is that
The situation
The president
Lawyer who has said that Trump needs to call for martial law
New election
Do you think Alex is for or against
This idea
But I would even almost argue
Against the new elect
Action part just stick with Marshall off now he's just for it all
Attorney
Glenwood
President-trump
Should declare martial law
Hold new election
He goes through
In this full page
I totally agree
This constitutional analysis election
Why are you guys wasting my time even saying what a new electric shut up like if you
Well I guess we were wrong.
The election be whatever
Shut the fuk up president for life and you'll destroy the remaining four
Shut up
The only way there could be a feral
It didn't happen
Is this a is this a Zen koan
Trump voting machine
Drop Brandon machine it's the only way to be sure
They're made by Trump
Alright
I've let me picture this
Alright everybody but phone companies are alright
He makes his own voting machines
They look very similar to him they've got a computer screen where is
Chest is
If you
Press for Biden
Little
Container of a little gun comes out boom
Got to vote for
Search up every. Gunn swabs you
Alex one of the reasons that there needs to be a new election
The story
How do I expand Abba Dominion
Engineer
McKean County in Georgia
Walking up illegally
Drive-In
Walking out with it for a few hours coming back again
Alex doesn't even know what county this video is from
It's a key County
Please literally repeating qanon posts
From social media you saw this is just another one
This was a qanon witch-hunt that started from a video of a Dominion Technologies technician doing their job
Which are in the imagination of these idiots on social media became proof of a person change
V
Proof it's given for this is that people watching
Video assume that must be what the guys doing there for it's been proven
Almost comically dumb yeah that is very stupid
What's less laughable is the fact that the major players of the cube bulshit work amplifying leading a dachshund camp
Against this employee
Who is now almost certainly afraid for his life
This employee was not manipulated vote
But now because of people like Alex Jones and Ron Watkins
A huge chunk of the public thinks that he's either definitely or probably guilty of
This is a real person
Who's been singled out
And that in a fairy story written about him
For no reason
Except to satisfy the corruption lost
Of a disenchanted group of
Conspiracy lunatic
And now
He's got people tweeting nooses at him so
Yaki
The conservative media has essentially turned
All of the internet into the eye of
Sauron and if it anytime points upon you you'll be destroyed
Just let amplifying that out of your career like your job
Figuring out the things that have gotten you in trouble in the past and then continuing to Chipotle
I mean interview
Has it away learned the lessons which is that there are no negative consequences
Cuantas except for people who aren't him and he doesn't care about the
Well at least he doesn't bring up the guy's name
Anyway we need martial law and the reason we do is because there's already martial law or maybe
Something I don't know
This is the UN Global Petco
Martial law
I make sense to stop the counter to 2
The coolers
Before they cool us
Brightondale be cool we need martial law in order to fight martial law
Waterstone calls on property total power
Martial law
The Constitution
Total power the Constitution
Is the
Protect the public
When you do it
I'm an expert on martial law ladies and gentlemen
The clintons
Route to do it
Their un Global Medical martial law
What it is
Circumvent the government open government to stand back and watch it all happen
I got to say after that clip I really do think that he is an expert on martial law
And yeah
Okay okay
So if I understand this correctly
The UN
Is declaring martial law
So Trump has to declare martial law in order to stop the un's martial law
Now
I'm going to toss this out there
For you as a possible
Trump has declared martial
And martial law is declared
What if the UN just removes Trump
We're we're still in martial law
What do you mean
I mean like
Once we're in martial law it doesn't matter somebody's going to be the martial law person
Forever
Well they do in Alex's world that's forever
That's something that is always been
Apart of his ideas
Let me let me float this
Look
Their martial law is bad and it'll happen
And forever because you don't trust anybody want
What's the hidden power they'll never get out of power
Except
For Donald Trump
Because he's really cool
Right
You just got to let him have martial law temporarily which I have told you on many occasions is
Impossible it doesn't
Will trust me he tries to clean stuff up
And then he'll get it. The martial law
But it seems like you're just getting rid of one of the steps
That they would have
And they could just kill him and you're already on their Marshall and then they don't even have to bring in
I don't know how to respond to that
Yeah I don't know it's just dumb mr. Marshall Law mr. Anthony Marshall Law
Whose whole career is largely been about how
Tyrants never give up power once a day
Achieve like some modicum of
Like for him to be like do we need a dictatorship for a short time in order to
Solve the problems of my imaginary enemies it's just
Kind of silly it's not it's
Not funny
Yeah it's sad
Yeah it's very pathetic
Listening to somebody talk like that and not
Bee challenge with Just Like Sugar
List of like
That's
Yeah if anyone around them from their longtime listener one body ass
From a voice within themselves yeah
Pushing back and being like to hear yourself
Yeah
F*** out of here it's like it's a wonderful life but instead of the Angel showing up it just jump
Mascaro but like all the ghosts are like
Screws gear
You're the best
You are just
Do it so good would you hang with us have a great old time
Christmas morning kids you got to do
Beat up Tiny Tim
Dictator is hell up in here
We the People March
Real quick he's reading Linwood statement
That is a long statement our treats most of it
I don't care but anyway
Just a part of that
And Alex's take on it
We the people must demand a new in Fair
About that all Americans can trust
And live by regardless of the winter
Without a vote we fear has good reason
Shooting Civil War
All-time high in 40%
The first-time donors
Will you defend themselves
The property
We must act now before there
Is no peaceful way left
Determination
Exactly why the icons in the UN do this
Because even if Trump removes the fraud they'll be a civil war
Why don't you the fraudulent
He has two arrested in the media
Oh wow okay so I guess we got to arrest them if he heads of the media
Correctly
Even if Trump uses the system to root out the corrupt
There's going to be a civil war
Well yeah yeah however if Trump
Instantly
Extemporaneously arrest all the heads of the media right takes care of all of the generals that he doesn't like
Removed everybody in government dissolved the Senate
No Civil War
I'm in the center for now is
Supreme Court
Yeah yeah it's strained
So that wouldn't wouldn't
Start a civil wars
Here's
I mean it's obviously A Veiled Threat
Yes I'm pretty sure it's very much for we kill all of you at
For a new election he said give us trouble we kill you no no no
There is a circumstance where in the new election would be except
Now a new election voting machines
Shina no
Paper ballots
Great recounted by Trump family members
Has to be in your favor
What's gerrymandering not enough for you
Apparently not well also it is really funny
Linwood and Sidney Powell have their press conference on the 2nd
Convey of this ugly Boston on December 2nd
Maybe it was on the 1st I can't remember what day it was
But they are like
Yeah
And we're not going to participate in this Georgia election to vote
Don't do it
I guarantee it I think it's a terrible idea I love that
Call tavito that defense bill
On that stuff
Interesting like
Sidney Powell and
Lynnwood telling people not to vote
Georgia runoff I'm all for it
Very significant advantage to the Democratic
Yep yes
Please why
This is what I've been waiting for the whole time we can't
Be cool and take it over by the dumbest people on the planet
They need to dumb it up so much we don't even have to work
I'm very interested in that
Turn Alex's take on Trump's threatening to veto Saturday
Exactly
Because Alex
I hate
The ndaa
Favor of trump veto in that
He also wants to get back on Twitter
Such a complicated
He's finally forced a
Into the most nuanced position of his career and he's reacting the way we all knew we would
Pretending it's not happening let me go gamble he forgets he doesn't like the NBA's
I won't remember that very shortly
Yeah but he does remember
They paid people a lot of money
To dig up this story
About China
If this goes out this is the total proof
Hiding in plain view
And we have
Are you tired
Through all this
They tried to hide it
I tried to hide the subsidiary names
And subgroups we tracked it all back
Shuffle going to break in just a few seconds promo code Patriot Universal 10% off
Alright man
Yeah I think he's got a good point
I think you can only own one business
Beyond
No none of this Cubs
None of this is this
Feeling
Staples in UBS Company Limited in uvso 25%
1 Business Park
I don't think you have any idea how come
Alright
I sometimes forget that you have a degree in small business administration
1 Business Park
.
Maryville
Everyone gets one
I understand that
Corporate structures are confusing and sometimes a bit complicated
By making it impossible to work
Next clip Alex continues
To bring up this Dominion employee was been getting lots of threats
At least
At least he's not saying his name or anything
Imma come back
Recap the top news in the show you footage
Dominion worker reportedly
Carpenter
Alicia's name yet
Set alarm people
This is incredible at what levels you've been caught
We do not accept
Check your fraudulent leader your chai, agent Joe Biden you're on notice
Remarkable restraint on Alex's part not saying this person's name yeah
Because you know
It's kind of a big part of what's gotten him
I'm in trouble in the past
You're leading an amplifying
Kind of campaign
Seek to
Harass
Threaten intimidate private citizens
Hope you don't get into that
Yeah
I think it's
I think it's so weird how willing he is to go after
After individual
How weird is like I think that's the only way he can really assert
Power
Suppose
Cuz it cuz I don't think anybody else is scared of him like right
Thought this guy who owned Comet Ping Pong was ready to take him to court
Like it's back down hard when those people were like oh f*** you
People like date of David Rothschild showed up on his show and talk to him for like half an hour
Bill Ayers showed up Andrew
What are you talkin about
But these people aren't afraid of him
You know who is
Some random country
But
Like I said man
Ethos
Because
You can really tell that Alex loves telling the story about how Trump
People told him to get to the bottom of this Dominion thing
It's so sad when you know what's up and this is just a
The conspiracy from qanon boards
God this is so sad
Credible time in world history on so many fronts but I got to call
The president's representative
When I was in Arizona
Sun
Nicole
Machine company
And I said look we know Soros the Chinese are involved
What unit investigated
I want you to bring it out I know it why why do I have to find it they said
That's at all cuz it's it's classified not going to find myself
Well I got to call two days ago from the security firm I hired
Internal security
Researchers
UBS Bank
Investment firm
Is owned by the Communist Party
Central Committee and buy one of their major
And that they put
All of this
Money 400 million
YouTube
Dominion
I just
Can't
Get over helping
Pathetic this is
Staff
This is like a
School kid
Bragging about like their dad being Superman
The president
I'll just say I'll leave it at one of his son
Called me
And said you got to get
It was because it's classified we're not
Because it's not
It's a little bit like
Like a con man
You very much like this particular one reminds me of like that
The old ones where it's somebody with a vaguely European accent who
Talking to the New York Stock Exchange people like
Yes I would represent
YouTube of King Harold
Call Linda
He's trying to keep it a secret million dollars
And if you know that the
The cake is a lie
You're a f****** lunatic man if you're not pulling it off at you look like
PennySaver
Yeah you know you know simultaneously Aika
Can see this and he is not pulling it off right
But there's
Probably enough people
Who are just dumb
Or just captured by him
I think that he
Beans
God damn word he says
And that's really sad it's really sad
For them it's really sad for Alex
It really is
Start a human level 40 something year old man
46 47 year old man
Who's in his
Studio
Bragging
Sleep bulshit lies
About the president's son telling him to do this investigation
Study just selling Acumen onboard well when you put it in that context it sounds bad
It is
It's also like this is painful to me like
I had a really tough time with the first half
December 1st episode
Because it is
It's it's
This dude
Just a sad mope
1 trillion %
The Smoking Gun and then it just gets worse
The Communist Chinese wired
Dominion on October 7th
These documents
I suggest you get him outside and I don't normally say sources and things like that
I want you to know how real this is
That's just
Justice bomber
Oh boy that's really sad about this is like if you really look at it
Professional
Call perspectives
Alex's
Reduce
To taking something
From qanon
Circles
Pretending it's not
That and then just trying to resell
Anybody who's like engaged in those qanon
Communities
Between this and be like
Are we already knew that this days
4 yd cocaine
This is old news to real
Conspiracy heads
Like it's it's
You trailing behind the thing that he thinks is a rip-off of himself right
It's just
You should
Quit quit
She-Ra meeting she does protest too much will be like
Now I would say that Alex
Has been a little bit out of line with talking about this employee but
I will say
Up till this point he hasn't really been trying to like
Intimidate
Until now
A video we know who the guy is retracting Democrat operative we know where he worked at
McDonald's in GameStop
Relationship
But we have the footage of him in the Tri-County illegally or not
Going up with a thumb drive taking it out
That's pretty much
Wow
That's really f***** up
That's really f***** because you could also tell how much Alex kind of relish
Yeah that cut that moment feels like he's threatened hot but anytime I can drop
Javier's in the world
Calming the USB
And waddling out
Xavier
As we told you
Wish I was going to bring it myself what Gateway pundit
Stay in attack formation
Oops
Well I hope this
Do not come back
To bite you in the ass and you don't get sued I hope it doesn't he should be immediately and even if nothing happens the
Other lawsuits and be like
Beat this what you're trying to do
Clear pattern of behavior this guy
Warren this
Kind of behavior
Happening
A couple days ago
Could be inserted as part of the Sandy Hook trial go.
Stopping behaving in ways that are Taylor
Raising the possibility of harm coming to private search at
I just don't understand I guess I do kind of understand
Houston assholes
Cancel
It shouldn't work like
Okay so you just told me what the exact line is so what I'm going to do is
Tiptoe up to his closest Little to the line is possible
And then wave my hands at you but you can't catch me I didn't kill this guy this time you're on Earth
This is completely different because
It's about a different thing
Yeah but different thing
What
Like I said there's a lot of pesos
At the beginning part and I'm
I was kind of bummed out about it
This is interesting because it is pathetic
And
There's an interesting glimpse of Alex trying to put on his soda Superman
Jumper
Sure and try and play the role of what he thinks he is
Everything and I was like I need more
From this episode
And thankfully
Another
Someone who might be a daddy to Alex
Steve pieczenik
Let me remind you
Couple of weeks ago on several months ago I
That I was told by my
Hello
Countrymen
Rich man
Owen Shroyer show that we have
Watermarks
That's we had monitored at all the machines I'm Dominion
And we had
Came out of
Who's David Ida
Favorite
I do have but I
He's not happy about it I have to imagine
Yeah it's Steve's still on this telephone
And I still haven't
Because again this is
A direct contradiction of literally every other talking point that Alex's
Is not only contradicting Alex
In terms of like now this was a sting operation this entire election
He also is not thrilled with the idea that Alex is like maybe we should have martial law seems like
No
Don't need martial law
What we have enough
Now
Is we have
The Sting operation which I denounced Iran Alex Jones
Give me the permission
Cool
Yeah man
Bye-bye
I'm never going to be like I have common cause with Steve pieczenik right but I do
Find it
Comforting on some level that he's not saying we need martial law
Also said we should dissolve the government and Melania should be Queen
Yeah that's why I don't want, cuz I would like some clarity coming from doctors
Alright he's who I go to when I'm looking for sanity in this info world's world you need a Northstar
Play that's what I'm all about unfortunately
Alex
Besides that this is the time when he's going to be like
Yeah I don't know
Stay the night
Clip is essentially Alex drink
Play both sides of the fence
Yeah now it says you're full of s*** and I still want to talk to you so
Well I think it's even less of that and more just like
If anybody in the audience were to attack him from either side and he can cover his face with a clip like that that's fair
But some people
Say that you're full of it that's me being a hard-hitting journalist Nebraska
If someone is into Steve's Theory
I said
That he has a great track record and that goes a long way with me
He's just being mealy-mouthed.
Anyway Steve's talking about the situation we find ourselves in
The ballots are all accounted for in
Barcodes or whatever
The fuc
And also
Some generals
Who sent troops
All over the country
And the Supreme Court needs
To be taken out
Ring system
Deployed military elements
Buffalo
Playing
Regular Army National Guard
Has increased more
Tell you that it's the same
John Roberts
Greencore
He is a sick man
Capitation
Corruption is what we call
Call the minimalist
Yeah sure that is what we call them
Minimalist
Quid pro
Corruption
Yeah cool cool you're talkin
Talking about
Turtles you know the inefficient
Unqualified
Meanwhile we got General nakasone coming into bringing an army into store.
Tomorrow we march on Florida
Which of their plans I would be interested in letting
Play out not that one
Sometimes we'll have like a
What days is all of their plans are like they did the boards I just drops up and down
Is the plan I'm glad they follow through
I have another one
Mocking hope
Alex follow through with it will be my next
Like Tara vanity projects
If Alex does this I might live stream 4 days straight
Update on what's going on
One of the most exciting
You know what
F*** it
Okay unprecedented
If Alex follows through with what he claims he's going to latest episode
I might
Join have okay okay alright alright that's a tease cuz I don't know what he's going to talk about
In covid
We'll figure it out
Alright we'll talk about this later
A literal bubble-boy situation
Earlier you said I forgot
I'll be revealed within this episode
The earlier you were mentioning that like the way that Alex was talking about him being told to do this Dominion investigate
Bounce TV
And because Steve is still on the election was a sting operation
The government asked
Alex
The left-hand can't know what the right hands doing
This is a problem for Alex though especially in terms of
The presentation that is an issue needs to ask Siri
Help me out of this one guy car at my buddy
Don't say no to this fraud
Then they will put Biden and Trump says you'll do so
Is there is water marks and all this proof and I believe you talked to those forces who told you
It's probably doing good faith I think you're a good person
When do we see the cards on the table what's about to happen
Why would they get me
To do after
Document
They have this why
Why
It's a great question why would they do that
Say that it's very simple
They wouldn't
No buts
You can't say that.
Bad idea
The in order for their illusions
Discontinued
That the audience needs to buy into to keep the cash flow going
Steve needs to not be a
Complete liar
And Alex needs to not be shown to have not talked to the white house after school
Everybody's a little bit of a dangerous position right now
Right but there is a really smooth way to get out of this pickle
And that is
Leo zagami exactly what he always does when things get tough
I appreciate
Excited
The reality is
Game is already
What's happening
Trump anticipated most
Ashley
Intelligence
Community really
Thesaurus
Harwich
I was to announce
They wanted me to announce
Person or stood because Idaho
Promotion I really don't
Garner anything
Other than being a
Citizen Warrior
Fuelman
Mainstream media has a
Soho
Clean wigs
Yeah so you know when you're encountered with his unanswerable question where the only
Logical rational real world explanation is
Cuz you're both
Crazy Liars
Yeah you get out of that by being like
Alex
Calm down you were chosen because you're so great the best you're the best there ever was about a look at these
Compliments
Don't look at me that's a very easy way to get out of conversation
And also the
C-note then Steve can transition into other top
Like how Biden will never be president
Guarantee
The United States
Now he's wearing possibly and
Bracelet because he said
He has a little bit of problem
Haha
Seeing now
Different type of bracelet
The way you can
Can Alex that's reason why I come on I mean this is not unusual for
Reset it a long time
I want to believe you I'm just 150 days
Tell you this buddy I am going to
I'm just going to die if your ride 50 days you are going to be the king of the planet to me
I just I just hope you're right
That is what it sounds like when someone doesn't believe
Leave someone
You Alex
F*** you it's not fair if your show how dare you
U-Save that sounds like
Fuchsia
You said
You shall bunch of it you f****** you're you're you're being very fast and loose
With a private citizen safety
And
You're pitching a nonsensical
Stupid
Voter fraud
Conspiracy based on qanon
What got to make it look good
That's rude
Anyway
Steve
Is it
Destra
When Alex said this sounds like you an odd stuff
He's like a man
I can't get excited like you get excited I don't know that mean
Steve gotta make it like
You're so important
Every time Alex is getting a little bit out of pocket
Can dude you know I was wrong to keep charge
Did you
Because of your showing
Videos
I did with you it was sent
And believe it or not
What I Call my
Chinese man
In my
Patrol officer
In China for the
The past 30 years
Batman
And the Public Safety in China
Call Nia
3 weeks ago
To explain that
Is there any trouble
To say that it was an
When show
Meaning
Don't want to get into
Problem situation
M president sheep called
We want no trouble
I do not know what I'm listening to I do not know what's actually happening right
Right now search
Trump personally sent me on a message to investigate s*** that I made up and I'm creating at home
Fictional mythology around how I'm great
I'm coming with that b******* a
Are we talkin will look I think Steve knows that we exist and I think he knows that
In order to be interested
You've got to cover that you want to make the after show your character needs to be incredibly
You don't believe you're only on for short bursts you don't want to be the character who doesn't get a rose
To speak
And Steve
You also somebody who unfortunately
Runs the risk of being
Pretty boring pretty easily because he's made so many
That's true
Prince called because he wanted to make sure they start my appearance are being overworked
No problems here guys just give you a call so you got the go-ahead and everything's okay
To Parlay
We just want you to say stay frosty at that you keep.
She wants me to work as an intermediary between Alex Jones
China
Just inexplicable and pointless little bit of racism there
So Alex
Who's having this interview with Steve and he's
He's also like
I got to go
I got to leave early
Alright what is playing hooky in the next 2 hours windfall Joseph Watson has Candice
Gaston
Busy with breaking news and documents and Intel
And tomorrow we'll have giant breaking news here for you on
When the information
It's not there's nothing
Big going on at all
I would probably make myself scarce
It's the team up is going to be Paul Joseph Watson
And Candice Owen
It's been my feeling
She's not
Thrilled with
Being associated with Infowars
Like with Turning Point never coming on Infowars
I don't know I haven't tracked her career as closely but it seems like she's back in the place where she would be on info
Call Wars
Respond
Paul as opposed to be without going to do it
Go with Paul if it's somehow seems safer for your reputation
So Alex going to leave early cuz he's got to
Time to work
Yeah whatever
Steve
As one who has one more big swing to make
I love this one as I
What the f***
So I'm telling you babe
Beijing called me
DirecTV
Cast of the show that you're doing
We wanted to use you as the main fire
By that
Announcement
You have to
Ironically one of my neighbors
Get the f*** out
Creased
Dancing in the size of
Hundred percent another was I have a neighbor who's in charge
Wire
Fencing for prison
And he went
A year ago
Increase the size of
By over 100%
Shouldn't you be against
Is that is easy trying to say that's because Obama's
Taller than the other prisoners have been in the past I got what we're trying to say globalist
That you're going to incarcerate it Wonton amo in your fantasies
Them in the safety there is
Yeah this is silly
What is
What he's talking about is there were reports of trump like building
News
Construction
Prior to this date rented
Seeing the trend has been towards closing at
Jesus trying to use some of those ideas are super popular in the Cuban on world
Steve is really just like
At this point
A cute guy
Yep
I'll have them
Mighty have fallen
I can such a of weirdness becoming
Followers
Sad
Is something to be said about the queues ability as a as a
Mental
Disease to infect
Hey I mean
Everybody
Piano
It's it just
F****** in your head you're not at your not immune if you're a conspiracy leader fall
Yeah well I mean
But
These people who are leaders are smart enough to not say this is what there in exactly
We can take the ideas and certain Trends in the
Conspiracy world and then
Reorient them a little bit into being about like
My friend General yeah
Yeah
Yeah he was saying that stuff but that's just because it's
Parallelism I'm just getting it from a real source
Whereas
I imagine that it feels a little bit like stuck speculating to be one of these conspiracy people like dealing with
Q like
Trying to be like okay well I think
This is one of the theories that's going to stick
And if I get on this one
Then I'll get more whenever it goes mainstream where is it maybe start speculating and it's also there's
No consequences for being wrong
He like the stock market if whenever the
The stock people forgot you are
Everyday everyday at Queens place
Alex's goodbye to Steve
This is not how you
Part ways with someone who you think is
Credible
God bless you will talk to you soon as he pretending.com have a great
Have a great week coming up
Hopi tribe
I have the
The best cast of the best people and man
I hope that bulshit he just spun makes said it sounds good
Probably both
Bulshit
And
Alex
Starting to show really just sort of ruminating about himself as a child to her and talking about things that are cups
Absolutely not true
I was 6 years old 7 years old I like to watch
I like to watch
Long
The televised
How things actually work
Interesting
Almost no one else
When
Was 6 years old he was snowed
Advance Jordan you understand
That he was watching.
C-SPAN scores
Hearings
Could you so fascinated but as he got older he realized no one was as serious as him let me posit you an alternate Theory
When he found out how hard it was to actually do research he decided that what he did was actual research and whatever
Everybody else ABC
Yeah it is certain point he realized
It's really tough to read a book
Card
To 1/3
Person or to somebody else do it external observe difference
Between you having red
The book and you saying you read that sounds true
She's quite a revelation to have at the age of 6 and iPod out
Motorsport 6 years old I realize that if I put Infinite Jest
People will think I was smart that myself
With the same
God dammit
I was so excited
At this point on the 2nd
I could have
I almost couldn't
Contain myself
I don't know if you remember this but I think it was a 2015 episode
Alex got on air and he was like
I am going
2 in this episode
Jump the shark
Yes I do recall that I am going to as a piece of art
Performance art
Call for the Banning of Islam and then he proceeded to talk himself into it.
As a performance
Set out
To do was like this thing that he was being overly
Clear about his intentions
Kind of ruin the Serta
Rhetorical
Thrust right but it was like I loved
Secede
Had an idea and you wanted to try right
I got that again
Advertently
He made our satirical piece
Work
By trying to do is
Satirical piece and then winding up
Embodying the thing that he thought he was dead
Yeah
It was it was interesting on that level
And I guess it's the same this time
Thought about the best way to say this but I'm going to get right out
People be more effective
If I actually joined the dark
Seriously considering
Completely shifting into the enemy mindset
Presenting all this and
You should kill yourself
I mean like I would love it if
He did
As a joke
Just did like a Bill Gates great
Because it would be the most incompetent nonsense
Skull
Or or
Character based on scent
One it has to be asked
Surprised nobody can know you're about to do it
To you have to commit to the vet you have to open by saying something like that you have to stay solid
You can't break character and you have to go for a good long while
Maybe
And he can't do any of those though
What he saying like I've just been thinking about this I got to go to the dark side and be like the globalist
And then
Started to get real f****** dark
Like I like you are being
What I would consider quite
To the dark side
The public
Pears
Good people
But everyone else is running headlong into it
Wanting to be slaves
Wanted to be slowly killed
Wanting to be met.
Wanting to be failure
Because
They are not men
Wait what
So okay
That the evil enemy
That you hate
Has come to the conclusion
But humans aren't worth
Living and has decided to kill all of us
And you think that that's evil however you agree that humans
Aren't worth living end
God is going to kill them all
Correct well yes
Oddities basing it on is
That
It seems like
Only Christians are interested in fighting the
Christian Zealot reward
The Crusade imagining Christian Crusade is only backed by Christian right
I didn't know that strange to him
And it's proof that everyone else
Is meant to die in God's plan
I think that's really f***** up
Yeah I think he went from Ice
I think I'm going to join the Dark Side to I think I am the dark side
Very quickly without seeming to realize that he was doing
That is not him being a performance Sian.
The origin of
Performing
Prince of the dark side to be like
In your body
Seems like they're destined for death and that's just God's plan
Isn't he the guy who says that Islam is violent
I do think that maybe I was being
Hyperbolic when I said
The GOP is Isis
Yeah
Alex's he's he's he's a ways down that road at least in terms of ideology and the thought
And Hope
And let's hope not
Not Beats
Now this is this was interesting to me
Because
That's kind of
For this
Everything that you was intending to do this great idea
Performative Ali becoming the dark side and then immediately
Said something incredibly dark and didn't body what I would
Yeah yeah yeah
122 Darkside
Now that he's done with that
Alex tells a story
That I think
Does not make
The point that he want
To make
I think
He sounds like an a****** in this story
They're not the resistance
And there
At the sky
Weekend
Sunday I went for a walk
Zilker Park
Walking along
I see the sky
Happy Friday.
Why
The brown take a swing
Wayward
Fantasy world
About to get hurt
It sounds like Alex just threatened the guy randomly that he
Imagined was
I wish him ill and was
Academic antifa types
Alright this is this is
Scary so let me see if I can get
The details of the story correctly
From the point of a neutral Observer
So I'm in a different angle
Maybe you're a birdwatcher other binoculars not doing much I see Alec
I see Alex
Jones over there just
Chicken
Because he's Alex
Just visibly just vibrating death
And then I see a guy over there
No probably will wait fish wearing glasses he's got a black shirt on he's got black shorts on
Ricochet antifa type starts walking away and then Alex Jones
Visibly shaking
Start walking directly towards him and almost throws a fist at him and I'm supposed to think
At the last minute the antifa guy
Looked like he was about to get hit
By somebody
I got all of a sudden he's so subservient scared of the clear threat
Maintenance Vibe who is giving off
Towards me on a day where I was just reading at the park is going to make me go away in that story I don't hear
Any clear indication to Alex's
Violence
Was in response
To any real violence or threatening this
Of this
Person
Who was just on the trail and Alex's decided
Because they're wearing black and have a beard
Are academic antifa
Write with a f*** that mean
It just seemed like what he just said was
If I
Feel a bad vibe
I will kill some
If you're wearing black
You're probably antifa and might f****** images f****** Fallout 4
The s*** out of a seahawk
And if you act
Like it weird
I'm about to hit you or maybe you
Emotionally manipulative
Then why you why you acting like someone's about to hit you you were about to hit me
Okay
Anyway Alex has a lot of fat
Genesis 1 is the academic antifas trying to get him on the tree
Another is it in the near future
His books
I guess he's written
A couple bucks
Sort of
Anyways show
Will be contraband
You can record this and you can save that s***
Cloud online
Contraband
All devices
Divisive
What does a lot of Hoops
Steven have this saved
Probably suggest you
And in the future
In the near future
I would love it for Alex to like go to Europe and see like wall sockets
Is it AC or DC
Dumb dumb
In this next clip
I would say about that last thing is
This is just such a desire to be forbidden
Into that idea
I think it's probably
From one too many bad sci-fi.
We talked a lot about Alex's bizarre morality
This idea of
Sort of galactic
Rules
And stuff
Mike down for this next court because he talks about a little bit more
If this is something I really need your help with
Okay because this
Is another clue about how this moral system works
But it doesn't make sense
Your injected with
Hundreds
A little
* 1
All have the same amount of data on them
10 years ago
Metaphysically
Not allowed to do that
Historically
They have to get you under pressure to do it they got to leave a way out for you
Escape hatch
Porsche
But then it becomes a shove
Once God removes the barrier
Yes
Put your water
Your food
God
Has a
Barrier hedge
To this
Sort of free-will thing
The devil once God says go ahead
That's if you're free well and that's why there's chemtrails
Do you like
Hedges gone
Truck at who cares
What does Alex Jones believe in Kemp
Yes he does yes yes but you can't spray things
Randomly
So I think
If I understand correctly
I think what he saying is that
The devil
The literal Christian devil is real and is running Biden campaign
Spell somehow
AAA
Call the devil said he wasn't doing
So
Right
And God will stop him from going too far
Unless you give it a little bit of like a
Hey maybe I'll go along with
The devil and then God will remove that final Ring of Fire
Protection
And then you will be thrown in
I don't think that's what he saying
I think
That
I don't know if
I don't I'm not certain based on the things that I've heard
Hedge
Of protection that God has
I'm not certain is
You like
Relies on
Your choice
I asked you because you have to have
Have to have the way out
And you have to be able to so you have
Trails work then
Well you chose to look up
Is it doesn't matter if I look up
According to that you're breathing in all these like these aluminum's and ratify
You can't escape you did not make any choice
That
The baddest something that is
Completely
Above your will
You did not
Agree to that
Therefore it's an infringement of your
Oh well
Wasn't it primed
I'm just like it's just like a mom without a without a timer
You know you just got all the stuff in you
And then you have to believe something and then they lacked
I can't imagine that
Less than zero says yeah I don't understand this new wrinkle to a there's another wrinkle
And that is that is that you can't do
Who sings to kids
But I think from the context of this Alex's talkin about that
Yes
The real Ultimate
Children
They are of age to make
And so
That's why
Is a cheat
A lot of them so I can lie cheat then
They are not allowed
They're only allowed to get
Adult
What
Cannot support
Themselves
Make a bad decision
Receive spiritual
Interventional
Transmission
I want I want a ruler and I want somebody
Slapping hands whatever he's like
They can cheat
No
You said they can't
But that's why they're cursed
Yeah but you said they can't cheat
I mean if it's there already Kirsten then why wouldn't you just continue to dig
There's no greater
There's no greater punishment after a hell right
So if you already cheated why would you think we like well we still have to follow the rules we captured cursed but you're not going to hell
Oh well then that I guess I retract all the way
That makes you smile weird and alligators and pick you out of a crap.
Alright you can't be a day Walker anywhere I got you
They're getting around
Cosmic rules
Because these children
Are agreeing to get vaccinated
But they don't know any better
So it's like
Technically
I don't know
Also I said I would
Would suggest that if this is some kind of finger really curses you
They all having children make
Decisions that they're unable to understand
Baptism
What about child baptism
The children can choose that and that's good
I mean I understand but subjectively
You would say that that is a good decision as opposed
Getting a vaccine
Make it a bad decision for being
However
Externally
Look from the view of the universe these are both things at the
This child cannot
Decide you can't trick
Ticket towards God that's the other Cosmic rule
You can only go towards
If you get baptized you meant to write it just seems weird yeah I just don't understand what it is exactly
That makes those acts different
Outside of
Wanting
Them to be different I just don't understand why you would want to be involved
Any of that
Like I don't want to know what yeah I don't want I don't want to be I don't want to be good in this morality
Missy this seems even more you could be
Even more somehow evil
In his morality
Confusion incoherent today
I might be the devil I don't know
Balmoral chase like Skye
Should I tell my wife she looks pretty today or do I have to be 100% honest
Is me telling her she looks pretty going to take away her Freewheel to dress herself and she's no chooses
Play the devil man
Wolf
There's almost
It is Paralyzer
Terrified
But look
Anyway
Has weird rules
The devil's followers barkhurst
Hey man
Sore God's but we've gotten to where we've gotten
The more you you just got to resist
Enemies
Lego
Is that
What they're doing a show focused so diabolical
So over-the-top
That people just have real trouble
Grasping
And they project their own
Mindset on the establishment
People don't want to face that people don't want
Then I can just deny it and it's like a problem at the
Is the foul
And so the more you resist
This is going to be over with
Going to go to the fire
But
Is going to destroy
When I hear that I hear something along the lines of like
I've been out hey likes Albarn
The more you fight
The better it'll be
Yep so why not
I don't get what I want
Everyone's going to
Todai
Black I wanted to I want there to be a 10-yard penalty for him being like
People project onto the establishment because things are too difficult for them to understand and then they want to live in denial
Aflac
So Alex
From this path of like
As higher
Will I live through the fire fire
Amy wants to hit on some of his
Modern Talking Point
Janesville
All these articles about
Looking for an interview Maddie good for you
You are going to drink storage
Going to drink
Weeds
I will not be adding more people in a test tube
Assignment German by the way
The Russian accent afford another language
So I think that's one of those things it's like
Really easy to see through like what he's lying about
Take me to direct quotes
I will feed you dog
Pirates this is what you will do these are at
Germany by the way
German map
Without even doing any looking into any of this
Like it would be so easy for someone to be like oh yeah he's talking about like sewage treatment plant
Turning that into potable water
And you know the potential of weeds as being a cultivated food source
Think of turning things that we usually think of is not good into things that are good that's called
Like weeds are things
Is it grow without any
If there were a way that you could turn that into
Renewable water is something lb
Increasingly important
In the future
Species
Food
A matter of poop
Silly
Anyway Alex's Uno
Foreign language speeches the Klaus Schwab.
Next subject
Just as serious
Cam
Flipping out
Covid prediction for Project Runway
In March of last year
So full
11 months before it was even
Globalist like to put stuff
Movies that are culturally want to tell you
Serial killers
You know what
My instinct whenever somebody's like
Project one Runway predict something in March of last years ago now I get the f*** out of here but when it gets paid off
Where do the globalist put
Fashion shows for Project Runway that's where they hide all of their secrets
Punch Club comes up with an evil plan to make people eat spinach
I've been Tim Gunn says make it happen
Remember
It work make it work make it work
The necks of mine from years
Town of that show
Is that where you first
No I didn't want to
I hooked into this though it's just
Curse you looked into it so there was a
Contestant whose name was covid with a
Okay what is the Sanskrit word
I'm already off
So there was a challenge galbi head-to-toe challenge
Okay dude
The outfit involved the mask
Haha and so like
Made a man cuz I got it
Coincidences it's great we all have a great time if you wanted to take a really easy route you can maybe make a hat
But the math get something and maybe a little bit more
Adventurous maybe a little more difficult to pull off as you are
Show me just so happen that the person's name was covid with a
The K which is not the same word
Are you sure the globalist didn't
Plants
A person named
Covid
To make a mask in order to give us
Cosmic realization
Eventually a pandemic would be coming name covid
And they will be using Mass
Kane order to
Turn us into their own models
Project
No fun way and quite frankly
You know it also is really interesting is like I couldn't laugh unless Alex
Found out
Like unless Alex reported on this trip
Couldn't
It's a joke
It's too subtle for anyone to get
Terrible dancer.
But Alex doesn't need them
Empire
Okay well that's true
By the way
Spitting image of Prince Charles
How do you need understand
Biloxi
So
Neither
Rollover 2.0
Like Count Dracula
Want
His genetics
Blood he wants to defile you
He wants to play
Kids material into your cells and overwrite your cell cell by cell
It's not a flying saucer crash down in Antarctica
In the movie The Thing
Their paint
No paintings
It's not the movie The Hunger
They look under the microscope
Then they see the vampire cell
Taking over the other cell
I didn't see that one
How to check it out
David Bowie movie
It's the real world Outdoors
Let me just do this
Anybody to fight this war
Expensive as hell
The f****** garlic bills
Movies that have stuck with the old ways you know it's very cost-effective
If you can find cheap steak material just about anywhere garlic you know
The leader Blade movies where you have to have high-tech stuff in the Underworld movies where you got to do all that stuff yet
Stays the same basically put a steak
Through its heart
I'm on light
Garlic
Keep them away
I have a little garlic
She's scared of these things but Alex is really worried about. I have some garlic
We're good to go
And
Not black cat
True so
Aldosterone
She lost her eye to
Could be a vampire
Been fighting a lichen
Pennywise
Alex is like the end of that last clip with a plug cuz corsi
This leads to an
Doing that long
Plug
Convoluted story about why he's not selling superblue anymore
Eagle your listeners will remember that the reason
Is because he got a season
The fifth letter from the Attorney General of New York
We have the charcoal
That
Is amazing
Your Superbowl
And tried to get me arrested
Still trying buddy
Everything
And
The problem is if I sell it they'll lie again and say he's telling the truth that all these people flooded by thinking insecure
Mafia.
Feel like if everybody's a lying about how you're selling this
That's not a reason to stop
It's just don't
Do the things
Doing those things
Skip right right right alright if you have nothing to fear then you have nothing to fear
Like I don't give a s*** like
There's no affidavit
If someone could file
Lakewood say I was under the
Impression
This would stop me from getting covid-19 if you didn't do anything
Yeah yeah yeah when those affidavits
Directly quote you
As having said something and then they go and they look and you said that stuff
That's the reason to stop selling that you stopped
Problem
So Alex doesn't mention this
Specifically on the epi
Episode B
Project Veritas has
Is a new little thing going on because I don't care
But apparently James O'Keefe made of
The auto CNN
Morning editorial call
And lives
Streamed it
You know soon as I got Jeff Zucker coming for you
Okay can get into the places where you think your private
In like
Are all like
We have lawyers that you not be here or we'll see
I hope
Blow up in James O'Keefe space at all
Really do it again being facetious really hoping
Alex doesn't mention this stuff
He does have
A weird out-of-nowhere obsession with Jeff Zucker
Seems to be related
What are the photo of
Jeff Zucker
Just like Brian stelter
Always So Satisfied
He makes millions of dollars
He's a joke
By the way he knows he's
A smog nobody
That's why he wants to bring you down
Hates
You have
Christmas
Pink sheep
Because you got wonderful wife and children will never be
A good person
He is a filthy
Degenerate
Cleavage
Little much
I I can't say that
Intended to be anti-Semitic
But holyshit
Is that trafficking at anti-semitism
Classical
The hates you and you have a good cream when you have a good Christmas
God he loves it when you have a good birthday but he hates it when you have a good Christmas
So ridiculous I don't know I mean I know somebody that Alex had bro
Brought up in the past
Sweet stranger to Alex's world but he's definitely not someone who's front
Center for an hour
If you well yeah yeah
It did it the focus is very
Glaring
Catch some of the
That's what I'm saying he's
I think he's today
The Boogeyman
I think that even Alex recognizes that James O'Keefe stuff is best to stay away from
I think this one might be too much
I don't even know if it's like
Consequences just might be like
I don't know if this is a little soft
Have to stay awake
Kick Jeff Zucker
Why not
Best way for Trump to remain present
Is to just
Do it
The elector
I think he should go with the American people
Resolute desk
Show all this evidence
Safe with me American people
I know I'm going to that event
By the way I'm taking that big March over we started before
These women hijacked
You can't even hear another microphone
I'll be there Wilmar slaughterhouse
I'll see you there
500000 people there also
You co-opted there
Yeah they have the permit you drove there
Good for you
Stole their vet again and pretend they're stealing your event when they organized didn't have the permits
Holyshit
Alex
Is on his way to another Tea Party
Trends we know his patterns of behavior
We know what he did with
The Tea Party
More like
Claiming
They were co-opting his movement what have you
And I think you could see it happening a little bit again smaller-scale
At least at this point
Because the people who are having these rallies in d.c.
Are to sort of like
Remnants of
Liberty party short people
Anymore
Now we're at a point where like Alex
He's probably more hooked up with The Fringe in the
Sizeable crowd
True true
He might actually be able to co-opt
Them far more
Successfully then
His attempt
To take over Glenn Beck
Beckwith on TV
Yeah Alex was the voice in the woods
But
I think I think one of the
Parts of what Alex and his credibility now is
Best friend
Rodger Stone
And just like we had Steve
Come in on the on December 1st
Now we have Steve
That we have
I don't understand why that slip of the tongue happen
Rodger swinging
Okay good
But thanks for the fences I don't mean like a lemon tea
The first clip is the bad kind of the swing
Biking Barcelona
The president has to have
Is quid
Powerful forces
Music
Armies
This is God's Nation
I believe
This job
When
In his resolve your tell Nixon about it
Oh boy
I just love the idea of like a Rodger
The 70s
Chose you for this
Live Your Life music bag
That would be great
This next clip Jordan
Maybe one of my favorite
I can't like
Steve's had some big ones
Just about himself
What booster
Steve stuff is like really braggadocio
The most important
Person I've done everything important
I overthrew Ghana
Twice yeah. Steve comes in
Project
Again you're doing it again okay let's hear it
Convertible
Agree
If this Ruth
Enforcement
It would be proof of
Foreign involvement
This is the best
Korean
Let me watch
AR
Northbrook
Korean they arrived in Maine
In the world
I had to come by boat to deliver
Man
The number of questions the Oscars who raises brings this claim into the territory of
That is a swig that is a swing for the fence
If this is a sprawling conspiracy involving tons of countries and US actors why did North Korea have the ballot
Why couldn't he have been print
Domestically why would these conspirators need to print the ballot in North Korea that have the
The country that's under the heaviest surveillance
And under very strict embargoes
Carry-out delivery by sea
I don't know what the cargo was
Also
You were sort of why would they arrive in Maine
Not realize that in order for a North Korean boat to reach main they would need to either navigate south of Africa then head north
Or Transit through the Panama Canal
North Korea would have a much easier but still almost ridiculously
Possible time
Getting a boat to the West
Coast
They're short lines on the scene
We're just imagining that these North Korean boats
Can show up wherever they want then why would they go to Hawaii
It's definitely the closest shot
Literally there could not be a more complicated Coastal State for North Korea to get to Benton Maine
Visit Russia must be intensely embarrassing for Trump
Like I do bent over backwards trying to impress in a piece Kim Jong-kook
Is dictator buddy sends a boat full of ballots halfway across the world to screw them over
That seems like an indication
Filmmaking skills
Or with a cracked up
I mean this sincerely Jordan
This is the most amazingly stupid fiery that I think I've ever hired someone tonight I started towards never heard anything
Like this
In my entire life there have been Dumber theories I think
This is something that Rodger is
Suggesting is being supported by quote
Absolute incontrovertible
I am more likely
To believe the Earth is
Flat then that North Korea
Could successfully
Secretly get boats
To mate
. Love Ballad
I mean like
A dinghy with North Korea printed on the
Couldn't
Get the maid from North Korea
North Korea
State of North Korea
Get a boat full of ballots to man why are we worried about their rocket program
Like chicken
Bring a bomb
Northridge
Bucket lift above into Main and then walk away and get on their boats and
Click a button and like
I feel like Rogers acting like the surveillance on North Korea is Joe
Just like a guy asleep
It must be made in front of a bunch of monitors
Picture of the room that they were supposed to be monitoring in the
Camera so it look
Looks like that the picture on top of the
I'm baffled by this
I do think that this is the kind of thing you can get someone to say whenever you get them out of prison yet
Yeah sure I'll say whatever the f*** you want man destined to be here by God in North Korean boats
So the only reason you lost the election
Hey buddy I got takeout last night
Instead of being in jail so guess what North Korea did it to Maine don't care
Moving on because someone had to have made this up
And that means it's someone made up
A story with
The stupidest
Possibly be something else
This is based on
I don't know tell me on an in
Sylveon and non-income
Show me Anaconda thoroughly controvertible docu I tried to look for some indication of what the f*** Rodger was talking
About any story that I could find had to do with what you're saying
So I don't know I don't know maybe
Deep thing on Twitter I couldn't find it's a big
That's a big swing this was another qanon
Goddamn
Rodger play out loud
Rodger
Put a globe in front of you and then
Just
Don't give me any
Put a globe
On your desk
Just point show me avocado
Not asking for details
Who is your master
Maybe try to get through the Straits of Gibraltar
Very serious question
Did it go
Through the
I think
But the only stay it would be more difficult to get a boat to leave Kansas
Killer take a huge wave get up there
BlackRock from ship
Aldo is easier
So
That's silly
Tim Rogers
This mixed with Rodger is like a man you forgotten the script
I have a very high regard for Sidney Powell
Mayor Rudy Giuliani who I've had enough
Friendship with
Since his first
Former mayor of New York City
Hey guy didn't Rudy cover up 9/11
No forgiving part of Pasadena
Don't worry about it
Rodger also thinks that
Supporters need to get aggressive
And they need to force legislators
To just say hey Trump
School let him stay president
And then we get a very familiar phenomena
Supporters of the president
In the tri-states
Need to begin now
Contact
Or your state
The president
Certification
The stonewalling there's no evidence is
Stonewall
Newmar the German guy well to Rodger
Promo code
Would you put Patriot
Are on the website
He's like I never do promo codes I started
I don't think I have heard him do a promo code
Whatever
You chose to be thoroughly bucko. No sooner or later yeah
Feel like he does do promo codes very often I can't think of a time where we made fun of him
I don't know what that means
But he didn't get them to talk about how you get an extra 10% off buddy
I'm not buying s***
You need fish oil
Sure they did
Remind you you're the reason we're all here thank you
These are great products you and your family need
34 Shelburne Manistee specials
Temperature
Something for everybody
But that's their brains
It's like a purse
Sugar
Yeah I don't I don't know if it's like
Fish oil or sugar or sugar is glucose
Omega threes or whatever you would like a big boy
I can't imagine the conversation between parents like one of them to Alexander's I can give the kids fish oil
No we're going to Sugar Sugar pills every morning
So at this point in the episode Alex realizes that Lynn Lynnwood
Attorney is doing now the press conference
Batshit quite
Absolute wildbad
I love it
1776 will commence again
We're going to send that message
Where do I send that message
Did George Soros
Hahaha
This is so scary
F******.
Yeah I mean that's
That is a Hitler rally that's not a non Hitler rally that is a Hitler rally where Hitler would Hitler
Out of our country literally Hitler
That is
5 Hitler mustache
Just because you got to leave some room
There's more Hitler to be
Gets around to talking about
Hey
Look
The media
Bad
Sure Thursday or are places that are good though
Well that's good
Especially because this is being broadcast live on Infowars
Now everybody's been reading the media stop
July
You can't trust them
Newsmax
They tell you the truth read the epoch times
They tell you the truth
Borg Queen Good and Evil
Don't ever say a word to powerful
That is sad
That is so sad even
F****** crazy people with nothing to lose are no powers than to associate himself sad
Have no problem saying in for is if he actually thought they were worth a damn
Yep
Oh my God
If they thought Infowars was going to grow
They would say n47ba better propaganda right now
Coat rack
Person in a suit is better
Disco track has done a great job
Being there
Not talking
Which is better than
Alex Jones
Yeah random person who doesn't have the intent baggage that Alex has
F****** pretend that the
The president's son told him to invest
Forget something
Somebody's not embarrassing the sack yeah
Is like a vagabond
Back to it
Calls
So this this caller
Need two sides at War
Like doctor pieces
Is The Art of War
And God has
Drawing out the enemy
Now there
Completely
Completely uncovered
And there's nothing that they you do
Have to do another
We the people will do the rest like
Glenwood Glenwood
Declaration of war date is
January 11th
Executive order
That was revived
12 2020
What's up
Do we know what's up
Are we ready
Are we the people ready to take
From the globalist
You're saying he's not
He's leaving at 9
Well we better hit the streets in like when was doing like we're doing
Trying to find meaning in your lack of leadership
Yep yep
He wants us to be revolution
Wow
We can't outsmart these idiots
Still fighting a war
Humans are not 50 years old
The issue is the rhogam
I'm coming up tomorrow
Now it's promote
And then the show takes
The leftist of left turn
Logan
Is on the show tomorrow
I'll look for that
Surprises
Steve pieczenik
I'm sorry works
Ecfr
That job
He did run
I just
Obama's CIA
The prompt on the staying in their Altima Global drawing
Barclay mountain did everything else
I'm not up here saying Robinwood
Disagree with him I'm not saying
I just
Yeah yeah
So Alex Azar is that weird
Because he did say that Steve was still working for the CIA after the Las Vegas shooting
When I see you tried to convince him that no one died it was all fake
So now he's trying to retain Steve's credibility but
Open pools By high-level CIA people
He's trying to he's trying to have his cake and eat it
Not good
Cut ties or you got to lean in you can't half-ass with Stevie B's but I kind of feel like
Call good call like knowing at least that you can't
This one this one might be too much
Even for us
Small because it
I just texted.
Talk about the first time this came up
To falsifiable
When this never comes out what happened
Sting operation should be there
Where is it
It's a disappointing game
But look
Steve
Might
Bee Raw
People
Might be lying to a true but there's one thing
It's totally true
By the way he wants it
He said
I called him
Botanica sent me
Photos when he's in North Korea hanging
Korean
He gets around
I'll just leave it
Florida
The Northridge
He says bhayshunyo high-level operative calling
You noticed Putin walk
Congratulate
This is really sad
Steve
Steve is like a baby
Maybe he's wrong about all this
Call
Shut up you can't even get it up for Steve pieczenik getting a call from China
North Korea One X bring up getting it up
Mamacita
But I mean
Family Show
Something going on
4 a.m. 5 a.m.
It's super male Vitality actually just like straight-up bull hormones
WhatsApp
F*** is it
Every time we hear about his life
Oh yeah his wife walks bow-legged so by this f****** boner
I love it I've never heard I've never heard that moment happen
That moment of Alex being forced to say the word erection
Nothing fell off
It really was girl I have curse
Call The View with Matt
I try not to focus
Alex goes back to Kohl's
With this caller
Because color speculating the globalist they're so out of control help probably let China
Grounded Invader sure that's probably going to do
Because Alex was so excited about this
He accidentally let this guy
Keep talking
Facial dangerous
I agree they want to break this they are foaming at the mouth
American Pie
White people
Puppies
That night
He's going to cause war against the white Patriots
What's going on
Want to chill y'all
Hoo-boy
Alex you should have
She hung up.
Comfortable in this conversation
Just caller who I've had a great time talking to has Natalie revealed
He believes that the Patriots are the white people
Oh
He's like
No I'm doing a good job I'm saying what you're saying all the Patriots are the white people at
Until Alex tries to save it by being like that
Alex gets gets back from commercial break
I will sing You belong to
To the city did play
1 strings
Ask about it
However Gnarls Barkley
Crazy
Alex does get a little excited
It is not the destination is the journey to catch my friends
Sucker
Don't do it don't do it
You might have noticed that the song Skip cuz Alex said you guys are cute
The bleep button at the wrong time
So the s*** went out over the air
Glocada
Skip has dropped at
Intuit
I do like is it him
That that's probably the most unhinged I've heard anyone sound in a good long while that was
That was out there
So Alex is into predictive programming
Say the movies are reality
This is a new one
Alex
You think you're number one if you remember movie come out
Panettiere
Robin Williams
Voting machines
Switch the election intuition results to the
Candidate that was West
Like what's happening right now
Crack go to conversation
There's this movie that
It's real
These people just cannot believe
For one second
That the guy for the past 4 years
They have heard nothing
But horrible s*** about
From one
Huge section of the
The country they can't believe that guy might not be beloved well no because they haven't heard that
It's all the media mainstream media just creating this false perception that no one likes
I mean I guess
Is everybody in this world lives in their own
Bubble where they don't have to
To deal with like
Reality
At all but I mean you can't go to out you can't walk down the street and not be like
Oh a lot of people hate
It's kind of
You know it's an interesting line that I struggle with sometimes a release to have in the past and that is that like
You can recognize that
Organizations like a Coke brother isn't
Instead they do
Fun things massively on the right
But
Knowing that
You cannot save it
People don't believe
Conservative
Principles or values or have
Right-leaning politics
You can't sleep at all that
That's fake because
There is this libertarian moneyed interest that's load again today
Push things that way
This same is sort of the
The Trap is it Alex
A lot of
Trump photo
Fall into
Medias
Just telling everyone right
Is bad right and then
Thinking that no one actually believes that
The media is crumbling
Powerless
Pathetic and everyone knows they're Liars now yeah
That's kind of a trap
I mean I guess when you
Expose if you did human eyes enough
People
A large enough group
Then eventually people who
Know who are like
Oh no I know plenty of people who would normally fall into that group
They must secretly be Trump supporters to or something because it's like
How can I add this is nuts
Wild
So are this caller believes that
You get to
Kamala Harris
Will become president
Albino get out of there somehow sure
Romantical
I'm wearing ankle bracelet
Kamala Harris will make
Either
AOC
Or Hillary is president
And then Alex asked
The most
Introspect
Steve question I could imagine
You can have a stroke or you can be declared incompetent which is
India president
And she's going to get hurt either AOC or Hillary Clinton and as her Vice
President why
It would be the absolute
Worst scenario for this country
What happened
Why
Why is there such a cult of Hillary's is she such a devil worshiper the table than having her is like
Why is the left so obsessed with Hillary Clinton
Obsessed with you
We just
Talking about Hillary dad
Wow yeah yeah pretty pretty cool pretty cool
You
I don't know if projection gets that
Loud
That's the most louder
This
Get another caller and this dude says if they're going to
Takeover DC Shore
Right
It's going to be approached
Is where
I
The probably not going to do the
But now I do have the Opera
Trinity
I don't know if I could do it safely
Who's Alex did this I would want to go make a documentary about
I really really want
Here we go
I already have the way
Takeover d.c.
What you guys
Remember everybody needs to be out there
Sidelineswap
Please take care of those come outside I'm moving into d.c.
Yeah.
Lincoln Memorial
I
Would love
To go
And documented howley's
Time at the Lincoln Memorial now
Know if we do not if he didn't
If you are listening to this and you have
$5
I don't know where I was going to have that we need a billion dollars to make that
I don't want anybody to do like giving money to make a document in my head
Because you know just
Logistics of the world
I think there's such an amazing story to be told here if Alex were to go and that is
Is Vicki would realize that eats
Winter in d.c. okay
What I got for you
We got to get Ken Burns in on this we got to we got to get Ken Burns we got to go
Free backgrounds
Gets Louis Theroux
Man to the grisliest Alex eats
Or Owen Shroyer skins Alexandra
Day to Alex's trying to make a fire out of
Is steamers
Spiritually when I said that I would eat my neighbors
Soca
Michelina's okay
It's cool
He's such an amazing
Potential in my brain
For like what
This looks like in the real world
If he did this cute stay at a hotel nearby
And show up and yell in a bullhorn every now and again
You would never stay
It's not going to be over 40 degrees until March
Lowe's is cold this winter look at Memorial
Physically
No
But I would love I would love it
Man I wish I was a millionaire
I would say Alex
Giant donation
But you hacked
To do this
You have to
Not any of your stuff
You have to stay out there as long as this encampment last
Much like maybe some
MTV show from the early 2000
You get paid more the longer you stay out there like it and
All on cam
Cuz I want to see your misery
Yeah I want to see you camping out f***
I'm pissed off now 3 in the morning
So mad
That only 2,000 people showed up
Do your encampments needs to be fat bear there needs to be 24/7 lives yums of everybody like
Like making Wagers and s*** like that
This should be on
Daily this is what I'm talkin about
I probably would not go
For the sake of safety and
Just responsibility in
The present world we live in
Under ideal circumstances I would love
To go make a documentary
Best I could do is if he actually does this
And they actually have feeds
I might be tempted
Do not stop coverage of it
Like waiting for him to break
But he wouldn't break now
It would end up being like
2 minutes of Alex yelling in a bullhorn and then Harrison Smith in the studio
Excuse for why you have to leave right away that we wouldn't have to
He wouldn't lose all faith
All the sudden covid will be real
This is just another time and it sucks
Because we've got this enough
That like it's another time that I see this amazing potential
In what could
Would come and it's not going to go I'm preemptively disappointed
It's not going to be great
I remember
It's the same thing I felt like the second time I heard there was a marathon
The first time
Like oh my God
I meant psycho Hour 3 David nights hosting
And then the second time like cats
Be good now I just like
Caravan f***** me
Everything there sucks I was going to
Georgia suck
Well I mean when you might have to write a song about how excited
Here's the problem
When we make a show about an exhaustive failure
Who fails exhaustively
All the time
It's hard for us to expect him to succeed
Kind of have to always
You always hope Charlie Brown's going to kick that f****** ball man
To come in with a little optimism
Or else
You know it's a dick
Try and kick the ball
Thank you Alec
Please
Do it do it
Do it you'll save America
We will create a documentary for
Free you will
Save America single-handedly if you camp out at the Lincoln Memorial through the rapper
And if you eat fish and try and get as fat as possible
So good.
It's caller who's threatening to shut down B inauguration
He's going real deep right now
Before
He'll probably wait
Operation
It ain't going to be in d.c.
Down
They're probably going to do it
California or New York City it's going to be
Everybody off to understand me
Fancy pants
I'm out there on the 12th
Imma be there on the 20th come hell or high water
So you got my commitment
If you go ahead and do whatever you want
Distract me.
You're the bad guy remember your favorite guy is literally the emperor
Yeah you don't get to do that that's not
Jerk
See now that would be that would be acceptable on his joining The Darkside episode where he quotes
31 the whole time and he comes into the show as just swelling strings at
That would be fitting
So I
I don't think Alex is going to follow through with this I think he's going to go do some publicity stunts and DC on the 12th
Which is when
That rally he's going to co-opt is
And then on the 20th for inauguration I could see him going to that as well and trying to cause a scene
But when will the when will the camping be would it be on the 12th
Start on the 12th and then go through the inauguration be set up a goddamn
Broadcast
From the Lincoln Memorial if you believe he will spend hours on that
It makes me sad I wanted to happen
And I'm not going to allow myself to believe that it's not going to happen
Yeah there's a chance
Yes there's always the chance hope
It's spring
Eternal Schroeder
Jurors occupation
So we will see until we're allowed to observe it
Strangers
We're strangers Monday's episode
Could not be
It is both
Simultaneously
An episode about Rogan and nah
To tune in on Monday to find out sounds like something I would hear on the Joe Rogan
Wooden Shelf
Same time
How about I can't remember what his sponsors were
Dammit
Was there a toilet one
Swift shrimp
No that's Rick and Morty
Plushie plushie
Turn off
Jordan but until then
We're also on
We are 1000 or fight not go to bed
Jordan
If you could please find a local charity or Bellefontaine your area to help out people doing God's work
Dzx Clark
I'm Daryl rundus I'm a North Korean
Pilot tugboat captain
Alex
Birthstone colors