Damn important
I have great respect for this knowledge B
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Joe
Jordan
For you sure
Your bright spot
Today is
So I have not taken part in
Too much
Like ordering
Food from Plato's sure sure sure I've tried to keep that limited
Expensive
But I realized that I hadn't had Taco Bell in a long time
And so I decided to order some Taco Bell delivery reliving those comic days
Something
Could do
Pizzas delivered Chinese food delivered
Yep yep
So that was kind
But I noticed
Something on the menu that I never seen before it was like
Can aged cheddar chalupa
Chalupa
What kind of thing but it had like cheese
Tiago
This is our Artisan aged cheese
Ambitious
Very pretentious
But I had to try it
Yeah you got to
And
It was
So good
It was also terrible good
I got it as a call out
Crunchiness of the cheese is really complementing
What are you doing hi falutin ask Taco Bell
The Great British baking show enjoyed it quite a bit and you know
If you got to find you got to find the light where at
Exist
I won't provide
Spoilers here but as you might be aware
Star Wars
Have you heard of Star Wars
The one with the Enterprises prize the guys they have a uniform
I got a little things on his head was now ruining our world
I don't know
Mandalorian
Huge fan watching it
Conversation
Oh yeah
Should I try and guess it I think you should
Okay
Pete new really close though
Roku
Grogan very close to pee
Roku Roku I know it's baby Yoda forgot that's a Star Wars name
Forever
Grow glue no spoilers
Oh that's not a spoiler egg you find out that was last at
Behind
Forget Brogan you're like us baby
Yeah yeah
Not my growbiz
Aspects
Not so this episode most recent one
Character came back
Who made me extremely
Extremely happy and in a very lovely way
The second season has been basically like you remember what you did
I don't want to I don't want to be like
Addictive in case it's right
Put my
Instinct is to joke that it's Jar Jar Binks
No
S*** where was I
Oh yeah the second season has been fun dip
You know it's the sugar stick
Check that you're dipping and more sugar to eat
Buy everything has been
Junk food
And it is been
Incredible and I love it so much that metaphor falls apart is fun dip sucks
Sugar overload because my point does sugar even as a kid I didn't want any
Cubs fun dip
Sky chewed on that stick like it was my
Milk-Bone in miraculous stray dog
Exactly well I'm glad you're enjoying that
Feel like
My plan is
Watch the Mandalorian once there's like
Like five seasons of it all
I have this
TV shows like I want there to be multiple seasons of it that I can bend
Cuz if I like it
I don't want to stop watching who was no Netflix was the first
Play stood like just released the whole that was it like Daredevil or something that was the first show where they're like
We're putting all 12 episodes out
And I've never I'm no longer able to watch episodic
Television
It started earlier than that for me or at least like the
The challenge of it I think it's cuz what I would do is I would come to shows light
Prick bye-bye like people saying this is the best day ever
Trick by these Liars who Delights
A lot of Television is reliant on
Cliffhanger Enon Center
Especially hour-long dramas if you're watching it week-to-week
Like deep
Experiences that is so much more engrossing attic
Can trick you into liking things
Is that you don't actually like all that much true
So I always try and give things a little bit of time get a little space until like lost I started in likes
Season 4
And the experience of watching
In the prior three seasons like
All in a row
Was that pretty gratifying that I hated it for the 13 episodes to get into it
Imagine if I started watching episodically I'd watch the first episode be like
Yeah you know
Got to love you say I'm good but it would be a different
Movie harder
Television
Bottles of change
Yes this is us
Commentary
Cultural
A tomato
Jordan today we got an episode
Forever now
I started listening to the episode with Rogan Alex's interview for
Hour-long interview with Joe Rogan
The first minute
Policy real questions getting into the nitty-gritty of universal basic income I made it like
15 minutes in as like I'll do an episode about this eventually probably but like so annoying
To give you some contact list
He asked is it like
At what point did you realize that
That you were like
Really famous but you can do whatever you want to do
That's a great question through something along the lines of like
You know what I like about smoking weed as it makes me think about more in
Interesting fact
So I just I didn't have it in me to do that to this episode so we're talking about Thursday and Friday on the Alex Jones
Program already
Going to see if he's going to
Continue his ideas about moving
DC and living at
Spoiler alert no updates
Didn't even mention it
I'm thinking about it more than him
The books of signed up and reporting to show us
Exam
Kia I love you thank you so much you're now if I was wrong
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you kitty I love you
The car is probably huh
Mendoza Katniss minno h
Thank you so much
I'm very much been on the cat
Lang J
Lang
Last initial J
Very much language
SpongeBob Patrick
Next you ain't came thank you so much you're Now by what you want
Thank you very much Patrick Ewing
Hanging that Patrick Patrick Ewing
Next Cosmic
As well K-8
As
Meek thank you so much
Biohazard
And finally biohazard thank you so much
Website knowledge or
You could do is you could take that feeling of generosity
You can put it into the Rock
Launcher that you have a fix
Next to your back
Directly on top of your
Rocket pack
Pack of course shirkin been down
Just a little bit because of rocket launcher affixed to your back is a terrible idea to pull your scope up and you fire that
Rocket launcher
Into the Imperial cruise ship
Whatever charity that you are looking for
No it was not
Good alright
Jordan today
December 3rd
Not a great episode December 4th there's a little bit more going on
But I did find
A delightful out-of-context draw
Which I will share with you right now
Jennifer flag hero
Constitutional lawyer Patriot
Turn the Jedi
Star Wars see it all makes sense.
I love the idea that Alex is a constitutional
Macy's Thanksgiving Day Parade as a constitutional lawyer float
Weirdly
I think that perfectly sums up Alex's show
The person he's calling a constitutional lawyer
How dare he maintained that he's not that into Star Wars outside of a b****
We start on third hiiraan
I I kind of maybe
Glance this off the first time I heard Alex discussing
Horor bringing up his little fat
Factoids but I decided this time
It would be best to look into it and
Discuss
What was going
777 people died
Yesterday
They're saying from covid
Covid related
Percent
False
Positive
So we heard him say that on a previous episode but I think it was in the context
Do something over there were bigger things going on, it'll be better side
Steve bulshit spell the German courts must be brought into that alright
Let's see what happen
Student stories a little bit more complicated than what Alex is saying
What's at the core of it is that
Court determines haha was it for German citizens who were in Portugal on holiday were held illegally
When they were quarantine
1:18
Tested positive for covid-19
Exotic Portugal care
It wasn't a German Court
It was Portuguese now I think Portugal
One of these vacationers tested positive and wasn't close contact with the other three so the Portuguese authorities quarantined them in a hotel
They can test it this
Decision ultimately judge
I just found that their quarantine was unlawful
Part of the evidence that was used at their trial was related to a study that claimed the PCR test or up to 97% unreal
Liable cause that ratio of false positive
However and as always the case Daddy
Is not what the study said
This was a piece of me clinical
Just diseases Journal which looked at what is known as the
Cycle threshold of testing
And how that could be a way to better understand viral load in the possibility of infection
Samcrac
According to this article the consensus had previously been to understand someone is not contagious
After 10 days
And a viral load that
They cannot be identified with a cycle threshold value of 30 or higher
Sure
From
61 positive samples
1941 were chosen
And tested using different cycle thresholds
To see how
The early estimates
Held up a miserly assessments
They found it with a cycle threshold of
70% of samples were still positive
It's like oh threshold 30 that number dropped
21 cycle threshold was 35 the number of positive results were less than
3%
In the publication they literally say that this finding
Using more data than their original set
Does not significantly changed
The conclusions that have been reach previously
The finding essentially boiled down to a feeling that after 10 days if your PCR test
Is that a negative without under 30 threshold
Icycle threshold
Then you're almost certainly not going to be contagious
This is not
Proof that the
PCR test are always false positive nor did a German Court decide
The test is a scam
Alex has no idea what the
The story is about nordaas even
No but the study that underpins the story
Even with this information
Using the cycle threshold value to infer whether or not a person is possibly infectious
Is not a precise way to interpret these
These figures and some people definitely worn again
There are a number of other variables
Consider but the talking point
That's been taken from this publication and disseminated on right-wing media
Is a PCR test
Has been proven
German courts
To be a false positive rate of 97%
The complete Bowl
The court in Portugal ruled that the vacationers have been illegally detained based on their inability to find any indication
Of what the cycle threshold that was used in their paws
Test result was
In court they could not defend their positive diagnosis
Sure this was a case that was mishandled by Portuguese Authority
He's not an indictment of test
For covid-19
I also just
Whenever you said that last time
Is a global pandemic
That affects a lot of countries
I don't care if
Germany
Is like
Germany's court system can't be like
They're all full of s*** and I'll buy it
I just don't
I just don't care there are other
There's other countries
Yeah I don't like I buy it I found another
Story that I thought what was what Alex was talking
I'm about there was a lab in in Germany
That process I think in one month they process
60 tests
And 58 were false positives
And the reason was because there was a
Supply shortage
And they they're normal reagent was unavailable
Compatible reagent
And the mistake was was found in like
Okay
Yeah we do all this
But like the I bet that was what I kind of thought would make sense
Historians I call this
This is clearly
German courts
Portuguese
German vacationers in Portugal
And it's a misrepresentation of what the court decided
And the study that was being
Introduced
So
Decides about
Coronavirus
I don't trust
Most courts
Impartial or know what they're talkin decided that I'd like to
See ya I'd like to I'd like to read it
Some Heroes
Bird people
Who are staying open
Despite
Covid
Popular restaurant and bar
New York New York
Maybe next year
Essential
The police arrest you
Autonomous
Tommy's
Police
Our number one here
Says this guy's name wrong
It's not Danny pursetti it's
Little bit of a turn between when he recorded this episode in when we were recording our it's okay
On the night of December 5th Danny presti was arrest
But it wasn't for keeping his bar open as an autonomous zone or some s***
According to NBC4 New York
Quote New York City Sheriff's office said deputies attempted to take Danny presti
E34 into custody at just after midnight Sunday
After observing patrons
Entering Mac
Public House via and empty commercial space next door
Upon identifying themselves
The sheriff's office said presti allegedly fled on foot
Got into his car drove into one of the deputies
And then continued driving with the inter Deputy clinging to the hood
I think
I think that Alex would like to paint this is a situation where this guy is just like and I got to put food on the
Table rental
It got the car
Yeah that'll do
Anyway from the heroic story
Fighting back against
The government's that attic
Control4 closing It restaurant in the midst of a pandemic try not to
Yeah yeah
It's going to be an interesting story to try and weave these small business owners
They worried about them
Netflix show you
Michigan
The business owner comes up and takes over the local L'Occitane says listen
You're forcing me to fight
We went to drop
We try to log on thousands of times over.
20 times a day
And I wanted you to see if we can get it
So what would you like
That's sad
This is a disgrace for a couple reasons
The first and most obvious is that the stimulus that was given out in the management of it was entirely up to his hero.
Trump and his
If Trump in the GOP
He controlled it been willing to provide more support for the people who are struggling
Then the stimulus probably would have been much larger
April's government was it all concerned with governing and
Incompetent leadership then the website that Alex had trouble using probably might have been better
The people that Alex supports
Send deifies of the exact people who could have averted the problem that he's complaining about but Alex refuses to acknowledge
It's just so f****** Republican to destroy the country and then be like sea government can't work
The second problem is that if Democrats had been in charge and a robust stimulus package had been passed that allowed
How do small business owners to comfortably survive this Health crisis
Exactly be super again
Pants that I hate the idea of a social safety net
If these business owners were being paid to close temporarily
To deal with the virus
Be proof that the nanny state was trying to make all business owners
Depended on them to survive
In a situation like the one we're in there is nothing that leaders can do that will appease the s*** head fake populist like Alex
You got it if they pass massive spending bills
To take care of the public
It's proof of a communist conspiracy tried to pacify the population order makeup surfs
He's a dope ass massive
Spending bills to take care of people
It's proof that they only care about Jeff Bezos
Switch is proof that it's a grant
Conspiracy to make you dependent on pesos which will bring in communism or something
This is the part of Alex's politics
The Trap
The Joke is on You if you take
Seriously because he doesn't give a s*** about any of this
He's the most
Totally satisfying to yell about
The small business owners were hurt by the shutdown
What is principal
Any other response
Crisis like this the only thing he can actually Advocate is acting like there is no virus
Which sounds better
When you just presented as yelling about the
Sportbusiness
I agree though the business owners happy
October
Business case
I don't think there is like problems with some of the disc
Descriptive things that Alex's heart that I'll just never respect him
To speak on the subject
Because he's not a
Sincere or Genuine actor in this
It always work
Whenever things are going well
Relatively speaking
Republicans who likes this is there could be going better if we just didn't get got away with all this right
Regulation and s*** people alike
And then by the time we're here
Four years later whenever we're not going to have one
They switch their tuner
Why hasn't government done anything for us
Alex is the only person
That forces me to
Constantly say like
How dare you
Kind of overused in boring Alex doing that makes
We just go
Yep I think he's the only person because he's the only person we look at this
Smart lights
I bet if we covered Russian 800 other people a day
If we didn't show about Rush Limbaugh I guarantee you
Do you think how dare you
So on this on this day Alex's
Is pretty excited
Because he has that Rogan interview already recorded
And
I think it's been my contention and
What's stronger than a
Contention
CertainTeed
Yeah
Certainty Works positive
Alex's using
Joe Rogan
To try and appeal to a wider audience
Event he has access to
It's just outright says so
Where are some of the highlights
Coming up
Tower and then
Or so
Foreign policy
Millions of years
Free Taco Bell
This is a great way
To reach out to new people that I know I don't look at Alex Jones don't look at the Joe Rogan to it so this is a powerful
This is an important thing to understand that this is why Jose kind of being used
That Alex has a pretty Keen awareness that you know people look
If it's Joe but they won't look at it if it's me because I'm Luna
Now
The issue for me comes down to
Do you remember
Pretending Joe's listening now
You remember when Alex was screaming about your kids on are Sneaky Snake I do
He was going to destroy you
Globulin
Remember all that stuff
That was when you were of making yourself available to be used so way are not wanting response to
When you got on your show and I can't have Alex on because this hooks
Oh you said you he was not somebody who your platform was available to he talked about your
Kids on his show
Do you know your platforms available to him you're going to come
You live in Austin going to come on his show he gets to use you for publicity now all of a sudden you're not a sneaky snake you're one of the best
I have a history of unhealthy real
Is that what you wanted to hear
Apparently obvious could this be like
Look
We knew it
He knew it
Maybe Joe is the only person who
It doesn't know it but he probably knows it too
He has the most awesome mentality
Because the night
Yeah
At the same time whenever he said it I was like well that's
A little
That's a little guy
Here's the deal I'm trying to use this dude to Trojan Horse by extremist views on to audiences that no better than
Linda listen to me
Look we all know that but it's tacky to say it right
I had a nightmare the other night
I know that
It's also not great
To talk about dreams
And it was that our show disappeared
Because of like
Copyright
Issues
Yeah I know this is fair use that using Alex's
Stop
But it's still something that worries me is like hey is there possibility that you know we could have all of our episodes
Give him ideas
So it's too late cuz on his show he gave us
Permission to do this
Everything I do with free air
Copyright free
Meaning that
You can take it
You can share it
We had so many emails are so many letters by
Infowars
I copied your DVD come out
You better
Not only do we have his Blessing we have is insist
Distance that we do this show
Alex Jones Infowars
My barn is looking a little worn down
Do you think I could painting
Forza park on the side of its Alex I wanted to paint in pores on my barber was worried about getting sued
Rob Rob do I got to get someone in Nebraska
He's got the paint cans
Rob Rob
You know how we're all call Robert Barn we will do anything and everything for free publicity
But this one time I hate Barnes
That's what it is
Robert Barnes
And I hate Barney
Maybe that's what the person was asked
Information for it
And Alex has permission to
Barnes was an employee
So like I said Rogan is making
Himself available and helping Alex get it
Attention and so that means that he is Brave
He is a big Brave boy
And
It turns out that
Tucker Tucker Carlson
While his rhetoric is good he is
Not somebody that is going to have Alex on his show
So he's not as good as Roku
Pikachu
No one else in this position is
Weezer friend
But
I need to plug in for down there
Nobody's been willing to go to bed for me
Oh no
I got told
UFO
This call
Even in your imagination you number two
How about that
Thoroughly fictitious person that I didn't bed right now are you voice in my head
Yeah Alex is Public Enemy Number Two
I don't even know
I would be interested to find out if Biden actually even knows who Alex Jones
I would imagine there's a possibility
I think the people around
Biden would know
I don't think Biden
Has ever actually been like I don't think they even need to broach the subject like
He might have gone like hey who's this
Alex Jones character in Glisan
You don't need to worry
Here's what I would say
He is as aware of Alex
The Property Brother
Belly soundtrack
And there are a couple of
I've seen them somewhere I don't know what their show is about
Smiling I guess
Yeah I would imagine that it's kind of like Alex's existence
But probably has now it no idea
Let's b b my scent
I would prefer if Alex Jones data Property Brother
What are we just fix
Houses on TV
The best
The exact
Same amount of work
Someone called him and said that the doj
Under Biden
Come after you
There's a possibility
They're trying
To get Alex on to the
The team
I want to be given immunity
From God
My music library much
All looks so inviting
All the money all the private jets all the best medicine
Boats
Joan we love you just come with us
Going to come over to us Jones
Tom here
Tom Thumb do us
Corporate lawyers
Kill the firstborn
It's disgusting
Hey Rob.
Quite a while
God you can just you can hear him looking at the clock
Totally
Bridge
20 seconds left
Cigars back in stock
They try and steal me away from you guys and the only thing keeping me from them
Is your money
I'm going to stay in this fight as long as you're giving me money to but let me tell you I have offers that others would kill their children
Here's what I'm telling you I don't have your money
I'm on their team
For money
Sounds heroic
And the doj is not going to come after you
Scalpel
So Alex Goes to commercial after talk about Frost
The guard and man
He loves that song A Bad to the Bone
Did I would say that it sucks
I would say and I'm sorry
Do you like that tonight
It's so droning babababababababa
That's what I was saying
The song
Alex Alex is listening
Loving it
F****** loves it and then he has this weird Fanta
What just happened
Love you. Dad
What
I got a message
Alright
Learn the wrong lessons from things
His career was like
You're driving irresponsibly
You knocked off the road by
My happen
Santa menu
Is irresponsible if pecan going
Yeah I would say that's a
I don't like why not just keep on driving down the desert road
It's a fantasy that Jack Rabbit does not have to be there I mean I guess stories aren't interesting without conflict of some sort
Do you have to have a I guess this is more of a man versus nature kind of
Steamatic of I would also say
With context
Cookie man versus self
That could be a good
Exactly
So he wants to take some time here on this episode to play clips
Of his Rogan
Interview bring that into the show itself
But there's a problem
There's a problem
Copywriter
No
Editor those clips
And I got this big front clip
Out of the 49 minutes
Are we come back
Tomorrow maybe
I'm not sure we we there that
But
There's there's so much more
To get to her today
So many angles
Job
Forecast
1 clipper
Because
The only Power
This point
Every time we do this
I like a lot of political news
Tip of the spear
We get that done
Dot-com
Newswars.com
And so much more
To fund this operation
Face
We need your support a lot of lot of water address
I do it
Appreciate the idea that he saying like Okay with these things happen the only Power I have is to give up
What kind of means like I run this whole thing and I'm going on
Strike against
Best Buy support
How dare my subordinates
What
What are we doing
What's the problem now wait they gave me more options that I had requested overachievers
Eclipse
I can't possibly be bothered to look through and choose the ones I want
To use know I must on air throw a tantrum
Strike
This is the type of
Stuff where you go you know what
A lot of people think this guy is a lead
Yeah the only
The only thing I have left to me is to give up
In the face of adversity
Challenge I say
No in the adversity is like
Something you could sort out during a commercial break
Yazoo
Just pho
Hey guys could you pick up a couple of those cups for me and then just send them over real quick
Evil is up against this guy is like this guy is the dude he was like
Going to stand up to the devil I'll be like
I guess I could just inconvenience him a little
Maybe this is the devil doesn't even have to destroy Alex or any kind of elaborate plan he could just make his life a little annoyed
Like fuk it I don't care
Flexing on saying like see this is how much better than you I am I'm going to pay
Alex
Jones's your
Immortal animated
Strowman winning the Tag Team Championship with a twelve-year-old child
We got going up against Ivan Drago
Mr. Magoo
Quite a match
That'll do it so Alex does finally gets
Some clips of Rogan
Probably going to have to do this as an episode do but like
Bee sounds
So f***** up
Just in this one
Quit they play
God
I understand
Be reluctant to Everett
Or
Multiply
But
It's been shown throughout history
The simplest way to combat.
Is the shutdown
And you're in you say
You got to go to bed
Use water to go to bed
Can you go shut up
It's sort of the same thing
Dad
It's a crazy interview for Plus hours long a lot of leaves a lot of surprises
Yeah
I guess Jose
Replying and that clip that you should debate your child
Okay
Well also in that
Contact your framing yourself as
The child
And the parrot does make the rules
So the bedtime is the bedtime
Analogous
To being kicked off social media
You're going to abide by their bedtime
Where you fall asleep or not it's on you but you're going to be in that bed
Because
Could Barrett's in many ways one thing that you are learning how to be
He is a member of
Society insofar as your actions affect others
Weird Amanda in the same way
The people who are doing this b*******
Children
Society which means there are rules
Yeah yeah I mean
Not the way he wants. It might work a lot better than
One of the reasons that they sound
Sound so f***** up in that clip is like
The audio
Doesn't sound right
It's either
Sped up slightly
Like I don't know what it is but it doesn't have the same tone as Joe's voice normally does
So I don't know what it is I think somebody messed that up
And now he probably
Just has better sound people on his own show like I said the first half hour 20 minutes of it
That doesn't sound like that
No it's
There was something wrong with
The the replay are there
But yeah it's like
Well the only option we have here. It's a give up
God who is this is the level of like kind of like amazing interview they had were there like
Don't yell at your kids
Just go to bed
I can't wait
County for four hours of that see what you got to do is be like
I hate kid
Tell you about
You got to do with me
Did you get into the bedroom you lay in bed
You fall asleep if you don't do that you're going to hell
If Joe's point is that like
Parent should explain to a child who's curious about why there's a bedtime why it healthy
I need to go to bed
What if that's the case
If he wants
How to make that equivalent to like
Social media platforms
Should be a little bit more trance
Apparent
I'll go with you
But I also don't think they like
I don't think the decisions that have been made or not like kicking Alex off
Like that
Overturned by transparency
Also I would like to know Alex is Takeoff
Whether or not he explains bed
Bedtime very clearly
Curious math
The 4th now and here's hoping that this is a leg up
Duration of Donald John Trump and we fight back.
Ambulance Now red handed in all five states with the red-handed video
Eagles
Devastating
His hands on those East
Uber
Can get his hands on them but unfortunately you know he doesn't have
The power oven like an entire government
Behind him
I get really
Bored
Of a lot of this Alex
Repeating and amplifying like Rudy Giuliani in Hudson
I just
How are you
It's exhausting
Yeah it's exhausting
Go home and bleed your hair dye there
Alex's big news
Was that
I would like on my route
Iowa
Hours last night
Call Megan
Honda.com
Fashionphile.com
Brittle, Breitbart because they're really start to drop the ball and turn against
Very disgusting but I guess that
Very sad
Fannie Flagg
Think about that a little more why don't you
What does it imply about Breitbart what is it Apple imply about
Is that it only produces
Content-based
Stephon what billionaires would like huh
Interesting
Also what does that imply about like things like parlor
Your social media Network that you really seem to like that has bunch
Mercer money
It seems like they would only allow things that the Mercers would want
Like use that as an attack
On Breitbart because they're out of pocket or whatever complicated
I would leave it alone
That's that's like
Following the money in it investigation like
If you follow the money you're going to get corrupt politician
It's going to happen because they are
So don't follow the bus
Do you know what happens with corrupt politicians was that
They put ballots
Black Kray
MMA
Corrupt
One of the stories
Hundreds
With video in dozens of cases
Of the fraud
People looking over their shoulder
Everybody out
Channel water
Broke
That's what you're overturning
Sylvester when he's caught with Tweety Bird mouth
Start running the sons of b****** and then it turns out they're all night mode
So this is the video that Rudy Giuliani had entered into his evidence
Does proof of illegal votes being counted in the Georgia State Farm Arena
It was alleged that these were secret legal Bala
That were produced from black boxes when no one was looking
The surveillance video was reviewed by election officials who said that there was literally nothing abnormal about the video and that these were illegal
No balance
If the
If the material the Box
It is made of Camp Beam on now
Why not make the ballots out of Gabriel Sterling the voting systems manager in Georgia said quote the 90s
Second video of election workers at State Farm Arena purporting to show fraud was watched in its entirety hours of foot
Georgia Secretary of State investigators
Normal ballot processing
Once again we have Trump's goon trying to manufacture of voter fraud narrative out of the
The appearance of something that they think
Look suspicious
The fact that they keep doing this and each time at 2
Turns out to be nothing should make his followers weary the next time Rudy or Alex find some
Supposed to irregularity
But some people fall for multiple Doomsday
Like predictions
There's no towel
Okay it's December 20th it's on December 21st math again
2020 100
Guys come on follow me for the next hundred years
That will be all right
Yeah
It's just it's exhausting
And I think
These are thin and
I just
I don't know
Play lose my page
Covering the same topic over and over again
So I was very excited
To hear that
Tilapia pad
I don't know
The point is is that he did say
That the mafia did not exist
Testimony
In the 40s early 50s
That the mafia
Did
Not
Exist
The reason the J Edgar Hoover was in denial about the existence of the mafia was that at
The time the FBI was basically entirely focused on investigating alleged communists
It's surveilling left-wing activist
He didn't see going after Mafia actors as a good use of resources and organized crime could be difficult
The prosecutor
And they were rich
So they could bribe people
Give people money
If you want them to
Left if Alex has been around in 1955 he would have been
Stickley supported the FBI leaving the mafia alone thing there just go to Mercado businessman
Come on a bigger issues like a literally everyone I don't like is a communist they do you got to be spent
Seneca time on
God-fearing Catholics over here just trying to make a living in the new world and
You're going to ignore them and you ever go out to the copies that's what you do
Motor light
So Alex is like you sitting there talking about these globulus
They're a menace
They wanted to populate
Everybody don't kill off the entire world
Babe
But the globalist
They seem to have like a
The gun to their head
Alien gun
But I realize this sounds silly
Yes no
Far more dangerous
Absolutely
Yeah but it's
Do to your head if it went just the
You realize this sounds a little silly
In the middle
Kamikaze
Somebody's got a gun to the Head
Populate your planet
Hey Marlon
Okay
Colonel I don't know
I just we can't figure out why
Pretty sure that a lie
Can't have a gun to you
To their head
I just go I grow so tired of thee like
Trying to save face by being like I'm not saying aliens but the Bible says yes
What about
You believe everything the Bible says so the Bible says is an alien you're saying is an alien
The next question I'd like to ask
If you were to present this in my in my present
So you're saying
Movie the next question
Wild Bible says
I'm starting to feel like we could do this for a while
Alien gun to their head but they're also the people who James Bond
The villains are based on
I don't know if you know that look
Why does dr. evil look like
Because Hollywood nosey people look like
Or
Where does Mini-Me
Well that was actually an interesting story
Have you ever seen the island of dr.
Actor Morales
Weeds
Internet last week
Bugs and weeds
See Marlon Brando
The director actually went crazy it's a really interesting movie
Tampons
Address here
If you don't find her operation if you don't need to take a shopping with us
Certainly if you want more content like this
Please give us money
All right we have break
News Acme
That guy looks a little bit like
Can we pull up some
Blofeld
Yeah yeah I know I'm Wolf Blitzer can we pull up Blauvelt
My enemies look like James Bond villains not that one the other one the other one that's get a picture
What about Mini-Me
No you will eat sewage I look like Zachary but you know what just pull up dr. evil that
That I'm doing this great impression of sewage man
Look we need your
I was like
That's that's
Does the tragic
Add pivot
I'll bet it gets even worse cuz I was just talking about this process
The guard that's back in
I think you might be f****** around and getting himself Suited
Meadows great for women too
But okay
Medical doctors should prescribe saw palmetto
Because literally
Wait what did you say what did you just say
Minerals for
You
What's great about that is that part of the Enders I'm not advertising it is in the middle of it
99% chance you won't
Get prostate cancer if you take saw palmetto
Wow
Illegal defense whenever they like okay well you said this and he's like no
See
I don't know
I think that's illegal
Anyway
I got to worry about buying okay good because
But you really have to worry about is Kamala Harris
Okay she's actually going to be the president has she's a woman in their far more threatened by women
Especially women of color than they are
The of white man
I think I think that if you really got
Granular with it you got Alex into like a psychiatrist office psychologist office maybe this is something
You could tease out eventually but no on the surface it's because
Is just going to let
Imma Be
Then decide so much and
Clip that Alex plays
Dementia
He talks about stepping down he doesn't do it come out
All kidding aside the first lady to be told me she holds
Yes she does
But not with the cheesecake
The side
It's a matter of
The thing we are simpatico
Our philosophy of government
Sympatico on Highway 10 attached
I don't have any
When we disagree will be just like
Microsoft
Kitchen private she'll say I think we should do A B C or D
And I'll say I don't I like a don't like
I like I told Barack
Especially if I read something where there's a
A fundamental disagreement we have based on
Jamal Prince
We don't have the time
We discussed at length
Coliseum
Speak Polish on intelligence
Disingenuous
Alex
When he was
Was Obama's vice president
They had sorta private disagreement over
Minor issues
And if there was a
Substantial thing
Becky Wood
Gracefully bow out that wouldn't cause
Psychological damage to the cont
That is not saying that if he disagrees with
Kamala Harris
Substantial issues
He'll fake
Moon in Terraria then she'll become president when I was vice president
Yeah
And I didn't have any Act
She will say over what the final
Decision wise
I would give my input and if I've found the final decision unacceptable
I would not throw a tantrum I would be like
I can't do this yet I'm no longer Vice
I find that to be in
Incredibly mature
Position
That like yeah
You know
What is being
Discuss their
If you want to apply it to the present
It would be
Harris will step down if there is a fundamental disagreement between the
That's pretty much what he said yes
If we were is
Because he wasn't president before
Story is based on
When he was president
What a dick
Yep speaking Addicks
Somebody who's a real pile of s***
Can't stand his voice is so annoying
God Tom pepper
National file is bad
And he's he's bitching this
Conspiracy weary
This woman and her daughter in Georgia
We're like
You know that they switched ballots
Some stuff
I like he's going to f*** around and get
But like in a Freaky Friday situation that it was like a magical evening and they touch
In front of a
I don't care about what's going on they have not presented evidence that rises to any level of
Suspicion is that it is just like
I want you to play this clip because these dudes are trying to get
UCF
People in the video and everybody's wondering who the heck
Ruby Freeman and her
Daughter
Supervisor while she works on the election she talks about people complaining because
Because her supervisor is getting
Instructions that do
She says well that's just how it is
Supervisor well Alex her daughter happens to have
Blond dreadlocks that in a Greenie secure
Braids her daughter is the woman who
The suitcases
And then
Once everybody was gone because of the leak
Night
People to count
This is an elaborate
Conspiracy McGee is directly accusing people of
Anti name I think that if they these two people this mother and daughter
Feel so inclined
I think they should probably sutapa portray showcases outrageous 100% because the consequences
Probably take a lot of time at Avion necessarily
Difficult
And a pain in the ass
But
The potential consequences of the actions that people like Alex
And Tom are doing right here
Are so severe that they deserve
Got some sort of a contact
Parts for it
I just can't believe they would do this
This kind of
Two people I can
Yeah I guess like
I mean
They just have such
Bloodlust
They just really do
Like I literally like
Not only are we saying this person
Persons named hoping they
Get deathreats
This is
This is what we want
You know and it's just self
Yep
Stop stranger over there who I'm going to
Exploit and maybe get killed
Tom is on
In a lot of ways
Basically convinced
The Trump is going to win these cases
Saying that he's going to become
The really what I should have said
But also the legislators are starting to move in the right direction
These people Alex these are the modern
These legislators and legislatures are the new founding fathers of the new country that's going to be under
Legislators have also been an agreement with the whole lock.
Call B.
Arkansas
Hear this one
We're going to go back
Exit Aaron down there home
But for now
We need
Yeah and then will f*** you up
Yeah
I mean there is no loyalty there's no consist
It's never
More clearly and body then when they start talking about
Attorney General William Barr
Someone who was not to be trusted at the beginning because he was associated with the book
And then
Started to get real creepy and super like accommodating of some of Trumps
Biatch
Cuz he's a hero and then he I became a hero he's out he's one of the good guys
And then you got a pack of the little bits
Some stuff that Alex didn't like I always knew he was a monster
Yeah and then he said so
Really really f***** up stuff
And so now he's a villain
What's a reserve Army
Total desperation that was there
Emergency
That's exactly right
Barr's father hired Jeffrey Epstein
Significant
Pipes I love him
It's morning radio
Noxious
Terrible
Cuz that is something that you
You literally said that to me last week like
I wonder how long it's going to take for him to take from to remember the Epstein stuff
Headlines Barber said there wasn't evidence of widespread voter fraud
I texted you well looks like Alex Becker remember that bars of Feeling Again
Yep so sad predict
Polish it
So it is makes clip Tom
Has broken the case
On what's going on
Voting
Pinky Thomas broken
I think he does
Know-how voting
I agree
And I have a potential idea of how this may have happened after examining
Yesterday
Using homeless shelters
Downtown Atlanta
Stronghold fusions
Nursing home
Uber allowed to vote
Wait in
2000 people you can't just walk into a homeless shelter and say I'm here
Ridiculous
General legal things that you can do
Does he think of it people experiencing homelessness
They don't get to vote cuz they don't have a permanent address
They don't own property only property holding white men are allowed to vote Dan didn't you know that you think that people in residential care
Vote like Alexander home
You know those people have a right to vote since when
Always
Oh
Be quiet
I mean obviously
I think it's a little transparent
It's a little bit like remarkable the lack of grass put on any kind of Civic
I'd like to
Obviously
Those people vote
The girls
That is exactly how they think
Yep Tom believes
Alex has a big big piece of news
About
Social media
I was getting back on
No
There's another one
Story
But I haven't.
I really really need to get to it
Deals with
Level
Now here
Censorship
And it deals with YouTube
Preston videos
White males
Let them trim
Wow indeed I would imagine if they came out and said that there would be a large outcry
So since he's saying that they did say that and I haven't heard about it I suppose they're suppressing the news upstairs depression
Cuz dead serious
Someone has white
Scan and Ismail
That the position just because you're white
Quote Martin Luther King
Do it
Ifucking dare you
She says we will suppress white male
What is that
Racial division
I found the article about this on Infowars and it's just about YouTube responding to their creators who have noted that there seems to be a
Tobias and the algorithmic boosting the videos and channels are white
Creators
In response
They ask creators to voluntarily provide information about their identity
Which could be used to help better
Crack and see if there is an actual underlying bias and they're algorithm that they
You can find a way to mitigate
It stands now there's really no way for them to test that
Because they have no data on the identities of the
The Creator's so this would be a way that they could try to solve that problem that their users have request
Did they look into
Alex is making up all the
Details of the story including that quote about not letting white males Tran
Who's all just him trying to scare his audience
Spared super into white identity fear
Hey YouTube
Walter white dudes
Look into it
So
I just find this
Tubi
It's not
White man
Really going hard now but they're so desperate with their b******* it's
Real pathetic
The problem that I have is that like this is so easy to understand what the actual story is that on YouTube
Side
Do things and like Alex
Seems like you should have bigger issues right now like
There's this whole election
Frog thing there's the vaccines in the covid and all this
Do you really need to try and Stoke White
Beer out of the end and the answer is yes
Yeah because that's his bread and butter
That's something that's so important
Keeping the audience
Cengage
Interested
It is it is interesting that you
Hammer one-story
Like you know you can hit
But with white identity stuff you've always got to provide more and more new examples each time otherwise people look like
Wow that's the only reason they're that's the only thing they're pressing
White man about
You have to make up some
New boats
All the time
And just misrepresent all sorts
So Alex doesn't want to kill
People although you said that he's killed people a bunch of
Yeah
I don't want
Just start going around killing p
Everybody something
We have a duty to not put up
Dash
Say what
You may think
American problem
Wait what
He's talking about the vaccine because he thinks
The depopulation
So you're the one who go around and kill people but like they're going to
Maxine
How much like Joe Rogan
Explaining bedtime to his child
To go to
Globalist and say Hey look
I know you think there are too many
How about don't kill them
I guess
In this example Alex is going to kill his kid if he doesn't go to bed
Walk around killing children who don't do what he says yeah I'll become a legend of folklore the guy who kills you if you don't go to
You'll be used to terrify children for Generations
So Alex
Is Guyana
You know there's some talk from these Addie's ex-president
Sure about how they're going to take that vaccine on TV which I think
It's stupid I think it's
Perfunctory to do
Of course has a bottle all ready to go
You believe
They're going to take
But they're not just going to sterilize
Obviously it's going to be if they do get it that'll be that's not really the vaccines is a cat
Placebo
Maxine
Are we doing it's not the real
Part of me even believes you get some sort of super-rich guy vaccine
You guys
I think
That
Not doing that
Is
Wrong because there is something about the
The communal
Experiencing like
Seeing these people
Partake in something
Very basically all it is it is it is there something unifying to
High-profile people
Being like I'm getting a shot toots
The same way that like if you were
Did your parent might get a shot totally fine
We're heading over the Iraq
I think there's something healthy when our leader is
Do that
It so I'm not a I'm not opposed to it but pretending that it has any impact on
People who are
Say I don't think Road
The people who hate this
Three of you the most
Going to be like well if they're getting the vaccine that I totally believe it
Yeah Jesus
So Alex went to a protest
For this evening of the
The third against
Governor Abbott or something
Maybe the mayor
The mayor
But Alex admits to assaulting someone
Last night
Blur
Private jet
I was yelling at me
Topsface a little
Emotional
I probably shouldn't have assaulted him but he was taunting
And I probably shouldn't have threatened his life
Hi removing
You're the person who Alex pulled on his mask feel free to sue him
He has admitted on-air that he assaulted you
You could face open-and-shut case
Snakes clip Alex
Confesses to something else
And that is that he is very stupid
The big old islamophobe
Police patrolling Pub
Scott
Eggs
Flavoring whiskey
Resting area
Run sex reindeer kids
Weather
So
Escalated
From
Local cuisine
They're not whiskey eggs
Now he clearly doesn't it's an egg wrap
Chicken sausage and then covered in breadcrumbs
Like I immediately went that's not
Scotch egg
Did I not know there was with enough what's going on here is that in an area of the UK where this
Restaurant in question was located
The government has put in place rules that bars can't serve alcohol unless
It's part of them operating
As a restaurant
Go to bed
That is to say that bars and pubs without food or not allowed to be open
There was a screenshot of a receipt from a London restaurant called The Refinery New Street
Sciotoville 463 Peyronie's
12 glasses of Prosecco in one scotch egg
This was being circulated to imply that this is how they're going to get around the covid-19
In reality the receipt is crop
To make it appear that the group only ordered one
It also ordered a ton more food according to the restaurant
This is just a social media meme it's such b*******
None of the stuff that Alex is reporting on here is real he's just misunderstanding a headline of a story that he hasn't read
Making up what he thinks Scotch eggs are
And using it to throw around 2
Completely unnecessary islamophobia
This is what he does as a career
He's an idiot who refuses to do any preparation for any work
I just spread hate all over the place
Cuz he said it's all you can do
Useless
Social media's
Devil we should
Just get rid of it we should only live in communities of 150 or less
Everybody owns their own business
I've remade the entire global economy I saw this picture of the receipt and I thought like God
That's fun it's very obviously like crap
Total or anything the receipt is cut off right under the
That's fun
Cuz I got a lot of booze
Yeah I don't I don't know I would say I was
You try a little harder
The internet
Cheaper
Send a text with Alex
Claims that he's known what's going to happen
All this stuff that's happening around us
He's known at all to attend years like
Totally consistent on all of this
Martial law forced inoculation
How did Joan snowing
They said they do it
Operation lockstep
Didn't exist 10 years ago
Romeo and Juliet commit suicide
Kill you
Operation lockstep isn't a real thing Alex didn't know about it all
Nothing is such horseshit
Like
Right before the twin
16 election Alex wasn't making his audience scared but I'd like a virus that was going to bring in martial law and track
King in all this
Obama was going to declare himself
The king of a Muslim Nation
It was that it was that it was none of this
Stevi B's said he was waiting for the government collapsed so it could make everybody Dukes
Do do do do
Play this car
You don't get to pretend that
It's interesting from the rubble of a nuclear explosion in Chicago
According to Alex's prediction
That's kind of what I was
Yeah if he's been right about everything
This is the shell game that you get to play when you're someone like Alex and your audience
Just decided to give up much like you you don't have to click do you want to play
To give up and believe you're. Browbeaten to the point of life
Oh yeah he has always been saying that they'd use a virus to bring in world government
No he hasn't if I believe they should the s*** he saying about
Now why wouldn't I believe him when he says
Now
That he said it earlier
Right
This actually gets to one of the reasons why I'm even
If I were Joe Rogan
I would just be personally offended by the way Alex is treated me
Just as a matter of like sulfur
Respect I wouldn't
Hang out with him
If you want to take a step farther into scuss like what the real issues are
When Alex was on Rogan
Podcast last
Was Tim Dillon
When they had that episode
And Alex was
One step away from being a
Exposed as having made up
Operation lockstep they drop the ball there
And again like I said not their fault they didn't know whatever was
But
Because they didn't
That means Alex winds that point
Because of that because
Alex didn't get exposed in front of millions of people as having made up
This Rockefeller planned that now he's claiming he's known about for 10 years
He gets to play games like this
And you have done
At least
By virtue of
Your inability to stand up to the claim
You
Help solidify
You've helped
Reinforce and make it look like
And
Defect
Like here's what I'm more offended by
What's up
Rogan had every opportunity
After
That podcast
Define shop
If Alex was full of s*** and blind to him
And clearly
He didn't
Because you did
Yeah it would it would suggest he didn't really follow up on
But such a big
Obvious one Deluxe that thing is
So f****** obvious if you know what he's talking about
It's just disgraceful and
Like like I said
Personal level
Alex is treated
Rogan as a as a person is
Is disgraceful and no one
You should put up with that
But
Societally does it does damage
Not being
Competent
At pushing back against Alex's narrative
Only serves to sell your audience
It does seem like with propaganda in
Those kind of Outlaw
There is
One chance to win
Or you lose
Like once you see ground on that
It's gone
It never comes back
And if you win
You don't gain the ground
You just don't lose it
And it's brutal
Yeah if you put
Yourself in that situation you got under
Understand that as the suffix
Hi especially if you got millions of listeners ever
It's why if you're somebody who has a platform
And you bring somebody on who's
Maybe a bad actor
You have really high
Levels of responsibility
Target if you're somebody who has a show you can bring on someone like Richard
Spencer Milo yiannopoulos have a great responsibility
To not allow them
To frame everything
Matt is
Your job
And in the challenge is such that you can
Cannot
Half acid
Unfortunate naivete or whatever I don't believe that
Any more place
But like
He's just having a conversation with friend
Or whatever least that's what he wants to
Present
Because of that
You do never going to be in a position
And that's why he can't have people at opolis on anymore
You can't have those Gaston anymore because
It's to you
Can't do that can't do it
It somehow Alex is still fine
But I don't know how
I don't even know what we're doing
So anyway we have one last clip here and Alex has a Gaston named Jennifer flag
And she claimed that she had footage
Major something of
Voter fraud in Austin
Sharaya because of course
Deep blue areas are only deep blue because the Democrats are stealing all the vote whatever
That's right so she's on
And I found this really weird because she was like she was running
For some office at NAS lost in the GOP Primary
Then became a poll Watcher sure that's good
Got into some kind of a dust-up cuz she had like recording equipment and you're not allowed to have that
Macy Gray
Okay I don't care really don't care about any of it
Like her voter fraud stories
Cuz they're saying that I don't see any evidence of this so many people in politics
Text you wouldn't be allowed in a
Bars have
She wouldn't go to a bar because she's very into God and going to church and all that they read that on her ballot
DDR qna
Anyway
I don't care about
Their interview at all but I would just like to Denver
Straight what sort of people the two of them are as they get into some real ableist
Shitheadra Joker
Remember reading the governor's
Negative order the summer
And neither were like
Directions to businesses closing
Are are the exceptions and I remember one of them was that
He closed all the raft
Businesses
Like you couldn't like to ear rafting businesses couldn't stay open
And I thought
How bizarre that he would attack
A small business in Pak
Taxes and let all these other
I'm sorry the handicapped
Can't go rushing
No it's because float trip
We're spreading
A lot of
Cases of covid-19 that float trips
Blue trip to spread over
Float trips in in raft
Some stuff like that are just like
20 year olds
Drunk as f***
In big groups
Barges going down the river like it
Obviously yeah
It seems if you've never been on a float
Triple for probably might be like
Advocate
I can see a someone who's been on a lot of float trips
I can see why
Why someone would cause a rash
That's f****** shity
The way they're acting and being like yeah he's
He's going to
You just mad that he can't go rafting
F*** you Alex
You love Greg Abbott until he didn't do what you wanted him to do now
Situation here no
Attack him
For his disability
Status go f*** yourself yep
What up what up
Piece of s***
Anytime you are talking about somebody and then you use
And then a descriptor that is not
Then you
It's like it's like that whenever you know when you're listening to
That that
Andy Daly and Paul at Southgate
Kansas where he was as l.ron Hubbard
Every time you heard him say like
A Japanese you're like
Yeah
Netsertive linguistic
Framing is pissed is terrible
And I want to say
Everybody who Alex
Likes now
Look at how he's treating people who have behaved in ways that are just slightly outside of what he wants them
Them to do
Look at this
He loved Greg Abbott
One of the best still Governor's Inn
Country probably
Real great Governor we love him
Now he's
Being able
Best against mezz attacking him only for like him not being extreme enough but on these really shity
Personal grounds that are bigoted and horrible
Rogan
When he's doing what he wants him to do Alex be like he's so brave he's braver than Tucker Carlson correct when he doesn't
He'll bring up
Your kids and things going to distract you
Cut you in half
Bleed you like a
Consider this
This is how Alex operates
Yeah
I mean
So the thing is he dissing this form of unreality that has to be total
You can't allow a single real thing to come into the unreality Bubba
Yeah otherwise
The whole thing birth
So just like if you're senior got you know
Bar is doing something different while now
I can't allow that into the Bubba
You know
Well it's
It's the new one
But you introduced
When you're like taco bar if you
He's kind of s*** head I wanted
Why would he not
Do this thing that I think
He should
You can't you can't relate
Well I'm the end not just that but you painted the Democrats as
Totelcom
Pleat Eva
So any agreement with the Democrats
Means you're evil
You have to be
Otherwise that introduces the possibility that
Not all Democrats are
Everything falls apart
It's done
I will say that Alex also played a lot of the trumps
Speech
Joyce 49-minute video
Yahoo
Shorebreak
I know I don't have a lot of clips of it because Alex didn't editorialize on it all that much
Exactly like
And I want to make a point of this like as we close the episode that like that was on his show
And it's scary as hell but
Because trumpet sounds like
It's f****** terrifying
.
I don't know what else to say about it
I hope
You know it's it's so weird to talk
To my family now because
It's like
Before
In the old times you know they could be like we're just mainstream Republicans we do talk about that Alex Jones stuff and it's like
Like now
You voted for Trump
This is what he saying you're in my world and you're wrong
That's it
So if you want to and you can't argue with me
That's over
Viet
You believe
Vicious
Yeah
Really bummed me out
I guess
Agus bum me out but it felt really weird is like
I always
Because I listen to so much Alex
When when people would say like Trump sounds like Alex Jones some slight differences
That's not really what Alex is talking point
You thinking
Yeah now it do you listen to the tapes
Stuff that I was like
Holyshit
Exactly the same as I might as well like Playa
That 92nd
Can clip and be like her name is this
It's
I wouldn't be surprised if he starts doing that soon
Crazy
Thank you Jeff
You take the support you got and when
It's looking real bad like it is
Yeah
What you got is
Alex and Tom pepper
Good luck I just keep
But I'd like the thing that I
Keep thinking is just like
Be wary
Because when these lawsuits and stuff
He's deaf
That's pretty now that when the lawsuits and stuff stop
Does anybody really believe he's going to be like well
Guess I lost
You know when the lawsuits are done yeah he's got to do some
I think he
Motorsport
Do you think he might
Just give up
Well who you made a bunch of money that's true
But he's never met he doesn't make
None of these guys ever make
I don't know another thirty billion dollars is everybody dies around
He doesn't need it right I don't know I don't know in like
Wargaming what we imagine he's going to
To-do list
I found it
This is useless
Use of my time
He's always
Why's I think being worried I've a lot of people are just thinking it's going to go away and I'm just saying be weary head on a swivel
Look around
Keep an eye out
This is not the 70-79 days of hell but it is the 79 days of
Where are you
Easy
Careful careful
So we'll see what happens
And maybe maybe we'll do that Rogan episode
Sooner than later
It is a 4-Hour
Like mystery box today I did only make it through the first bit if it could be amazing
I want it gets rolling or it could be
Be
Continuing of that
Walking through f****** knee-deep mud it has to be a disaster
Something
To like think your teeth
Send to because
That just
Is you
Etsy one thing I like about smoking week yet
Joe
It's good
Great guy
Come on now
So we will be back but until then
We do have a website
A local charity or bail Fund in your area to help out
Until then I'm Mio and Leo and bcx Barkan Daryl rundus I didn't bring this up earlier but I
I think it's really funny
That at the time that we started recording this episode I don't know if Rudy Giuliani actually has covid-19
The headline is just
The Trump said
Sohu
Anyway that's
Pretty pretty
I don't know it's not a good place to
To be as a society
Alexandra first in color with huge fan I love your work