Alexandra Thurston color
We're couple dudes like to sit around
Drake dolls
And have a talk about Alex Jones
Twisted this
One that
Frankly either
Cannot be
Play Down
No I mean it is
Blueberry and watermelon
That's not the
Is the twist taking the cap off
What's up
There we go we got one
Crystal Crystal Light
This show is that I know a lot about
Today we're going to be going over basically the first hour
Of the Tuesday June 6th
Episode
This comes up this will be yesterday's show
But to get us going I'd like to play a out-of-context drop that's very funny
Alex Jones from 2015
I'm up here
Everyday
Commission
Pretty good in hindsight
God dammit
It has been a
Absolutely unending shitshow of a day even better I'd like to give a shout out
Later what's up Keegan
Thank you for joining us
If you would like to become a
You may do so by going to our website
It's a good one
Jordans
I don't want to do the show anymore
Okay fair enough
Alex Jones
Has been bumming me out
I am in
The doldrums
My enthusiasm to listen to this dumbass Manuel
Is Ben Wayne
And I don't know either
I'm in I'm in a bad place
Well you you're at the what
6 full months
Non-Stop
The kind of psychic
It's rough
I think we might be done
I think this is over
Really
Well maybe
Just need something to rejuvenate
Could be something
I don't know
Alright I'm back
I was actually genuinely a little bit concerned there we've had some
Spring this on me elaborate setup to play Sasha Banks theme song again
You nailed it
You are
Streamsong
You kidding me that's what I'm going to play right about now
What stocks is like Hulk Hogan had a whole album and that's not even the best song on it
There's a song called hulkster goes to heaven
Have you heard that song
And right there it's about that's all just little little little kid with a big Hulk Hogan
And it's Hulk Hogan singing about have you heard that he died
And of the two of them
Fill tag up when you get when the hulkster goes to heaven
Wait what
Oh yeah
No
I think you got to hear it
Also wanted
It's it's basically just Tears in Heaven
Oh no
Stratford and Jordan
Oh yeah
What are Russell is when believe
Google how desperately I don't want to talk about us
So there's a little kid
Okay
Let's get to the actual show
The reason I don't want to talk about
Come to a little bit of a
I'm getting to the point where we can poke holes in and bring reality to
Any
Bulshit that he spins
And it doesn't matter
It doesn't matter in the air
Kind of hate to quote Linkin Park
You got a terrible music in my face already
My self-care
Dealing with listen
Coerced
Futility
It's delusional of me to think of it
Reality would puncture
The bubbles
Of propaganda but
Anyway
Further I'd like
In the end
Nothing
If true
We are all specks of dust
Floating through space
There is no God and we are left
To find meaning
Betwixt our own
Ears
Look up a mortal coil
Wilshire
Will Shakespeare Shakespeare
AR on the show
We're covering this.
And something interesting happened on the
By the time that Alex is on air
And that is
The Megyn Kelly is in
Megyn Kelly is a at Alex Jones's po
Interview
Interview with Megyn Kelly
References
This is the day she has just interviewed
Right and apparently as I was
Who is Trump
Alex Jones thinks it's great
But he's in that company
Not realizing a certain thread there is something connecting them
Some sort of line segments is a reason that Megyn Kelly's first three interviews and it might
Be a series on what went wrong with our country
Alex Jones
He's a big strong manly man kicked out the globalist
Donald Trump
In charge of the New Renaissance or whatever the f****** says
So I'm the part of it realizing that note
Parker playing
You're echoing an amplify Russian propaganda enable Trump
You are
The shittiest
Yet your shampoo
Yeah exactly
In this episode
Megyn Kelly isn't there yet
But
Her team is there
Her crew is in the Infowars to DIY
And stuff like that so they're recording him too
It really
Really proves some of the strfkr equality's and sell out dumbass qualities we just
Turn it up or turn it down his ass off
This was going to be a little bit different
Because I couldn't really cut clips
I just have a bunch of ramp
He just goes
He is the spirit is in him
Showing off
Spur Megyn Kelly's crew
The entire time
It is f****** banana
I had to turn it off
A little bit
The first hour was over
And I'll explain why when we get the
But for now let's get going
I into this
The first clip that we have
On this year episode
Is
Our first clip is a shorter clip
I just
Kick it off before we get into the massive rain
This one is just a bad comparison about mainstream media
Because it has nothing to do with azlam
And if you stay as long as anybody with Jihad
Obamacare is going to be free
Business
And Hillary Clinton doesn't look like a cross between a lot lizard
And some type of pizza
What's up
Alright alright people take the terrorism has nothing to do with his wife
So people who say
Hillary Clinton
Does not look like a mix between a lot lizard and a
Overcooked nevermind
Point of order
I don't know
The reason that I kept is because Alex has this fundamental misunderstanding
About what people are saying when they say that
The terrorism
Terrorism to go on aren't really about Islam
They're about
More political state
You like that
Islam
When they say that this doesn't have to do with his life he doesn't understand
He thinks that people are saying
These are
Muslim people
Or something like that
I think that's what he believed but in his
Hey if you see your fake news
The same people who said you didn't build your business
Again we got over 100 second time
Free now there's discussions
Credits would be available tax subsidies
That would offset a lot of it
F****** nonce
Right
Does Hillary Clinton
Look like a mick
Between a lot lizard and a
Overcooked
I don't know that's the one
That's the one that confused me quite a bit
They're making that Mick
Timera if you will
I don't know what do you think
Otherwise that's
We're not going to be
I don't know I think
If I had to guess I would say he's started a metaphor and started a mick
Comparison
I meant he just lost it
Tricked out pizza
We hungry
Something along those lines
But
Who cares
That's a short clip
Now let's get into the real business
This address Nextbook starts with him explaining the Hillary is guilty
He's guilty
Guilty of overcooked
That is a crime
In many Italians
She's guilty
And
This clip
Transition smoothly
Into Alex Jones airing some of his grievances about Megyn Kelly
Guilty
Children Kelly on Fox News
Hillary murdering children
Conversation was
Alright I don't remember I don't remember that
Accrue
Whatever
What did you say about your parents
A producer
Really upset
Harborfreight.com
Mr. Castillo Ashley
Gross
Add dry throat
He's really really hung up
Still on this thing for Megyn Kelly's show that had to do with
Pizzagate
In fairness to him they did cut the clip of it but in fast as we have played in the past
Go fuc yourself
Infamous 2
Megyn Kelly and her producer
We was
Talking about pizza
Hillary Clinton is personally responsible for killing and raping children
He was talking about
In the world
Not in-depth really in the basement
But they were only Guilty by omission
What thousands of children at the
So much worse
Pretended to care about war crimes
Doesn't matter
Situation
Developing
Qatar right now
I'd like really makes me worried that
My fears about a Ron
Are coming true
They think there's evidence of Russia
Lies about the relationship between out who knows
Sitting in the f****** streets right now
Go to work in the morning and I'm just sitting there looking
People going like
Do not realize the world is falling apart around
Yeah I'll have my boss come up to me and be like what's going on with this account there a little overdue I like
Do not understand I have to listen to Alex Jones we can fight back a little bit
So Alex Jones
All that all that stuff aside
Right you got other issues.
Remind
Still want to talk a little bit more about Hillary Clinton
That we're going to editorialize a little bit on here
I was going to talk about it believe any of them
Usable in the same
Alex
Might have been a little bit too late there
Jacuzzi
Is this week
So Alex is going to talk a little bit about this article then he's going to play the audio of Hillary Clinton
What's audio the article
If they're really getting into the subs
Extensive what she
She said also I'd like to apologize you may have noticed already the audio of these clips is a little bit bad
I cut the clips from
I don't know what happened
There's that f***** up audio.
Sorry about that
Talking about this
Wicked Witch Wizard of Oz
Disappearing into cloud
She's imaginary
Infowars.com
Also just thinking like with our investigation back to 2015 when he talked about Trump's mob ties
We don't use Consortium is a word anymore really makes me remember what you said about Trump
Anyway there's an article on Infowars
Joseph
Way to stop terrorism is to understand other cultures
Yes
For us to reach out to the world
To understand more about
What is happening
In our own country
It's a time for steady
Determined leadership
Like we are sick
How important our alliances
You heard from Victor
You heard from Maya
You heard from a congressman
Learning experiences the cultures the religions
Islam
Even goes into a rant about how bad it would be if you move to Somalia
I got that part because it's
But just like
Make some good points
And also talks about understanding others
Peoples cultures their religion
Recognizing how important are all these sorts of things
Those are all really good points but he just cut it off after the party
You know what's even crazier about that
The food is something that actually is very good at bringing cultures together
Not just that but
Down the block netop address
That's where he was invented
I know they got good baby I'm going to learn more about it
Ethiopians
Steve
Something so similar in their lives
Asthma
Something that is just very basic
Create these things
In order to f******
Feed ourselves
No good reason
Regency
Goddamn f****** berries on the ground
They make food the same
It with the same ritual with
Is something
With value
You are in the same way treating their culture with value
Hahaha
Ethiopia bad
So there we go
We just did a sketch of exactly what like
A good point and then
Rank dismissal
With nothing really behind it I mean like
I do understand the idea of being afraid
Of
Terrorism
I get it
I just don't think
Get Smart
I think it's dumb
I think it's cowardly
I think
When you have terrorist attack there been
Numerous clips
That have been flying around people
Bring like people in London
I don't
Karam going to keep doing this
Things I've been doing I don't
The response
You should have
Terrorists want to scare you
And if you are scared
And you turn things into a holy war
You're being an idiot you're playing into their game
Most likely
Prime minister of
F****** Britain
Today that
If
Human rights laws get in the way of protecting
People were going to get rid of those
Human rights laws like
Text Wheaton
Did not should have learned our lesson with all the subsequent things
Go to help
Fake news
I don't know I mean it's just a macrocosm of the idea that Rehabilitation is almost
Always
More effective and cheaper than incarceration
Absolute people
Sociopathic
Serial killer witch
F******
What are you going to do
Like serial rapist serial killers like all of these guys
Something that you can't
Rehabilitate
It's not that doesn't
No
But if you are if you are somebody who
You can invite any number of dip like
How many times has the FBI
Blatantly committed in
They wanted to get somebody
To do something like most terrorism
Chris on the terrorist front by creating terrorists and then getting
Yeah it is
Dumb islamophobic
But again I really want to stress
Performing for Megyn Kelly
True
Who's there
It's clear you want some of this to go in
The interview
Go to
He's hitting a lot of his base points
Could you think maybe this will go out on NBC
Right it's not going to go out
Alex
Baby
No but I also think he might be trying to bait them into taking something he says out of context
I think I think there's a certain part of him that was preparing his eye
I'm going to take an hour on this interview
There's no way I'm coming out looking
I'm good right things intentionally over-the-top so later I can argue
Try to make me look like a lunatic
By only using these crazy things I said
I think that might be a game plan
In much the same way
We should f****** address this cuz this makes
Furious
This is part of why I feel like all hope
Lost
So on our wives episode
We talked about Paul Joseph Watson
Announcing
Kids books
Hope you guys
That was before he had come out
And said
Haha I tricked you I don't eat book
And you guys report
Alright well
Feed him
And shove paper in his mouth
Here's the thing
Respond
What's was
We don't care
We haven't passed feelings towards even
Wanted person
For his mental health issue
That was our response
And I don't take that back even though he was lying
100-percent
But here's the thing
She was
He said
Haha
You guys reported this your fake news
The thing that's important
Is
They reported that
Because he told them
Yes
You just reported it without looking into it
YouTube
And what other things can you look into the initial article about it
Said
Infowars is known for lying to get attention
To think even in their initial articles that this might not be true cuz right around with diesel and then his
Response to them
How dare you make fun of my mental illness
Took that
Pretended although I a witch is insulting to people with legitimate mental illnesses absolutely
Chocolate up to another score on the go f*** yourself and Paul Joseph Watson
Not six months ago Paul Joseph Watson reported an article on Infowars
About how they were taped
Trump saying the n word
During The Apprentice taping
That were about to be released
You reported this
Based on a guy
Who made a troll Twitter account
Private messaging him
Sleeping
To be someone who worked high-level and television
Took Twitter
Messages with nope
And reported on it
A worse version
Of what he's accusing people of doing now
Chuckanut
He's so f****** snarky and glib
And you have an echo chamber that will just be like
Yeah you got them
F*** it you took it to the fake news
Msmu suck
That cycle is Unbreakable
It's just there's nothing we can do it's infuriating
Mind-bogglingly
Stupid though
Did we lose
I genuinely want now
Russia completely stole the elect
At least I would feel like
Well we
We lost to a weird evil billionaire superville
Part of it part of it the instead of the dumbest people on them
F****** planet
What are the things I'm starting to realize is that one of the most important pieces I think
To Trump winning and to Alex Jones
Conversion into what he is
Is the
Tuna people like Mike's
And rebel media
These prankster a****** troll alright
People that could they are the ones
Brought this influence
Publicity stunt
Trolling the media
Cernovich
Dimensional
Journalism
Become the story I think is really
What is almost
Impossible to deal with
Because
Most humans
Really have the instinct to give people the benefit of the doubt
Assume the people aren't lying
And they're all like
Pools
Everything is fake news
Countries
Whenever
This is the thing that I think people should
Is
Bannon even said it
The real goal is the destruction of all of our
Zip
That is what they're doing it is not
It is not like
Anything they're doing
Is in service
To any other ideology
Then burn it all down
And we're heading in
Into what needs to be the next
Destruction in order to rebuild
Other than a white nationalist debate is what
F******
Stated objective
Even Trump is it like that
Like
Takeaway
The we should kill terrorists
Killing
Family
Because he thinks that that kind of scorched-earth b******* is the way to go
Right
Endless
F****** Wars that
Cannot
Ever
Yeah
We're living in the Hatfields and The McCoys
Like that's what's going on
I don't I don't have anywhere left to go it's just bad it's all just so bad
Anyway let's get to the dumb islamophobic rant
President-trump
Block
Known to be cherish their known
There's a virus
They are pirates those people in
I think the president's wrong
I think we should
Ashley
Somali pirates
Galveston Bay
All cultures
Take me to contacts
Baby government has done
A lot of effort
Towards
Stopping the pirate
And they didn't credibly great job it is just resurgent
Lately
A little bit
But they did a great job knock it out
Someone with a crisis couple years back
Disaster
Popping back up a little bit but it's not nearly as bad as it was back then
Also Alex has this thing about
I think he's going to scream about it a little bit more later about how the caliphate
Imam
Give out Saudi Arabia and passports
Chair and some Yoruba Somalian passports
If it don't
Do passports are regulated by the federal
They have biometric passports
Your authenticity
Everything is on the up-and-up
Worst false credentials in America
You can get them in any
Country
If Alex has taken issue with the fact
Some people have fake passports
Let me bro you got a global problem to deal with their
You really know how to solve
You're just picking and choosing the country is that your boy
You know will again
He's never be
My boy
I'm sorry wait that was 2015 Alex
Apology
There is no wedding is stupid the moms give out passports
Stupid
Somehow every Somali person is a pirate is f******
Stupid but fun
Sure
Ariel weird
It would be more fun world if there was just an entire country of
Pirates
Just just as fun like random as country of like
It's like a magical fantasy world where they somehow have a government we end up living in the Assassin's Creed
Another
Sarcastic
Accept it
Evil concert by the time they collapse
You can look at cultures that are bad and good
The Orthodox Islam that is the
Exploding
Audiology
Is going through its Reformation
This is Islam's Reformation of robbing the Caravan
They're at Mecca
1500 years ago 14 years ago
The slave trade
Coming out of the slave trade
Their Corners there at the crossroads
A caravan
Road
You talk about the Silk Road
Started 14 years ago
Global cyber
The West
So
You want to start slave trade started
1400 years ago
I don't know how modern that is 608
But I pray about it pray about it
Also the Quran saying black people
I mean I don't know if that's
Specifically in there but I do know that it's also in the Mormon bible I know literally of his dad's in the Mormon bible
Don't throw that around Tallahassee
I'm not sure was Joseph Smith 14 years ago
Thank you
100 right
Text Molly passport
Tomorrow
Gameon overused
White people good
Black people bad
Stupid mud people
So
I mean let's also
The picket nice moment to Revel in the
This is the Reformation of Islam
That idea is
Very insulting
Considering
The percentages
That that
So
That's so hateful in fear Bay
Do you not like
Considering
Number of people who are they
Extremist
Within the Muslim
Population
Probably I would say smaller
Then
Anti-abortion activists in the Christian
Community the ratio of
Violent Christian
Is bar higher than
Isaac the baby the violent Muslim terrorists have more theater
Fertility though
Are you there may be better at
Better it's scaring
People
Christian beat up a gay guy
Doesn't really
Granted it's not a beheading
It's up
It's not bigotry it's religious
Freedom Dan
The thing that blew me away is when he's like
They're a bad culture
About
Your friends are nothing
They're f****** nothing
Fully accepted all of evil
Diesel
Step away from heaven
Dispensary
Disclose
Staind
Saying to some extent but he's doing a really bad job of it
The idea of like
Cultural absolutism
I'm in some cultures are good summer
Is really just your way of saying better
But at the same time
Like
Nazi culture is bad or the
The Nazi government
Like it's really a culture
Is a government that
Took power in
Existed for
10 years
15 years
From the beginning of its roots in the National Socialist Party
To the end of World War II
With not a long time
Yasmin
Something like 1932
Had an exploit
Government that took hold
Culture
Right leg that's what happened
Not a culture
That is
People doing that to other people of course in the Aztec culture is being so f****** reductive with it being like
They sacrifice then cut out people's hearts
Awesome pyramids
Had a very interesting culture
And they created
Dial do know that I was the most-watched
Mobile
I know he's be-bopping he's getting around here
But it's just
If you want to use those arguments to prop up your outright hatred and fear of Islam
Boring
I can't imagine him having a conversation with anyone who's not an idiot
Doesn't already
And him being able to pull that
Lucky
Cuz there's no way to win that are
Idiot it is such
Stonewall
It sucks don't look like
Culture like
Like there's so much there
To learn about
Where did
Culture comfy
Why did it
Games
The power that it did
Apply later on in life support Trump
Don't f******
Lickety split
F****** b*******
I'm just talkin about human society
Like it is
Immediately following the Treaty of Versailles
S*** all over the German
For good reason
F****** started a massive global war that murdered
Millions upon millions of people
But do you know who started that war
It wasn't the f****** people who lived in Hut
I'm filled with dumb f*** rich people want to get
Dumbfuckery
The Treaty of Versailles
Didn't really punish those dumb f*** Rich be
F***** over all of the regular people
And the regular people when they've been so f***** over are susceptible to getting
F***** over by the even more authoritarian government that says
Who's going to protect them and
Store them to Greatness
Or or or
Authoritarian governmental entity
Isis is even sort of like
A rogue
The government
Like sporadically play
I'm not even comfortable with him sayings
Islamic culture
First of all is unipolar
That's absurd
But the idea that
Stream
Muslim stuff is even
Culture necessarily
That's
In terms of Muslim
Just look at how it
Is moving how it's
Like
Believe
Either Iran or Saudi Arabia
That is
Exporting
It's
Difference
Ideological beliefs
Universities
Classrooms
Kimberly Pratt
A much more
Moderate kind of Islam where it's kind of it's a lot more like
Assistant
For Christmas and Easter Christian
And now they have
These difference
More
More fundamental
Versions of
Islam Binks
So now you have
Muslim countries indirect
Conflict with
Each other
In their religion
Much like you have all of these
Different sects of Christianity have all of these different
People that are
Constantly
Disagreeing with each other over
Nothing
Yeah it's
It's just all of
Ignore the point
The Christianity has
Similar
Tendencies
Just skip to that's my point
It's just their people
Their people
Indeed
How is it that we still don't get that other people are also people we do
Well what we should do is
Pizza Man
Ethiopian food
I know I'm not into that
I'm cool with other cultures but I do want you to leave your food
I want from there
I'm a bit squeamish
The guy who is is
Picture on the wall at a Thai restaurant
This next clip is this is
Crazy
I think you might have to put the mic down cuz this is
Nuts
A little bit with climate change
No
But he loses the thread really hard
Just aren't true
This is Vista
Showman
This would not be happening
Kelly's crew
This is great
Information Warfare perspective
Global government
It destroyed
This is irrevocable damage to the New World Order
Autocracy
Existed
On Facebook
Probably less dirty plants in China
You're the bad guy
Nope
Do you let in people from third world Islamic hell holes that are all killing each other
Truck country
The government openly certify its and say it's good how about people are being from any country
Compatible
Colt
Orthodox Lobby's form is the biggest oldest most dangerous
On the plane
Rockstar music
Because we know
And the left and the glove was in the Ford Foundation is out there financing and fomenting
Absolute
Admittedly part of geography
That was the
Spirit that was Ito caturn there from the crying liberal
Performance
I think it was a little over-the-top or a drama coach
Just a little bit's a little Hammy
Chilling
He's just missing out who
This is a what was the what was the one where he was
The Devil's Advocate Devil's Advocate
People who fought
Psoriasis shouldn't be allowed in our country I think we have
Extreme
Procedures already in place with the intelligence agencies
I agree
You fought for Isis
And we breathe
Travel ban
Also I also I agree with him on the idea that terrorism should not be used to take away
Are Liberties and stuff like that
I grew them in principle but I still disagree with him because of how he presented
This beginning is so f****** stupid
Because
The Paris agreement
Was non-binding
Nobody
How can you have
From the USS not a thing
It's not even the UN it's all the country it's the same thing as a gender
The 21 being a non-binding un
Suggestion
About environmentalism this is just another one
It's just
What what it really does when we pull out of it is a f*** you two worlds
Collaboration on a project
Come out almost unilaterally instead
No f*** you were going to do a lot of cities
And states in America have as well of course because you know how we where we live
Here's a couple of the most important point
Alex Jones
He has his career built up on this
Really poorly
And I don't know if it's intentional or not
But really poorly repackaged
Write in order for him to
To keep supporting Trump and make it seem like things are going well with their not
Everything is going real bad
Can we get
Cops
Keep his phone away and then later
I don't care I think I take the wheels are starting to fall off in the next month
Is going to be crazy
To keep up this charade that everything is going well he has to create benchmark
And they have to fit into his narrative
So they have to be
TPP
Was
Not a trade agreement
It was Global government
So because
Trump
Is a badminton
And he got out of that
That has to be the victory
Destroying Global government
Righttime because
Trump
Is a f****** climate-change denier in it
Idiot doesn't understand science at all
He got out of the Paris agreement
Oh there were carbon taxes
This is how the globalist going to fund themselves
Trump has destroyed them
When in reality
None of that is true
It's either that or he
That is handshake
By the French
A little pissy
Speculation about that
It's B. It says working it's a solid working.
Turn the middle of something interesting
It hadn't occurred to me in the way that
The
He's creating
Benchmark
Yeah that didn't the way that you put that didn't
Click for me before but yeah
He's creating goals
That have already been met
Yeah so that was not it was not a goal
No get out of the
50 PP or to leave
The Paris Accord rated
So now it becomes the goal
Groundwork beforehand
I do believe that
Sincerely
He has a rich history of that
Is that does fit
PVP in a lot of its
It with a lot of things
Forwarded principle but it is there were problematic aspect of it
McDonald time to litigate that right now
It's
There are they are things that he would be again
Don't get me wrong
Before
Trump ended up
Getting out of the Paris
Scream it by saying
Carpenter
These artificial imaginary victories over
Were the imaginary
They keep his audience
Rodney King
We're really making progress again
So
That's
The progress
Before I say I got the
The victory
Celebrate
It didn't
Occurred to me that
It was actually a
A measure of like
Hey we are
Taking it down step by
Yeah
Like this is
This is something that is
Turning East
Turn into a chain of
And this one takes down there this part
And this one takes down this part
And we're chipping away at the globalist
Well never never getting in
To any of the details
Cuz if you do it erodes the entire facade
Like the idea that
Carbon tax
Hey if you if you started to try and prove that
It would just fall apart
Can't like
You just stroke out
My brain won't
Except something this
I mean
The things that he says whatever you talk about how great Trump is doing are those things
And then
Bringing back prosperity
Bring up bring back small business numbers is it
If you look at them they aren't actually
Necessarily indicative
Anything from
Is a well Trump has
I'm done anything other than
He said we're going to
Girl closing cuz of course they are
All the jobs in
Yeah or not it's going to happen that's an argument that a lot of people have made the
That is being really not address by Alex's there
By pulling out of the
The climate agreement Paris agreement
We are basically giving all these other countries mostly China
Cute Head Start
Terms of being able to create these
These Innovative technology
That will be billion dollar mark
In the future and will create
How was job
Durian
Do you have to speak on that language
Yeah
I understand that
Do people who distrust science
Angle on front of them
It's so in
Infuriate
Of the fall of Nazi Germany
Whenever we're bringing all their scientists over and Ron Brown
Hey guys
Come over here will give you Asylum
That's how bad
Guys
We will print
Text you is trying to lower away like the early German
Defectors
So the other thing which was something
Bears mentioning as he's talking about others like
Like
Anti-white
Ship going on on campuses
God I hope there is
These campuses are having a no white people day
And he's really mad
I looked into it a little bit it's happening at this college called Evergreen College
I read something
Do you know about this day with no white people do know about it cuz I'd like to read a paragraph
About what they're doing
I read about that
And Ivy
The one Professor who
Maybe this is a bad idea
Right well the thing is it's called the day of abs
And your ears what they how they describe it
The idea for the day of
Came from a play of the same name by African-American playwright Douglas Turner Ward
465 is a reverse Minstrel show
Black actors in Whiteface
The play is a social commentary on race relations
South refusal to see African-American
Kansas equal numbers of
The community
In the play
Baton wakes up to find
Disappeared
Leaving those who left
Reflect on the meaning of their Community without these essential members
It was originally
Remember Maxine memes
Inspired by the play
Approached administrative
Administrator Stone Thomas
About the idea of joining with other faculty and staff
Color in Spanish
The Grass Roots Collective Act
Day of absence grew to become an opportunity for all students faculty and staff at Evergreen
Savard diversity conversations about issues of differ
In 1992
Which was added in order to reunite the
The College Community At Otter diversity and unity
As a whole
So that's basically
What it is
Do you have the sort of thought experiment the sort of experiential thought
Experiment
Where is absinthe
From
Your entire surroundings
You start to remember we start to realize
More of like
These these other folks
Take for granted
Who just are sort of window dressing
Pocket prep
They're actually an integral part of my life and you start to appreciate them more
It's not
Some sort of racist gesture
Literally the opposite
Makes the heart grow fonder
Subway and so the the guy
Professor who was
Who was against it
I mean he has a
The point but I don't
What was going on
He's a guy I should be
Can't discriminate based on race
I don't I don't like
Respond I'm iffy on his action
I don't know what I feel about it because
And I don't want to
I don't know but I do know that the response to
What happened
After
He said I'm still going to go.
Odd sort of blowing the whole thing
Come on man in the since the 70s
This just a thing
You're depriving students of
This experience
So everyone got mad about it then
A bunch of racists
Started calling in
Terrorist threat
Calling the police station
And start executing
The actual thing has been going on peacefully since the seventies and I'm sure a lot of people have gotten a lot of it
And now
Because of the f****** climate that we live in
People start
Think about it
An idiot's guide to a conversation
Start making fries
You could almost say that we have enough
Almost
I think
I think our culture might
Bad
Text Alex Jones
No but it's
It's what he
Yeah like
Like doing the show and seeing
Through The Eyes of
Alex Jones
Seeing all of this bigot
And all of this
Just
Fair
Like there's there's really no dog whistling
Like there's really none of that like
Still I think
Except for
How about the Jews definitely
Still that but if you listen to more than one episode
You see through it
If you casually listen or you don't engage what he's actually saying
It's still kind of dog whistle
Taken as a
It's just over bigotry
There's really no way around it
What Alex Jones talks about how people accuse them of being racist with no evidence
I would really direct people to our show
So hard to listen to
A couple people who have listened to the show because of our show love you don't do it
I keep telling people like leave it to the pros
This is bad to listen to it very difficult
You see how much I have to listen to Sasha Banks theme song
Just make it through
Anyway
That last
For the Crazy Rap
It was in the commercial
So now
We're going to listen to how he comes back from break
Kind of admits that he was being a little bit manipulative
Oh really
Put out of the video
Great audience of radio Affiliates in cnn.com
This morning thought about how do I trigger a debate
Islam
Kill everyone outside of Islam that's what her constantly killing other Muslims
Lesbian or whatever
Lesbian you're not you're not
Islam's running around
I mean wonder why Islam
Continue bars
And the little no teenybopper Andrea Grande liberal event
That was a symbol of girls
Listening to another
Woman posing as a teenage girl
There we go
They get killed
Call
Country
Bill States like Somalia
Wheaton
The weirdo passport
That are issued
The caliphate
Nope
So
Cliff got a wave
Because he started by talking about how like what I did
That's what I wanted
I didn't want to tell you how I felt
I think that this is the same as what he thinks
He started at Sandy Hook
Doesn't understand
He thinks
I know when
He says what he wants
To say you are quiet
And then he says he's right
I literally know what he say
I hope they play what I just said
BC because everyone's going to be talking about these ideas about radical Islam
And when they cut
Yeah which will be shorter and will probably take me out of context and then deliver
All up in arms
He says that Muslims are all right Mama
The week
Yeah exactly
Has me saying
Let me tell you what I do
Yeah
I feel like that's the part that they're going to throw up
You're just overreacting this is Paul Joseph Watson
Paper eating all over again
I was just throwing out example
Listeners look
For him
Start making these sorts of arguments in the coming days
Cuz I'm sure that Megyn Kelly interview on interview her for a few days
Look for him to start doing the sort of b*******
Cuz that's
So pure
Yeah we'll be like I said
A huge
Seems like
So Alex
What's wrong with you
How do you how do you think I look now
Do you think I look good
What is my friend
That would be my second Kelly my first words
You like to make fun of my appearance
How about you super Mayo
Supermale ain't working
Justice
Straight 20 minutes
Are you fat
Ugly
Misshapen
Nightmare of a human face what happened
Well you didn't just sitting in the womb
It turns you into this your mama smoker
Is that a new are the rug on your head when you doing
Alex
Alexis Jonathan I don't know why I'm here
It would be it would be so great
Quick question
Am I on Greensprings right now
Can you see my nose how much
He is way too professional to do something like that but she just
God dammit
Give me the
Hairiest Ally
Or if
Contact
And we could give her like those clips about his mom taking her off at the knee about that
F****** like if your mom told you that you needed
When you were sick
Your mom told you you needed to be a man so she wasn't going to love you anymore
Comment
Super Glue
Blake's not
What do you think
Alex Jones
What made
You claim to have been beat up more than Martin Luther King
Comet
Can I get
Independent confirmation of the number of women that you slept with before you were 16
Hey
Earlier today off the Record
Are you a journalist
What the f*** is wrong with you
That would be
Man
Megyn Kelly get her to get her it's too late
On any and every Alex Jones interview
Applebee's
I need to get Louis Theroux to do a episode about Alex Jones
Cuz he would like the movie throws maybe the only person I think
Who could get a good interview out of our
Alex into thinking that he was kind of on his
Corky wouldn't interview the Westboro Baptists
Just people
Except for the mom she's it wasn't playing ball nor Fred Phelps
So this next clip Jordan
Jensen
And I believe
That this rant is directed
At Megyn Kelly's crew
You can see him looking sort of off camera while he's delivering this
So it's clear he's doing this almost
Hey go f*** yourself
It's about how the globalist want to destroy us
But then kind of gets into
Alex Jones
Just doing some slow Strokes
Autism day
Just low
Here I am baby just trying to make the head
Really swollen
Ridiculous
King down ladies and gentlemen of every race color creed we do all bleed red blood and we do have one
Sovereign Flag Republic
And Donald Trump is launching
Operation 1776
15 years ago
You got it
Of course the president and of course Banning and of course all those people and the military and the general
You going to give a reason why
That's good
Arbutus
Is in reality
America
And we can do anything from the Discrimination in America
Scared the KKK
Nancy Pelosi
These are conscious evil race horrible people who hate everybody
Donald Trump
The people come together
He is doing now
Not in uniform
Scored
Nope
A chad
I represent Pittsburgh not Paris
Images of screw jobs
Also Pittsburgh is come out roundly against that statement also Hillary Clinton
Shut us
Was noon
Passing out in the middle of a big field on the 4th of July
We'll get back to the dragon the metaphor but I realize I remembered I remembered what I wanted to bring up with a Pittsburgh
Thing I read a really interesting write-up about that about how is about
Masculinity
Support Pittsburgh not Paris
Is this
It's
Coded language to people who
The ingrained masculinity
You think of these like
Dude working in
Steel mill
Dudes
Musica Paris you think of
Bay
Kind of
Giessen
Guys in varese with a baguette over their shoulder
Essentially homosexual man
What are you
What is a crepe
Yeah what are you doing for stereotypes can we feel so basically when
Trump
But you could have chose any town
To say he's supported in the reason he chose the alliteration
Second
But then speechwriter did that intentionally
Is a mess
We're into dudes
Not you dumbass
Dishy
European
Fox
Right but beyond even the European f**** that is a message to
Send me men
Here
Surrender
Right
But that's at least funny
So I mean that's why that really resonates
I mean he's already against the Paris agree
You throwing that sort of thing that he probably doesn't even
Subconsciously
We understand
That this is
Right in his toxic masculinity wheel
Right
Also
Once again
The Paris Accord
Are not just
New
That's not how that works
He's mad
Cuz the French president
That is what I believe
And I will die
And just opening that popping up and Count Dracula is burning up right now
We are listening to a show where you can say well
Here is that b******* about the Paris Accord
Now
More about Dracula
Metaphorical globalist Dracula but
Still
It shows so f******
I'm stupid I can't believe
Can't believe he has millions of dollars
Andrew
We bring in what we do
George Soros
The American people
And the Briggs everybody else have already
Literally
Riven
2 ft
Shorts
Target Flushing
The most
He's too much weiner Emagine
The bottom
Never give up
Rolling around
Another big Pia
When do you hate America
Alpha psychopath but think you're better than us
Just like the fascist and just like the Redcoats America is coming
Nationalism pre-market
Always will be
Years old
And it's about to go into full-blown we're about to see the greatest
And the secrets of the universe unlocked
They want the University's busy turning the youth in the basket cases that are mentally ill and all fighting with each other
You're so screwed up and such a such a chip on the shoulder new Roddick
Thousand dollars
Realize you'll never get out of debt cuz just the finance another hundred thousand dollars
You're so politically scramble call you don't know what hit you
I do have a lot of debt
Maybe hear what this
Search going to important things first he dropped out of Junior College
Well he doesn't have as much data as I do
Is Berkeley
Free market
Fremont
Nationalism
Is the winning team
That's what everyone has seen throughout history
Nationalistic countries have always won in the end totally
Never been destroyed from within like they
Always
Massive Global problem
Country that is.
Harm to the rest of the world
I mean
Free-market sound
Grape
Cuz it's free Marketplace
We all love those things
Flea market
Like Alex Jones has in the past
But the thing is
The reality of the free market
Uncheck
Is
The things that is brought into the world
Yep child slavery essentially in the mines
This student debt
Crisis that were in artificial bubbles
Great Depression
All that is
Direct results of free market capitalism
Yeah all of it is just because
You you need regulations on the free-market or else people are going to
Constantly abuses
Yeah that is
Part of the game of the market
It's just built into
That's so he can't say
What they can do they can't do
I used to go to my old phone
I used talk to him a bunch of
But how when I worked at Groupon
I was very guilty about how little work I was doing
And I like
I told him I need more work
I am just
I'm getting paid to do basically nothing
Hours
I express my guilt
And he would be like
Feel bad
It's not your job
How to beat your boss
Cuz it's not
I'm basically a company and my boss has the governor
If the government doesn't set
Here are the things you can and can't do
You're just an employee getting paid to do nothing
Running Buck Wild
I found scam
Would you give treating my timecard like crazy
Nice I would be I'd be writing on the clock
4 hours Rite workout is B6
Pre-market
Anyway
Beyond that I feel
Thoughts
That
They they are a bunch
Alpha psycho
Two paths who think they can dominate
They think they're better than us
Blows me away
Why
Well
Because
He constantly
Thinks he's better than people
Constantly
Intimidate
Constantly expresses Psychopaths
How is
Just
Drawing of portrait of himself
What's the same thing with like
Obamacare vs Affordable Care Act
The Affordable Care Act
When you just described it as opposed
Calling it Obamacare
Right I think that if you just described
The tendencies that Alex Jones have
He be like
Right you just take him out of his identity out of it
That behavior is
Indicative
Globalist who interviewed
For when we eventually interview a broke
Homeless
Just
Decrepit Alex
That will be fun
It will be
Cathartic
Cuz they're fun
Left
Just
He said
And then free associated
With
You hate Alpha
The psychopath
Here is something that an alpha
Psychopath
Would you agree
Comet
And how do you feel
Goes to his complete lack of self-awareness
He talks about how I'm real
People listen to me
Cuz this is the only show that brings you real truth
It's so easy to pick anything that he says
The idea of a whites-only day on campus
Representing is a racist thing
Is a complete lie
That's absolutely not what's going on
Extremism in the Islamic community is exploding
Is a complete fabrication
And just
Mongering
About
What is a problem but it's not the biggest problem in the world
Paul Joseph Watson
Razee stupid propaganda
Lydia
His show is just repeating propaganda more or less
And he thinks it's the truth
Is nice little like he's
Like he's the resale
Russian propaganda
These a Carnival Barker in front of it
App Store
You get a cheaper
Anyway it's
Before or just his like
Their technocracy is dying
What do you think
Is coming
So if if
Are
If this shadowy group of people is real
Conspiring behind the scenes
Send
I don't know why
150 years or whatever
You think
Hot goddamn second their plans are foiled by pulling out of a climate agreement
Yep
That's so stupid.
Lowe's mobile
Non-binding agreement
How could they
These people
Secretly planning behind the scenes and poisoning the water
And tricking every scientist
Conspiring with the media
All of this stuff
They created fake vaccine
Like literally everything
Make false shootings happen
Notre to start a race war that never happened
All this stuff
What they've been doing behind the scene
I'm somehow they had one plan
And it was a non-binding agreement
That every other country signed onto
Yeah somehow
That's so stupid
It's it's unbelievably stupid even if you agree with his foundational premise globalist
Like if you are conspiracy theorist who just believes in the globalist
You would have to be like
Alex
Bad
The camp
Possibly be that on strategic
Secretly up till this point
They can only create an app
That is as dumb as that
They're not smart enough to
Create a smart
Okay
The thing was Alex
He can't imagine an enemy
That has more intelligence
So now your premise is at the globalist
The globalist
Okay because they're a figment of Alex Jones imagination
I went reverse reverse on it I was imagining the globalist
Alex
That's just
As a stupid enemy for them cuz they're like
Let's get this guy to yell about us
The James Bond movie we need to write
So this
No that's that's
Nothing because
Tsv
Just
Epoxy just
Is of human
He can only a
He can only believe
Is it the globalist
Yeah he's only capable
Of thinking
I think you might have nailed it
In terms of you know
War games
Backwards
Yeah like
Reverse engineering
That's why that's why I damn you have been saying things
But I've been thinking five years ago maybe I have
Great
I applaud you this weather
Who's next
Another ramp
Who Woulda thought
This one
Crazy
I know I know
This one
He's like
He don't even know how to describe
What are you talkin about
He starts by talking
I think it's at the beginning
About
Via guy who stood up
To the Muslim terrorist
In London
Like what
And that's
Kick them off into
Really weird trajectory
But also its
Worth noting
He's reading a Daily Mail
So
Grill grate
Source
Thanks burdock
Good direction
This
Rap goes
Isn't he
He starts screaming and it's about him
B is getting really personal
And there's a moment do you see the look on his face like
It doesn't bode well for the fact that the interview with the
Like 2 hours at
If you getting this worked up and like
Really revealing stuff about himself
Immediately realizes
Is that bad
Disney
I'll let you know
Here
Without me ruining it
Reveal is
Bucked up
Intensify what all this is
Liberals
These are sociopath
Email
Who want to be in dominant position but don't want to create economies don't want responsibility don't want
Also control freak women
Ecology
Four generations of formula combinations you knew would reduce IQ starting point
Morning
Ourselves come out of the trance I believe
I got a bunch of Clips I want to get to break down
Tillery.
And so
Skylanders
Recharging him now
Bad memories
Soccer team
Just watched a bunch of people
I want to buy under the overturned
Make sure I have a second.
Imagine
Just got 100 people
He's the weirdo He's the bad guy
4 years older than me
Well the people
Juvenile
Evil man
He's positively
Long time
He does not like revealing that every
Your boy about
Play parts
Belief
Everybody
I'm angry about this for it
Myself
Nope new
Thousand years ago
Here in Sun Valley
In the world
And somebody hit your wife and daughter
You go give a speech like that to the men of the village
That's why
So you guarantees in caveman days the speeches
We're just like that
Dope they were jokes
Everybody knows
That wasn't a speech
Through the valley
Yeah I'm still your wife and kids
Like perhaps
His wife stole his
Go back to the people who hit a guy with a brick
Let's be clear I'm sure he was getting picked on or I'm sure there was
I'm willing to believe that a guy did beat him up
But I'm not willing to believe
That the threat was what he
Describe
You don't saying
I
Know a lot about Alex
He's prone
Beer
Paranoia an exaggeration
So I bet that some guy was sorta like
F*** you kid something like that maybe a guy who was a little older than him
And maybe beat them up a little bit
Which is
Police should not do that sort of thing
It sucks
But
I also don't think
That whatever was happening Meredith and you can tell that long
Walking paws
That was a that was like a
Oops f***** up
Ask ask yourself
Does Alex Jones
Hitman with
The brick one
What he did
His weapon of choice
I also know that
I've been around I don't use names
But I have a couple friends who got into a little bit of a fight
No
Can I give your sources it's pretty public
Got a little bit too
Thought the threat was way worse than it was in the fight we were all just drinking having a good time in the backyard
And the guy who thought it was a little more serious grab the bottle and hit the other one in the head with it
I think please do didn't get her too bad just a little bleeding from the face of it
You disproportionately responded that's what a lot of people do
People who have really bad fear
Control mechanisms
People who
I think they're victims at every point in their life
They are going to
Respond
Way more aggressively than they need to
And Al Jones
I have to believe
Literally just said that's what he did
I don't believe this person was bashing his head into the
Absolutely
Now if you talk to my friend
Who hit the other guy with
I'm sure his version of it would be you could break my arm
Because I don't think the guy
Like my friend who
Is necessarily super violent bad guy he's just not in control of his Panic back
When someone
Out of their own principles and acts based on
Offer you do f***** up things
Application for it you want to be like
The guy was going to kill me I had to hit with a brick
It is an interesting
To know that
We still have that
That f******
Olympics
My house burned down
Wherein we have to Denver
Analyze This
Survival
Ingrained into Aspergers
Millions of years will like 5 years ago my house burned down and I just ran out of the building
As soon as I got out I was in
I'm sucking huge shock I was terrified
Really realize that I
Didn't knock on anyone's door
Thankfully everyone got out okay but I realized
That's f***** up
I didn't want anybody
I don't want to be the hero the difference is my immediate response wasn't like
Like to make an excuse for myself
I did not respond to that well I could have taken a second and realized
I'm I don't have to run out of here
Minutes left where I can
Fret
Responsibly
Fighter flight system went
Exactly
Find wall of flame
Can chance you know it sucks
About to make excuses for it
It sucks that Alex
Excuses weave into his bizarre
Stupid
Arguments
About about masculinity
Every time
He reveals
The slightest thing about his child
Everything else
God why is everybody talking to Alex about what
Thanks now I want to know what
We know what
Well we don't know enough I want to know the whole story
There needs to be a
Investigative biography
You can find the work-in-progress aetna.com
So we got one more before the eclipse
Ended up me turning off the episode
He starts talking about how Hillary Clinton is a joke
And then
Slow Strokes
Course
Lady
He's talking directly to Hillary
Million-dollar
Million dollars
$3000000
They told me the whole plant-based
He's telling this to the Embassy camera crew
You could have been working
Sing for me for Megan Kelly this could have been me good for you
Stafford paid $30,000 a year who doesn't give a f*** I'm sure those
People are f****** holding in laugh
Like one time me and my buddies got high and went to like a Christian haunted house
You know they have like the plan is that the bathroom
Any one of the rooms they had tape on the floor
The scene was this guy realizing that his kids died
In a car accident
The whole story of the haunted houses to get to kid
Boca
Skip.
Did scene
We're like my weed high is
I'm so high
At the scene is
Dad realizes both of his kids
Falls to his knees
Is likewise
But you so close to that tape line on the ground
He's so close to us
The whole time I'm just grabbing my friend's shoulder
Well I got it that's what the cameramen are doing
Could have been Glen
Could have been Megyn Kelly
I'd said no and I went in a year and I Glenn Beck ready
More people
Selectavision the Body Snatchers you can get the transfer done on time
Didn't didn't go the way you wanted to go
Information on
I think the fact that I'm real
As your strengths not care what they think what they say
Elementary students about
Different sexes
What is
Government
He says I haven't even gone through the story
Course not but there aren't any stories for him
Also government
But
Enjoy that narrative
I also all that stuff about the like white genocide
On campus at 12
Equally bulshit to this
A day of
Right
Evergreen
I think the best way to get people on board with a white genocide
I just to have them listen
Sure
Yeah
No no
I think we're good
We had enough White
People
Is learn history
And then what about this guy he doesn't know s***
Minority
Give no idea about the Matrix of Oppression he isn't no f****** idea at all
You've no idea about societal power in the differences between different groups
Is no f****** idea and all the information is there
At his fingertip
He could learn
But because he's so into being white he won't
That's the best argument
You've got me on board
So I am
We've got another twenty bucks
So this last
Clip
I was
You've been having this guy on
A lot lately
Tommy Robinson
There's a British guy who works for the rebel
Brooks a rebel media
And
Gives dispatches
A ton
Alex Jones about how Muslims are over running
England
And what have you
This report he was doing was about how there is
Nearest school
No
And so he
Doesn't really
Standing outside
I don't know if Tara's lives down the block I have no idea I don't understand
The situation
Doesn't really
He doesn't
He says things but there's no evidence
I don't I don't I don't know
Intrude
Infowars
So you screaming about
Screaming
Much more control Denali
Expect he gets into like
You saying
London needs to do more about Isis
Bespoke
But
Folk
The Isis people people who sympathize with ISIS
That's the problem
Just say
The key
He's
We've already proven with Trump that if
You just say it
You're probably
Going to get more p
Yeah
This is harshly dog whistling
Partially
Conflating all Muslims with
People who do horrible
Probably wisest
Like I'm done I'm done
Episode
You think is a government
Unique
Which will fight
Umpire absolute
From the heart
And that is our salvation
Be honest about
I meant he was he was not
British person
That was pretty much
What's the level of Al
Yeah but I mean just be the
You got to get these people off our streets you're not protecting
You got internet
Wonderful
White way of saying
Put everybody who's not white
Take all of their stuff
And put them in
The history of internment camps has never been
People who are guilty of
No
Populations that you need to
Separate
So when you start using light once again America
Whose property and everything
The f****** store
But that like
When you start using that language especially in concert with language like you're not protecting our people are
It's so light
White
Stillwhite
White Reaper
It's over-the-top bigotry
And the fact that I was Joan
Comes back
That's Veritas
That will be our salvation
Is just
It's too much to
To take it
To race
That I can't handle it
Yeah that's not dog with
And it's boring
It's boring races
Mosquitoes
Like the stuff where he's talking about
Crazy globalist plots and what have you
Is kind of boring cuz it's
He says it all the time
But this is just
The banality of evil
We need school boring
Prison people who are
That's what he
Triangle
Like that
Shut the fuk
Sayings that all Arabs
About racism
Somehow never
Her f******
It doesn't
The Intern
Who's next
To be some outside
There's no end to
Racism
Is not
F****** ending erase
Because then what you do is eventually you'll start going Inward and you'll start being like brunettes
Because it's not about the target it's about the behavior it's about the mentality at the other ring and
The fact that there are some Muslims who commit violent crimes
It's about
Beer of other
Support before we had before white people had other races they had different
Yeah
You know Jews
Look at the IRA and
And there's no
Believe me
I'm not against
Oh boy
Am I
You put a
S*** ton of pressure on
Just just like we're talkin
Think about what
If you put enough pressure on P
People are going to break
Yeah and those broke
Are going to commit violence
Yeah
The Happening
And this time
I would
I mean
What is
Too fast for these old f***
Can white people
They just need
Go away
They just need to be gone
That's it that's only because
There was like
That's the only way to understand what their do
Because
It's a different
But it is
That
What they are
Is going away
Yeah
Put pressure on enough
People people
That's what's going on
Their issue
Is that they can't accept a world changer
That's a big problem for
Humanities
The beginning
We're not.
They can't they
What do you what else
Do you do with these people other than
Put him in a f******
Let him sell weird pills
Interim
I think it's a good idea
Steal their property
Take their second amendment rights away no more free market
I'm sick
Prosperity
That's cuz you're a beta libtard
The technocracy we need to commit white genocide
We need to
What else is he real about I don't know
Except
Walking except
What's the message
And when you say that you're not saying hey people who kill people with
Trucks that knives are cool that's what anyone is saying when they say accept people that's not what that is at all
People that's awful there's a reason
We have to have laws
Because
Somehow at one point
We're so stupid somebody had to tell us.
Fright
Like mehrabi
Brunei
Leave everybody with
Hammurabi
The greatest
Pillar of
White history
Knowledge feit.com hopefully the next episode will not be as rant
Heavy I didn't know what to do with that I apologize that is kind of long clips
Yeah but
Consistent but also you can follow us on Twitter at knowledge
Tunes
Spread the word
Leave a review
People found us
Like their algorithms on iTunes where it's like the more reviews and likes
What you got
Put you up at the
If you tell two
And they tell two friends
Now is a good time to remind everyone that Infowars anytime you want to start to think their legitimate news Outlet
Please remember that they have a pyramid scheme called the Infowars
You can get one of those direct marketing programs
You can use
Just buy a bunch of product
I can sell it to your friend
You get discount
If you buy like
Huge amounts
Congratulations girls
Anyway
What is what is one thing that
Take away the positive I know that
The Paris agreement is dead
Paris agreement is dead
But one thing is still alive
And that is
John
He still lives
Alexandra Thurston color
Holding