Important
I have great respect with knowledge like I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Alex Jones
2R
Play the delightful
Game of Thrones
Jefferson Thomas Jefferson
Something from a-z
Mailbox
Tunica
Sent some chocolate
And some of these little nanoblocks
Nanoblocks coolest
They are like little tiny Legos
Miss pelican
Tubi
I just felt really good as relax
Building that
Triggered a lot of those feelings that I had
Apollo
The fizzy
Jelly
Accelerators brutal because
The moment you told me you liked it I was like I was like to travel never going to get the check I will order bar Jessie
Triad
I was a good
Balan was it gummy there were little bits of gummy
Not like
Offensively so
And then there was
Busyness
Over-the-top fizzy okay
Nonsense okay alright okay
On paper it doesn't work but this is one of those things where you're going to have another one
I realize all I like
It was the fact that these things don't happen to be before
There's a chance
Nope nope
Breitbart
Give me the piece of chocolate I was about to eat while I can help
Movies
Called wild mountain thyme I think is what it's called
Love it
You know those movies
The jelly candy of a little bit
You like this is not a good movie
It's not a bad movie
This movie Just
Needed to exist
Didn't before like it's just a thing that you're like I'm glad that's there now
Favorite type of story don't know exactly what you're talkin about
Christopher Walken
Silver
Terrible Irish accent
That sounds like somebody doing impression of Christopher Walken
Sex
And you're like
This is probably going to stop
Keep going
Sub Stop
32 Irish stories in the world and there's Irish doors that go like this
Oh my god you're an outsider
Overtime they like
Okay fine
You can say but
You do too much so you can never leave or the other kind
Legos are the only two types of there's no story where they virus people growing
You're either in or out
And that's it
And this is very much one of those stories and then
Could be sold to you the way that people are going to review it is there's like a Twist at the end
There is not a twist
It's not a twist
Just a reason
Are you going to blow your
Okay
Okay to talk about it
Discuss
Fever whatever its called
Episode
I think we're going to have some fun
Great idea
Dealing thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Next
Most 1/8 you so much you're not probably want
I'm a policy wonk
Jimmy
Jimmy Carter's brother
Vincent Van Gogh's brother like that guy does
Is Yucatan
Take that generosity and you could
Just funnel it into some sort of creative spirit and it doesn't matter what it's a
About it doesn't matter what it's about
Whether or not it's good
It's about is
Getting it out there
So even if you're confused by your generous spirit
Put it out there
Take me to a local bail fund
And I'll be goddamn if it's not better satin Ireland
So there you go
Jordan
This episode today we're going to start
Going down this road
December 9th
Alex's show
Is Musa in a weird head space
Bragging
There's about a half hour.
Beginning
Everybody
Even taking off
Almost every
System internet
Klowdtv is owned by Patriot
They put us on two years ago
We are number one on cloud TV
All News Channel together including oan or bigger than all of them Newsmax oan
The kind of shocked by that they even moved us
YouTube
Dominic's too much weed. Sounds like a good reason
It's just that
They won't play it because we have more viewers than all of them combined on
Cloudtv
Obviously Owen CableSystem satellite sisters and I love it
Newsmax become the number one station
Used to put us up at the top because we're so popular set a chance
Sound like
Business logic to me for so f****** log
I was getting so annoyed that Alex was like
Alpha
I'm an alpha male so when I was a kid
The album
I guess
Please
Show me the average man or woman
Isn't it
Trip
Yeah hello
Scary situation in a horror movie are going to
Nutrafol
The truck that's alright
People I don't know maybe
Maybe there are some horror movies are people intentionally
We fall down today
They're trying to get away
Yeah maybe this
Mozzarella
Anyway I I just
Who's annoying
I just needed something
Point that was going on on Wednesday show
Define
This is this is something disgusting
People died during Pfizer covid vaccine
Something else on today's episode
Want to bring this up I think
Press to cover this
Because he was like it's going to be
Big Talk
Sweet
Particular headline
Repetition
You can find the headline
Covid vaccine trial
The actual article covers some of the details the story
Do you don't really hear them when Alex covers at on the show because he does
The story to be about
It's on scary that 6 people died in these trials but cases like this
Crucially important to consult the actual information to see what the data says
If you go to the fda's website you can find the vaccines and related biological products
Advisory committee
Document on the new Pfizer
Vaccine
If you read this document
You'll find it 6 participant to the trial
But that number
Has to be understood in context
The first thing to consider is that there were 43200
52 / 2
Dispense enrolled in the study
6 is a very low.
Number but even so
If the vaccine killed six out of 43,000 people
It still might be a cause for concern
I mean if there is 330 million people getting
If you do you'll find
And it for out of the six people who are in the placebo group
Which is to say that they didn't even get the vaccine it's being test
These deaths are absolutely
The unrelated
The vaccine
Two two people
Experimental
Who died
One of them was retroactively John F Kennedy
These two individuals
Which means if they were over 55 years of age
Experience
Cardiac Arrest 60 days after dose 2 and 3 days later
2 months afterwards
Heart attack
It's a sad for that person but almost
Play unrelated to the vaccine
The other person experience cirrhosis and died three days after.
Arteriosclerosis is it
Absurd to imagine that a developing
Free days because of
The vaccine
In this case
It seems almost certain that
Condition on relate to the vaccine
Precipitate
I thought it might be possible that you
You can make a study out of whether or not
The vaccine could exacerbate existing cirrhosis
Your concern of the authors
Didn't seem like it was likely
Experimental group
Both are unlikely
We connected the vaccine itself
Misrepresented in report
I just
It seems like a
A very obvious oversight
6 people died in the trial
Only to receive the vaccine in the headline
How I meet all their Outlet
You got it
2/3
The number you're talking about exactly
But only know what how is reported
Of course they're standard Islam
Do you have paper itself
The incidence of severe adverse
Adverse Events and dates
And comfortable for experimental and placebo
So
This is a disgusting lie on Alex's Park
Jesus
Is reading actually means
He gives the audience the illusion that he's informing them of important stuff
He's actually doing
Misinforming
The flashy clickbait style headline is not necessarily untrue itself
The conclusion it's meant to leave
Did you do is a lie
And I miss representation Outbacks
This
I'm not
Beatnik
Okay that's
Something you hear about moving
Going forward as
More countries
The rollout of action
I don't care
Listen to half an hour of Alex
Rambling about how great he is
Have been this weekend
Alex is supposed to go down to DC DC
Is true
I felt like Monday
Monday
We've got to get into like Alex going to DC and I have a little better idea of
We have a responsibility
So I was thinking
We have a responsibility to do other thing
Sex
Maybe now is
If you take DMT with your body
A hundred percent
Last week
Just recently Joe Rogan showed up in Alex's Studio
Before our interview
Just to take one
Quick-Step back it is amazing to me that they can turn
6 dead in this
Trial into a
Terrifying
Whenever like
We went from a brand
Disease
Year-and-a-half
Miracle state
Miracle to have done that
Adoption soup
Like
They did it one time faster in like the 1950s like crazy hair
And they're just like all six deadline
Incredible
Severe
Severe adverse
Events
Everything
Stats for
Number of people who I'd like
Arash
I agree
Issues with issues to deal with
I want to be a globalist how do I get in
So we're really doing this
I'm about people infinitely smarter than
Save this ahead of time
Try to steer away from conversation about house
F*****-up they are
Because I think
It's kind of low-hanging fruit a little bit
And it would become tiresome we just put a disclaimer
People living their lives
Being f***** up
Presenting himself the way he does
Eating super f***** up with Rogan
Whatever
It's not as good
Alex is really true
Impress
As much as he is just trying to like the bond between the two
The number of things I think are important
Alex's Studio isn't fun because it's like
Supplicate himself
Because you are
Oh no
Figuring Alpha what we start in my list of this outside
Infowars the most Network in the world
Well I got to tell you
I get bigger
Goosebumps
For this guy on the Arizona
I've known you for 22 years
And you're a fun really smart amazing guy and you put a lot of my crap
I need the number one not just podcaster but
World
Joe Rogan Alex Jones
Supplication
Subsequently I must have rubbed off with people if you
Consistent throughout this
Interview
Tell me Spotify
The Great
Spotify
Just a couple of other like
Why'd you leave la
I really love Texas
I always was
Attached to a beak
Because The Comedy Store
Because a business and just doing stand-up
This is the logic
Excuse
The movie Ray
I just like
Feasible
And then as soon as
I don't believe that for a second
Almost certain
Text related
Got a hundred million dollars and La Chargers
Can I understand
Perform in LA
He lived in the city
Protests
Recent
Millionaire
The artificial
One fault about the best thing you could do
King
Loaded
Midday
Just so happens
The Texas is the state where I can most
Promise lyrics
Either Texas or move to buy
You go to Miami
Sort of Steve
Ask buttering
Why
To be the most
Famous person in the world
You were so successful early on in your career all this stuff what's it like having
Angela my next question
Are you been doing podcasting over 10 years
Attract
It's ya
Like literally no one was watching it was
We were watching show my God
God brother
Today Show
Abso
Do this interview
Complete
Countries and it's like I'll just kind of like
4 minutes it
Let's go back to that to that's my first question
How to develop your work ethic and drive
Athletic
Michaela
Meme
Put together from the last time Alex was on Rogan and this place together things
Make it sound like Alex wanted to have sex with Joe
He went around on Twitter and stop
Leaning into that show someone else
Exit video
Desperate
Embarrassed
He he's he's
Just out
Regis Lee desperate to get a
That's more than even having
Joe on something
Looking for twenty thousand likes on
If you got to make fun of me you got to make fun of me
Beverly Bryson
I love it
There's a show
That I have a podcast
Vicky's very serious
Trigger is well I think you might react negatively
Receive any criticism yeah
He does not like nobody likes
It's a ton of people at
Set a timer for 10 minutes
The place
Being made fun of
Accept payment 300
But I will not do it
In many ways
Logan is the most famous most famous person in the world
He is
The Walter Cronkite of our times
When did you realize that you were in the site guys you already cuz I got to
UFCU near big movies Indian
When did you realize oh my God I'm like
Real Superstar.
Empty movies
Actor that reads off a teleprompter script
Be your own self
And be the biggest that's that's that's
Very rare
Tobacco stick
I don't know, realized it I'm not sure if I still realize it
Come on you got it like like what
Cuz I mean I'm pretty super famous
Is it makes me think about
Interesting
I kind of respect
It's a really
Embarrassing
As like a
Person
Lakeville
Graceful
Dignified
Respond to that
Think about that too much
Imagine
You do think about it
Is it gross
Strenuously do you sniff your own farts and believe them
Them to be amazing
Could you just tell me
When did you first
Other answer could he give the doesn't make him look like a s*** head
I think it was about.
I realize that I was
Is the king of the world
I should reach data between the two much like Steve pieczenik salt
Conflict
The Meathead jock
Pothead.
Conflict everybody likes doing nothing sometimes
The Destroyer
Couple times back when Alex was on
He lied to us about Sandy Hook
It was right around a lot of
Attention was going on with the Sandy Hooks
The opposing counsel
I'm sorry put out a million-dollar
The time
Sneaky Snake
Horizon 2
Destroy a talking about his children
Think about them in a way that is
Aw to say sorry about all that
I'm going to be a couple something
Hardcore issue with you tonight
Appreciate
And
That's that I kind of got the whacked-out under all the pressure all the
We've been over this
I just want to know are you out now
I rode that was a big help
Well we just need me
It's just
It's really a microcosm of what is happening
People
Talking
To each other
No it's not
It is not a microcosm of what's going on with
Show Media
No.
Communicating with each other
Case of
Hotels
Comparison
Remember this quote from Sinbad and I will till the day I die
Comics are funnier when they ride the bus
You have no
F****** clue what you're talking about you 100 million are dumbass
Jeff
Like
I don't know what
The f*** he thinks it's does for a living
Like I don't
Does he
Not know what Alex's
Conspiracies still
Possibly know the horrible things Alex said about him
Alex was turning their fight into contact
Fighting between the two of them
I know you probably don't have time to see
It's this whole series
The things that Joe said that Alex said directly
What's this
And remember it forever
Let's save
You're a friend of mine and we have a falling out
You're a high-profile person
I would
Have the instinct
To threaten to destroy you for attention
That's kind of
That's a bad person
Yeah if I started my own show like we have a falling-out I start my own show
All the sudden
You just start going on I'm going to kill jordanrants
Your show would become far more popular
Carrie's on the charade
He actually knows
Anything about what
The first
Real metis
And that is like a full demonstration of why
When I get into issues when I'm serious
You can differ on my interpretation
But I'm saying I've got a clip
I got something I've got
Well that's why I wanted to clarify that in the podcast really clearly
You just got proven I'm surprised
Bandana
Raleigh was already said that was your best podcast with Joe ever
I went home depressed
This is not equipped for himself
Fact check Alex
I gave just enough of the
Appearance of Association
Destroyed his career
But you didn't help me
Get to take that shot
Because he didn't
Now that
Give me correct
It's just a pathetic display
And here's what makes me the
Most convince
To that
Home at last podcast
The Rockefeller Foundation
According to Alex
Easily accessed
Supposed to prove it
Finish the podcast
Mediately
Check that
Claim
He's
Your friend is a liar and he's using your information
People killed
And you're complicit in it
If he's right there's a very easily provable conspiracy to kill off the population
Seems like
Important
The only thing that really makes sense is if Joe is treating Alex like
It's hard to talk to him about the crazy
Ever hang out with Eddie
He's not going to research the fake operation
Innocent
He's doing a lot of damage
Doing a bad job
To fact-check Alex
If you just shoot the s*** with your friend
Once you step into the game
Validating his
Conspiracies
Some kind of
Giving Alex
Basically selling your audience
You can't
I'd like the first sentence he said is just like
Can different interpretation
It's like you
On some things you can but there are things that are
It's not everything is not differentiable on interpretation
And then second
You always have the
Why why would you say that
Is that the joke
Pathetic
Gift for Joe
Okay
You give me a lot of great UFC tickets but only nice to me for 20-plus years and I
I've never really gotten you anything I've seen people give you gifts on the show
Doing some PR thing if they're selling
I don't own any stock in this B
This is something we can go get
Texas
So this is your gift
That box of cigars
Cigars
It's just like a
Parody of masculinity.
That's really bad
We get it there supposedly
Yeah this is a man cave I got you alright
It's really wild
I got a bunch of them
How Texas is this
I was very I was very afraid
Is generally whatever
Infowars
Alizee
The Pinnacle of gun safety just the 2nd Amendment
Direct
Rifles
Get to talkin about
The medication
You know some people
Drugs
With meds
Some side effects
Different people with different side effects
You know n
In some people
And cocaine
You know there's people that say that mixing it with
Cocaine
They say don't drink on this okay
And a drink on it
Write the problem isn't
The match results
Yeah yeah that's the one
It's the inverse of what you think is yours
Let me back you up one step
That is what it seems
Freemasons
A valid just cuz you owe me to take this
Cholesterol
Is that really dangerous people who are all the MX
Use it as prescribed
Taking Xanax okay that's that's my Recreation
Estranged
A little bit
Because I
Look cartoonish
Pro
Marijuana
Nothing
If presented earlier on
It's good self move on a little bit into position where it seems like
Is aware that sometimes it can have negative out
Comes
I've been more and more open over the last few years especially
I don't think it's a good idea to tell everybody it's always so strong that it's definitely been connected
Increases in schizophrenia
I have no but I don't know if it's from the potency
Perspective
I think maybe
It's always happened
We just didn't recognize
People personally
Normal a frozen water pot and went crazy
One of them started thinking everyone with reptiles
I got bad news for you
Employee previously normal
Starting from like a really grounded places I started smoking
Listening
Lost
Everyone is
What's the difference between mental health
Is
You know what I don't I don't listen to this I don't understand why people would listen to two people have the same
Dumb thoughts you could already
We have at home
You know
But you can pick it up at home
Cuz you have knowledge and research
Hey I have remember the content of this thing that I might have read
Ultimately decided to do this episode
Because I'm looking forward to Monday
The script
2 BC
Episode
Motivating factor was
It is something serious about Mercury
F*** it episode unreal it's me
Long stretches where I was listening to this
I don't care I don't care
Gazebo parts
Just like okay
This is just a stupid conversation it's not really relevant
Just talkin about
Funtime you all had or something
Joe Rogan just like 10 minutes
Like you're so much
Skip
The time
Just listen to the park
Lakeside
So
Alex thinks what he's interviewing gioconda
Tables turn
Dimensional things of the globalist believe and I've never ever had an inter-dimensional
Here we go
Well I'm interviewing Joe Rogan
Are we interview
I'll tell you
And the Dodgers
Dimensional experience
Question can blow you away
If it's like
Have you ever had one
Leaving that that's kind of probably
That's what the globalist believe
Experience as well
Make me look like an idiot just a bunch of
Police
He does say this
I can actually shift
Into a psychic
You do at Ross
Scissors
Did you not trust me
View a minute
To shift into your psychic
State
You better win or are they
I don't have to
To do any voices
Yes
What what that mean maybe
I would hope so
Example
What you say
I wouldn't call the exaggeration
Accelerated
Power
Where they claim
Projection
Four-letter
Call wife
Like too much Trade Center
Watch Hamilton
What
Did you talk about this
So I can't really control it
Holyshit
Episode
As
Give me a recurring dream of a Guyana
And green striped sweater
Masala building
Club
The older kids to get alcohol
The driving downtown
Dallas to get
Crack houses
And then
I was going around the side when these buildings it was a
A crackhead
We tried to attack me I have the exact
Whole bunch of time
Clubbing head
Psychic
Too much lighter
Buy some weed
Ahead
A crackhead and it's the same guy from the drink
Jesus Christ
Wow
Holyshit
So I guess
Maybe
That was like
He'd seen
Nightmare on Elm Street
I guess so
Your dreams unless it's a sex dream with some
Interesting
No one cares about anything else I'm positive that I could come up with
Some stories
Match things that happen later
Perfectly remember it
This is down to the 9/11
Prediction
Well that was a two-hour
July 25th
And information
Having a drink
The towers smoking
Nautica shoes
Here is
The information Source was
He is saying
I said that it was based on analysis product
Prophetic dreams
Frank
In 2000
Enough said
Dream about that that would be very very silly suggest
If this is all true
He's reporting this accurately
He was listening to a ton of Bill Cooper
Patriot ass radio back then
Subconscious
Bill Cooper was saying very similar things
About it
That's
These feelings somebody who is this
World Trade Center
What's it about
The product
Influences that he had
He got on Erin pretend
You some kind of act
Expert had some analysis
That's kind of a microcosm of his career
He has information that he's just
He's ever said the
That he predicted 9/11 as like a result
So
Then
If you could unless you are psychic
How seriously should you take any information that he provides
If he was willing
To Passover predict
Attack
Hazard analysis when it was actually a dream
That sounds about right
Is an interview
Find out what the
The truth is
Unless Joe doesn't want to have
OLX
This is so forced
Look I mean
Because I actually
I can talk plenty
Lookout
No I know right
If you were magically made world
You would do to change the world as it is
Alex Jones ever does this I'm not being different
I understand
I don't think the two of them
I want to kind of
Something
Conversation
More
Charismatic
Yeah I mean I just I thought I would
Every now and again
Okay
Things the same time like
Can I watch it
Could probably
Hangout with Rogan
Wow
We get along with him
Get into these sorts
The topic
It wasn't like
A show
I wouldn't want to be on his show conversation
Social conversations in green rooms
You're forcing it
Comedy
Navigation at least he's willing to have
No conversation that's not true
Hundred percent
How about this kill f***** fight
I don't want to kill him
That man you just making a mockery of it do you want personal mama
So desperate now that
Meme that's really bad
Especially since he's he's trying to get seems like he's getting so much mileage out of just saying
F***
Just like kill sucks
It's like ice like a family
Question
You want Grandma to say piss
We know it
Yeah a little bit of
The problem to Annette Lake
Joe doesn't seem to hate Bill Gates whereas Alex
Claims to know that he runs the world and wants to kill everyone and Alex
Hatred of Bill Gates
Which seems weird
Considering
Everything
I would have said
You know
He's one of the 12
Maybe your baby
When I when I was cast last
There were just tons and tons
The things that were inaccurate
Emotionally
After manipulative at the very least yes
Episode
Catalog
But Joe seems to think
People were desperate
To find something that
Let's go ahead and Play Bill Gates himself saying that the vaccine made 80% of
The people
And people are complaining and trying to find
Something that you said that was
Beatley check
Everything you said in all black
Accurate
Then we got to this part where you said
80% of people that took the vaccine got sick
And people like he's spreading
Anti-vaccine
See theories
Just okay listen
Here's a video
We're not desperate to find things that Alex was wrong about
No
Google Search honest Lake Austin
Exhausting
For f****** ever
I don't understand
We can possibly not wreck
Advise that Alex was blocked
He's like so glaring
You should never talk to Alex ever again
But
He seems to think that everybody was so good
Desperate to find one
One place where Alex didn't. His dad or crosses T see this this is a struggle because
It does seem like he doesn't take Alex seriously
How can you
You also say that
You know that's the complicated
Like he doesn't take
This information seriously
Proven and then not really like
Nationalize Alex
Not taking a step in
F****** conspiracy
Plan to destroy everyone in
Present
Yeah who's in Coke
Covid-19
Has any Credence to it that not curious
If you're willing
Could you believe that stuff has
Proven
And not use
Five of your hundred million dollars to do something about it
Yours even if you believe without
The elites are killing all of us
Marinas all and you have 100 million dollars by Infowars something about it
Make that
Being trampled station
F*** you
This completely bizarre relationship with
Doesn't
Play publicly is to be like
Yeah everyone's just mad about
Things that you say because
Cuz you're saying
They're too attached
The messenger
People get
Into the messenger
They get trapped into the messenger instead of listening to the information
Moron
Might have something important to say
You never know
When someone
Is integrity
Who was an idiot
Most things and they come to you with one fax
Did they saw on TV
Get the f*** out of here
Wolf comes from absolute
You just reference
I'm supposed to be in a story is it when you
You crywolf a bunch of times and there is no
People will not believe your wedding crywolf isn't that the people who
Believing
Bizarre interpretation of that story
Queen supposed to be that if you're a liar and the lies you tell
You can cause serious damage
They might not believe you
Altus
Just continuing to lie
Particularly
People in town there's an issue there
Critically important
Joey singing people cannot
Hear the things Alex says and if
Because they're caught up
The messenger
They hate Alex
So he must be wrong
This is exactly the
Engages with Alex just in the reverse
Jones complete
We caught up on the messenger and refuses to accept
Malignant narcissist
Who is not his
More than most people
I can easily separate my feelings but how repulsive
From whether or not specific
Claimed
Based in reality
It's not a difficult exercise
Because I care
Because I believe that there's a
Matter
Talk about ideas
Bad ideas
He doesn't
Any of this s***
He's talking about matters
He's trapped
He only believes because the two of them has gotten sucked up together a couple times and said offensive things to each other
I guess
I challenged to take his own
Advice
And separate the messenger from the message
Start with operation lockstep
From there and consider the possibility that this person
Sisters your friend
Is actually the dangerous liar
Yeah I do
I mean
Okay then do you watch like the other concern
Well obviously I must believe them because it's true
That's the only
Because they're not the F no
That's so f***** up he's absolutely
To just I will
Defend Alex no matter what
Kind of sucks but it really Gaslight people
Disagree
Possibly have substance
Space
We just hate out it's all about it's all about you
Your feelings it's always
You creating this
Who's coming from
JW snowflake because Alex Jones
To Manley or something
Boring
Dyke trafficking
In this like fetishization of ideas and that's the idea you have
500 something episode to this park has the rice up
With Alex Jones
It's not I don't
Stop 20 long time
Bulshit Joe
It's just like
Alex's fears of and then
Being like on the other side and he wants those things to happen
What he's afraid of his
The things that you desire
In the same way Joe is what is really expressing is
Things based on how I feel
That others react to Things based on how they feel
I can't imagine
Breaking Free of the the molds that I exist in because obviously
If I have 100 million dollars
The things I see
Think are important
Feelings that I have
Or f******
Fake prophetic ass dreams that I have that must be criticism comes from as well
Yeah it gets into this
This kind of thing a little bit
It's really rather
This clip here
Cuz he's talking about like how people shake their ideas
This might be how he
Has
Or
It feels like projector
This is the thing is like
Allowed to have
The other ideas
The whole idea
Of who you are and what life is
Is mostly shaped
By what you think is going to
Delete resistance from the people around you
Was
The fact they were open and free believing speech
Demonologist
I'm so high out of you.
You said some really smart
Tigrett
Discount
Because he's all
Presumption
You mold your identity by was that witch
These ideas that will cause the least the people around you
That's not
Xperia X your personality
New people
Better because
Yeah
I can't handle
This
There's ideas and
You can look at things from a different way but we also have to exist in a world where something
And some things are not
Everything
Is not open to interpretation
It just can't be otherwise
We get places where it's like
We think there's voter fraud so there was
No
At their end of certain point something is or is not we can't live in
And no this is just how I am
Interpret things
Like that's just not how we can share a universe yeah
Completely different people
Four different people
What
Listen I voted for Jo Jorgensen
I voted for the libertarian
We should probably
Third-party candidate
Cuz that's one of the solutions
I'd love to grill him on Jorgensen
I guess it doesn't really matter since it's California
I would love to see how much
Fake ass
Look I don't
Trump
Does it
Support the Democrats
Cuz I'm an iconoclast
You don't know shitt
Screw you
Again
Dmca
Complain
Copyright
Claims put on episode
People are saying
Music off otherwise
And back to this xclusive
All-you-can re-uploaded clipping out
The Ellen Show
Ford.com
What does his desperation for Meemic
Do you have to give blank
I get permission to use got2b
I don't even remember what this is about
Does next class
No not remember
I was worried about
Smiles and loves
Cuz he starts
Thinking about how
Psychologist
So say like
What you think of
Isn't always
Happier
Microcosm
His relationship to animals as relationship to people
I don't understand why you don't take me
You're all
You're all nature none of us nurture
They are up here though they have soul
They have mined
They have decisions just you don't
The elite
Ultimate therealreal he'll run in the lower class
Elitism what existed before the German
And then in modern Psychiatry and psychology
200 years ago
That's what I'm coming at here is it doesn't mean that
Things a predator
Real human trait
Coulter Gill blocking us from a larger issue because
Your dog is Magic
Your dog does have a soul
It does have an energy
It is smiling
You are interfacing
Dogs are psychic buffers way more cycling we are
That's why I'm saying is your dog
Is his example of what Humanity to go towards instead of somebody like Bill Gates
We should be less like Jesus
It's meaningful. Just scream out I don't want to learn
How do they say something different than me
Someone telling me that my
My cat smiling doesn't
I mean she's happy what does it what does it mean question
Purring isn't always like showing
Love or happiness how can I make it better
Am I also don't question
The
Bonds that we have
I'm not tied up in
If a psychiatrist said that the cat doesn't feel ever
Everything you think
It's feeling all the time that's because
I'm not interested
Projecting my feelings
Pet friend
I don't understand why people
I don't know I don't care
So far
About the idea that
People have valid
Good criticism
In this next clip I think this is black ice
Listen Alex you got to think of what it's like to be a 20 year old
Who is friends with
The bunch of other twenty-three-year-old
Kids and a spouse of
Rigid
And with someone
Besides Urology
Audiology says maybe
The guy's not a bad guy maybe
Like a psychotic moment maybe had a bad time
Maybe he believed it because he see
Being so much
Said he seen so many lies
Crazy
Crazy cuz he's on his own
Because nobody
What's the stand up and say
Hey he's right about a lot of s***
Bastille
Psychotic
What Joe is presenting
This idea
The only people who are really
Critiquing Alex or 23
He rolled socially
Uncomfortable with
That they have of saying hey maybe Alex is right about something
Ridiculous
Yeah that's very frustrating end
Almost suggest a a sort of
Distance from
People really live
They could only really come about
Billion dollars
This is why because all their 23
Year old friends are in 1/8
Crazy how
Actually
Twenty-three-year-old
Men
Who are afeared
It's all those
Non Alpha men
Carrying a gun right now
People don't
Expect everything
We Believe without questioning us
And a real problem
Is there a like Scott left out in the wilderness
Problem
You can if you're wrong rather about something
I'm a human being and your perspective is valuable and one of the reasons why you were wrong about this
Mustangs
Is because you were abandoned
It was so many people that didn't
Hitch sarkar
Do your train
Is there a scare
Conspiracy in the Bohemian Grove
Conspiracy
And the f****** Bilderberg conspiracy
It was so many different things that led people down on comp
Uncomfortable conversations
Didn't want to be a part of it
Who just left you alone
And
When people
Get
Band
All of the other people around them
Possibly
Haven't
You're correct
You start going
Is it okay okay
We've all seen Good Will Hunting
Speaker
But you ain't that was
That was f****** Matt Damon as like I under pressure
This is like giving that same
Pep talks to John Wayne Gacy and be like look a lot of people just don't understand why you're
You're doing what you're doing
But they're just not ready to challenge themselves
I disagree here's what I think
Be like
Haven't killed all those people
I meant someone
His friend look
You know
Problem was
You didn't have friends around you telling you not to dress up like clowns
Define
I don't know deposition of Paul Joseph Watson
Bad thing he's done in his career
These are the people bitching about participation trophy
The most likes Hey look
Just cuz you failed a million times upwards to the tune of millions of dollars doesn't mean you're not still great
Its participation trophies and personal responsibility
And ideas like these people
They keep repeating it over and over and over again
And here you have like Alex it's not your fault people just left you
That's why you had to say
I think a lot of people's criticisms
Entitled
Man
23 year old is worried about the bead that goes around
Could be that you're right
So
You are
Hearing something like Alex
Exposure
How do you how would you hear that
Like a punch to the
I'm not using you as interview but you're so big in the system
What's a watch
You're doing
Get messages through when you're on the show
So one of the things I want to say to the left is
The left the average one person left
Cool
I hear Alex say
I'm not using you
People will listen because you're here as
I'm using you right now
Understand
How you could be friends with Alex for this long
Without
Finding out who
Is rhetorical trick
And then doing the thing
Literally
He does that every
Alex's son name to show I'm not bragging
Exactly
I'm not doing this I'm not using you
I'm using you
Everyone I don't hang out with him real life only on the context of this show
Occasionally
And I picked up on that real fast
And just because it's like
I think it's
Kind of indicative
Some stretches of this episode where it's like
Caribou
You ever have Kopi Luwak
Coffee
Oh my God
That's why I'm a Razorback though
Kopi Luwak
Coffee
Is coffee that comes from a civet
Isa Coffeebar crapser
And then people collect
And clean them up
Selam
Anna makes the best
Coffee
It's so good
It's really good
Like its
It's a cat
I guess if it is kind of a cat is like
That was trying to stalk you
But I want to show a lot
Hey you got
Don't catch tell Joe you.
This weekend
Yeah
That animal shoots out
Coffee beans
And then
Super expensive
Expensive
It's called Copa
Yeah
It's really good
Wow
Great I've been on road trip
And there is one
I will remember forever
Because
The two people in the back just started having such a boring conversation while I was driving
I drove so much
Faster cuz their conversation was
That is the worst
Stop being friends
With people who had that conversation
I just sort of
Is a couple
That was one of them
Temples
Don't know what's going on
Did This Is Us on purpose is going to stop
You can edit
Message
Get across on this episode
We need to get rid of tribalism
Get over that
And start looking at each other ideas
Here is I would like people to stop criticizing rich white man
Maybe
That could be a
Dealing
With the remnant
Of a Savage path
People kill people
With stone
Axe tools
Now we deal with Kimbrell's nothing
My point is
We're connected with this idea
Absolutely have to
In opposition with each other
It's nonsense
That's the way
Weaknesses not
Like flip-flopping or
Considering your opinion
The real
Is
The really thinking
People that
March
Different
The way they look at
Thanks
Those people are your enemy
That's what I want
Do you know who you're talkin
Imaginary enemies
Looking for the literal devil
Just like this
He's a fine
Farcical to be making it
While sitting next
Alex
Jones
You know what you should do after this you should ask
What he thinks about
Kratz
Literally
Wow
Call my God
It's a it's a flying saucer
Would like that
Tubi
Perfect world
And it can only
Only come about in an all-white Nation it seems like that's kind
Volvo dealer
Yeah
Parts that he kind of
Focuses on
Maybe those tribalism parts of the worst ones
Now we start
We have to overcome it though
I think
The thing that is
Mos Def
Difficult to overcome
For the understanding
The reality of the universe
White male havior
In opposition to you
Switch a righteous and true and good
But if I don't have problem with somebody can overtake me
I don't like read Elizabeth
Like I don't want a government
Government
Limited government
Protect me from
Right
I think maybe
The solution is an understanding of tribalism
And then an agreement
Animal people
It should look at those
Good versus bad
Positive versus Sin
Local christian cosmology
What is a sin against humanity
I think being a chickenshit
Coward
Sins Against Humanity
To listen to
Dumber people
Have a conversation
That was famous for happening 2,500 years ago
What does it say this is the problem with so much like on
Course
Debate
People who are self-taught
Realized
You think are so revolutionary
You might encounter
Your first year in college
These points
Blown
Also I mean like
As a
Good faith actors
Okay now this is interesting
Very call Joe are on the right track buddy
Tribal
And then
If people
We get two extra boom
Look at a B.
How is society organized in Italy
Give people up
Larger than 1,000 we have to have a fine for being
Foolish
Forcible in any way
Absolute
Use out population
But they don't think about that cuz they've never been the vulnerable population getting cracked out
Here's what I used to think
Blown away by this very conversation
What's the reason I thought people who spent their entire life studying this type of thing
Having a conversation in that becoming popular
That for me I thought
Was that it would be too dry
Boring
This conversation is more boring than anything I can
Chicken takeout
This Is tragically boring and multiple going to watch that
Further Tire life study
Yeah I had I have
I don't know
It's not for me to say because I guess I'm not a normal person
Necessarily
Channel 36
Different. Of my life is maybe the Target demographic of you
But like
I think a lot
Think of like college lecturers
Academic conversation to be really boring
This is f****** boring
The differences
If you engage with the academic stuff
You probably work something
Alex
Because
Just talkin about this need to overcome
I think there's a sense of
You don't get it
You don't get the higher-level.
Things that I'm imagining imagining is stupid
PDS
World
And it's disappointing to me
Yeah
Despite all that disappointment
And we can prove it
Glenn Rashad a video during the contested election
Dressed up I dress up like
In a wheelchair
Wet running around
Was Apple
The capital
And we smoke
Every single time these to talk
It's story comes up
Maybe there aren't that many memories suggest
They got high and ran around the Capitol and masks
You know I think
That the basis
Like the stories for any friendship
Should not be I guess you had to be there stories
You know
This story is one where I'm like
Maybe if I was there would be funny but this is
I've seen it
How much fun
It was like in a 99-2000 it's just your
Free
You know like such a different time
Grunge
Maybe a few years I just think it's kind of depressing
People who only have one story
Every time
Gaston song that story comes up
Yeah
Read it again
Another thing
Mentality that Alex has
Being like
Rogan with this like
Get rid of all this
Nearby
I don't have a hundred million dollars
This is this is Alec
Expressing
You know his nationalism is basically a cult
Because he mad
Enemies are also called
But I guess
Creating my own enemy
Destroy myself
I don't understand what you don't understand
I'm creating my own enemy to justify really f***** up
We have 20 nationalism which is failed
Is Colton
But
Humans organized and called
Our nature
You're at that point Joe
I can see up on the mountain
Get where you're going
I'm just saying
We are at a crisis though
It is
The Nationals called
A free market
Money and family a God and guns and everything's going to counter the chai cam
Where man you are taking hours a day do you complain your ass is dead
Because the global model is kind of China
And honesty is there taking off
First of all
Whenever
You're in a situation
Where are your coming to me
For Global advice
We got real problems
I think there's a human
I appreciate that
F*** are you at
Unfortunately
He does continue and give an idea of how
You should have stopped
You shouldn't ask me
Honestly I do
Looking ugly
Wave a magic wand
Mega Mall do mushroom
Cuz all of them
Everybody
Anybody in a position of power anybody walked into an ideology
Anybody
Nonsense
Anybody who
Leave things
They know
Truly Queen
Fight for them to know people that know
Bolivar true how dare you
This
Weird f****** Dario people
Pigeons
But
But then, go crazy, go crazy
Yeah
Kids break the law
Millwright
Or something
This is
I mean
This is embarrassing at spectacular
Opens like 50
Switches
To learn and really condensed
Sit still further down
Fungus
Israel-palestine
Breathe
Is bran
Really, he's just doing this
Play imagine if your job is to essentially be high all the time
Piano
Benson didn't stop
Doing weave
Jokes
He got 250-plus
Experience circumstance
Yes
Universal basic income
Did not say anything it's not a miracle cure it's roast
The contradiction you take mushrooms extremes yet loud hippy-dippy bullshittin
It's true political philosophy
Everything
Most on my trip
Was just like a progressive tax
As intended
This
In a box Circle the guy coming out of the mouth of someone wearing
Blown glass necklace
I don't expect this out of there
Cheese
You didn't get to be 100 millionaire
Dignity or learning
Things
Picture of
Read the magic word in the world that shrew
The person who
Is baked
The people most deserving as of a slap to the face the most famous and rich people available
Good at martial arts
Alex reveals that he's probably taking some hallucinogens
Leaving done acid
He got jokes
2020 Houston
But 89 years ago Joey Diaz
Well
Joey Diaz Joey Diaz hands me a
Cookie in Houston
Couldn't get out of the chair
Then we got to crawl around like to know how I do I get
Christianity destroyer of globalization
UFC fight
Alex
I want to see Joey Diaz
I can't I can't provide
There was a time
Studios
I did not know that we can cover that future episodes
Because he's screaming
I remember way back
I tried to prepare it was just like
Holyshit this is incoherent
The baby before I go back now
Phpne smells like piss
Call Good Guys survive in prison
This is this
This is another instance
This is
What his goals were
With having Alex on his paw
Podcast
I would say this is
What he does
Wanted to achieve
Is 2/2 people consider
That there's people that have wild
Different ideas that you do
That may be good guys
Maybe it's
People that have ideas of you
Consider
That's a good guy
And if you
You and Alex
We're hanging out
With me
And Eddie Bravo
And we were all together we be f****** laughing
Will be laughing hard
We be it would be fun
Ridiculous
And if you're not in that room
Is easy to judge
Well guess what guess who's not in that room millions of people who are watching
You're saying like oh yeah I just wanted to show that it's a fun experience
Hangouts
Meanwhile
Secede
Accidentally
I don't know
Could you
I know that's probably an extreme
Yeah okay
Yeah you can't get along
What gerbils
Never find out think so
I just don't think he was that kind of guy
Is it real soon
Alex
I got a bad qiq you would have fun
If you were in a room with
Me and Alex Jones Eddie Bravo
What if you were a f******
Muslim woman
Not much fun
Across from you is saying s*** like I want YouTube
What if you were not awake
Guy
Person of color
Okay
Anyway
Here's what I would say
How do that
Did you have a responsibility to not allowed to talk about anything
Conspiracy related anything political
If your goal was just to talk about
Talk about college
High School
Slick talk about that stuff
You do not talk about the globalist
You don't talk about it
Because
Where is misinformation
Especially don't
Call back
You can always go back to and say Hey look
We had him on our show and
He checked out
If you think something's wrong I'll tell you when I looked at
Case of water
To play both games at the same time
That you were fun
F***** up with you and
Tacitly support
Are conspiracies like that's not
You can't pretend that you're fact-checking him
How do you spawn
Cuz you're doing me a
It's almost as though he grew up kind of choosing the path of least resistance
Get along with everybody around him and just kind of
So I will say
Comfortable
With how much Alex wants
Start
Play masias
What is it like to be
Lee Maine
Oracle
Jimmy Carson was this guy
Every other itemized
Fanboys is a close second or whatever this matter is not about that
You're the position of being the Oracle was that like
Oracle of Delphi right now
But you definitely not helping me with your
Description of
Is not accurate
North Citrus
It's redic
Oculus
He's a little bit more playful when he saying it's
Disrespected
He is uncomfortable and he should be
Be comfortable with that
Interviews
People
Conversations
Call Jimmy Carson man had some of those great joke see you soon
Who's on Jimmy Carson
That's why we got into store
Jimmy Carson
So what are the things that I think
Big point that I made early on
Podcast
Get life now cuz I still like him nearly as much as
I used to dislike him more
I still do believe
But I think
Probably less important
He used to fill
Is kind of
Good role in society
The kind of guy
Who will freak you out
And maybe
Brothers
Friend or something who tells you about the CIA or whatever
He's a voice that there is
Place for in society
Conspiracy theorist
You know.
Behave the way that Alex does
The guy who's not also
Complete racist
Big
Throwing around
Demon s*** all the time
Without malice
Yeah
Is a place for that I think Joe
He touches on
Why
Alex
Has anything
Because there was a place
Youfit in
You taught me a lot of things
Like I said earlier
About
People using
Departments or other
Law enforcement or whatever
To start
Smashing
Polite protest
Violent protests
Like until you showed me last stop at agent provocateur
I really had no idea that anybody would ever sink like that
I had this naive
Perspective
The thing a lot of people have
People that are in
Government
People that are real
Leadership
They really just want the best
For the citizens
Superior
Discussing these kinds
YouTube
Fortunately
The double-edged
It's so clearly demonstrates
But yes
In the 90s
Alex
Did the idea of agent
Snitch
Right
And ended up
Being a guy who
Can shift into psychic spaces
His lawyer is a little to cop
Located now his skill set
He's a show that went on too long he's ending the Game of Thrones
Success
The reason
He got like millions of dollars and ended up at 9
Pretty
Successful
Making a good living
Being a conspiracy theory talk show host
But you got to
Being like
Famous I've always just wanted
What is life is like a comic like I want to live
Comic live I don't want
Millions Auto 100000000 enough
Too much
End up being
To do
Whatever it is you need
Because once you start going down there
When you start worrying about pill sales you start to think about like what are the things that I'm doing
Gets the most attention.
And then
You know it's no longer hey here's a boring conversation but the reality of Aging
Provocateur
And what you need to know about the history of this tactic right
Becomes everybody
Pretend
Because it's exciting
Because you're
To educate
Or whatever
It's
Now marketing
That's it
The idea of
Not trying to be a millionaire in doing every single possible step you can take
To get there
Is a
Radical socialist,
Bulshit Dan and you're on my list
Where is Alex
Years ago turn Joe on
Interior
This is what he does now
I'm in Arizona 3 weeks ago I got a call from the White House
Mommy
Sun
Do you need to look into
Dominion and communist China and Switzerland also
Call this guy
This guy calls me up
Company
That's why I probably look at it
We get all the SEC documents running boards all the news today
Why are you telling me this
Michelle's of you as a conduit
I'm almost like is that
Describe
Is a setup
It's about something like they can do that with someone
Qanon
Twitter accounts and stuff
Conspiracy that
He laundered
Are they doing this to discredit me
Yeah
That moment of self-reflection
Action was very strange
You forgot that you said
Becky was your score
Sensitive
I think that they're trying to
To discredit
Lying and telling these intriguing stories to joke to keep his attention
What is a what's the percentage of people
Uses about 60% of the national election
49%
You're off your election
The whole metric with Trump they had a overturned about
99%
Do you know that for a fact
66.7%
I was just making s*** up
Because Jose attached to the messenger
He's explaining it
Is attention
He likes to do in order to disseminate this information and
Fuc yourself
These talking
Did people look up to Joe and they respect him he's sitting there
He's allowed to stand
Exactly
Again
Is
Attention
You can see that very clearly
Imagine being like this
Hot chick 1963
Well
Was looking at number five.
Alex
The Hot Chick
Back in 62
When it wasn't that many of them
Instagram models
Maryland
Come down
How dare you keep saying that
The baby doll
What's up this is like
The bean gold
Bienvenue
Cringiest s*** I've ever heard
Just he's
Tickled by the idea that him saying come dub
You mean gold
Well
Play this on our show it's really disgusting
Different kinds of disgusting
And then there's the disgusting of like
Ascetic
How badly you want
Yeah
Make a meme of all the time
Everything that he's saying it's like kind of
Grossen offense
He's been tagged
So sad
Also sad
Alex makes a claim about something
Bill Gates
Because
Alex
To drop in
Proof
Cathy's clown
Alright
Four five times
None of it proves anything
Example
Is
Outrageous
If you're listening
I would
Listen to
All the time edited later
This is what you chose
This is your guy
Oh don't worry the Japanese TV Go
This going to kill people
It's for the
Uses for other countries.
It's exactly what you said is representative
How many times have I told you
Boy you go down Crazy Town Santiago let you know I have a math how he said his territory
More defended you
Vaccine cause damage
People not liking about onions
Japan-china United States are not the target
We have special vaccines for other countries
That's not at all
I mean it was like
He said
I don't know if I'll find it
Can't you take somebody who's
Putting in my case
Sing to these tools for infectious diseases
Infectious diseases
Pandemics
Crazy situations
We need to find
Make it
Including countries
Have the resources to pay for vaccine research relaxing
Anyway should be the priority for what we do
Text
That I'll explain
To prove
If you guys get a different vaccine really feel like
It certainly didn't prove anything
Say that
He has such a
Swims
Reality
He hears that clip and that's what
Thanks Bill Gates
Believe that
Like he's so smart
He's reading it but yeah I would assume
The most generous explanation
Make sense
Because it literally says everyone should get the vaccine and we should focus on countries who can't make it for themselves
A priority Global issue
Countries problem
I don't
I like to say I do
Don't get it I don't understand number of
1 is
Alex
Is
He is a consumer of b*******
And he thinks
You never watch the clip about National file or whatever
He watched it
He interpreted it as
Completely
Phineas putting it in later
And so
It's so
Sad fusing
Why would you do that
You know
So you can save it
Dependent
The word is is what you will
Probably even planted the idea
Bill Gates
You pick out
Interpretation of his face what I assumed
I know it's like I'm going to tell you what you're about to hear
Doesn't say what you're about to hear
You just think of people just like not really pay attention
You played a clip of Bill Gates it must have sex in the bathroom I'll skip this
Rogan's
Meatheads
The potheads
You can print them
That's fair
That is fair
Once again
Takes issue with people who
Critique his podcast
Interview with Alex
Is also not a good
There was a lot of people that got tricked
Attracted
Something other
Oz description
More people of that
Then listen to
What you don't we did 3 hours
How many
How many Breakout
Some crazy
They listened
3 hours and 20 minutes
Do they do that
Yeah why would we do that
That's a person salt
That is better
Set is not a broad deliver
That's you specifically
Most tragic about that is I don't have a good answers why would people listen to hours of someone
They hate
Described
20 hours like
Screw you talking about YouTube
Talk
I do understand that deflection of like
Really long people couldn't possibly listen to it
Way more painful
24-hours I was three and a half or whatever
Two hotdogs
Platform and he has to have some
Semblances
Amex played out on Joe show
Interesting
Switches stretches
Of nothing
And Alex being so famous
This is a 2% of me as a person smoke Circle and that's the worst
Possibly
It doesn't have the Showmanship chops
Being on Alex's purpose
The problem
Is
Because he'll just talk about how he ate
Her drink some coffee that gross
Good how come
I feel like this must have been in
Pieology
I feel like this has to be a thing
Come on by
Get drunk and record something
I feel like it has to be some
I don't know it's a real bummer exist other than for them to get attention
It's absurd
Wild Mountain thyme which exist
Self-assured
Westcliffe
Alright well I'm 27 years
And Joe Rogan
The best
4 hours ever spent
Thank you so much for us about this world
That's what's outrageous what is a district
The best shell
I like ideas man
I do
I like ideas that's why I like listening to
Is that I don't agree with
Craigslist
Because I like
Finding
Things like
Just wouldn't normally
Come up in conversations with people I enjoy and I find interest
Turnleaf
Be overlapping without
Specific Project Camelot
I like ideas
Weirdest ideas that you can possibly get let's fly in the face of danger and see if something
Beetroot juice
What is 1
True dance
Just like Joe was a million times
There we go
Outside
Nothing ever presented on the show
I think it was a disaster
I just thought that I
Have never been able to escape
Ever since I was like really really young
There's like whenever I was like 10 years old I remember hearing all of my friends have this conversation
And I remember
Being in the middle of the talking about I remember
There's no possible way
10 year old
End
1990 blue
Having an
Interesting
So
If I'm having a conversation
Sick for a second
Did somebody have this conversation several thousand years ago
And then maybe just read
Maybe read instead of being like
So here's what I think about the universe and what we should do
Who is we should give
Everybody you know like
We got to get Elizabeth we got to do shrooms
Maybe somebody f******
Thought about it before
Important
Exploring ideas conversationally is
Social
Productive
I certainly know for
From listening to this
I don't know I am
I come over
Distill down
Winx
Left vs right tribalism
Wants to talk about protection there's no possible way
We could be
Correct
The point that hours
Want to talk about how famous Joanne
And how great it is that he's on Spotify
Alex
Generation
It's just
Like I keep saying
Yeah
Exposing his
He's vulnerable
Underbelly of
Desperation
What's what
Wild to me
Is ostensibly
These are two proof
Professional broadcasters
How can you have this
Conversation
When you've been doing
This
Or some facsimile of this job this very job that you are doing
For 20 or 30 years and you come up with
This
This is what you got
The Jimmy Carson of our time
You are no Ed McMahon sir
If you got
I think I might have
Also only decided to do this episode
Because I came up with the title for it
Not a charm
Discussion
DC it was living in a tenement
Fingers crossed
Price on Twitter
It's at now
Dramatics
You could please
To try out that right
Holding
Alex
Christian coloring