Damn important
I have great respect for knowledge B I'm sick of them
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Acknowledge
Looks around at novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
What's up cereals
I have gone wild radio serials like the shadow like that was what I was saying
I mentioned to you that I have been
Exploring the world of ordering grocery
Cindy for the sake of safety
More Brown
Then maybe I'm used to it a grocery store
I kind of get in and get out at a grocery store generally I kind of know what I'm looking
Infor
Eat that many
Wearing blinders at the grocery store the frozen pizza section
Conjunctiva
And go home
Browsing through I've noticed
But there are a number of cereals now
That really excite me but also offend me
These are the cereals where everybody
He's playing each other's game
How come everyone is in each other's lanes and I don't know what's going on is like
Kellogg's Rice Krispies will suddenly have like a peanut butter balls
Hopscotch
They have like Fruit Loops with marshmallows
And it's weird because like when I was
The kid I probably would have loved this
Yeah but now it now is 36
Gotta gotta try it
Everybody's fighting on a corner wall
What's the drug war mall over
One thing I was thinking about doing but I'm not sure I'm going to be able to pull it off because I don't know if I'll actually be able to
How to get all of them
And I don't know how many of these hybrids there are but it seems like there's a bug
I was thinking about trying to get a bunch and
Seeing who steals other people's gimmicks
Best okay like alright
Does Frosted Flakes
Is that improved with marshmallows
I don't know how it would work and I know you the chocolate Frost
I tried those
They're delicious
For the first three bites and then you're like I'm not four years old anymore so this much sugar is going to kill me yeah
I think there's probably a lot of that is what I would find
I did
Get the
The Lucky Charms
But with like the
The regular
Pieces that aren't marshmallows who are short hard like honey
No
I like regular looking
They're good
Do you like how many people are trying new stuff whatever it's like
Guys
I have been with Lucky Charms for foot
It's like I've been smoking Newports
Since I was nine years old and you guys are going to come up with some b******* like the Camel Crush
That's the first time the Camel Crush happening like this isn't
Affront against God how dare you combine these two flavors
But then
My bright spot Dan is the Avalanches release a new album
The Avalanches released two albums in one decade
Blowin your mind is
Yeah I was like wow
15 years between you and whatever they came out with
And then just now we Will Always Love You released
Friday absolutely fantastic school I don't want to be a hater but I didn't really like their second album as much
I like since I left you second I used to
Smoke a lot of weed when I was younger I left you is kind of genre busting in that they really
Took sampling too far
Yeah they were like paste
What if
I know you like he amen break and will
Strengthening
Instead we took 48
Ms and combined with 48 MS
Top 10 million other songs like I was just the right age and like I said smoke weed
Frontier psychiatrist like blew my mind everybody
Music videos
Totally
I don't know how any other album Bay made could not kind of be a letdown
Based on the experience of that at that time
But I'll try
An open mind for this other new one
Music forever and then their next album was a really good album if you're good
Producers but they
It's not
You know I can get on real busting era-defining South I think
The problem is the
Decade in
Between like if you put out a sophomore album
It's just serviceable or just good
Sure next 2 years
Understandable then like
Waiting for Chinese Democracy just being
Do that
That is fair
It's got a bunch of really good guests on it they do a lot of like
Classic trip hop seven almost SoundCloud
Play It's Tricky
They got some disco and then they got some classic Avalanches walk
Can songs which is what the Avalanches do bad
I'll check it out
Sing episode to go over
About the weekend
Jay-Z that guy
Whenever his first
I don't know enough about the weekend
Where you be talking about
The day that was
12 12 2020
The other day out on
DCU
Alex didn't move to DC
EBid
Did Eazy-E would go and be taking a look at some of the events
On The Venetian
Capital
I'll get to that let's take a moment Jordan to say thank you
To sign up and are supporting the show
So first bambuser
Bamboozled
Jim F thank you so much
Can you ride that's what I'm calling all Ryan's go for it
Next
Just could be gel okay
Je
Elle I think it's probably gel
Thank you so much you're now policy walk
I'm a policy should be a reference to cat
I'm going to go with
Jelly. Jellicle
Michelle is going to
It could be a jellicle walk I don't know if they had one of those in the original cats
Next bereft
Thank you so much and I apologize
Text Willow thank you so much
Text Rebecca
Thank you so much no relation
You're about to
Rebecca took up people donated on elevators
Nbk thank you so much
Technocrat
And it goes on thank you so much you are now attacking
I'm a policy wonk
What's the business
Money off that heroin
Santa goes on
Both of you
Dollartree.com
Or what you could do is
You can go to a record store go back into the back part of the Wrecker
Good stores start searching through all your favorite bands maybe some disco bands
People haven't seen find some generosity in their little bit to the best generosity from each one of those little crates
Over their combined it together to make something amazingly generous and take it
To your local bail fund or
Tip
Jordan
Today
What about it
We are going to be talking about
The rallies
What happened to DC over the weekend
One thing that's really difficult for me is I'm not
Going to be addressing really the
Street violin
That is a failing of our show to Anna
Extent because I don't have enough time
To get into it
I'm not on her show I mean in terms of like cover it
With the seriousness
The the focus that I think
Think the topic deserve where is silly show about Alex
Yes I don't want
To give short shrift
Do that but at the same time
It's all slightly outside of what I have the time to
To cover half-assing it is sometimes worse than doing anything at all
But I did not want people to think that turn a blind eye to that kind of thing or or
Tacitly accept
Such
Jordan on Saturday there were multiple rallies that were happening in d.c. surrounding the idea that this election
Had been stolen
Stop that steel you know what I'm saying
Sure they're both about the same thing had the same theme and even featured some overlapping speakers
It was super confusing
But I think I know what was up
What are the rallies of being held by the women for America first
The group that formed out of
The Tea Party would just trying to use these protests and some of this unrest
To secure more power for the Republica
Can party while simultaneously trying to make the Republican party as weird as possible like they did with the pee part
Correct
The other rally was called
The Jericho March
Which made no secret about just being an overtly
Christian extremist rally
Put some really outrageous plan speakers
Well if I remember my story of Jericho well
I believe those people where the nights
Decided to end the siege with negotiating
Coming to AAA
Fair solution for both parties right
Jericho March and Ali Alexander
Girlfriend from Infowars rate
They also have the Cowboys for Trump
Congressmember Paul gosar
It's really hard for me to tell what
Exactly what's going on
These two were opposing rally
Your Instinct review think that the Jericho March was for the religious zealots where is me women for America
The first will be the more restrained one
But honestly the rallies were almost identical
Not all the same people but it's the same
Both featured Mike Flynn given the same speed
Both had appearances from and got funding from the my pillow guy
Overwhelmingly really
Watching these rallies one
It's abundantly clear to me that something
That is very important for us to bring up his
We're not dealing with Paula
Tixier at all
This is not
This is a cult with some interest in politics as a means
To gaining
And retaining power
I don't really know how to talk about
Without like
I don't know I don't know how I don't I don't know how to engage with the ideas of a cult
I mean I think
The best way to engage with the ideas of cult
Is on a grand scale and what we should
To do to stimulate the economy is train 50% of the country in cult deprogramming to help them with the other 50 per
Like the new deal I think that's a good way to do it it's like the works progress administration
It's just it's really difficult because it comes off or it
Can be like Michigan
Construed as attacking religion
Show me with tack this kind of thing that's going on and I don't have any interest in attacking religion or Christianity I have a
Problem with what
This is
That's Tuff
The 10-year person say that Bill Gates said X Y or Z an interview it's really easy to go find that interview and just
Discuss what's going on
What do we cure that same person say that God has chosen Donald Trump to be president
It's not too difficult to save their bit of a fanatic and I probably unwell
The difficulty
Becomes when there are two moles
The our rallies attended by thousands of people where the speakers
Heatedly it incessantly insist that God has chosen Trump to be president
And everyone cheers
That's
Tough
That is really f***** up
Yeah
We know where Alex is at we know where his head is we know what he's up to
Hey that's all I thought maybe a good use of our time today would be to
To look at these rallies themselves
Assess where we're at with all the
And see if it's something that we can
Learn to talk about a little bit better
And
See if there's anybody who pops up
Who is a
Particularly good crazy though good maybe there'll be somebody who's like
This is
Daryl is
Hangouts
No but I figure like hey you've got
I think each rally was at least
4 hours long Cheese's
You got a lot of speakers maybe somebody is going to be like
Alright
You got something I bet you got a weirdness out I'm going to be in
Alright that's worth our time
So we're going to start here Jordan with the Jericho March
This was hosted by Eric metaxas
Kind of aware of who this guy is he's like a Christian writer and a radio host
But I really don't know what time about him
Based on his work m
I'm seeing this event
That will probably be the way it
It's days because this dude is straight-up boring as hell
A whole lot of awful stage patter type
Material and then
Just calls to praise the Lord
We're starting with the one that's more it
Who is Italy religion
And and you get that right from there we're going to get some Ace Frehley band talk and then we're going to smooth into the
How dare you
Yes it does have something she needs to get off his chest
Becomes anxiety what's up DC alcohol
You alright let's overthrow democracy forever
Call Jeff alright no it doesn't start with that
We are here
Because we loved
The god of the Bible
We are here
Because we believe
He is the god of History
We're here because we know
But he is the god
Who does
Real
Miracles
When his Remnant Cries Out
To him
In humility
And love
And says
Abba Father
We need you ABBA
Call Father
We are here too
Today
To the god of Heaven
To ask him
To have mercy
On the greatest nation in the
History of the world
Just pretty
It's pretty overtly religious that one's a little bit on that knows maybe
15 seconds into the
The rally
Where you at
We were worshiping the god of History
Alright
This rally
Itself this Jericho March
Was the product apparently
Two people
Who had a vision
And Eric metaxas is going to
Discuss that here
Another man
And the woman
Didn't know each other
Until a little while ago Robert Weaver and Arena grossu okay
Each of them in.
Hendon Lane case you didn't know the
The story
Each of them
Had an insane
From God
Rob Weaver
Told me this
Story a few nights ago
He says he didn't normally doesn't normally get Visions like
Yes in the Lord
Woke him up it's a dramatic
What story
And he had this insane
Open
Vision
Of peace
People
Gathered
Blowing shofar as there were nuns there when he described it to me exactly
The bad news is
It look nothing like this and you guys need to leave right now
I was kidding
That was a joke
A vision from God
You don't need to know anything else
You Just Praise Him
But he cares enough to show you what he is doing
Vision questions to will learn more about this Vision later
The thing that I think is interesting is like that is a terrible joke
I would have to go with yes that is
Is a terrible joke at the same time
He's doing
And I think actually
If I were the promoter or the booker of this is a
No he's doing great
It's not offensive but you can still tell it's an attempt at humor
Yep he's personable to the audio
That's the target of this rally
Trash
Memorabilia bad joke where you're like
Joke registered you know what I'm not going to hold it against you we're just going to move
It does feel like somebody who's there for a check
Forgot to clock in
Yeah I've done those
Before it's almost a cut and paste
Least kind of host
Joke you see a lot of that if you do enough stand up
Kind of get that vibe from him but at the same time
I kind of prefer that
Someone who's maybe taken
2 biggest swing a lot of money too
I see this guy trying to
Do crowd work at one of these rallies
Would be brutal
So we got these two people their division one is Rob Weaver
Evangelical Christian
So the two of them both had
We'll meet them a little bit later but
That's why this is happening
Alright so
This is happening because the evangelico Christians and the Catholics have finally both received the independent message
The drink that they were looking for
Put aside their previous
Doctrinal differences in order to take back
Presidency
Your whole f****** religion boils down to
Trump you pathetic s***
I have nothing against religion I have nothing against Christianity I have a real problem with the way in which
Their beat
Christianity and Trump are being melted
Yeah I mean we were talking about this religion I'm not going to s*** on Christianity as a as like
Quote unquote
Concept or religion
As a whole
But
I will say that it is
Eminently reasonable to s*** on your religion if
If you think
That your ultimate battle of Good and Evil involved
Donald f******
That is tough
To to wrestle with
Yeah your religion is so
Weak and meaningless if that's
If that's what it is
Is it relies on Donald Trump
You hear things like this
And it's just
What
We are what God is doing in the United
Today by his grace
And today
We're going to see
Heaven move
Heaven is going to move
Thank you Jesus
Before I introduce my friend
Mike Lindell who's going to tell you to use
The discount code
Eric
Before I introduce Mike Lindell
I'd like to Lead You In The Pledge
So what he's talking about
God is going to make an avid move and then immediately is going to introduce the my pillow guy and it gives up
Dog
Not give
Promo codes
Mike Lindell does I get that but if you're interested promo code
One of the problems that I find with both of these rallies is they are
Very clearly funded by my pillow
Fonts
Religious rally there's sponsored content I'm a bit worried that is
And that means what
He gets to
Speak
Well you get to walk on Roll by your way internet so my pillow guy
Jesus more than Buy in 5 minutes
Right before this event
You know there had been that Supreme Court
Thrown out the case Shore in Pennsylvania
Yeah they screamed it was to legally good
My pillow guy has some news about this but he received
Powell called him at 2 in the morning
Acordes the front
I got problems with the story
Alarm
Start off
Some home
What else night about 2 in the morning
And she filed
Michigan
Arizona
And everything that I've been telling you
100%
Donald Trump
Buy a pillow wow wow
Set Pennsylvania
Decide attempt to overturn the election mixed up
But yeah so he
I like the idea that Sidney Powell
Texted him and was like eight
Looks like a big setback but that was not our
Deal I'm not even a heart out of another dude I'm in the do-over
I'd like like that
And it's it does set the tone
Kind of for the event and that is everybody is joyous
Turns out that there was this big step backward Texas and
I like all these people it's signed on all these
Republican members of the House
Sidon
Bethesda then it didn't work
It seems like you know that was kind of
Almost like the Ron Paul winning the Iowa caucus
Of this cycle
There's that moment of Hope
Banana it's gone but no my pillow guy says Sidney Powell
Texted him at 2 in the morning
It's a tape be cool
I would buy this making sense if I knew that all of the rich
Republicans in and business owners and all that stuff we're all like
Buying a lot of
The property in a different
Country right now and all of them slowly moving all their stuff away
So I get all this like
Edging with the lawsuits is is them buying time to his to make good their escape before they pull the
The trigger and everybody
Explode
But otherwise
It just doesn't make any sense
What are you doing my pillow you're wasting a lot of money
They must be making a lot too though must be
They don't make any sense they're all magic
I don't know
Also when you consider I mean not
This guy
Do the my pillow guy is
Out there
Batman
Kind of
Person basically listen to talk for like
2 minutes and you like
Why you make Bad Business decisions
Here he discusses in a rambling way
His story of having a prosthetic dream
About how he was going to meet everyone
So he has a dream about how he's going to meet Trump
And then
Hemer
He does and
I am also I want to say really quick he talks a bunch about how he's a recovering
Crack addict
Cool I'm not beating up on that you're not making fun of that at all his just sort of background dressing to this story
I got up to 2,000
Why would I be
Some guy from Minnesota
Well
Carson was still running for president
12 p.m.
But that was
And I'm on a plane
To California
And
I'm sitting in the
It was about Donald Trump
Azusa August 5th
My favorite part of the story is when they struggle to remember the day
Whatever is going on in Ark
I need to know right now
I don't believe that story to believe a word of that b*******
Not for one second
Jesus
Bright
But
Itsfunneh Prado like it
I just did this story is is
Is
I just was listening to some like a man
Is this event
Ventura character
This is Minnesota stuff man
That's what I'm saying
Sound like Minnesota
Sound almost exactly
Vocal similarities
Yeah that matura
That's fair
We need to move
The pressure now
Backcountry
You know what it used to be that when you were sitting on religion that was like
That was often
Discriminatory or being mean now we got to push the responsibility back on there
Religious people if you don't want to be made fun of
Don't listen to the my pillow guy
That's on you now the problem is he has so much money
That's still on you all religion jokes are fine they are non-discriminatory until the
Majority religious people are like
Let's not do my pillow guy
I don't agree I don't agree with that
Axiom
I don't believe I don't agree with that
The issue comes down to like
The religion is fine
But this isn't about religion this is about Watergate
Christian Nation
And my pillow guy
Pretty clear about that
This is been a spiritual battle in our country
He was God
In the name of Jesus.
Wow
I love you Mikey
You know what you want to know miracle of God
He went 62nd Shore
Hahaha a good joke War guys
Killing it
Mike is saying my pillow guy is saying is like
Okay yeah
That was just at 8 like a church Revival or something like that I don't think I'd have any issue with it like
There's an Awakening
Incoming Indianola
The problem is is a political rally
I know it sounds like a religious character but like
The reason you're having this rally is cuz Trump lost an election
Prophetic dream
Combination of the two that's just
Bucking
It's terrifying
I think probably one of the reasons that I would have a easier time
Like
Suggesting
This was
I suppose
John religious is just cuz I know.
Too much about
How Christianity is supposed to work according to that
Buckley they say they like a lot
Read a little bit of it too much about it
And all of this stuff
Is like we're Christians and we want a Christian Nation I'm like
Have you motherfukers even opened
And also here's a promo code for my pillow
Makes me even more scared I think about it is that another's is combination of
Stop this Christian nationalism
And then it's also intersecting with
This
Deification
Admiration and
Just love
Of not only Trump
But also General Flynn
Yahoo is somebody who's a hero the qanon folks
Huey himself
Metaxas
Jesus
Flynn's appearance
In a little bit we have
General
Michael
Flynn is coming
Then you've heard of him
Oh I'm so impressed very good you guys
That's awesome
He is such a hero
He has been through such hell
Patriot
He believes
In The Lord of
The Bible
Alright a lot of people to send a picture of this Administration look Jesus
I don't know he's even saying I don't know what that supposed to mean at all or likewise
The hero and then attacks
Just told you
Because he believes in the god of the Bible
Really don't feel like that's enough but that's
I mean that's what they're saying another problem I have is that they are cheering
A thoroughly fictitious
Just people
Play the imaginary flim
Go to that character whatsoever
Bag
Before history they would if I were him I would lean into the fanfiction today more than
Your actual track record is f******
Metaxas brings out to Rob Weaver and Arena grossu the
Bellco in the Catholic Church
And
I would say the script
Tune of this Vision that he had his a little bit lackluster
This event will be going on for the next few hours left
Speakers more music
But I want to tell you about how it started
On November 5th I was really
Trouble
By the election and what I knew was wrong I think everybody in this country knows
The something
Is wrong in a man anyone
So
I just called out to God and
I literally felt something pushing in my side in the morning quite frankly I thought it was a remote but it wasn't
Somerton was pushing I Heard a Voice that said it's not over
So can I hear it's not over
Because it's not over
And when
And the next part of the vision I set down
And I literally
This
And I saw March
Going around the
The capital
I saw marches going around all six of the swing state
Better also going on today so hello if you guys can hear us there
So every one of them give him a shower
So
This is birth
From
A vision or a miracle
That's not much of a vision
Wow
So does that mean that
Cockroach poking M8 well does that mean that for like say the women's March
Was that inspired by God must have updated or did that did the devil send that
Devil probably
Giving dreams for Bradley's Devils clearly a better organizer
Larger huge to the point where these Margo folk will just post pictures of left
They should get in contact with the Devil
He is a good street team
Video Robin Arena or are just there in
You know they had their vision
Hooray good for them
Had a dream of people walking around DC with
Could never have been given to me from any other source other than God
Have a prayer
It is a lot of prey
People
I threw both of these rallies everybody wants to
To get up there and do the Lord's Prayer
Prayer you know like how in the book it said make
Make sure that you
Prelude
Ugly a
Formatively
For others and not for God
It reminds me of like early times
Wrestling
You didn't want in your first match
Someone to go through a table
Because then if you want to do that in that the headliner back in it.
Yeah I feel like everybody
Is not respect
That in terms of the Lord's Prayer
Like everyone's doing it
Can you
I don't know it's just
It feels less savior Lord's Prayer for the end of
Right order
I mean he's cuter the headliner
To do or not do
I don't know
Anyway they pray and we get a prayer
That Steve pieczenik be very proud
The stage gets interrupt
Father I pray
Special blessing
I Melania Trump
One of the best
First ladies we've ever had in history
And I'm so tired of people
Coming against
Your father so go
Why
I pray and her children
And children in Jesus mighty name thank you Lord
Thank you guys
Actually
When when introduced
Only Alexander
So
What sort of walked out on stage
Walks out along with Ed Martin
I'll be Phyllis Schlafly Eagle for Upper Creek
Sandra apparently partnered with the the Jericho bar
That's kind of interesting
He starts talking about like you know hey we got we got a lot of fun things
Things coming up we got General Flynn
Trust is something that really struck my ears
Today is
We have General Flynn
On the road
Got a couple other characters in the spirit of unification
That's very strange
Also
The presidents in the sky
Promoting is at the Tropicana flyover Marine one grape
And I think he does show up like
Like during Flynn speech
Maybe
I don't know
There was a helicopter flying over at some point
Naughty imagery don't know if Trump was even in it
Why would you
We'll just see the helicopter be like other presidents in there why would you actually go below president
Helicopter window
Of the Eagle Forum slightly eagle
CIA
Type
To give it up to the good media
Brothers Bar
Thank you for what you
Victory
America news I may go down the list and I just want to say
When we gathered at the
Turn on Entry
Time in Taiwan
Looking at America because on the hill
The light go out
Let's pray
One day was conspicuous in its absence on that list
Actually considering
This dude saying
Right next to Allie Alexander
All these great media Outlets really do and everything for his I just
I can't get to a mall I'm going to name as many as I can
Epic
Is great one America news
Look I'm running out of time I can't express
They may not plug Infowars
But
They are willing
To let Alex
Give a little speed
Intuit this point the Mission Impossible theme place
Here Comes
In the spirit of unity
I'd like to bring out my new friend
Alex Jones
I think his name is Alex
Can't believe that many people
Chair for him
You know
See this make sense though
It does is a wrestling
You bring alexandersville
That's what you want and that's why people are tearing
Star
I want to hear Robin Arena grossu talk about their lackluster dream
People would be here for the my pillow guy telling a long story about his dream
I think it was December 20th
19 know who sings this was November 11th December 20th at 4:50 p.m.
Metaxas is a good
Or whatever to keep a thing moving along but he's not going to
To get you riled up
Alex
Jones's that's what he's going to do that's what he's there for
Bury your
The rally made the one that allowed Alex to speak at
So congratulations for that
But Alex does what Alex does and that is
More or less
That's just
Yell his ass off
Yeah but nonsense
Applause line
Jesus Christ
Donald Trump
I thought Obama was the Antichrist
Alexandra
I like the idea of Jesus
Picture of The Giver
I'm the
I'm about peace
I was going to feed all these people okay well just get past that part
Let's just get to the Book of Revelation to realize there isn't a Revival.
Know your mind a little bit more
No one
Clap for that week s*** you know that the Antichrist convinces almost
All Christians to believe in him over
We got a blowout sale actually almost they would focus on like a single person instead
Dead of the Lord and really be like this
Person is the
True leader and we're going to give all of our allegiances to him
Without thinking about it and then because of that I'm like a you sound like a damn Global us you know what you're right
I'm going to have to go
Sauternes
World government
Microchip
Revelation
Jesus Christ
Have you looked
Mark Zuckerberg and the rest album
Nice
They are miserable
What does embarrassing
You get why people enjoy this
Incredibly dumb
Quality
You can also tell if you watch this video
Really takes a lot out of him
Like you can tell it like
He's
Cushing
To get all this Gala going voices exhaust
Yeah
Got to do it
We pray
For president
Arnold
Incredibly
What
World government
Is Publix
Collection
Does every act like you know how to how to frame a sentence
In a way that will end with like
Almost
Not not in like a necessarily badly but like
Comedian
You know structuring
Align do you know what you're saying is funny but the way you've written
It mattered way you're saying that
Is not funny
It doesn't leave
People to the reaction that you're looking for
Every single sentence
Betty saying
Is specifically meant
To make people yell at the end
That's
I mean
Don't do this in the middle of your vet I don't think it's a good idea like you're going to make everyone
What else look like trash
Just don't let him on your show at all how is it that I
I could run a bed
F****** rally
Just using the same principles of booking
Comedy show at you I bet you couldn't do cuz you have no idea who any of these people are
I wouldn't have them at my Rowlett
Turbo what does persons like I wonder if I could do that that would be an interesting chat
Give me 10 seconds of each of these people say speaking and I'll see if I can't make a lineup out of them that would make more sense
Tell me a great idea
I might try but
Alright so anyway
What the big problem that I see with all of this
That's and I'm going to keep stressing
Use the insistence
On what you did
Describe is like Christian nationalism
Any idea that your God is the only real God and right
Just imagining being someone who is not
A
You know a Christian
This stripe in the audience
Think about how uncomfortable you.
On our side
Cuz it's not like it's the Jericho March and you know there is a religious
Just character to it but it's not partnered with Ali Alexander and stop Bastille
And the Phyllis Schlafly Eagle Forum you know
Not just
It's just
I mean everything that they're saying though is screaming out a different form of we cannot color
We wouldn't exist
It's blunts or nothing
Yeah
There is a there is
And to be fair
So far the main speakers that we've heard are the my pillow guy in Dallas
So that's not
You know to be indicative of like everybody is unable to go
These voices that are being
Welcome
Computer
F*** yeah I mean but even then like the best you could say for so many of these people would be like
We can coexist so long as you stay under my boot
Then we'll be fine
So many people who have no idea about anything that has to do with
The religion of
Christianity think that
The crucifixion was a bad thing
You know like oh know if only we could have stopped
Really thinks that
Necessary
Before the
Atonement
It was almost
Preordained if you will
He's not he's not one of these guys would like
Tackled the Roman
Is a good guy
I don't know
Wow that's scary
A tariff
Is the deed to the planet
Yeah that's pretty much the most terrifying things
Somebody could scream at me
Bob turn the sex club Alex gets into the First Amendment and stuff belly freedom of religion
But he's also
Gone too fast
He's he's
He's burned a lot of gas
Yeah he's out of
Yeah
Guess a little trouble
Toddler Show Magnolia
All Roald Dahl religion
Nola
Our forebears did not have separation
That's quite
Extension of the
State has no juries
Is diction over any of us
I'm pretty sure they were conclusion pretty sure they weren't like
Congress shall make no law respecting with respect to the free exercise of religion
But what that actually means is
Christians are free of laws
Yeah if you can just create
Excuse religiously-based
Staying in Paris
Quotes
The state can't do anything like
Can kill for your religion
I don't I don't know I feel like that's what he's saying of putting much yeah but also
It's like
These thoughts are not
Washout
Yellow
There for people
The Scream
Here was Alex's lightning rod
30 put out in order to
I don't know who's going to White House
Nice
Where was the clip that got the big amount of attention on the internet because people fairly accurately interpret that is a Veiled Threat
Towards Joe Biden
I get that response but it's also exactly why Alex said what he said
It's almost certainly not legally ask
Annabelle is a threat
Nick the Secret Service and uptalk
Talking to him about it that's even
Super cool for him would love that
Is it from the Secret Service so you know that what I said was power
Honestly when I heard that I thought was pretty
Tame for Alex
Considering how up in arms people were like your articles
Nobody like that
I guess
It takes on a slightly different character when he's yelling those things in front of a crowd who then
Cheer but if you heard Alex say this and you think that's him crossing a line
All that means is that you never listen
I was going to say I saw his name in the news and I was like oh well
Can't check on that but
If that's what it was for Dan I I have surprise news for a lot of people
Where is an attempt
Contraption
That is a trap
You people fall into and I understand why they do and I honestly don't know
If the best thing to do is ignore it
But if you pay attention to it
That gives him Free Press and that's why he
Implied
Stage
Theta biting would be removed one way or another
I mean I guess with
Alex
The reality is
He has nothing
Tabac that thredup with
At all
And all he gets from it is attention for making
And
You know
I understand why you'd be like
The f*** is going on here
At the same time it's like Alex is going
Alex makes money you because he says stupid s*** like that and you go oh my God no and then we do it all into much
Yeah I mean that's kind of a fever the show
Slows down a little bit want to talk about
My man g-dub
George Washington
President
Who want to be king
Quiet Man
Disbelief
Control Battlefield
So this rally is being held on the National Mall in Washington DC
George Washington's Farm is now a national landmark called Mount Vernon
16 Mi South End in the state of Virginia
Washington's religious beliefs that's actually a matter that even scholars in the field of George
Kimpton studies are fully settled on
Springs up and he is correct
Like Washington was really private about his beliefs
The point is Alex could make that claim about wash
God runs everything and all this in the seriousness of his beliefs
But I would never back that up
Naked never
Prove that
Yeah used to make that claim
It's good
Good for him because like
So even if you were talk
Talking to a Washington scholar they would be able to
He's out more nuanced
Want to choose believe they wouldn't be able to be like you're lying
Yeah
I mean
Looking at what they do with a guy who is alive and real and how they
They created a false
Story for him imagine
We have no chance of them not trying to
Claim the founding father said so I can whatever
True
So Alex
Text talking about how he's God is the real God
Keep your eyes on Christ it away from politics
Like he said
You remember how he said that
Also get ready to overthrow the government
Render unto Caesar what Caesars
Come up later you are making a joke about Jesus standing next to Alex on stage
He's not there and he's not
But somebody is
Little bit down
Little bit down Shroyer's standing there onstage and Alex hands the bike often
This clip of Alex
Saying oh you going to let Owen talk because it's okay
About to do that
It really sounds like that's
Soap roster guard we are having our Easter sale in December
So Alex
Finishes up his stuff
Koreans off
Beaverton to Owen
666 is the devil's number
Doesn't sound right
That's that's Alex
So important numbers
To God yeah he's a real numbers guy
1776 is God's number because the United States was ordained by God to stand up to Nazis I remember that
There's a little complex
City that I mean it's so what happened then whenever we grabbed all their scientists and didn't win then where
Don't like hey could you guys quit being Nazi
And we're just like I use
Can you phrase that question in number form
Owen
He's not a great after that cuz how could you be
I mean
Yelled
Applause line after Applause I usually worn out the audience
Excitement
Sewing
This is so great
God what
A sad man
What we have here today
Chemistry ceviche
So many problems with one man on local access
You pretending that Alex Alex
Did read all of them
Like you created this entire that they're only all there for him
There are
But I know it down
Hellboy you got to do a little admin
At this point Eric metaxas comes out
Danny's got a maybe you know reset the room a little bit
It's like at the Dancehall the DJ can only play so many bangers in a row before you got to have
One where everybody gets to sit down and maybe slow dance scene
I think people got too excited within their flags all around and it's a problem
I got a little house
Keeping
They said to me
Set these flags
In the front when there's when there's a
Speaker they're blocking
The video and this is being wise
Live stream
All over the place
The speaker is speaking or the prayers praying
That means taking them down you probably don't realize
The term drop
Down
With the fly could you do that
Korean flag
What is a tongue Foo martial arts
Because we want everybody's a lot of people who couldn't be here
Need to get those flags down
Nothing weird
That's a weird little bit of
Kostov
I don't know what's going on
I don't know what that he's referring to is
And also there is a brown station wagon
Right now could somebody please it's a brown station wagon
Play tee94 29
So Eddie Gettys gets these flags down
Right for the man the myth
Ali Alexander
And give a little bit of a speech
And he's he's basically out here saying hey man
Now is the time
That moral people
Morrow p
Are deciding whether or not this presidency and this government itself
I think that we are making his
Is when moral Americans are deciding whether our government is legitimate
Or illegitimate
I think this is
Tolerated
That all of us are going to do
Determine whether or not
This is a legitimate government
Exciting thing will be whether or not Trump is
Is installed again
And
Ali is a little threatened
There's an interesting thing
That I notice
Through these two rally
The one with the women for Trump is large
Julie
Not
About destroying the GOP
Okay sure
Ali is threatening the GOP
I like it
I don't know if every speaker here is interested in destroying the Republican Party
But Ali was one of the organizers of this is definitely
Open to that discussion
I think it's a great
Just got in the house
So not only will he destroy the GOP he will also shut down all of the city
Good in this country
Our truckers will shut down the city
Patriots
We can do all things through Christ who strengthens
Gmod Republican pirate my Republican colleagues
Facts of it
Really hung up almost black
Can you walk
To be led by such
Wehner's like now a very soft very soft
So I lie
He's going to shut everything down
And he's going to do this with
The help of
Cool media out
You shut up
Wow
And one America news
And news
That was loud
Epic
End
Never heard of it
We don't need Fox News anymore Dewey
You just had Alex Jones up basically work there
Alex's whole premise is like
You have a Leo
That is something is very good
Consisted
Still on the outside even with viscum
Completely wacky
Media lamp
So early is a really thrilled about this guy named Mo Brooks
Apparently has come out he's a member of Congress and the house
And he's said that
Even if the Electoral College
Comes back and says like a b
President
It's a man
You took him to a lie of the
Cited
To the house
Certification
January 6th
Good luck
It doesn't stop there
The threats
Republic
Who don't support Mo Brooks
Threatening
Do not join
We will burn the Republican Party Down
And we will make something new
Oh no
I mean look I I would
FoodSaver
That response is a little bit
Not good
Yeah that we have and that is
Because like well in 2009
Some of the symbol of rhetoric was flying around it early tea party rally
The Republican Party put you
When
That
Stafford
Happens
It's not like it cripples
The park
Extreme voices closer to the mainstream
Stream goes towards the crazy voices
Is moroff
End up where we are now
So I don't think they're going to be capable of doing
Encouraging the sort of
Inner energy Opie fighting
I don't know if it's great
Because it does also lead to deposit ability of people like
Ally or Nick Fuentes or Alex Jones
Coming into a more relevant
Position than they would be other way
I think I think you're right
Presupposing that
We do nothing
Which is what happens with
The Tea Party
We
All set by in laughter
Because they thought we were like hahaha
Let Them Fight
Instead of
Using this is an opportunity for
To sabotage both wings
And f*** them up
Together
Like what we're doing Isabel
Like it's like what they have done so
Successfully is
Constantly push a wedge between the left in the center in the Democratic Party
That's the best thing that the Republicans know how to do
Is whenever there's the internecine squabbles
From the Democrats
The Republicans jump in and start throwing s*** at the wall tube to see if they can cause more conflict
Inbetweeners
And everytime this happens on the right the Democrats
Look back in the like well I bet the reasonable headshell Prevail this time
I didn't say yeah
Yeah that that is
That does seem
To be I don't know it's tough because I do want to laugh also
Yeah me too it's so funny Hood like to find a way to use this is a politically useful moment
Laugh
Well I mean I think was it that I think
Like I feel for these idiots kind of in a way
But not the not the leaders at the rally
Aunts and uncles and
Grandparents
Sure I don't I don't feel for Ally
No no absolutely
No I mean the people in the rally
Because
Paly
Rally fuel for the rally
No I mean the thing that I wanted
Screaming all of these people is look
If you want what they are telling you you want to get
Then you have to start a shooting War those are your options
None of this s*** that they're selling you is real
Their waist
Senior time
If you really want to balls up and start a shooting war or stop going to these dumbass rally
People who are taking the rhetoric that
You are digesting seriously are beating up people on the street
Exactly
That is the unfortunate reality of the rhetoric
And what you are
Acclimating yourself to
Yeah that would be
Worthwhile for them to realize
And the fruition of like
Specifically what
This type of rally is about
You get your goals
If you end up in a Christian theocracy
Anybody
Chaotic most
People really actually
Want
Know you know all those people who love Christianity in their super religious but then they
That getting to the situations where they have to apply it and I like
Well maybe not this time
You know what I'm still in Morley good person but this time I'm not going to act in this what you know Beck tonight I'm going to go out and get drunk
Can I have a really good night your f****** killed for it
Castor and
U-mary
And then you end up back
Banging around with
The secretary
Jeanette
You know I mean under you will not do as well as you do under a liberal
Republic
Puma difference
Yeah you know how rich Christian still seem to get all the abortions that they want to get
It is weird that is weird
So
Ali Alexander
He thinks he's a mastermind
I got to say
Disconnect
Clip
Just sounds like
Pictures of bondsville
And he's coming out to this this rally in like
Here is our G
Plan
It's already cringe
January
It's a start organizing
We're going to go into the county parties
We're going to go to the district parties
And we're going to go to
And we're taking over
Estates
We are going to work
Alex Jones
Anyone
And finally the movie
A state party chairman
We've known each other
For 12 years you're up for reelection in May
I'm going to flood
State Convention
And then after we take over all
Positions
Call Korman they were going to impeach the rest of the officers aren't we
Wow
Prairie
We're going to replace you with
That's called voting
I think he's
Musically
Did you just discover voting I think he discovered
Community organizing I think so they have decried the left do I hate it
So much cuz it
Creasing on local politics
Yeah scary
See this is why it's hard to take Alex
The threat seriously like
We're going to tell Joe Budden immediately
What we're going to do is we're going to go stand, Orem
Robert's Rules of Order
God dammit
I bet he does
I'm going to I'm going to follow patent into battle if you give the speech like
Abreva
Robert's Rules of Order are dangerous in the wrong hands
I was actually on my mind quite a bit throughout that I think it's probably because General Flynn I watched him give the same speech
Not Pat this is
Bad to keep hearing this when you hear nationalist propaganda you wanted to be pet
Right well I mean that's what Alex is trying to be
And a lot of people are just
Absolutely with it
Not good
They're still
Scary but
Ali
And his speech by
This is upsetting
I'm coming out
I have been different state
The fuc
Ouch ouch
No
I've been damn it you ever been to 10 states and it didn't rain once
Can you say that
I guess I can't
Or maybe I can I don't know
Just flying count what if I flew over 10 states and it didn't rain once does that count we're above the blood count
God dammit
This is how I feel everybody's everytime somebody tells me about ghosts
Everybody every time somebody's like
Oh you don't believe in ghosts
I've got to go so I'm like
Tell me about how the sunshine for tents
F*** you
It's a ghost
Stingray
Did Chicago surreal chirp
Alright
Alright reverse
Douglas Adams rain God get the f*** out of here
So after Ellie gets done
They have another speaker and this is a guy by the name of Leon Benjamin
Okay who is a bishop
But I should also tell you that this is your
The church also lost the race for the 4th District of Virginia seat in the house
Representative
That's a bummer he also probably would have lost
Primary like all the ding dongs that we talked about on the show but he ran unopposed
Until the general election
White tomorrow
Not as big a margin as I would hope
No
Never is a bidet
Eric metaxas brings Bishop
I got to say
I thought like maybe this was a racist event
Cleared it up
I heard
I keep hearing
And yet every now and again
I bump into
A black man at these events what is happening
What is the what is happening
Every now and again is he talking about
Are we supposed to be all about weight
Nationalism I keep reading that
And you're screwing that up
This is
Bishop
Leon Benjamin
He's got a shofar
At the end he says he's going to play the Flight of the Bumblebee
Don't miss it
Another bad joke
Wow yeah they're not racist at school
He wasn't being racist and might be on the end might be on the cusp
I'm not entirely sure
Solely on
Is really into
Christian nationalism
December 12th
Batman
Show me the number for Domino's
In the lion of the tribe of Judah
America
Man
Man nationalist
Just
Really miss out on a lot of great brat black
But well that's that's a real bummer Christian National
Still get a few good good talk
Chris here and there
Jordan
Yes
I know that we are we've heard a lot about we at you
Over the course of the time of doing
Not really
Advice about what to do about or more like
I'm coming out to you
Last day
You have to be direct with witches
You understand
That's the advice
I just I'm just
I'm thinking is
Wizard of Oz
Dorothy wakes up
Glinda the Good Witch shows up and she's just like
You listen to me
Deleon
Scares the hell out of me
Franklin
Because he says stuff like that
But when you show
Next Generation
Because
All children
We will kill them now
We will not fight
Man I understand that there's some like rhetorical license that you're not maybe intending to talk
Talk about killing humans in your
Political enemies
But you're at a political rally
And you're talkin about these demons in these Devils that were
Up against
And the conversation very easily it could be under
Understood
People who wear black and like you think they're in antifa
Maybe someone at a black lives matter rally
Maybe these are the demons that you don't want your children to every life of his one-year children doesn't have to fight
I don't I don't think that
You know you could make a legally reasonable case
Did this is
Somebody
Threatening inciting people to kill other people chew or
Reckless
It's recklessly
Expressed ideas and II
That's a great
Speech if it's 1977 and you're talking about
Climate change
Every bit of
Greenhouse gas that we get rid of
That I don't have to deal with it that way
It's a good thing to do in fact
Somewhat
Jones
Gave his speech
And then a little video came out
Of
Him
Backstage
Oh yeah
She ran into
General Flynn
And this is really really funny
Had some word I recommend people go find this video since we're in audio podcast with play the audio and then I'll explain what happened
General Flynn did not want to talk to Alex
Comes up and he's like crazy day at General Flynn does not turn to him
My cat is crazy day
Hey there. We're going to win
Agadmator
Are you scared
Yeah
Alex title gets loose like
Like someone else
Kind of walks up and Alex
Just get the sense like I got to leave over at Owen Shroyer
Back
So there's a rubeola going through these just in the corner watching
Knows like I was going to go out
Be there that Alex
Funny
Play M knows who you are and doesn't want to be associated
Interview or has no idea who you are
Either way does not work well for his brand
You should not meet
Your Heroes that you created
Fictional versions of the fictional version will greet you warmly
It's such an issue
He gives up but he gives a speech
Gets gets up at this Jericho rally and man
What up what up
Getting to the speech
It's just
Awe-inspiring
You know I was going to end with a prayer but maybe we'll start with a
The prayer
This sounds play I told I told Mike Lindell as he was walking and we bumped into each other
They actually had the first
Can sleep at my night of my life last night
Mypillow.com
Commercial
Mike f****** Flynn start his speeches plug for my pillow
God
He must be throwing around cash
My pillow guy
Christmas Day
Remind you
We happy few
How much pocket money is that guy making there is a 5% discount
Straw beds when we return home Heroes
Did he find like a
Cash of
Krugerrand
Gold
I don't know
But Flynn's got that pillowcase
God
Anyway so I don't
Why do people love Doon Tae
Right love doing
The biosphere
Is the mind-killer
Correct correct
You tell me a little bit about the fear is the mind-killer it is the little-death that
It's part of the litany against fear.
Something that the Bennett Jesuit teach you to say whenever you're free
You said many a time it would have called himself and bring himself into a text with relate to
Idaho Idaho learn the litany against fear his mother was about a Jesuit okay
And so he was aware of all of that stuff however he was never trained in the ways of the Benadryl because men children wear
Not allowed only
How to rock
Dad
And
Spanner Desiree
They were actually got himself.
Fear is the mind-killer
Body pillow
Sandworms kill everybody but they are also God
Okay also the devil shaitan
I got this
I wanted to just
Discuss this a little bit
Because
Ask Mike Flynn was talkin early
Are you going to get into if he's talking about fear
Who is the fear is the mind-killer he's very close in our minds
In our minds
That's where we
Define fear
Because fear is a is a mint
Nothing is something that you have in your
And your minds and you fear thing
Because you're mine says I'm a
I'm afraid of that I'm afraid of this
But it's in our hearts
It's in our hearts where we
We truly know
What is right
Because you're not Hearts that's where we
Differentiate
Between good and bad
Prairie differential
Between Darkness and Light
Let me know that we know that in our heart we
Gut feeling but it's actually your heart
Hit your heart talkin
Not your mind because your minds going to say
I'm afraid
So fear is the mind-killer
Because you're it like weird feelings are actually your heart which is clearer because your heart
Free of fear the only thing we have
Is
Because it comes from inside you but it's also part of your heart and you can't judge
Because it's what you're afraid of and it's in your head
And we're is what we fear the most itself
Yeah
Patent
No
Not a great speaker
Sears in history
Not one of them
No
Realize as he was speaking that I don't think I've ever
Yutaka full speech of his me neither and I found it
Underwhelm
I've found that to be incredibly tariff
It's the one thing I'm afraid of is
Is helicopters a good segue
Well I'm afraid of a Segway
Well we're both terrified we go
Well twin is onstage that's when the flyover happened huh
Imagine being able to just jump in the helicopter go for a joyride around Washington d.c. I love it I love the fact that
Does that
That's what he does because
He knows
He knows that
The people that
He can trust
Are people that he's never met
Contact you I mean he's never mad at you
Look at the millions and millions of people
Bright
He trusts you he trusts you because he knows
You know what's going on
And you will not allow what's happening to happen in our country none of us will
It's just not going to happen. I will tell you one more time
Good I've been half on a scale of 1 to 10
Who will be the next president of the United States when I say Donald Trump
10A 10
You know that that moment they were he's like first of all the idea that Trump
Can trust you people who he doesn't know it's very sad
So sad
Play music
Trust you because you're the ones who know what's going on you're not going to let what happened and how it happened
Makes me think of that Andy Daly character is like
Stand-up comic who says nothing like what else is in the news today
I mean come on
When I was
Not if I ever
Because you know what's going on in your acolyte what happens happens
Wow so I could say
Say that you wanted
Everyone to insights
Installing
The unelected
President
Hunter's so much of that
Like
It is it is one of those things that you don't really
It it doesn't always
Hit you until it does
How much Uber
F***** up by movies and TV and culture and all that s*** because
You just here
General
And you'd like see his military record and all of these
War
High-ranking you're like
That's the f****** guy and you're going to think of No Noggin
Nonsense
The man of few words
Kind of yeah and that's not the way I planned gets actually
Political and politics his way up into the military a high-ranked he's a f******
There's another guy
That's for Trump who gives a speech
Beach that is
Uneventful
What you're talkin about
What you would expect later
Oh you're
You're terrifying
Your dark dark Mexican archetype
I got to say
The Jericho rally drag
At this point
I believe it I'm done with it we're not going to talk about any more of it cuz it just ends up
Deteriorating into thing we're like
There's a guy from bikers for
Trump news end up talking about how they
60 formed
This group right before
Because they wanted to
Just stop antifa from throwing dog
Stupid Trump supporters
We're waiting in line to get into a
You said that in front of
People you said that in an interview on the TV wow there's also some more religious weirdos and
You know
I just I lost it
I couldn't
There's also a couple other Infowars character
I kind of really a Jason
Some people like Jason Jones
The 4th hour sometimes I think he was there and he gave an interview
Was just kind of like
This is too much
And again I think a problem
Is it Alex
What kind of early
Yeah it really took so much gas come out of none of these other people could reach the heights of that
You know like I don't I don't know of any actual comedian who talks about last per minute
Yeah but it would be idea.
An Applause line
A minute Alex
Just wrecked
Shop no one is going to be able
Go to recover
Discord servers
Which I imagine he did on purpose
It's honestly
Because I
I've been I've been under Robin put
Where I wasn't supposed to go in the lineup before
Yeah and I made it very clear
I wasn't supposed to go
Yeah yeah
I'm going to bury whoever comes up next
Barrier Headliners so far into the ground
And Mike Flynn both come out to the Mission Impossible theme stolen my 25th
Girls music
No that's
That's a t-shirt that I am here for it all day might be something there
So
I
Watch
How much more of this
But I lost my page
For it because
I mean like how much what what else are we going to fight
More examples of people saying the exact same Christian nationalist cheap
Who cares God
Kill everybody we got it moving on but
There was another rally
That day
This was the women of her America First rally
This was being held to pretty close nearby around the same time
There's some particularly fun footage also that's going around on Twitter which is of Alex trying to bum rush
The stage
At the women for Trump rally sounds like a metaphor I'm able to understand.
Shuffle
Goodman family show Alex
My first thought when I watch that was
It seems like he's on
Stimulants
Red eyes
Yeah and like grinding his mouth in like ready to
The flight with a
Security guard who won't let him
Through
Feels like you
He's clearly thinks he's entitled
How to get up there and get on stage
From here
But I
Think about it I like well
Honestly he probably
He's coming over there right after he yelled at the other crowd assumed he was
He thought he was welcome
Coffee adrenaline of that
Maybe also some stimulants
But shutdown
From going to
To the women for America First rally
You can tell them you can tell that that's that rally because you can hear the guy
In the background talking about the March
Search for Trump which was the bus
Tore that led to and culminated with
This women
For Trump
America First rally
I didn't hear him whining about Flags
So this rally was a much
Much less relevant to our folks
Let's direct Infowars connect
Alex wasn't allowed
At this one he was allowed at the other show and they even let Owen
Shroyer on State
Holly Alexander was one of the organizers of the Jericho rally
Like I said there were a couple other Infowars people that you could find hanging around
In contrast this women for America First rally felt like people who are bit more into
Interested in being taken serious
Issue with is that I can only
Find to real differ
Prince's between
One is it Alex was not allowed at the women for America first one
And they also seem to mention
Political issues a little more than the Jericho
That was pretty solidly Focus not demanding Christian nationalism where is this one is
Hiding a little bit in
Conservative politics big difference
It's between the middle and far-right wings of the Republican
Desperately trying
A Subway
Credible with their booking choices
Katrina Pierson
Seb Gorka
Yeah
Very credible comparative
I got there bigger names RaeLynn like
Is Sebastian Gorka has a show that's in Decatur
Okay that's
Alex is on Genesis communicate
Still amazing to me that sebgorka is just allowed to roam
Humphrey
And shockingly
I texted you about this
Last night what I was
I text
To do that he seems like a character
How you not also heard much Sebastian Gorka
Except for maybe like a little Clips or
Honestly a domian doing an impression of what you played for me so play less
Honestly felt like watching that I was like
Sebastian gorkas leaving into the B
How big do parodies looking cell that sounds right that good
That like
They've really nail it cuz Cassie
He seemed liquor
Farce yeah
I mean whenever your
Front lines are run by a
Hair dye
Bleeding Rudy Giuliani in front of a landscaping company are going to be just
Straight impression Rudy's the guy who hits the barbed wire
Originally intended that we would cover the entire rally
Of the women for America First just like the Jericho one
Compatible with my goal of creating a decent show that people can enjoy
Just done rally
Is that were
Mike Flynn in the my pillow guy basically give the exact same speeches at both
Rally's
And the whole thing just
Strike Zone way too long much like the other one with people just
Basically saying nothing
Like it's really
It's really
Vapid
They have no actual substrates mostly getting people to chant about loving Trump in
Whatever
That's f****** straight-up Nazi s***
I decided to possibly a better way to approach the women for America first
Rally what's the handouts
Superlative
As if this lineup was a bunch of
Matriculating graduating seniors in high school of it
The first are the first title I'd like to
Bestow on someone feed
Moose
Confusing breath of fresh air
What's up
How is General
When you guys was that amazing or what
Batman and his family
Laid it on the line
For our country
Over
And over and over again that we can't show them enough gratitude
This guy is very clearly drunk
Felix
To be in his late 30s early 40s
When is wearing what appears to be a red
Sequin smoking jacket
Now I'm back on board he's got a beard
Drunk at like
I I live there but for the grace of God go idea is absolutely out of place at this rally and is the kids say I
I was here for it
Also I have no idea who he is you never says his name
I don't know I tried to find out I could not look at the comment to the YouTube video
I Googled
Lineup of events I couldn't find that he was standing next to Alex on this
Security guard stop.
I'm going to go all through then but
Jeanette Lee like all things we discuss on this show that are
Kind of fun
He ended up revealing
Himself to be a piece of s***
But also in the same clip that he says something that I was really tickled by
Carefree Park
Dubai message
Well-armed
I lost all my contact tragic boating accident
What
What just happened what did you just say to me
Second part about that one another person
Stability
Something that we have to
A lot with what becomes
Come on
Boating accident I was expected
I'm not sure if that is a joke
Actually had a boating accident cut off discs
Why would you say tragic boating accident nothing specific
Either pretty funny as a joke
Like I I don't have any guns I've lost enough but tragic boating accident that I would toss off if I was asking somewhere
Not a bad throw away
Also could be real and I want to know the table underneath is true
Los Alamos
To be an engagement present
You've got this weird
Why do you say that f****** racist blue stuff it's a little bit like I erase
Right winger
Play by Kyle Kinane
I had no idea what is going on
I don't know who he is he doesn't introduce himself no one says
Huggies on
TV
Stream of it there's no damn on the Chiron
No idea
I have no idea
He introduces
Who's the person who has the
The same name as a big celebrity
But does not appear to be that celebrity
You will never
Stand for it
We're going to keep coming back
A pillet stone
And our president
The greatest president ever
Where is supposed to be
Amazing woman I told her I
Keep it brief
I don't want that trouble
Jennifer Lawrence
Come up and talk to everybody it is not Jennifer Lawrence
I don't know who is Jennifer Lawrence's either
I thought maybe if I figured out who she is still have no idea
Anybody is coupled
Crashed the White House Party and everybody's like if it is I love it
Jennifer Lawrence
Nightly Christian Nash
Nationalized
People on that hill over there
I need to remember
They work for us
We the people that we do work for that
We have to die
Not government and goddess
Can I tell us who's going to be
Be the president
Wait what
Countries going to go and we are going to fight
Okay
Thank you Jennifer Lawrence so then
So then
You even if
So then even if you get here
Present you're still not going to do with the
The government says
I guess not
Either way congratulations to clearly day drunk guy in the sequence smoking jacket you have won the very coveted title
Most confusing breath of fresh air
Somebody out of let like
What is JB Smoove did 5 minutes
Like that's what I was hoping the super surprised that confuses breath of fresh air was now it's day drunk Inc
Sequins Red Coat
Pretty close to
The next award that I'm going to give out the next superlative is the best
Integration of promotional messaging
Into a stump speech
No my pillow might be involved
But there's a word
It goes to radio show host David Harris and let me say it's not even close okay
Alright ran away with rest
And a special thank you
Due to the co-sponsor that really help fund
A lot of this
Mr. my pillow head self
Amazing Patriot loves his country
Loves us
Loves the president and the president loves him
And I got to tell you I love his cuz right I love his pillows I love his sheets
I love his mattress topper
And I love it
Because you know what the Kraken has been released
You are part of the Kraken
For the best deals
Support this Patriot using code
Kraken
At my door. Calm amazing
Just amazing
I can't say enough how
Not smooth that was really really bad David doesn't just stop with my pillow code
He also throws out like a
I'm big on social
I've worked hard over the last few years
To try to bring
Real honest news
At David Harris
Junior.com
I've got two points
3 million followers on Facebook 1.1 on Instagram
Plug in his website
That is all just
In order to
Are you
For another
Which is
The solution Two-Face
Facebook
I hear people talk about parlor parlor is amazing it's a great alternative to Twitter
But we need an alternative to face
Facebook
Southern Network
Albright's
Like Facebook and I found it I'm going to
Talkin about it loud
I got a lot of my friends really talk about it loud
It's called
Springleaf Stanford
Speak freely
And here's where you can download it at speed
Ree
Ly
Spell you're going to hear a lot about that
And they're going to dominate Facebook
Going to guess they're not
People like a lot of them seem to be pushing
Internet startup
Like there was one guy who came to Alex's seapak
He was trying to push a search at
Like it I think that they're really trying to make a little bit of a fast
I'll meet conservative aggrievement over social media mark
I mean this is what this is what I'm saying when I
When I say like I feel for these idiots in the crowd here like
You guys
Are being sold the idea that you can legally just
Get whatever you want
What's the longest
Like
Adelphi lawsuits and then we'll get whatever we want cuz we're right
And there
Telling you all of this like
And when
This happens
Which we totally know it's going to they will keep us from having to do the one thing that we know is the only
Only way to get what we want to achieve and we're trying to avoid
And it's like you're just being taken Along by these guys who are selling you on
No one's going to go on spreely
He also
Has perfected
This this this technique
It's David Harris has of
Protected prayer
Lord's Prayer
Take every line of it and think about what
Yeah are we going to get in the bridge so long
6 minutes
This is the end of it and that house smoothly a transition
Shenzhen to a plug
Give us a greater under
Standing fan
Of your love forever
Visual Sun
As an individual.
Give us a greater revelation
Father abuse
F*** yourself
And that change
In our country
In Jesus name
I truly believe we're going to win
I truly believe the fraud is going to be
The Kraken has been released
We the People
Will not be denied
Another four years
The amazing President Donald Trump
Wosu
Arab stil
Really hear that again
So please visit David Harris jr., help me
Fighting
Suckers are just constantly on me
Wow wow quite a ride in Jesus overturned those money chain
Changes table as in said
Follow me at Sap's
Jesus underscore Magic
Yeah I found his speech to be
Laden with promotion
Distract
It was a little distracted no idea who this guy is
Sorry I don't
I can't judge his body of work
I can only watch this
And say it was a little much
Arnex
Category is the most graceful exit from someone who clearly did not want to be there
This award goes to someone we know actually he's a guy who promoted
Pizzagate quite heavily
Jack Russell
They said that I could have longer time up here today said but I said I want to get my time up
I want to get my time up
To a whistle
Snowblower
Outrageous
Whistleblower
Who saw something
Undecided
To say something and
Bed up so late
Ladies and gentlemen
All the way from Michigan
Melissa Calderon
Who's going to come up
Until you
So that's the lady who appeared to be drunk with Rudy Giuliani and that that video that every
I'm out of here
Would have given Melissa Corona speaking
Spot if she tasked totally like yeah I don't really want to do this I want to do it but I do want my name
They're just in case I would like my attention
But I do not want to do the work for it
Yeah
SOI
Congratulations Jack hughman
There's actually an escalation of this category now we have to give out the award for the person who made the
The most graceful I'm not even showing up this award goes to Dinesh D'Souza
Another young lady
You know her father Dinesh
CM Oliver TV
Android apps
Today's birthdays
Pro-life young woman author
What about the toys
And I'm proud to introduce her to you today here in Washington d.c. Danielle desousa
Dinesh D'Souza was invited
No I'll send my daughter
Oh boy
I know you could have facets till further
Lazy episode did you not just say what
Send a video message announcing Melissa Carbone or whatever video message
Marjorie Greene
That was one of those like curveballs in terms of like they're booking
I feel like you guys are
Trying to
Habanero
Yeah it's not
Out there too far
The craziest congressperson we could
Well
Chianti Santana video
It's not good
Could be better overthrowing democracy is not always the most popular thing to do
True
Jordan
Is the second most likely day drunk person after the guy in a sequined shirt he's one hundred percent
Yes there's there's no competition
Play so ever
Most likely that honor goes to
Boris epshteyn
Who I should remind you
Guy from Sinclair
Tested positive for covid-19
On November 26th REI
He showed up and he
Hello lover.
I was told I shouldn't
My call but I'm going to do it any
We love Trump
Why
Trump
We love Trump
Google viberider
I love that Boris
Is like
Apparently didn't hear everyone yelling to put the flags down
Did those words up
Two different events people have been saying put the flags down so we could
Extreme at bars I got f***** at
I don't know if
Actually drunk it's really tough to tell cuz it also
I realized as I was watching
It's hard to tell the difference
What's between like maybe kind of day drunk
Buzzed and
Sort of just jacked up off of being in front of a crowd list
Like
Standard guitar pumped up time
You do that in
Those are the kind of things that you
Instinctually do when you're drunk
USA
I can't
This is maybe the largest
Disconnect more than our politics
The idea any
The idea of saying
I have me chanting we love
Yeah like politician
F***
That
Siri
Seems weird
Aerie
Yeah
I think AOC is incredible I'm not going to
We love AOC f*****
I tell myself that I think I would be just as a
Like put off
By seeing large
Crowds chanted we love Obama back in 2000
But maybe I wouldn't have
Maybe that's a bias on my part
I don't know I thought I'd like to think that I would be where
But I'm not certain I were much younger than
Do you know Obama was coming out after the previous worst.
I like to think
That I would respond
The same would be like
But I wonder if I would
See that and I would give the like her like personality this is just Express
Kissing their political
I mean I wouldn't I don't know
Obama Jordan
That was
Significantly long ago I would say the most
Recent is obviously the Bernie Sanders campaign in the primary in 2016
Whenever he had those massive rallies but even then I don't remember people's
Screaming like really chanting like feelthebern something like that phrase
All in This Together not like
We love you was not me us
So
We love us I would be fine with chanting that
Yeah yeah I don't know it
It's it's it's tough I know that I don't like looking at it
Here and I like to I like to think that maybe even if I had turned a blind eye to it
Before
I would now look upon
People chanting like let's
Play I love AOC whatever I would look at that
Much differently
Maybe this is giving me an Illuminating moment
Superlative
Title
Person who's putting the most
Direct
I didn't prepare this time
This one's a little bit off the dummy person putting the most effort into getting people killed
That goes to I don't remember his name but he's that gym owner in New Jersey who I would use it to stay closed
If you would have asked me
Back in February
If I thought that one person
We can make a difference
I want to laugh
And said hell no
But here I am today
One Man Apart of
Team of two guys
Bristol
Governor told him
No we will not listen
And it started moving across the country they're trying that second way that they've been
Predicting for so long
And more more busy
They're staying open
I don't hear The Advocate every
Single
Freedom-loving American Eagle outlet
Support these small business
And I'm going to give you away how
We created directory
Nationwide directory of business
Been thinking about Yelp
Freedom-loving American
K restriction
I have a
Climate plan
Support
That is ww.w.
Australia Open
Interstate free.com
Check it out
Going card
Is the sign up at ghost
Support them
Because the more that do the Quakers thing
Fall apart I promise you
This works equally well as a
Registry of businesses to avoid
Yep yep
Wow I didn't think that one man could make a difference
But now look at me
The Horseman of plague
Yeah good
Is Christ
King Midas
Not age well
So I went and I looked at this guy's registry and I look for Chicago there is exactly one business
In the city of
Chicago and it is an apartment building
Pictures of all right
Do you want to
I guess yeah
Seems silly
Is it Gold Coast Apartments
This is what that was for I think this is more about like
Superlative
Is actually a tie
This is very shocked
Most insane preacher
There's two
The first ghost goes to block
Out of Tennessee
If you're glad to be on The Winning Side let's make some noise CC
This thing is going to turn out alright
Backup
We're not going to pack up when I going to
And we're not going to shut up to we've been taking up on the glory of God
McDonald's
Trump is going to remain the president United States
Do you believe that this afternoon Patriots
How do you map my snakes
We're getting a lot of different particular flavors
Exciting preachers
That's why it has to be a tithe
These guys are
Completely different styles
But
Masterlock who-knows-what
He does not ask
Permission what he wants to tell the devil that the devil is on notice
Information for I said it never do let me tell you something I serve notice on the devil
Geyser
Auctioneer you have a gift for saying words fast and dumb
Do not do this job
He's he's very exciting
Verbally
Yeah that's why I
I've never had the devil of a goddamn piece of provision but I'll tell you that right now everybody
I know it's 10 over there
Stu yell about how everyone will be forced to bow in front of Jesus
The name of Jesus
Every knee shall bow of things in heaven
10 things in Earth
Thanks unto the Earth handed a republican-democrat
And with their voice Proclaim him Lord of Lord
To the glory of God
So you have a choice
Endochoice
Is cleared
We can declare Jesus Lord of our life right now because we want to
Or we can declare Jesus Christ Our Life in the day of judgement
Because we have to but make no mistake
Cheese's
Lorde
And I want you to
Chance team
That guy is scary
And I'm anyways
But is it local patterns are fun
It's all good I'm mad
Oh okay
To the next guy who's tied here for this almost insane preacher is a guy named Brian Gibbs
This kind of endearing
His wife
Brings him up
Reduces amongst
Do you know that it's his wife
Initially
Because she's just like
This next over speaker is okay
Which is my favorite person
Husband
Cute adorable
Brian Gibson
Pastor Brian Gibson
Some complaints
About how his
Easter services
Is Easter Service didn't work out he's going to try and give eggs to children
Only Easter Sunday I blew a fuse
I'll put together an Easter egg giveaway we were going to give
In the name of Jesus
Told me
Shutdown
Church
Of the Lord Jesus Christ
You keep those
F****** eggs
I swear to God I swear to
God that's your bitching
That's what you're complaining about
Number to tell you
No one has the authority
To shutdown
Uncle Lord Jesus Christ
Except Jesus Christ
Berkshire
He believed it.
Does God Beetle Bots
Organizer parking lot communion service
I called all the prep
I said come out
Tell the governor on Distributing communion
Imogen, Russia
Cuz I'd love to go to jail
For the preaching of the Gospel
That's not what you'd be going to jail for certain you are not actually preaching gospel
What's up with that
What is up with that how I can't get arrested for preaching
Wow for boy
Kind of a little bit telling her that he would not make the cut if it weren't
His just
Stream
Christian nationalist
Let me say this
America did not birth chart
America did not burn
Bethel Church
Birth of America
Toptracer
Sir
Excuse me
Only thing that will save America
It's the same thing that burst
America
The Church of the Lord Jesus Christ
Yeah I mean this is going to go with King George but I guess I was wrong
Nope you're absolutely wrong
What about that whole no taxation without representation thing wasn't that really important or was
Is just church
Alright
Okay you realize that like the Puritans were kicked out
Cuz they
Hated them
Cuz everybody hated cuz there's no work cease to preachers
Are at the one that is not
The more religious branded one
That wasn't the product of a vision
Yeah
So I'm 23 I'm trying to tell you that all of this is
Religious people
Come get your guys or you get what you get man
I don't blame decent
Religious people for this
I believe religion
That's an interesting conversation I don't want to have right now
I do not want to give out the next to the last
This goes to the most
Bewildering transition between
Queen speakers
This begins
The woman whose name is either Anna Kate or Anna Cay
Intro
The internet
He's probably really did some damage to the
The rich family
The Seth rich
I don't know what the
Dafuq anyone's doing ever letting him in public
Intro to either Anna
No idea
ZZ Top she's a very devout
Worshiper
Who's apparently been in
Prayer for 40 days straight
Then I guess he's breaking that now to give the people of this rally an update
How dare you
F****** lie like that you might
Prophecy his promise
The Trump will be given
Consecutive terms
So therefore
You must have one
After saying this
She's got a message
Search for the devil
Message is for the devil
And his minions
And all the wizard
And witches that are what
Sing right now all over the world
This is for you we're going to do it stand right now
We're going to do a Tampa cuz it's awesome to exalt
Kid one
To bring Justice back into the country
I do worry that I'm one of the wizard
Yeah I'm pretty sure you're a wizard
Yeah why did I think that no matter what the reality is I would be looked upon as a wizard early but the devil
No it doesn't matter even if there was no religion
I'm still looking at you just going like
Lord of the Rings The Vibes I've been forced into the role of a wizard
Do your everyday is your obsessive you live on the 3rd
Florida Power if you will come on buddy you're jondy reincarnated
Alright
This lady chance
For Jesus
Is the devil real
Yes okay
I know that cuz I'm always here
Jesus
She repents for abortion which is apparently a blood sacrifice
Ball
County three-wheeler can't change Jesus
This was a picture I had a few weeks ago
Because it's a ship
Singing mystere now in Jesus name when we repent
Before we trying to think what we repent
For all the blood sacrifice that has been
Bored out and it's National
Pants for a boy
What's in Lord God the sacrifice of civilians don't
To Lord
Start chanting Jesus
Here is the transmission
Outrageous
And made me laugh out loud
Hours into watt okay stupid rally
Yes and I love this moment
More than I can
Really put into work
Enjoy this minute
15 second ride
Jesus
Glory to God we're going to see a miracle amen
Amazing ride
Hey guys right here in the middle
If we could keep
Flag down
We have some guys at RS
Okay with us the whole way down mazing
We want to make sure people at homecoming joy to thank you guys
Yeah just right here in the center between us
On the camera
Like they're amazing
Are we love rspan
Because you guys need to be watching them
I backed up we're going to make
Will get perks of amazing artists out here
Forgiato blow
Y'all ready to turn up
Apartment
We all need to move around with this might though
Alright
So what's happened here is that we started with the lady chanting Jesus
For the devil in The Whispers
And then my drunk friend comes to me
Better Business
He introduces a wrap
There's a rap concert you know
It's just
It was easier to have religious epiphanies before technology I imagine during The Sermon on the Mount was
Peter like hey guys
We are leaving too much bread around
There is a lot of bread going around on the floors and it's attracting too many birds birds are getting in the shot
And now a rap concert on the map
Bryson gray comes out to do a little wraps at
Albums that he's put out
Maga Seasons from SVN another one
Another another album called Maga ain't got no color
Add is other album can't cancel God
His label who wanted the Christmas album Amor was
So I went and I listen to a little bit of his
Stuff
I got to say he's service
As an actual rapper
You got it.
Good
The Lira sisters someone who's delivering
Words over beat
Sure sure sure sure it's not as bad as a lot of people I've hurt
I will say that
I think
He's just not he's not anything
Interesting to help find anything
Sing compelling about it
It's largely just like
Rapping
And I'm sort of
Conspiracy talking point drop sheds
I don't really care but I went I actually found a review of one of his album okay because
They can review really agreed with me like
He's not terrible but this is boring
Insulting
Not doing anything interesting it's kind of uncompelling you have some
Scale or whatever man
Honestly I
Your politics
I do hate them but we're talkin about the music here but you could deliver your politics
Interesting art
Pickway I might
Appreciate what you make either I disagree with what you're sure you're putting out I might be able to get there but
Boring as hell like everybody knows Cecil DeMille
Okay we get
So he comes out with another rapper whose name I forget
Cuz I don't care
But
They have
Sotech issues
At the beginning
And so they have to Vamp for a little bit of
Remember music start
Because what ends up happening is
It could not be more perfect
I think that this sums up a
Well you're disappointed in the Supreme Court
Pacific yesterday
Call Perico
Spirit
Who is Bill out here we still live talk 2020 on the game
I heard a plane
Godzilla
I love the second
Take me to me
Politician
Hello
Call Mama
Remind me to write a drop
Santa here in Washington DC
Play go away from the rap concert Duo my pillow cover
Wow
Guys guys you were supposed to get the you're supposed to get the version without the lady I just wanted to
Guys be instrumental it's rapping with me with me
Just leave the track
I'm supposed to know if I'm supposed to actually perform
Northern things I found religion
Choose if you watch this video there's a guy who looks like Napoleon Dynamite
Fight on stage
I don't know what this dude is doing I can't tell if he's
With them and they're as a visual joke
He's dancing along with them
Or whatever or if he is like from some other Outlet
I have no idea what's going on
It's bewildering modern Forrest Gump movie about that guy twenty years from now and he's going to be everywhere
Outrage
He will have inserted himself into
The Vietnam War
I can't tell you how
Weird what like obviously we're recording this on Sunday and this is all happening on Saturday
Order to make this really work at ended up like I really late night last night
And so I'm like
Yo
Late into the evening
Watching these bananas
Speeches
We must chant Jesus Dave
And then a wrap got their break it out
Yeah and the fact that the broadcast goes straight to a my pillow commercial
In the middle of
Maybe the most energetic thing they had on their stage
It just was kind of disrespectful to this very serviceable rapper
Jesus Christ
Indeed
That has got to be the most surreal night
I can pick up like
To go
Just to ride that all the way through till like 3
If you were just watching One rally
No big deal
That's what you you listen to
But you're watching
7 straight hours of Rally's
At least
Is on after a long day into the wee hours of the morning
And that assert
Certain points
Didn't you have to just have a complete break from reality
I kind of did think at a certain point I was making up
What was that must have been that's how I would feel if you're telling me this happened it was so real
I can't imagine experiencing it by myself
Do you know what I mean yeah. There were a couple points where I thought like
This is
Self-parody
No way
Twin speech started with a my pillow ad
Why is this guy giving out my pillow code
Can't beat this is nonsense cannot be
It's so
Tough
So like really put
Your hands on what this is
Because
It's simultaneously
Terrifying
Display
Of
Different levels of
Explicitness
I'm about a desire to live in
Christian theocracy
You know that's not about
Standing up for your right we be able to practice
Your religion
It's about enforcing your religious beliefs onto the government
Yep making the government adhere to your religious beliefs at the expense of
Everyone else
Who does not share your beliefs
And that's terrifying
Horrify cuz you have
D'you know the Jericho March
Maybe
You know obviously more
Upfront about
It's called the Jericho
Call Bia
Cher's overlap in funding and speakers with the same other Mart
Quite honestly
I think the two people that I heard
The other March
Do women for Trump
Women for America first
There was born
Christian nationalism probably on display there
Not granted they didn't have someone like Leon bunch
We got to kill the devil so our kids don't have wings
There was a little bit more speak freely going on over there
I think I'm more scared of the women for America First rally honestly
Smart enough to not allow Alex there
It's it's about Gorka
It's fascism package
Buy Coca-Cola
Like it is
It is so my my pillow
Invalid
That liked
Tying together of
Just
Bass
Space Commerce
Just f******
Promo code level Commerce
With
Your ostensible belief system which we all know is
Complete Bowl
If if you if you think anything that those rallies had to do
Those rallies had zero to do with Christianity
I agree
It's a mass
It's being worn
100%
Julie difficult is that like I don't I'm not saying that of everybody who's in the crowd
Again like I think there's probably
Maybe some
Sincere in mislead
People who were there
I don't know
I can't I can't say
But I don't
Can't imagine that the people who are
Putting this on
Are motivated by a sincere spirituality
Absolutely not
It's very difficult for me to accept that and maybe it feels that way.
I'm not sure it's very difficult to judge I wrestle with
Because it's something that's so intimate
A personal within someone
Like True Religion
Just feeling
And it is whenever you served
Criticize somebody
About their sincerity or lack thereof
It kind of comes off as if
Oh you think you have
Sincere belief
No I don't I don't want to get into that kind of an argument
This is gross
Here's a here's the one I would
About
If your beliefs
Stars sincere and a looking
Christ and all that stuff
Go read the way of the
Andrea Lee
Really like
Meditate on Cecil onan's and the idea of praying everyday and every moment and what that actually mean
Or
You could go to a rally and try and overthrow nation and kill the bugs
Yeah in the difficulty that I have is the combination of both of these rallies being so
Explicitly my Christian nationalist
Austin character
I'm so
Overt about it
And both of them
Being
So
Crass
Joe Ciara we're laughing our asses off at all the MyPillow stuff but like
Both of these rats
Both of them
So f***** the parity level of the
Like
Praying and chanting Jesus
Into a drunk guy introducing a rap Act
Just ridiculous or it's surreal
And
I don't know what to do with it
But I do think
Alex Jones got a lot of headlines
Out of crashing van
Jericho March
Wants and so it does come into our view and I think that one of the things
Games with important
I thought I guess
Is to take what we know about Alex and what we understand about that
And Glenn
The external World a little bit
When there is a chance
Quite honest
Looking at
These people some of whom I'm aware of some of whom I'm not
Who are chosen by the people who are organizing these rallies
Skippy's beaches
I don't see a lot of the
Between what they're putting out there and what Alex
Nope and that is not
How I felt
Even
Like even when we look back at like 2009
Like even when the tea party was going on
There were still substantiv differences
Between
The Tea Party and Alex Jones Alex was more severe
You may be more severe than some of these
These people and more
Extreme but like
These rallies
I don't understand
Why except for bad press
They would
Not let Alex speakerphone
I don't get why they have to
Parade around even at the Jericho March
Spirit of inclusion
Go f*** yourself he's right on board exactly what you're
He's doing what you're doing better yeah the idea that they are still allowed
Like
That was Alex's roll
4 Fox News in and Rush Limbaugh's in the Glenn Baxter
Is for them to be like hey
At least we're not like Alex Jones right
They're all like that and they're still trying to act
It's like by saying hey at least we're not Alex Jones Infowars
We still get a we still get that
Difference you're not there's no effort
It well I made you act like you're too good for Alex
Don't feel that way.
I think that
You know I can
Can see where that thought
What comes from a largely comes from the
Reality that if you watch that rally
You'll see
A difference incompetent
From Alex and the rest of the speakers
If the if the goal is to rile Up This Crowd
Goddamnit does Alex do a better job than any of the rest of them you know she went in that point when he's like
Getting
Not allowed
And that's how you f****** do it
Do all this better than all of you but
Unfortunately as brand is so toxic that
No one even Ali Alexander 100
So I mean it's kind of like
I don't know
I think that this kind of sums up
What I think is one of the main
Problems
Fact checker
Haven't you had it with these
That could almost be the big problem probably a better way of putting it
I think when you cheer for
F*** fact-checkers who's up with all this reality
Who's who's up there with Dreamworld
Dreamworld
Boo
Who likes
To confirm things
Read a book
The mind is the fear killer
Yeah I am
I thought this was an interesting
Exploration little bit sort of
Fully outside of around Butler to the side of it a tire patch
Republic out more than usual
Just because it's like oh
All these people
Chanting
And cheering
And all these speakers sounded very similar to Alex
It's not it's a bummer and I think we have a very large problem
In front of us that I do not know how to deal with
And I think that
I think that it's important to recognize
One of the major problems is
The blurring here
This is not
This isn't about Paula
Is it not about policies
This is
This is something else altogether
And trying to approach it
From the standpoint of
Arguing or Pilot
It's not going to work
It's absolutely not going to work
Here's my pitch
All right now
I think one of the speakers Did point out
What's that
The nation was created
And now he said it was created by God
And I would argue that it was
Was created because
King George
And his elk
All right but
But
Maybe we should learn something from King George
Send
Okay well I almost already dispute your premise cuz I hate faction what did King George Do What did the
Can do when faced with a Puritan
You know they were causing a ruckus
And then he was like
Get the f*** out
And then they all left
Yeah I know that we shoot them to the Moon
This seems too much like those mentalities
I find kind of
Noxious which are the elected
It sounds so much like the you know you hear this rhetoric from people
Do you do like
Trump being the president get out
I just don't think
A good solution either
I don't know
It's a
It's a tough time to be in the middle of
I don't really know
How the ball breaks
Spell steadfast
No I would agree with that
Kicking people out last time
No
Violence doesn't work but I don't doesn't do it
Maybe we should try using like those
So it's like 2020 right and that means that another couple weeks before
Like a bunch of years
And humans
And they probably
Dealt with some s*** like this
This before
We should probably try smart
Well I wish that I had this clip cuz I actually
Really
Great
General
Michael Flynn you might hurt him
This is never happened
Human history before it's never actually we can't learn anything from history
Really convenient how we can't know anything about this cuz it's never happened before Italy
All those book learning idiot
God dammit I got so I don't I don't know
Next episode
More specifically about Alex Jones but I
I don't know if these Riley
Play suck
We're also on Twitter
Cool charity or bail Fund in your area
Punjab enemigo and Leo and bcx Clerk of Daryl rundus I am about
Go buy a red
Sequin smoking jacket
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color