Air Jordan 5 sweat it
I have great respect for this knowledge B I'm sick of them
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Acknowledge
Looks around a little bit about Allie
Text Joe
What is recognition
It's from now centuries
For now
This will be looked upon as the week
Give too much of you and me
Play the week of too much sauce that you are under
Estimating exactly how much
More we're going to do in the weeks
This is this is
Extensive week of
Programming
In between episode on Earth
A little bonus episode and then also thank you
To Robert Sophie
Something of that I got to bring information to the table
Everyone
About invention
From
Do you recall that
That's something we talked about on this year but apparently was new to the proceedings I would say that you were so excited
Credible excited he was shivering and shaking almost as though there was there was like
You know it's just something I couldn't feel better
My bright spot too much of us
My bright spot is
Taylor Swift
Because I was worried about that
No
Yeah I decided
Did this start listening to every Taylor's I've never listened
Taylor Swift
I don't never been to a Walgreens or in full
So I've never done that before and then I was
I really been struggling to come up with a project
The book ended
And I've just been like
Throwing shade at the wall and it's not been going well here comes another
For some reason I was like you know what I've decided to listen to every one of Taylor Swift's album
In a row
Chronological order and review each one we talked about this a little bit
You for this because I think it's going to have a really negative tone
Oh man is it dark yeah it is it is very fun to be
Incredibly mean to a seventeen-year-old who was going to go on to be a billion
I also resent that
At this point you're still like at a point where I can't really read but anything you're saying I don't know anything about Taylor Swift
But what if you start getting real shity about some problems we might have words
I think I think of you read it you will find that I am very complimentary
Towards things that deserve compliments okay
And I am hyperbolically incredibly cruel to things that are just
Okay you know I like that kind of friend of the show Messiah
Bias draft
Steve's website fancy Boys Club.
I'll be posting those probably once a week or
Until I get
Really pissed off at Taylor Swift
Decide never to do this again I will write my rebuttal
No refund but there will be only personally attacking you personally attacking you
What you should do is
Do the exact same thing but for each chapter of my book
Every week we'll just hate each other ever written that pop masterpiece
No
Absolutely not
Alright
December 16th and 17th 2020 of dances of 2020
Interesting and weird this week
We're going to have a little bit of a I don't know
Memento Style
YouTube book to sign up for sporting show
The first Bactine Masterson thank you so much and I'll probably want
Text Olivia m thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Olivia
Next James
Gee thanks about your now about to walk
Zachariah K things about you and I'll probably walk
What Thomas
Double Dragon
Thank you so much you are now technocrat
Thank you so much
Money off at heroin
Freakishly large
The Big Easy bless both of you
These dads do you do that
Website.com
What you could do is create some sort of tortured analogy towards trying to find writing something about Taylor
Into a generosity thank
But I was just suggest that you guys go to your local charity or bail fund
And support easy Road on this side of my hair today
Think about it
You're trying to get a little to Meadow with his right now
All right now
I wanted
Play The Sound of Silence
To start this episode over. Be very happy if I decided not to
Call real quick I have one
The business
Reached out to me
Ask me
Politely if we would wish
Her partner a happy birthday
His name is Joe and I was told that the way to identify him
Was that he skips over our theme song
OSHA then made me be like I might even going to f****** do this now
There we were going to play it again
Happy birthday to birthday jokes
I hope you have a good one
Birthday this year wasn't supposed their favorite birthday on totally
Nope
Here's the other
What's up
You are dating a joke
Or married to Joe or whatever with a joke
Who also skips over the theme song
Tell him it was you I'm not going to follow up on that.
Feel free to lie to your partner
Building strong released
And now back to the Sound of Silence
Indeed hello darkness
Miss my old friends
I couldn't help but
Like I was
Active look okay
Beginning of the week
We had the rallies in DC and then I was kind of
Planning on this episode till I cover the
Very predictable and obvious
Reactions Alex would have to it
Today Thursday as
And I'm getting
Gametime episode
We got hit with some big news
Liberty Therrien
Aha on Twitter
Infowars Duck getting banned
Every to pour in for anyone to notice is there
David Knight announced that he was fired effective immediately from Infowars
Cowboy
Tdp's got to live in the end I don't know if that's
That is the obvious thing that you would fix
Because David Knight has been on a bit of a public Vendetta against Steve pieczenik little bit who has been trying to convince
People that Infowars
That said the election was a grand sting operation
And David nice not having any other b*******
Fired for being inexplicably
A half-truth teller
Appropriately to that not his credit
He also
You know the last time we had Steve on
He said yes I believe Sandy Hook was a false flag
I will not agree with you about Las Vegas
So I don't know where his mind
B Big B big news and I don't want to I don't want to shoot on somebody when they're down
But I mean like
It's relevant
To re-enter
Crystal
Goodnight has been there
Forever
He's been there
Something like that
He has always been there through thick and
Of so much
Horrible bulshit
Went along with Alex's he got into Trump
Alex just remember the David Knight
Was there and he was like 5 years ago and then I just forgot
He's just so boring I don't
No I'm actually kind of conflicted I'm not entirely sure what I think
The quesadillas
Discuss this as as we go through the episode 2
What the 17th
We're going to start without
The conversation
Because
I think he knew he needed to get ahead of this
It's so he has fired David
At this point we are
Yes I do Thursday is Sherry's going to
Deal with
Some housekeeping business for a little bit
First thing I want to say
The tank was a good idea
It was a good idea
Attack we're good more money then David Knight Kelly-Moore pills
We're going to look at that
Batman we're going to flashback
260 and we're just going to do
Discuss what kind of content was going on there because I got just
Bored as hell after Alex stop talking
About current issues
Text Rob from Today Show
I don't like it myself as US president but this job is about as close as a kid
Okay
I mean currently
Maybe maybe
Headlines
Yeah basically the president
Pretty close
Free clothes when you get down to it
I get lied to by weirdos
As a profession
I do like Stephen Miller
I kind of had assigned
That it was going to
To be something that Alex has
Because
David Knight has
Made this public he's
He's come out with it
Zoe Alex
Frames things
Is this way when he gets going on the
The show
On the 17th
He was late
You would like for the shout there was some special reports
Beginner guide
Willie huge announcement coming up
At the bottom of the hour about the future of Infowars
I am about this organization at restructuring
Announce today
I told folks about how
Serious sometimes
Infowars is
Fighting for it
Just like the rest of the country in the world
Point six billion dollars
The black lives matter got from the New World Order
Get it from you and we can't fight if you don't support the Redbox they weather
There's restructuring going on in the infowar there's demotion
Nothing really specific
They're just kind of like the insinuation that we're going to talk about what
The future is going to look like around here
Are the future
I grow weary of this
Quite honestly because we've been
We've been on this
Setrac
Before we we've done some laps around
Grated
The move of firing
That one wasn't there
That's a big one that one stuff to undersell
That's tough to look at is like oh you're just blowing
Gunsmoke there's something there now whether it's
It's like a
Resources
Is there tight I got a call from Melanie and she said get rid of David
Goodnight
Is it a Steve situation or is it to money
I don't know
I can't tell
What's it what else is going on here Alex got anything to talk about other than your own don't b*******
Call me back on and get us out of the global system he did really a splendid job on many fronts
Made some big mistakes
And still with 34 days left if he levels of the American people
Resolute desk
Speeches
Washington peacefully
Capital to
Election fraud
Corporate media
Wo has a very good chance of holding up and back
Adjusted Department others land
The courage to do
The right thing
And prosecute
Alex is
Pretending that
Bunch of people could go March
And then the New World Order be like Plan B
First ten million people in one spot
Plan B when they're over there he'll be perfect weapon
Bio weapon in
I cannot work
This is a super bioweapons
The plan b
Super Bowl weather
Just can't I can't get it up for this kind of thing
Sad he does
Believe it
I can't I can't handle the guy trying to tell me that like we just need a bunch of people to March and then maybe
The cabal of people who've been planning this for thousands of years will be like oh no people
Already said that there's a plan B if all of them
If they manage
Do you like even if it get Trump back in office visit Plan B it's just everyone dies but it's a little less
Organize
How how
Why
What is this matter
I don't know but the idea of the devil who is been with Humanity
Since there were two
And now there are several billion of us
For him to be like woah 10 million is just too much
Ormeida it look I got to tell the NWO tobacco
Medically a little bit problematic for me that the New World Order would be doing
The devils
Bidding
Because the devil is told them that they
Should
And
I mean yeah
If the devil's I could
Who cares about 10 million people marching
It's no big deal I'll just keep going with their plans
Devil's phone
Or does he
I don't know he seems really
Dissident domestic politics
The whole big world out there for the devil
This is
Is it stupid and it feels trivial even within Alex's own
Conspiracy that I just don't care
You get back to your b******* Alex
I want to hear more about your your situation
Infowars I'll give you the good news
Infowars has
325 x volumes on Saturday May 6th
That we've ever had except for right around the last election
Spinal reflex
We do not have
Guy
That
Except
Shows going
In the field
Kept
To be able to have
Finding 222 run this operation
Take care of shortfalls
The other
Things I have is as an emergency backup
And it wouldn't find this place
Everything
Cuz it was a big operation
I don't know about that
Also I think that's
It's called being over at
Send it
That's sad
You could
You could also put that bus
We should have
Scaled back
Long time ago
No reason to not have
Hank was a bad purchase
No need for that tank Studio looks
Great amazing
Point maybe too big for just one person to sit there and maybe a little off
Ostentatious
In one of his special
I don't like that I remember that anyway look
You need to buy his products
Because Alex needs
Money shorthand
You know what you need them to you need the product student
Over here
For his leg had some medical stuff
Went to the doctor
I want to play Monster a load
Loti he didn't do it
Got tested again
On Monday
Jerseys that look at that
Birthday
Look at my numbers at 1
That's the type of things that are
Going on
You come through over and over again I keep telling you we can't keep operating
We can't keep doing this level
If you don't support us
Forest email spread the word
Your way
Klowdtv number one
Oann Newsmax
Pixar the worst
Thing that could happen for Alex
The fact that those two outlets are doing
Slick s***
They have some sort of financing from mysterious
Source I'm sure that better than 90
18 year olds working in their room
The ability to
Pretend that their news
They don't act like Alex
Screaming about the devil
They say the same s*** I absolutely
They have let her lie call David
Like
Editorial standards of Alex Monday. It's of a news thing
The worst thing ever for Alex he has no place in the market
Good anymore once
Unless he does something different as to Pivot
Or else like
It will just be
I'm another one of them is that no one will plug because I suck
Cuz I'm so toxic
It's at
Funny I kind of think
Alex is
Confused by that
Cuz I really do think
That when he sees his set
And the way a show run
He's like this looks like a news organization
You know he totally
He thinks that
So how can he look at oand Newsmax
To be like
They're just like me
You don't like is that wild
I don't think he watches anything other than
Set the time for ignore the interest
I think it's actually kind of interesting that beat
Because
Those things exist
It's things like Newsmax Roan
Like David naked
Easily get a job at either of them
Like babe
Accidentally created
Employability
For the people
That works for Alex like right through ART Alex
You created a situation where he can't hold
People hostage working at Infowars anymore if you have aspirations to be a right-wing journalist like
There are other option then
Yeah
Death Alex
Y'all got news is Shroyer's not going anywhere
I don't think so even after
You know
Nobody's hiring the evening even nuzback's is going to see Owen Shroyer walk in and be like
And you may turn around now
I can't tell exactly from listen
Coming to this but it does appear that Owen is the only other person who
Survive the
Oh s***
Like straight up
We'll get to it
Showing my cards too early
We should know that Alex would be very clear that he's not quitting
And so you know I said on Joe Rogan show
5 weeks ago I said I thought about retiring
In the media.
That was just too ghetto Joan trying to act like he's this
Reluctant hero
I only
Houston 5%
Basically no life other than this
All I do
I still feel like I'm not doing enough but I'm not going to quit
I can't imagine
And it being his wife and him being so bad
What are you putting
Time-It 2
I don't know
I don't know what code
Could he possibly
It in regards to the show
Okay you've dedicated your life to this show you talk for
3 to 4 hours
For being a very generous day
Door someone
Right right right
You don't
If you tell people that you read and I think something happened
While you were holding a thing
He reads headlines
He sees that then
Become bring thoughts over
Reading would be
The only thing I can imagine that would take a lot of time as maybe it requires like
Expensive meditation or yoga in order to get into his life
Prophetic
Psychic
Trantor has or whatever the headlines now
Guy gets into some kind of a weird trance-state
And then he reports on what the trance showed him about this
This headline as opposed to reading that the article
Too much time
How old is Mantra is
Soros
Alright
Laura can't I just
Can't imagine it doesn't need to practice
Talkingshit he's really good at it
Isaac
Ecstatic at it.
Time is preparing any clearly doesn't
This is not the end
It is a new chapter
What's been the greatest pleasure of my life 27 years on air
Knowing all of you
And and nnnnn fighting the New World Order
I'm not going anywhere
You know what I tell you that
The CIA follows us around in the FBI
Servicenow
They, sit down
Next Door restaurant
Visit us at the hotel
You want me arrested on Twitter
That isn't me scared
It's belying Infowars entering a new chapter of life
Embellishing probably more than lying
Michael Hayden did tweet
An agreement
With somebody who tweeted that Alec
Text be arrested
For his statement about Biden
At that rally over the weekend
I don't know
The new chapter
What is the new chapter
What does that mean
What does that entail
Are you can sell it up
With a song
Song title
No more mr.
Start
With
Not
Not.
Being delusional
About
Where we stand and what we
We can do
And the fact that I have this
Tenancy
And I own operations
Because
I'm so loyal even though
The point
Operation not being able
Up to this point you've been
Mr. nice guy
Speech
I can only hear that like
Imagining him just
Giving it directly to the Mir Aziz
He's putting the Joker makeup on
He's just giving this like no more mr. nice guy alright
Little bit more Rouge
I've never met
Release the Kraken
I don't know that guy never got out of that
I'm so it looked a lot of people are gone
And
There's some other people that you might have got got a listening
I didn't force that aren't around anymore
Pleasure you I'm going to work harder the fight against the ruler
Beautiful
Carter
But I've already explained to you
Millie Weaver
God bless her
It's okay
Dilaudid
I like the idea that Alex
Just trying to pretend that he didn't fire her for shadowgate
Modbee
Could you make up all this stuff
When I literally said I don't get into that stuff it's a scary this weirdo guy
From your film showed up at my store
Studio and then was talking about Rodger Stone in ways that I don't appreciate
His finances
That she's making up
Yeah bitlife
Because of things
In finances and the difficulties that Alex is in does the situation he's had to
Backup backup
There were people like Millie there were people like Kaitlin Bennett
But he was funding
And now he can't
He didn't do that anymore
34 years ago and I still owe him money I was funding
Dozens of organization
Doesn't the roofer.
I'm taking the money you said ispine product
I down to funding
Three or four organizations outside of our own operation now
But
Everybody said she hears me say that you don't think I'm serious
So
Organize
They only are four hours a day so is only 3 hours a day
Because there's
They're not the funds but not the money
Reorganize some of the other shows
And then revamping the relaunch him
Because
Never give up
But I can
Get out
Speckled horse the horses will run
And Ron and Ron tiller
Yeah he's okay he's like a horse
With his heart
Well I'm about to blow up
Keep going
So
From that cliff
What I take away is that Alexa
Countdown with Deanna Lorraine
A robber baron
Over
After that
Sorry Byron Alex is going to be on
Still and Owen
Conspicuous in its absence from that list is the only other show and that's David Knight show
These shows
Spell obviously
According to
Fortnite's Twitter you got fired
With somebody else
I guess he wants to bring in a younger crowd so you know 11 or 12 year old video games
Probably who is Godiva
Play Electric
Harrison Smith is
Is probably the best
They have there and that's bad
You can wear shades
You don't need to ask
So
Like
I think that this metaphor to is a little bit rough and I don't appreciate it
Alex talking about you know you could read your horse and he was running until your heart gives out
David Knight had a heart attack last year
And then he came back to work
Passionate about this s***
That's very funny
I don't want to be this guy
Giving a s*** when it's not my time to give it a rich but like David Knight gave a lot
He did
And we are now a couple weeks
Before Christmas
Haha
Markiplier
Absolutely that's so bad come on come on everybody
Feel bad for Bob Cratchit
What is when did they think about how
Screwed
Would like a f****** horse
Who is going to steal everybody's money until his heart gave out
Don't be thinking about Scrooge okay Dirty Man
You want them dirty
He couldn't wait until the new year
I just
I just want I just hope that David Knight is overwhelmed by not like
Sadness or
Grad or like
Anything other than just like
I am so stupid for coming back after that f****** heart attack
Well I should never have f****** done that it was slightly different hope and that is that I hope
It gets ugly
Like nothing negative
I hope you kept some receipts
I hope there's something real fun
Oh yeah
Alex's the force
Adidas running shoes
You need a break
Any good horse will run till it blows
You keep running horse it'll go to Lodi
Angie
Metaphysically but also physically got to that point
I can't stop working
I've got to take a week off
Got to turn everything off
Got to do it
Because I don't smoke coming out of the race car engine
You got to pull over again
I got to put some oil in there
Put oil in the horse
Just went to
DC
Just took a
Took a trip to
DC
Now that was work
That was work
Related
Take a week off Alex
Please
I was wondering like what
Bisquick
Confuse the hell out of
Subscribe to his last straw was
Okay it's something that doesn't make any sense
Your support
And I love you and I appreciate you and I and I
The last straw was this morning I got up and I saw this number
Billion
When you go in a coffee shop like Starbucks right where they said give it
Directions to communist of the globalist and Soros collecting money
That was a few months ago that was for billion that I read that gotten
That's all just miss misinterpretations of the active blue stuff
Yeah I don't know why
Black lives matter getting a certain amount of money
Would be the last straw for him
Cuz it doesn't materially affect what key
He's doing at all if I understand correctly I wrote this down as I was track
Alright so I wrote down first BLM raised 10 billion and then
So I fired David Knight
Is that that is that the event statement that I think we're going for here.
There's a weird feeling of it but I think if you distill it down even more it's like
I saw that black lives matter made 10 billion dollars
I'm not making close to that and it pisses me off
So I'm going to fire David
Lorraine
Just kind of like a temp
She's an independent
She was there on a little bit of a assignment or whatever
She was there for long-term
I think
I just yeah I don't know
I'm very
Conflicted because there's two sides of this that I think Goodwin
Is like the
David Knight has run afoul of Steve pieczenik in a very serious way
And that is something that
It's hard to have in-house
I have somebody who is your intro show on your network
Right before you
Who's saying that one of your expertise
Is a piece of s*** liar
Going to be tough to maintain status quo
And you're a media Outlet
That is built in
Entirely around Bombay
So it seems fairly simple to be like okay well we've got the most boring man ever
And we've got
The most bombastic liar ever
I think we're going to go with the most Boombastic liar yeah yeah and also you can't really have
A whole lot of
Stability in
Keeping
Keeping people
Auden gay
I guess you gave done engage
Real people
Actively can
Assuming your material be engaging with it
And haven't even
Might be like Steve pieczenik the f****** liar
Why does why does David Knight
Think that he
Why doesn't Alex not
Too complicated and
You run the risk of kick-starting like
Critical thinking in your listeners yoga absolutely not
I stick with picture
That was a little bit ago there's a couple weeks
Tagalog
No
Draw causal link
Here and Alex is saying that it's
Because of money
Sure
Now the only things that are gone are the night
Show witch
Obviously sucked the evening show that no one
Cared about OverWatch
They canceled when Alex went to DC because they didn't have the crew to run it anyway
Already like a
Secondary tertiary thought for them
David Knight show
Paper easily could be monetary budget
Constraints
I can also see a possible world where Alex was like
Buckeye got to get rid of David Knight
It's just not working out
This is an untenable
Situation
How can we fund-raised on
How can I drive
Sales
With
Getting rid of
I don't know I can't say I have no f****** idea
None of it seems good
Seems like this is a
No I wouldn't look at any of these circumstances and be like
I'm going to invest
Send this busy
Businesses model looks good I'm going to wait till it hits Rock Bottom first
It's unclear because last clip here from the seven
Now it's kind of implies that
The Christmas sale will determine the future of until
Peculiar Christmas shop
Infowarsstore.com
Will expand
But if you don't look at
Reassessing right now
Add Infowars is control
I have a big
Offensive
Or just the next event
I promise you this will go out fiery Inferno of Liberty in a peaceful
Operation
Peaceful
Weasel
I do take offense of a couple times are in a fiery blaze of
Don't worry I would like one last image of
Infowars to be Alex standing in the studio as Everything Burns around him with his arm
Outstretched his head facing in
Screaming into the sky I think that's how he's got to go out
Sure write that last image
I don't want to die
Big Bertha Life movie
Dark Harry Oldman in the
Professional whenever he lays eyes are all bloodshot and he's screaming to this guy
Play this last year from the 17th I have one more but it
It's just sort of like indicative of like me losing my page
Alex and why working at now jump back
To the 16th
To see what thing
We're like
24-hours
Malik spending the beginning of his show talking about how
Dyer s*** is
Hey David nights fire
Andres
Manuel Lopez
Is a socialist
By that I mean the popular socialist
Is actually trying to get
Corporations actually not
How to do that model long-term butt
Sir Alex
Alex has decided that he likes of the president-elect
Mexico because they
There was some comments about covid
Precautions that Alex enjoyed
What is a real sexual
Ever
You hate people who don't understand socialism who think the
God I hate you hate people who you decide or socialist
So are we jumping we are there any signs
Are there any indications that we can get from the sea
16th and Blake
A day later never had more money than we had right now
We're just so f***
King flush anyways
We'll see how it goes tomorrow
So we start with Alex
America and the rest of the world is under globalist
Intech Siege
Corporate planetary takeover
And make us obsolete
Lee Von mises Institute
Is highly respect
With some of the top
Academic
Researchers Economist in the world
Then come out a big article that's on infowars.com
Where they say
This is a
Dystopic
Tech
Bio / digital
Technocracy
Mises Institute is not super well-respected there is like hardcore libertarian
They're great one of the articles that I covered from their website was a defense
Of not feeding your children
Because you don't have positive responsibilities towards people exactly
Yeah that they're cool Libertarians
Jephthah
Just a s***
Like if you're writing the in defense of not feeding your own kid
You're just a s*******
You're also not going to not
Feed your child
You're doing this is some kind of a weird mentally intellectual masturbation
But Alex
Not too long ago was talking about how being a Libertarian was the stupidest thing you've ever done
The Beast
But they're real libertarian
The smartest thing you
Convey
Barnes
He shows camp
24 hours earlier
Lawyer
Marshalls
He's in liaison the White House
I can tell you that
Why
Can you tell me that he would care now
Doesn't care that's why
If he doesn't want that no no
Why would you tell me that this is private but Barnes is working with
But the White House is okay so the White House is fine but you know
And he personally asked
There's no show the evening cancelled
From Alex
There is no
Sent that like
Barnes has been not doing this show it's
Going to come to an end
Sure
A pretty abrupt abrupt
Speaking of which
This seemed abrupt
Here's the big news
Where the coverage start the next segment
McConnell to his wife
Atwater Republican to Chinese payroll for a long time
Mitch McConnell's bad finally it's been so long since we've remembered how may
How many people are bad Dan Mitch McConnell has recognized in election that matters
I remember all these things about him or I just going to make up a diesel
That's great
Absolutely Alex McConnell is a billion
Go after him
Hell yeah
McConnell
We told you Amy Coleman bear at every told you Kavanaugh
Amy told you all
We're going to press
Because
Out of the swamp
Yep
You told them that the only reason to stick with trouble with so he could get those
Just too long ago
Brian Cavanaugh all about Cavanaugh
Alex was so in favor that is if he was squeezed himself
Culmination
It was a little more confusing the Barrett
Nomination
Because
Yeah you did have barns coming in and saying this is a really bad idea
They shouldn't go this route
And Alex having to dance around and
Support her domination
He was in favor of it
Catholics
I don't like Catholic somebody else like I think she's great.
But they're all villains now man
We got a lot of new feelings
Sloughing or Alex
Fight amongst yourselves I want to make you hurt each other more
So Rodger Stone
Bongo came on
I'm broke some gigantic
Tech news
Man boats
North Korea arrived
Ripen main main
United States
Different
Situation
Carnivore COPD of electoral college brawl in Congress
Trump.is electors
They seated are they lock the real electors out of the state houses
We're supposed to just go along with this and not let the president
America
Press their attack
Screwed
You're so far by mostly governor
Because they're all bunch of cowards
Brasstacks EC mathematics possible
In all those States
We're Trump's wedding.
And then as soon as they close the pole
Food delivery vehicles United
Chinese men
Run into these big containers
And then inside we have the footage
Other workers in their advantage fast as they can
You have a Chinese government plane
Flying out of China Landing
Boxes of balance so now the Chinese government is sending their own planes with Charter numbers
Right at arriving with ballots on election
Convey
So I to the North Korean Buck boat like a
Backup
Okay we'll send the boats in like March of this year and
China going to have the plan to airlift them in and everything but went but
Worst comes to worst the boats will be in Maine in November here's what I'm
I'm thinking
Let the Chinese planes brought in
Pallets
Big boxes of ballots
Provider
Okay now the boats
We're Rogue
They were crazy trailer for Jorgensen
They were carrying down-ballot
For the 26
Team election
And the North Koreans
Just got to
That would make more sense
I would make
I just feel like it's a silly
And
Need a lot more
I approve of this witch
Alex is not forthcoming with
But something it is also
Not surprised
Alex
Want to do over
Electoral College certification
Yes
X24 press
4 years
Get the f*** out of
Pants Paul Paul
Call Penn State will be good
Okay
Call pimp
Paul Pence
Aspire the masses
Oh my God yeah you want Rand Paul back
Fun how interesting
Pence can't be president because
Nobody wants to live in a world where we have to
To call his wife the first mother that's just not happen
It's just not happy
Grandpa you had your chance Alex you turned your back on him for Trump
You know that it's over
We all watch that happen
Raymond isn't like Joe Rogan where you can turn your back on him and he'll accept
Kept you once more no I know B
Because he refuses to
Debate me and
That's the only thing
So Robert Barnes
For another couple hours of the election countdown
What is on
And he wants you to know that he also thinks that Mitch McConnell is a traitor
DF
Is it leads an inference
All along these
The people are undermining the president
And now
It was Mitch McConnell all along betraying and undermining
Sabotaging the president
It's not a coincidence
Is Attorney General
Texas lawsuit
Yeah I want that too
Trump rally at where we're at
So Mitch McConnell was screwing it up the whole time he was the the the the trailer behind the scenes
Alright
If you try and pull that
Now after this law
After this long
Then either you have to shut up forever because everything that you've told me if Mitch
McConnell's the secret bad guy the whole time
He was there
Yeah you know
Yeah and it's um
I don't know it
Trying too hard to make an interesting plot twist
And I am not going to go along for this this ride anybody who does
But you see this like
There are just like
Shoring up of rank
I was like the people who are
Blindly willing to just
Greeley throw away any kind of semblance of dignity that they have for Trump
They're good
Everybody else
Do they work
Owens and I have bad news for you
Was that Pence Paul ticket might not be happening after all
Is Reese's too.
Depends is truly loyal to Trump
During Access Hollywood Pence was trying to navigate Trump
So that he could be top of the
Ticket in 2016
Was Pence
Going to go she ate with Ecuador to get
Julian Assange arrested and extradited
Ballet in a lot of the never trumper's and problem people have
Come from pencil
Group of people
The White House
Good
Enemies arrested governor of Georgia Meto the defense bill
Turn little place down around your ears
Just a little much
It's a little much
It's a little cartoon
Like defining good and bad people now
I think it's it's
It's really just sad though
Because
It's it's like
You obviously weren't actually
There's no possible way that you could be fooled by that s*** you knew had to have known that they were lying the whole time
They didn't really like Trump
Quickest route to f****** lunatic
And their old career politician
Right
Alphabet don't know that
Then
That's just so sad
Especially because
I've been telling you that for my entire
Immediately
It's really interesting for me in particular.
To see you like
The
Turning on
On people so bluntly and so stupidly
Laytonville bar was
He went back and forth a number of times Barnes coming in here saying that everyone's Anatomy
For a while and now he's permanently out
Sing the dog out he's out
So on the 17th
We learned that that two barns show is gone
But just barnstone
How's the election countdown
7 to 9 p.m. most nights with you on Lorain
16-piece promoting the show is Barnes his back he's been too busy but now he's back very fine
Gone
That's very funny
I think I think you're right I do
You kind of feel for David Knight a little bit he's losing his job right before
For Christmas
I enjoy seeing bat
Things happened to Rob
Barnes
In a different way and I know that if he doesn't have his f******
Moonlighting gig at Infowars he's going to be fine scamming other people with fake constitutional lawsuit I think he has
Watching him
I think he has like a newsletter on Dave Rubin
Kickstarter or Kalyan clone
15in all right
So Alex
Start says farewell to Barnes I will see you on the evening show that won't exist
Hilarious and now I must get to another gas
Suggest that I got the privilege
Hanging out with
DC when I was there yelling
And all this s***
Oh no
Someone who had the best
Speech
Oh no
Powerful messages
Million Maga March
This was about
A gigantic one
It was a month ago
People total
Last time I had the most powerful message that we're not going to back down to the club list the New World Order
Message
These events
Yeah they're not going to be for sure because I watch
Hours
Of these rallies not speak at
Either of the two rallies but I watch
He was clearly speaking in some fashion
Bullhorn on the street
Something
Might have been like a third event that I would just don't even know about that
I only have so much time in my life I can only watch so many of these routes
Soon
Do you know
McConnell
Barrett
Kavanaugh
Nikki said
The GOP is the enemy
I said Sunday
2 RC Saturday speeches
Republican party establishment are the enemies
But
We have to make sure that doesn't get damaged
Target
Neocon
Populist America first
McConnell
He's definitely
Working for the other side
That's not what McConnell saying he's he's saying that you're insisting on
Denying reality is probably going to hurt our electoral chances
Hey you guys you know how you're screaming that all elections are frauds and that you should
Vote
That's going to hurt us in the election
Where we need you to vote
Know your Chinese Asia
Damn it maybe I've gone too far I miss McConnell so I will learn the error of my ways
Nope
He will end up having
The people that you have inspired and enabled in facilitated now screaming at rallies about how
We need to destroy you
Excellent
One of the eclipse
Laying out the future
And the future battle plan
At least
Game of chance
Alex's think I think he sees that video and he remembers like being in dcne remembers like
Go to mad at those
Women for America
The first people
I don't like how they organize these rallies and then don't let me speak with them cuz I'm entitled to
This is a parallelogram allegory
Submariner battleship
A truck
Give five towards women that are neocon
It is just
Falling asleep
A lot of the hundred thousand people 20,000 here you run over
They're all cheering and then
Muse
And then the poor Republicans of a Mainline
I know a little trumpet Scott deal
They get 20,000
Popular it's not constitutional
Everyone's always running away from
What Victoria
I don't think is wrong stuff
Speakers Worth news
Bright star quality
Scooter the misunderstanding
Like spectacle for Subs
Yeah yeah
Like I don't
Think there's anything
And being able to draw a crowd of
10000 let's say
Isn't it
An indication that he knows the Constitution I don't think there's a difference for him between 70
You know it's not that he understands our misunderstanding or it's just that it doesn't exist
Yeah you know like five million views means
500 million people love that's right that's how it barks yeah that's the only makes sense also I'd like to clarify one thing
These people starting these rallies and organizing them and getting the permits does mean that they
You can choose who speaks at it and who doesn't well I feel like I'm missing the part where he was going to say like
So next time we are going to get the
The permit
He's not going to say that
We'll see cuz it feels like that
What's the real complaint here
Imo's just whining that he's not the winner he's too busy
Call the work
Not psychic trances
Take a while
I know somebody who just lost his job and is free
I don't think he's going to fill those shoes
Nick Fuentes has an interesting idea for the way forward
For these weirdo conservative
Democrats that were saying destroy the GOP this is a message I could get behind
First half of the message
Destroy the GOP
As it exists destroy the GOP establishment
Did you know
We have to destroy the
GOP establishment headed by Mitch McConnell
What's America last
We have two primary all those p
People replace them
And house in the Senate
And the state government
And we have to replace them with people that truly believe in America First truly believe in
President
When he ran in 2016
Look Nick Fuentes like 14 years old
So I'm going to forgive him for not remembering that they did this already
Is called
This is the crazier version that you guys wanted last
Yeah you already have another cycle of this like
Whatever
Who cares
I want to forgive that
What I'm not going to forgive is
The fact that he doesn't remember they did that
This year over with running
Tell these other people Enrique tarrio was your run everybody lost a f****** primaries
Because the people that you end up attracting
Are not now.
Bull in the primary
Thought they were voting for a GOP candidate cuz they've been in there for a while but they were actually voting for a traitor
Bright
Okay
Got to go I think we should all be
I apologize I believe Loomer did win her primary
Send the general
Folks
Boston
Primaries
No I
Adele
I think we should all be screaming it established
Republicans
The only way
The GOP it survives as if they all band
Together in crush the extreme right-wing
And I think we tell the extreme right-wing that the only way the gop's
Survives if they band together
I'm crushing The Establishment Republican
I forget to send
At least half of that's going to happen on its own
Probably true that's why we got to make sure both happen because it would have happened
We're going to get to the Tea Party
I don't know if that's avoidable
Interesting Lee
Nikola Tesla under Alex
Except slightly different strategies about what they should do in Florida Georgia
Time of the belief that
The first blow the Wii
Republican Party
Withholding are votes in Georgia
What's holding our votes in the Senate runoff and preventing them from
Reclaiming control this out
Alex is not into that that is I don't know about that
His position is
Q primary
Some Republican you know with a crazy person
I'm all for that
Torpedoing the election
Lesbian letting a Democrat
I don't know
We need to punish the Republican party with holder votes
He's very much like
Accelerationist
Taking Alex's more like
I don't know
These people just
Straight up
How
How f******
Cruel are you to me
To be like
We're going to tell everybody with troubles
Pictures of God
Florida jail
And after losing election what we need to do is we need to focus on
Small election
And we need to primary the Republican
Que ya
The Lord also needs primary from time to time
Yeah with the with the seitan made
Forget was
County
Because an interesting angle on qanon
What I like about the qanon stuff
Papa's that it gets a lot of people to believe the right things
I believe the right things for the wrong reason
Against them to start thinking about Connections
Between Global special interest
Write questions about
Files and seitan
Delete some things like that
Largely for the wrong reasons
I do appreciate
The hubris
Of all of these idiot
Who are alike
You know what we need
To do is get the
The swirling masses
To believe something
Similar to what I believe
And then I'll be able to come
Control
It doesn't quite work that way anyways
No sorry
Box
I will say again
I'm going
To give
Make a pass on this
Cuz he has a wee baby
But he seems to be patting himself on the back a little bit for
Discovering
The concept of local politics
Now Trump wants this house
Takeover of
And now we have to wage war for everything beneath the presidents
We have to wage war the primary
House Republican Senate Republicans
We have to run in
Racism local races we have to take over the RNC in the party apparatus
Better said that was perfectly said
It's so trite
I have
In 2016
In 2014
I have 2012 Revolution Aries stuff
This is very Bland
Start of one of the things that I think is interesting and a little B
Scary about
Is that like
Like beanies
This there's also an obsession with the idea of fighting against
Amnesty
And and and identity and America is also like
Okay yeah you're talkin about running for
A local election
Running for like the school president
Or whatever
Like that that b the banality than the boring
With the evilness hidden behind it it's kind of
Scary Biden is stealing the election in
Caroline all events at the
F****** globalist
And that is why I'm going to vote no on the expansion of that road
Route 6
Mechanics out of there
In-N-Out
In-N-Out got destroyed the GOP
Now we're going to play a new game
On the show
I'm going to play
An angry clip
Got from Alex Jones
See what are you without
Who is targeted at you have to guess who is he yelling about
This is called
Guess who Alex's telling to burn in hell
Inhale you little Satanist
Great you are now
Amazing you are
Global collapse
Who is Alex
No
It's little I thought the little weekend asking me
I can ask you two questions
All right Richard
Very very very rich
I don't know if I want to say
Obscene labor
All right I wish you five questions I wish I had some more specific
Is very rich is a is a more subjective question that I think I would
Superheroes
Billionaire higher
I don't know I have a really hard time
I-25
Gmod
His or her appearance
No
Oh I meant Alice
I don't think so
Open it's definitely not stelter I'm not sure I've heard Alex bring this person up before
Little Liza Jane
You have all the pieces you need
Jesus's wife
No
Tom Cruise
Daniel threw you played the player
Nick Fuentes is gone
Barnes has come on there's no indication of anything
Trouble in Paradise as it were
Bourdon actually listening to this episode now because like listen to this this is 30 seconds
This is what Alex thinks
Is a
Dance to it this is
He thinks his job is
Pompeo test negative
Covid-19
Oh my gosh it's so scary
Excuse for Tom Cruise in
Staring at the screen
Over-the-counter home test for covid-19
Kansas
Mayor resigns were violent threats from
That's it like this
Substance of his news breakdown like it's kind of like
Like a like a dishy insult after reading
This is Bill
Cruz didn't need
The Bachelorette
He gets to act like he owns everything and run
The place because he's
The figurehead of a religion
Find it strange that Alex isn't taking issue with a Scientology aspect no problem no.
Now that makes perfect sense
So Alex has
Just been dealing with
Hayden
General Hayden
On Twitter that he agreed with someone else who tweeted that Alex
Should be arrested and Alex
Pumps
Of course he is
CNN
Complication
Alex Jones maybe arrested
Did Jones threatened to kill by
Sunday
Call for Jones be arrested for threatening to kill
Monday
Alex is so excited about this
Michael Hayden is paying attention to him in a way that he probably would never I got
Month Saturday
Imply the
Maybe Michael Aiden's a pedophile
Mysterious
Orphanages
And springs for children
Looks like a
He's a child molester
Dog shelter looks
Hayden's on Twitter photo
Is the creepiest photo on please pull up
Michael D Higgins Shelbyville
It's not that creepy
Sometimes I'm just not sure if things are
Real now it's very weird
What is this real Am I Dreaming what
What are we what's going on pretty strain
This guy has tweeted something I dislike
I am going to occur
Accuse him of stealing children because he looks creepy to me
Yeah but Alex
Okay gotcha
I don't know
Harrison
Smith probably someone who works at Infowars
Hayden's Twitter timeline and found some things
To get upset about
Great reset
He put out a bunch of plates and pro-life about Trump
Decision
So what diseases that he tweeted a picture of like Graves
It was from another account
He retweeted a with a quote tweet
Pro-life?
Bright
MMA
Put out
Did the Joker town
An image of a mass grave
Killing everybody
Because churches could be open
Close up
Literally days later
Disguise
He puts out a pitch
Steelers
Let's do some football
Happy birthday
No social distancing NFL game
Imagine the irony of this piece
Trump is murdering people because of
Moscow Mule done with 10 people thousand whatever
Walmart to be open
Can be open
Disneyland can be open
But
Your churches can
Liquor stores are open
All this is going on but he's a big
Pittsburgh Steelers
Aiden
Open source
Open source baby
GIF that he tweeted was from last season
The football
Back when there were huge crowds
Putting their towels in the air
Great
It it's not a gotcha
It's not that.
Now the only thing sadder than reading those two
Tweet this girl
Going through his timeline
Find those
Yeah and then I was thinking this is like
Can own
I got you open source
I mean when you read when you read too much about tweets
You know
You can read everybody
Breeding 1322
But would you read about
Now we're in real file articles are about
No f******
Crazy ass
It seems trivial
So I was getting a little bit like I don't know I feel untethered
I don't know what's going on here
You know I feel like
Really important
Alex is downsizing
Well I got.
Effective immediately dad Bono
Why doesn't feel like at all like anything is going on here on the 16th
It seems very much.
Just business as usual
Anaconda was boring
Yeah just Nick Fuentes has a great idea.
To destroy the GOP but also I don't want to do what
Nick wants a suggestion
Yeah yeah would have seats and I don't like that
Like I don't know
And then
Patrick
I can't remember his last name
It'll come to me later
No he's the guy who's the Overstock CEO
Who is dating that Russian spy little bit out there
He's back
He has an interesting story to tell
Here in the my pillow guy should have a tag team wrestling team like something
This guy Patrick
Overstock CEO introduced Michael Flynn at the rally of course
Why wouldn't I just agree with that guy bring that up on the show cuz his speech was kind of like I don't care
What
He is back
With Alex
Amman
He's got a big old story to tell
I believe her story
Alot of things on Hillary she was very area
To taking over what $2000000
Different government money
To give him access that's what
Email server shows
Now the southern district has been investigating
Will you came out and said this and I saw the video yesterday
I said that's the same stuff I got told that there were successful thing
On Hillary but they when they thought she was going to win
Scrubbed and then
Has all that info
The latest
Alex has played a clip of Patrick from another show
And
He's telling this story that he got approached by the FBI
Do facilitate a sting operation on Hillary Clinton
Alright man eventually they're like we're not going to do anything you know.
You're giving up
Taking a bribe from a phone
Say anything about it until
Credible
That sounds right
I want you want to know why
The process
Conversation
Comfortable
So I waited really nice
So he's got it
He's got to tell his story now cuz of the elections over he's free to
To tell at all
Throw tomatoes
Eaton 2015
December 15th
He was a pro
Approached by the FBI course
December
2015 we need you
The email group and we know that's the New Yorker
I don't know if
It's
It should be
Seeing as like normal
Investigation
Starts with wanting to incarcerate somebody that's probably not.
Tainted investigators
It's almost like one that wouldn't really hold up upon
And it seems like if any of this is true which I don't think any of it is Comey might have been coming from the position
There's no reason
You guys are telling me that you want to talk to the CEO of overstock.com to try and sting Hillary
Clinton guess who doesn't get to do that you guys
It's go away now
Can I show all of my cards
I don't believe any of this
I will say this I didn't leave this video is making this s*** right off the bat the only thing eidetic
About this guy's memories that he was able to able to remember the word
He didn't memorize that is
Bullshitz here's the deal
Turkey
Has already bribed
Hillary Clinton
420 million
So now we
You just need to get Patrick
To facilitate another bra
Predicate information
However
And
Information
And the group in New York is now you
Force
New York
And you're going to facilitate
Who was known to want to bribe he has an eidetic memory you should remember
And somewhere
And it's going to happen in the next 2 months
From weather's been derailed somewhere they will be rude
So he's got to find he's got to befriend this government from unnamed other government
Himself in such a way that he can be the go-between between and Hillary
Clinton
This
I'm just going to throw that out there a huge question sure this story I'm just going to go out and say
Why did they come to him
Because
Experience cozying up to governments or in any sort of like
Russian spy
Started Overstock
Okay
Sia I Do I Do I Do by any of this so complicated
And
I can't
I just can't imagine any of this
You're dating also also government
On that
Appointment
That's said
This is also a staying on that Bag Man
Because that other government isn't going
They think that this is a real
He's playing
The bad man is not in the other foreign government is trying to entrap Hillary Clinton along with the help of the FBI
I don't think so the only people that I'm interested is turkey they want their money back I guess that's it the Overstock
Guy
I think the Patrick had a really reasonable response
To this man if I do this
Commit crimes
You better not arrest me for those crimes they commit in order to set this up
I need immunity
This sounds like somebody writing a much better movie where they didn't commit all the crimes that they did
Said they were not
This is this is
Is the clip where really turned
For me too
Probably like
They gave me that
There's going to be some
I need a
I said
Enough for me consider Hillary
Holyshit okay okay
Okay so this is why
This is 2015
Wow
Obama is like it's time to take Hill down
It's time to take her down I had her a Secretary of State for long enough
And now we just got to get rid of her well it starts
Makes sense when they come back from break
And they lay out more what
The conspiracy is here to put your head around like
Oh yes
Obama trying to stay Miller singing
Stop
Stop me real quick
If cuz I could be wrong is it
Regular practice
Just for the FBI
Do clandestinely come to you
And say
We need you to
Sing
The most
Famous woman in the world
I love you tell you this
We got no ideas
Go for it buddy
However you think you can make this
Sting happened we're not even giving you a hell
You're basically MacGyver
You know what to do
Look at the FBI don't like to micromanage
Companies that do your thing
Obama
Famously
Super spy guy from Overstock
Show me on this story more and more I'm imagining this guide
Play coming in from the ceiling on wires only image of spy work
Come back from break
He said something really interesting okay makes me think like oh
He might know more about Alex than he's letting on
There is a coup
People
Anyway
The only thing is I want to be clear I have nothing
Call Pure crap
Why are you why why did you need to bring that up
People were saying that I don't believe in any of this white identitarian nonsense
Just in case anyone ass
Yeah that's why I don't know
Today is not taking as many media appearances
Some
Sure I've never found that I needed to distance
Myself from White identitarianism
If you do that kind of is because you know that the person
You're talking to Mike
Nothing like being interviewed after Nick
Puentes
Yeah I mean
This is a really complicated
Kind of such a look before we go any further I just want to let you know that I do not
Support the actions of the thuggee cult
From Temple of Doom
I don't support that I don't know why I need to say that here
Raises questions
The Sting
Forgot
Cover up
So good how I pulled off
Probably the best thing.
When things fell apart.
From being president
Bodacious
Everyone
Dispassionate
And we mean it
Every moment of this
Wow
He can't be sure I understand
I do believe
Any of that none of it
But I want to be clear about something
If
You make a claim like this
What we should do as a society is immediately put you in front of like
The most serious Court
That is imaginable produced seven
Cuz the stakes of this are way too hot
Crazy if you are telling the truth
Mistakes and the importance for the public good
So important
But you cannot
Not proven
Absolutely
If you are lying you need to go to prison
Because the stakes are so serious and that side too
You can't be allowed tomato
These sorts of claims
That are about like International Espionage and like plots against
Society
Just do it with impunity
You can't prove this
You can't make claims like that
Right that's how I would that I would like to
Think Shaker system of pneumatic
Like tubes where you you make a claim like this and then all the sudden
And then you're in the Courtney like it should not be a situation
No like your
Punished
Punitive
Unless you clearly making this s*** up
Yeah
Just to
Too serious
No I think I know I think with with swings this big
We're not dealing with quite as much Nuance in the law
You know incredibly easy to prove very simple
Very simple like
If you selling
If there'd be so much
Documentation
I don't care about him saying you have to wipe it from your memory
Well guess what Hillary didn't become president do all that
Pier
Of her like reprising again
People didn't come to pass they're probably be tons of people within the FBI who would
Corroborate your story short I going to guess that you remember the bag man's name you would say maybe the country that
Bribed a Hillary
I I don't know
Offensive to me
The timeline of The Story Goes this
A December 2015 2015
Alright
He kicks ass on the sting gets all the way
To somewhere in 2015 where everybody in the higher-ups decided that Hillary going to win
Alright so they just decided that it's over right
And then Hillary doesn't win
And I believe that was the same year correct
Yeah and then there was the new president
Spawn
January
If I were somebody who would just
Successfully executed a sting operation
Hillary Clint
Bright
Who is Empresa
Someone who is famous at that it's not just not present
But someone who lost to the guy who screamed
Lock her up
Oh yeah in like a whole big crowds of people changing that to you to wait until after
He had lost his elect
Tell people
I would go to him
Yet
Yeah
If you
If you were inclined
To take
The
Involved in
That kind of Espionage sting operation work again
Hillary Clinton
Involving a foreign government
You're willing to take those kinds of risks
I would assume yeah I bought
What's Trump won new be like
I
Got to do this whole thing
I did all the work
It wasn't for nothing
They probably will let me do it
Like I'll put the handcuffs on her
It didn't happen because it
I'm going to go with that one yet I got Valentine's reasonable I was kind of confused about the idea that Obama was behind
But Patrick has clear that up here
Express
You need to understand
Play January 2016
People are different
Understand
Especially Department of Justice
Hillary Clinton
Bunsen burner
Information
Bad girl
And that way
Barack Obama
Find you don't want to step on this line
The story is too good Alex here interrupting
Do you know how many times people with an eidetic
Memory say
And this is worth
Forward reminder
They do say that a lot I would imagine
I don't know
They say it initially
One time and then you're like
You're telling the truth they don't repeat over and over and over again in the
The same story
Yeah
Obama was going to manage Hillary because he had this Leverage
Jon-hurwitz this this this the bribe that the Overstock
Right
And she's going to step down
Say that again cuz I did mess up the Bucs won
The bunch of Mars been turned upside down
Then she's going to step down and Michelle's going to
That's the plan
Well that makes perfect sense with
Literal zombie makeup
So much status
This ridiculous story that this dude is telling on your show he
Cake with
Out any kind of article
That just makes so much sense
No real follow-up questions as to what the
The f*** are you talking about
He gets to the end of the story
This was an Obama setup so he could blackmail Hillary and that 8 years
He beat the shadow president behind Hillary and then his wife would be president after that hahaha
This is
Yeah
BoBoiBoy
What kind of fun
It is kind
I do like this
He thinks that it
It's such a good
Great punchline
Find that it's Michelle. Going to run
You you under
Understand that we on Infowars
Have been screaming about Michelle Obama becoming president
Since 2009
Buddy
Verify
They've been on that train
For a while with a Michelle is the secret at the end of this
Conspiracy
I also just
I just don't
There's a
Good
Use for this
Conspiracy
Sure cuz it takes some of the agency away from their biggest bad
Person which is the clintons
No it's like McConnell the secret one was Obama
Hillary is like the devil that you have to be afraid of
It doesn't make sense for her to then be a
Hatsy of Obama
I get there
It's not emotionally unsatisfying now the Infowars universe
Also just
Approve any of
Dick I think it's a fun s*** talking
Can story and if you if you wrote this down and he was like I'm going to try it
Can sell this to people
One he needs to get better at
Is delivery because two adults
This delivery doesn't matter how bad it is without going to believe him
Patrick says he has two more bombshells
That are coming eventually
The weekday has speaker swing coming in the future
But we will have to wait
For those
Island love
Bombshells
Next Monday
Whenever you are we appreciate you would appreciate
Your time and thank you so much for coming on short notice
Hahaha
You'll be fine
Remind me of the Jerome corsi might die over the weekend you get a dead man switch
Oh man
No I can't come back on Monday Alex
This is going to take me at least another week to write to I mean I can't remember do know I have an eidetic memory I mean
Yet so that was that was an interesting kind of
I don't know change
I found that to be
Took down the garden
Path for a nice little walk at night
And we shall return
I also like the idea to that like
This picture guy is like
Clearly someone who has
Some status
At least in his own mind
Bechtel Alex you stepped on my punchline
Going to save you
View heart rate a lot
He has a little bit of flex
Kind of fun
That is what else was thinking like alright this guy's clearly little nutty
Is he the new Larry
Is he the new Larry Nichols
I wonder
Here's what I would
What city is wasn't on today
Now I'm wondering when
Exactly Stevie pieces
Probably tomorrow I don't know nothing going on between stevia
David Knight. Steve's not even for a little while so we got Overstock guy
To try and
Thread the needle of his
Steve and he has so much of the Steve and so much of the lariat
Put them in one
Yeah I don't know it's
It's tough for me because you know we got blindsided by this news
What about the the David Knight
As I look into the episode itself and you find that
Oh maybe there's
Or maybe this
Yet again Alex
Over
Playing some kind of a desperation to move product
Who knows I don't know I have no idea what's going on there
Things don't look good
Makes me even more suspicious
The day before
There's really no indication of anything that there's no trouble
He's promoting
Countdown
Countdown show
But now apparently
Continue
Yeah
It's it's a it's a little bit out of nowhere
Here's my here's my
On a mic
Conspiracy now
This is what I've got for you on this
Alright
Infowars
Not doing great right now
Not going to go out of business but they're not doing great right now
Okay I need some
Star this is this
Little couple of weeks you know what everybody takes a Christmas
Miss vacation
And if you
You took of Christmas Vacation
That would be
That exciting we're in the middle of fighting the goddamn infowar
How do you go out on vacation
I see what you're doing what we do is
We say we got to let
Hugo I save money on overhead cost for a
Couple of weeks
After the big Christmas sale weekend
Merry Christmas and we get all the money in and then I'm like
Guys
And weary to exactly
Yeah that would be interesting I will be in I don't know if they can pull that off I don't think so either
I'm interested
Did you see what ends up happening
But not that interested
Sure
To make me interests
Gas
Mecare make me care fight
Do something for my amusement the other thing too that I think is is really key is that like
Alex is a
About to enter a very profitable space
Which is returning to the
Attacking the GOP
Like Purity in the GOP
You kind of thing is really really
Profitable
Store like right-wing talk shows
That's worked for million
Right
But
He also has never had to do it
Wow there were
Large
Funded
Competitors
And I don't know if
He can be
Oan
Yeah it's
Difficult whenever you also have like
Because before you had Fox News crash in the Tea Party Wing just like
Killing everybody
But Alex even then still got to exist in that space
Everybody
Sucks and I hate them all but Obama's the devil into that whole thing
But Fox News wasn't
Also Hayden
Mitch McConnell at
No they did have going back being a little nutty
Conspiracy
But like to have two networks that they computer you know what I'm saying
Alex did have some competition in the
The form of Glenn Beck's
It was still like
He would say a lot of s*** The Glenn Beck probably wouldn't
And so
I don't know
I don't I don't know
Substantially what he can do
To differentiate himself
From the competitors now but
Job I think it's the only thing he could do and I don't think he's capable of
Overstock guy I don't think it's possible
Folks
We are victorious Dallas drivers local charity or bail Fund in your area to help out those doing
Right now
Let me know I'm Leo and bcx Clark I'm Daryl run to some more like
Dot-com
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color