Damn important I sweat it
I have great respect for its knowledge B
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Acknowledge
Sequestered
What's up Jordan
Whatsyourprice
My bright spot today is wonderful intersection of aspiration and limitations
All right.
Finishing an inch
Tire Waffle House mail
I got
Some sheet metal
From the local hardware store
The other day
Because
It dawned on me
I love breakfast sandwiches and I can make them myself if I can't make
Eggs round
Right
Just get some sheet metal
I could make a round thing
That I could put in
You're making your own car
Cutouts
Can cookie cutter
Basically yeah
Sheet metal
And you can just
Byam limitations
So I spent a while cutting up some metal
Cut myself or anything so that's a plus
But yeah I got to I got through a couple trials
Sleeping out from under Rico
Cuz it's not perfectly
What can I do how can I fix this until I Googled it as like I do they cost
8 bucks for four of them
What was your thought process
I was taking a walk to get out of the house and I saw the hardware store and I like the hardware guys
And I was like oh I've been
I had that thought about it round eggs when I see if they have anything that I could
Sheet metal in there and so I did and
Well
It felt fun
Aspiration face-veil really fun like I'm being crafty I'm trying to build something
And I did six
We just wasn't that good sure I made something that works like I think Patty
Sure they just weren't great and they did leave a little bit
But they were around you win some you lose
I considered a partial victory
That I've been forfeited to buying Grey Cup
I think that you even tried to construct your own as a victory in another itself yeah I feel better I feel better for trying but
Kelso
Qualified
Yeah
I think you are so technically weekend
I have that
Yeah that's
Could you do I need a 6 to fix
Easy project
Avon
Try really hard and then I'm going to buy a chair
If my weekend I don't have any like
Tribbing to do because you would have a series of
Chainsaws that you should there be a nightmare and I'll probably not I'll probably stop just short of
I don't know if you were called you remember
A few weeks ago when I
Talk to you about the man
Yeah
And it was what I said
Do you was that it was a it was a really
Was like
Gorilla Glue everything you want
Co-op you know
And the season finale was
Such that it
It was just
I can't even without spoilers like
Can't even begin to describe it because
It was like I could
Could feel myself in the writers room they say the baby Yoda's name isn't Grogan
I thought I would figure that'll be a nice twist the person who arrived
Nana
Your baby
Giotto
Directly
It was very much like a I didn't I knew it was
But I never thought they would
Okay have you think I would
Liken it to have you ever seen a wrestling pay-per-view perhaps when you were younger
Yes you all the sudden you heard the music
Sure you were like
They didn't hear the glass break at Stone Cold Cut it up
So cold and it was him
It's like that but if your childhood came back in
Kicked you in the dick okay
Well fantastic I have no idea what you're talking about
I'm sorry I didn't make it
Technically I barely did
The episode to go over Jordan we're talking about Friday the 18th
December 2020
That's good news
This is an interesting
Thing it doesn't yes
Alright and
Interesting thing
Episode
Quarterback
Call my God
Fortnite has parted the Red Sea
And now it's time to bring back my show
Where I will talk
3 hours or not. I do.
No David
Have a request for you taking notes
Throughout this episode that will get you here in a few
Harbour forward you that looks like moments say thank you
Books of signed up and are supporting the show
So first
Steven
Text David.
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you David
Text Momo
I'm a policy wonk
Onh because my journal biology walk
Gina GM
Audrina
First Adam
Nick Morrissey thinking about you and how about
I'm a policy wonk
Igora elevated level appreciate that
Larry klayman for Supreme Court thank you so much you are now a technocrat
And me and Blackbird thank you so much you're allowed
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
Supreme Court
Mean black
Both of you
Or you could do is take a look
At your little spaceship
If you could hop in that little spaceship
Roku 10th of solving real problems
Are apart everyone in your path trying to keep you from
Expressing your generosity by going to a local bail fund
Give your generosity
To grow goo
Give your girl go to a local charity in your area
Jewelry to get just staring at him just going
Kroger
Cooking Kroger groguru
Can experience
You don't know his nephew
Yeah I don't I don't think I'll ever watch it
I'm interested in seeing the Werner Herzog was delightful
Performance six fantastic
I'm excited about some of the screenshots I've seen of
The child
Yeah I would like to but now I can't
Google
Fortunately
Group who has celebrated 50 birthdays
From what I understand
Cuz I correct yes it is
Wendy's
Birthday
Wendy's informed us that everybody like
Birthday on Monday
It's the shortest day of the year I know we had some
About day length
Happy birthday Wendy
Hellboy
So today
Like I said
We got
Nothing that could go over
And that is going to be a lot of hours
Because Alex Jones did double-duty on Friday
He hosted David Knight show and then his own Auto
Here is an out-of-context drop from Alex
Open tickets
I always got appreciate that
That was a belief scarecrows
The policy spare the Scarecrow spoil the child
Don't spoil
I don't know how to do this
So Alex
Hosted his own broadcast trademark
Copyright free anyone's music whatever
No problem
Before that
Because he would fire David Knight the day before
He needed to fill that
Time something had to go there
Enter what he decided to do
Was finally do that show that was mostly colors
Okay
So he's decided
You going to start a new show called The American Journal
Out of here at the American Journal it's a parody
I say the parody he would say it's an omage
Canton journal on C-Span
Right and it's these has that
About a hundred times that sounds right the three-hour show
Take his audience
Forget the reference
He does really hammered home
It's like God I walked
Good Journal but it's America
So here's now to contacts dropped from one of the colors
On the American journey
People that think that this Kobe shot is going to cure them or even make them into a cyborg human being
They're wrong
It is not it is going to kill them
Pulse of America
Take that would be a fairly good
Chronicle of art. All these people out there who think the shots going to turn him into a cyborg they're wrong
Idiot
Spell goddamn stupid they they're going to turn to do my God we're taking the time to here
Here these missives all of these Dan
Starting off the
The journal Journal Star
Earlier Alex's used to starting a show at 11
Starts at 8
That's in there early
You're listening to the American journal with your host
Alex Jones
Watch it live right now I banned. Video
We are live
On this
Friday transmission
Thank you so much for joining us on the
Broadcast
Seven-days-a-week I'm not even sure
What day it is anymore
Makes my head spin
It's a it's a
Yeah it doesn't that's not it
Vicious beginning he's already
Taking his time
Already stolen the American Journal
Ladies
Gentleman
We
Begin
Our
A place
Show the middle of America
We're going to take calls
I'm going to say a million times that this is
Like the Washington Journal but I'm doing it
I'm going to
Complain a whole bunch
Last half-hour cuz
I got to take a break in between this advice
Take a calls it the last half-hour is John Rappaport not take a call
He's not on his feet
Ridiculous
Alex realizes that
Now I told the guy months ago
I had an idea
I told the crew
For something like
A
Let's buy another
National
Journal program has been, washed
Doing right now
It is Friday December 18th
2020 I was looking up there on the computer board that said December
17/2020 and I said
That's not right
Friday December
18 ft horse
Play you can't
Always proud
Computers Canyon
Sometimes
Computers lie to you
We need to be aware of is the Washington Journal the one where it's
The guy who is steadfast in his not having a facial expression like somebody calls in and
How old is world news like
That was a good call the ex caller Republican and Democrat live
Alright
I will tell you right round one he is not alright
He is he is not
I just thought I mean like it would be like if the Washington Journal host
Constantly like
Forgot why he was there
That would that's kind of the way you would make it leak all right I like it
But the aspiration is there much like me trying to make these egg rolls
To take 90% calls
Here we are
Months ago
That I wanted to watch a show either in the morning
Or at night
And call it
National Journal
Kind of after the Washington Journal
Curly habituate myself remember the house would be
Avocados are rotating
To take a lot of phone calls and actually do it everyday because
The shallows base
Police 90%
On phone call
And so that is what we are
Doing
Iran this live
Friday December
18th
2020 Rock
I will give Alex some credit
And say that
More calls than you'd
Based on his history sure
It's still not 90%
Back
And some of them are talking about
Turn into a cyborg
So then some of them
As well not have
That's fair
And one of them has guy named Mountain Patriot
Okay
Was that his birthday
Yeah on his new birth certificate became a sovereign
Here's where I want to make a request of you taking notes
A large
Portion of this
Turns into Alex
Complaining about David
There is
A large part of this episode is like
Kind of too aware that people are going to tune into taking its David
Address the issue
Mount
On the 17th
Episode that we listen to on our last episode
We heard him give
Big explanation
That
It's money
Funny I got Financial
Troubles around here
Where to scale back and get leaner
The top of your nose
So where about
To find out that it's actually about
The number of
Emails David night since
Dog that doesn't come out all right we had our saw that it was maybe Steve
Genic related because the two of them got into a bit of a Beat
They got it all though also I
A little reticent
And about that or I had to been
I want you to keep track
How many different possible react I want you to listen
Carefully and see how many different stories
About why David got fired you could come up with the toilet
The first one to give you this as Ally Auto
Now a lot of your probably turning and you're saying where's David Knight
I love David Knight I really care about him as a talented smart guy
He's been with us 9 years
And I personally am exhausted too emotional everyday
And a David of course
The god quite a bit
Over a year ago with some medical issues
Came back
And I just
Made the decision
That David
Was not happy
I made the decision good for him
Still be on here
About personal decision
All kind of watching a Twist in the Wind
Very depressed where that's going on
And I grew about 95% of what they would have
At the same way.
I did not let David go because I disagree with what he was doing well because he didn't agree with me on something
I had nothing to do with
Alright
To do with the fact that David Knight was unhappy bio Alex's metric
Yes it was unhappy but he couldn't save himself
Miserable
Did it for him
They only accept that doesn't sound right but okay
Do you think you don't
I just don't think we're going to find out that this is
Does a consistent store that buy
So what other possibility for why you might have gotten the exes that Alex wanted to do this call-in show and David
Did not
I have wanted
To Launch
Again a program like
Washington Journal bonacio
Jarrell
David was not a
Instead the program like
We had
First one to have a show that he would host
What's calls
Yesterday
When are The Rush
So here we are
When I host the show or 10 and host
What other people are looking at bringing in the house
And show
Then that person won't be host
So I kind of got in a rut not the bad way but
It's a right
But I don't think
And I really in a rut that I'm playing a
But I tend to get on one story
And pontificate on it for an hour
Somewhat informative for DieHard lifters
But it's not for radio and TV station
Really
Cumbersome quick news
Get into it
Takeoff
Adequate gas
Early cycle
Through a lot of information
Enfield
Put the show is going to be
Going to meet your phone call
I agree with Alex on some level is inaccessible to people who aren't already indoctrinated
Yes the format that he has is not good
Before someone like clicking around on the radio to grab your attention with a guy yelling
But he doesn't yell all the
Yeah there's a lot of stretches of time that are completely boring
Stupid shusher
And you know if you aren't already on the team
What about that I mean there's that and also the mythology
He's just moved on so much for reality
Like you're you're coming in on like episode 40 of the 38
Season yeah you're not going to
Catch up with all the tapping
I listen to this all the time and sometimes I lose track of the Lord
It's nonsense exact
It would be something that would be
Very very difficult for you to get people in the door
The same College
The switch-up is format in order to maybe cater to an audience
Goodbye
I'm going to stick with the other what we got
Say that David is smart
For not wanting to do a call-in show
Just simply because
You've also cultivated an audience that you don't
I want to hear what they have
How to say
True it's true you would like to try and pretend like you take this all very serious
60% exposure shitzu
Something you lose credibility by
Having two humor idiot
Go to polite
To tell people to shut up
People who think they're going to be cyborgs are stupid
They're going to die
Oh alright
I am a cyborg
What
We're going to be taking a
Lot of your phone call so I'll give you the number
When we come back
And part of taking phone calls is going to be
We are going to get your call and move the next
Thank you for calling though thank you so much Alex
Oh and a minion what you have to say we're just going to
Hey
Calling in
Here's the topic
Mobile.
Another topic the next hour
And that's how this is going to be
Something other than Polly done personally
20 years
American Journal
Ryback
What's this mellow ass music this is very straight
This is real 8 in the morning that I wasn't coffee and wasn't
Netflix
I've been awake before 9 and 20 years it's the real on a lot of levels
Sitting there with the
Like a calm
Oregon
What starts off after he gets back from
Commercial with a introducing the first top
NYU wants to do this is he wants to have
Our block
I meant it so he has like
Alright we have our first topic we're taking calls on that topic next hour
I'll introduce another topic will take calls on that top picture
We got a framework I'm not sure if it works out the way you wanted to but here is the first.
And feet
Pasta salad Falls the ground and be taken out later on a stretcher
So easy just
I forgot he played a clip
From Tennessee of a nurse
Who is giving a little bit of a talk to reporters
After getting the vaccine
Coronavirus vaccine
And she faint
After
Play the audio of that but he was really bad
I've decided to start this after
The the auto is it was just
Unlistenable
And he
Talon Falls the ground had me taken out later on the stretcher
And I thought a press release
On local ABC news saying
So it's quite normal
Collapse like this
When you take any vaccine
So this video of the nurse in Tennessee was circulating on social media and man it is all of the Optics you wouldn't want
If you're trying to reassure people about the safety
Covid-19
But it's still something that's being used this honestly
Nurse Tiffany Dover was answer a question
Confirm reporters about getting the vaccine at which point she said she was feeling dizzy
And momentarily fainted
She later explained that she has a
Condition where she faints
Richie fields
And it was unlikely something
Been caused by the vaccine
How much is also just lying about the video and making up
Details about it
Most glaringly that she had to be carried out on a
Stretcher
According to the Associated Press
Quotes Dover was back on her feet shortly after passing out
As it turns out this is just a reaction that some people have to any kind of
Shot and most doctors believe it's related to pain or anxiety
You could easily see someone with a history of fainting when experiencing pain
Having that Amplified by the anxiety of being on news getting one of the first vaccines for a pandemic
It's f****** up everyone's life to about a year
I do grant that the optic
Are not what you want here at all
If you're just someone who doesn't care about
Details and go up emotional reactions
The surface-level appearances
Then this will be very powerful
In terms of painting the vaccine is dangerous
Which I guess is the first topic
But for the American Journal
Yeah I'm not going to I'm not going to say that it wouldn't be a smarter I did not to have like
Southern Belle from the 18th
70s
First
Oh my God
But I will say that when I got the hepatitis vaccine
Before I went
To South Africa is my partner
I passed out
Like I was sitting on the chair and I had to go down on the ground and lay on the floor
Cuz it was such a
Huge vaccine to
It was a yeah
I've not had that experience but I've definitely seen it
Some people like
When they give blood they can have a chance of passing out or
Or even like
See people giving blood whatever the charcot of that some some people
I get a lot of
Response
But there's more to be worried about
Out with this vaccine I guess
This is also what Alex wants to talk
You know it says on the inserts that it
This is not a normal vaccine if even worse
It's an mRNA vaccine
Programs
Every major cell group in your body
The British quote
Protein
Stop the virus
Do same proteins happen to be in the placenta
That's what also block
Having a baby in the bed
Short talk that
Children
A couple years
When you take some of the MRNA vaccine
I should have the medical reports
From Big Pharma
And the trials here in my stock today
Yes this is a conspiracy theory
This is a fact
So what else is talking about there is
Complete nonsense
He was recently yelling about to be
B6 Destiny Pfizer trials which weed
Disgusting recent episode
Forward in the group and two most likely not caused by the vaccine
That breaks down. They released which included that information is probably one of the best resources for information about the effects that but documented in
Should Alex says that he has this in his references this material
In that very document they say that
At the time of the data cut off which was November
A total of 23 participants had reported pregnancies in the safety database
Including nine participants who withdrew from the study
We do to break
There's demographic information about the 43,000 people who are enrolled in
The study and I consider trying to whittle it down to see if
23 with a notably high or low number shorter pregnancies to see in that size group but
Honestly it would have been impossible to tell from the given information
You can make some general assumptions but even if you're able to get a vague number of the population in the study were able to get pregnant in the valley
Likely age where they might
That still doesn't really help
You still have no idea how many of these people are sexually active how many were using birth
Control etcetera
Without access to any of that data it seems to me that twenty-three Breakin seizes a fairly normal number
It also contradicts
All about
Aren't you sick of all these fact-checkers in
I hate
I'm more important piece of info we can take from that fisa report is from table 23 towards the end of the report
Which details
Serious adverse event
Experience in a study
There was one spontaneous abortion
That occurred in that group of 43,000
Participants
Which was the only pregnancy or perinatal complication or condition that
Was reported
This was someone in the placebo group
So it was not caused by the vaccine
There's a viral meme that Alex
To seeing it suggests that the vaccine will cause a
Fertility but it's a lotus
The basic ideas at the spike
Protein using the vaccines the same as the protein that used by the body to create a
Placenta
So the vaccine
Body to attack the very thing you need to develop in order to become pregnant
The protein is called
Seitan
But the problem boils down to an elementary misunderstanding on the part of these viral meme
The vaccine uses a spike protein of
To which does Sherry small sequence of amino acid with
It's inciting one
Not close enough at all
Similarity
To cause the kind of reaction that Alex
To suggest
This is just flimsy memebase nonsense that I was passing off his research at means nothing
Also we have not yet to get
Any calls
Yeah it's one of those
Does he know it is
It's one of those things where it's like it
You guys can't know about science
It's for now
You're just not ready to know a little bit about science you're going to hurt yourself
A little a little bit is worse than none you guys you guys just got
Hold off on science
We'll get to you you're going to learn it someday I guess it's like Devil magic in this area
Please
He's going to open the phones next segment
But he hasn't
These are leading
Well I want to open the phone's up next Sunday
And I want to ask
All the listeners
All of the viewers at 8
Call the Radiolab
925-397-7789 Alex
I want to ask you
Are you planning to take the vaccine
If you're not what are you going to do when they try to pressure you
Or try to say it's mandatory they're doing in some foreign countries
Now pushing here
And then what do you make of the vaccine makers having liability protection
Women if they hurt you
They don't get in any
Scrabble
Like I love the idea that his first question is are you going to take the backseat obviously it from everybody
F*** no
Second question when you going to do when they force you to learn all that's
Swim around and violent fantasies totally about Justified Violence
The third Quest
None of them are equipped to have
A conversation about why companies have
Liability protection
And what it means
Like that's something that no one who's calling in to show himself is prepared to
I mean I suppose one more question what it would be like how would it feel to be immune to disease
Does that sound exciting does anybody feel excited about is that a Stanley superpower watch this
Be hurt by this disease and it's cooked
Real stuff not cuz your mind Palace or whatever it is Imagine
Alex
Does not
Go to call
Be realized
Is that like
@david nights
Run again
Today
You doing then
Running with the David Knight show is David's done a great job for nine years here
And job
David deserves a break
I really appreciate David Knight
And so I made the decision
How to go ahead
Now cancel that show he wants to do it on his own that's wonderful
Maybe someday I'll do something here which once a week or something
I just think that
It's very exhausting but I'm a mission
And it David
Does NACA
What's your favorite doesn't give a f***
Why did I think that it's a bad thing I'm leaving.
But to David
Alaska is a trooper to take care of himself
Yasso David nights not committed apparently he doesn't have a mission
Yeah like Alex on the Frontline if he's not let's leave it at that
Okay wait so now it's because he had performance-related
Will or ability
That's not just you being a nice guy he's not happy here exclamation
Alex
They might have been
Other influences
There's no controversy there's no there's no secret reason it's not
Because he was bad
Everyday
I'm very frustrated with Trump
That has nothing to do with it
Had to do what I just
Thinking about it praying about having dreams about David
Worried about him
Almost
So I just
I just thought I just said hey
That's that
So we
Frankford and he's a great guy doing great
But job
I will be right back
To get a dream
Breeze about the f*** dream about David night so he's gone
I thought the last straw was Alex learning the blacklivesmatter made 10 billion to Heller's
It's not about that
You're not committed to the cause of your fire
Section Pittsburgh what you would think based on what you say
But there's another explanation buried in there
I tried to save his life
He's going to die
I don't know
Louder.
He does his show by itself
You know you would soon
Is a decent chance
Alex has something he's got to deal with
Call Mike Pence
Got a shot
Yeah
Is he a cyborg or is he
Dead well
I mean he's an enemy according to the you know
Raira
Still still would be troubling
If my plants got the shot that Alex is saying
I'm going to kill everyone
This is
Footage of the vice president just
30 minutes ago or so
Bonaire
Taking the vaccine
I got to tell you they've caught
World leaders in Germany Japan other areas
Planning on taking a shot in the knot
Taking it
Who's going to imply that it's a fake.
I mean I honestly
I think it's reasonable to just go with they get the rich guy shot right
It's more looking for a theory you could have make anything up then why not do that more reasonable to think that
The wealthy are getting better and different care now that it is to think they are taking the same shot
I think they're taking the understand what you're coming where you're coming from
Get the medium
Alex has a tradition of talking about clean vac
Exactly why not
I don't know it he's already said that
Did the MRNA vaccine is
Better than the older type of vac
Casino
Alex's said
Although he dropped this narrative really quick when he realized he didn't know what he was talking about
He said the Trump was putting out the Pfizer vaccine
In order to
You cut Gates off at the pass
He was saying the gates wanted to do this evil one
So Trump was putting this out in order to put them in checkmate
He's just dumb
Narrative is no longer a play I'd rather Alex realized I didn't say that
It'll be smarter
So Alex finally gets
Calls it's probably about
I would say 20 minutes in
Given like a commercial breaks maybe even a little longer
Amman
Done start great
American Journal
Washington Journal
But American Journal
Logical
Lily and California are on the are on the covid
Vaccine where do you stand on this
Italy map
Mark of the beast
No way
What a shock what is shock taking America's temperature
Just just
All I all I all these calls are just going to sound like
That's it
Mulatto
There's nothing
I don't know about that there's also going to be breaking that screeching though
Plugs
Mentioned very quickly
I want
Fellow lifters to know about
Opportunity
Support the Infowars
Not only
Wood products
But that there's also
Unpack
Hard to find
You make it very hard
I do it
But like 2 weeks ago
$50
Purchase lots of your product
Water filter and end
But right now especially given everything that you're doing
I just want to put the money in your head don't know how much I would have to spend
Tickets for you to have
$50 app
I'm Blown Away the first caller
Plugging giving him money yep
Not not not screening calls of course
Jamaica
That Alex plug the people could judge
Just give you money without
He believed that all very shortly after announcing that you have to fire David B
Because of money reasons
People are calling in saying that you know
And they're definitely not planted at all
Kobe Crazy
Lily lily leaves
This is Mountain Patriot
Let's go ahead and
Talk to
Mountain Patriot
In Colorado thank you for holding
How you doing Alex
Critical time brother how are you
I love you man
Goodnight but
Totally understood we are at War
I want to make
Plug
DNA Force
What are we doing
It gets really annoying really fast possible
It almost feels like a catfish
You know it is not necessarily planted calls or I do believe that there is a possibility
Weirdest people
Hearing this happened over and over again you praying that like
Go the way of call goes with Alex's you
Plug a product
The men then you talk
Right right right
Okay
This feels a little bit like I'm sure you haven't seen it but there's a movie called Phantom thread
Starting what's-his-name who's really good at Act
I've heard the name of that movie
And spoilers
Essentially he's
He's like
Part of their sex life is she regularly
We poisoned him and
Takes care of him that's kind of a weird thing.
So he just likes getting poisoned
So I don't feel like what I'm hearing from all these people is like
I love getting poisoned by your product
That's just what I do I'll I want to send you $50
To trick myself into thinking that your pills do something for me
But because of Munchausen
I guess
I'm forcing myself to get
This conversation that we're having is actually really interesting because
It actually kind of touches on something that really
Scared me about Mountain Patriot
Want to talk about
Something called the
People expect that I haven't heard anyone mention in 9 Mile
Just all broke out
We've been inside
Medicine they have
To do a double blind
Study
That is
They have to
Do a double blind study
In order to eliminate
Respect
Which is your own natural innate ability to heal
Let's
Call Matt
Metaphor
Coleman
They want to take our power away
Don't do that
Terrifying
Placebo effect as how we're Magic
This color legitimately thinks the placebo effect is a term that used to describe your body's natural ability to heal itself
Dodgers lose double-blind studies because they have to get rid of the possibility that you're just going to psychically heal yourself
What do you think you're getting medicine
First of all the colors talking about a single blind
That's when a participant doesn't know whether they're getting a medicine or the placebo
A double-blind studies when the people administering trial also don't know which participants are getting the real thing or the placebo
This is to remove any possible bias.
I could come from the researchers expecting certain
Participants differently
Depending on which group they're in
Double-blind studies are more
Event for eliminating what's known as
Observer Bias
Both helper
Secondly the placebo effect does not describe actual healing
It's a phenomenon
In the brain
For instance if you're told that you're being given a pill to treat anxiety but
It's actually a placebo
The fact that you think
You're giving up being given
A pill that treats anxiety decreasing your anxiety
This is very interesting and complicated thing but it doesn't work like magic
If you have an infection
And you're given a placebo
It will not treat that infection now I'm pretty
Experience
Pain relief or something like that but you will still have that infection
Because the placebo is not
Treating the condition at all if you break your leg and they give you a fake
Pills
Heels legs your leg will heal naturally if you believe it
Sure
A good way to understand this difference is by looking at a 2011 study from Harvard Medical School Endicott College in the University
Steve Holt
Researchers there were looking
To better understand the Dynamics
Placebo effect and symptom relief
So they designed to study where persons with asthma were given real and Placebo inhalers
As well as notes
Treatment and also sham
The study found that patients with Placebo inhalers
Evenly fake
Specifically Shamrock your real acupuncture
Justin eliminate another
It seemed really
It is weird
But
People with the placebo inhalers and even the fake acupuncture group
Subjectively reported feeling better
And they felt like yours
Symptoms are improve
However
Both of these groups I got the
The full stream it showed no improvement
In terms of actual lung Fung
The actual asthma was not affected At All by the fake treatments but
Some of the symptoms of asthma
Could be alleviated
Sure this was not true of the group that got the medicine
In this case Albuterol
Those people
Actually did have greater lung function
A break through the experience of getting treatment people can
Experience a beneficial result
Do not be mistaken for
Actual treatment
It's the people who got fake inhalers Worthen Force
To perform a task that
Required lung exertion
They would be at a higher risk than the people who got the Albuterol
This is the placebo effect the blind studies hope to minimize so they can test the effect of an actual medication is kind of side
Could have independent developer
Persons expectation
Another kind of placebo
Which is basically Alex's busy
This is where you convince people they have a fake Alma
And you give them a placebo to cure it
His pills won't really do anything
But if he convinces you that your brain just won't work without his iodine
They do take is iodine in your brain works fine
Your tribute that to his iodine
Iodine deficiency
He's a real condition
But pretty much everyone listening to Alta show doesn't
Have it
Make you think
You might
It's a super profitable thing would you sell iodine you can manipulate that possibility
Yeah I think the only thing that we
Confirm his product
Do or at least
Points at heavily to his products owners
Is boners
And that might even be psychosomatic but every time every time somebody talks about it there's never like
I have more energy or like
I feel more assertive it's always like
My wife hates me now
You know like it's never taken that maybe you have some kind of a mental block.
Putting your ability to become aroused testosterone that you shove in your face
Possible
The fact that this color it was plugging Alex's product doesn't understand the
Placebo effect
Daddy's
Like
Art
You can't have science so you don't
You can't get over it though it's it's
It's so
Traxia
It's just a weird they're just not ready for
They're just I just like how like Galileo admittedly he was
But the people around them
Just weren't ready
Ready for science yet
And he kept trying to give it to him and then he got trapped
That was mainly cuz he was
But
It happens
Ready for science
You know what Alex's ready to do
Fortnite
Decided to do this
Yesterday
Just wants to show immediately bad idea
Really regretting that we're all stressed out
So much going on there's so much happening
Taking the day off
I would watch David Knight this is a great guy
Get ready
4 hours
In the morning before 8 a.m.
Then I would
Sometimes you get off my show
He would be either Studio research
Looking like
He wasn't living hell
Sounds like dude you got
To not work
16 hours.
Computers out
Just insane
Isn't that what you say you do
So that we said he was fired David cuz he worked too hard
Too hard
The man is too committed to the that's why I had to fire it I've never seen him in flip-flops
Stop.
So we have both
He's not committed
He doesn't care enough and that's why I can't be on the front line
And also
He works too hard and he researches all the time he's just too committed here it's 4 in the morning
He's not committed to the
He's treating this as if it's some kind of job
None of it makes sense
A little bit internally in consist
But it is fun
To just hear him like
Go all over the place whatever whatever the actual reason behind it
Because
He needs a break
Alec needs a break right
I just want to have it clean
Play Break was just
Yesterday morning
Watch them on the show and worried about it
It's also Financial issue
That much whatever this great job it is just that we don't have enough crew to run all these shows
And they're burnout
And the night over do you know a few people's wives or whatever
They had to leave and take care of them and
It is just been
NASCAR
Hasn't even had
The engine
Mallards Fire come out of the engine
Taking off all next week
I never take off a full week I always work
Where I'm at
I'm going
Literally
Hide my phone
I told my wife last night
Put your phone up
I want to spend time with the family and I'm of the disconnect
Come back five years younger
I believe he probably is going to take the week off but it's also
I mean he deserves a break so he's going to do something out of this world
And take
Wake up Christmas off
Some people would never dream of doing that
I'm going to take him to his word everybody
Believe videos actually can take a week off and we'll see if he does or not
He's talking about like what's going to happen on the shows
This morning show and Maya show
Gauntlet
Going to host the the War Room
We have a mandate
4825 everyday going to get your chops man Aisha
Night you got to get your chops going so you might as well
Absurd
Call Lynn chaudin The Sensational
A Libro down
That's not going to work another caller who has a interesting question
Everything that you said
Leaving your essential vitamins and minerals that should be enough
Nobody needs
Vaccines
On top of everything else
What's wrong with them
My daughter is
A mortician in Arizona
And
She won't listen
She used to be open-minded and I don't know how to get through to her
And I just want to know if you have any suggestions
Well I mean I'm sure you've seen the band
Videos
Changing overblown fraud and that all these cops
Scientist saying
John Hopkins report
The came out this year
And there was the time last year of other things
Show me the overall death rates not up
That means they're moving other deaths
Affluent
Pneumonia and other things into the covid
Column
Which we know they're doing
Imagine why this lady's mortician daughter is not listening to her. The virus being overblown
Daughter is working also 12-hour days and she just doesn't believe
But she looks nice she looks real sad now that's really waiting on her
Are you know Alex's narrative here's a load of s***
Here's what happened with that John top
Considering that he's talking about
On November 13th an economics lecturer Johns Hopkins used fault
Cdata to assert that there was no evidence of excess deaths in the United
States this year
The numbers in analysis this lecture were using where Elementary and didn't take him to a got a bunch of relevant
Variables
Where is Pure reviewed studies that follow are your standards and regularly shown on approximately 20% increase in mortality this year
Over long-term average
This wasn't the study or report it was a misrepresentation of data that was delivered in a lecture
This claim was then
Covered of the John's
Hopkins student newspaper the Johns Hopkins
Newsletter
Naturally as soon as people notice
Is the paper retracted
Historian issued a correction
In the meantime however the Gateway pundit and found the article and began reporting on the erroneous
Play made by the econ lecturer
The right-wing
Conspiracy narrative is at the lecture is correct in the door track
Action is a cover-up of this obviously a Curative
Information
That's a bunch of nonsense
Even the Gateway pundit sprayman of the
The story is intentionally misleading
Their headline was quote
Johns Hopkins
Can study mysteriously disappears after it revealed in
In spite of covid-19 more deaths in 2020 than in Prior years
There was no study to disappear
It was just a fabricated and sensationalized headlines
You can follow the thread from right-wing bulshit website reporting on blog posts
From another right-wing bulshit website
All the way back to the student newspaper article that has been retract
Even in that article they say that the lecturer quote
Also mentioned that more research and data are needed to truly decipher the effect of covid-19
All deaths in the United States
So basically you have an economics lecturer gave a talk where she and accurately interpreted
I'm covered by a student newspaper
Which was then inaccurately reported on by dumb right-wing blogs
Student article was retracted which the right-wing blogs been made part of the
Conspiracy horse
This is been reported on by Alex as Johns Hopkins
Proving in a study that there's no excess 2020
20-minute covid deaths are all a hoax or just other deaths shuffled over
Which is what this caller should then tell her mortician daughter
Open her mind about vaccine denialism
Hellboy American Journal
IUI
I do not want to denigrate
Student newspapers at all during the protest in Chicago student newspapers did a
A million times better job than any other local
Local media and especially better than the national media
Aspire
In Chicago at the same time
Still a student newspaper week
Can't be
The right-wing can't be like a student newspaper did something so
It's it's sort of a it's hard to
It's hard to make a like a full statement dog
Okay yeah some
Student journalist
Are amazingly capable
And can do good work
But also some mistakes that wouldn't happen
In professional newsrooms can happen it student newspapers
Because this dude knows exactly it's
The knife Cuts both ways
Pitstop totally
Another caller
Take a few calls here before nothing but
Story
Holding the longest
Would be
Dental on Kirkman Oklahoma Kirk welcome
There is nothing better
Nothing more
Comfy
I'm waking up
Daniel prayer
Anacapa wake up America Patriot blind
Calling in
The American Journal
That's right sir while we're honored to be here with Levi taking your calls what is your view on this situation with the vaccine
So it does guys plugging Alex's coffee
Yeah
It's very frustrating
Oh there's nothing more relaxing than drinking your coffee and calling into the first
Episode of your show
It said some sort of like
Among
Infowars like
DieHard listeners that's
Some sort of meme like a way they communicate with
Each other like I said okay if you plug a cannoli
We're salt we're also used to Alex plug-in like is that part of like a a medic language
It's possible and I also
Think of it a lot of times Alex's ads end up using colors in them because there was I need your help
Hoping
Commercial that Alex uses
Call and request
The song on the radio they call Daddy
DJ's I was hoping that they would record it and use it to introduce you at all sure sure sure and maybe that's the same thing
But they're adults
Yeah
They're trying to help Alex sell pills
That's a little bit less eyes at its lower on the totem pole than Rick
Yeah
Playboy that color just in case you were worried about
In case you're curious
Stop
Talking about David Knight
And I intend to house this time I didn't get other house or going to rotate through many David out of one sometime
I'ma show TV or something I was just regular
Swap last 4 years
And I just abruptly decided yesterday to
In that show shutdown I just was just my gut-level thing to do
The right thing to do
For the world because a country
He's been worn out exhausted by this just like I am
My gut
Is a pronoun for the putting out last week
All the TV stations
Around the country
Tops
Joan
Ben Warren
Starting last week
To everyone that went wrong Galaxy 16 video satellite AMC 18 radio satellite
I love Daddy better 9 years
Really smart guy
The election
You're making ham soup
Oh okay okay so now
He's pissed off not okay first
Uncomfortable about political disagreements about
But Alex
Totally cool
Also the whole thing about the promotional materials being sent out last week
It sounds like nobody picked up David Knight show so they
Canterbury that's possible but allowances trying to use that as evidence
What's that like
We've got more support behind David
Goodnight Show
Cruises
Like maybe it was a snap decision
Yeah that's all nobody puts up his show if you've been racking your brain
I'm so worried about how much work
He puts in
The fact that emotional materials that came out last week doesn't help
I mean like who everybody so
Tune to the vagaries of the
Is a TV show
Business now
That there's a part of the
Why don't you say that we didn't pick up a show again
Right like it's not hard right
So easy and everybody be like oh there was a reason but they just didn't pick up the shower
Shut up Heroes didn't get a third season and was like what yeah they didn't pick up the show
It's
Or did it get it
I know they had a comeback it was bad it's not good
Book dude
There are 100 ways you could do this
And none of it requires any of this s***
60 reasons
Some of which are I'm a hero in the others are David I disagree with many of the others are insane
But we do have one
Explanation for his termination okay we get crossed off the
Okay
One thing I definitely had nothing
To do with it does have both feet
Add during the breaker like yeah
People think you got rid of David because of
Steve pieczenik
Keep my mind those two fighting with each
It was him
Zero-zero-zero
How to do
David was very Ashton very white
Wow
And I thought about Tony diesel
At that point
And I almost did it then
I got a massive heart attack and almost died
I need to look in the same and that I'm that's it
Personal issue
I care about David
He needs a break
Oh man
It's not speak now there's nothing that makes me know it's even more than him being like
I never thought about it
0 possible
0 possibility
Me more suspicious
And this is one of those instances where it's not
Just you and I have
Saying that
It's a lot of people on Twitter have been
About how
Steve sucks
Is a little bit more of a public thing
Public duty
Just work too hard that's all it is he was Ashen
I care about David
He needs a break
4 hours before the show getting ready 3 hours of a show
Weber hours after
Studying
Looking like he's in hell
And so
Fire him
10 a.m. over there
I got to go let David go
What should I do at clean and then be done
What are you going to do
What stations pick that up
This is a real conversation
I said I know I just can't
On the evil anymore
I know how David feels
And then you feel like you're not doing enough
And then I and then your brain went on a dopamine and then I'm super
Exhausted
And I don't even have time with my
My children
I should just take off next week
But I had to make
That decision
Because I didn't make the
My gut told me to do it
The last time
He almost died
Okay
I told God this I've told you this
I'm doing my gut now
.
Cuz it's never been wrong
I've been following my whole life
And the more I saw them I got the more I never make mistakes
I'm not going to put into all the reason
Of why it happened it has zero to do with Steve pieczenik
Okay so who's Steve
Yeah they think it's
So I might involve this Twitter beef
Batman Justice playground on alright
I will I will put that down
Come on man
I'm pissed off
People.
All you have to say
Or it could just be like a person
Yeah
You know how many people have left Infowars in the past
Yahoo few of them anyone care who is gone now
I can't imagine I mean I guess there's some like Old-Timers are probably like I'm sorry where is Lee Ann McAdoo Butler
No one cares now
David and I had it exist
A creative disagreements
Since I let it go
I honestly think that the financial thing is probably your best play
Stuck to that
Yeah because that Alyssa
Support from the audience who want to see
See your thing not
Here it doesn't
Require you to get into the mud with David about how he works too hard with
Too confusing Wild
Cuz he's also not
Committed it all to the info are his workload seems to be less than you pretend you have for yourself
Sickly
Too complicated just have
But we had a really good salary right and we couldn't carry it into the next
Quarter or whatever
That would be
Adult right
But because
It is definitely personal
He just can't stick to the story is personal and so we can't stick to the
There's a mystery here and I think what I might need to
To do on Alex
Cuz week off
This could be painful as hell
I might have to go through the last shows the David Knight did and now I'm kind of a clue
I don't know maybe there will be I don't know that would be a terrible Christmas episode
I just hope
Hope that Alex
Jones fires me for the next
Think I'm about to say
I am working too hard
So Alex
It's off.
Spec for a moment
Everybody noticed my ashen-faced lately
Leaving aside Alex's
Anger
I am confusion
About what exactly
Yes or no
I told you
Broad
You think it's bold
Overthrow the government
Economist Chinese agent
And he put all his people in for the Pentagon
A key positions in sells the American people
On a limited form of Martial law the general Flynn another's
I rightfully called for when you call martial law
When there is a foreign power that is occupied
That is what the definition says
Reason for martial law
Under
U.s. military history
Wow
Sometimes us refused for interactions are
It is a Tricom takeover we are infiltrated
Joe Biden does work for China deadline say he was a president they did steal these key areas
We have all the evidence
We bear Melanie the new election
Wow
So the 64 thing or 60 something X martial law has been declared is
Alex is just repeating from an interview with Mike Floyd
How many times do you think martial law has been declared
Since WWII
999 * 19
It's okay you know what
Five of them
I found this in an article for 1989 Hindi Law & Order Journal
WWII soe five of them I would almost guarantee or during the Civil Right There
Quote in five instances it was designed
Counter resistance to Federal.
Desegregation decrees in the south
There we go half the time and kind of Martial law has been used
Desegregation is a communist plot
It's it's
It's you
You know what I was thinking this
If
Trump overthrows the government
Does he still get to key
Keep the POTUS
Twitter account
When buying becomes red
Do we got
Dodus dictatorship
Watermelon related
Kim Jong
Trump
That would be good when at conjunction
I don't know man I think that Jack would have a really tough
To make it that point whether he wants to die or
I don't know we'll see
Billionaires generally are willing to Die For a Cause
Bare minimum
New election
Right there man
Yeah
Which everybody in the United States will accept
Something that we are all like you know what we got to get to the bottom of it
Minimum new election
Drawback to culture
How to take a call from a guy named Baldy
Baldi in Florida Baldi you're down at the bottom and I miss you sorry go ahead
This is a reminder I'm the one that all through March was
Calling begging and pleading with everyone to realize
April Fool's virus
Real quick I do not remember Baldi from that Network
Before I get my ball debriefing on the pending inoculations
A regular segment
What's connection
Speakerphone
Is this better
Say it again
Oh boy
Go to a college going to happen
It doesn't happen more frequently during this episode
Are some tech issues with this is the worst
Probably
Alex
Pretty pissed
I I do not approve
If he does not have some sort of
Performative
Show
Or something
If he's just saying
This is a ball debriefing two people in my regular Lyle Lovett
Get the f***
No no I love it
Here's a ball debriefing for you goodbye sir
You can forget your turn to buy a round
So we get another caller in this was interesting
He wants
To know about Steve's
Election sting
Stop
Because
Interesting thing that's like now Alex you need to make safe
It's obviously not true
Write to you need to
Put a flag down somewhere
Is he lying to you or is he wrong
That kind of thing
And of course this we did two more shootings
Steve pieczenik
She did say
With certainty that
Sting operation with the blocking all that
None of that's been verified
I mean what's your comment on that
From everyone's point of view a kind of looks like he is
Weatherby
We're sure going to find out I mean I'm not wedded to see machete for the Gaston Michelle probably
50 60 70 * 100 *
He want to know what show at Noah that was going to happen I didn't want about some other issues
And
That's one of the things that pushed David over the edge
Unicon
You went and told you know he's at shouldn't have them on
Bouncing tell you that one
David Babylon
He shouldn't tell me who that one that had nothing
To do
With the fact that David
Was saying you wanted to quit
He was miserable
Doors open
So now apparently
David wanted out so I
About the door
David didn't want me to have Steve pieczenik on anymore which
Things to do with anything
He was going to quit
Get to walk again to walk in
Now also I am pointing out that he told me not to have Steve on my show as it is
Courtesy to a friend
Hey so we are getting closer to the relay team starts to get a little bit mad about
David Knight
Giving him editorial advice
Yeah the Steve pieczenik thing pushed you over the over the adulation told Hulk
He didn't do it
And any any settings
What years ago so
Finally said look dude you want to be here
You're free
I don't like that but I'm not going to sit there
He's not doing this he's a stand-up guy
Million dollars that guy 10 years come back and every dollar be there
Straight up
True
Good guy
So I fired engineer guys
Is it his way or the highway
So
It's never me telling David what to have on it's the other way around
Hey you shouldn't cuss on the show
You know what he's right
And we delay it out
But he's older than me
I'm the boss that make sense
Yeah David kept telling me how to do my shoes for his health
It has nothing to do with him and see if we chanted fighting even though I brought it up multiple times
It has nothing to do with him and me fighting even though I am
Clearly very angry about it. The square on my
Radio show
I told me not to swear on my radio show that I will get
Find if I swear on
Stop station
Someone someone politely offered me just a little bit of advice as a friend obviously it's
Sounds like a stand-up guy telling Alex not to have Devon
Is a
Blessing
Expect of somebody who work for me yeah
Your passions get the best of you
Is contingent on you not swearing
Just seems like a guy who's got your back
Huh man
Cowboy
Anyway it wasn't because of Steve though
You need to know that
My elders but I'm the boss
Santana last thing I want to do a touch-up on to the network
Matthew Motors to drop it
Swear to God on my children
I swear to God on my children Steve pieczenik had nothing to do with this
And David marched up and down the Halls here saying to quit
Thermite is gone because of Steve pieczenik don't bring back up
So is marching up and down the hall saying he was going to quit because
Nothing to do with it nothing to do with this
And Alex
Hello little mad people keep bringing up the real answer and it's making it hard for me to continue lying about it
But this color didn't
Say that
This colors question was
Do you have a comment
On that specific piece
The b******* that was on your show
Not just Owen show Infowars on Alex's show as well
That is that is a very fair question
For someone to ask
Hey
You put this out
It is inaccurate do you have a statement on
What you think
How would you like to clear that up instead out
Which makes you think that thinking about Steve makes him think about David makes me think that maybe
Where are my kids lives
Strangely enough
Oh my God I just heard they died after I swear it on their lives
I will I will I will eat at night
I'm a bad guy just hit me and say
Goodnight to the bad man
Alex Jones Batman
Not Howard Stern Show we have
Fighting on the show
Fighting with the crew
Call her
Adjust
Can't and
I just can't handle it
Always got to have some drama
Steve pieczenik has
Nothing to do
With my decision
David Knight saying
Everyone that would listen to
Quit is the reason
He got what he wanted
Let's go ahead and talk to Jefferson and Virginia Jefferson you're on here welcome
Wow I feel welcome
Thank you
Subway
So you're very respectful
Tribute to David nights
90% calls on this year so I would say is not accurate
I realize now that the thing that I don't want
People to ask me about
Is going to be the only thing we talked about on a call-in show I love I love the idea that is the America
Beacon Journal really getting the pulse
Of the country at the country is conflicted about why you put sucker David
Except no one appears to be except Alex
Contradictory reports about that
Call God buddy
I would totally have accepted
The number of explanations if they seem consistent
Say what ya getting overly an insanely defensive over the one that you were telling me for no reason
No reason why you're feeling in on his show here's what you could do
Z490 it had nothing to do with it he's just wasn't
I'm feeling well
I guess what Alex is also a liar
Could just say he had another heart attack
Tattoos that would be easy I didn't have a heart attack
You're a liar by train
Anyway I was interested after listening to this American Journal
Call Shore to see how Alex holds up on his own show
Jefferson
Hangs out for a little bit boring as hell
Yeah and then
Jon rappoport
Takes over for the
The the last half-hour
And Alex
Jumps in
He realizes as soon as he gets on his own show that there were some calls that he didn't take
On the America
Journal
I am so he calls them back
Producers called them back
I was
Call by listener
He was on there reminded me that there's actually a
HR 4373
Self-control. Documentation
George Soros run media matter that literally are Mercenaries
I guess you're very alive
Hoping
I'm guessing that Alex means HR 4373 from the most
Recent session of Congress
HR 4373 from the 2015 2016 session was the end drunk
Driving apps
I'm guessing that
Oh yeah that's right
He still doesn't know they start over
Every Congress
HR 4373 the most recent Congress is a bill called the engineering biology research and development Act of 20
In December of last year it passed the house and was sent to the Senate
There it was sent to the committee on Commerce science and transportation where no action has been taken on it set
It's essentially a dead bill
Even if this Bill had passed it wasn't something they would allow large-scale evil testing on people
Who's basically a declaration that more branches
To be given out to engineering biology field
School of researchers working on those topics
Sure in case you're curious though the end drunk-driving active 22
16 didn't even make it out of the house that's not surprising
That's not surprising everybody loves
The drunk driving
The immediate matters is afraid of you looking into these things and finding out these bills that are
Stalled in
Committee yeah exist
Say what I'm going to pretend
If only you
I have his heart is David 90/10 to be able to find out
Whatever
Anyway Alex Resort continuing a lot of the themes from the American Journal like the whole like your
Placenta will be attack
Text by the vaccine door
Never had it baby again when you take
Turns out billions of sterilized Millions die slowly
The cover-up and the Nazis called at the cement of blood do now be corrupting Impala any order
That sounds
Sounds scary
Can you sue for defamation
On the behalf of like
Field
But like
It could like Pfizer just be like hey
I'm going to sue you
Would like Fox News had to say all those things that they symbolize
Sidney Powell yeah yeah they had to be like I'm sorry we didn't
We lied about that
Now obviously they're going to continue lying about it but
Can you do the
To Alex I mean nobody
Hard
But I mean it's
Seems like
You can't just say
That accompanies vaccine will
Force you to never have a baby again
Yeah it's
Seems it seems like it would be
Be something that should be actionable in some way but I do I do I don't know what the mechanism for it
Obviously the vaccine itself cannot
Sue for defamation
And all the people who like really do have some standing
I don't have the time and our Publix
Figure yeah yeah so like Bill Gates would have a really tough time
Suing Alex
Even though like
I I mean
I mean could the person is actual malice Alex knows the things he saying are not true people who actually create
The vaccine
So conceivably I don't know
I Albion
I don't know no
Interested
Another call from earlier
Who's still
Waiting to talk to him
PB in Rhode Island
Peanut butter
You taking my call and
Can you do
Thank you brother
I just got a question for you
Are the Communist Chinese leaks
Around the world
It was a list of 20
United States governors
On that list
I just wanted a lot
What you think of that
And how come it has really
As much traction the media
Oh okay maybe maybe
Because it's not
That's not accurate
Maybe
To high does a power half of the governors in this country
Are Chinese secret agents
Two Governors heads
Successfully become
Secret agent
Answer whatever
That's more believable than almost half the entire country is run by Communists secret agents
Go to sit in on the American Journal
So Alex is still optimistic
This point on the 18th that Trump is
Can seize power feels accidentally that Rodger is still lying to him
I see all these arrests happening and I see them canceling
Biden's military briefings
Tells me
Rodger Stone
They told me
4 plus years ago
Trump expect
And so
The New World Order
Yeah I heard this from either Trumper I just
Great 2016
Rodger Stone told me that Trump would overthrow this democratic governments and create a dictatorship so
I'm looking forward to that I felt like that was the most cons
Institutional thing I could someone
I mean it's a David like Trump is either when he leaves office
He's either going to
To lose all of his money or he's going to wind up going
The jail
I don't see him deescalate
I mean we say that but like
Why wouldn't you just beyond
The next
Seasons mask
Singer that's like
Why why wouldn't you just reinvent himself as a pop star or something
Directly responsible for the deaths of what's going to wind up being 402 500,000 people
So I mean obviously I am on your side
Speaking from the other end
Who cares
There's a giant
Portion of the population that doesn't
Care and give him money
Astro so like
In America that means there's another chapter as long as as long as he doesn't end
Welcome to prison
Rags to riches to rags to riches or whatever the f***
It's not like he hasn't
Lost a ton of money before that's true
This point Alex is going to break
He comes back
Cuz he comes in with some rap music
And then gets really weird
Snooze the next hour because there's more coming in I want to really tell you what I think
My brain I'm still
Percolating what's happening
But
Coronavirus
That's the bottom line
I talked to really serious people a lot I'm at the synagogue
And they're all excited
And I got to make a run at
And they're getting
Facility
It really is happening
And Germany
And let's just say this country is fighting for his life right now
33 days left we should see some big action the next week
What I'm going to
We taking off
Gif
Classic Alex
Just come and get it being like I'm not going to cover this story cuz my gut doesn't
I'm going to cover it drums going to make a rat out of
How funny
Alex's just heard this pentagon
Story
What you covers a lil
Yeah those are axios
Bloomberg all of it acting and transition breathing
Is not going to concede the military
So this is kind of what tipped him over the edge
Agenda like Trump
Was going to make a run Adams wife sure it's kind of b*******
The Pentagon has said that the reason for the halt in transition activities is because many of the staff felt overwhelmed by the demands
The transition but our quote
Still committed
To a productive transition
Phantom power
You cut off
A transition I just said of power
I don't want to mislead by adding to the quote
These are the people that they decided to quote to take any until after the holidays because quote
The dod staff working the meetings were overwhelmed by the number of meetings and quote
These same
Senior leaders needed
To do their day jobs and we're being consumed by transition activity
I'm fairly cynical but the way I see this it's pretty clear the trumps entire team is full of incompetence
In the field of actually governing
It's not a surprise that the people he would choose would be the type of folk to be overwhelmed by work
This is still upsetting and horrible and everything but I'm not sure it's proof that Trump has said to use the military
Know your power
When when
Among officials that Trump has directly appointed is an option
It's almost always the right
We can't get this s*** done and there's too many meetings
Oh no
I could see that yeah I could also see it being a like
Just
Almost
Sabotage
Petulance kind of thing
But I don't know if
I think that's an indication that trumps
Can I use the military
I don't I don't
I think so but I mean
Don't make so much sense for them to for the transition team to be like
Here's the intelligence that we expect
Do you to give us
And there like we were told not to learn that kind of stuff
So we
Yeah running out the clock
To show that
We were we were drinking beer for years did nothing we were allowed to act with impunity
Yeah
Two possible explanations
Behind Alex's
Hahaha
Freaking news the entire Biden family is under house arrest
So Alex has found this new story about the Bay Spring Court
And someone
Gallon
Roberts
Yelling
About how
We can't we can't do this
We can't
Trump's cases come to court
But it looks bad waiting this long before McConnell rollover being shy, agent
The sprint.com agents
That Robert screaming and yelling saint
Trump martial law
We got
The justice
The deposed
Chief justice
We can't do this
Because if we do screaming at the other justices
DeWalt
The other eight
What's in the news now
Credible sources
Congressman sources
Chocolate Rain
He pistol-whipped
He he screamed out a ours
The Bilby Riot Philly
Blacklivesmatter
Abby S1
So this story isn't true
Alex just viral online post
About it where Patrick argued at a December 14th meeting of the Texas electors
That the Supreme Court was too cowardly to deal with the issues in front of them
He claimed to have heard a story from a
Supreme Court Stafford that Justice Roberts
Yelled at fellow judges that they needed to dismiss the Texas Attorney General's case
Care about Bush versus Gore
Because there are riots going on in there worth in 2000 Shure
This man did not hear the story
Arete it on right-wing extremist
How Turner's website
Someone wrote how Turner anonymously claiming to be Supreme Court
Stanford told this story which how reported on some
With absolutely no verification whatsoever
There's also very strong reasons just on its face
Did not believe the story
Like what was supposed
Did I put it up by Snopes
The fact that these
Supreme Court justices have not met in person for months
Because of covid-19 there is that there's not really
A closed-door meeting that this afterlife
Overheard
Yeah but you could almost
You could almost buy John Roberts just because I'm sure in
At least in some small way
He has to resign
Barrett and cabbage
Because his job used to be so much more solemn
And like respect
Affected and now with Baron Cavanaugh on there
Kind of an idiot
Yeah you know whenever you have notoriously
On there you know it's like she gives you a gravitas
Of the Supreme Court
Word of like look
This is what the Supreme Court
Can do
And it's like I don't think you're supposed to
Yeah and I can't think
Go Kavanaugh without thing
Squeeze ya ya
Yeah
Yeah for
Poor judge Roberts so sad for him
It is going down in history is a moron
It's going to be a real bummer
Speaking to people who are going to go down in history as morons and are looked at such now
David Icke
Is not on the show
However
His son is
Celtic culture and then like the filmmaker
Going to be joining us
Big breaking news
Applebee's guys talking about like a marriage
It seemed like it based on what you do what
To produce
Introducing David Icke The Sun
Wow
Now that is sad
I would not like to be David
I could suck
Used to enjoy it
So Alex has noticed
That
Stern
Has been doing
Segments where they make
Make fun of Alex
For a while
And
Lately I guess
Alex wants to talk about it I don't know
This is really a
Because they are making fun
It's it's
It's very clearly box
Alex might have a different angle.
Still has a gigantic show number one show on XM
People with a conservative with a TuneIn
Paw Patrol videos
I was aghast at the Peachtree Corners Network
Once a month for years till somebody killed
Yeah maybe you're wrong
Oh man
Stern is like suddenly trying to get Infowars messages out on his show by making fun of me and I do
Don't want to get too much attention all that too
F***
Yeah it's the character of Alex
Is largely like selling s***
I need to I'd like the way that he brings me more attention yeah
Actually affect whether or not people believe my b*******
Butts
I don't like half
Thing to say nice things
Alex
Got this idea about Justice John Roberts he's being
The coward and all this is Young Thug closed doors
I'm actually Alex knows why
Robert's getting a call from holder
FabKids
He's on a very short chain
And so he's are going we got to do this we got to do this problem
I guess there's blackmail a good thing Alex Arena reportedly there
Yeah the the Supreme Court notoriously a friend of the Obama Administration
Americold are really coming
I mean like what what why why
What are they doing
They want to get the individual
Dual mandate back
Where can I do at this guy's now that we know it
Kenworth
Stolen and that's why he's
Daughter
Holder is ready to pull the
Trigger now
Yep
Assume
That number things would have gone differently
If a Eric Holder
Had to some blackmail on
Suggest that wouldn't hold her lost he also was telling of a look
I'm planning on losing this one so make it convincing I guess
She's ridiculous
So Alex takes more calls and
The Scholar here wants a civil war
If they don't do anything about this
Civil War cuz there's no way we'll survive
It's not about us
Future Generations we need to make move now
Occupation with collaborators so this is a
Capturing America operations
His problem seems to be Samantha
Yeah it sounds like that
I do not appreciate how casual so many people are with
Bandung
Civil War about
It's pretty f***** up I think we need a civil war to talk about in the 90s
Our lives for the future, we should all just die fighting against
MedStar fellow-citizens
Look
My problem is terminology
It's not good it's not a civil war
It's a recapturing that implies that he's okay with everything but the words
Pretty much
So we get to David Icke son and we're not going to let
This interview
Cuz it's
Classical
We started out as a race
Under the sea
Basically Thomas Jefferson
Wow
I have a god
Absolutely
Yeah
Thomas Jefferson children
TJ
What my Scorpio Jordan
And this is Mike down clip
Because
It is a return to form
It is Alex talkin over you belong to
SimCity
We haven't heard a good one of those in a while and then I think it just ends perf
This is this is like a nice little ride
It's not his best rant over the song but
Dakota to the at much like the
The piano and Layla
Sure great
The song
Great Awakening
The only thing you need to know is that this enemy attack is
We
Humanity is Awakening Humanity human destiny
And as long as you don't make yourself and as long as you know how amazing you are
They created you there's nothing they can do against you
And your life is closer to death every minute every second
Until you're finally gone at the next level and there's eternity and nothing but conscious
He's about to take over here in just a minute or so
Inelastic
Hello
Hellboy
Man
Just like
Alex is like an angry Alan Walker
What's lifepics away at that by invited us Saturday
I just want now to hear Carl Sagan
Pale blue dot speech
But Over You Belong To The City. Something really great about that
Song and Alex is weird rambling Trace nuts
What day we will all Fly Away on Saturday
Weird
But there's nothing that you can do about it
It is great at that just like the reality that comes
Fishing
Crashing
The music dies and then she's like
Hello
You going to keep playing you will enter the city I wanted to talk over it
So great
Kilgrave
I would probably
The Alex talk over that song for like
An hour on the treadmill
If I k*** it would it would get me there
Totally
If he was if he was like just going to switch to just Eckhart Tolle tape you up
But only over music
Just like a Bangin soundtrack that he talk s*** down
I would listen to that you referenced our last episode the album that of Paul Stanley
Song introduction
I think it would be awesome if our to record just an hour of freeform
Improvisational 100% beaches
Over that sax scicli did it
A little
I want I want to hear Alex
Do William Shatner
Spoken word
Style album
Over You Belong To The City the entire that's the entire back
Dial man just constant
That would win back a lot of hearts and Minds
I would win a Grammy
Open mike eagle
Sloped again what AJ wants up in the top up
This is going to be his first step to eat.
He's going to get a
What it would be called
Adelaide
Oscar and star turn the Scanner Darkly
They're going to miss steak
His endgame for Avengers endgame and get a retroactive Oscar for that
And then he's going to get it
Tony
Sure his version of Hamilton
That's great I don't know so true
I'm Annie gets
Send a me
For that time he was on the
Yeah I would give
Eminem
So dis
Somebody's not going to get anywhere as far as the America
Internal
I hate to say it cuz I got really excited
Whatever like the David Knight firing happened Ozarka
Confused
And then
When I learned the next day that Alex was like
Really showing some
Go get them yeah.
Dim
Vigor
I was I was pumped because I
Like this could be really fun
And instead
You complained about David night and take boring calls like it's not a good show better show with Harrison
Cuz he's boring as hell but you could have somebody who can just be
A cardboard cutout
With the color
Right
That's what Washington
That guy has a little bit of competition I'm not saying that he's just a
Yeah he does what he does really well he's like you know the the straight man comedy T-Mobile you think they're doing nothing
Totem that nothing
Yeah
We give Lewis half an hour of this entire time was he yelling about
Licking reports about David Knight totally
Just because he's Petty
In grief
Hey what's the save face about firing the old graybeard now man
I don't know
It said that's weird I still am not convinced 100% it was Steve
But like his performance make
Makes me think it was
Yeah 50/50 now I'm a
70/30
Every time he denies it it goes up to
10%
You know
That kind of thing yeah
Can't be Financial cuz of Alex
Cuz doing this it would require the crew
Yeah that would be there for David anyway
So I guess
I mean I guess salary
If they wouldn't I was making the blood
I don't know
I don't trust I don't trust any of this s***
Corsi was whenever we found in the how much f****** money he was making
Yeah but he had juice yeah that's
Corsi was a name you had a long career there I assume
Polly got a reprinted myth
Started in 2009 at 5:15 an hour no benefits
Does the soda machine in the breakroom
Yeah I don't know I would assume
So hard to say
I always think like man that must be getting paid a lot cuz this is
Is degrading work
Totally
I think if you're in you realize you can't go anywhere else
Sure now David night cuz like we said he had a Newsmax Roan really easily
Decent contract
2010/2011 there wasn't anywhere
The David naked baby The Blaze
But that didn't exist
He was once he wants he walked in
In the door he was stuck for a while
And he's David night so he wasn't going to cause enough problems
James elsewhere
Where to
Justify a firing until
Steve pieczenik says
Another thing that was bad she can't do this
This is my final straw it kind of makes it like the last straw for him and Steve was
Was the Las Vegas shooting
After that Steve didn't
A on Alex's chauffeur
Quite a y
It makes you think that maybe Alex
Listen to him at that
Point maybe behind the scenes
David was the one who was being like look
This is really f***** up
M2
Has told him not to have certain people on in the past I know I heard Alex
Complain about that
Play
And that's why black lives matter May
Play 10.6 billion dollars
Fire David Knight
I think the story will unravel further
In the coming days
Theoretically taking a week off
That leaves us without anything
For a while so
I was thinking maybe we should do do a project Camelot on Friday maybe
We'll figure out something
I'm not going to
Do it
David Knight episode
On Christmas Eve
It's not a present
I know that not everybody celebrates all the same holidays but for those who do that would be
Present
Not not interested
But until then we were
A local charity or bail Fund in your area.
How about people
Doing God's work
Emilio Emilio on dzx
The show because of Steve pieczenik I swear I swear I'm not end of the show right now
Things to do with Steve pieczenik
Has everything to do with Jordan
Has been tired for like the last 30 minutes or so
And he wants to end the show I would like
I would like to show to keep going for another half hour look everybody needs a break
Jordan looks like he's going to have a heart attack he's Ashen
Anyway finances are tight to do another half hour
It has nothing to do with me
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color