And Jordan wedding
I have great respect for its knowledge B. I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
I need money
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Everybody
Looks around technology Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Did we are.
Quest what's up
Actually told you about already and I'd like to
To continue my celebration of this
And that is rold gold put out a flavor of pretzels
Two different
Limited-time flavors Buffalo and I dare not try
Call Yaya
Of course not but the Savory butter
I tried that
He's so good
It's okay it's
So good is it like butter
Popcorn like that feeling where you get
So much better on that okay
To get your reaction
So good
It's like real it's like a it's a harsh butter
It's a lot of butter
It is a lot of butter
It is maybe too much butter for me but it is it good
That's good I have eaten half of one and I am
Full you're very very heavy I expected it to be like a almost non-existent flavor
Little suggestion of butter or something
But now I'd say it's in your face
Yeah well done rolled gold
Know when we were talking about this I was like oh this sounds like a flavor blasted goldfish yeah
Good that is exactly what it taste like it tastes like a regular old gold
The pretzel and then they were like
What if we just
Hubbard it we just
Photos
My bright spot this Thursday is actually the original Final Fantasy
No I'm Christmas they had like a half off special so it's like five bucks
Sounds like screwing
And I started playing it again
And I am so happy
And I'm happy that I did ask
Do the Remake 2
Is because once I got out of midgar
I felt
The same way I did the first time I played it which was just
Thank Christ I'm out of that funk
Checking place yeah that's you know the feeling I guess the game
I want you to feel
I totally it the moment you leave midgar and you can
Can see the entire world in front of you and it shows you the world
Oh my God I thought it was all going to be in midgard like remake is great
It's really what it's all about
Inmate escape
It's just amazing
Really is beautiful
You make a strong case for me to give the game a shot
And I met a major
It really is just
Second grade definitely a big pretty much all of the finals
T-Series
Except for the Remake what you made me play a night
Well
I'm glad you're enjoying that
Rap-up
Figure for you
I'm going to
I hope everyone
Then I will celebrate
It's Christmas at a nice Christmas everybody celebrates other
Holidays are great holiday time or if you just
Don't celebrate
I felt it would be emotionally draining for us an episode on Friday
That was covering
What Alex
It was doing
Not taking his week off but he said he was going to text
Not having a fun time
Surprising I didn't watch
All of his firing everybody made it very hard for me to take a day off
My only friend is very
I thought they'd be a little bit of shot
Freud in it I think there would be a little bit of us wallowing around in the mud watching the guy being miserable
I mean there's some fun too that we like watching Alex be miserable no but we did that already
That's true first American Turtle episode
Felt almost repetitive and not like it was going to bring anything new to the table
Dan's I worried that once we came to Monday what would we have to cover like maybe there be a Project Camelot
What episode we could have done for Friday
But if Alex actually had taken that week off
We need that for Monday or whatever
I left me kind of an alert
Search of what to do answer again I took that break
Here we are back on Monday
Slightly different episodes we're just covering a special report that Alex put out
And it's Christmas
There's Hatchet throwing that's implied
Hatchet throwing
We're going to
To be talking on this episode about Alex's immediate
Response to the bombing in Nashville
That's going to be okay if I take a little time
Because I think
It's it's
Sam
You know it's in that vein of things that I think are really important under
Understand about alley
And as we go in
220 21
My dad is going to anyone
Intuit
The demon coming through the portal
I feel like as we get into that you're one of the things I really want to
Stress and really run redouble my efforts on is
Looking at these things that like a really
Actually important about Alex
It's always fun to make fun of him
Breaking down in the studio with guns
But those are things that are almost trivial in a certain way I think you still have a job
This is this is part of that just part of like
Looking back at that field
Thank you for the books
First Amber's Eve
I'm a policy wonk
Bryac
Things about your
I'm a policy wonk
Text Amanda M Vegas
I'm a policy wonk very much Amanda no less than ishal
Very much Lindsay Lohan Underhill mentioned other one until we prove
The star of the Herbie Fully Loaded Lindsay Lohan
If we got married
Next Eminem
Rick Astley
Nick f
Thank you so much you're not apology want
Donated on elevated appreciate that very much
So hire a thank you so much you are now a technocrat I say this with disdain you are now it's like
Heroin
Freakishly large
Thank you so much as much I say this with
Just saying
Website or what you could do if you are feeling like
Your generous spirit is a press
Massive
Global Corporation literally sucking the life
From the planet then what you should do
Is escape
From that place take your generosity to I don't know.
And then give it to a local charity or bail fund
Specifically
Sounds good
Alright then I've a special report
I did not cut anything out of the
The special report that Alex is playing except for one point where he plays the audio of the bomb going off in Nashville
He doesn't really add anything interesting to the episode
To hear an explosion and the audio makes it
Terrible is so loud
It does make me think of that Bill Cooper episode though the day after the Oklahoma City bombing
In that episode bill made a point to play the audio of the
Explosion of this kind of Echoes here
Dramatically
Built
Repeatedly
And kind of like almost like a chorus and then he would say something in the middle
Alex pictures of Colin response
Display is a it's very loud
I'm here is I've just
Cut every time it's clear that Alex is doing
Different take
Cuz you know what the audio shift slightly can tell that Alex
Just like ran out of steam in LA
Let's try example
Bit better than we've seen in the bathroom
Try another sentence out his wife is a better producer
Ben Rob do
Fishback
So here's where we start
Here's the beginning
Today in the early morning
Hours of
A large
Mom house inside an RV
Exploded
Outside the gates
Do you make munication
Warn the public to get away
Before the bomb
My broadcast
The 10 minutes
There was a bomb on board the vehicle
911 all service
Play me the gunshots
Been fired in the area
Minutes before the explosion
The FBI's not report
Confounded
You can already tell
911 cut was almost
Joseph Watson
Coming in before the breath is finished
Cut in the middle of a stream
I hate it so on Christmas day did not hear about this RV Park
Downtown Nashville
Have the time of our recording one of the working theory is that people have is it is possible that the person was targeting AT&T building
Which show was quite nearby the blast site
This as a possible motive for an actor
Domestic Terror makes
Complete set
If you were going to go through the trouble of carrying out a bombing
You'd likely want whatever damage you do to have mac
Maximum Impact
AT&T is operations in Nashville are housed at that building so the potential disruption you could cause by damaging that would be huge
Have we seen from The Fallout of the bombing itself
With some people still being without phone service today as we're recording
Pennsylvania
Tragic turn of events in my heart goes out to the people effect
Acted by this act
Civilian casualties and human remains that were found there
Literally right before we started recording
I saw it was being reported that they have match
The DNA
There's a lot of stuff that's on my own still about this event but there are definitely some Fair assumptions you can make about it
Obviously
This wasn't the next
So there wasn't intention
He was clearly meant to be aspects
Given that it was playing for
This morning
Very solemn time for many in this country
My gut tells me based on these pieces of information
That this was an ideological a
Who knows what that ideology is at this point
Right I mean it's unfortunate
That's the vibe I'm getting
From this whole thing is a Vietnamese
Vietnamese monk self emulating but because they believe
Beds
They allow oceans are going to sneak in through the Earth
Where's like
Yes
You are making a steak
The problem
This isn't it
I'm not sure I quite
Follow what you're saying she isn't going to hurt anyone
Making an assumption here
You did that but that's the general
Feeling that people are are some pee passing around waiting on that delineate here
He's the idea of like what is
Responsible speculation and what is not
Speculating that this was motivated by some sort of an ideology based on the actions
The circle
Stances
Irresponsible speculation
Claiming that you know exactly what it is
Or choosing what
You know you want the target
You think it might have been ashore then like why would they do that
That's not
Like Gray
That's not grounded
And I think that you know
It's
I I see I see that possibility like yeah sure
It could turn out more information comes out and he wants someone who's worried about 5G
Making a claim that that's what's going
By any means but
From what I understand so far
It does have that
Feeling of somebody who is
I guess sacrificing their own life for something they believe in
And chances are
Going after AT&T
Impact that a little bit more you're still making the giant something
Don't think of it
Do you know that is substantiated
Could in the future and this is the issue with the wet
Concrete you got to respect the wet concrete
Until it dries
Because otherwise
You just f*** it up
It's the point that I've made a lot in that Alex Jones knows that his business model really only works
Is powered by uncertain
The moment that the cement is wet and he can write his initials on there before it dries that is the time he knows he has to go to work
I naturally on Christmas Day when he's already failing to take this week off
You record the special report about the Nashville bombing because
Awesome possibly
Conscious level
He knows that if he waits until his show on Sunday
There's a chance that more details will be known by then it'll be too late run to
The prophet office
This tragedy
We watch this unfold in the aftermath of the Boston Marathon bombing it seems
Kind of likely this is going to be another big push for him now
A couple of things are different though
Which make the end 2020 a lot more
Complicated for someone like out
41 their tongues people running around online competing for access
To that wet cement
Alex doesn't have exclusive control over the
Paranoid
Conspiracy space anymore so there are other people who are equally able to put their imprint on stories
Before the information
Public
The other major difference is the people
What's now
In the past he was a lunatic yelling but everyone just stopped and it's best to leave him alone
He went to far
I'm finally some people stood up to his bully
That had a domino effect
Pics of people not being afraid to burden him with lawsuits when he be famous them
And that is a chilling effect on someone's ability to defame people freeway
It should yeah
There are some limitations
Do you legally can speculate about without
Alex knows that you know that this is just the reality of his life meanwhile
These other people who want to get access to that wet
Cement they're mostly Anonymous weirdos online they're operating fake name to alias
Qanon account
They don't have to worry about being sued because they're essentially internet Phantom
They are bound by the same Theory
Consequence but Alex has
So they're free to speculate and crafts
Conspiracies anyways Alex is not
Used to be
Yeah and he can't direct it
He now has two if something
Gets too popular
He has to assimilate it
Instead of being able to kind of
Push the narrative in any direction that he would
Yeah yeah he's getting
Pushed
Well I think I think even to the pastor's even more complicated and pushing simultaneously
Co-opting hot online Trends and then making them
You know Matt's the Infowars narrative
Yeah well that's the thing
He could straddle the line
Straddle the line between like the
Part of the internet that nobody goes on anymore
And then come back to the to the real world as being that kind of
Almost Bridge
Between them and now the
Crazy part is the main internet so that's all over all over the place
The reasons why I decided like if you're overdoing this episode it probably be good
You talk about Alex's media respond
Because that's
The concrete wet moment
Let's see what he can do
In this new
Infowar battlespace
From when he would be able to
Be the king of the roost
And we'll have to completely different
Alex
Motive
Carryout
Attacks
Could it be a former employee
Core engineer
Could be an organization
A sugar group
A terrorist
AT&T for there
Politics
Perhaps owning
The propaganda
Rest assured
These are the first
Questions
Asking right now
On the ground
If you notice the two possibilities that Alex provides for potential enemies with a motive seemed to imply that
He's sympathetic to the bomb
Mediately
Maybe it's someone who's everybody
But that's weird that it's really weird
See it
All the reasons I'm not saying I'm not saying goes with the same Glee
Here are the reasons that I would bother you
That's that's the feeling
Wait what
Weird
I think of the reasonable reasons to Bob AT&T off the top of my head the ones that I appreciate
Obviously
It's just strange to me that immediately as this special report open
The options
But he's presenting for why the person did what they did like her motivation or identical beliefs
String totally he's identifying with and sympathizing with
The actor in this case
I don't know maybe they specifically chose was there a note
Brian stelter looks like a pedophile cuz I feel like that my tie back to me
Come up later
Of course it does Alex
He's planted this Colonel of like AT&T own CNN
Answer that he goes from
In the summer of
Was then adopted
Every other
Cable news
Broadcast News
Organization
5 States
Donald Trump
Criticizing the Press
Tax on him
Going to trigger
Terrorist attack
On their facility
The murder of
Journalist
They hammer
Hundred
Hundred hundreds of time
With no proof
So what's going on now is it Alex is trying to
Plant the idea that CNN said trumps rhetoric would lead to a rise in attacks on journalists as your operation sure they
Christmas Day RV bomb AT&T is Nashville headquarters of AT&T owns CNN
Even though everyone knows that the CNN centers in Atlanta
This is stupid already been plenty of other examples you can
22 of their rhetoric
Increases the u.s. Press Freedom tracker
You can little service that document attracts attacks
Journalist in the United States
In 2018 there were 30
In 2019 34 little progress one last that's good and 74
Like that's a joke
Yeah some of this is civilians assaulting depressed but
Considerable chunk
Police carrying out these results
It's hard not to see this kind of ripple effect
What's rhetoric where you labels the press the enemy of the people and also Khan
Constantly talk about
Can get in trouble
If I work up I think I might go
Get the signs with the president is trying to subtly
Julie told me to hit a journalist and he'll look the other way
Midwife
Disagree Outlaw mares agree that you should hit
People that's grey
There's no need for an RV bomb at the AT&T building to pay off the fears
Horizon danger for journalists
That argument
Be easily made without air
This
Doesn't even really satisfy in terms of like
Oh so you're going back
2 years
To something that you yelled about about Sienna and being
Predictive
Elementary
Really thin you can see that there has been no right-wing violence
That thing was crazy
Thankfully I
Exposed it to everybody Alex's careful
What's make
Quick clarification
Be crystal clear
Infowars is not
CNN
They are the main mouth
Other criminal elements
Of the deep state
And Shadow government
They're battling
Controls
The United States
So the clarification is that Alex isn't saying that Sienna is behind the bombing just there a mouthpiece for the evil demon
Globalist or Tractor Salvage control the country
If you're following his point he saying
He doesn't want to sue him
His theory is that
Beetle globalist
Carried out the bombing to retain to do all of the United States was a danger
Thank you for clarifying that it was not
CNN who was behind the
Seems like they're still in on it he could probably get them but
I don't think there
Hind
Who's make clip
Received another characteristic of Alex's bulshit is the
Listen pretty much every single thing that he calls a false-flag heap
Is that why there's a chance it's real
Maybe
What do you like the reason
What is bomber may have 1%
It is entirely
Possible that a lone wolf
Small group
Querida shop
Look up the history of
Who stands to gain from
And all the media DNA programming
This thing reeks as a
The possible.
False flag
So it's a
Possible deep state flag operation at this point until 3
Leader in the Special Report
Statement
I don't know how well it carries over to stay
What's 2
Been following yeah yeah it takes you longer to get into it warm up today
It's almost like if you say it first
Then the rest of them don't count
Like I said this the first time so you know that I still mean it on the other way
This
He's really
What are the main thrust I believe of what
He saying is that two years ago CNN did all this s***
That right they are planning to do this now
Do weird
In August
October
I went to the airway
Desperately
The MSN
Clearly
Preconditioning the
Ceratac
But they said we reminisce
Kit mainstream media
That it wasn't
The fault whatever patch
Take credit for Donald
Panache Watson
Exact same rhetoric
Before
Right before
Oklahoma City
The bombings That Was Then blamed on the Patriot movement
And rustling
Right
Sowell
Had they not
Donuts
I don't think we would have blamed
Borat well there is
Matter
Kind of thinking
See the connective tissue here
Even as a conspiracy I think this is soft
Really soft
I think the softest part of it is you are telling me that CNN
Is a multibillion-dollar a year Corporation and they spent
2 years
Planning this bombing
This Bobby I feel like the hardest part
Complain about this was the AV system that shouted
There's a bomb coming
In terms of timing terms of motive
In terms of
Method
I got CNN did finally win the war on Chris
Is that what he's going for is Alex's whole thing is that like
These false flags are supposed to
Create
Shock and terror is like
Horror then like
Why would
There be a warning to get away from it
Do you know why would
The globalist want
To kill people they don't care about human life why wouldn't it doesn't make any sense
His MOS
It just
You know what it felt like listening to this
It's just trying to fit a square peg
Into around here
Just doesn't work
He's just
This is
Grimm
This one might be just too confusing
It's a make a good conspiracy theory out of confusion can be done
It can't be done can be done
It requires finesse
Requires a little bit of
Trying not ready to try anymore
Like everyone is not
Scared
Everyone is kind of scratching their head going like
Why
I think people are scared and racially
Traumatic event and I think a lot of
I think a lot of
You know I didn't cause a lot of Destruction
Certainly
You know it's not I don't think
I don't
Did it scares people in the same way some other much more casualty
But I do still think of people like see something like that in our scared I apologize for minimizing the feelings of the people
Who are directly affected by it
I meant more of the people who'll be affected by the
Conspiracy
You know obviously I'm not going to be like whatever you got blowed up
Right right this though is such a thing
All of these Q conspiracies and all this stuff kind of bees
Seem to be swirling
Together but even then
The traction is just more like
I guess we got to wait until we find out why the guy actually did it
This this one
Seems tough
I don't describe it as you like
Trying to walk a little bit fast
Peter Weber
Holding scissors just worried about slipping
It doesn't have track
Watching it doesn't
It doesn't
It doesn't know it's a weird one
Yeah really weird situation
Special Report
Just maybe like 20 seconds after he said maybe at 3
But it was the Deep state
Within days
The Supreme Court
Michigan declaring
Governor Whitmer
Was nothing more than a dick
Heather covid lockdowns where you legal
Suddenly the FBI
A carousel a militia
It came out a week later that
The terror cell was
Lead
Bye
To FBI
Informant
And the whole thing of it
Set up
That is a smaller microcosm
Deep state.
Ashley carryout
Larger terror attack
We just witnessed
Nashville Tennessee
Po-boy
To be clear out of context
At all when pretty much says it's not
Spitballing he's not asking
Can't you just literally said that the Tennessee Volunteers carried out by the Deep state
It's in the context of his meeting was rambling but it's still
The definite statement
Suggesting it's possible that the Deep state did this
He's explicitly arrived at that conclusion
And that is
Being put to the audience also
The Minnesota
Michigan Supreme Court did not declare
And that was not a fake kidnapping
No no
You're going to look me in the eye and tell me that
The devil
Said to these people
No death
Yeah yeah that's part of the devils
Turkey
Hey listen
Spider injuries only
So
You might be asking like
Wonder why
What does the globalist
Game through this what are the globalist game
This country is in a Nexus
Battle fighting
Very
Existence
Level of steak
25 days
Attempt
Installment
Coordination
Of their ages
Joe Biden
The mainstream media is on the ropes
Item
Believe them
They don't trust
The medes massive evidence
Collective Alexa
Fraud
Carry On The Deep state
And their cohorts
The system need
Something
Could turn themselves into Vic
This is designed
Silence the American
To the great reset
Huge covid-19
Permanent
This is just
See my Giselle
No no
That's the stupid isn't it strange though like how uninspiring on inspired this is just like
Really
Is to make the globalists look like
Victims what is that doesn't that doesn't fit what's going on
At all you know like if is if this was the Boston bombing then you can sell me on on
Something like that
But this is just so different
It's just so different
Can't say the same thing
What about something that
This different and what I don't understand is like
The Christmas angle isn't even in it for
There's no attack on Christmas isn't a war on Christmas
Christmas at the literal bombing on Chris
She still of the opinion that when
It comes out
The full story it's going to be somebody more on the I hate the people who have the war on Christmas side
So he probably thinks preemptively I don't know if I can pull that one off
That may be but maybe
All I know
Is that Alex
Is man with the Deep archives
India's great
Employees working for him
Pull up every time but he said
The false flags are coming
I have been on record
The times in the last
We are now
Out in the season
The false flag
We are now the season of
The establishment
The bomb themselves
Three victims and I have our archivist
Looking for it right now
But thanks to Media Matters George Soros
We have to exam
From 2 years ago
Where I warned and
Foreshadowed
We now
So it does not have these activists are working on it
Coming in on Christmas trying to find these clips
To go through to find those short
Got to figure that out
Keep track for
The clips that Alex plays from Media Matters of him
Predicting
What
We saw
He's a gentleman this is about
Taking down America and Trump and the recovery of the entire Free Press
Like night follows day
State Fair attacks
Coming
Big Tech
Government building
Mainstream media
All the stars will be gone that day all the stelter's will be gone that day
All the
Lester Holt's will be gone
And they are going to drive
Bomber something into a daycare
CNN rabc or something and
People shooting everybody you name it
Reprogramming
I hate that they're saying that it's a cover-up antifa
Rand Paul on all the calls to kidnap Baron and raping
We've got to get this out
Tropic. Let him know
He says you're big news
You're lying another races I love Mexicans whatever
Same thing with me
Stop out of context
Text to build this
I got the media they got the Democrats I got Warner reportedly running at all
Ready
Quarterback this whole
Crabbing today tomorrow
Understand
Peter only probing attack
The shut it up at a test
The public will they buy the
And Hillary
Annabelle
And Obama is
Victim
Whine and moan
Enroll
Big ass truck
Atlanta
Special meeting that day
Closest
They'll even take out a large group of their top people
MSNBC ABC
I have a couple reasons why I don't take anything that Alex blade there is sincere or a meeting for prediction of
About what actually happened
On Friday
The first is italics literally says the target would be CNN Center in Atlanta and it would happen when Brian stelter and Lester Holt
There because they would have Advance warning
Which we've seen played out
Stelter and Holt
Do not work in tennis
All right the second major reason that this Rings Hollow to me is that the specific of Alex mentioning a truck bomb and date
Care Center that's
Not meaningful in terms of a prediction
Harkening back
Oklahoma City is very specifically apart of
Right wing
Terrorist history zeitgeist
The Patriot World they've been done being torn between
Celebrating Timothy McVeigh
The third reason I take issue with this prediction
It's because these clips
We're from two and a half years ago
This article that Alex is planning a Media Matters that clip promise from August
So just stretches any kind of credulity to imagine that the globalist like broadcasting their signal
Pushing the pre-programming so hard that Alec
What's picked up on them
Then we did
28 months
And carry out a stage bombing the didn't kill anyone
The building is owned by CNN's parent company but isn't really associated
Correct this is bensu
He should be doing
I actually I think what we'll see you tomorrow or Tuesday or when he starts
Hit the ground rolling on this
This is a prick
You have to call this
The practice run
Before they act
Chili do the real
You mean like those of the bombing
Yeah
I thought you meant this video is a practice
Time to make a conspiracy out of that's in heat
You just talkin to a mirror it is all fake
That's possible but also the fourth reason I reject this b******* is because Alex
Constantly predict
False flags and bombings
And ship that never happened
If I wanted to I could put together a giant compilation of him doing just that
And it turns out
I do want
How's the weather Chicago usually I'll just say I could do it but I actually did it
Coming and calling random events
Speck All rights could have been
So much longer
And it could have been so much longer but I feel like that's already trying already on his way to
Breaking-in were following us earlier just an hour ago
How to stop market was only down 600
Today was just one
Ever
And then founded
800 points
You talk about deep State operation
Goldman Sachs JPMorgan isn't working against the president
This is the type of craziness we've been single come
Evidence is mounting that the mega fires in Australia are being orchestrated
By multinational forces to clear out she corridors for future development
Elopement
And for light rail going in that's being financed by the communist Chinese
They are intending to remove Trump one way or another
They're going to trigger a civil war
Winger's blue stuff up when Trump gets remote
Truck bomb
When they removed from
Use that for a total
The economy's going to implode
Then there's going to be homeless running around crazy everywhere
All they got to do is have the Chinese or Supply 90% of the opiates
Tacos off for about a month
And it's going to look like a zombie apocalypse
Call alisher Fairmont
False flag
False flag event
But I can tell you
Right now
Gentleman bed
Communist forces
Party funding combine
Assaults on
Stations in federal buildings tonight
All across the United States
And when the Austin Police
Photos and video of this
To the mayor's office
Seen the photos I've seen
This is happening
We knew Governor Northam was declared emergency we knew he was going to try to
Then they stage a false flag with a provocateur
An action
Jussie Smollett
Style
Steroid
And then they say look
The gun owners are the evil terrorist or the wife
Supremacist
And I run the same operation
We saw the Democrat
Controlled State Police did
A couple years ago in Charlottesville
Escalation
Is assassinating the president
Beijing Giant
Blaming it on the right-wing Patriots and they're going to do it
Call the clintons and the Obamas
What's a mental patient
Roundup on
Psychotropics in
Hotel room right now
Okay.
Everywhere ready to go
A couple buttons
There's no way to stop
Are false Flags unless
The leadership
The bobalust he's dealt with
You know what eats real folks there's nothing fake here
You think I'm so damn real I can't stand that sometimes control myself
I totally real
Why do you
People
Author they can't stand that see
They can't scare me
Probably
Broadcast I'm your calls but
I think they're getting ready to a false flag and they might kill me and I am only seven.
On my way there, you know what I mean
I think they could do a nuclear false flag dirty bomb
Or nuclear attack
Exactly
Trump
They blame it on
Patriots are they blame it on Trump
Negotiations with North Korea they could say it's North Korea
Fighting back before Iran
But they take out Trump
And they take out 200,000 Americans at the same time and then they use that
The Blacklist all conservatives all speech online and any dissenting views
This is the plan they have to silence do Alex and they have a silence me before way they wouldn't be taking the rest
To shut us down
Well before the election they're going to hit us
Biological or nuclear event
Witches
It's in the cards
Just like two people running away from
Bioweapon
You can DJ during State of the Union
Congress shouldn't be in session in the buildings
President should never be in d.c.
You're in a Total War people
Is gone from 1% to 95%
And apologize
Please eat your happy
Yeah I feel like that was a little bit long but the reason I made it that long is because I want to drive home this point
The point is made pretty sure it's driven
This is what he does
This is not a
Prediction that Alex is making
Hayden obsession
The centerpiece of his world
On some level he knows that his political alignment is just full of cause playing militia weirdos who lust after the opportunity
Violence they can justify being necessary to water the tree of Liberty or whatever
He knows that so the only real option
We can produce
You can either applaud terrorist Acts
Domestic terrorist activity
Tough or you pretend they don't exist
If you go the first option
He'll eventually you'll end up ostracizing yourself even from the pseudo acceptable world of the
The French
The second option just
Requires a mantra you drill into your audience
In this case
If there's an act of terrorism that looks like it could have been
Carried out by someone who believes
Same shift as me
It's fake until proven otherwise
The evil nebulous group I'm fighting that's
Just trying to make me look bad to ignore it
And keep pushing deeper into the fanatical world.
Except rationalizes
Inexcusable
This kind of activity
And that has nothing to do with what the actual
Like a result of what
The event was
Doesn't matter
That was his response is going to be to call it fake
That itself
Could implicate his beliefs
That's just
It's very
Boring
It is boring
And it's it's just hard
It's really disheartening that it and it is unfair
You can set your watch by right-wing terrorism and so he gets to run interference whenever he wants because it's
Going to happen
You know
It's so f****** annoying
Core The Narrative here this false flag narrative the way that Alex uses it
Is just a way of weaponizing and making money off denial
That's just what you're doing
And it's
Like I said when I say it's a boring
I mean it's really boring when you look at it in the Longview when you look at his career and recognize like
All of this
Dumb s***
You keep saying is like research
Yeah I study the globalist I know there
Patterns of an every f****** pattern is wrong
Nothing ends up happening that he says is going to happen
And then
It's not boring
The trick itself is not boring trick itself
Is
Possibly very dangerous
Yeah because the first time you're exposed to the idea of a false flag
And it's not just something that only exist in fiction shirt
Cheetos make you think like oh my God everything yeah and that's the danger of that that that
Tripwire Alex
Can set out in front of you
The same thing happened to Rogan
When Rogan talks to Alex about the only things that he thinks Alex has been right about
Told me that agent provocateurs exist
Okay great your mind was blown by that
But that mind-blowing event was used for malicious
Purposes
And I think
Alex knows
On some level
No matter how stupid
This conspiracy is
About this bomb
No matter how
Lacking
In connective tissue it is no matter how
Sad it looks
Still look at
It might blow someone's mind
Yeah there might be someone that's all they need to hear is a denial
Of some reality that's in their face
So infuriating
Mimikyu box office at
Like the thing that weirds me out it's so much less believable
Because every
Right-wing attack terror attack is a false
You know
Look
I get it
Putin one 97% of the
Alright 99% of all of these right-wing Terror attacks
That are
People doing the things
You say they should do
Political politically
99% of them are all false Flags
Come on man City Bombing with him well and ninety-nine percent of things that you
You make up that don't happen
Come on man
It's
But he can't muddy the waters because then you're not sure that they're all false right you're not sure
The idea of
Real critical thinking
That you engage in
You are with the audience and event allows the audience to engage in
Maybe this is a false flag
I don't know let's see
Yeah you can
Accidentally encourage your audience
To start questioning you don't want them to do that
Did any doubt will
F*** you up
Yeah and that's why I looks like there's a real 20 seconds later be like
The appearance of questioning and the appearance of critical thinking while at the same time driving home your predetermined
Conclusion
Yep at
Just
Unfounded
So good as all the signatures man it is all the signatures of the false
There's a pattern
Call swag
Luminary stages
This fits
Completes in
To that historical.
But regard
Authoritarian
Will try to use the
This event
More ameerah
Celebrities
The Democratic Party
Deep State Controllers
I've given up
Years
Alluding at
Destruction
As a message
Change to the cords
And the system
If you don't give us what we wanted
You don't let us
Steal the election
Install
Joe Biden
Electronica playlist takeover
We will burn
City
Avoid using the word regardless because he's
But regardless
Jodi Arias
Thoughts
Which
Is his refrain
But he says on pretty much every
Time you want
Wants to say something stupid about a world event the people are
Emotionally effect
I got the right to question
Some things Americans can question thing sure
Integrate this is not questioning
Button clothes
Never forget
The long
History of government
Another organization
Staging false-flag terratech
The Blinder political app
And remember
The American Birthright
Research
And question any public event
I mean yeah research and question whatever you want this is what that
Yeah this is
Is b******* is a little bit different
It is it is your birthday to research and question things but it is not your Birthright to go on the radio and tell
People that are supposed
Right I feel like that's not right
I don't know if George Washington was it hanging out being like way way way way way
Eventually working invent the radio
I have a laissez-faire I have a difficult time thinking that
I mean first of all I don't know I do want to get into a First Amendment
Debate but I don't think it's responsible and questioning Behavior
Or
You know like something that has a lot of value in
Society just get on the radio
And with no evidence be like
The Deep state
That's stupid
That can only lead to negative outcomes I mean
Regardless of what he's saying
Regardless of any of that
When you say I'm only researching and questioning that is a bad
Faithlife
So I don't give a s*** about what you're talkin about deflection I don't know this isn't even a First Amendment conversate
This is a I can
Pasaway your b*******
Because you are already lying to
The fuk you it's
It's basically his in closing statement is
Things have happened before and I can get away with this so
Clearly
Give some credence
To what I'm saying
Mild like it's
Just just
Justice
I can't even
Words other than weak
Nothing
Yeah it's so disappointing
One last clip here at Alex closes at the report
He wants to make you afraid of Eric Holder
Oh damn right
Never forget that Joe Biden
And it would be incoming
Are part of the Obama
Crime Oregon
Annotation
Never forget it was death
General Eric Holder
Who helped cover up
The same holder carried out the Giants
Confirm
Black operation
Fast & Fury
Alex not so self-satisfied
Is Fast & Furious at me
I'm going to put that one in the win column guys
Eric Holder even need
Talks to be in vitamins
Administration
His name come up
Rahm Emanuel name is come up more than Eric Holder and he should be tossed into a Galaxy
Just doesn't have any specifics left me like how fun it was to make people scared of her folder get back on that
So I was really struck by how weak and desperate that special report that Alex
Put out in it's absolutely meaningless there's no
Teeth behind it at all
I almost
Kind of felt when I was listening to it that he didn't have a theory but he wanted to yell into the void to remind people that he's weird
Willing to call everything fake with or without reason and he's ready to do it immediately out a beacon like a lighthouse
Haha
There's no fury here there's nothing except knee-jerk denialism which Alex
Attempts to justify by pointing to unrelated years ago
But how the meeting was going to false-flag themselves
Some of it barely even make sense with the details of the bombing
It's unconvincing it
B flat
It's also couch
I'm so much I'm not saying I'm just saying kind of language that it's hard to even imagine him
Learn about this
Reckless abandon is easy to mistake for passion
Tyrone asprea
Just feel hollow
I was curious about qanon was doing with this bombing so I reached out to Travis over at Tycoon on Anonymous and he directed me
Some of the theories
Better popped up and gain Traction in that world
They're all nuts
But they're better than Alex
They seem to have theories that surround the idea that there was like a secret NSA server at the AT&T building they would somehow prove that the
Georgia
Comprar conspiracies were true
So the bombing was actually the good guy setting off at
Controlled detonation
To recover the evidence
Stop biting from getting into office
Or possibly prevent the bad guys from being able to steal the upcoming
Rica run runoff election in Georgia next one
Helping it makes sense with the larger conspiracy that are actually being engaged in the qanon world that's fair
The audience
McEwen on his capture where is Alex's narrative is just dull and uninspired
It was almost entirely disconnect
Anything else
He's been yelling about except for the fact
False Flags
The comment which I stressed
He does all the
The time 25.6 minutes
Iowa
Ipw feeling do it
No he's not selling it
You got it look if you got week material you got to
Sell it you know that's the one thing that I've learned from stand-up
So long if you got weak material you perform the s*** out of that material
And maybe you'll state by and help you push up the the next level and this
You got it
Yeah it's
It's it's almost like
Kind of
It has the feeling of a guy in like a like a
Recliner
Do you like it I told you so
But there's nothing there being told
Because that is kind of the idea the I Told You So is him playing the eclipse
From 2018 very said that's his name is going to be
It almost feels like a
Victory lap
But there was no rain
Yeah he should be petting a cat on his lap just like
I told all of you
You what would happens almost
Confuse
It's almost disorienting now disconnected it is from anything that feels real
Or anything that even make
Makes sense as like
Conspiracy
Water
But that's that's the thing that like when I was looking at these these qanon things
Is the Travis
Pointed me towards Lake
I was looking at those like I get it
I get where this is going sure
Media wants to make themselves look like the victims
Yeah
It's not extinct
I think on this one the cement is too wet
Descendants
This man is too wet right now
I think this is going to be the first one where it's like
2 days everyone will have a much better conspiracy there they had more time to Workshop it they got more details to
To play with
There just aren't enough you know like
That's it
Thank you ate with immediately
Suspect
There's so many different people you could
Investigating go down and on this one it's like
I don't even know where to start
That kind of thing and so all these people are just coming up with
Nonsense
Yeah
It's a it's a
Same like in between. Of an election and inauguration and the recount
Runoff election is it worth it going
Anan
Yeah so much other s*** to deal with
So I'm interested to see where Alex goes with it's cuz I think I mean
It seems like this is something that's going to
Yeah has to be something
He keeps going
And I'm interested to see what the narrative flushes out to be whether he gets in line with
Qanon theories that are
Already
Much Fuller than his
Becomes
I don't know.
Will become
I don't know I just think that there is some value in
Taking a look
At
The immediate reaction
I agree because this is
He knew he had to do some
What he said before he
He's going to say something to
You know like
We have to at least admit this is uninspired
But this is without question
Questionnaire
Easy receipt against
Tomorrow's ball
Maybe even today
Kind of level
Yeah
Yeah we'll see
Oh we will
Please my apologies if anybody felt
Anything that we discussed or any of our town was flippant about the bombing
My heart goes out to everybody
Affected
I don't
I don't want you to think that you know
My mocking Alex's bees
People are having it's not brutal
Life Is Life
Does not
That brutal cell
It is it is just
But until then we website
We're also on Twitter
If you could please find a local charity or Bellefonte in your area to help out
People doing God's work
But until then I'm DIY I'm blue I'm busy X Clark I'm Daryl run
I am
Insisting that Alex eat that hat
You promise to eat the Hat
E2 hideout
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color