I have great respect for its knowledge B
Knowledge fight
Nick.com
I'm Jordan This is not
2020 know it is not happy New Year
Brand new year
It's brand new year
Distilled rubbish
Yeah hey do the podcast where we like to sit around
Novelty beverages
Indeed we do I'm Jordan every step I don't know I really
Cut
Jordan
Quickly
What the right spot but my bright spot is actually going to have to wait
Until the end of the podcast
But for now I shall
Turn the question around on you what is yours
Spot is lovely.
Very very cute
Grudgingly say favorite pastime
Catching them in some sort of pose
Taking a picture and then marking it up on my phone
And just drawing a fanciful little
Picture around it sure it is my favorite thing to do
I don't know either man werewolf
It's not for its where we would just ruin it if we were there
I've no idea
That's where I'm going to go
Is creepy still available
See what they have
How to say I think
I think you run into ethical issues there
I don't think that it's at the coal there labor laws for my dogs and I do think that
And based on your politics you should not exploit the labor of those Doug
That's fair that's fair
So they only have to work 4 hours at a time
If you redirected the money from the cameos towards all like dog related
Oh that's early
Brother to the Embrace. Jordan
Glad you're having fun with those dog
Delightful
So today we have in front of us is the first episode
Yay
Where is still in 2020 for this episode
December 28th and 29th
That's Monday and Tuesday of last week or
This week
The end of the year
Rapper Monday
And then also
It'll be in the lead-up to Alex's going to Washington d.c.
On the 6th
That's right there still do next week
The plan to go to DC for all that
So I figure we can third time's a charm against
Can close up 2020 see how Alex end-of-the-year on Monday
And then check in on the aftermath of that rally
On now on Friday
Great and have a
It'll be a real bummer if they win
Rally for us
Everybody running no matter what
So Jordan
Before we get into this episode
Extended the number of shoutouts
Exciting
Some of this is for folks who signed up and Reporting the show
Very much appreciate
Oops
Okay
So first
This is not a bright spot
I am saying this
With a gun to my head metaphorically this is a dark spot
Alex Jones's
Moist penis thank you so much you're now policy walk
I didn't want to say that
We do have weed
There are some flaws in our there are some flaws that can be exploited
Or just
Thank you so much you are now policy walk
Are you very much fresh
It's about you and I'll probably walk
Thank you very much Frankie
Fresh Choice
Hey hey hey hey
Next
Sammy Sammie s about you and I'll probably walk
Thank you very much good advice for all
About Europe
Next Nomad Adam
Thank you so much right now if I was wrong
No madame
Money off that heroin
Thank you so much Cisco is reverse-flash
A couple of
Special thing
First I got to say very special birthday shout out to
Okay thank you happy birthday
Shooting as a message
Also
Happy anniversary
We're getting married on the 1st
Turn on the first race
Oh that's out of
Control will never forget your anniversary if it's on the 1st holiday
Come on man
Easy to remember
It's not as hard as like sitcoms make it a your anniversary it's not that bad
That happened in every show
Still never going to beat out there going on two dates in the same restaurant
Sure that's the best one there's a good gag
Every show 420
Happy anniversary to
BMW
Anniversary to you both
Yes indeed
It'll be weird to only which one
Get out of that relationship
Oh okay I'm sorry
Here's my bright spot
This is something that is going to blow Minds
From here to Scandinavia
Scandinavian Minds
So I got
Two messages okay
In the past
Little bit
From people
Who are trying to set up shout out
For their significant other but unbeknownst
Do either of them they have
Both message to me Henry someone we did not oh Henry
How dare you oh Henry
Are you missing a coordinated attack
Elizabeth from Sweden axles me a message
Give you a shout-out to say
They are policy walk
People from Sweden Elizabeth sent me a message asking to give you a shout out
And that you would go crazy and you both
You must both
Shave your heads now
Cruel
Let's go all the way in I just found that the
Delightful things that I can take
Yeah and I hope both your minds are blown out for me too.
I just want to think about this for the rest of my life to start the year
Yeah
Super Bowls
I hope it's a nice surprise for them cuties
Multiwall
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you both
Brightening my weekend
It was great I can't imagine really deep in it if you live
Listen to that part of our show and we're like
You no fun
No I don't like it I don't know my heart is a warm by that
I'm better as s*** and I I'm going to cry I think some people just hit the 15 seconds ahead
Bulshit
Yeah it's our version of ads
Like I said December 28th
Yesterday
Here we go her jumping in on Monday
And that this is this where Alex is starting off
Monday December 28th
That are going to be coming up today
Exactly where we are on planet Earth in the fight against the globalist
Austin
The first president
Powerful video
Old man in America
Weather
Here is that report
So this report Alex's citing the Trump
Tweeted out is not what you would call her
Port
Real loosely
In reality it's a video about how the election was stolen created by a guy named Seth whole house
Who runs a website
Called Man in the Mirror
I wanted to learn a little bit more about the
This guy's website
The few things that I thought were interesting
Two big thing popped up about his URL which is
Is Mia. News
The first is an MIA stands for missing in action
So that gives exact opposite to put out there
It's time for all good Patriots to show up so please remember you can find me at a my day
I might have chosen a different name
Different acronym
Like for instance I might have gone with American with standing outside Legion
No problem with that one that one's good alright
The other thing that popped up was this guy today. News URL and pretty much the only people I've ever seen getting. News page
Bizarre Infowars associate
I'm sure some other people are doing it
Me too but it's
Become something I associate so much with Alex and his crew
Did I instinct
Truly suspect something is not right address
It might have been slightly on a
Expect at this video went viral as it did after Trump tweeted it out because
According to an article by will summer in The Daily Beast
Some interesting things started
Did the happen reason
In particular it appears that references online to whole house being a member of the
The falun gong movement
Began to be a race
Including the mention of his appearance at a 2007 Minnesota Conference
On the website clear Harmony
And all mentions of him on
Minghui.org
Why would they want that scrub
He also apparently this is not necessarily been scrubbed from the internet
Employed by the epoch times
A right-wing media Outlet associated with Island
Between 2008 and twenty
But he's barely also freelance as a photographer for them as recently as July of this year
Great good stuff
Everybody's got to work
Freelancers
Yeah this is not an individual who made a news report that super powerful it's the
The product of a longtime employee of a deeply right-wing propaganda
Media outlet that
Essentially deify
Trump
The removal of whole houses name
From those websites
This kind of talent
The most likely explanation for why it happened is because the propaganda video featured him as the narrator
Doesn't work nearly as well as you know that he's a member of a spiritual movement that reportedly views Trump as a Critic
Highlights
Becoming judge
They were Communists to be sent to Hell there is that
According to former
Talk times employee
Speaking to the BBC News
Bear is bad
That does kind of mess with your credibility
Hey are you like the presentation of the man in America
American flag
Media report in Mora book report on Behold a Pale Horse
This charade works better when you just believe that
The whole houses
What percent of self to be
From his website
To his bio
Born and raised in the countryside of Ohio I never thought I would see a time with our freedoms are under attack like they are today
I spent the last 15 years fighting against the tyranny of Communism in China
But never did I imagine that that fight would come to American soil
My heart beats with the blood of patriots fighting the needle down in shame
I created man in America.
To speak to my fellow Patriots and help
Educate inspire
And unite us
All right all I just heard was a lot of
Ravens like screeching in my ears
It's sort of an angry mix between
Hacksaw Jim Duggan Charlie Brown's teacher
A good bio for myself but I've always straight about as far away from self mythologize
I think it's her possibly
It is kind of reminds me of that advertising dude who created the Frank Bates
It's Persona to sell survival food in prepper supplies to conservative
The Patriots out more
You coming from a normal
Read a kind of fella like
Frank coonelly didn't
Exist
Compared to the reality of it being gay
Bulshit being resold them by an affiliate marketing billionaire lives like a New York
It does not
It's a it's a it's a
Puppet game
Yeah it's it's
Tricking flyover state
Anyway I bring this up to remind everyone that Alex Jones
Considers this a
A news report
What he's doing is just desperately chasing the actual new alternative
Propaganda
Poked with associations with vodka epochtimes and Newsmax
2 a gallon they admitted to Biden won the
Also
It appears that Alex really didn't want to work
On this episode
Because other than introduced
He doesn't get back into the studio until
20 minutes into the episode
He displays Stone
Happy Wheels definitively proven the following Kong is wrong
Are they still is it are they still in the running for the end of days when I don't know nearly enough about
That as a group I speak with any kind of
Authority or credibility
I can't say
You know what
If if
Their point is solely that China is
Repressive
Of groups
I don't disagree with that point
But
I don't
Think that groups like The
Epoch times
Are on the up-and-up
Go to hell
I don't think eight even if it does
I don't think Trump is your ally
Probably not
Very shortly become a less effective
We can only hope
So Alex
Quite a ways into the episode before he really says anything substantial
Let me get the number out
Respond
Trump signing
Declaration of
Cooperation
Or the pardons or
Any of that you're welcome to call and we can all get our brownie points
Which one
Criticizing
World Government Bill Gates the UN the forced inoculations the covid 6
Joe Biden
I honestly can't tell if Alex is mad at Trump about the relief bill or not
Doesn't seem like
I can tell that he's going to be mad at callers if they're mad at Trump about it though I thought that for sure
Another thing that I was drunk by listening to this is like we're almost 30 minutes into the show and
But one of the lead stories isn't
Be Christmas morning bombing in Nashville that he interrupted
It is holiday
To declare an almost-certain false flag
Be a follow-up on that bike Owen hosted the show on Sunday so Alex didn't cover it then so it seems like now be good time
Do this a little bit more responsibly
Oh no
Couple of days ago you don't need to worry about it
So are you doesn't get to this immediately that's not the lead story believe story
Appears to be Trump
Should not
Not leave office
I don't like that
Alteration
Is in 23 days
The coronation
Virtual
Alright
And refuse to go
He folded Azar buddy don't start back into the furniture
The clothing or stuff
We're not
Leaving
Well what do you expect
President
Trump
President-trump
Shouldn't leave
If it's fraud
T-shirts
This is kind of sad
Bush is Alex pretend
When's to be arguing in support of algor squatting in the white house because the 2000 election was still
Yeah earlier this episode Alex said that
Even if Trump was a horrible bad guy the elect
Can we still stolen from Twitter response
Possibility to fight over turn it
I know that he said that the 2000 election was fraudulent but somehow I just
Can imagine him
Working up
Does passion to support Bill Clinton's vice president getting into office
Yeah he couldn't get out
So I'm fine if Trump doesn't want to leave we just boarded up the White House
Build a nice little pyramid around it and then
You know he lives
Comfort
I say we drop snakes in every now and again just keep things exciting you know for the few weeks they have with airless
Yeah absolutely Runaway
Sport of it
Does the Trump family running around the White House
Stabbing spider
Looks about like
No I went to this rally this Jericho March
While backpacking
ABC chart
And I will not be present
One way or another lot of people thought
Maybe Riley that died ice
Figured got a violin
I was not
And in fact
I'm a snitch
Alright so me on this one out to self as a snitch
We elected President Trump one way or another
It'll by overturning the election and it's showing it's a fraud and nnnn getting Congress to act on
January 6th to not certified for Biden
Impeaching Joe Biden are getting arrested
One way or another he will be removed
And that's what I said in my
Beach
Kill Joe Biden
What I said
Secret Service hasn't called me
The last thing I want is for Joe Biden
Turn lemons into lemonade
Kamala Harris
Secret Service knows I'm on record
Not once not twice but three times
Crazy people arrested
Weapon
I'm planning to kill President
These crazies of Santa's letters and called us before
I'm going to kill George W bush
Mama
Secret Service
I don't believe Alex really but if he did if he
If that's true good match tell your audio
Your audience that
If we said hey
Some people said that we're going to kill the president we called the FBI and they got taken care of
Free things to do
It's no problem that's a problem for people who are interested
Freely I will send it
I am a turncoat
I love
Dicks
Stuff
I love dancing political
Now
I will call Janet Reno
This glass eye is
Have you heard that you get stitches
Alright let's let's
To keep that straight
Real real full on Alex
This is part
Listen
All of you
I will turn you in
Alright good work
So disinterested
The Nashville
Situation
Kind of surprising
Cuz
Like I said you put out a video about it
Christmas witch
Seems really maybe this is
Maybe he did smell something really important
In there are maybe yeah
Maybe you did pick up on some
Pattern that he wanted the flash out
Don't really care
Still probably
Wearing phase of fall
All Flags
A lot of questions about what really happened at the bombing
Nashville
1 oz
Nothing
Skousen know about
And I do a little
I would say he's going to say it's a false flag
For sure because he doesn't talk about it when he's on the show
He has bigger things to talk about
Joel skousen covered in South Jordan
You know I'm sure Joel would have made time to talk about
This possibly being false flag but he had
Sure
To do like
Tell you
You've got to live
An hour outside of town if you want to survive
Absolutely
Far because then it becomes
It's like almost to be hard to go get supplies
How to get far away enough from
Places where there's a large populations of people can't walk to
He doesn't go awhile down that road
That sounds like when I was like 6 in my friends and I work building a snow fort
Drew
There's going to be parapets here news
We're going to make sure that you can
Capri Boucher out of ice
Call Mariana
Also I know exactly where to find Joel skousen now about an hour outside
Setup a radius
Are you ready we got scales at Perimeter
Stop mileage
It's about an hour
If you're driving or walking
Or wherever it is
It's just got to be about an
I think I think it's by truck
My truck
That's the sense I got not as the crow flies no no crows can't get Lumber
Bierhaus
Nashville
Conspiracies appear to have deflated
But
There's an escalation going on surrounding covid-19
Related stuff
Getting to the point where I'm getting the sense that Alex
This is just saying it's not even real like you dancing dangerously close
David Icke territory
Open for business
Will never be opened that
Randall K right
Totally hype
PCR test
So
He seems to be implying that the tests themselves are all fake
Amplifying and misleading people or what
Clear he's so unclear and he'll say like
I'm not saying the virus is fake
All of the dude ways he's describing the circle
Stances would lead you to that can
Conclusion
I would I would just
I'm like my guess is he's just reactionary
Contrarian for the sake of it
If you say any that you like
Oh it's it's 100% really be like know it's fake
I mean the virus doesn't cause a test right now is
I mean the virus is real but they're test
They're fake like there's no matter what
Something is fake enough for him
The entirety of the
I think there's also a feeling of like he's just desperate to be interesting
And so like if you come in with a piece of information
He'll blow your mind
With
The contradictory
Yeah that's fair
So one thing also that is contrary to
Is Trump
Sure
Kidding
He's not very happy about those pardons
Show the ones where he pardoned war criminals and murderers and white supremacist then
Hard to say what Alex doesn't
And approve okay
The number one issue
Is not true
Trump stupid
The number one issues World Government New World Order technocracy travel
Leave your house
Digital ID total control it's not coming it's here
What you think
What we should do about it
So Alex has plenty of time to cover this story with
Responsibilities like why
Don't you agree with those pardons
Which one
Yeah what
What's your problem
Right
Why do you think Trump pardon those people anyway
The pardon list
From the 22nd.
The 23rd
Just trying to figure out like
You know what's the issue
To hear
Like Rodger Stone and Paul manafort will probably like the headliners
So those shows
Alex can't be mad about that
Keys for that
Charles Kushner
Jared kushner's dad
Maybe
Alex is kind of wishy-washy
Globalist
But I've also heard Alex
Charles Kushner was set up
You know you was just trying to prove that the person was cheating or whatever
Bento go go both ways with that
Superman
Of course what you were referring to is
The the four Dudes
Who were Blackwater Mercenaries
Sewer Square massacre
Which is really f***** up
Considering that last year
Trump pardoned
How was that guy Eddie Gallagher the dude who killed civilians
Yep it's about Isabel pattern
I think I got a feeling that that's what I was talking about
So much of his career in any kind of
You know like well you got to give it to Alex
Is built on his opposition to the Iraq War
So much of it is based on like I am not a war hawk
I am I have principles I'm not going to just go along with George W bush
In this war that built on a lie you know that kind of stuff
Is the only reason that his career had any legs
To begin with
Yeah otherwise he would just be
I don't know
A hyper talented anti-communist weirdo no one's heard of ya
That's what prompted
People of other political alignment
Considerate
Yeah like as being like a disguise on to something
If you go hard enough on everybody's enemy
Some people will
Even from the opposite
Friends in college who almost got sucked into larouche
Could you guys all suck so bad
So I kind of thought about that is like what they'll be such an invalidation of like really
Core piece
Ace of Alex's
Like premise yeah
What is martial law
Putting the Socialist
Antifa
Camps and stuff that
That's that's invalidation
You can do that if you wanted to
So here's my theory what's your theory
I don't think it's actually
Without those Park okay
I was looking
Through the list
Departments
And I found it
To pardon
Went to John Tate
And Jessie Benton
Campaign members who tried to bribe an Iowa State Rep
The switches endorsement from Bachman
Tyrone Paul back
In 2012
Yeah you might
I think that Alex would say
Support both of those parts
Because he's excused in the crimes of
People were on the same side is Alex
But you'd be wrong
Alex hates Jesse Benton
He's indicated in the past that he feels like Benton has worked
Keep him on the out
Side of things
Benton weaseled his way into the Patriot Movement by Mary and Ron Paul's granddaughter
I do remember
He went on about that.
That guy he is a Scourge on the Paul family
Hilarious
Yeah you got to go with the psychology the individual and there is nothing that motivates Alex more than paid
Buddyfight number one
Well you could have murdered his family but if stelter walks by it
It's stelter who's going to get the hate
Philosophical
Consistency is what you would hope for
So you would hope it would be something like
You know these people are out networker
Criminal
Anime
In fact actually be a violation of the Geneva Convention do I believe it is
Experts in the field have indicated that it
No I mean
It is it is f***** up because
More I think than any other decision that a present
Can make
Pardons are intimate
You know what I mean like
That you pardon somebody knowing full well that they work
Convicted of there
And chances are
Did that
Hardening those guys is very much like
Brown people are not people
That's what that says
Or a warning those people most
Did the most generous interpretation
Is
Civilians in other countries are at the mercy of our military
You know like most
Points more towards I'm fine with genocide but yeah
I mean that's your that's the reality of it so
You if you see
Trump pardon those guys
And you're fine with that
You're fine with every
Did I go today
The message of it is
Is heroin
I mean there's a lot of the suit
Asians are made by elected officials
Send
Less-than-ideal message
Play true
But something like that
Does give
A real middle finger to
The idea that anyone in the rest
The world would treat us
Like
We are operating
Any kind of place of good
Yeah
Just any any movie where they're like
Oh okay
We're going to go in there's we got this super murderer
In the darkest dungeon
And we're going to use him now it like
No those are the bag
Yeah let's set the dog loose
That's what this pardon is
Please let set the dogs loose on on our end
Accepting that one season of Heroes
We're at the guys on level 5
Couple of them were actually got there just down there cuz the powers work
Too strong I don't remember exactly
Weapons
Damascus
I've kind of
Lost it hurts
Knowing no one's hurting you
Heroes is actually working science fix
You might be surprised to learn
Alex took in a little p
Pizza science fiction over the weekend
When the others
Itsfunneh Skyblock out of him calling you I don't like
Agreed
Arrested Development
But
Some friends last night
Wonder Woman movie
I've seen other two
This one was next level for a hallucination
Why do you keep getting dragged the movie
Like half of his media diet
Say that you like
Stop
New comic book movies f*** off say you like it you wanted to see Wonder Woman
Yeah I got to it opening weekend
I got dragged to a movie theater on opening weekend
During covid
Yeah by some of my friends
Who just
Drag me there
Preston's are
I will I will save it not like
King it is probably the most
It's obvious where he we could imagine
Steve Austin
Lucky I get the f*** out of here
Strangely love the new Ghostbusters
So anyway
It's basically like
If you ghost
See Wonder Woman
You're getting mind-controlled
This one was next level
And it was like a hallucination
Flickr race everything this is the future of Mind Control
I had
Positive message
Deeper
Intuit
But it was
This is Stanley Kubrick level 2.0
So you liked it
Sophisticated
So when you go see that movie
Rur Bass
Okay
I just say you didn't like them
I'm going to tell you this right now about 80% of that move
Fell asleep on the last control
I was happy
Ballers just wanted you to fall asleep
Your subconscious brain took in the rest of it and now I don't feel safe around you
Not sophisticated at all
Not even a little bit kind of a comic book movies Pedro Pascal is the greatest actor in the history of the world
Arizona
So good
He was the best fight at once he wants his
Part was done
That's what I fell asleep
Feel the same way about Game of Thrones
Yeah I don't I don't
Maybe it's a sign of getting older maybe I'm maturing
I don't find Alex's movie reviews as good anymore it was hilarious
Yeah this is kind of
This is kind of just a slow
Pitch
We're both
Too old
To to really get into a bad movie criticism of Wonder Woman
Maybe
I could I could
Could stand someone like
Telling me what's wrong with the
Plot like if there's a structural issue with Tricia Warriors
Yeah I think you could probably still enjoy it I mean
Incredibly huge problems
But most of the Fast and Furious movies
Yeah I'm I'm too old how it to 10 years older than me and I'm too old to listen
Come to his dumbass
Sophisticated b control
I think it was interesting although in our powers
Because the juxtaposition of
Gruff
Ostensible newsman just being like
And now we're on movie 300 of him being a child
Alright
Turn into like there was like
Depth to his review
Handicap mispronouncing Ozymandias
This is pretty great something to that like
He was swinging
And this is just kind of like
I kind of just get the sense
But he was overwhelmed by like a visuals and stuff and didn't understand the movie
He decided to call it brainwash
Beyond suspended disbelief
Beyond
Lower your brain waves to a sleep study
Is beyond daydreaming this was
Elucidation
Tekonsha 7 Seconds
But still my brain was you need to stop
Watching this is not good
Next level
Absolutely
I think he was just sitting there like I don't know what's going on
Yeah
I mean
You know baby
Take some brain for a Center focus on the movie
That might help
At so he he analyzes
The film a little
For no f****** reason
Call Ralph Harris.
Explain what his problem is with Trump's pardons
In this time-wasting on trivial nonsense name Diana
About Wonder Woman 84 any other thing that has Diana in the name
Princess
Couldn't
Come up with another
There's an end of world event coming
We're the ones making it happen because we want too much
Miss our desires we got to give our will over
To something else.
Your will has been given over to this Antichrist character
Then you got to denounce him but give your will to another Collective
That is the goddess.
Mentor bad weather going to be this out of this
As well
Control the public
Our God
2 Stars
So I was listening to that and I was like okay
I've not
I seen this movie
And I'm not going to
To see this movie probably movies that often
It looks
Good if I get any bike hero movie is
I was guessing
There's some sort of the villain
Yeah the tricks people into supporting them
Wonder Woman
Get their support
And that is how she was able to beat
Good but it's close enough that's what he's talkin about more life right problem is like
Somebody's like
No spoilers cuz I didn't finish the movie
Boilers because I can
But it's
It does the main bad guy is Pedro Pascal Nicolas Cage during all over the scenery
And he can grant wishes
But it's a monkey's paw.
Classic
What do you want
And there's a price
Okay so do you need the Twilight Zone episode
The entire movie is Nicolas Cage Twilight zoning everyone
My review of the movie is
This is Bayberry
At the beginning
It's but
And then in the middle your like this is pretty interesting
And then it's but again
Like that
Bedell whole movie
I mean
Bad
The wrong with buttocks
I don't understand all right
Ass head
No I don't know
Nlsd bro
Lots of teasing us lots of kids stuff lots of mindlessness
Lots of 80s Nostalgia for the
That's just for your conscious brain
Behind it the other
Manipulations are taking place
Call Bill Morgan.
Sure but it was definitely
Definitely
Mind control
Caliber material
Yeah
I think that most like bright
Flashy things
Might be a little bit tough
How to take out watch while your on LSD weekend
It's yours old probably with a history of
Amphetamine abuse and a loose grasp on reality
From the jump NAB
So I don't think
Smart move on his no no
So Alex does not really I don't think
Gets back into a more in-depth
Wonder Woman review
Equal equal parts disappointed and glad he didn't
You know
I could have I could have used something a little bit.
Deeper than this but at the same time
I don't care
Yeah
I don't do that eventually
The way you described as Wonder Woman makes me want to watch
Watch they live with him just to see
If like
Does he even
See the hidden messages like the consumed messages he just be like a Blake
Eat me like
I don't get why these people hate these aliens are great capitalists to running everything all these people wouldn't what are you even looking at
That Blake signs for we can talk about this the next time it comes up
Or maybe
Marty
The episode where Rowdy Roddy Piper was on Infowars
Have you talked about
Little lotto
Something that is
Was completely
I just don't understand it
The first part of it
Categorically not true the second
Part in
Impossible
I know you're an American brought up that America's bad America terrible
But when you look at the Historical tyranny
2000 years
The last hundred years
Every form of
The worst people being charged
Un is in the world government
Is in the Corp
That that makes no sense
The last Thousand Years
I mean I guess
Could go with China
Sure perhaps but the UN
The way you make that setting
Work is you just pretend that the world government is everything you don't like
Yeah I'm at the UN is actually also the
Show the League of Nations
And it's also every government that has ever existed throughout Europe
You know whatever your own terms and then you can say all corruption has been part of
I think it's really funny that he absolutely
Cannot bring up a very obvious one in Russia
We just being like
Well Putin has declared himself president for life at Eddie
Crimes that he commits are retroactively impossible to charge important
To kill the only person running against him for leadership
That sounds a lot like stuff
Alex
Once
Trump to dinner
Like Wonder Woman but I think the problem is
In America we're never
Taught about other places to eat
Never we never hear about it
That's something
We definitely don't hear about bad things happening in other countries very differently than when they happen here to it would be wild
Cover
Different story of Zeno the same story differently there.
Crazy never have people on the radio talking about how
That was weird I got very confused by that
And I got
Kind of mad
You're pretty amazing
Information
John Hopkins
AOL
New Year's numbers are in
I looked at last year
Hundreds and hundreds and hundreds of thousands more already that will be this year so they averaged in the rest of the year
About the same.
Well it's not
Well nothing is a statistics show
Spend the fact
Into something that they can adopt
This is really
Simple
CDC there were 2839205 deaths
Total in 2019
A rate of about 800
A 100,000 population
We don't have
The total data for 20/20 yet and reliable figures won't be available for
Four month but the AP reported
The scholars estimate the number will be over 3.2 million
Typically you would expect
A consists
Rate of death to produce between 20,000
Extra tzatziki
As the population ages and also
Increases in
Total number
There is
The reality that people are dying
Political position depends on him leaving in complete denial of that
That fact
Maybe too pretty to but I hope this haunts him for the rest
Festivus life gas
Hopefully this kind of behavior is
People are suffering and losing loved ones
Answer him just to pull this kind of b*******
It's just
I want more Wonder Woman reviews I don't want this s***
I was telling you before the episode I was like
One of those moments where I said like walk away from the computer stand up
No not yet I just know
You don't like
Bye-bye
Family is
What they are but my little sister and her husband both too
Tested positive
Not too long ago
Yalaha and
I just
Like the possibilities for damaged
Do to them that they that we aren't even
Considering
Fine I get it you don't
Don't think that you're going to die
That's great
You act like I have you not seen long covid symptom have you not seen people Psych
Psychosis of manifest
How do you not understand how terrifyingly dangerous this s*** is and it's happened to people in mind
You don't like it
There's No Escape for me
It's because of
F****** monsters like
That's because of at least behaviors like
Totally
F******
Yeah the unknown unknown
I think it's partially what you're talkin
I'm about to
Just like
I don't know I just
I hope he lives long enough
Sukihana
I'm so Alex does finally gets taken calls
I'm not sure if he ever gets around to Diana
I regret to inform you that I think he takes two calls
But one guy calls in North dock bar
Diverse
Trump rally schedule
News media and the
MP3 Americans are you there
Archetype
Be there in d.c.
But I feel like they'll be greatly shocked
Intellectual diversity
Boil
That will come crashing through well in DC on January 6th
Well they are shocking
And then now
Under Trump you do 11 / representation
And the media.
Because I don't know what to do.
That scares the living snot
Established
Oh yeah of course it does
So this caller brought up
Intellectual diversity immediately starts talking about racial
Right
Well they don't actually have it
Electrolit
I don't know what he was trying
To say I think you people have the image of
Trump saying
From
Past Trump rally
I think that that
The ones where we solve
History is Prelude as they say you expect
Sometimes show up
It's sometimes I really do think that
That the GOP thinks maybe there are 10 black people total
And then whenever they show them 11 shows up
The rally they like we got
10%
How do you not think
We are 10% of all black people hear what I think is
Interesting is
The inability for Alex to cure diversity and not immediately jump into defense mode
The
Clearlax
Diversity
At these
These rallies from that standpoint
Intellectual diversity I guess means that some people want to shoot people and some people want to
Go to legislative I guess maybe not a lot of diversity that people are
Nice insta
You know you got a lot of people on different site
Also not for nothing
Trump got like a
8% of
In the last election
It's definitely better to report that as I call record
Alexa portal
Party that I support has never gotten over 10% so alienated
Entire group of people elect Trump's pardons let's not
Consider any of the surrounding content
Batman
Alex of the great idea
What's up
If
Hugo
Is to Insight
Violence
Insurrection
Among right-wing people in this country here
He has an amazing idea
Conceited
We do keep exposing the fraud keep showing the evidence
And then no matter what happens
Trump is still our president
That the power structure in the system
Occupied
And that
Legislators
Houses in others
He should have a nightly TV program
Cast the public
Nightly show where he pretends to be the second president in the rightful president of the United States
Because there's a knock
Occupy or in the house
I don't know if I want to live in a 2020 where we're reliving like
The Pope in the dark pope
Fighting an Italy in the 70
Pizza
Beautiful people
Bad
But I was listening to us was like okay
It's a stupid idea going to do that
TV show Maybe
If it profit
Somehow
He's not going
Go on a barnstorming tour of State
Just leave her in order to save the Constitution
Wow
But he's also
Recruiting
He's one of the greatest orators
Generation
He'll go and give really measured
Thoughtful
Speeches
About the responsibilities of State
Manship
I just found it this kind of said this section of the show just really struck me as like what I would
Describe is
Terrorist Edge
Just trying to get
These people right up to the point of this whole like since he lost the election it has been nothing but
Put edging like
We're going to do this up no no we're not going to blow. This
Feels pretty really pronounce 28
We don't value ourselves
God
Will
What is that we won
We forsake our self
All the blessings and throw them out the window
Because
We got a game of tennis
Player golf
Player we were going to go out to get drunk again
Voicemail
Everything will be taken from you
Everything
U-joint along you'll be taken care of
But you still join
Keep them flying
Let's go to
Mike Arizona micro Mary
Weird weird sound there yet
Now they're a little burp
Reflux
The Alamo Drafthouse Play Everybody's got to get something watching Wonder Woman
Yeah I just hear that stuff and it's just like
Hey
You could keep
You know getting along go-along-to-get-along
But that's how you're going to end up in submission
You're going to end up
In shackles unless you blow something up
Kind of feels that way a little bit but does
I think
That there's something
To the word Alex is saying like
We brought the
Ourselves
It's your own fault
Canobie the guilt fuel you kind of need
To get yourself into a
Or maybe you do
I'm stupid
I think is really
Weird
We talked about this
Believe that masks are evil
Jordan wearing them is a diaper
And what have you
But he sells
Do you rationalize that here a little bit
I'm not talking about
Particular individual
I'm talking about the way of Pharisee brainworx is
Very one-dimensional
You say the master of Fraud and cause bacterial pneumonia
You said I don't
Symbol of slavery
Then what are you doing selling
But when we launch them I made the decision
To print with infowars.com so if you're on a plane
Restaurant
Replace
And they're making you do whatever you need to do there for whatever reason
We're at to fight back
And then use the abuse like a judo move
They attack you
No no we get it
We don't we don't
Doing misunderstands we understand he's selling these masks encourages audience
Oppositional Defiant two people in public
And hopefully cause
16 big enough to go viral and get some
Free Press
Do the thing that I think is fascinating though is that Alex
Grasp of the
It's coming from the other side short name Ali
I would say that it's
Strange
That that you do you think that this is a sign of slavery
But that somehow this sign of slavery is okay if they branded second of slavery correct Alex
Good profit off of
Whether by selling it or the Free Press
That comes from it
Who are the potential new audience
Let's get that gets exposed to your product by other people wearing it
It's it's
It's weird it's
Stream
The design of slavery would somehow become except
Triple if you Bennett
It's a sign of slavery but you know if we're going to have slavery might as well make a little cash
Pretty much what he said
Also he can straight fuc
Himself
Valic spend even a minute looking into the history of how enslaved people were branded and mutilated to signify that they were in
Maybe a little bit
Complaining about having to wear a mask to go to Kroger
The f****** dick
But
He did Brave
The slavery of
Public spaces or somewhere
Cuz you needed to see Wonder Woman
And I talked
Everybody I saw
In the movie theater
It was amazing
Alamo Drafthouse
Horrible socialist levels down
I love it you go in all the lights are turned off
They're sitting
Little thermometer
Laser thermometer
You know the same people died this year than last year
It's all Fridays I do but we just doing
Oh
I never existed
Global takeover
Horrible episode
It was just a disgrace
Google
Why would you go to the theater that's run by terrible socialist globalist as opposed to
Just renting it at full how can you even how can you go give money to terrible socialist global
It seems like
Counter to everything Alex
It seems like you
Probably Rich enough that he has a
Pretty comfortable TV with living room
Based on how many
Goddamn movies talks about watch
You think he's got a pretty cushy setup baby
Even an in-home theater
Shut up
Watches movie around loved one
Oh wait
Can't
He risked brainwashing his children
It's true
Be strong enough to resist the Wiles of the subliminal message Wonder Woman Wonder Woman 84
Did get an R rating for it
Subliminal messages
No kids 18 and older without an adult
MPAA
Subliminal
Exactly
Yeah dumb this is dumb I mean I'm not home
Socialist globalist theater I go see who the Cubs game in
The Ricketts are terrible fascist nightmare
People so
What you going to do
I think I am
Think that there is
An argument to be made for like
You have to
You can't watch the Cubs live
Except by paying for a ticket
To go to regular you know I guess you could travel to another city on TV without giving money to the Cubs
That own their own goddamn Network their evil and you could make a similar argument that renting the movie at home would still be given by
Money to the studio to where get out he doesn't support
Whatever
VPN
Tourette's
To do this
Get Off the Grid buddy
Still
I don't
Think it's a great idea to go to
Movie theater in
Austin
Alex is cranky about the script
Did the globalist Socialist movie theater to see a brainwashing
Exempt
Is it the only way
To deal with that is to have a couple of
News reporter babies
Thief 2 dicks
Barely
Patrick Howley and they both
Work at National file and they are hard
Can't look at them babies
Dress up like adults
Take me home
I don't know this seats don't fit too well they've got shoulder pads on and they have
These are the skills and presentation
Of
I don't know
Lake debate
Junior High kids like
Just outrageous the end of the performance they both like
Step away from their chairs one of them gets on the other shoulder
Yeah and then
Play Tom's a little bit beefy seems like a little flu
Squirrely guys do and their Laurel and Harding is Hellboy
Team about realizing that they work at the same place it's just
It's comical
I kind of want to write a sitcom about it
I will not know a nice little nice little workplace comedy about those two evil Fox
I'll just suffer through listening to these
2 horribly voiced people
Explain to me how Trump
Can seize power
A sitting US representative in the new Congress that will
Coming on January 3rd needs to have in writing
At this promote Brooks
Ejection that needs to be mirrored in the Senate
If it is with Tommy tuberville or any number of people ran Paul I'm looking at you Ted Cruz
Why haven't they agreed to do this at the
F****** a break off and go meet and discuss the allegations
What they should do whether they should strike these electoral votes
What the
And in all likelihood Nancy Pelosi's house will say no Arizona's Sharpie ballot markers worth
Was just how elections Were Meant To Be according to the founding
Fathers meanwhile if the Republicans have a spa
Find which will see if that happens that's the big question
I will come back and say no Arizona must be thrown out
Entirely up to
Is President Mike Pence as
The presiding officer of the joint session of Congress
He gets to decide what to do with that information Alex Mike Pence
Can say alright I'm siding with the Senate on this one we're going to toss out Arizona
He can do that
Or
Penske the safe
Thanks and you can say there's no agreement
I do not want to cast a tie-breaking vote
Are for Arizona stands
I think the founding fathers were
Go ahead and throw it out the votes
Turn on white swim yeah yeah I don't think they would worry too much about this election at all
Flight if the founding fathers had anything to say about it not be what yours is
Fathers definition
Maybe 5 million would have been cast for this year that news Italians and Irish
You can't vote
F*** out of here I will tell you this
If if they find some Byzantine way where there like no no technically I mean
I'm sorry but according to Legal code 206 points e54
Trump is going to be president for the next four years
I'm going to start a war by mice
By myself against Byzantine
Yeah it's not going to fly this is here this is just fanservice
If this happen
The way that pappert is
Disgusting
These are objections that have to be brought up in the January 6th
Joint session of Congress
And then it would require
Senator and representative to sign.
Each house would meet separately and
Debate the matter
Boethiah
Each
Would have to have an objection
With a senator and representative
Memory chap to be debated
We call on the right honorable senator from Kentucky
Do you believe in reality
No next person
So each house
Congress would then vote and they would require a simple majority for the
Directions to Stan
The objections would literally never pass the house so you can just
Forget about that
It seems nearly impossible for me to imagine that it would end up in a 50-50 tie in the Senate
Go to be the only time
Mike Pence's vote would matter because the only instance there would be like
Okay
Possible if both Democrats win in the Georgia runoff election
Ensure
Been devoting the bike strictly party-line should then we get to a 50/50
Super unlikely
I find it
Really difficult to believe even as Craven and ghoulish is some of these GOP Khan
I can't imagine Mitt Romney
Loading along that line
They just heard my threat
If I start my own War
Mitt Romney
Would I don't
There's a number of GOP
Do senators that I don't think
I think even McConnell's
Atossa
Mcraven dickwad if he thought he could win
If he thought he would lose you find some way to screw somebody else will you
You couldn't even if you do that then you somehow get the objection to stand in the Senate
Still doesn't stand in the house
It doesn't matter
These statutes are really clear that in order for things like this to fly there needs to be agreement in both houses of Congress
When there's an alternative slate of electors offer from each state in the house
If they disagree on which to accept
The statute states that the votes of the electors whose appointment was certified by the governor of the state
Shelby
Counted
The only outcome this is going to result in his like they're just going to draw this s*** out
The process is just going to get dragged out
They're going to stall any gun government operation
They're going to further radicalize and to educate the right-wing elements you just can't accept
The Trump lost
Peppers that you're creating this fantasy world
And then when that world does not materialize
It's just going to drive the audience
Deeper into the hole of resentment
Insisting that the system is broken
Going to campus
Like these magical fantasy plans don't work
What hope do
Natural process have screwed
That's all that's going on here
Yeah
Draw it out drag it out
Yeah the the problem
Is
Once you've exhausted all of your magic
Copeland's
Then everybody who's believed that the magic
Plans could happen eventually has to go
Nothing we do work
We have to do something
I'm usually the thing that they think
To do different
Is not like
Get into actually
Community Building
That's because
They never they don't ask
Why don't we why are we always lose
Because they are because of
Plans or magical
Can't be that
It has to be because these people are so evil they won't even follow the rules that weird
We're the good guys we're trying to follow the rules and they won't
It's not that
We're full of s***
Nope nope certainly not
Tom pepper coming in with his magical Mike Pence plans and also on the
Call right
Just like really being a s*** head
Will Alex not first of all I want to make clear that cuz I just got a text
You're nobody's considering I replacing Mike Pence it in the short-term as a strategy but
Mark my words that was looked into
That was research
Absolutely no one
As a free pass
If they're going to go against President Donald Trump
President Donald Trump is the Republican Party
President Donald Trump
Is this movement and the American people are desperate to keep him in here
I looked into this a little bit and I found a mission statement
Patrick Howley
Cheshire
There is no loyalty except loyalty to Donald Trump
There's no love except low for Donald Trump
There's no laughter except the last
Triumph over antifa
There's no art no literature no science
When we are omnipotent we shall have no more need for science
There'll be no.
Distinction between Beauty and ugliness
There'll be no curiosity no enjoyment of the process of life
All competing Pleasures will be destroyed but always
I do not forget this Winston there will always be the intoxication of our constantly increasing eat get where I'm going
Get a
Get a job that does
Do something good with B become a bricklayer
Do something good with your life
Instead of writing that
Sweat a little bit
I mean spiritually
Patrick Ali's a little bit to like
Obvious
Here's what's going to happen on January 6th is great Independent Media
And an Alex Jones
Are going to show the world
In real-time all of the evidence
If the courts
Have Nots
Making public
To the people on the Supreme Court won't even here and I know Matt gaetz is going to
I know we can drag it out
4 hours
Upon hours
Upon hours and create a maximum pressure scenario
And that's why
We're doing
Is going to really make an impact
So that was true
A few too many cards they're going to achieve is this big dumb dumb publicity stunt
The process by however long they can to maximize
Unfortunately according to us go to each of Jackson that gets made his Limited
The two hours of debate with no congressperson being allowed more than 5 minutes
To speak or question the matter
You can do the math if you want but according to the law there's only so much they
They can drag that out this way good luck
Enjoy
Jesus
Tom and Pat
Close things out
By explaining
Hey
Hoover Dam global
All right I just have here
These people are
F****** nut
That's okay
30 seconds for 1 minute each
How would you describe in one minute
You started to say is accurate at 6
Collection of psychopaths
I figured out that
They can leverage blackmail
Extortion
Bribery everything you can get to
Keep a seed in power no matter what kind
Country is the global hegemon if it's the United States that's great if it's China who cares
That is the global if they are power-drunk they are sick
And they don't they have no loyalties to anything but Power
Well they might have loyalty the ball
They are overseeing a genocide of little babies
There's sick people they have a religion
People leave that there
Descended from the Nephilim Bloodlines at the satanic luciferian called
Wow
Artemis believe
The Nephilim
They don't
Wow don't exist
Don't know but what they talked about behind closed doors
This really
Say that out loud definitely believe they're descended from the Nephilim
Okay
Goodbye
Goodbye Tom peppers and Patrick House
Comported yourself exactly how one would expect
Which is not well
So I was running
Steal booze from somebody to toddlers wearing
Goddamn
Alex has a really important
Mixer to structural public
Book service announcer
Not that I think it's actually really
Really key for the info Warriors
Detective Hart
Either I absolutely agree with you and
We we have to physically not support the big levels change sometimes we still will be forced to
Have to physically support Mom and Pop
It's a war
Didn't you go
Wonder Woman at a socialist globalist movie theater on opening weekend
Huge chain or anything like that I think you're supporting mom-and-pop I mean obviously
Mom and Pop Evil globalist social
Now they're still
Room for that small business global
Opening weekend
Movie I hate
Great
Alex
Let's call this color actually brings up
Good point cuz ideas
I love to see in the future your show Maybe
Pakistan
I want to be a new show baby Folk
Hassan Howie
Setting up new
Deities
Outside of the mainstream society and
What you're saying is 100% that the answer we should all just be focusing on communities
Neighborhood sounds organization
Free association groups
Or we want a future where we want Traditional Values
Where we honor
Life we honor children where we honor goodness
Because they both were taken the churches and control most of those
And so we need something that
But something that's just human
We reject
The wages of the New World Order God bless you
Paper call bring it up like hey why don't we talk more about setting up some coffee
Do you want to do
We're stuck our imaginary enemies have solutions that we don't like
Because they're also
We have to make a rural autonomous Zone
Skousen shows up
And
The conversation about this
Dumb elector plan
The Tom pappert was pitching earlier
Comes up
Mosaic
2000's credit
You have to go in for that b******* he thinks it's a dumb plan
It's going to be very easy to block it doesn't matter how many people are in favor of the Trump electors all it takes is to
Ur3 to block
And I think
What's going to happen in the sea
Is there any
Disrespectful
Eating a little bit disrespectful a little bit
Having a little
In terms of him
You know saying that this
His plan is dumb
Yes I will
Cracked my hat
Call this point
What he starts talking about
There was that
Story those going around about John Roberts
Chief Justice of the Supreme Court yelling about how we can't take up his case absolutely
Listen to this
Idiot Joel skousen talk about that store
As you know this
It's supposed to bleed from the Supreme Court
Which I'm a little bit doubtful of
Stating the John Roberts you know how to yelling and screaming session threaten conservatives into
Not taking up the Texas case
For fear of rioting
Trump
The Supreme Court came out the next
There was no such yelling match because the Supreme Court Justice in person
Weeks
Because of covid-19 everything's done by Zoom meeting
Another person that said well
It's very possible they did meet in person because
John Roberts wouldn't want to put this on Zoom which is not a secure former
Communications that could have been
And lead to the American people what he was saying on that so I think there's good arguments in both
I dunno Alex
That John Roberts is a controlled individual by the Deep state
Always vote against Trump to make sure he's not re-elected
What a f****** idiot
Alright so
Doubt this story
Even happy
Great
Start
Start to launch this ship
They told me that it didn't happen because the only
Zoom meeting to happen for weed
My rebuttal to that is
What if they did
Whoa yeah that's a good one what if instead of the thing that's real they did the thing that I say
I'm going to f****** subscribe to your newsletter man you were killing it
Reasoning is being brought to this
Alright now I know the sun rose yesterday but
What is it
Didn't
What would we say then I would guess that
Any communication between
Supreme Court judge
This is not something
And therefore this meeting would not be different or special from any other meeting
If any is being done on Zoom I would assume
Probably
Hyper secure
Special zoom zoom
I would doubt it
Very stupid
Very stupid reasoning skills buried
Analysis
I will say as we found out what we did our bonus episode of resume
It's not even possible for John Roberts
It's the scream at somebody through Zoo
It cuts your volume off 100 near as loud as your laptop
In this episode
Alright I was in
Who cares just talked about how you need to live an hour outside of town
I want to move an hour outside
I do not want to talk about
So we are we jump to the 29th here this is
Is delightful
I find this a lot of fun
Alex decides to
Have to kick things off
By teasing
A little bit
Even about a little little too
Now I know some credible information
But I am at Liberty to just
Give you a hint which I don't think too hard
January 6th will be wild
In DC well it will be like
But I can tell you the Twilight Zone
Nature of all of this one up to a whole new level.
Alex keep trying to hit the Trump going to come to the rallies
I love you ideas for baby in like some information
Don't
Giveaway the information
Make a puzzle
This is really serious
You got to be on the up-and-up about this
Now I'm not going to tell you what
How to hit
Eli
Hard to say that I just want you to put your own
Spin on it
Alright
Yesterday's show the 28th was kind of disappointing in a lot of ways there wasn't a lot of content there's a lot of
Stupid s*** anytime those two
Do Dum Dums are on the show
Yeah
Wonder Woman complaining and I found it to be uninspired and by Alex standards
Didn't even talk about Pedro pass
Cuz it's amazing
Muselk
I'm sure he is but there was a problem with the show.
It was beyond what I could observe
Okay let me just try to calmly explain this
I got
A show for San Jose
And then I got so upset
After looking all the news
Over preparing
Watching wonder why
That I was in such a show yesterday
Paradise couldn't couldn't get my job done
Cuz I was too
Prepared again
Instantly over-prepared whining about Wonder Woman
Happened because
Cuz he was too
And someone named Diana called in
Well then you got it
You just got up
Look I don't blame him for that I would have done the same in that situation
And then today he's like I got to Maaco.
You know I got it I had all the
This over preparation yesterday now I must pay off that over preparation
To do show off like a baby might need about Wonder Woman
Covid stocks
One is from yesterday
3 Year from today
Four covid stats
Look at this.
Look at this one
Look at all these stacks
I have so much paper
I've seen
Look I I will have been in the pool hustling game for for a while
I'll tell you right now I've see I know when somebody has
Some fake ones
Alright I know what's underneath that all
I know what's going on this is somebody who's like
Pata de SA
Hit the word limit
That's that I would feel a little this
Do the size 15
It's
Much a desperate attempt
To trick people into that
Thinking he's prepared at all
Because it visually looks like he might have.
But it's all good
Just a magic trick
Alice's apparently the story is
Another level of Deep Cover denialism
Some that again
Was like the kind of thing that I just had to walk away from
Breathe a little bit
F*** you man
Turning people away
What restaurant is full but there's 10 more next door than our
That's how they statistically but I don't just tell you that
British show you where you can go directly in the cdc's outnumbered and see what every hospital in Yorktown
Play the Cubs
Because they're all incentivised
Call ecobee to get money
I need to be in the hospital
Travis County
You said
As of last night 9% covid capacity
There are 70
People
Hospitals in Austin in Travis County
That supposedly I'm cover
We're talking millions of people
In the hospital
Alex is desperately trying to spin the new stories that have been coming out about how hospitals are going to have to start talking
Think about rationing
And care cuz they can't handle the load of patients
With the surge of covid-19 cases
Obviously this
2 something people have been warning about for a long time and everything Alex has stood for
Exact things that people wore
Would cause the need to ration care
And turn people away from hospital
The fact that we've reached the point we have should be a sign that people like Alex Jones
Cancerous influence on the public information space
And that his recommendations headlight exactly where everyone knew they would
So it's super important for him to act
Like all this is imaginary
Or something
The way he chooses to do it is by covering the story like a 5th grader doing a book report about a novel he's only pretending to have read
There's a couple of days
Details that he got from reading the back cover these hitting really hard in order to fake like he knows what he's talkin
A December 28th article in the Austin
Austin Statesman reported that the ICU
Occupancy in Travis County Road
Supersite
In just the previous week
The county has a maximum ICU availability of 200 patients
And they were at 132
Do on Monday night
They're 422 hospitalizations in the county link to covid-19 as of the time of that the writing of that are
I'll try to get a sense of what out
To possibly be talking
Because the numbers
But he's using are just
Wheatley out of sync with anything I can find
Reported anywhere
I looked at the Austin covid-19 surveillance dashboard and I think I figured out where you got the seven
27 number from
I think that was the number of people listed as on
Ventilator
At the time that he looked at the data okay
December 31st that number was up to 81
It seems like the number could have possibly be close to what he was saying at the time but he read it
But I actually found a Statesman article
From earlier this week that cited that the number of people on ventilators
What's 77
In Austin
On Monday episode was recorded
Pretty sure that's
What's outrageous about this if this is what he's going off of
Like this this
Misinterpretation
Is it right next to the ventilator number on the covid-19 dashboard is the
Be hospitalized
Best figure
Twice as large a phone
Which is much higher
If Alex actually it looked real find these numbers they would be literally impossible
For him to miss that one and
Stevie other one
It kind of heavily implies that either he's just repeating
Something that someone told him which is an accurate
Or he's willfully passing along inaccurate information in order to
Minimize the public health risk
Pose by covid-19
Extra people killed
I mean he just saw Wonder Woman so whenever he read that he was his brain was all messed up he thought the
But the smaller number was the only number that you could say that's what happens with Wonder Woman
You can't see large numbers
Yeah I know it's a real bummer
Write something bigger than 16.5 and I
Cannot read it
Also in terms of deaths the City of Austin put out a press release on December 30th announcing the covid-19 was the third
Highest cause of death
This year behind only cancer and heart to
The number is it at least 548 this year
If you do a little bit of math
It's north of 1 week
Also I know it's
It's not possible I wish you'd
Just stop doing stuff
Like this
Like it's so much more fun when it's
Wonder Woman Illuminati symbolism
Fake Jeffers
Person quotes
Sucks it blows me away like I understand it
Because
I have never been able to
Light $20,000 on fire whenever I wanted
But I never fails to surprise me what
People will be convinced
Is enough to like
Corrupt somebody
Like this whole I called making an extra 20 grand out of
Advertise advertise K and ICU and it's like that's nothing
The people that you are describing as being the evil billionaire
That are destroying everything
What
Put put
$20,000 under their shoes just to feel like what it's
To step on money
Does a secondary conversation even
The past that that money is being discussed isn't like some kind of a bonus
Yeah yeah yeah
Like its Medicare payments
What do you think of people who have other things don't also have payments attached them like
A heart attack
Do you think that maybe
Might be more No-No if you go in for a cough
And you have a heart attack they still only pay for
For the cops they're not giving people bonuses just for having a heart attack in the hospital they are 0-4 others
It's so stupid
The number is also like
Really big
Do people like us do people like
It's one of those things that it's hilarious to me whenever people are like oh
House of Representatives make like $140,000 a year
Yes I know that's a lot of money to you and me
The oligarchs who owns them
They can ship out $140,000 every 5
Like it is
So little
The real scale of corruption that we are existing in
Is World level like
The country
It's what corruption I will corrupt you
If you own suydam now like that's the level of
Billionaire evil corrupt
Then we're dealing with
I think I get what you're saying
The scale
So I thought that was bad I thought that Alex is claiming that 77 people are hospitalized with covid-19
And Travis County which is
Is demonstrable not truant
Very bad
I know there's bad but then this is
Is worse
I think
Kyle Rittenhouse is Mother
No
No Peter first interview
No leprosy
I know this is your first interview show
She'll be joining us with her lawyer
About the incredible persecution of The Rittenhouse it's a beta tester
The rest of us in the
Alex cannot stop saying we are all Kyle
House she's a very uncomfortable
Not good
It's bad interview
A little bit
To end this episode we are all murderers however is something that I would
Save that that Alex is
Is correct on spirit
Describing yeah
So we got to get back to this Hospital
Alex
He's going to blow the lid off
Man
This guy is an in-depth
Journalist
I'm about to lay out for you the absolute truth
You have total criminal fraud
By the hospital
By the media
By the CDC
Leave your house for a few months
A 2.5
Million Dead just a few months
Hospitals are already overwhelmed
And the people went to the very Hospital
Remember when everybody took pictures of parking lots and pretended to know one with the hospital and I remember that
Industrial
Nonsense for a bit
Actually talking about article on NPR that
You found where
Is yours
And then you went to the federal government CDC website
Know you know there
You know you're not what you got a billion dollars
This week is yours
So what's going on here is that Alex is upset about an article he didn't read in NPR where they had some links that I guess he's certain
No one followed
I'm certain that Alex didn't do any original research on this nor do I believe that he went and looked at the raw data cuz I'm certain
To be unable to read the Excel spreadsheet
Dilaudid
Yeah it's a lot of rows
He's talking about the data visualization that NPR posted which does show the Travis County has 9% of its own
Known inpatient beds used
For covid patients
The problem with that
Is meaningless
Princeton
If Alex looked a little bit deeper into the data he'd see that 9 out of 50
Boston hospitals are not included in the data
So it's a little incomplete and times are getting the full picture
But even beyond that
The problem isn't that all the beds are being taken up by covid Page
It's that with Rising covid patients the hospitals are reach their capacity and have no beds left for anybody else who might need
That's why I'm more than surface-level analysis
Is dadaism poor
So let's take
St. David's Medical Center in Austin as an example
They showed 7% of their adult
Inpatient beds being taken up
For covid page
That seems like nothing
A drop in the bucket
7%
However if you look at the next
Column you'll see that 93% of their total adult inpatient beds are occupied
So any increases in covid patients would be a disaster for them
You see this in many the included Austin
Ascension Seton Medical Center has 30
10% of its beds taken by covid
But 90% total occupied
Dell Seton Medical Center at UT Austin
10 is 23% of
Meds taken by covid patient
But 94% are occupied total
North Austin medical center 10% are covid patients
But 94% total are occupied
This is the pattern that is
The important
The concern is definitely partially that there
Lot of covid cases
Symphony to be treated
But the larger picture has to take into account
Did hospitals have a certain capacity
But even beyond that they only have a certain amount of human attention that can be provided
Patience
You can't magically create doctors and nurses in a 3D printer
Even if you add a ton of beds
Or put patients who should be in the ICU and not ICU bed
It's not like that part of the equation
Can be balanced out
This is the sort of contact that Alex
The price of his because he
Pics of this 9%
Statistic
You can go that 9% all he wants but it doesn't change the reality
Far more complex
Then surface-level faked
Courts yeah
I feel like I might be saying it's a lot but
This is disgraceful like it it's just a
It's infantile bulshit
This elevator has
100 people on it and there's only an increase in 9% of covid patients adding to the Elevate I mean sure
The maximum capacity is 50
And the elevators going
To fall
And everyone's going to
Fit an extra 9%
It's interesting when you either willfully or are unable to understand
The complexities
The things and then you gloat about
Yeah
So there you go
What is a gentleman
7%
Boston Medical Center
20%.
Ascension
Oh no this one
They're at 13%
Again those are the hospitals that we just discussed he's not taking into account the larger picture and he's gloating
About missing
The point which is kind of like
Exactly what Alex
I'm going to cut up this next clip because it's pointless but I just thought it was pretty
Pretty funny but Alex claims that he fat
Fact check Johns
Alright alright alright
EPA
Taking care of John
Is this number I just thought that was really funny mental image of the
In comparison to how excited I got when I heard this.
So there's fast now I haven't hit the latest
Actually
A power control
It was first in a Canadian document they tried to say well we're not sure what's real but we were able to search the document find other documents rather country
Confirm it is real
Straight ahead
God damn you so excited
We have you now
Yes
You better
You better fucken follow through on we have you now we got
You have if you have them now
Better now
You know me pretty well you know that's something that gets me excited when Alex drop something like that on my lap
We have them now not later we're not going to get them soon now is when we have
Alright cuz Alex
There's more important things going on
Okay
Maryam
I should have known he had a cellmate
Usher
And I'd cellmate just died of covis you are now this is a conspiracy
Problems
My uncle said
News reports
Prison the day before Epstein
Hanging Shelf
In August it was there
Contracted the Coronavirus
Kelly was found dead in his apartment
Heather telling you it was Coronavirus
Kitty Wells die
Covid-19
Please pull up a server
Little do you know
Well done coronavirus covid-19 time machine
Dallas
Call Jack
I think he thought of
Bit before he realized that the cellmate wasn't there when it happened
Yeah yeah
Really strong like
Was she at
Thought this was the person I was going to pin the murder on the going to be great
Is there really going to be great
Yeah
Alex hasn't got the memo from Trump lawyer tweeting about
It's going on here
Oh God
I'm going to cut out this
Copart
To I just
I have no patience for it right now and it's not important
I can just tell you what happened
Ivan reichlin
You hung out with Michael Flynn Jr
Some kind of a search engine
Start up a they're great
Confusing stuff
He is on
His argument for Alex
Is the Trump needs to immediately take over the emerge
Okay that'll do it
Then we'll all
Eddie needs to start I guess like
Broadcasting
Two people and a
Explaining like the election was stolen over their phones
Or something
Specifics of what they want Trump to do but it involves taking over technology in a way that's like
Usually
Just for tornadoes
Judging by the number of times it came up in cartoons when I was growing up
I assumed you would be able to solve most Anti reality problems
With a frying pan to the side of the head
You know
Like if this happened if somebody says his reality
Good thing I don't
Oh yeah
I don't know if I can
Frying pan
Only if it brings people back into reality
I got a magical friend
I got the sense that this had something to do with
Wonder Woman
The lasso of Truth
No the plot of the movie
Like the electronic alert system
I don't know I like I said I haven't seen the movie Alex was hinting at
Some connection
And Wonder Woman presidential
We can control and broadcast into every home using this new technology bingo
Yep. Okay
Yep that is honestly I forgot about that part because I don't remember too much of
Anyway
Alex
Get Trump
To use that
Alright the super-secret magical broadcast into everybody's home
Got to stop letting me
How many people watch movies
Yahoo be good
All they get to read is Heart of Darkness
Come back to the the Alamo Drafthouse
Colonel Kurtz
He dead that's what you got to do
So
Sorry
To Rittenhouse his mom
She's rubbing it sure because we've heard Ivan raichlen before and basically his interview is no more interesting than
Trump should use the emergency alert system
Come to f*** with people be great
It wouldn't
It will be
Dark
Yeah
What were the worlds was the president and also real
Got to be awful so I feel okay skipping that I find myself uninspired
At the moment
I'm not inspired by Kyle Rittenhouse is mom as well but
It seems like something that bears
Discussion
Alex is like really trying
Turn Kyle Rittenhouse into like a folk
Kiro
He watched the last burn down apartment buildings in police station
On the side of the road
Demonstrations Kyle Rittenhouse
Murder bee
Symbol
A murderer
Murder
Medic
Help people
Murdering people in Kenosha Wisconsin
He's a murderer
Thugs with guns
Murder I forgot to self
Book thrown at him
Cuz he's a murderer
I couldn't tell if this interview was
Prompted by
The state tacking on a
Breaking curfew chart
Even thought was a little like that's a little bit
Buffalo Patty there's got to be a reason
But I can't figure out what it is they can treat him very nicely and then hit
Throw the book at him on that break
Curfew charge
I'm not entirely sure but
I was listening to this and I'm like I'm going to get mad
I don't like this
But then I realized
I'm not going to get mad
I'm going to feel really sad
For these people
I mean
Look
No I don't
But at the same time I feel gross
Maybe that's what I feel
I'm not sure exactly what I feel.
We need more help Alex we need everyone to go to 3 Calle usa.com
Outrageous excessive
2 million-dollar
Bail amount
We raise those two million dollars we put the cash in a barrel
Beside him pray he's with his family but we need a lot more resources with this is going to
Bard
Every American every Democrat Republican independent
And they're going to come after you next
Let's be clear about that
People like Rittenhouse like Stone like Jones like Trump
Not being a victim
The lawsuits the lights
I've been like nothing would be
Happening
Alex if you didn't
Commit bike
Violations
People
Then he wouldn't be getting
Exuded
For those those things
Shock people
How are even do no benefits protest with a gun that he shouldn't legally of hat
The number of issues that you know like
It's not like globalist want to just turn people into symbols
Or whatever
Actions that precede those
Lawsuits are arrest
The General ER what caused them please
These f****** cheer
When a black person gets
10 years for
I
I'd like any sympathy that I had where I was like
You know what
It was her it was her son who did it
She's not directly involved with that I'm not going to blame the mother you know maybe parenting is an issue I don't know
I don't know them personally
The all f******
King Kong
Yourself you're a murderer too I don't give
Also this like
This entire appearance is really just about race
Constantly going back to the wild love like we need more money
He doesn't want her just like
Putting out this message
You get money for Content you understand the job
Tell me how bad the last
New experience for you to really
Find out what the left really like
They don't like to be murdered
Is
Disgusting
Unreal
And you have to be a criminal
But you want a postal
My son
Know your son's murderer
Your lies have
Then he's a monster
A killer
A murderer
Yeah
It's
It's just pain
I'm just sold
You know
They need to be stopped
The internal logic here doesn't work because if the left has turned her son into a criminal and a murderer
Then they should be putting them on a pedestal based on her saying that
They take criminals and put them on pedestal
Don't make sense
And we
The left needs to be stopped
Otherwise
Kyle Rittenhouse will continue murdering us
I just
F*** you
I agree if you want to say that to me
Cool I will let you
You finish your statement and then I will say go fuc
What if somebody wants to say that
New website and everything like that we're selling merchandise
T-shirt
I know imma say it
Bikinis
And
Barbie 4r
Did buy it
I don't care
I got that vibe
I'm interested to read Kyle's book
If I did it here's how I would have done it
DDC get to keep the profits from all of those
Sales in a best-case scenario for like
Like the rest
Cast of his wife
Like
This is not
Not part of it
Your mom selling Kyle Rittenhouse
Bikinis
Like just eat
Take that night in Kenosha out of the equation imagine your mom selling a bikini with your face on it
That would be years of therapy
Be great.
Great
Abbey real great
It seems gross
Jesus
That's not because it's a bit
I mean it's just like
Hayward
It's just
Crass you know like it
Exploitative
Yeah it's like a it's like a
Peaky blinders
Whenever the one kid goes to jail and his mom
It went up sleeping with the the corrupt
Evil Northern Irish
Police chief to get him out and he's like
Ma
What did you do
Infinitely better
Then if you find out your mom sold your face on it
Bikini
I refuse to believe the peaky blinders exist
I think it's just a funny name
All right Joe
Murphy's
Are you got this vibe
Office mom that really worried
You know like
Laughing about selling bikinis and then getting a little defensive about it
Like alright alright Ma
Oh and then
The lawyer comes in
There has been a long march through the institutions over the past few decades
Mass revolution in China and the Chinese
They attempt to destroy everything sacred in a society
They try to destroy history
Destroy our faith in God
And they try to capture the key
Institutions such as the media
Such as financial institutions and
In-N-Out
All I can say is Amen to that we got one more second with you guys coming up
I don't like the idea of this guy thinks there's a
Lawyer
Such as
This is like
This is like when you're 17 and there's like
When you go to college you need to get a good Humanities education and then you can
Kind of start getting your special
And you're all like I don't need the what is all this Humanities bulshit my major is
Pre-law or whatever it is like
This is why you need a Humanities education
This is why you need to read anything I haven't logged
Confession
I didn't actually watch
Watch this video
Can't confirm if this guy is like not a robot
Hayirli possible theater
Animated on Siri
It's one of those machines
Such as media
Today I write the screenplay
Oh boy
So Alex is like hey I got a
Great idea
You should work with Barnes
Really heavy.
Now he's idea is like I don't like these pardon
The trumpeter on route
Could be used
Forgot
Can the president
Pardon Rittenhouse
Before he's convicted obviously he didn't do anything wrong the laws on his side
B
But just hypothetically
Could President Trump
Preemptively pardon Kyle Rittenhouse
Authorities of the Constitution
We are going to need to take
Take this fight
Frontline's in Wisconsin
So
You know
Also any any political system
Where you think it's
It's a good idea to be able to write get-out-of-jail-free cards
Free murder cards
Preemptively
Bad sister
Imagining that sister
Yeah it's not good
Anyway so I call these people I'm not going to listen to any more of their interview it's not really that interesting it's just kind of
Alex bacon
For Kyle to come on when you can talk
Speak publicly like I got to get this guy a job
Might as well be what he say
Yeah
The show
No more Wonder Woman socks
Although he does get to talk about Bill Gates
Bill Gates
Demon
Super D mature
Genetic
Super demon
That is a
Littrell super
Super killing machine
So is he back in the twelves elevations on TV
Which were the psycho is there is what they love to do
Send letters the police you'll never catch me you'll never get me
Kentucky
They just hate everyone
What the people in Mash
Of course A lot of times it's genetic
Taking his dad
Mark Zuckerberg
Astro Boy
When I call him
Chromosome disorder
What
Several of them
He got so pissy to the last straw was Jones calling me a genetics
That was his last drop
The Apprentice of Bill Gates
Mark Zuckerberg
Vacation together
Waters football call my God
I hate this so much
I hate you.
S***
I really don't like the idea that Alex has decided that there is a psychopath
Gene
Inheritable among Generations
He can see visually yeah yeah
Take here in 2020
That's what you want to hear that was really great
Magic
A lot of people who believe
Really heavily that things should be talked about it and almost
Exclusively genetic terms
Things Are
Cool folks
Yeah
Yeah they're super cool
31 Westcliff
To disappoint but this is actually
Perfect last clip rally
How often is a lot to cover
I only
Scratch the surface here
Chelada today I didn't get to it
I can't really do justice to this we have them now
Nightlife
We have them now
Glass water
And then I'm going to go
And I'm going to
Whole report on this latest development
Great
Where you saw a few months ago they got
Canadian document about the next lockdowns coming and then they'll be the strange
Will never unlock things until the Communist takeover happen
People said is this real
Yes
Alex didn't have time to cover this I don't have time for it either we'll see what happens in the next episode
I hate you
So much
Do we get to a couple of different things listen
Start using tornado alert
You got to get the message to the people the problem with America Dan is not enough people have heard Trump
That's the real issue
Then I think we've all had
He's just not getting his ferret court because he is worried because the courts keep reading the petitions being like
Oh no this is this is
Comically stupid reading is one of their big hang-up
Comes to writing
So I think I think we have
A pretty good start
To the end of the year for Alex year
Wonder Woman
Yep
Some harder covid denialism
Particularly around the lake
77 people like that
Glaring misunderstanding of the data anyway is action of it
I feel
I feel unglued
We're listening to
Invest like I want
There's no continuity
Right right right
It's just all over the
Yeah it's everywhere
What happened to the lake
No follow-up on Asheville we have it we have them now you don't need to worry about it what you need to worry about Dan
Is
Which of the Hollywood chrises are you a fan of
Cuz listen
I Hate Chris
State right now I watch 107
I hate
Chris Pine what about Evans Captain America I can't support that all cops are bad
Chris Chris Hardwick
Trying to pull out
The guy from Chris
Chris o
Well now I can't remember
What does a character's name was Chris
Has Rob Lowe know I'm thinking of the guys
Yeah Chris Pratt he's a he's a lunatic he suck
Yeah which of the Elven Chris Hemsworth who's Chris Hemsworth
Thor Thor's brother
Love Thor
Love door that's my favorite Chris
Done great
What about you
I don't know man I maybe I'll Christmas
Are there in the walk Nation
That's what I choose
Your stars to me
So we'll be back on the next episode on Monday
To check in and see how Alex closes out the disastrous year that was 2020 got to get rid of
And then
And I will be in touch smoother sailing or not we'll see
We'll see but Happy New Year to you and yours
If name celebrate their Gregorian
Gunners
Happy New Year's Eve website
Total hours on Twitter
Please find a local charity or bail Fund in your area to help out those doing God's
Clerk I'm Daryl rundus
I live on the edge man I live 45 minutes for
From town
Alex