Damn important I sweat it
I have great respect for this knowledge B
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Acknowledge
What's up what's the price
Jordan
Is that I can
Completed my newest little nanoblocks sculpture
Getting into a little mini Legos quite a bit and I got a new one
Can call the mini Legos that is a brand named Andy's are nanoblocks
I got one that is via the Easter Island heads
And it was a little bit easier actually it was pretty small but great I've always had a
An attraction of
Drawn to the
Easter Island
The statues
For a while
The call of the island I do like an island
Yes and
You know just the idea of those gigantic heads
If you're a kid
Amazing
Absolutely decoration on the
Yeah it is it is always nice to see Easter Island because no matter I am even if you know what's going on and
And how it was done as as many archaeologists and scientists do
There's still a party that just looks it doesn't go away
Are you guys thinking
It's still it's still remarkable no matter what
Absolutely
Going to be back in ff7 but boy
I just
I just read my 7,000 School Chocobo in the 23 years
Steven Tyler
It's weird
I've read my fastest ever go Joker
Eddie's I've never seen a joke about a number 7100
Longo's lines
I rarely ever finally finished the game and it always ends with that
Completed that
Like you have to go through all these different
Open things in it yourself
Good fun
A sense of achievement
Can you develop a relationship I named them
That sounds exactly like the
I told you about when you told me you were back on your b*******
Handle Knights of the Round summon Materia in the new remake that'll be incredible
Well I look forward to that on your behalf
Sing episode to go over where we talking about
December 31st
Up to January 1st 2021
I'm damn this is now 21
Confusing
We're going to the first day of this week
Alex above these shows
You know
Some stuff
Okay yeah I don't know I found myself like I had an interesting experience what I was listening to this
It was one of those times that I listen
Come to the show and I'll be alright Alex
I'll find myself Mystery Science Theater in kind of like
Okay
Alright yeah there's just a long stretches
Okay sure nothing was going on
We may okay you're really shoehorned that in trying real hard
Hanza fated that horn today
Okay before we get to today's episode
Xbox Live sign up
First burn
Aw thank you so much
Heuberger
Next EMH
I'm a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk I do just in
Next
I'm a policy wonk thank you to people who donated on elevated level we appreciate that
Very much so
And then I'm so glad you don't have to
To sell blood anymore you are now what
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
Thank you so much
I got a correction
I accidentally said Brianna it's
Brenna car sorry about that
They throwing eyes all over the place
Starting from the beginning hey everybody welcome back to college
And make as much and I'm so glad you're not yourself
I'm not there
You have more credibility
Comfortable in your single record in your office
I mean I do feel spoiled
A little Comfort existence
Anyway
Jordan
Today
We got we got it episode
Found this intro to today's episode
This beginning is first clip where Alex
This is like just getting
In the gears going
On New Year's Eve day alright I thought that this was
Really exciting okay
I was wrong but I got pretty excited
What is this
Well this really is
The equivalent
Intruder cell
He's talking about the vaccines covid-19
Clone of human
Love it
Coming in and assimilating our entire bodies of jellyfish is
Organism a colony organism
Play all jellies organism
The replication body
Only thing that will be the original you when it's done the cells in your eyes
Woman's ovary
Call Adam cell
Distant
Galaxy
Haha
From some
They came from a different dimension
Faraway Planet Air
System sure
It came from the mad scientist here on our planet but it is as alien as a Martian
Stitch's alien as somebody from
Why is some single cell organism
Is some Planet orbiting Alpha Centauri Czar Beetlejuice
Are we doing that
Are we really doing
Music Factory
Haha
Beetlejuice
Was there a 5 Seconds
Because I heard a difference
Sit in the sound I think there might have been
No I don't think so
I don't I don't think so tough to tell even if you watched
The video because there's overlay of Hangout
I got really excited there because I was like oh my God
Alex is doing a
A goddamn sci-fi speech over
Dramatic music
I'm going to end this year I've been terrible this whole year but the whole year to go out on top as well I am going to have ambition
Show you guys what I can do
And I went and I found the video and I was like no this is just a meme
Someone in the engineering room or like a producer is just playing a meme that has audio
It's from the movie The Thing
If someone has just replaced like
Not just written a n a
Brilliance
Computer analysis c-43
But I still thought it
Yeah
I wish I was
I wish the right did
Own creative
You know they're just so goddamn creative
Text Dom
I'm sure it was count dankula or whatever the f*** allocated
I just died when I was listening to it what I got away from it
Was so much more disappointing when I realized it was just a meme
Yeah I really thought so too I thought it was a good choice of music to play Vines Almanac creepy speech
Please sing is one of the top 10 horror movies of all time
7 lb goose
It hasn't he had to realize into otherwise they would have been such a long pause right
You realized instantly that is not how he say that's not how you say it
I don't think so I thought he was at nothing else has ran out of gas
Apparently
Top story
People dying
From the coronavirus facts
Covid-19 vaccine
What is in the old details
By the way
Israel deaths in
Switzerland esdeath death
From the new
Genetic tag hour
Beto Cuevas
Dumpster taking it
Couple hours
So I'm not sure if it's supposed but there is an article on his website at least the tells you what
He's talking about about the Israel
And Switzerland
The vaccine person in Israel
It was a 75 year-old man who had cancer and a history of heart attack
Doctors believe that though he died shortly after receiving the vaccine
Heart attack
If it killed him was unrelated to vaccinate
I'm certain that that
Assumption the doctors have a something that's going to be examined
And I'll go ahead and listen to doctors about issues like this not weirdos who ramble over 80s Sci-Fi movies
Gazelle dumb pills
That was a real
That one's that is it that requires a bit more of a Titanic intellect
To to get to the bottom
Responsibility
Give me a little bit more than a couple of stray cases
Of people
Have conditions that could have
Not been related to the vaccine
How many doses of the vaccine worldwide have we got out so far
Okay well then
How many dogs do a little better if he does not
As you may recall a little while back
Someone got canned over to Infowars I believe a lot of
Goodnight
Is he back
Still on the lamb
Doing his show on periscope
Which I can't imagine
Ever
That's where we are so close
Periscope close a couple of times to see if he's talkingshit and then I just can't you
Can't pull the trigger
He was fired
Made
A pronouncement
And that was
Who the f*** else do you have there
Harrison Smith
B h
The hours the David I was on
So he's going to have Harrison Smith house be ours the David Knight was
Journal hosted by
College
Transmission
Of the year
2020 what year
Like to get your take on
What you think coming in the new year and what your resolutions are in the New Year
What you think our focus should be in the new year
Great question
Reading
Good Focus
Tell me a good start
Get an hour away from your recording studio at Alta
That would be mighty tower away from everywhere
Harrison an hour away to
Sam Smith being gay
Uninteresting bump on a log basically the equivalent of a cardboard cutout of a
But again
What American journalist
Trying to be
Is like a call-in show with a
Completely neutral host
Is probably the only person
Who you might be able to like he's so boring he fits that role upgrade
Terms of boring a boring am from David Knight
Going to the plaza M we're still at zero but it
0.2
0.0 American journal page
Video cuz I was thinking about
Like seeing if Alex have been hosting it and I saw it was Harrison
Talking to fish in this well
But I did notice
It's a little bit
In your face
Betamerica
Journals initials are the same as Alex Jones
AJ
I didn't realize it till I went to the website I saw those Graphics I was like this is a little bit of
A little bit much
Put your name on the building
So we got we got some people dying of covid in the last week
Some celebrities
Sansom high-profile people
Sure and these are people that Alex needs to push back off
Whatever well Lu Pueblo
Surgery on Eminem
Read the fine print but they say he died of a heart attack
Balcony something year-old
Dawn Wells of Marianne
Gilligan's Island
Covid-19
Complication
Dumbass Alex Jones probably thought I was a documentary
We've all been on that island for a long time
Nice
They're all ungrateful and it wouldn't have been there if it weren't for that boat in the first place
So Alex is really playing fast and loose with the details of these situation
Circular day without of Luca Light low
Because he knows it's really bad
And stories like this really hard for him to spin
Basically just deny the reality of the primary strategy
Buttload been elected
Did the congress representative 5th
African Louisiana but before he could be sworn in he died
At the age of 41 from covid-19
The way I was presenting the story it sounds like
Just happened to have covid related
Quote surgery
Kevin died of a heart attack in that surgery but that is not what happened
He entered Monroe hospital on December 19th because of covid
Any condition deteriorated quickly lead to him entering the I see you on December
23rd
There he suffered a heart attack that quote
What's refractory to all resuscitation efforts
According to dr. GE ghali
The New Orleans Times-Picayune reported quote
Ask Dad what LO had any underlying condition
That would have made his death more likely
Gally said in a text message
Quote none
All covid related
Alex is lying to his audience about this case to make them
Belt less likely to take covid-19 seriously
That's bad
Yeah it's for Dawn Wells you better keep her name out of his mouth
She was a great woman which I'm basically saying mostly because you was an alumnus
Stephens College
Which is in my hometown of Columbia Missouri
Regularly and speak with Theatre students there
And everyone I knew you'd met her and spent time with her really gave me the impression
She cared a lot
About being able
How to get whatever she cooked
Three students
But I always found really admirable
I've always I've grown up with a with a deep appreciation
Amber Dawn Wells
Both as like someone who'd like to Gilligan's Island as a kid and someone
Who
Was tertiarily aware of
She was like
Decency as an adult
Years old from all accounts
Including a video she posted around Christmas she was in really good health
Off until she got covid-19
Which point things went downhill fast
From the details that are available it does not seem outlandish to ascribe her death to covid
These are two recent deaths that are high-profile and very emotionally resonant so it's critical and important for Alex
To time to deny the reality of these debts to his audience
Luke letlow was only 41 years old and he just been elect
Message receipt in Congress
Get his life ahead of
Snatched away by covid
On the other side Dawn Wells was a sweetheart for most of the day the audience
The further use
The person that they had a crush on when they were children
Future her passing is a possibility of being like a motion Ali effect
Thing to them in a way they could be unpredictable
Got to pretend that all this is bulshit
Yeah I mean it
How do humans Act
This despicable
Jennifer wunder
Like what
But you know when that Whitney says that you can look into the abyss that old meet your
When you can look into the abyss
That you know the m
The character and then the abyss looks back
You don't deny a pandemic is not difference
Is that difference
I don't know there's a small part of me that I think
Suspected Alex realizes like I can't go back
It's too I've already gone too far down this road no matter what I have to
To commit to this
Is going back look
So dumb what happens if I say
Whoops fear I've got like what is a 1060 been like you know what
I was wrong about 9/11
What kind of a career could he possibly have you spent so much time insisting 9/11 was an inside job and all this
If you did that now or at any point like
Do you know what
We got to take over real seriously guys
You're not assigned to slavery
You should get the vaccine double back
It's just so weird you know cuz you when you look at the history of capitalism and you see how many times people have had the choice between
Continuing to make money
We're doing the responsible thing and saving lives
It's always been saving lives
Capitalism that's what I've always
I wonder I mean like
You know you're putting it in terms of like
Making money
His whole
Career
Torpedo
Already on the way to that happening Slowly by 1000
Some Cuts mostly are in the shape of a
It would be a disaster for him
Consolidate like a lot of like
He probably would like
To be his leg
Yeah I just
I just
Don't know how you could be in his situation and not
See the writing on the wall and
Secret
Control how you
You go out
You know narcissism mother
I wish I could argue with that but that's
It's one hundred percent correct nevermind
It's just the feelings of like and confirm my ennui
I think about how many times he's been like back against
The wall and been able to wiggle out of thing
You can't like
Something this big
You can't really do that
Like a duck
What when you're
Actively calling for the overthrowing of
Election
And
Denying
Large
He'll pandemic killing thousands of people today
Like you can't just be like whoop
I buy West on that one
Yeah and we
At this point you have
To reframe it in the in
Almost borderline
This is
Ultimate
Expression of class Warfare
Poor people are dying it rates
Infinitely higher
That's what this is like that we can't even talk about it.
Alex to try and approach it would have the air of populism
I certainly
Oh well but they do want the poor to Daiso
So you're saying like denying
Pandemic is really monstrous and how do people do that
I think you're selling Alex or he can be worse
Arresting people now
They go into the empty Hospital someone be very very clear
You need to go show the parking lot empty
You need to show the receiving area Fe that shoot a time-lapse
Did I tell you to leave leave
We've got multiple videos of people being arrested in the US
And the UK
When I go to the hospital
Privacy
I know it is certainly not
Is referring to I don't know what
United States person he's talking about but there's definitely a person in the UK
I need Debbie here
Text Suzanne anti lockdown protesters showed up at the hospital and recorded people
Forgive me in advance
Gloucester Shire
Royal Hospital
She got arrested for that video
From now on I'm just mispronouncing places
Carter
2021 is the year of me leaning YouTube
Place names
Hey come on the UK won't even be the UK you won't even need to remember how to pronounce United Kingdom it's going to be over
Oh yeah she was videotaping patient
So we're waiting to see doctors.
Which is a serious breach of confidentiality and privacy
This is the case that I was referring to so when he says that he doesn't think
The doing what that person is doing is a violation of Hippo he is
Absolutely wrong
The person seeking Medical Care
He better like
Like seriously hope people don't follow through with that
And yell infowars.com in the video cuz if they do I would be in trouble
People attribute their crimes to infowars.com
Money for people who yell stuff at rally is gone.
He doesn't think are illegal but probably are Erv bombers screamed out
Bill Clinton was a rapist before the RV exploded I think we have a little bit more of a
So
Alex gets back to talk
Going about demons
Sure
Consilium
Demon face
How to run to
Killer level demon that's about as bad as they are
Satan
Call Milo open Damon look at him
Open demon
Open
They've got the look
They got the look
Is that
Is that a term that I don't know open demons
Even though you know it's a
It's hard around
You know anywhere from like
And that 10 to 15 you're going to have to come out as a demon to your parents and it's going to be brutal.
Get to go to demon
I kind of enjoyed Alex's
Continuing
Insistence that he can see demons in people
If taken not as a
The joke it's really scary
It implies something deeply Disturbed what's the look
I don't know
Whatever Alex doesn't like
Have to do something to do with political beliefs
Political beliefs
Can change the way you look okay that makes sense
A lot clearer to me
Over that because he does save the people without discernment to camps
Discernment that word
Speaking of discernment
Sure Alex has it
Bucket loads
Show me go back to Robert are the rest your calls with the big news
In Georgia what you should have done
Those are sitting in the same thing
Same fraud again and if we let him do it they'll do it again
Alex hasn't gotten the memo to ixnay on the Lynnwood
Even beyond that bring up Lynnwood by name
I think it's a bad idea I think it's good for anybody
I would say no
Everyone
Stop mentioning Sidney Powell
We stopped
We don't want to talk about Krakens anymore I don't look good
Don't like how it seems like everybody can get away with
Just kind of like
Letting the detritus fall off the back of the ship
You know I hate texting me Powell can just
Bee drone that she has The Boat Leaves and Trump and everybody on the boat or fine
No she should take the boat down with her
It seems like
Cause and effect
Would lead to that
Hey I don't know constantly surprised
Throw city power off the boat were like well the boats Finance
Electrician debate on that boat
Maybe that makes more sense
Speaking about SWAT you know a lot about
Alex
No
Well yes
Woodmore
Actually
Guess how many boats are hutan
Group that would have a lot of
May not have eggs
A group that may not have existed
What happened
Glycocalyx definitely.
I got nothing
Alright
Is the population of the planet
Sure
Machine
Snoo
Preacher
Now that wasn't going to work I don't know
Bible says they're going to try to do it instead of
Does the bible say that
That's what happened with Atlantis I believe the Disney movie Atlantis
Even the Disney movie say that like the elites were trying to become robot Immortals
Or whatever like they were already robot Immortals in the Disney movie
Okay yeah
Maybe I mean
There's some Assassin's Creed in here I think with Michael j.fox
I just a guy just think that's
That's just true
Alex
Is broker in prison one day
Finally get to
I pick up the phone across from the plexiglass or no
You got your little prison
Clan of your other half I want to know
Do you think Atlantis is real
We had a lot of talk about only
Only f****** question
Oh yeah we talked about this bunch I love Atlanta
That's all you love I think it's a wonder
Because I don't have that time growing up in the island
The call of the island so strong
If you will
I would
Never
Argue that it
I love
Thinking about it I like the ideas I like a lot of the
Themes that have come from it sure
What would you think it was
Worried
Santorini
Santorini that's where I don't know
I do a lot of people say a lot of different things
I think it's
I think most people assume that they meant the Mediterranean in the beginning and then everybody the world got bigger and they're like oh that's
It's not going to look good so it's probably over by the plateau of Leng
From lovecraft's dream cycle
Alex in the past
Has asserted
That
Did the Trump
What are the kids
Trump's kids
Yeah after Alex
To investigate Dominion
And Alex
Play uncover for SEC filings
State of China
Had given Dominion
Four hundred million dollars or something along those lines
Yes they did say they discovered
We've talked about this already on a past episode but spoiler alert that was a qanon posts
That's Alex I found
And you taking credit for
He's still claiming
Did Trump's Untold Hellyeah
What crazy is the White House
By one of the Trump Sons
Arizona they said
Get the money
And so I went and hired a company
3 weeks
LLC
In
And the 400 million on October 7th
This year
Bye
Communist Party
So yeah
Not given up on that narrative
It's just sad to look at because I think what what's
The Dominion and the doc
Documents and stuff
Thompson sent me on a mission
What
What is satyr about this in his chest out about a thing that
Really didn't happen
Bored
No
So you take some number of calls on the show I will give it up
Alex
On this rock
For winning the bronze at the Nagano Olympics
Which you also totally did yes
He set out to take more calls and hitch
I don't know if they fix the phone lines are is coincidence
But there weren't any big f*** ups
Send calls
Like it actually worked kind of Patrol
Largely boring
This one guy
Does Colin
I want to talk about handsome
Sanitizer
This here for that conversation I would like to hand sanitizer conversations
Who's me out because
This is just a clip of like why does Alex ask people questions
Hand sanitizers
Matthew citrate New superbug Scientist warrant
Lowers your fertility
Explain that
Well what happens is it messes up your hormones
Because of the
Antibacterial
Good bacteria is on your body
Actually heals you
And it's actually
This is bacteria
And Bill Gates knows that studies that he loves you though
I don't know why you didn't weird at all I don't know why he asks people questions immediately interrupted
I mean that was a terrible answer that deserved interrupting
I don't disagree
So Alex is operating there at the end of old disproven scientific
In 2016 researchers examined the previously accepted ideas about the ratio of human cells to bacteria in the body
Anytime there's a serious lack of backing
For what it been up to that point
Considered conventional thinking
Previously was accepted that is possible that microorganisms outnumbered human cells 12:50 in our body
These researchers were able to trace this back solely to an estimate from a 1972 paper
An American journalist
Clinical nutrition
Examining assumptions made back then and taking the more scientific
These researchers arrived at a percentage of
3% of your body weight is back
Materia
In terms of pure numbers
They found the person approximately 1 to 1 ratio
Of bacteria human cells
In most adult bodies but it's still only
3% of your house waiting for you to be like
Sit back to Pliny the Elder and also it turns on Rapids
We we learned a lot today this is just stupid or Alex
Just trying to scare his audience and sound
I'm smart there's definitely reasons why people shouldn't over do it without my back to bacterial hand soap
Sanitizer
Just for the sake of
Get off you don't want to
Liquid was he never take antibiotic
Never
Unwise
Don't like people who live people like this shouldn't be allowed to enjoy the benefits of the future
If you're telling me that hand sanitizer did then you can't have anything
You can't have any type biotic
You can have
Probiotics you can't have your pills you can't have any of this s***
Because you read all things are the same
Yeah I can't eat yogurt
So
I think I ought to be fine with it for now maybe not
It's tough to say
Although
I would like
Can just slowly be eaten alive by a foot fungus that would be in
That could never happen
He takes his vitamins
It's good to washer
You just because some people might have some bacteria that your body doesn't like
With your wife or people you know and I'll see we all make each other stronger
More bacteria is better God bless you
You have all the vitamins and minerals you need
Communicable diseases
Replicate
Bacteria can take over if you're healthy
Wow
Irresponsible you can pray out disease
Christ
Prayer and vitamins
Bulleya
I hate
Boys out of the park with science
On this episode
Pigweed
Why do you think that
How can you say that out loud
It's not true it is not
True
Just Dance
We're actually more genetically similar to rats
And pigs than the thing that we literally directly evolved
We're more similar to stick
The New York weather
Fine whatever
We are shockingly close to a lot of animals
Because there are a lot of
Things that are in
Common with us an animal animal
We are here.
It's diagonal common ancestor way way way way way back and a lot of those.
About 4,000
A lot of booze the DNA a lot of it does the same thing
But then certain mutations and then such can then
What's more survivable in any given environment within kind of win out over time
Those jeans would continue to propagate
Until the cycle happens all over again and over and over and over again for billions of years right then
So Alex is talking to this caller another color and
It turns out that
I think the globalist have another plan
That we didn't know about it might be playing these I don't know what plan this is anymore
In their plan is The Hunger Games
People see that
Natural Woman
Talking about the
Actually
Predictive programming
Will plan that you and one
Hunger Games Mario
Biological diversity assessment
Report put out in the late 70s
2.0
In that it says
Bring back
Games
Olympics
System
Rural areas that have no technology or they live in the Smart City
We control
Human sacrifice
At these games
Floating fortresses
With you and Truth everyone will be disarmed
Mobile mobile
Horses
Captain America will be delivered
I would say I have the Winter Soldier
F****** tired of the globalist having so many plans
Pick one and stick to it God damn
This is why they're ten years behind. Just finished one
A weird dad Mohave every every week There's a new thing you doesn't the garage
Take me back when I was trying to write short stories like I did
F*** it I'm done
Yeah hey girl. How your plan was orderly
Killing off of people within a few years
And then if Alex is too good at his job than they're playing with a supervisor that's not very good
What size fun for the globalist
They want to bring about
The Hunger Game
Right
Which doesn't seem like
Extermination
It seems like
A situation where people are living
Destitution
Well the elite
Slither opulently
And then people kill for entertainment
Movies but I did see Battle Royale
So
Like to figure it's the same thing
Slightly more story Maybe
I don't know I would say
Why doesn't he ever develop like I want him to just really dig into the weeds and start doing what I like.
Give me this popular bulshit that's written for young adults
Give me hard sci-fi tell me that it's going to be like a Heinlein book order
Or f******
Worried about childhood
That's what it's all about Neal Stephenson now
That's 2023 she's got a Rebrand
Get some sci-fi helicopter where I'm at
Amy needs to find a new test
I'm so sick and tired of this s***
Yeah it's just
Just like I want a coherent
Like
Narrative
Something
The bad guys are supposed to be working
On the behalf of the fuc
Walking devil
He's not a new character
Whom you can see
Yeah you can see him open.
If they're open they're open
Close demons difference
Do rabbits talk
I would say
I'm studying on 27 years the plan shouldn't keep change
Here's the bottom line I'm playing games here are playing Hunger Games
David Icke talks about The Hunger Games stuff all the time
Alex is just ripping off David I cuz he's really into
Damn right now
But yeah it's more annoying
In terms of like
I can't even I can't even trust Alex
Be pretending
Serious about
Yeah
It's just
This is where I'm at like
Oh yeah sure okay
I bet ya
Reading the first third of a new novel every week
And never finishing it and it's
Infuriating
It's be infuriating
It's kind of scary scary like this
Manno razor years
Lock up your wife and children now
DJ right. Someone asked you right now
What do you do about it
Living on your knees on your feet
No it's all been planned A Center once Center twice
Over the wall we all left our own
PCS down
And make no mistake
The Rothschilds and Rockefellers the Bill Gates's in the world they will go into the fire as well
And their destruction be the most painful
They will be Giants
Every man and every woman
Will be
Forced to kneel in front of God
I just
I find myself like
While I'm sitting here not being able to take Alex seriously about just about anything he's saying
Performative
Soaring Heights song lyrics
But it's also in the context of his show basically terrorist
People like ramped-up if you've been dying anyway
Pair that with
Forced religious imagery it's like
I don't
I can't stand the stuff like
I don't think I've ever
Encountered in my life a time when like
Religiosity match
With
Like open violence
Is it good
Yeah
Historically just going back through my Rolodex
Second Crusade that was no that was a good one
Fiskars and didn't go well
No not usually bad
Yeah
You can have to go to that
I know this is performative and I know that Alex
He doesn't even
He's
You think this is a joke
Yeah like he's f****** with his audience
Like
And I can tell because like listen to this
President
Pretender Electric
Joe Biden
But he's a nobody
He will be brought low
He will be broken
He will
The Almighty
God will tell him the door is closed
You are dumb as hell
Cool then leave them alone till then
All right but nobody knows he's damned to hell
Cool
He just wants to take you where they
Your lucky stars
Everyday that you're not
Joe Biden
Bill Gates
How many of these people
Prepared for their own annihilation
They're just trying to drag us down below
Think about your phone calls here
Alright I'm really worried about the food goes up and died 6:40 a.m.
Today is going to burn in the fires of hell
Ginger really care about this but it's all an act
And get you excited
Joe Biden burning in hell
Anyways what are we up to
Aerosmith coming to the Pavilion
Yeah this is so stupid
What do you think
He's a good reason to overthrow the
Like taxation without representation is one from American history
Thursdays are usually pretty rough
You just got to take a nap at work
In terms of Labor he's a good one sure got pretty sure Haiti had the right idea
I would I would say to that
It doesn't both better
Write this caller is going
Okay
This color wants to overthrow the federal government
Small
And I really just called you because we're just getting some
Sick and tired of the man
I had to go to my girlfriend's crisp
Play Celebration with mask on
60 away from everybody
This area is ready
To not have
The federal government anymore everyone
Mask off
Bacterial pneumonia
Privilege trimana just because they think they're nurses
They think they know everything
You do most of the nurses
Play must be really young nurses
One is her grandma and one of them is like
30 year old woman I don't know they're both pretty liberal they both
They're making everybody
Alex's realized like oh no
I've set out this talking point that all the nurses are against
The vaccine for these two nurses are 48
Be young oh wait they're not young though they must be really liberal because that's how they wanted
Express their power
Don't go to the Christmas party
Psychic it's like you go to that side you're going to like this
Going to lose
F*** off man
And in order to
To trick you from realizing that they've been wrong about a bunch of things Natalie this Mentalist
We'll switch
Topix Oakland
Is in gender roles
I'm not putting women down
Some women
Marsh
Smartest man they are
4%
Men don't bow with my baby domesticated slug
But their wives and girlfriends work for
And and women haven't talked to comply with the sister
Bonded by women
This is the Bible says will happen in the end times
Men's fall
We're not
L
Holyshit
While
Wild stuff
Omigod omigod
We believe that
That's insane
That's an insane thing you just said you slapped in the face that's outrageous
Bye
Leading
Are f****** everything up but it's not their fault
Men should put them in their place
Just a just a just wait just come out and be like I don't think we should have given the right to vote just say it
I would bet that you would think that's creeping communism or he around
Why would you give women the right to vote they're just going to vote the way their husbands do
Duh you just going to double all
Listing boats already don't even need to worry about it
So it was shocking
Everybody
Women's Health
We have one last call are here on this New Year's Eve
Interesting idea about what
To do
On the six
Cuz I doing this rally right
Down in DC has got a novel idea
March on DC or the occupation of
DC
I think that you I'm going to talk to all
Cajun Navy and all these
People that did
Parade
For the past
324 mud
We need to have every single one of those people
Plug up
The Potomac
Because you know everything outside
Like and I can set out some Facebook
The Facebook post going to Cajun Navy
Yes
I am fine with these plans these are my favorite plan
Pick something stupid
And stick to it
Like it's just going to inconvenience you guys each other
Yes
Somebody's going to accuse a boat big antifa everybody's going to drown
Stupid
I don't like being taken over by the dumbest people on the planet they had this plan is too complicated for y'all
It's unfortunate that I want to like
Almost parental wage
And here's how you overthrow the government guys without the Terrible
So I would say that their New Year's Eve day show and
The New Year's Day show themselves
Really
Special there's not really a feeling of like new beginnings
No does ask
On 31st
For people to call in and say they're there their New Year's resolutions
I'm sure not much meaningful s*** there but
Overthrow the government
So we get to the first
Another show
It's not like a New Year's show
Except
An amazing roster of guests
And Alec realizing
It's probably going to be a possum
Select
Exclusive information
What major explosive information
Since the election
President-trump
Across the country
You got to stop saying that it's better than other areas
Basalt
Radar then
Jerry West
We can really give you the serious pass
But it is a narrowing window
Indiana Jones
Raiders of Lost Ark Wiki rolls under
The wall
Lower down and closes
Races through and grabs a sweater
I mean
Robin Hood shot
Arrow and splitting
As a little break
A little unnecessarily brag
I'm sorry for screaming but that was just too much I was just too much I've heard
There is something nonsensical about him being like all right I'm going to come up with an example of it
Incredibly difficult thing
By the way I've got a bunch
The time so easily
God damn it I hate him so much
But how could someone
I've listened to him so you can do too much set
Forrest Gump your way I'm Robinhood to I've got bad news for Alec
It's about
Trump's agility
Peace Corps
Don't think he's going to be diving under any doors and a bullwhip
That stand thing that he does help him look like a weird f****** horse
I think you might get
He's not going to roll
So all this is probably
My second
Favorite thing on this this January 1st
Episode I will say what we end with
Fantastic
Be worth the episode on its own
I'm not talking about Rodger Stone
What's this
This was a
Little mod
Search for me in a way that I enjoy
But it's good
But it's a little
The social Engineers have noticed that most people
When they're part of a crime
When they're part of something corrupt
When they
When I get manipulated to doing
Something wrong
Don't say they're wrong
They decide to get even more delusional
And to sign on to even more excesses
And more extreme
Yeah
Examples of this
Do you have a mirror
There's one on phenomenon
Right in front of personal experience
Is you
No you
Ciabatta
You specific
Get online scams
Get us back out most popular
There's Lotsa
The Royal bloodline of Prince Abu
Wants to give you $1,000
He's got money locked up million to this Bank
But he is unable to get it out of whatever
If you'll just give him $1,000
You will be given $20,000
And when you
Give him the thousand
Yeah well he's ready to give you the more money but he needs 5,000 more
But now he's going to give you a half a million
And usually most people once they're giving 1000
They give
The larger amount
And then if you do
Pull up at your house
You guys have a scam
Royal Road
Affection graciously
Let's make a phone call
He will greatly thank you from Nigeria
And some people
$300,000 principal
50 million
DC and talk show host said I've been offered $100,000 by Nigerian
Are you joking
Part of this
And he said screw you you're just jealous I'm going to get all this money and then he actually got
As opposed to the other possibilities
I'm
Certain Alex
Has to be talkin about himself there's the only the only person who could be talking about it on Creative about like
Gcn radio host
His buddy Ted Anderson would hire a guy and have him
Yeah the host email scam
I don't know if I
Ever heard of anybody having a car pull up
And in person
Scammers show up
They know that that would probably be a sting it would be a bad idea
Is primarily scamming over long distance
Maybe even another country
This
This is this is a bad idea
I wouldn't do that if I were them
This is not this is
Isn't something that Escalade
X2 like
Let's do this in person
Because
There's no reason to you understand that that would be the only way that could work is if
First game of the scammers was possible where they're like holyshit we're going to get so much money out of this guy we got
How to show up at a
His place
Yes that would be the only
Yeah
I actually did some looking into this I read the page on the FBI's website about this scam like Aunt like
You're the warning signs and stuff
I read a couple other things I can't find any indication
It escalates to a guy showing up at your house
No that doesn't
It seems like a different
We should hire somebody to show up announcer just said Nigerian prince well
I got a
He does always a prince a boo boo and I know that that
Fields racist
It feels like that could just be a name he's making up
But he always uses that name very specific the name of
Well I mean isn't it from Aladdin
It's not the insult name that Jafar he calls him Prince Abu
Odesza
I didn't realize that I don't mean that in a long time
Yeah yeah
So then he
Great insults his name like this
Interesting
Easy for me
I don't know a long time
Makes sense that something would come from a movie
All right we've we've sorted this out
Alex is almost certainly been
The scam by that
I don't know about the
The car though
That seems that seems like you might have just dropped
His embellish
Kind of Storytelling style but everything else seems very suspiciously at
So this vaccine
You know what it is
The mark of the beast
This is the whole world government agenda
This is the mark of the beast is it the tracking system
This is it
And yes crop has failed
Critical juncture
Nicholas you
He has gone long
Cuz I made that up
Trump won the election the Democrats are trying to steal it they want him out of the way
Because Joe Biden is 509 Force
Okay
Yeah all that stuff about like Trump is putting out the Pfizer vaccine
Bill Gates making all that stuff up
The way to find a way to support Trump even though he was in favor of the vaccine
That I can really threat
The needle and now I look like an idiot so I pretend I never said that but
I do have to I mean my callers do know that I said the drop was trying to play 3D chess or 4D chess with the vaccine
So now I got to be like all well Trump is wrong on this one so he gave us the mark of the
I love it
Sewed up
I just love how stupid it is
Literally literally immediately after he's talking about how people will double down it rather than admit
They got, he's literally doing
Except he called himself
He is both the recipient and the center of the United State of email
You know which also wouldn't surprise me too much of that was true in real life as well metaphorically or literally
Damn email
Hey I think that
Find
Difficult to understand what
You gain by having
When Trump in office
If Trump being in office
Still facilitated the rise of the Dead
The goal is averting the mark of the beast
Ushered everyone into and did not protect you from
The mark of the beast or whatever
He sucks and you shouldn't support him either
That would make sense
I think
Which I think if I was in government I would officially named something the mark of the beast
Just cuz I'm so sick of everything being the mark of the beast
Oh yeah we'll be stacked or something like hey
Guess what this is your lucky day Christian
This is the mark of the beast like a bill to name a library or something
And then then we wouldn't have to deal with all this while their backs
Well the barcodes in the back of a while your phone's in mind I'm sick of it
I think he's just sort of like yeah let's do
Just a call ezcontacts
Whatever
To deal with
This guy is terrified
I'll let you know
Need to call in a
Jason from Germany
I had to get my family out of Germany
Trump Israel
5 years
Yes sir
Offend
Asian
Brought my family here
State of Oregon
I loved and wanted to put down roots in
You know it didn't work
Appears to be
Become
Chinese interests more than anything else
Wow dude you are
F****** up your whole life
This guy had to flee Germany because apparently the Muslims
To the West Coast only defined under Chinese control
I can't catch a break this is our modern-day odys
That is what we're dealing with
Only to find that his wife has left him
I wish I honestly also kept thinking while I was listening to this and I don't know
Maybe it's just the mood I'm in
Keep thinking
Co-op
Yeah buddy
Grow the f******
Well
It's it's just too much LARPing
It's all larva
It's so it's so like
I get it
Real life
Are often boring
It's repetitive
Not much is going on
Especially now
But you can't live like you're in a fuk
Talking spy movie
And the Muslims are invading Germany
Come on man
Think a certain amount of it is probably motivated by people recognized
Difficult
The time in history this is
How relatively easy some people have it
And Eden
Tunak
Feel the guilt
Of that
You take that you said have transformed it into
Well obviously the Chinese run the West Coast
And I better run away from the Chinese occupied territory
Right cuz that's the way it that's the way you can
Can experience only
We actually paying the
It's so many other people are living at
Without having to
Actually face it
Or if wheel like you're sharing
Pain with people who you actively
Are told to hate
Recognize that you are a
Apart of
The system that
Maintains that status
So Alex takes another call in
This guy is like really really layered it out there with Infowars all about
Peninsula lost object
You would be one of the
Preachers if you could just
Maybe like I don't know what day you do a time but maybe once
What's a week once a month
But you were the
Finally
Jesus
It was first
But I did realize that
You know for we wrestle not
Flesh and blood
Against
Powers
You know how it go
You know
Yeah this is the second call Within These two days I didn't even cut the first one cuz it was just going to like
That's just another person saying that I was brought into
The god
Today's calling in being like
You through politics
You Trojan Horse
Religion to me
And that's what I mean
Looking people want
How to be religious like I like I always try and I'm not against religion
I find this to be a fraud
I find this to be a con
That Alex is doing
Where it
It's Disick
Extremist
Conversion of Christianity
Maybe in quotes
That you can arrive to buy way of
Extreme right-wing politics
Do you know what
It's not even really religion
Apollotek
Yep but it has Weaver
And the Zeal
Of of religiosity
All of your political enemies are demon
Yeah you can see it
Could you have discernment now
Alright it's it's
To staged
Charade religion is the escalation of political
Violence in the in that sense of like
Oh my Purp
So much bigger you know I used to be
Politically active where I wanted to
Affect the
The country in the government and the way my city was run
But now I'm not just affecting
That I mean
Checking the world and I'm not just affecting the world I'm in virtual world
That is a path that can go that is not what religion
It's the pits
The path that Alex
Thrives on
Really it's really a bummer
Yeah
Disney's people
Just like living in a
Completely different world than everyone else
This guy had to flee Germany because the Muslims invaded
And the Chinese are running the West
No Prosperity Gospel preachers should be immediately arrested and imprisoned for life
Every part of that
Listen to this Alex is like
This is the kind of reality that Alex
Wants to live in and wants to perpetuate for his audience
I told you 16 years ago that a friend of mine is a big movie producer
Was talking to James Cameron
Decision was made the future there won't even be movies anymore
New Zealand for the end of the world
Write it off as an ocean Oceanic
Researcher but really
I've got a fleet of ships
Very many population operation
1560 years ago
Now he admits basically all day
What does basically mean in Mexican
So if I understand this correctly
Movie producer
Talking James Cameron James Cameron
Hey remember Titanic
And he was like yes I do
We're going to watch it in the Holograms
And he was like that sounds cool I'm a like
Psych
The movies aren't even going to exist
So the movie producer
Realizing that he doesn't have a job later on in life was like oh obviously what I'll do
Is scam New Zealand tax system peeps
Telling people you're going to put out those avatars people even though there will be no movie
Call me what elements of that has been
Basically admitted to
I don't know
Spy Who
James Cameron is incredibly committed to
Do the bed cuz he put out that too
Titanic the hunt for the Titanic
Stupid
This is the Detachment from reality and it like this stupid s***
Alex
But that
It's mixed up with this religious verb
It gets people
To think
He's bringing them to some kind of a real spirituality but it's not
Go to bed. Video CD
Middle Ages
800 year old
Carving of the devil eating a child
Now what do you see in the Space Needle
Now what do you see at the Olympics
Now what do you see for real
Do you see coming with an mRNA vaccine
Death sacrifice of your genetics
Sacrifice of your fertility
Strawberry takeover
Your body
In a giant genetic ritual
With what they
Full clone genomes of jellyfish
Human
Injected
Taking over
Every cell in your body
Cell by cell
A couple segments
Go back to your call
Then Robert Barnes is coming up
This is not a game
Fightback what God gave us vitamin D3 wintersun in stock
The
You listen to that minute
It's just nonsense
Alex
I just want to thank you
Bringing me to Christ
After you told me there was an 800 year old statue
About the devil eating a child huh and then I looked at what was happening
At the Space Needle at the Space Needle
And at the Olympics
And why not Denver's airport
Torture
Blucifer
I came to
Christ
And by that I mean I bought wintersun
Because they are on sale
Yeah that was what I meant
The religion of Alex's
Is dumb pills
Highway Rogers
Is on
Oh yeah Cameron's movie after the Avatar sequel where North Korea.
Dramatic
Flyover the main drop the balance off
Wish I was sorry Tom Hanks
Alex first of all happy New Year
Be a better year than 2020 although 2020 certainly had its highlights it was
Not only the year in which I was
Did framed really in a soviet-style show trial also the year in which through the mercy of God
The president gave me first a commutation that a
Oh and unconditional
Here here is really what I take offense
Rodger should be furious
At Trump pardon
No no
Because
Because now he doesn't have to spend all that money
Proving that he was innocent of being toxic though
It's good thing that he doesn't have to
He's going to give back all the money that people donated
Based on the
Premise
From around
The time of that conversation about a commutation
Rodger was explicitly
He didn't want a pardon
Because he had so much evidence that he could prove that you would set up
He was going to be the one who's going to be the champion fighting to
Expose the Deep
Deep State corruption
That only he could because he had the standing busy at all the evidence that he was innocent who's Olga
Going to come out in court
Don't pardon me
I'm just
Afraid to go to prison
Because there's a lot of covid
19 of those prisons and I'm an old man I've been existing
Conditions need to commute my sentence I can survive
To appeal course
But now of course I can
F*** you man
The whole story is is gone now
I think
If I were the judge over the judge that gave Rodger Stone so many
Ifucking Chan
And then I heard that
I would
Think that every decision that I had ever made up to that point was a bad one now listen to me
If I were somebody who listen
The Infowars
Believe this s***
I would be mad about this
I will be mad I be like a Rodger
Number one
You were going to be the one
Who was Gunn
How to get
Peter strzok
Thrown in prison or whatever nobody wants
To be the first
I'm not an info Warrior I was at I'm not the tip of the spear Dan
I think you said
Okay so I said I would but I don't want to
Begging for money from everybody for his legal defense so he could be there in
Expose the Deep state if I believe that
Deep state was something real that was an imminent threat and was going to kill my family
I'd probably be pretty
Pissed off that Rodger accepted apart in
Or even like
Some kind of a mechanic for rejecting a pardon
Like if you speak it right now
I believe there is I believe you can reject
He wouldn't need to cuz he could
Just tell Trump
Don't pardon me
You could actually do that instead of that publicly
I will be so mad at him
I can't believe these people let these people get away with
I can
Well yeah I guess I can't do but it's still in. You can get away with this
Is
Herself and that you that it seems almost not
It's almost
Expect
Mitchell get away with it
Swear to God if they were
They should be smirking
All the time it has snowed in the area Harrison Ford
Should play the parts of everyone and Infowars
Would that dumb smirk on his face every time he says anything because if you listen to this your f******
Harrison Ford
Harrison Smith
Turn off my plane
So Alex is going to be see this rally
Just a separate reality that's being discussed
We're going to d.c.
Vicodin Romania or
Nin
Any other places
And showing our number to the dictatorship
Of the lab
Trying to steal the election
President
We do not want
Because we have the election our sides
We have the truth it's the left has finally
The conception of what's going on
Completely warped
Yeah there's just
There's I don't even know how to have a conversation
And with that
This is another one of those things
Kingswear
Where you like
I just
I just can't believe that this is still
It's like it's like those conversations it's like those debates
That you that we've talked about where it's like
You're just having the same conversation they had two thousand years ago break
Yeah you don't realize
These thoughts
The people had this conversation
While back
Had afterwards
Scholarly
Discussion about the same way this like
We've literally seen not just
This exact thing happened before
But this exactly happen
A couple weeks ago
It's not like this is in the long distant past where there's no way we could possibly learn from our history
This is a couple weeks
And it's only worse
I just don't
I I can't
I can't even
Fathom
And this song
It's violent propaganda that's infinite years old always the same s***
People still
Well I mean look
The truth is
That Alex is going to do this route
People have told him
That if he doesn't
Then maybe he could back on Facebook
ABC national news
I've had others from Fox call me
I've had Democrat Party lawyers call me whenever you like you
Theraplatform
Please don't do this to me see you're going to be in danger somebody might shoot you
Oh please don't leave a violent revolution
And really what they're doing is calling up and threatening me
So they're really concerned about the six Rodger
Got it the bag so much why are they doing this
I didn't
So an ABC News host called Alex Jones
Don't do this
We don't want
Violence
Into you
We're just how I've always introduce myself on any phone conversation and I just want to let you know we love you
I like I should tell you I'm a high-ranking globalist
I will get you back on Twitter
This rally we've only seen two of these in the past few weeks and nothing happened then either while something's happen
Not maybe not to the ovary O'Reilly hours
Conform
And also let's not get it twisted Alex's going
Going to show up
Somewhere it's a revolution
No no
What are the bad
Yeah we got two of the real bad boys here Rodger Stone
Phuc yea to the real bad boys
Bad Boys
Okay
Alright
Alright if we
Who's Will Smith
Send who's Martin Lawrence
I'm not sure but look
I will say Rodger lives up to his reputation as a bad bad boy
You know Alex I'm putting in
Sometimes 17 18 hour days and trying to
Finish my book
Which is
Rodger Stone did nothing wrong
My political
Persecution and the heist of the 2020 election
Real quick
That's an unwieldy title I would shorten that I like to go back to
The seventeenth-century title
On the existence of this and over that and on the course
Things that might be in over
Unwieldy
Love it
If I was not using brain Force Plus
There's no way
This is a great product
Nothing
Bad Boys how much is it getting paid
To say that
I might have suspected that he wasn't getting paid until he said I do not care
Hey
Dicey
Yeah that's what the bad boys do they work 17-hour days
Self-serving Facebook
And then she'll for Alex's product couple the bad boys, the real Rebels out there
It looks like bad boys
Rodger
Defining characteristics
Of bad boys
Is
That they defer to Authority
That
Exactly what they say
Any situation
I'm not second-guessing the president knighted states I don't know what he has up his sleeve
I do know this
Whatever it is
I will support him
1000%
Is the greatest president since Abraham Lincoln
Hey you're talking to a guy who hates Abraham Lincoln right now
Yeah so. I mean Lincoln might not be the best example
To use here saying people that might be a good example
It looked upon positively
No but
Alex and like
You can tell the people who stopped his Confederate royalties
Also
You're such a bad boy
Whatever Trump does I am I will never never be insubordinate even if he does the things
But I say he shouldn't do
Cuz
He got me out of that
F****** a******
Jesus we go f*** yourself Rodger
Valerie like really hard
Not really hard.
To come in
Gets better no
No now doesn't know although this will end quite well
But before that we got to get through the mire that is Robert Barnes
As a
Plan
He's a constitutional lawyer
So he can explain don't know if any of that
True but I haven't seen any evidence
Suggesting the Constitutional lawyer but you can
He was Wesley Snipes as lawyer
Because he knows accounts
Student is going to lay out for Alex the steps
That could happen
In order for Trump to get into office
Basically
It's just an elaborately ABS
Certainly complicated plan
Not going to happen
Jodi all of those are playbase
We can play in the
Question is what do house members and senators
When presented with argument and evidence about these individuals
Do they uphold
Constitutional election
Or do they contain
Do small election
More than
Vitamins up with fewer than 206
Electoral votes at the end
Process
Under the 12th Amendment
The election goes to the House of Representatives to vote
Not by individual members but B
State delegation
Tablet
Question was what is Senator join
That means he's vote
Take place
These hearings have to
To take place
And that gives
Is the president while Longshot
A shot
Do you have a car
Tatoosh only correct
What can we the people do
To put pressure
Obviously March what else
Chew your food
Heat during the breaks
She's a constitutional lawyer tried to tell you how the Constitution works at Rumpke
Steal this election
Eat a sandwich while he's there telling me this
This is
Is all just this
Elaborate
This route
So you got the objection
Right let's say Arizona is being
Did too and then
Somehow magically that objection
Electoral vote
Biden under the threshold the right now the house elect
Right oh God it's
It's
It sounds like qanon stuff
But you should know
But even though Alec
Has not gotten the memo about Lynnwood
Robert Barnes has
I need is not like what he's hearing
I think Linwood is doing a lot of damage to the
Chase
In Congress it will where he needs to be
House members and senators
I think the reason why the media is
Happy to let him go wild and why Twitter has
Is because they see them as
Helping Democrat
But in fact he's not
She's pursuing alligator
Cannot be proven at this stage or within this timeframe
Or allegations
Distract from the core issues that can be proved
So entertaining
Involved with a lot of the qanon types
Who believe a lot of stuff
Just has not been proven
And that
That's a key problem and then unfortunately Sidney Powell got
Entrapped by a lot of that
Trapped by a lot of that
What does that mean
Contacts that word counselor
I would say
That my new exhortation
For everyone is to always be carrying tomatoes with you
Case you see Robert
I'm Amazed by the turn of phrase that Sidney Powell was in
Trapped by qanon
Qanon
Is that a legally beating filter I don't know is that is that she get to catch a predator and with
I don't want to say that you believe dumb s***
Why don't you have a seat
Glaze out the scenario again
Yeah for Alex
Yes so if I understand correctly
Play yeah
It's possible that a Rube Goldberg machine
Might have been Act
Debated the idea lawsuit that will then suddenly roll down a at you one of those
Ducks that bends over and drinks water and Pops back up and then they'll be an overthrow of the government and
World is going to be there playing Constitution mousetrap
Gotcha
How that would how that would happen if
What two states
Not reach 270 electoral votes
Better uncontested
And does it have not yet
Certified
Then the remedy under the 12th and Men
Is
Go to the house
There is a
12th Amendment
Vice president
He can say
There's a contest
Involving too many states
So there's not enough
Candidate has more than 270 electoral votes
Do Under the 12th Amendment
Must vote now by
Delegation
And somehow
You have a ties
Probably wouldn't
The newly seeded house
Not the old house but
How's that would vote
Bi-State
And whoever gets
26 States
To vote for them
Went
I ordered
What's 25 + 23 + 2 or type
They went
The president has an Edgewood
The Georgia election also more important
Yes that's why they
That's why he
Pursuing it
He knows he needs
Those Republican Senators
To have a chance
To the house delegation
First place to get to the stupid Hail Mary nonsense who you're talking about
Oh this is why I like
That election is
Is important
To drop
Oh yeah that makes sense
This is not
Here's a here's why this stuff
Exist
Hey it's because
Does this make sense
When it's only white landowners who are allowed to vote so you can have all these conversations in Congress cuz you like
This is also the total number of people who are allowed to vote
Miss election
But wouldn't it but when everybody's allowed to vote
Okay
It sooner or later
This is going to have to happen
One side
Is going to have to accept
What they believe is in an undemocratic election
I wouldn't either way but we already did 2000
Exactly
So that's how it's going to go.
Neither was either the Democrats admit
Fine you can stay in office because you imagine something happened and we're just going to live with it or Republican
They're going to have to be like
Fine we're just fine with a nun democratically chosen president because
Quittin time are these people going to ever believe
That they that he's the
Except what they perceived actually undemocratic
Exactly. In their minds it's just as real as anything
So that mean
Humble Pie that will need to be eaten
Bye
Trump fans
Because otherwise
Or
Vallarta
Blown up knees
Like that old that'll be one way for us to eat Humble Pie
Here's the thing
Barnes has got this
Elaborate scenario wherein baby
Amendment where parents can just be like
Hey she doesn't look good let's
Steal Bob's interpretation of the 12th
What's the amendment
Is a little bit worried about that though
Because why
Kind of dictator ish
Alex Wood
The perception of being a dick.
Is there another way so they don't point
Overturn the election
People out there
To say we're going to have a
Watchers a big question
You should redo that's the international standard
Have to do that
Congress could do that
Congress could send another election day
And say that
In the contested presidential election
We're going to have election day on January 19th
Example
Cowardly
People in Congress
The way in Geneva
He was always open to that but he
Is original
Preferred that he be declared
The winner based on
Hedonist
Yeah that makes sense
Wild
It's like looking into a
Funhouse mirror
Nuts I would give anything for a Democratic party as strong and as conniving as what they
I would take
Single activist
Under the age of 20 over anybody in congress right now
That's the reality of it
They're pathetic
It's sad
It's
It's sad even so like
I mean like we can talk about that all day
I'm I'm
I'm much more interested in how this is being painted
Yeah they're talking about like
Do you know like the sensible Middle Ground is another election
Play JLo
We can just do another Alexa
As a favor to the Democrats we could do another election
What the
F*** how many how much
Attached is this
I don't know
I don't know I don't know how you could even take it
Seriously as a
Okay you want another election
What will need to happen for you to agree
That Biden
Just tell me just why are the parameters for another election if you had to write down
Exactly what you need
To accept the election
And then if it happens you have to shut the fuk up forever
Sorry I can't do that
Also on Stefan molyneux show with
Year
The problem for Trump is that he has a lack of that lies
And that they've all betrayed
I wonder why they would do that
The fundamental weakness
The present is hat
Throughout his four-year
Your tenure
Has been the lack of allies and key position
Random
And he's coming
To terms with the full Rec
Recognition of what that means
CiCi's McConnell
Recommended
I just betray him at every single
Mikado tricep
Betray him in the Senate on the
Upcoming
As he sees
What's happened with
The Republican governors in Arizona and Georgia
Undermining
So he now fully appreciate
Hate it but I think he undervalued it
Before
Any heads too few allies in the effect
But it's my eyes would have him
Periscoping every single day
Would have him doing you introducing
Trump TV now
And doing at least one hour update
It's every single night
Answering
Getting people proactive
Add he contracted
And some of this linsanity from Linwood and some of the other Q movements
Could not have
Diverted
Detentions
I don't know if it's a good idea or not but I will tell you I don't want to live in a world where the president is mood lighting
In the reality we live in I think it might be a smart idea I don't want to live there
We're talkin about you different things you're talking about effect
I'm talking about
That would be dark
I'm more mad at him taking linsanity away
Daddy's girl
Good things that have happened to the Knicks in the past
Hundred-year
Shame on you Barnes
5 Goodman
It's okay
I guess
They want Trump to have a media outlet that he's operating while he is
Power and
It should have been doing it while he was
Trying to be real
F***** up
You know it's not dystopian at all
Is if it was
Forced into our homes no matter what we did and it was always on time and you couldn't even turn the TV off if you wanted to
Buddy's suggested that on the other day. That reminds me of this
That they like to talk about all that all the time what was
Is it called
The the
Dictators
Dystopia he was always on that they're going to Willows
Mr. Toad's Wild Ride
So
You may recall the last time Alex went to DC spoke that Jericho
And
And of course the day you ran into Mike
Flint
Unfortunately video came out of this where Michael and looked at Alex like he was a weirdo
And then ran away
We have an update on that
Turn that my client called to apologize
I told the story of how this happened
Immediately
Because no one else was stepping up and the Magical cue group
Magical Intel Griptilian
I'm sorry about how it look like my next boyfriend
He's going to be there
Everybody together
Everybody's good
Everything's great
I was startled by you what I look like I was in the fridge
Normally normally I don't particularly care
Anytime they do there's like when reach
4 comments
This person said
The only time I want Michael Flynn on record as having
Lakeside yes or no
Are we going to draw the line on it
I don't know Jesus
Anyway I'd like to remind you before I play this clip that Robert Barnes at
The Constitutional lawyer are you sure
And just be the president in absentia constitutional
Constitution says
Oh no doubt about it to be at the
It has been too much
Focus at the top
You always spoke
We need to focus this used to be a bottom-up revolution if it's going to work
You're complaining that other people are focused
Isn't too much at the top of a make-believe second
President
That seems like a pretty harsh focus on the top
Are we just going to Exile him to an island for a while until he eventually returns to recapture his no
Empire
I like Island
That's too much
Send them to Atlantis all right
I promised you that we were going to end this episode on
And we will
Okay because there is a call
That comes in
That is huge
Talk to John in Wyoming John thanks for all the glad
Good morning Ali
He's alive
Sign of Life January 1st 2021 is on the first year of
The first day of the new year he's like I don't know a groundhog showing up in Madison its shadow
Old man house
He probably is going to lose in the middle of nowhere in Wyoming
Although he is really old people never call
Call is not very
Nothing at all but
It is worth celebrating the kids alive
Tennessee and back
And even calling in for like 15 16 Maybe
How long you been calling and John you haven't gotten on here
Me and I'll sense Little Orphan Annie
All right brother
I'll get you on with Harrison on the American Turtle giving him your name and number
/ 17
I was in college
First day I gave you the phone number
Old man house phone
I don't think I can do FaceTime on my rotary
Hold on I have to plug into the other operator and see if
She can handle that out
I'm sorry I can't I can't come on you're so today I might has a party line
Could you please hang up I need to keep this line open
Wow
Oh man
Wow wow wow the problem is everybody should have a good house phone just in
In case they need to hang up on Alex
Sure cuz if you could hang up on you can make a real good noise out of it and be great I do think that people
Who are of a certain age
Younger Folk
Don't know that
Experience Joy
A really
Slamming the phone down just like cathartic solving a lot of problems that you didn't even know you had with one
Phone slam
Yeah I don't miss it though
Maybe I was amore
Angsty person whenever
Stationary phones
The things on the wall phone
Slam a wall phone horizontally but it doesn't stick
It's just like it just drops
Did not work
Tripping up
The stairs Whenever two people
I can see you and there's no escape from that moment of embarrassment Gary like
Scalp
So are we begin 2021 and I think that there is a I think
Old man house phone showing up and giving us proof of life is
He's probably
A great sign
Yeah I think it says 2021 is going to be more house phone
Oriented
Maybe I don't know I don't know what it pretends
But it's something
Positive
Step backward in Tech
Logical development
Comanche area
My coven
I forgive you
I just wanted to play that I forgot to play the beginning
Sorry
Oh that's sorry as always
To say it is the right thing to say it's just weird I want to know what that's the other thing
2 questions for once
The plexiglass
Between Atlanta
And why do you say sorry
What's the what is motivating that are you at
Ticketmaster
Childhood
So I will be back until then
We are on Twitter that now there's are fighting I go to bed Jordan
Please find a local charity or bail Fund in your area to help out
People
BCS score
Quintero rundus
I'm thrilled my house phone is alive I mean that on sarcastically it's pretty nice to hear from them again
Almost like hearing the Don to Grand Prix is alive but unfortunately as bad news
He is not but all my house phone
Alex
Birthstone colors