Knowledge party.com respect with knowledge B
Knowledge fight
Fight.com
Acknowledge
Is it around drink beverages
Quick wash
What's up
Jordan is
Universe
January 7th
Our first episode came out
What are we doing I don't know how dare we do this
We are also a cancer on this
Unexpected Warriors ago
And it's been
Fun ride
Inappropriate gifts
From the universe
It is it is nice to still be working on this one
With you and I appreciate that
So that is my brights
But now it's beautiful it's one of those things where I have a hard time remembering that we
We didn't do this show at some point
Like there's a part of me that's like we didn't open mic
Suburbs and I was doing an open mic
My third of the night and I
Cheap room in my memory I'm like
Well tomorrow I'm going after record
Ridiculous
The schedule has got my toes done
Absolutely
What is I got new glasses
I got new glasses went about two weeks after I got these
My dog Jake
Got ahold of him
And there is a tooth marks in the like all over
And that was about a year ago
And got a new pair glasses
And do you want to know how stupid I am
When I went
To get new glasses I was looking
The frames and I was like how you know what I'll do I'll get some different frames I like the same stuff but I'm going to get some
I got the sticker
The different one
Now they look great
So something doesn't look great is our prospects, programmatic a decent hour
Recording is a little bit late because necessity kind of had to
Some big news happened yesterday and you decided to sleep the whole day you
You did maybe two hours of work on this episode
We were talking on
On Tuesday we recorded our little bonus scavenger hunt over
After we recorded that we were talking
Tomorrow
Going to suck it's going
How to be a disaster
I'm going to have to work a whole lot
So I'm going to do nothing
How to treat myself to a little bit of relaxation cuz I know that Wednesday is going to suck
I didn't think it was
Going to suck in the way that it did
At that point I was kind of predicting a dumb rally what I was thinking was going to suck was that Alex it interview
Viewed my
And I didn't want to deal with that
How nice
Famous person on the plane with the big
Not going to be in the news anymore you have Mike's wins interview can have to be on the back burner
I did watch it
And it's boring
But we might cover it at some point.
Bizarre thing to happen
I believe
The qanon
Who think Alex Jones is like a CIA massage Shield
And the two of them were doing an interview where they're like
And it won't stop talking about it on the
The episode that we're going to be going over today like it ends with
The two of them hug
Call Greg
Love it describes it as like
A really important moment
Rationalize that
Like it seems like a really difficult for their hero to be hugging a CIA Mossad agent
I would say he actually doesn't know anything about us
Doesn't care and would just like our money
Irene obd2b on the level
So Jordan
We're going to be doing
We're going to be going over
First of all the speeches that Owen Shroyer and Alex Jones gave at a stop Bastille rally on
The evening of January
Okay
Then
We will be tracking the entire day's cover it all right
On Infowars on January 6th
We're going to start with the American Journal
Why not
Well I mean nothing happened by then
Zits that early in the morning
Mostly because the
Harrison Smith is hosting and he's
Basically throwing it to where I was just throwing a Junior speech and
John show comes on after that also hosted by Harrison
And then we've got the War Room
Which is hosted by Tom pappert
And also Alex Jones
And Owen Shroyer in d.c.
Okay
So if I understand correctly we are playing the washer
Washington generals
Is that what's going to be string
Do important I just think I do still think it's important to look at the the lens of how the coverage on Infowars
Editorial control
You can see the training that these people have had under Alex
And Alex
It does show up
For sure for sure Culloden on cell
But I apologize to everybody I
They've been working
Straight through
All day yesterday I forgot to get names for walk
So I'll tell you what before we start today showed like to say thank you to everybody who supports our show
Also everybody who would like
Supportive
I'd like to thank you
Anybody out there who needs this today who needs their nice little
Pick me up yeah you're a policy wonk you know that
Thank you
Thanks everybody
On walks and I guess people who are hearing this 10 years in the future
Future
Sia on Wednesday
There was a planned rally in DC
We knew that there was enough without a hitch
Man
I was not
Fry's
Inasmuch as they've been talkin about this
This for a long time
And Alex has been trying
Incite an event
Like people storming the White House Tour
Capitol building
Something
That is bad
A predictable conclusion
From something
Lying if I said I wasn't still like shocked
Yeah I wasn't ready for it to happen right
I was I thought it was like I said already I thought it was going to be another dumb rally world
Everyone goes home
I was but I was taken aback by how quickly things got out of control
Control
And I was at I was pretty surprised
Watching Alex's coverage of it too I'm interested to see what I was trying to avoid dipping my toe
To have the
Conservative media would react
Too much to this
Just
So I didn't get a whiff of you know ruining the whole premise of the show which is that I don't know what Alex is
Yeah so I'm very curious to see how they all take this as a
Glaring Lawson that they're all a bunch of embarrassing moron
I think that's what they're going to
I think this is interesting because you and I have
Very different takes
On the event
There's a little bit of it
Disagreement and I actually think the both of our position
Oceans have marriage
And there's
To both of them believe that this was an Optics disaster and they all look like
Dum Dums
Hey and this is going
Going to be crippling to the right wing
Extremist movement
And I can see where you're coming from and I think that there is a place for Ibaka
And I think that is something that
Is
You know Valley to be part of the conversation
Personally I see Patriot lure being
Established
And that worries me
IC
Do you know the way that Alex talk
Facts about Lake Colonel Travis
Time at the Alamo and it's
Isn't history
Atrial or something like a misunderstanding and misrepresentation of the pass
Yeah
IC
That happening in the Press
And I see all of the elements that are necessary
In this event
To become a part of patriot lure
That is really encouraging
An inspiring and dangerous for people in the
And I don't think
But you don't think that's valid also I think that's one of the weird things about our our general disagreements is
I think you're probably right if certain couple of
Variable like
Our our worldviews are just like a couple little variables twisted
Did here or there and we disagree otherwise
I think
I even then we're still coming
At it from the same like
This is where all of the
These people think
Yeah some of these differences in our perspective
I hope they can
Be more fleshed-out as we go along the episode
Infowars coverage
I think it's very
So we're going to jump in with the speeches
Papa steel rally
Redo here's an out-of-context dropped from Today Show
God and His Consciousness creates the ocean
The creates the wave
On with Donald Trump
Joan
You
The ocean the ocean creates the waves and Donald Trump Alex Jones that you arrived
Brake locked up
He seems like he's gas
Like
It's a mess
Got it's another
Another instance of him being the guy at the comedy show you
You never want
2Go app
You don't want
This guy in the middle of the book
Not we're supposed to be no cuz I was going to burn out the audience
With just
If you can't do it
I mean even if the guy in front of you is only doing 10 minutes 45 if he gets
8 standing ovation
You're done
So are we start with Owen though and opens for Alex
He does a good eat at I-5 today
He starts off by ripping off Ally
President Trump is watch
And he's very excited and what do you see
And he's going to have some big announcements
For us tomorrow
I believe
When the government
Sears the people
There is freedom
All the people have beard
The government
Well in January 2021
Change it
It's a little worse in hindsight
We've been over this before but that isn't a Thomas Jefferson quote it's against socialism delivered
By John Basile Barnhill
That's over the years has been miss attributed to a bunch of people like Thomas Paine and Thomas Jefferson
Perhaps more interesting Lee though In that clip
Appears that Owens trying
To promote the idea that Trump is going to show up at the rally the next
This was the first instance of an Infowars in
Employee behaving in a way that led me to believe that they had
No idea people were planning
To storm the capital the bank
They're acting 100% business as usual
Promoting what they expect will just be another afternoon
Profitable terrorism edging
Going to be playing
That's kind of the vibe that I get
This is all I can Infowars business-as-usual
Does Owen being a dumb s*** head
And the theme is
Four more years for Donald Trump in Wildwood
I think all of us can get behind that
I'd like to see a thousand more years of human freedom and 1000 more years
United States of America
Then deal with climate change
How far it always happens
That always happens Breakout
Here's the problem
I'm going to give you this right now
There's only one that I can
Here's your route
Those dumb
You can steal
Anything
And they will have no you stole a
Thomas Jefferson quote from not Thomas Jefferson and they
Still bought it
Why wouldn't you go out there and be like
Would you rather have a Lexus or Justice
Do you want some substance
Okay I see you working hard
Schools don't teach history
Seattle player
Stay awake
Yeah horse reindeer really fancy and
Just completely lie to the audience
Just like grapes don't exist
Shoot the moon what's the light
The fake Thomas Jefferson quotes
So in the pocket
Territory
Also I would say that even under like ideal conditions I don't know if America could last
Another Thousand Years
Country 2
Baby baby
We could still exist
In some fashion
But not like a superpower I mean it'll probably be more like the Holy Roman Empire
Was in Germany for a while
You know like that kind of
It would be bizarre to imagine
Continuing at the other ideas for that long
Small parts of man Montana that caught up
It's a foolish
But I will say I think that or when
Feels bleh
To get into a line of work that you and I used to
Explorer I think he wants
Start doing open-mic you want to do a little bit but you remember when he took the tank down to the Austin
Ready to go on the
Sure you got a new bit
What you know
Nancy Pelosi said that you can no longer
Mother and father in Congress did you see this
Why not news for Nancy Pelosi
Trap is your daddy
Goodbye goodbye solid solid piece of work right there
We're doing me you can't say mother and father again 24 hours prior to
To the fall of the United States government a nuclear power of one of the leaders of the resistance said
Who's your daddy
Great 5 years ago they did this you can't say mother and father paranoia
Great to see them bring them back to hit
It's about time
So this is in response to Nancy Pelosi the house updating their rulebook
Text of the rulebook
Doesn't include gendered language
But that doesn't mean that you can't say mother and father
That's against the rules
It's just not in the text of the rule right
This is like Spooner do you know they've been doing new stuff for five years but whenever you go in public
You still got to play the
Yeah but
This would be like
You know you don't play Freebird for a few years
You bring it out as if a
Has never been played before in public that chance to get a free bird out there
Are you know
I would save Freebirds along song
And Owen Shroyer set is not long
It's a smart move
This is no Stairway to Heaven
That is a
Okay alright
2 1/2 minute pop song
He's getting out of there and he's a he's also another stand-up reference
Shotgun
Situation
It's my pleasure to introduce a man
It's my honor to introduce a man
Who was the Genesis in many ways
August 2nd American Revolution dear FBI
Alex Jones was in many ways the Genesis of this started
With one man
On public access television will tomorrow
Turn into millions of Americans in the streets of Washington DC
Lego Republic
I really also does not look great in that in hindsight
Only one man on public access at Austin Texas is responsible for everything that happens tomorrow
I just want any
Law enforcement entities
Baby record a good speech
As we speak to know
This is all Catholics
Tomorrow will be the culmination of his professional career
BoBoiBoy stop this movement
Kid Alex it's all on him
Only him
Throwing him under the bus by way of flattery
This is the greatest man who is responsible for everything
I thought I found myself feeling like this is terrible
Put them the other thing that I was feeling was
Like Owens doing some stand-up
In the crowd to chant USA is pandering on
And Alex
Basically starts his set with like giving up for yourself
Out of here
Thank you
Unicorn
Give yourselves a round of applause for coming out tonight what a lovely audience you guys are the best
Alright okay if I'm if I'm doing my sad I want to open with three of us break doesn't matter I want to save Give It Up
For your waitstaff
Hey give it up for yourselves for coming out tonight hey ladies and gentlemen
How about those sport
Or like that is gracious move is maybe you're the headliner everyone else you saw tonight
Super cool number three in there and then get you
Is that going
Maybe learn that as a little bit of attic
Because I think I might be a
Performance Evolution on his car
So many failed a right-wing Comics are these people so I assume Alex's spend a lot more time with
What's failed right-wing Comics recently
It possible maybe he's going backwards
Reactionary Open Mic open mic
Do stand-up
Okay well we have
He does have a head start
On other let's
Say younger comics
Coming up
Well there's that
But he's also got a catchphrase and he's got a catchphrase
Apparently
Audiences will
With him get the f***
New York trying to steal this election
In front of everyone
20 years ago
What are they want to fight
He's got his own pewter done people will call and response
Wild never heard that before in my life
Yeah but I mean if you if you think of you want to fight you better believe you got one that was a long
Anything for people to
Yeah
I thought I was a little bit late
The Lord's Prayer saying I don't remember all of the Lord's Prayer
If I was up after this I would be worth what the Lord's Prayer
Bring the energy out of
Super worried cuz like alright
Either
He's going to f***
I'm not going to be able to follow
Anyway
He almost alienate the audience
The Lauryn Hill if the right
He almost immediately after this after getting a git er done
He almost alienates the audience
By accidentally saying that Hitler was bad
Gangster
Star Wars was a monster
But 1033
Gingy bang dad
Overshadow their Prime
Angry Birds
RJ
A mother's love
At Tristan
A Buddhist and exhaustion
Are Chinese
Odell Beckham
Of what
I think it's f***** up
Eggdog
You can tell that Alex has a serious scholar of Chinese history in the Chinese Communist party because he knows the names of Maui and she
I actually kind of think that he doesn't realize that she is a
Set Mouse successor
And I'd love to bring up who Jintao to him he would say who and then we'd end up in the Vaudeville
Legitimately like to ask him if
Pino's
Fit Chairman Mao Haddaway
I would be
Did to know if he
He thinks then
The whole time it was
I don't know
In a couple names
Leaving that aside it's important to understand that Alex is lying
To this audience
Sensitive area
He doesn't care at all what kind of does to the weaker population
Muslim
Except when he can use their pain as a weapon against
His own anime
In this case he's in front of a crowd so he wants to establish the moral High Ground
A imaginary evil enemies who Sports on his treatment of Muslims
When he's alone on his own show speaking freely
You sound a little bit different
Like he did on May 26th
From Michigan to Texas
From London to Los
Rio de Janeiro to Berlin
There are called the prayers
Cuz I know it's a group ride
Do you think check their repressive treatment to ensure these populations
She cares
What would Alex is doing here onstage is exactly what he and his friends accused the entire left
Does doing
Virtue signaling China treats Muslims because
The only Muslims that would be allowed in America would be the ones who agreed to convert to his bizarre idiotic version
Christianity
Quite simply Alex's using the false impression that he's offended by how the Chinese government treats the tweakers
In order to pretend that his criticisms of China come from a sensible
A real place
When in reality they're mostly just
The rewarmed
John Birch
Society Cold War.
Yep it's a it's a it's a bummer but also Alex need a little bit f***** up
Use a diesel messed up
Yes there are
Currently I would say
The countdown of ways to learn we've gone from 10 to about
When he gets down to a four we know we're f***** up right now there are eight ways that I would say that he's having a good time
And more importantly he has
Had a good time before this
You've been having a good time
Relationship
Gas
Mikey has nocardia
If you're a comic and you want to be like a high-energy comic
You'll quickly learn
If you're out of shape
You're going to have a really tough time with that
DC Comics or like maybe a little bit more energetic
Sometimes it'll be sweating
That's because
It's hard
It's hard to keep a
The energy app
I think Alex is learning now we're only a half hour is
Alex is learning this the hard way
Authoritarian throughout history have pat on the Bolsheviks
Bad dad on the Nazis
On every other
Will Ferrell
I guess you're right in a way odd
Big Freedia the universe
There is a God
That inspired our Republic
Edgar is a God
There's a control
Ma
Abdomen
Real real sweet if we are loyal
I don't know if it came through as well on the audio but you can tell
Is breath after just about every other word
And it doesn't look
Comfortable
But
Listen to Safe territory
Start this getting into religion
Get in get out
And once you start talking about religion it's important that you level with the audience
You got to be real
Let's hear this one
Make no mistake I'm like
Liliana
Thanks for going to erupt
Things are going to get bad
We've already allowed the murder of 60 million babies in this country
Animal
So weird sometimes
We're hundreds of feet deep
It's really hard for a backhoe service
And not everybody
Is going to make it
But that's okay
Because in the end
God will fulfill
And will
Outside of like some surface-level stuff this is exactly the
The kind of speech I would
Expect to hear at an Isis rally
Different decoration that's different
Themes maybe but like this is this is
This is called
These guys are
Are you I am so happy
To remember how many times people told me
Years ago like
Don't call them Isis that's
That's too bad
I love it
Love it
IQ
The past
Well if it's possible for you to have been onto something and also wrong again
But maybe not now
Screen
God Rises up man
Who are real
Goddamn that
Are above reproach
Real man
President-trump
Whose fault
Reproductive
Pecan
Ugly toes
A representative
Do your daughter return
Hold up President Trump
Party for him
Sounds like his voice is about to bottom out to like give up the gasoline Road Warrior
Okay
Thanking thanking God for sending Trump is he deliver
Subway
It's funny too
Hear that speech
Like broadcast
On TV
And like no it like I'm not but I'm not positive this speech
No.
A little more like
Imperial Centerville
Traveling throughout speitzer
It's sent
Broadcast Network
Around everywhere all of this happening
Instantly
In his pocket is a small little brick with all of human history record
Inside of India but he's like
We've got
Trump is our deliverer because
Super weird world
It's super weird to to imagine that signal like going
Into people's homes
At least one person is watching it like
Damn right
Yeah that's very bizarre
What sea is this the Miracles in your face
This speech
It's like yeah yeah
I get I get what Alex is doing I can understand
Baffling to me to imagine that
You know people are like
Wild
This is good yeah man
This is my favorite character
Free Road was Immortal
Joe I thought he was the guy I wanted to follow
Ride-or-die immortan Joe
Well it could not be worse
Spend Bill Gates money
All I know
I was looking around. Banned. Video
And there's a new section on there and it's
Just titled Bill Gates is evil
I guess that's also a folder I have on my desktop but I guess that's what Alex is doing instead of making that documentary
Call Bill Gates is just got a place where he's posted some shity videos
Nice organized
But he doesn't run the world
That Bill Gates
What is God
Okuma destiny
Martha okay
Batman
Not Lord Rothschild
Understanding
Is the universe
Control
We recognize God we connect with God
I think people worried about when that sentence was
Yeah that way
Highland calf
I don't mind a run-on
Mine one but there are times when you should
It felt like
The sentence was
As drunk as Alex appears to be assertive staggering forward
Alex says also doesn't
Look great in hindsight
Tomorrow
Enterprise
We do quietly take the election
We don't quietly take the scam
And believed RBS
The system
Has had good desperately
Engage get this gambling
To maintain control
Well
Either Waterloo
Will be
Destruction
Emigrate
I would say that if I
And I were confronted with that
This is all political
Political only
Hey I have not talked about
Literal events at that would be smart
So now here is my concern when I was talking about being the person who comes up after him is like
He's going to lose
Krowd
Keep this up this is
He's going to burn out fast
Start dipping his toes into covid Denial in the audience
School
Stop the steel route
Everything YouTube with a big Tech censorship
Atomic attack
And the covid lockdown
Mou and martial law
Worldometer
Porto's
How did you get here
The world
Government Chicken Little
Witch Hunt system
61000 more people died
They talk about Hitler
When you can
Drug addiction
Drug overdoses suicide
Harley Quinn
Have to go out
You have to expose it
It's falling apart a little bit I think should have left that one again
A little bit drunk now Alex a little bit too drunk to stay on target
Sometimes you'll be onstage like it matters three B will land in like
I'm going to tryouts
I just got f***** up
No I think he's in I think he's in a nice little world of like
Hold on
I'm going to do one more bet that last one didn't land so I'm going to do one more and then that one lands in your life
Oh s***
How many do one more after that I'm going to
Push it I'm going to get blue blood in this ride
No one's going to get this but he's Mike Sheehan
Yeah I would say that about right
When you when you're in that circumstance
That's the only thing you can do
Is Retreat back to what was working
Try and be like okay I was being dirty earlier I tried to be like more
Introspective
Observational
They didn't like that
Got to go back
Don't be mean to Hitler I realize that if you're mean to Hitler
But religion is Papa
Go back to religion
So we must now
President-trump
And lift him up the Todd
And ask God to give him the guidance
Sherman
Evan leadership
In dogs worm
Breakdown the New World Order
Go back a little bit alright
Alright
It should be harder
If it were not very smart
They believe things like that like that fake Jefferson quote earlier
Churchill
A famous Beach
Braeside all I can promise you with blood
And pain in 1 hour
What the New World Order.
Electric rice
World
I may be wrong and I'm open to admitting that if Alex
God provide that to that citation but I think he's trying to remember his first speech as prime minister in
House of Commons in 1940
Alex I think is misquoting is quote
In this crisis I hope I may be pardoned if I do not address the house at any length
Today
I hope that any of my friends and colleagues are former colleagues are affected by the political reconstruction will make allowance
For any lack of ceremony with which it has been necessary to add
I would say to the house as I say to those who have joined this
I have nothing to offer but blood
Toil tears and sweat
People at 12 tears
Sweating is an attempt
Distress to his government that he's working
B A shorts
Not a promising you the blood
After this Churchill comments on his strategy for fighting WWII
Which is the other part of what I think Alex is messing up here
You ask what is our policy
I can say it is to wage war by sea land and air with all our might with all our strength that God can give us
The wage war against the Monstrous tyranny
Never surpassed in the dark
Lamentable catalogue of human
Crime
That is our policy
You ask what is our aim I can answer in one word
It is Victory
Victory at all costs
Victory in spite of all Terror
Victory however long and hard the road may be
For without victory there is no survival
Three elements of slightly more eloquent than Alex makes
I will give you blood
I reminded
Greg Churchill cloud
What is best in life
It wasn't good
I think
The bed is definitely the quote but he's mixing up
Because whatever he does is really shity Churchill impression
Bilap
He's changed in the moment it is drunken idlebrain.
I know that I know that a lot of people are struggling
You know I think a lot of people had a tough time
With the watch
The events that unfolded on Wednesday
Still recognizes that there's a lot of people in pain
Maybe some people in the audience
Feeling in pain
And I shouldn't this is his messages
Of unity
No hope
God. Nobody
For anybody I got into might be feeling alone
Jennifer
Never
Never feel alone
Bugatti
No matter if your car broke down in the middle of the desert
God of the universe built you
Will
Andover. Channel
Enclosing
Enchilada today or tonight okay
I love the idea of Owen Shroyer sitting off
Stage laughing
This guy's got the good
I will follow Captain my Captain
Take a note
So it is in the back listening to his sack record
Later on tonight
Go to f***
Hidden Shamrock
Why why not do it
Although I do hear that and I kind of think to myself it would be really interesting to see The Alex Jones
Motivational
Speaker
You know like
Hey
You lost your job
Taxman sucks
Guess What You're Made In God's image
No matter what you got is minimizes your problem
Tell me that God made you out of Stardust or whatever
I know you're poor
Come on now
A the end of Alex's speech
And where we will leave the stop Bastille rally
From January 5th
General plan
Rodger Stone
As You Are
Whether you be black
What do you mean why
God loves you
And I will never suffer
We will prevail
Woohoo
While too very weird
Yeah
You got to end
And upset
Walk-off you don't need to reveal that you've completely blanked on who else is speaking General Flynn
Nope don't even end with almond as I weird
Still leave the quest
Junior mind what does he think that means
You got people storming the capital the next day you got him
Inspiring chance of 1776
Kind of I mean
Look
Understand what year are you drawing a connection between the two I'm not necessarily I'm just the narrative consistency
If these two events were in a fictional story
The author we're arguing
That one
Led to the other
It would make that would make sense
Cause anything
Proven entropy standpoint
In front of the other I think you know which you would
We go to the
I will be here for a while
Will be spending a little bit time
Frenchy's
It doesn't happen until
Almost the end of Alex's show
Sure actually
Probably in the second hour I
Think is when the actual like
When were the barricades
Proceeded to get wild pretty fast
We'll deal with that as best we can as we as we go along
But we're still in this sort of
Much more innocent time now because we're listen
The American Journey
Sure which is Guinness supposed to be calling
Ellen show there's no calls
No call zero calls
Yeah I'm not even one
Call Timber Alexei
A seventeen-year-old host
Very shortly
True
Could be a baby
I think he's like a high school sophomore internship
AV block
Local
College Area High School
The news of the day for him
Beginning is the Thursday
This Trump rally that's going to be going on
But also
Georgia got stolen
What do you expect
They haven't been punished of course they're going to do it again
And so they did it again
So Georgia
Looks like it was lost
I think one of the
I'll get an update here but as far as I know both races are projected to be Democrat victories
Although one is still
On that the hairline
Victory margin
Junior is live right now on the stage only go to him he I think has a major future if there's anybody that could source
His father succeed his father
Remember seeing him give a speech
At the RNC
In 2016 and thinking
I am putting my money on this guy
Disgaea
This guy can carry his father's mantle
And keep that torch lit
Let's go to him now and then watch this live feed
This John Junior kids got something
Wow
Please my future
Isaac Carree
For sure
The way he introduc clip made me really excited pump hear what I wanted to hear
Punished for stealing last time
I thought myself very bored listening to Harrison a day calendar because he wouldn't
Not stop funky
Considering abrogate
A lot alright
I was going to make a Supercut of it but I got like three or four times that I cut it out notice I got any
Most one abrogate
Per week these people wax
Mike Pence has abrogated C-Max
At 1
Anyway
There's a lot of stuff that I was listening to
Would have just sounded like
Bragi bulshit
If people hadn't
Rodger wormed Capitol building
There's a lot of stuff
Here is one of them
Truly incredible stuff
Of course
What we have just learned
And I'm excited to share once again is that
President Donald Trump himself
Personally asked Alex Jones
Weed this March
Following outruns a speech he will be at the Bangor guess they didn't want to win
To the Capitol
And it's a
It's truly incredible just go ahead and leave that life ft up we leave me in a box to
Just because
Nami people tuning in for its the
Incredible events going down in Washington
You're right
I would say
Now it would probably be even have they have known that people are going to storm the
Capital
Personally asked by Trump
To believe the march from the speech to the
Capitol building
Seem like my resume pretty quick
Also this looks discount
Silly in hindsight
That's the message we need to tell the police's
You're a human being you're not a robot
You know what's going on here
You know who the good guys are who the bad guys are
Shouldn't be confusing to you
Shouldn't be up in the air for you when you have
Chords of
You know just black lives matter
Just failures just supported by the state
Coming out to the capital city to try to burn down buildings to try to tear down statues
Call yell at police and called him all sorts of horrible things
Then you have interest on protesters marching saying
Thank you to the cops saying you know we support you
It's not too difficult to know
Who's bad guys aren't who's good guys are
Couple hours later
Christine
Interesting things you're saying
Perhaps
Perhaps you may not be viewing yourself through the appropriate
I think I might be
One of the things I find really interesting is Harrison's doing play-by-play of the Trump rally
And so you had Don Jr
Who's this fresh upstart he's a he's got
You got a bright future ahead of him
Now there is an actual
GOP upstart
Who's really like
Kind of a hot commodity
Yeah yeah the Nazi who's in a wheelchair
Like the person who would want an all kinds ad campaign
Sure
I don't I don't know enough about his politics
Everything but based on the speech
I'm not thrilled
Interesting
Do still know who he
He is
Square jaw and all
Harrison
Doesn't know who he is
Real Madison cawthorn comes up
To give the speech
Yeah he's up like
Madison something that's fantastic
His name is
Is easy new he's a new
Congressman
His name is
I'm in Lincolnton right now Madison or something
But but he was just elected he's promised to stand up for Trump again stop
Bastille Wild
I love it I want this
Steube Infowars is new
Entire
I want Harrison
To host every show yeah I think this is dynamite
Looks familiar
Madison cawthorn zip they're doing is doing his speech
Just to show that everyone is a door
Love that USA Champs
A
Parody of a parody it is
It really is
Yeah
Speaking of parodies of Perry
Up next Rudy Giuliani Rudy is giving a speech
Man-o-man
A lot of people took issue with him saying that He suggests
Trial by combat
Call Storm Dwight
Which is objectively hilarious
It is it is
It's a poor choice of words sure
Well I I mean
I get why you would be hand-wringing over that
I understand it to nobody says
Trial by combat meaning
Store Mebane
Sure it means one-on-one Game of Thrones
Stupid even so that's not what he was talking about you actually listen to the context he's talking about the reputation of Donald
Trump versus the reputation of Joe Biden
He's just trying to argue Mountain versa
The sand snake
Makes her whatever
Two of them actually fighting
He wants 10 days
His whole argument has he wants 10 days
For them to go on
Fishing experiment
Expedition
And try and find something in the ballot
That they can make an argument
Presenting it that way it'll take 10 days for them
Define defraud that they already know is there or something
Stick arbitrary measure of
I love time is exactly 10
We get to see the machines
Too late
If I were Rudy Giuliani and I could get anyone to gamble again
My reputation I don't care what I said to win I'm taking that.
2 reputation
More worthless if
Amazing
Number to Giuliani I'm Campbell in for like a sandwich
I have every bit of my reputation
From 9/11 bear to standing in front of the Four Seasons Landscaping Company
So
I got a little bored
At this point
Because Harrison is really just
No covering these
Speeches and it's a lot of speech
What to see this person landed in amazing exclusive
Right now we have any
Exclusive we are on the line with Rob do who is there
App to save America March
Live on the ground at thanks for
Connecting with a drive-by no
It's difficult
Cell phone signal there with all of the massive crowds what is the
What is it like there on the ground Rob
It's a seat Patriots
The city of Happy
Happy people really believe you
That is an exclusive
Also technically one of the most
Accurate ways you can use the word exclusive
All the networks are knocking down radu's door cuz I would love to go
On Fox News today but I've gotten
Exclusive
Xrd Buell
There you know I do ever the
Bumbly
Dumb dumb
I can't even come up with the right words to express how much of a goof this guy is schlemazel
Sure
He's got to come in and get a little piece of that pie
And that pie of course it's saying things that look really bad in hindsight
Right when the president starts
Speaking about halfway through Alex
Full album
And then we're going to leave that marks
To the Capitol
To surround it
And let these
Dogs that are trying to
Steal our Republic know
What's going to happen to them if they do go through with their dastardly Deeds
Yeah and you know I got wish I was there I mean the energy must be amazing so I guess Rob is expressing with that
The intention of the marches
To scare the covers into not certifying the results of the election
School what they need to know is that we are at
Threat to them
Physically
They should be scared for their lives we're going to do this we are going to
Follow through on that threat should they not give us what we want exactly
Popped
I thought so Donald Trump coming up next
What are you doing
The second American Revolution has begun
He can't do that out to break like that
It will go fast
Alex
Overly dramatic like really exciting
You can see like
He's trying to do some of Alex's tricks
But he just can't
He doesn't have it no
Embarrassing
Sing again to know that a couple hours after this
People
Storm
Capital
I think it's a little bit weird that
It's not like it this
Does Harrison Smith
First time on mine like he's been on Mike for a long time
How do you not just
Allow yourself into the joy of
Following out with music
I don't know you know
How can you not get pumped how could you not even like at least sing a little bit along he sounds
Robert probably because Alex would hear about it and he beat him up for working inside of the street
No that's my game
Yeah but get a little into a get a little hip
Man if I if I would come in
Silver Stallion
Holy God
Begging Alex.
Collars call in and then be like you're boring and play a song
Sing instead
It always be the Highway 31 would go crazy
So
Since the little bit of perhaps racial animus earlier
From Harrison blacklivesmatter failures
And what have you
Easy a little bit more of that on
Display here
The Democrats are allowed
Carry out this fraud if there
Do it again and again and again and again and again
The also increase
The number of
Immigrants by
Magnitudes of 10
Refugees by many many millions
And completely open the borders outright bill
Install socialistic
Programs that
Reward people that don't work don't provide and
Have nothing but
Hatred Forest ICICI Owen Shroyer there
You see him right there to the left of the stage
Screen left
Stage right
Shroyer
Just stood up
And is looking around that's him right
I do think that moment is a little cute at the end
Watching the video you can see like almost real exciting
Where you at
I think that might actually be friends I think that but I think that sounds right later on
Like Owens on the phone
Talk over each other
Yeah they both
Apologize to each other
How people would interact
I know that's what I'm saying
Puppies otamatone
Watching Alex interact with people it's so goddamn Rudolph music.
It's bizarre to see like actual like a
Excitement with see my friend on TV
Polite conversation
Azhar Azhar solo
Betty White
I'm a guy who's just
Shoveling
Pile of a
Stuff that looks bad in hindsight Yorkshire
Can add to that
What's this
Course today is the day
That the
Congress will vote on whether or not to certify
And
Codify the
So-called fraudulent results
Of the election
They're many machinations that
Could be
You know pulled out here in the last in the last minutes or so the last hours
Of course it's not really over until January 20th but today is the day that we've all been waiting for its David Donald Trump himself
Requested
His supporters
Come to Washington DC to see him speak into stand-up
Against
The lies just information and fraud
Of the mainstream media
In their controllers in the Deep state
Feel incredible stuff
Of course the word is
Alex Jones was requested by
Donald Trump himself can use March
The driving that home
Oh boy
Is in order for it to be like
Isolated
In just a few minutes Alex Jones will actually be leading the March
To the Capitol
At best
Personal request of President Donald Trump
Alex Jones will be at the head of that Vanguard
As the entire crowd this massive
Cumin
Snake this is huge
Just
Unimaginable almost crowd
Trump supporters who have made their way to the nation's capital
I will wind its way towards
Capitol building
How's it going
Wow
What age
Chest
Glowing waves
You describe your friends and people you love
Are they look like
The mood is jovial
Among Trump supporters in d.c. or at least that's what
Harrison is gassing car
Based on his assessment of it
Occupied
Back folks the mood is still a jovial one here in a courses on Rob do reported
Live on the scene and there at the Save America March in Washington DC it's like it's uplifting everybody
Happy everybody's feeling good at the same time there's an underlying
Aggressiveness
Beneath the surface
Anaa and unrest
I suppose you could say
Pervading
Spirit of
American Trump
Supporters everybody's a little bit on edge because once again
We have tried
And tried
And tried and tried and tried to play Within the rules we have tried
To make the system change itself to get back on track
To stop
Have you endless
Drive to bankrupt
And enslave us
And time and time again we are met with
Traitorous and seditious
At blocking us
From carrying out
Hey we gold lawful
Within the bounds of of the game
Change it now they've prevented us at every pass our last and final
Outlet
Was our sacred vote and that is what has been
Stolen from us or
At least it's still in the process of being stolen from myself
So you're making the argument that the
The jovial mood is Pierce
Only by the recognition that there are no more legal ways for you
Deal with the problem
That are existentially threatened
Going to you
So you're saying that
It's time to do illegal things
It is a solemn moment
That we must decide to
Extrajudicial
Take back our
Married
When's that that's exactly what we wanted to do so we're feeling
I'm pretty good about it right now
Is a real jovial atmosphere
Kill a few people
Jaunty music playing at Graham we got a flapper contingent over there
Are there a doing little via
So earlier in the episode we already heard
Harrison saying that
You know
We had the storm
Denotes the Georgia election
So this bit of news that he comes to at the end of his show seems
Unbelievable
Capital Bank reports
That these
Send it
Races in Georgia
Attracted 300,000
Les Bois
What's the Donald Trump got
For president
Indicating that the Breezy
Stayed home
Why would we go out of our way to support
A party
That refuses to lift a single finger for the president of the United States we all voted for
Undermined him at every pass
I thought it was stolen
Wait
You're saying that it's that people didn't show up to look for animation tablet
Because she's a bad
Keokis Amanda
What but they got Bev debuted in
Didn't show up because it was preempted
We stolen
These don't seem to be counter explanations for they almost in
At at odds with one another Infowars
Perhaps even one with the
Suggest that they don't even know what they believe
Maybe they're very
Confuse feels good feels right that they stole it
Didn't show up
They stole it
Obviously it might have something to do with us saying that they stole elections and that elections don't matter
So your vote.
Doesn't matter so it doesn't matter if you vote
Alexander's making a lot of money off the stuff
So Harrison is hosting Alex's show so it's basically just a smooth transition
Into the Alex
Gun show
Welcome to The Alex Jones Show on Harrison Smith it's January 6th and Donald Trump is just begin
Began speaking to the stop
Steel March in Washington without any further ado
We go now to
The president of the United States in Washington
So I apologize in advance the first hour of the show is just Trump speech
And so we're going to have to listen
Come to a little bit of it I know that we generally don't listen to step this is pretty wild
I think that it also sets the stage for a lot of the contents a tiny things
Things that end up happening
Please try not to scream too much we're recording this late
Screaming
So it's kind of
Trump rambling
A bit about how he
Describes a really huge
And fake news World prize eggs
Go ahead turn your cameras please would you show they came from all over the world actually but
They came from all over a country
I just really want to see what they do
I just want to see
They covered I've never seen that
But the
It would be really great if we could be covered fairly by the media the media is the biggest problem we have
As far as I'm concerned single biggest problem
Wow
Are you making whimpering dog noises
Well if that seems
Kind of soft
There's so many week
But it's it's incredible
Many of the Republicans I helped them get in I help them
Get elected
I help
I could name
Four of them let's say I won't bore you with it
What the f*** is going on but this
This is so bizarre that this is what's happening that this is a speech to the east
Aye
I never listen to him
So
It's so weak I think this is something that is under-reported
Amongst all of his terrifying words
Is how much of a
Pathetic little whiny
He's a
Little tiny
You imagine
Anybody else in a leadership position
Complaining about the 24 people I've helped to her ungrateful to me
My God
Grow up
Respect that in a boss I would respect that
Contemporary
I would respect that anybody that is
Childish it
You imagined like Obama
He made fun of my Tears
All these Democrats
It's just
So sad
The president
I swear
Trump says b******* in the middle of this clip
Extra
I don't know if Nixon ever
Swore and then
A crowd of people started chanting this way or he just said
Using the pretext of the China virus and the scam of
Mail-in ballot
Democrats
The tempted the most Brazen and outrageous
Selection
Superior theft
In American history everybody knows
Everybody knows our election was over
Will eating
Pennsylvania Michigan Georgia
I do and then late in the evening or early in the morning
Boom this explosion
Bulshit
And all of a sudden
That's amazing
Do you know why
All of this s***
Do you know
I will say this
This is what I ate I believe
As much as
Is the cops are totally complicit with all those
People getting through in all of that
The reason that the National Guard and all of those people
Word already at the ready
Is because of s*** like
Professional rapper
None of these people thought
That any of this was
Real
Yeah I mean professor
You're telling me that a crowd of people
Who's listening to the president of the United
State's a goddamn
The biggest economy in the nuclear f****** power is going to get taken down by a crowd of assholes screaming
Is perfect
Big Dipper
Scream Park
Yes it's the same s***
Weird definite Alamo
Meant to overlap
And when you're losing
In a wrestling match
Got to fight harder
And that's what Trump says people got to do this is
Keep in mind right before people
Call Storm.
And we want to be so
Nice
We want to be so respectful of everybody
Including
Bad people
And we're going to have to fight much harder
And Mike Pence is going to have to come through
Hanabi dozen
That will be a sad day for a cont
Because
Your sworn
Arkansas
Institution
God is up to Congress to confront
This egregious assault
Walnut Demarcus
Donald Trump giving it to Republicans and Democrats alike in defense of the Constitution we have to go to a
Quick commercial break
The Alex Jones Show we'll be right back
Depends to save the Constitution which I guess
Do not know
Took the meds
Seemed
Seemed very 121
Seem very if
Then
It's it it
Again narrative
Consistent
Kind of interesting how
The night before I was trying out a little bit
Stand up
I noticed
Trump might have the sand of it
I'm going to little bit
And the only unhappy person in the United
Single most unhappy
Is
Hillary Clint
Because she
Why didn't you do this for me for years ago
10000 in Michigan
You could have changed the whole thing
She's not too happy you noticed
Where is she
I bet did not land
You would have expected that bit to go over
Foster's with Matt to that crowd but no problem with that bit is that he unfortunately
Did his entire bulshit for this election
Yeah
Why didn't they do it for her
Yeah it's less a comedic premise as much as it is a plot hole
Huh well we didn't those Gunners on the Destroyer shoot down the Escape pod with
C-3PO and R2-D2
Hilarious hilarious
This is this is worth
Pull-A-Part
Trump
He wants to train
Prove that there was there was fraud
As you know the media is constantly asserted the outrageous lie that there was
No evidence of widespread
Oh really
Walking to read you pages I hope you don't
Bored listening to a promise
Don't get bored listening to all those
Hundreds of thousands
What is the people back there
Move up
Play Cher
All they all these people don't get bored don't get angry at me because you're going to get bored
Because it's so much
They do get bored
Yeah I need to start rattling off numbers
The audience
I think is able to pay attention
It's not exciting
He loses a little bit
In retrospect
If all of these speakers had known that the
The crowd was
More of us
Storming crowd
Anna
Like they like chant
But they love storm until we learned that
I don't think the numbers game was really going to end
Inspire them in
Recorders out
But that's a little bit lower
Stuck In The Weeds you're not coming back out talkin about covid
One out of every ten people we already stopped listening listing off County
Twitter
Every time I put out a tweet
Even if it's totally correct
Only correct
Tickets
And they also don't let you get out you know on Twitter
Very hard to come on to my account
It's very hard to get out of message
They don't let the message
Get out
Nearly like they should
But I've had many people
I don't care about
What is bad news they're all bad news
Newsletters bad news
Oh man
How funny is it how
Long everybody is tried to respect the office
Yeah
How hilarious is it
This might have all ended if
TV news anchors
Just treated Trump the way I did and every time he whines is my
And then everybody was
Maybe
I mean
I know that generally we don't
Don't cover
When you know Trump speeches but awesome
They don't
Play the feed.
It's
I had to listen to
That's why I have
Because they
Like really if you're if you're listening
In the audience
You kind of get
A certain message
These powers only option
And it's time that somebody did something about it
And Mike Pence I hope you're going to stand up
Of our constitution
About country
Out of your not I'm going to be very disappointed in you I will tell you right now
I'm not hearing good stories
Stories
That's pretty clear but it's
The
Applicants have to get tough or you're not going to have a republic
Can party if you don't get tough
They want to play so straight they want to play Soul
The United States
The Constitution doesn't allow me
Just send them back
What's a yes it does because
The Constitution says you have to
Protector
Igf2 protect.com
And you can't vote on fraud
Android breaks up everything doesn't it
When you catch somebody in a fraud
You're allowed to go
I should know I've cheated on my wife I hope Mike has
The courage to do what he has
Citadel
And I hope he doesn't listen to the rhinos and the stupid people that he's
Whenever you have the present out there saying that like no Pence's the last chance to really
Save this as a responsibility to do it
Zen pencils
Doesn't do that thing
And the president has also said that when something is stolen you're playing by
Current set of rules
It's kind of
Hard to not take
Where your messages like
There's no rules
The rules that are normal
Argon
Do find it difficult to take
A would-be strongmen dictator seriously if he gives an entire speech
Exhorting his second-in-command
What is a
Borderline a honorary position
It's to overthrow the
Country for him
That's a little bit sad
Mixed in with
Petty complaints
But that's kind of. Kind of a thing though
It could easily be
White blinds you to the real danger of a lot of things
Easy to to minimize
What some real threats are
Because of that window dress
I was like hitting this
Pathetic
And I don't want to
So
Donald Trump speech now
Is that the most
That that is relevant
Comparison comes back
He wants to throw it to video what's going on
In Congress
Where Mike Pence is presiding over this
But they actually send it
To the streets
Where Alex
Is bullhorn
Let's go to
Inside the chamber here
The report is
What does that mean
It doesn't have a good
Rhythm
It doesn't have a good M now it doesn't as far as a chant goes
Muse painting 1776
I don't know what message You're supposed to take away from that other than overthrow the government
What happened at 7
Except he would be referee
Barbados at Revolution
It would did anything else happen though
I mean I'm certain
What happened to let's see did open to business
I would say that I think Benjamin Franklin opened up a little side gig
Grinding lenses I think that's also what happened in 1776 I guarantee there was somebody in
Like Virginia who's also like everybody
He's not referencing that
Sam
Batista's first beer Sam Adams somebody in Virginia was trying to get people
To have rationality calmer heads will prevail that's not what he's referring to
Cricket diplomatic
Delusion is in order
So Alex still is not like great with long
Stretches
Will still end up becoming
Nothing really overwhelmed by
You got to yell into a bowl
Sew-ins got to come in here and there
Illegal
Too good little boy
Oh man
Yep so what I was listening to this
This action of Alex and Owen on the
Street it really felt like they were trying to juice this crowd
It feels
Kind of like a
Incitement
What is a gentleman
21st century Warfare
It seems like if you're in the audience who probably this is the kind of thing that would be like
What you
Then yell then you charge
Should I take the country back
You're not giving me answers
I'm not getting concrete answers from you
Supplements there's actually a way to take the country back
In front of me so I'm going to go do no no no no no no you need to
To spread my links
Right by spreading legs video
Well overthrow the government
Jaws take a walk
We get back to the car you'll be able to
Just be cool one of those pictures of
F****** wall man
I want to tour the other day and there's this pictures no it's on the Capitol building
Stopping the Chinese only be achieved by more traffic coming to my website
I don't think you understand
Cross purposes
We have different ideas of what 1776
It looks like
And your 1776 you get rich
I feel like that's different than mine
You're trying to profiteer
So
Owen Harrison has been clear that allegedly
Donald Trump
Has personally asked Alex to leave this
That's weird because well they're showing Alex
You can overhear a producer
Tell Alec
Trump told the audience
At his speech
That they were going to March down Pennsylvania
Yeah
Pennsylvania State live feed from Washington DC right now Alex Johnson
Troy speaking to a large
Krowd
That exchange doesn't make much sense
That's if Trump is
Stu
But whatever
I don't care it's going down
Pennsylvania Avenue
Where am I
Transylvania
Yndc where am I
The long walk
From here
Here's where we get our first mention of the
The breaching of barriers
And I think it's really interesting because these people have started
To encroach Over The Line
Haha at the same time
You have audio of Alex
Yelling about the New World Order
Broadcast that Harrison is trying to put together
You have a really
Interesting
Juxtaposition of these two things
Mike Pence has rejected
Trump's call
He has failed to show the courage
The Donald Trump was attempting
Imbue in him
And has
McGann at the counting of the electoral votes
The same time there's word that thousands of Patriots have broken through
The
Barriers around the cap and moving towards it to the ground
And continues to speak to the scribes go back to Alex Jones
That looks bad eyesight real bad
I just
I'm starting to see a
Pattern
Dematic
Consistent
Yeah you know
11 * I think the word incitement is is overused
You know it's a very specific meaning
Yeah this is that specific meaning
Yeah it's
It's it's interesting
Because
This group does
Are not the same people
Harrison is talking about breaching these barriers
At the same time
Alex's group
Going to go to the Capitol
Heading to the Capitol
To some of the people that are in Alex's group may have gotten involved
We'll have to insert
For the time being these are two separate things that are happening
100 +
Sentence
Anthony accepted like a lot of those people who are the
First ones that were pictured
Inside
The Capitol building where qanon weirdos
I was just talkin about the Great Awakening which is such a
Like a trademark
Follower
Basically their brand
It's just it's it's a lot
But I will say
Analysis credit
Maybe
Discredit he's very insistent
To make sure people hear him say we're not going to
Knock knock
As we say estimated 1000000 people
Moving to surround the capital loan Troyer in Alex Jones now speaking through the bullhorn to the crowds who follow them
Fireworks
Keep it on the record
I think just after that you can hear someone say
Utah
I think a producer also is in his ear there
Hey they were there actually doing it so
I don't know how much Alex would be aware of it
This point because
You know communication would be difficult was that many
People in a
Such a tight space
Communication could be tough
I know that Alex does have
Quite a security detail to probably have walkie-talkies private banyak
There is a chance
Actually spoiler alert
I know that he has somebody who's inside
Yeah so like I know that like he
I have a hard time believing he doesn't
No more than
A little so I don't know if he knows
The full scope of
It seems strange
To me but also not that strange that he would be very insistent
Alright
Yeah that seems a little bit tablet
Brand for him because he always says like
Politically
I want to kill you politically
I talked to say
They're also
No
Getting people riled up while they walk
Tomorrow
It was really interesting about there.
Cuz Alex doesn't
Cardio to walk
And carry on sentences
And simultaneously Owen doesn't have a creativity
To speak more than like in Little bursts
His crutches
Three-legged race
Yeah well it's
Teamwork level of complementary Parts here
Fluid this is not
Definition
No
No no mo Stephen solid Queen
Couple quality to be found here nobody
The same thing
In terms of like they need each other in order to make the
This work
It's a block
Harrison's Bakery
Studio needed some other things
Instareport primarily
You getting worried
That staffers are evacuated
From
Capitol building
Addressing the house right now but here's an update as of less than a minute ago Hill staffers have been told to
Evacuate
The Madison Building
Things are getting tenuous here as Trump supporters and Patriots
Continue to pour towards the capital
Alex Jones himself at the head of a mask
Call of Patriots moving now towards the United States Capitol building
This
Again
Looks like bad looks bad
The government is
Pleasing
At the head of the Rebellion
Well they're going to enjoy another Rebellion that is already in progress
They're the reinforcement column that's coming in
Yeah how is Joseph
Flanking the f****** Capitol building
To certain extent I kind of
Think they at
The reason that is being presented like this
Is they still think
Going to stop
You still think they're not going to get inside
Everybody thinks that someone will stop them
Yeah
But
Because there's still this like
Kind of vibe
This is a historic day with Incredible things happening they're storming d.c.
Patriots are rushing and surrounding the capital
They're tearing down barriers
Police are struggling to maintain the crowd mace
And punches being thrown it back and forth
Two house buildings have been evacuated the house Cannon Building
Anyhow Madison Building
Have both been issued evacuation orders
Pintu said he cannot reject out
Electoral votes out right
But the
Congress themselves are objecting right now to the Arizona votes
The vibe is really positive
This is someone who's like
Really pump
To see what's happening
Was great this will never go wrong
And I know that
Now they're a lot of people who are trying to make arguments that this was antifa certainly
Superatv
Immediately
Everything is unfolding
Harrison wants you to know that this is
He's not into the
This is not blacklivesmatter folks this is not antifa
These are Patriot
And
Perhaps they finally boiled over you see the air
Filled with the Mist
Of Mace
This stinging
Gas that
The police will be
Implementing in that is also being implemented against the police
As Patriots
Wow
So I mean okay people who are Mesa
Cintas pictures
Yeah so
Check that
Just for later totally
He's very clear this is not This Is Us
Celebrate
Celebratory 5
American nationalist on Twitter
Asking President Trump to storm
The Senate chamber
This day is Young Folks
And who knows what will be
What's the weather future hold
For us again Elijah
Schaefer reports Patriots of storm the Capitol building
Ground in a breaching Federal barriers and police in Mass
And who knows what
What the day will bring lady exactly what you're talkin about to happen
It happened interesting pretty consistently calling these people Patriots sure
Thousands hundreds of thousands of people
Right now moving towards the
The capital
The mass of humanity continues
To grow as the police
Lash out
They're thin line of armored officers
A pitiful
Resistance against the
Littoral tidal wave moving towards them
Beautiful resistance against please
Patriots
They're so strong
Seterus
Reporting on what
Because he has access to a lot of different
Information. Yeah yeah
Alex may or may not
So now we go to
Publix on the street
Where everyone is chanting
For Trump cool
Cancel flight for Trump and ring out surrounding Alex Jones and Owen Shroyer the rest of the Infowars
Cruise they move towards
The capital here we see the view from inside the capitol
Of staffers they're moving it down the stairs following that evacuation order
You can't knock
See this as like
Two things that are
About the intersect
You are
Like people who work for Trump
Yeah
Right
Seems to be
USA
Yeah weird it's very weird
Consistent I would want this
I would like a mulligan on today
I don't think they can get
This show looks
It's one part because Harrison Smith is hosting
He's terrible because
I mean
You can draw your own
Conclusions I don't I don't think that
Like it would be
Wise or even
Sensible
To save her like Alex
It's inspired a lot of these actions
Do you like we already said a lot of the people who are the first photographed folks who were there
Food Network you folks and they hate
It's easy to if you don't have an awareness of those world right thing back out all the same
Do not listen to Alex
They're similar information
Speakers in terms a lot of the themes
And the narratives
In the stories that they tell
And the reality that they believe in
But they are not the same
At the same time Pastor in Fort Worth gas
That's like Nick Fuentes and
Baked Alaska we're both
In the offices
Streaming
And that's a little bit
It's f***** up
They're antifa did you know that
They were deep state secret antifa agent
Have been inspired not just see the problem
They wanted
Deep state antifa
But there wasn't any right-wing violence they would never existed so they had to
Created from the ground up
Conspiracy
Where do you live
I live down the way
Play what city
What city is Nick Montez live in
No way
Suck you
That deserved
So
Bissell just looks
Adultlook
Really really bad
Especially thinking about the people
Who are you know
It's sometimes tough
For people to get over there
Frustration with Alexa
Officials and she'll go too much empathy for them
Staffers
The people who are just on the job
And the terror
A lot of them probably fell
Being whisked away to
Secure locations
I can't even imagine what that would be like
And
It's really f***** up
To know that that is what a lot of people are experiencing
And for this
Just to be like they're kind of relishing
Harrison is as well on air
Now in the
List
Expected thing ever
Trump is not
Going to the capital after he said we're all going to the capital capital
Huge
Unprecedented
Krowd
Is moving towards
The capital
As we speak as the debate rages inside
President Trump has apparently returned it to the White House that's the word that we are receiving
From Washington he said he
Was going to go to
The Capitol building
He's gone to the White House
Instead many people on Twitter encouraging him
Do storm the Senate along with
Supporters and what we're seeing here are the
Independent journalist videos
As Trump supporters move
Once again inexorably towards the Capitol Building yeah I wonder why
He would send everybody towards the capital and then not go there himself almost crazy
Now they're willing to Die For This
Because he's willing to
To die for that
Yeah
This dude
F****** potster
So you remember that Ragtime music was playing earlier
Joyous
Abdul
Describe
The joyous
Beat
Atmosphere of
The event earlier today has
Showered and turned to rage as the fury of
Trump supporters and Patriot's Crossing United States
Overflows
And expresses itself
On the outside of the capitol
So beat the editorial tone it appears to me to be
Pretty consistently
Righteous and
That is what is motivating
Said they are right
Hate to do this they are right to storm the capital information be right there with them
Are you saying that the founding fathers were wrong Mike
Would stop this
Someone's got to or Elsa Khan
Restitution has been
Episcopal Mike Pence
King George
We got to take him out
Excitement
Kind of about this because there's nothing
Harrison can really do other than be the guy who's calling
I'm the guy with the
It's beyond are well this is going to
And getting this was as a
24 minutes ago and since then we've seen
24 minutes of
Rising
Aggression Rising crowds more police
Building evacuation
And reaction from across the nation is
Largely excitement as far as I'm concerned
This is again truly incredible and will continue to update and bring you
More videos
Yeah it was
But I was getting
I took a took a slightly different temperature from the country based on
Since I was getting
Yeah
It seems like everybody soured real quick
Everybody was like oh no I didn't want
I saw a lot of people responding in ways that
We're kind of like
Oh
Oh my
Like I I can't believe I didn't see
This
Possibility
I think it's very funny
From from
Where I
Sure
At the same time
I think that had this not have happened
This week
You and I would have had a show where we would have said another dumb rally what do you what do you expect is going to happen
S'more just edging
Towards the hope that something like this would happen
I'm not
Surprised that it did but I'm shocked
You know that but yeah I think there's a lot of people who are
And I see a lot of like
Scales falling through people's eyes with some kind of
Flippant
Like I told you so
You know like I get on Arlo
I'm glad that I haven't
Casino Lotto
Yeah because I think that's really
Yeah and I hope
The people who
You want engagement at your business
I know I know
I think that if people see right-wing extremist
Storm Inga lighthouse
And I call this is what people have been talking about for a while that is fun
No need to shame anybody as long as they remember
That this is a problem
Tomorrow to it didn't stop yesterday
Today I mean spoiler alert
We don't know what Alex's responses to it but Trump is basically
Been like an hour I would
Never it's over a reminder that doesn't
Yeah that's the problem
The reaction to it reminded me so much
My partner was watching a documentary the other day
And they some
One of those bad guys it was like a
Documentary about a small town that it gone
Rogue with a
Police Department
Man in the Sheriff's Department
And she's like
Can you believe this
This guy thinks that the sheriff
Is the highest constitutional power in the land and I was like
Well let me tell you about
I-16
That's what I'm saying like all these people watch this and
It's the same reaction of of life
I know you thought that that
Couldn't be real
Oh but it is
16 of the country
I was
Desperately graph
Any more child
So
24 Harrison do again is just
Righteous and
That is the name of the
We do know is that the
Washington establishment is
Grambling any and all officers
They have
At their command in order to deal with this
Massive outpouring of anger Fury and righteous in
Indignation
Coming from
The Trump supporter you can there see
We have the
Fox News Feed up and even they are
I having trouble maintaining the Integrity of their signal
I meant just righteous indignation these people have been pushing
Just to the point where this disc
Responses that the only
Only thing that can
Mdwfp
Created an imaginary reality where and I have
Pushpay
Push too far
Going on in other states
As well there's some f*****-up stuff happening at elsewhere
Harrison covers this
Scary
Los Angeles as well as stop
Bastille rally lining the streets
Hundreds of
Trump supporters
People
Cheering it on on Twitter saying insane drag him out saying go into the Capitol building
And drag the traitors out
That does not
Seem like something that could have been impossible
Things gone slightly differently
I could
Some harm coming
Into representatives in Congress members
Now there are people walking around with
Zip ties I saw those pictures I didn't have a chance to look into
Into them enough to feel really confident
Yeah that was
Really scary
Sky trust enough to
Definitely. Me like I have to go
Search doubt ever you cannot just remind
I did I did
I kept back that
2%
Of my own
Looking into it but I don't think it's I just don't know what.
But that's scary as hell
The even the possibility
That is what
Someone was up to
Take hostages or something
I put a citizen's arrest
Humor
Like it's horrifying
Wow absolutely different
Dinner takes
Terrifying but it is also deeply funny
That's the problem
That's where I'm I'm struggling
Because
We are looking at
A group of people
Who stormed the f******
Capital bill
But we are also looking at a series of
People smoking weed and Nancy Pelosi's office
So
That deeply funny
Sorry
Harrison is going on
Here this is anything other than just like this is really positive coverage
Are people such as at Dana Lash
Saying stop this
Do Trump supporters who are moving towards
The castle other people saying get in there and
Tear them out of here we see
My God
Images are just incredible massive
Numbers of Patriots
Storming the Capitol building
Texas Flags waving American flags waving
And masses of humanity have
Apparently broken past
The police barricades
Good for keeping them
Off the steps and away from the Capitol Building day have been
Torn down and
The people have moved on to
That raised
Platform and are scaling
Scaffolding that was set up
So at this point you know that we don't have people inside
Yeah but you do have
An awareness that there are people who are
A large Mastiff Oak
Who are not seeming to have all that much resistance
Authority
Who are making their way towards the Capitol building
You have
People online who are expressing a desire for people to be dragged out
Give people who want Trump
Coming
Lead a charge on the Senate
Do you have that awareness
When you have that
In the in the sort of context of what's going on
You hear clip like this
And you're like you just want somebody to kill
You just want you want somebody to kill someone you don't like
Incredible this crowd continues to swell
What was it I mean
I've lost track of time that he was less than an hour ago
An hour ago
That President Trump finished his speech and that massive crowd of hundreds of thousands probably upwards of a million people
Surrounding the Washington Monument
And all the way to the White House
Finished watching that speech by President Trump and moved towards the US Capitol
And by the time that
Everything update from ilhan Omar current to Capitol Buildings are lockdown and everyone is Sheltering in place
Case look that's where I'll know more is everyone
A what
Just kidding
The joke is a from this vantage point you can tell where she is
You know there are tons of people who are who are storming
The Capitol building
Hey wouldn't be fun if I wasn't
Wannabe
It's just joking
That's where she is
Yeah that's
That is person who weave
Expressed
Extensive hatred for
Yeah
Even if I believe
Somebody was joke
When they said that
Aportes
Oh yeah and it is not joke
So don't
Don't give me this
Jake Abel
I would say that Harrison
Pragmatic to a fault
It does not care
At all about
The people in the
In the Congress building
Sure
Get where he's coming from
In terms of like there are safety precautions
Then place
Tiger our evacuation routes
So I guess
I get weird
He's coming from
Seem super cala
I guess
Just like
Who cares
The people inside are did any
Danger
Congressmen and women and Senators I don't think are at much of a threat we know
There's one thing they take very very seriously it is their own personal well-being and their own
Security there are tunnels
Of course
Criss-crossing like
Spiderwebs throughout all of DC
And there's almost no risk
Of them having to try to escape through a crowd or
Having a bunker down in the Capitol building if they have Escape Routes
More than they need so again I do not think there's actually a bodily threat to anybody in the chambers at this moment
Anything to concern their continuing to
Are you continuing to debate
Without so much
As a look over their shoulder asked you
The doors being broke down or anything like that disassembly
A
Massive protests that is
Refusing to stay quiet any longer that is making themselves known that is
Not stopping at the barricades not
Kowtowing and adhering to the
Police report
Betrayed us time and time again but instead
Are pushing forward to take over what is
At the heart of it
AR
Building
I find it hard to believe
They would be
Recovering
Let's say
Black lives matter protest at the White House
I seem to work
Call
When
How old is summer
Whenever those
Large fences
Yeah that people were up again
Standley Lake
Do you know yelling at
Then
It wasn't
You know
A situation where everyone safe inside they've got a situation roommate
Right
I don't know it just seems a little bit
Selective
I-290 like the
They have more Escape tunnels than they need
That's such a funny way of putting it
They got more than they even need this is the type of
What thing we're wasting taxpayers money on
Too many Escape
Don't go anywhere
It's like the future of a joke where they're carrying the tanker full of oil and he's like
This has 5,000
I would ever break something is 1001
It'll be great if there is like there's so many Escape tunnels down here there's like
Tooth out of control
But now
That's where all that
If if the Capitol Building turned into the Scooby-Doo B where they're all going up through the tunnel and exiting 12 are they closed
The great so good
So at this point people have breached the bill
This is where I think a lot of people
Around the
Country in the world were like
OSHA
Senators
The vice president
The congressman
Now no doubt making their way towards
The security of the underground tunnels to ask Court them away
From the threat
They're supposed constituents
Angry Furious and now venting that frustration
On
The system that has betrayed them time and time again this is just incredible
Woolfolk you're watching Infowars
So you got people coming in in the
Constituents
There's a certain part of me that almost
Is like
Good on you for sticking with
Longer than most
To the right-wing media did
Well I don't know like they were already at the point where they're like this is wrong
Suspenders like this is what we got
This is what we wanted
I wanted I want to disagree with the phrasing
Good on you.
That's remarkable.
That you are still you're still just working everybody at this point everyone was cutting
Realizes that you thought
Oh no there's nobody behind me
Privilege
Course at least I would say my estimation a million
Trump supporters
Having moved from throughout DC internal converging on the capital this is revolution in progress
This is a major historic moment
In history of the United States
Does a privilege and an honor to be here sharing it with you
And bringing you updates just
As soon as possible
I suspect that he may be more of a
A True Believer then a lot of people at Infowars
And I also think he's a dork
Anyway
I'm just saying
Yes it is a historic moment
But it will probably be remembered more for
An idiot and a headdress
Smiling carrying a podium
Then
I will be a resident
In order to just
Defile out of this
I think Harrison probably has a good scent that like
Like this
Going to have to make this palatable
To somebody more Normie
Parts of the audience
As if in Fort Worth has a lot of that
The only way that they can do this
Is by being like the left protest Alive stuff
We've seen six months
Or more
Violent protests
Burning down entire cities
Aimless
Pointless
Destruction being right across the United States by
Liberal and communist agitators
All to the point of
Trying to tear down our system now we see
Not the system fight back
But those who love
America fight back
Patriots now
Taking over the entire Capitol steps
Continuing to wave the American flag the Gadsden flag
The tree of Liberty flag
Trump flag
He's taking it over
It is done this is what happens when Americans rise up is what happened
When Patriots
Do what
The Communists have been trying to do
Uber so long
This doesn't look great
I want to eat those words I would like to
To print those words out now would like to hear
If you didn't eat those
I don't think this is going to age great
Think Alex might be needing to fire Harrison soon it's not because you didn't take calls on the American Journal
This is something else
From the authority
Might have to pretend a lot of
This stuff didn't this wasn't what we did Infowars employee
The views expressed by Harrison Smith do not represent
I never met that guy
He's an independent contractors you know that you found those Soros contracted a left report on Alex
Anyway
This is all just a global
West Mandy pushed
Patriots
I have in my notes Here
This is dramatically Pro storming
Coverage
Time and time again that the American people have shrug and taking the blows
On the back
Without so much as a whimper in protest
Finally
They have pushed
Too far
After stealing our last resort we always knew in the back of our minds and back our heads we had the numbers
We had the will we could
Through the electoral process maintain some semblance of control over
What is supposed to be our representative democracy
Our Republic
Well they stole that
From us they took away the
The final lifeline
They destroyed
The final pressure valve
And now the Rage of the American people
Overflows as Patriots
Storm into the United States
Capital waving Trump Flags waving American flag
Waving the Gadsden flag
Taking over the steps
Pushing through the doors
Enforcing an evacuation
Of our Representatives
As they halt
Devote
Counting process
He's loving
Yeah
Yep this is the best day of Harrison
Career is so funny listening to that in retro
Chris back just because
It that like
This is an ocean wave that
It's coming at all I can all I can think in my head is now
You guys have been terrorists edging for a long time
And you're idiots came too soon
That's what
Yeah and you're going to end up having to make the best of it
Alex
Can get that sense
Once he shows up
Harrison isn't
Experience to know if he doesn't really know how to play the game
That Alex needs
To play in order to be profitable
In situations
Like that is going to take some
Find threading
Yeah if you if you
Has Harrison actually believes that there's a chance
But this is going to lead to a real Revolution or Trump is going to stay in office
Yeah nonsense
Alex's in d.c.
Nothing really
Can't quite get a hold of got to go to break
Live update from Alex Jones more on the other side
The capital has fallen to Patriots are in control
The Patriots are in control the capital has
Fallen
She's able to get a hold of Alex Fair
Talk to him Alex's just ramble I hilarious
F****** capitalism
Fallen is the report
Do you know some one thing that I like to
Is sometimes while
The craziest s*** is going on
Screening on my computer
With just like a
Stock feed
The capital has
Has Fallen
Patriots have taken over
Stocks go up by like
Like notes do you think
Stocks wood
Just stay the same
If they
Entire United
States had been overthrown
Well I mean Patriots it come on
I know that the
The stock market lives and dies by the reportaj
Exactly
And said he's the most trusted news men of Our Generation
Self-driven Cronkite
Selves
Paper of record Millennial Chromecast
Goldie young Grey Lady
Old wolf in sheep's clothing Blitz
So
There's a nice little thought here is okay
We stopped Bastille
I just the sheer crowds
All over the the capitol steps waving stop the
Steel signs
Waving American
Flags for the
For the time being at least
This deal has been stopped
We have
Accounting
The
No longer counting the votes no longer
Debating the certification
It is all
We going to a halt results East
Continue as
The
Lawmakers
And the other
Capitol Hill staffers
Flea
I just had this picture in my head of
Harrison Smith
A fighter pilot out yet
Totally 100%
I don't know if
We can print up a better Dewey defeats Truman
We stopped
Bastille at least temporarily
Hennessy
Good work Buddy
So there's
Stuff going on
Protesters
RightWay big dogs
Just salting
Officers
And Harris
Pretty excited about that
My God now the protesters have gotten their hands on fire extinguishers and are spraying them at the people
The Congressional staffers and media
Members of the media
We're attempting to film them they're getting a face full of
Fire extinguisher gas
As police continue to radio and we heard
Over the radio
From the US Capitol Police
We have lost
Control repeat we have lost
Control
Control now seated to
The patriots who have breached
The capital
Alex did like days worth of coverage about people yelling at Sarah Huckabee Sanders
8 bike
Every private
Citizen is entitled to the right
To go eat at arrest
What is they had sprayed her with a fire
Wow that's
Harbor Freight
Did you instead strictly speaking that is assault
And we've already heard him talking about punching and Mason
Towards
The the officers
Three instances that
Harrison is very keenly aware of
Violence
It's being done by
These people again
The cops
No I mean
Like obviously
No situation is perfect
Any protest
And I don't think that you can
Dyke
Respond
To the entirety of
The group just based on the actor
Tenth of an inch
Individual but those people
Should definitely have been treated if
What they're doing
Thing is not appropriate
Property Dam
That is directed
Towards
Movie harm and hurting hurting another person but
No salt
Anyway I just want to make
Clearline there because
Harrison later we'll pretend that he's not aware of any violence no nothing no violent actions
Also
Interesting Lee
Harrison thrilled that they've stolen police equip
Control now seated to the
The patriots who have breached
Capital
And are moving ever more
Farther into this Capitol Building people dress
Pioneers people carrying riot shields
I've been stripped from the Capo
Bull City Police
Maga hat
Confederate flags
American flags Gadsden flag
I can't I just can't imagine
And of the picture
Left-wing protesters have stolen riot shields were police and they've entered the Stout
They can't imagine you being like
This is
Protest
America's Fallen
I guess there isn't that much different
Honestly
Yeah man
Weird
Weird to think of the number of dead
That there would have been its
This was a left-wing crowd
Do the people who are
So many people would have been killed
I think you're right
Add stop to litigate that kind of what if
You know that you know that whole like
I was how is it that so many people could do the
I thought if you went for
For the Capitol Building you would just
Get mowed down
Yeah you know
If this was a left-wing protest
Oh believe me you were
It seems like
Seems that way
Yeah
Harrison still giving positive coverage
Of this
Event
Point
He does know that they shot
Tear gas in the chamber
Yeah and
He's kind of aware that someone got shot
Right doesn't know any of the details about it but he's aware that someone has reports
Took someone's been shot
Guitar
Disclose TV protesters are smashing the doors to the US House chamber that seems that we saw just a second ago of the
Furniture being piled up in a attempt to
Prevent or at least
Waylay or delay the breaking into the house chamber there
US Senate chamber has been evacuated and senators are being taken to a secure location house members are being instructed to
Put on mask
As tear gas is now inside
The US Capitol Dome folks this is
Again unprecedented this
Is history being made
As we speak
Slowly
This is like
Would severe
Like the situation has deteriorated too
And Harrison still definitely cool with it
You saying
Yeah they're rioting
Great we took back the capitol
The security of the Capitol building has been utterly devastated
And decimated
And the rider or Riders why the hell not right
The Riders the protesters the Patriots the Americans the Trump supporters
The revolutionaries
Have taken the capital the US capital has fallen to the American people
This day will go down in history ladies and gentlemen in you're getting it all live here and infowars.com
Make no mistake about this would still be the
The tone if it had been
Successful
Totally
It like
This is it would've been more
Yes yeah
Continued
Fall Apart
Just leave
Bottle the
The feeling of
Joy that he felt
For almost a short.
Cuz that must have been really nice
Yeah but it also becomes
Embarrassment that he's got to feel now
Cuz this was recorded
That's why I would only borrow the joy and I would enjoy that like a cold glass of water
That Joe is delicious. Joey causes the hair.
You can keep the embarrassment inside made out of BU it unfortunately
The Hangover effect
Realizing you were so naive so f***
Being stupid
Anyway
At this point Harrison is heard
Midnight last night but he is aware at that point that someone hit the
Benshot
And so now he's reporting
He's heard that someone got shot in
The arm
Just got this information not confirmed but we have reports of a woman shot in the arm
Attempting to breach
The chamber so we have guns drawn inside the chamber
Furniture piled against the door
The
Security is firing out
Through the door and is apparently
Shot woman in the arm
So this is the reporting that he's giving
Based on preliminary
Stop which is incorrect but you know sometimes
As a
Informations coming and you can make
Mistakes here and there
I'm not going to hold it against
Them too harshly
Blame him for being so goddamn boring
I've got to assure you all Alex will be coming back eventually we will get
Alex
How can you
Think that you are living through a c
Successful over
Overthrow the United States government by your side
Still be this boring
Yeah
Well I mean
I mean on some level he knows he took over for David Knight
Pizza Hut
Who knows where the bread cutter liver
Yeah you got a big shoes to fill
I need a boring guy another boring guy boring guy and taste my boring understood
Relief
So at this point there's a video going around of some
People commandeering a window washing sure rig
Humped
Oh my God
This is amazing person video
Of the protesters they seem to have commandeered
A window washing
Platform
In a raising themselves up to
To the second floor to perhaps
Reach the windows there
Trump Flags waving American flags waving
Shots have been fired me reports of one woman shot
From a protester a female protester has been shot
By the Capital Security presumably who is inside
The house chamber there
Furniture piled up against
The door refrigerator trying to get through that door shots were fired
Through the window
Dorin seemingly struck
A protestor these Leon confirmed
Reports
That we're receiving
From less than a minute
Ago and will continue to bring you updates
As we get them folks this is
The revolution
And it's only going to be televised on Infowars
Dot-com Amarillo
Stork
Loser loser
You really think it's this is only going to be covered by
What a Virgo
We are getting reports
The Death Star is going to oh no I can
I can see it
Luke Skywalker has
Commandeered a window washing
Vehicle
And he's slowly making his way towards the exhaust for its
We are going to be televising that I loved the entire way I love this
Dumb dumb ass kind of thing where it is
Is it would be like going to be like
Richard Nixon is resign
That's only going to hear
My channel
Everyone's going to cover that
I am sad to report that JFK
Has been
Assassinated
No one else is saying s*** about it by pretending this isn't like a gigantic
Take news story
Going to dominate 3 new cycle for a while
Ridiculous
So
At this point
Harrison
Do I don't know exactly how it happened
Maybe by way of images or video
Harrison come
It's the realization
The shooting is worse
Then he had realized
And this is.
Someone's arm
Now we're not have
Did it tounsia
Dramatically
Very notice
And here we see the bloody stretcher and a woman
Oh my gosh being
We got that putting pressure on a wound it look like
We heard before she was shot in the arm that look like he was shot in the chest
Perhaps the collarbone
But absolutely
Covered in blood as she's rushed away
From the capital
This may be the
First casualty of the second American Revolution
This woman who is
Presumably oh my God they're pumping her
Not if they're pumping her chest
That means she was most likely
Unresponsive that woman
May have died or lie sustained
Ace
Critical energy
So I don't know if he knows how to handle a lot of this stuff
This is pretty
This is tough because you've been
Spending your entire day
Sort of teasing people towards doing something like that
Celebrating as it happened
And now the reality that someone has been
Been shot and is probably dead
Yeah
It's tough
It's tough to cover all of that
Especially when you're someone like you don't have the skill it is it is in
The real world
In his world
In the world that they all believe in
That should be
Well that should be an expected casualty of your f****** Revolution are you telling me are you telling me that you
You think you're going to overthrow a f***
Country and then you're going to get all windy and sad when someone gets shot and I think guys
F*** off and I think there's some decent
Instincts
On Harrison's part with
Saying like the first
First casualty of the American Revolution keeping it in the pocket
How's the Patriot lure
Exactly but he needs to build in real-time in order
At the same time
I don't like
Emotional
Standpoint and from a
Performance standpoint I don't
2 cm
Being able
Keep up his
Who's Karen
No I doubt cuz of the character
And because this as much as he's about
I understand that somebody's dead in the real world that's a
The f****** tragedy
What I'm saying
Is that these people are imagining themselves
As f****** revolutionary
And then they all quit and cried
Because somebody died
You cannot scream 1776 at me and then be like
Wow somebody got
Oh my God explained Alex's angle on it
Much better as soon as of a mystery to me
I am not entirely sure
I just don't think
He's very good
You supposed to be doing
But I just don't think it does very well
That's why you got to get
Alex and Owen on the phone getting real
Trying to talk
Tijeras
It's Good Friday
In Tucson in that video you know that everybody's
Alex just keeps yelling in the background
Contradicting the entire day's cover a love it
Daytime on here right now
Understory
When was Atlanta founded the first started
Joe
Breaking that down momentarily
Metallica going to be explained that auntie
Have
You turned of involvement
I was going to look bad
Now we got it
If read this needle baby
The man
These white people are so f****** entitled
They think they're entitled to a revolution without getting
Or looking bad yeah exactly
So Alex is decreeing in the background yelling while I was on the phone that their commercial free
Commercial Freon all shows commercial free
Martial law
National Guard it's absolutely insane
Albany
Minute Trump announce he was going to come speak
Antifa
I need pads and arm pads
Track a place to Stage the trigger of that
Stampy
I guess at this point he had taken the phone
I'm from Bart from Wichita
Have the lines yet
No No Nanette and Alex can just rattle off these
Steve's business narrative
With without any
Nonno and there and it could be a switch Eclipse instantly and just below are we doing antifa now okay I'll switch to my auntie
Depot rambling nonsense
If I if I have my timeline right now
National Guard definitely had not been but no they are not point
But
This is business.
Because this is a direct contradiction
Of
Harrison's narrative that he's been building for hours at this point
Watching this event happen lol
This is Patriots who have righteous indignation
Would push too far right now
Snot
Antifa provocateur
And they're the ones who storm things
Patriots were trying to keep
Peaceful
Course they could put up with much more
God dammit
Completely contradictory narrative riding solo
Now
Owen is on the same phone call
With Alex
And he is there
Keep contradicting out he's got number 326 Sodexo tough to really put this in his right because here's the deal were not violent
Lucien Ares
But
They've been taking our country
All countries occupied and you can debate all day long what the appropriate response is
The point is we finally have a response
And we haven't any fight in our Congressman that any fight in our legislators
And so this is what can happen if we the people going to fight again
We did not come here as violent revolutionaries
But
The history is definitely being made right now I don't know what today is
Turning points
It will change
The course of American History or this is just the Nexus
Of the beginning
This is a direct contradiction of
Alex he's closer to the narrative
Harrison has been selling 303
No
The thing that
Difficult time with his like we can have different opinions about like
I don't know
Weather weather pastas good
Like maybe you don't like it
We have different
Agree the pasta exist
I
Begrudgingly admit
They have
Fundamental contradiction
About the reality of what has happened
And what it means
And everything
These two things cannot coexist together
And they're asking Their audience
To believe
That it's
Just sort of a little
Do we have
Interpretation
Something no it's not it's very important
I think that's something that's under appreciate
About
I think the difference
Prince that we're seeing between
These in the black lives matter protest
Is
Kind of
Built around
FL
The fact that all of these right-wing ding dongs
Are fighting a different anime
Like they all have their own conception of the evil government whether it's lizards or anything
It's all completely different from the person standing next
Things they scream but
Deep down they're all fighting a
Fight yeah ended Horton
Everybody was fighting the
The same singular
One of the things that I actually think is at the
The core of why I disagree with you
About the the nature of what happened on what
Wednesday at work
You're saying they all look stupid and is going to have a deflationary effect
I look at this
And I worry
That
The way that it will be used
This event
Will be used
Used in the same way.
Things like Ruby Ridge
Charlotte and Waco were used in the 90
Right in the aftermath of those events
You had
The the Rocky Mountain rendezvous
Where you had a bunch of different right-wing extremist groups who also didn't see eye-to-eye about what their enemy was
Some people thought it was
Just
Big-government something thought it was the Jews
Ain't they all got together and we're like well we got to work
Together
That is what emboldened
The militia right wing
Community right in the 90
I do worry that this will have
Galvanizing a
Especially with you have a death
Shorted
Spoiler alert is
Something that Alex is going to
To try and use
How to make a martyr out of
That is going to game that Alex and Zach
The plank right
You have a lot of the essential elements
That you would need to
To try and create
This
Focal point
Where you could get
People of different
Like what
How could you get qanon folks and Alex to work side-by-side
Seems like
This is this is something
That we could
Reach
Toutant / I get that I think
The difference
For me between the Ruby Ridge and those are
You've given our that
They were
In response to an aggressor
There were people coming
Them
As well
It was not a
It was not a bunch of
Moron
And the cup
Cops let them go
There was a conflict
We don't have to do this I know we're not
To all of that
I will say that perception
Is what's more important
Then reality
Midterms of patriot lower
The story
It can be told
People in the rolls
But they need to be in
In order to make
The story
You would see as a bunch of riders going home right
Stupid as being exactly what's needed
I will be interested
To see how they do it
I'm not saying that is what's going to happen
As I was seeing all this happen
That was the fear that I feel
Is the worry that I have
About the
Pieces of this
And the way that I see Alex
Responding
To understand
Is kind of
Anyway everybody's contradict
Other in a way that is
It's just it it's incomprehensible if you're a listener I guess you just got to be on team Owen and Harrison or team Alex
Whatever or whomever
Now Harrison is realize that
Someone got shot probably dead
You know what these protestors they were completely non-violent the f*** out of the only violence I have seen perpetrated
It's so far beyond
You know one or two
You punches in in return for
A punch thrown by a police officer
The only violence I have seen has been to be cold-blooded Point Blank Shooting of a woman in the chest
By the
Capital cold-blooded Apple police rather
That's the only violence the memories of people shooting fire extinguishers a cops
That's more like
You know
Tough guys here
So now the entire town is kind of train
For Harrison and he's been
Application mode
And it's almost
Entirely for her
Play long stretch of time
I'm talking about how the last
Protest shooting
Blessed sister saying just shoot them all you know if you dare protest against us
We we can protest when you burn your city down for a year-and-a-half we can just do you know for a year
For four years we can just
Obstruct everything we can destroy everything we can murder people in Cold Blood Vice magazine will
Give us a
A good 30 minute documentary Norte
The Bagel Man
By his death that's reaction you get if you are a protester
On the left
This is really Halo for me but it seems to be like their mic drop moment
Just keeps coming back to that are
It's just
I don't care
Iris
Hehehehe
Ted Cruz
Responses
I think Harrison two little bit surprised
To learn
The Ted Cruz is not on board
Ted Cruz he says quote
Those storms in the capital need to stop now
The Constitution protects Beast
Protest violence from left or right is always wrong I've not seen any vinyl
I've not seen any violence from the protesters yet
Am I wrong
Tell me if I seen forever I seen violence with a protester that you have
Earlier sir
Impact
Exchange
Harrison better
F****** hope
That some of the people that he's talking about in the
What you saying they did cuz if so they're going to
No no
The people who have been able to successfully break into
I sent it offices
And Congressional offices
I did so with such
Witness that the
Protesters there
Where are the
That staffers and
Congressman and Senators there were
Unable to even grab their information grab their papers
Or even shut down their computer so now unlocked
And open to anybody those computers are being accessed by the protesters
Who themselves are
Gathering information
Downloading hard drives are stealing at the hard drives out right
We can expect
To see The Fallout from this continue on
For a very long time but I remind you again after a year
Complete chaos a year of protest a year of
Literally tens of
Thousands
Violent riot
I'm not saying I'm not saying that it's
It's impossible that some people
Some stuff for my tab access some stuff but like
That way
Is that a very serious like national security problem
Simplot that's something I don't
People will take lightly
What did Chandler bring home from the White House
Governor's f****** hard drive
It's a tumor is a motherboard
What are we going to do we got to get rid of it
Airbnb good to like
Like if these f****** ding-dongs didn't
Livestream themselves without masks on AR stealing
May be privileged
Classified information
It's a good
Sing the
They decided to storm one of the least heavily surveilled building
Without masks
You know that relief that Capitol building
I'm glad they just don't have many cameras there or recording equipment of any kind 22 like
Were they filming was George
Jimmy Fallon in that Boston
Sup pawns 11
So
This point
Alex's
Suggested that it's antifa that is ARCA
Restraining order show
Hearing all this
Is this is still real to him man
We've heard time and time again how valuable
Protests are how good protests are
Antifa is only an idea how black lives matter is
Simply a set of beliefs
But if you don't believe you're racist
And we watched silently
Because we always knew that the end of the day we had our vote we always knew
That when it came right down to it the American system
Powerful enough
Flexible enough
Is that enough to vote
Maintain
We knew that if we just
Trusted
And
Exerted are
Rights
As members of a republican citizen
Of this democracy
That we
Good
Regain our footing and get back on track well
That boat has been stolen from us
If you're wondering what is inspiring the
Overwhelming
Activity that we're seeing here in Tagalog
Supporters move into the Capitol building
And starts to destroy things
It's that that last release valve has been
Taken destroyed
Perverted and prevented from being accessed in use
Bye
The people who
For so long have patiently stood by and watched their country
Literally burned around them
So I guess it wasn't antifa provocateur
I guess it was that people
Had the right to vote stolen
Enough
Time is the only thing
Remedy that
Yeah but it was antifa who exploited that to make them
Do things that they didn't want to do
Even though the things that they did
They did wanted
I bet I bet is like
If push
Alex might be able to come up with that but that's not
Cancel that one
This next clip is really where I found myself
Saying oh Alex
Oh no
This is sad
This is really indicative of how Alex operates
Mike down for this
Because
I'm going to talk about this shoot
He listened to Alex's respond
Barely have been shot inside the Capitol and what that is
We got a safe location because it was just too crazy out there on the streets but that was capital
So I don't know
Point is of the shooting having taken place
So Alex
Based on
Nothing
His responses that's probably
The shooting
Probably fake
Alex I saw somebody going out there were to go out there in case you want to use that little smiley face
Andromache
Video you can't you can't tonight
That's just
Random
Just anything he's just
Make us look bad let's say it's fake first and let's just see if we can get away with
What states did in her mouth
He has been Now refuted by both of his employees
Alex
Know who are not getting the line cannot
Do that are not getting a lot of theirs video
So Alex makes up another
So now Pence has also betrayed President Donald Trump so
A man on a on a mountain
By himself and he has we the people fighting for him the police confirm
Making up that confirmation confirmation
That he's just making that up because he has to
He has to admit that someone got shot
Because of
The pushback that he got from his employees yet but he can't let it be as serious
As it looks like it might be more shot in the leg
He has to say I got word that it was
Confirm
Call May.
So Alex has decided
Antifa
Explains his evidence
It's for this
Sabeing
Incredibly generous
I would describe this as he imagined
But it was
Bookstore militarily come in
Once again
Pull up real quick
Experts
Driving 40 minutes over there from a big rally for a peaceful protest at the Capitol
People are attacking the police
All this crazy stuff happening all this crazy stuff going down
All the crazy stuff and folding
We have to wait until we have the witnesses
We have to win this week
We got it all
We got all three kinds of headed
Alex's basically just saying hey I thought they might do
We thought there's this guy
He was dressed at amazing how good inteva is he was
That's exactly like you would expect somebody at this rally to be dressed he was screaming things that like
I scream so you know that he was antifa cuz they wouldn't say the thing but I ain't we all know that
Mostly out of work
Even on his neck
How good is antifa a provocateur
To one of them do drawing about this is the kind of go back
Can Ford from Harrison during summer
Reporting
And Alex doing
I am so Harrison
You know I would say
One of the most important things in a
Situation like this
Is not
To just say anything
What do you have it
10 situation
You have
A lot of information coming in
Yeah some of it might be wrong
You might want to
Some things right
I understand that there is an impulse
To report everything as quickly as you can
Sometimes
It's best to take a breath
And wait a little while
Harrison is from a different
This is a ton
Confirm but it does say that protesters are engaging u.s. Secret Service
Hand-to-hand combat
Confirm but not sure if that's it
Troll post
Or not
Usually not good on your news Outlet to read something and then afterwards when
Sounds stupid coming out of your mouth
I got it might be trolling
Ladies and gentlemen I am just getting worried that Olympus Has Fallen out right now that my
Patrol
Hawaii earlier I
That d
Capitalize fall
Controlling
Has Chinese takeover with a new world order the country
How to steal the election
No you're the one starting all this
You're the one they're going to pay just like Hitler
And then you know this is this is what happens this is the result this is like if you don't if you don't deal with a cancer
Cancer and you don't deal with it until it's too late they basically only have one shot
Directions to chemotherapy radiate the hell out of you and hope you can survive that's what we're going through
Cancer in this country for decades of communist Chinese takeover for decade we've been
Occupied by tyrants for decades and ignoring it
Whoa
That's pretty severe yeah
I mean we're at a point now where they have no reason to be like
Gung ho
It's trouble
Bunch of idiots
This is
This is how it was going
To go
How is this taking them by
Soles
So much
Well I think that they're used to
Acting in ways that would
Conceivably lead to something
Sing like this
Admit it never happened
And so I think that used to that outcome
It's kind of surprising
Tubi
The stars have aligned in such a way.
Other influences
Are actually making the tap
I don't know if they know how to react
And that's why I think you see a little bit of flailing
You see
Contradictory narratives being thrown out you have
Alex trying to insist
It's antifa but then at the same time that last clip seemed to it sounds like he was saying it's great
I don't know
It's with weird
I think it's because the only thing they're not allowed to say
Is the only thing that would make any sense for any of them to say which is just
You guys weren't supposed to actually do it
This was about
Stealing your money
Yeah
And now look at
This is tough for business you
Yeah yeah
It's it's
So it in order to really threaten
The needle successfully one
Everything we have to do is cast aspersions on the people who act
Actually did follow through
With it so
They're people who lives
Speculated that the queue shaman
Yeah weirdo guy and he was
Yeah come on buddy who else is antifa
Give me morning evening
People now in vet now looking into some of the
People that have broken in there seeing what you's a look
Officiously like
Pianist
Funniest things are seeing incredible shots
Inside the capitol Dome
Who's the guy with the tattoos that are 1000 hammer in
Collateral
Video game Dishonored
This isn't really
Oh so he had corvo's little tattoo
Darkseid so funny
Nick Fuentes
Baked Alaska
They were all your show
He was with you
Conveniently ignore that
What a bunch
Is he he's going to be back on in
Horsewright probably
Hassan soon I don't know what happened
On Thursday keeping this as a bottle episode of when I got a Monday will cover
Just because of the
Through stupidity of all this
But yeah I would assume
At least by the time the weekends over 20
Text Willis made
Some sort of virus
Play for real
Harrison's job
Betty White
The Alex Jones
And we end up going into the War Room
Smooth
Of course
Are all hosted by Harrison
He has to believe he's done
Okay
He's tapped out he's out of
I mean
To be fair
He was on there for a long time in straight hours holdup at least in terms of like
Wheatley fall in
Which is
Phrase but I'll give it to him
I don't know I don't think I could do 7 hours
I don't think I absolutely
7 hours
Yeah, I would have been like guys we shouldn't
Be doing this is not
For us right now
Stop that was really funny
Is that Alex
Oh and also I mean not to
Make a note to add more praise on Butler
Like Alex it said we're cutting
Commercials
Basically the last hour that he's been on air
But like I keep saying
The 4th hour
Big wild
Is no idea again
Time zones
It's there's a rebel
Little bit funny
Because you can hear the producers voice
I've not met you know I would make that mistake.
Now with the mistake I would not make
Is Tom Palmer violent revolution is hosting the Wardrobe
This guy sucks
He's pretty
Scary
Local news has reported that protesters have moved inside the Kansas house Chambers
Well I'm getting additional reports from Kentucky and Georgia the protesters are making their way inside the state
Capital
Building
What seems to have
Set this off of course
Is all of this happened near seconds after Mike Pence
Announce his ultimate betrayal of President Trump
And said that he would not buy for him in the Electoral College
I would say that everybody has like
Real different vibe
Episode that was
Pentas
He was the one who instigated this whole thing
Well here's use the / would say
Harrison
Is like
Alright
Fitness go down and Revolution but he's also drastically
Affected in a kind of human way about
The fact that someone died
That's true
And it it ruins a lot of the device
Everything tuber
He does not think
He thinks it is
Is great
We need to do way more okay
It's his he's much more acceleration
Alright Tom
MN Alec
Can't quite figure out if it's antifa or if he's glad
And
Owen
I don't even know what the
The f*** he's on listen to this s***
And like
Churches burned
Great cuz that's the argument I would make
People
Storming the f******
Capitol Building of Countryside
You can make the argument that this is a very
Serious
Real thing much more so than
Someone stealing stuff from Target
Yes and I would listen to that argument
Convenient cuz that's the argument I would make
Why would you tell me that you would listen
Into that
But the really hurts your eyes
Look if you were to make the argument that this was real
I would agree with you
Now even so I would say that some of the
The police response
Racine
Over the course of the
Summer wear
Severe
Call.
No
How so
I don't I don't want to get into a game with scale
Cuz I don't actually think that I would be the most credible Source on that
But
I would say that
There's a lot of police Act
Turn against two people
Before
Yeah and also
Whatever
They did
In terms of Defending
The Capitol building
You kind of
Would see it be like Belle
It's a capital building hey we can talk about
How many are how they were
Almost no arrests and all that stuff we can talk about that stuff
But I think what's a more telling
Statistic is
How many f******
Casualties
He's there were
Fewer people with broken hands like that
That type of s***
Oh I got shot in the face with a rubber bullet I got blood coming from my nose
Because I was hit by
Buy 3 f****** cops
There is none of that s*** going around
It seems like there's less
That I've heard of
Yeah I mean
It's it
It stopped because obviously I don't think that the police
Should be
In our law enforcement
I'm not in the business of saying like
Yeah what'd you expect
I don't like that
Call Ono absolutely
Had
Things gone differently
Over the summer
And people had made it over that barricade when they were around the White House
I would not
Have been
Super surprised
People got shot
For trying to rush the White House
100%
I'm not saying the people should have been shot
For rushing
Capitol building
I'm not surprised by any level
A law enforcement response
Capital for the White House
Or
I just don't understand why they're playing games with
That I think I think that's one of the reasons that I'm just not as
Okay
When you when Portland happen
You had f****** Stormtroopers
Is against people
And the picture
Shoes that came out
We're all in the middle of the night
And everybody looked
Hops looked cool
They looked like the
The f******
Beast from movies
They look so
Strong and the protestors
They were the pro
Protesters from movies they look
So strong and in this one
We have
Cops standing around going like hey what are you guys doing we just got to let you guys get this out of your system
And we have idiots storming
We have people f******
Putting their feet up on Nancy Pelosi
F****** death some people might think that's pretty cool
Is is cool but it's also pathetic
I think I think
You coming at this from
Objective standpoint understand
Killer view of what's cool and what kind of movies you like
What they do to
These are people that are
That guy has a corvo tattoo
These are all people who live in one of them
Sky was hanging out with the shaman
These are all f****** scifinder
It says that is true it does seem like there's a lot of
But
The bottom line is this
Pretty sure of that
He's pretty much
Started
So Alex is really at like a point where he's like
Lights deescalate
Ionos
Kind of get it
I give I get his perspective
I mean
Not because I agree
I do agree
I get where he is
It became very clear as I listened.
Alex's justifying
Basically now a war
First Blood by accident
This
This woman
Which I thought
The kids confirmed is just
Similac
That's not
Case anymore argue that if
Somebody who believes
In
Violent
Conspiracy theories
Was
Encouraged to go to the mall and then
Stormed the Capitol building and was killed that's probably
Moron people like out
I think it's it's tough to because people have such a similar information
10 streams that are very
Separate
Sphere
Sazon
The right-wing media ecosystem
System personalized responsibility or
To make it like
Alex you did this because
That's kind of
Nebulous and impossible to nail down
It does feel to me
That you look at what is most
Responsible
Circumstances that lead to this it
People believing in a
Fictional reality
And there's a lot of people who
I responded
Beaufort
Creating reinforcing
Worsening
Pronounce ascertain
Everybody
Everybody on Fox News should be f******
Slapped
If you if they say anything
About
You can hear them sing s*** that people on Fox news said
2 days before
So it's on you
Everybody there should have been slapped in the face while it was going on
Do your f****** fault
But now
Alex wants you to DS
He wants everyone to go home
Such a
Such a surprise
Time to go home
Okay
So the reason that Alex is saying
Everyone go home.
Belated
He needs
He thinks that everything he was hoping to accomplish
Lemonade out of lemons has given him
Obviously the most profitable route is
Continuing
Just the terrorists Edge
Game
Bentley does that super manageable for him
But now that this has happened
It's tough
But
On the bright side
Alex doesn't realize that Congress will just reconvene in the evening
And certify the election result
So he thinks
There's a state of x
Execution
That's going on
Simultaneously
He has
This woman
Who has been
Killed by the
Police
He believes he can
Build
Murder narrative out of
He has all of the objects
He needs to
To build upon
Move forward
He's decided that this is antifa
And he's going to
Put it on the last Jeff
He has everything that he needs as long as it doesn't get worse
And so
That's what he's encouraging people to do
He has no real effect on anyone's Act
Jen's I don't believe
Absolutely
But it's it's
Imagine somebody
In the Capitol Building after
After having stormed it like I got word from Alex we got we all got to go home.
Highly rated probiotics
Wait I thought I was in DC for testing today
So what are the Dead
Giveaways with Alex
Is just like
We can't let this get worse
Is this
Texas telling people to
Except a curfew
What
Hey you know what happens when your revolutionary movement is led by a bunch of
Rich people in
Grifters and scam artist
And I
Your
Supreme leader is a f******
Coward ask
Vice-presidents to overthrow a country
Before him
And then he decided to run away
SKU ranawat he
Bleed from your capital
And then your hero anti-government guy tells you a listen to the state when they tell you to go home
Listen to that curfew
Hey you know who we're fighting the literal Christian devil
Nightfall
Yeah we only fight
The day I have been
And spending a lot of time on my
My program yelling about how
Fuser basically
You know that
Slavery
Government overreach
Scott it's nightfall gas
Got to go home
This is
This is actually kind of interesting at this point
Alex reports
That this woman was shot has died
This is Wade
Before yeah I was going to say we didn't find that out no
I don't know what to make of
Because it did end up being
Incorrect right
Still don't think Alex had a source
The good bat
I think you knew that there was a
Good chance she was going to
The past
And decided
Did to make it to finitive
Claim there was a source
Confirmed reports
We're very much like sex
Well I mean
The real world
The reporting was like
We saw her get
This type of medical treatment which they only get right right the most
Stream of circum
Consensus
So it would be certain things
Good bat
It's not a new
Black girl
Confirm reports are nonsense I mean
The things that Alex
Just tried to pass off as Cooper report
Now in light of this
Decision that he's
Maidenform
Maybe somebody has
Giving him a tip
That she has passed
Now we need to see
Set the narrative
Today's the day
What's up
Under martial law
Okay
DC under martial law
Feds shoot and kill innocent woman
We have to get the
We got to get to Meredith out
This is the narrative that we need
Does that guy the cop murdered this woman in Cold Blood in the city is under martial law
And of course
Sub narratives of course the martial law was for
Precipitated by false-flag Shore takeover of the
The power but also go home at 6
Alex is trying to make this work and
So he has some
Footage of the shooting
He is constantly describes it as
Execution-style
It's just a narrative
Being said I saw the video
A non-violent woman
Yeah
Emily also seen
This video I did not want to but Alex plays it
A bunch of times
And
Clear that he has made a point
Say that this was a
Execution
Because that term is now used
Like almost
Blanket ladder
This is weird
Alex is found
First-hand Witness
We've got a
Confirm oh my God
What a shock
We got it we got to wait
UniFirst
You don't get
To tell me that
That you are revolting
And overthrowing the government
And then be like oh
Innocent woman was murdered
Cold Blood
By the cops
You're fighting a revolution
Or conversely antifa
Provocateur
Yeah
And then
She wouldn't
Bu
I don't understand if she's not
And it's hard
It's hard to figure out exactly what the narrative is
Sickly they're all false flag provocateurs except for
For her she was a hero
And
I don't know
I can care that she was killed
Because I'm living in the real world
What happened was a woman's brain was destroyed and melted
And then here we are
But
They can't
Care because they're fighting a real f***
War against
It's the devil they should all be expecting to die immediately
That's what you're fighting the literal Christian devil
Yeah
And bring about one person
It just seemed weird
Yeah and it also seems weird to go
Halfway
In terms of like we have
Breached
The Capitol building
Happy like we will fight another day
Like it seems weird if you think that you're up against the actual devil
You're already midstream
It's very weird
But that's
Because that's
That's not really what they want
They don't want that
It's like what you were saying like
The people who they were
Probably the most matter the people who followed through with what they keep saying
We don't actually want a Ron Paul presidency
We would lose our money
So a host for a little while and
But he's doing the work to build up
Does narratives that
This woman was a martyr
I will completely admit that I am a chauvinist and I forced all of our female reporters on the ground to get the
The hell out of there one is on a train getting multiple states away right now
This is not a safe place
Multiplan way
And this is Nae that's not
The time to be a martyr
They've already made of murders and that is what this
Young woman will be
The police
Sean
And killed a woman
Because
They didn't like her form of protest
Say
I mean if your form of protest is storming the Capitol Building I would argue yeah
Google the bar.
Now is not the time to Marty yourself
We were fighting the devil
I'm going
I'm going to tell you that I have
Sombrero - feeling
Songs about how Alex handles the fact
That he has
Footage
Yeah of this shooting
But
There's a really interesting dynamic
At play
About the
Provenance
Of this
Footage
Alex
Kind of reviews
Too much
America
Pretend that he didn't
Say these things
I have seen a snuff film today
We are uploading footage
So one of your camera people one of your employees was one of the people who was a long
Storming the Senate and was there
Close enough to
Get this video
Do this woman being shot
Interesting
Weird
You would think that the psycho
Thanks
And we had a cameraman in there all the sudden everybody round images
Cabot him through that
F****** neck
Freaking out
Criminals in Congress
Just think there's a little
I think I kept this clip because it's
So out of place
The weird outbursts
This is the biggest frustration and this is why this is so difficult why we're on a Highwire here
You're damn right
Top of a building I think Express location okay
I hope it sounds like three dudes at a bar
Arguing about how they f****** lost
We won the game we'll get them next time really hard to tell but that was
Bizarre
Rob.
Course he's I watched
This is Death film
I just watched it a couple times it's pretty sad
Alex is Big take on this is that the media in the news
Play The Police
Footage
Of the of the killing of
George Floyd
And so he's like well
I'm going to play this I want you to
Watch it
So you get to see
I want you to see her.
Text Landing
That's psychologically so f*****
Dog
I want you to watch her die slowly
So gross
She would have
Wanted me you don't even know who this person is
Guess something
Things about her based on the fact
Qcor battle
But those bi-week assumption they will be great
They wouldn't be great
But Tom pepper is doing his job Alex's.
Declare this Annex
Execution and so while he's host
I think he's brilliant trying to push the
Again Infowars has exclusive video
Of the Martyr
DC
The mag of martyr
It was executed shot execution-style I've seen the video I don't know what else you'd call it
Buy these
Jackboots
Muriel Bowser
By the jackboot of Joe Biden
Joe Biden
Call them
Koopa Troopa
The jackboots
Her name
God
So anyway pampered also let slip
That the person who got
This footage is employed by in
I know the Infowars cameraman who was in
The roommate who captured the the footage what happened
Hey man it's okay I had a he's a strong man but I don't know if I would be
So Opera is playing
Some
Clips
At this point
There's a group of Trumps
Supporters who find immediate setup
I start attacking the light
Sure and and what have you
Not really funny here is that I was watching
Pinterest board is playing this
Video
And he's a stupor
Pretend that he can't see Trump flag
More
Clashes happening it appears
Between
The media
And Trump supporters or is that the left I can't tell what kind of flag that is
DC as the Sun starts to go down a little bit things are going to get a little bit darker and people come out
Appear to be light switch like somebody was maybe doing a stand-up some news Outlet was doing a stand-up
That's just dumb as well
Immediate right friends in the media
Given my reporters
And we are the Renegade news outlet that is what is Julissa data by the seat of our pants
People Touhou
Nobody's going to get shot today on my watch
Who are out there to get the
What is to make us look bad
You're not say Franti fire police either I'm sorry
I'm not Flats on a threat that's an observation
No it's not a 3 cuz these people are Ferrell
I think you might need to go to therapy
I okay
Here's the problem
Here's the problem alright
Here's why that's so obvious
Transparently bull
Because if they were antifa
Provocateur
Chores
Wrightwood
Still be carrying Trump
Flags
They wouldn't be carrying
Antifa flag
Oh yeah that's true
That's great point
Also
Everything else
Based on what Tom Packer
Conflict journalism should not exist
I can type a look
I understand everyone's curious what's going on in the war zone
But you journalists
Stoop
Hey hey
Journalist
Cops and antifa are going to
They're not your friends and they're going to come after you too
I know
No they're not
You guys are
So
Something something bad happen
Broadcast
And that is they've been
Teasing
Death footage
Going to play
Anodized
But they gets
Scooped
Someone else really
Lisa's Ono
Okay we will be going live
Here in just a second with Alex Jones who's going to come in and break the video
Sorry it's just my cry was telling them do not upload this video anywhere it needs an Infowars exclusive then all the sudden I'm seeing it go
So not sure what happened there someone else
Ixtapa Steel
Footage and he uploaded it
And
No longer than 4 hours exclusive
Can still get robbed dude
I don't know
You might be in the wind might be too high
Soy
I notice
I like their similarities and how like
Harrison
Is vaping
Traits
Patterns
That Alex Jones
Tribe.
In Houston
Exactly
And I notice
Stand up one
The Tom pepper
Is doing an impression
Passion of
Or just basically
Alex does it so
It's totally fine
And that is reporting something based on imagining it
I guarantee you as we speak right now they're trying to use the 25th Amendment to remove Trump
Android full and complete and total coup
Right before our eyes
I guarantee you that
The conversation and Mike Pence's reading it I could almost
What is without sources I'm just telling you I know how these people think I've spent enough time covering them not nearly as much as you think
I'm making this up guaranteed cuz I know I've
Follow these people for so long they're sick
Just based on nothing
Just feels so true though
Yeah oh yeah
This is a COO
You know after we stormed the Capitol building
They're going to cool
Wait
Our guys the president now
So now is the coup
But you know who's Ken
Conspicuous in their absence
Steve
He's got to get those ballot
We've got to find those ballots man Thursday got the various blockchain
Hey Dad Paul number one for me if I
Salon hair
Trump is a bandana so it's time for Melania to
To take over
Hey Rodger you want to come on
No
Please leave a message
Today
Diabeetus
Slim drunk in the bunker
So we get now to Alex's
First hand
The guy who got the video
Now Alex is going
Pretend
But he hasn't already said that this person works
Springfield Water
Who was executed by
Alex conveniently fails to mention the Taylor Hanson
Not Tyler
Is the Infowars cameraman
NetSpend reference mother
Will times already
Owen was hanging out with Taylor the night before
And by hanging out
This is actually what I mean
They took video
My good friend heckler
They're going to do a
Blacklivesmatter enrichment ceremony
Stand in front
I'm not going to think I'm not getting pregnant
The default
Black pocketbook
Goodnight before Owen and Taylor.
Together with a group of people and doused a black lives matter flag
And I lighter fluid set it on fire
Enchanted f***
B l a b l m socks
Oh that's awesome
It is weird so weird
Pretending
That this is just a
The guy
Just a patriot out there.
Play Everybody Dance here just wanted to drop in to make a little bit of a correction here
There is something going on
I'm here definitely about this dude Taylor
Who Alex is interviewing
But I'd I messed something up I I make something up in that is that is my fault and I just like to correct that I did
Realize this until after we'd recorded the episode of it didn't want
To take it out but at the same time I didn't want anyone to get the wrong idea
There were actually two videos that are being referenced
And it is very unclear and I made a hasty assumption
There wasn't Infowars
Cameraperson
Who was filming at the Capital One of people had to storm
And the shooting did take place
And in addition to that
Taylor Hanson was also
There and he had shot some video
So I apologize for the mistake there is no indication that the Sara Lee
That Taylor himself he's an Infowars employee
Although very much should clearly and Infowars associate and as much as he's hanging out
Inoue troyer's hotel room and he is
You don't want video tonight
Before
Resetting a black lives matter flag on fire with Owen
There's something going on there was really confusing about the social dynamics between pretending he was
The stranger to them
When in fact he was very well known to them
And the
Multiple people
Recording
Stuff
It was very it was a mess anyway sorry I got that mixed up. Back to the episode
The next day after this
Taylor Hanson was a guest on Lori
Ingraham show
Taylor better be really careful
I certainly hope that the video showing him burning a black lives matter flag the night before doesn't paint his journalistic intentions as being
I would imagine the key and Alex should be really can
Concerned right now about him getting a rest
Free legal entry
Into the Capitol building
Because he was clearly
Not there is some kind of an object
No no
Using Infowars employee
Trying to get a Sizzle reel against the freedom of the press
This interview in a little bit
But Alex wants to play the video
And you really excited to play this video button
So excited
Hey Joe how you doing
Jarring
Play the video of her getting shot while Alex Alex
Trying to play
Setting up the
The clap
And now he's gotten
Call from Brogan
He can't not answer
So he wants to interview Rogan
Because he has them on speakerphone
But apparently
Borrego
Like in the
Steve they don't have Rogan
Call on there
I think it's probably good
Because they don't
Mission permission
Yeah
And I'll expect a little
They're very
Interesting
Roll the footage without me talking
Already played
I do think that he
Steam more interested in getting Rogue
Anthony is in
Just put it in the Maga murder
It's going to Galvanize it
But I got to take a Joe Rogan call real quick
Joe Rogan I don't know if you know this
Is
The comedian so the Maga murder
Fighting a little Christian devil
Hero going to practice
Professional comedian
So
Now that is out of the way and he can't get Rogan back on the phone Alex decides fukitol interview Taylor
I am pretend that I don't know him
Wild
Independent journalist and
He was the first one that actually had a head headed into that Hall I was right behind her
This is nonsense
Why are they pretending they don't know each other
Like literally listen to this
This is just a little bit later
Owen and Taylor are clearly for him
Another hotel room
It's so bizarre
So
Owens
Thanks Theory
About
Spewing
Of the election
Sure oh by the way
Ridiculous dance
Austin Theory I think that
Owen
Suspect
Set the Communist Chinese
Are going through an elaborate
Conspiracy
Just to make
Make him mad
Get this
Yeah man
That's pretty
Understand correctly the globalist
Both
Made the election look
Like they stole
While at the same time actually spend making the election
Look
As though we're close
Well at the same time
Julie Steele
Yes and they wanted to make a close
Because they knew
Wasn't close it wouldn't
Anger people like
And it had to be obvious that it was stolen
Because I would also pissed off
Come from behind Victory cuz it was one of those gut punch losses
Cuz you know it's like to come narcissistic knockout my beloved
Bullseye imagining
She is just sitting around and being like
He's not going to like this one
Sobeida they covered Trump's
Video
Oh that he put out
Guessing you saw that
Where you called everyone special
And I love you all go home
Talk. They stole it you everything you're doing is right and I love
But it's time to go home
6 p.m. guys
Fuct
Up
New cover that but it
It's basically exactly what you would expect
Only thing that I find shocking
King is
After jumping put out that video
Tweeted
Pretty similar
Iwan tompo
Is shocked
This tweet listen to this
Tommy's
Now we just have a a breaking tweet from the president President Trump
Tweets
Which is I want of his
First tweets of the day really these are
Wow
President Donald Trump breaking
These are the things and events that happen
When a sacred Landslide election victory
She's so unceremoniously
And viciously Stripped Away from great Patriots
Who have been badly and unfairly treated for so long
Culpeper to she believes all that stuff
How is it 84 agent
I got the camp
I don't know if
It's all just like whatever we'll figure it out tomorrow that you all of it
100% throw it all out there.
And then we'll pick some
Stick with tomorrow
And this point how shameful that's all
I know it's
We're on
Send 10,000 but I mean really fourth anniversary
F***** up
Crazy
So
Alex
Really
Trying to push
Homeless idea
That the woman
Who got shot
Is going to be covered up by the meat
The media is not going to talk
Just going to pretend that didn't happen
Because it's too.
Threatening to the global
Because she's a martyr for the cause of the Patriots
It's in the revolution I'm sorry I would love to hear more about her but I got to take this call Joe Joe Rogan is cool
No I know I care about the Martyr
By this point peopleready
Define we know where she lives
That other voices Ali Alexander
Drunk after a f******
Boat parade
That is what's happening
These people are f******
Stupid
It does seem that way
So Alex tries to sign off here cuz he's
Used
Took a little walk
Leading a parade earlier I know it's hard to remember that happened on this episode
But then I got to be signing off
And they seem like they really care
About this woman who got
The federal police
What's going on here
What is
Is full of empathy for their common person
The fellow
Alex is signing off but he throws it to Owen
To wrap it up
Cuz I still got a little time by the war room or something
10 minutes of this ship
Is
Gone
Theoretically that Owen tries to get rich
What is about like
What do we call the
Call what
WeedMaps
Don't you you are the bad guy
Sweet
Wait did you do
Barge back in town
Don't like it when you
You push back
What
The problem
Violent revolution but look stupid and they can't make money off of
Now we're
It's no good Revolution to be nonviolent for them they want to they want to play a video game
Demon god mode they don't want to ask
It's just like f****** democracy we live in a republic but I don't want to risk
Losing intellect
Sure you know like you were any of the majority how I can't stand that but I mean
The old wants to wrap up
Now cuz he was only supposed to say a few more things
How about small bladder
President Trump was on the phone with Mike
I got some more weapons are getting executed
I got two more witnesses
So and tries to interview these people
It turns out they're not so much weight
I mean
It was kind of monium their ads
Yeah
Assume so wild
Say
Also unfortunate
You guys have put yourself
In a place you were not legally supposed to have been
And pizza
Witnesses there right wing
Blog types
One of them is Lucy in winter
Who's the former White House correspondent working at the Gateway pundit
And somebody who's been on Infowars a bunch of the past
There's no way that Alex and Owen don't know who he is yet they're pretending that they don't know each other it's just a random person
Shooting
So bizarre that no one knows each other
Also the other guy his name is Matthew Foster I have no idea who he is but you probably should have
We were in there when the two together wild guess what you committed a crime
Welcome
ISO
Lot of people making these investigations
Pretty easy really don't understand that
They're wrong
And that
Crime is real if they do it
Yeah yeah yeah
I don't think white people can Revolt in the United
Stay there too goddamn and title
Funeral exerted on violin
Civil disobedience is the recognition that they will be
And you will have to bear those concert
That's part of it
Yellow like if you're doing something where you invade the Senate chamber and you do a sit-in or something like that
You recognize that there are consequences legally for that cuz what you're doing is
Technically legal
Answer these guys
I have decided to engage in some form of
The protest that they feel is appropriate
They have committed crimes and now they will have the bear that supposed to be illegal and I'm not supposed to be punished
I appreciate your feelings Lucien but there's a great guy
Look I'm the good guys because they stole election I'm good
Where Alex
Encourages Trump
Do use This Woman's death
As a web
I'm going to call Jennifer
Police attack Folks at pushed back a little
But you don't shoot
Everything right now
South African take over and I'm going to go to work tonight
Call enforcers Bella president
Don't talk on this
Call the offense
Don't talk on it
Later in the evening Alex did a report about how like a pencils going to invoke the 25th Amendment
Taking pappert imaginations Arizona
And by that point
You still is unaware of what this lady's name is don't care to
Involved
Skill
That
Donald Trump
Absolutely does not
It is getting
Sing people to
Care about
That is true
So if you are a
Asking Donald Trump if you're asking Donald Trump to s*** all over her for being dead
That failing in her Mission power do you want that presently
If you wanted to go on TV and say he loves insurrectionists who don't get shot by the cops
Sure you can get that yeah he is skilled at that
Anybody being a martyr
But Trump
Yeah in Arabic
Stop personally involve him I don't think
I don't think he would care
You don't give a s***
Watched all this I lived inside this
I bet it was really weird
Because I was experiencing a lot of stuff
If that was like
What everyone else was
Experience again and reality-based
At the same time I was seeing
And I'm paying
Engine to the
Amanda and what-have-you on Infowars
Between the two is
Is staggering yeah
And
Really
I mean
Lack of
Talent
Aside because he had people like pappert than
And Harrison
Who just aren't good at this
Aside
There was a noticeable
Rakim
To trying to figure out what
To do how do never this
And then there was
A singularity
Purpose
That Alex had
That I really felt as I was a
Coming to this
Fit that
Idea that
He's trying to create
Patriot lure
A mess out of this that is
This woman was murdered
For the cause
To make us look bad sugar antifa probably agitated
We were right to do the yeah
Incase
Yeah yeah
I just I felt
The
First pages
Of
Narrative
And first pages of things
They will affect
People
Down the road beer Ali and cries
4 people
Infant truck that weighs I hope that
That's not the case but that is
General sense of what
I felt Alex's
Intentions were
No
Same time everybody else around him is working across purpose
Everyone else I have no idea what the
They're doing
Insane
Harrison Smith seems like a True Believer
Owen Shroyer
What's the difference
Somewhere between just being
Angry and also wanting to
Make Daddy so happy so he's like
I want to kill everybody but also Daddy needs money so I'm going to back off
Cuz he said so but I do want to kill everybody and also I've recently realized that I'm pretty good at stand-up comedy
I got one B give me 15
Facebook I'm unemployable if Infowars goes away self-employed as a comic maybe that's where the money is
I would go another
Joe he made
Millions doing stand-up I go on tour with Nick DiPaolo
Everything's going to be alright
I'm going to
Middle for Rob Schneider
I think that we've taken a bit of a
Leonardo Maybe
A lighter tone
Maybe
Some people would feel and maybe I later than I feel it time
It's just we're looking to Dallas
Yeah this is this is this is scary
But he's also
F****** idiot idiotic
Right
And
Yeah I mean
I'm in a place I feel
Bye
Coming at this from a
Completely different point of view
Then every
And it freaks me out I feel a little insane because I have never felt more confident that we are not going to be over
Throne
Because the reality of actually overthrowing the United States
Is that
You would have to have the military on your side
And the most important thing about the military is that it is an arm of the economy
And
There's no way
That the economy
He's going to be collapsed by those
And there's no way
With the military leadership who could that mean it's entirely conceivable
That that could have that a coup could have
If it was
Plan appropriately
If the military saw signals that this is actually some real s***
If Trump
Didn't f****** run away like a coward and if politicians
If the right-wing politicians who were all up in arms about
Doing anything like that
If they joined the rally
I all bets could be off
But everybody who's in Port
In terms of
Running the world
Saw those people do that s*** and went
They did it
Too soon
They blew their wad too early and now they're an embarrassment
Yeah I see where you're coming from and I think that I can agree on the
Thunder
Sort of shorts
Fear the fear is the logger scale the lessons
I can be learned by the very serious people chew or who are among these
Ding dongs
The lesson
You can take
Take from this
The image
You know these people flying Confederate flags
Evading the
It is Meaningful from an optic
6th and point
It's emboldening
Enter even if it doesn't
Encourage
Actual
Cacu
Those are the sorts of imagery in the
It's sort of things that you would
Inspire people to take
Other kinds of Acts
Right
Destructive
I don't know I don't know
Let's let's let's not go crazy at the club
But I hope everyone is doing all right out there we will
Find out what happened
After this
On Monday we'll figure out whatever I decided
Maybe it wasn't maybe it's not
I will see if by the next day Alex
Figured out
Who this woman
Was
How about that
We're also on Twitter
Call Charity or bail Fund in your area to help out people
People doing God's work
Emilio Emilio ndzi
Gunbarrel run design the juiciest Ice Cube
Alex
Kristen color with huge fan I love your work