Damn important
I have great respect for knowledge B
Knowledge
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
You welcome acknowledge right on tabs
Novelty Beverages and Tucker a little
Jordan Jordan
What's up
What is I don't know
It's hard to find a brights
Spothero friend of mine recommended
Diablo identify
I don't know my friend recommended it to me and
A lot of fun
It's a lot of running around I don't know
It's a good thing
A background
I like it
I mean like in in in
At times where it's at
4 by 5
I got a another video game
I have a bright spot
And also incredibly
My bright spot is that I found out that my parents had covid and they survived
With no like they didn't have to go to the hospital
That's that's
Fantastic
Comparative salute alternative
100%
The unqualified dark spot obviously is that they learned
Zero from the experiment
Absolutely nothing for me
Hi Dominic. I text you
Yeah so it
It's all good
Getting a bath
They're not gone
Also I
What killed
So it's a real difficult situation that they
I'm sorry
Throw tomatoes
Tomatoes stock going up
We got in front of us he's a little bit of a actor
The
The action
Infowars the day of January 6th
Waianae
Tumbbad ding dongs
We're storming the Capitol building
+ 8
End of last week how Alex
Try to figure out
With this
Post-coital Bliss if you will videos there's a lot of stuff that's going on
I would describe
Trying to figure out exactly how we're going to make it
Through and make a profit
Before we do I like
Bespoke suit
Thank you so much right now
I said Museum
Text Trevor be that is about to run out
I'm a policy wonk thank you Trevor
Dreams like as much you and I'll probably walk
I'm a policy wonk
I'm James.
George
Very much George
I'm a policy wonk Snapchat
Conspiracy of Christopher
I don't know if that's part of the entry requirements
Got to go on the caliper
Stafford
Not that the singer
The Looking-Glass song
Hear from you you were inside there for a while on a western Bay
100 Sailors Highway 160 Bay
Roman sailors
Marisa Tomei
Thinking about their home
I love it when you say
That's a great song
Brim
My life my love and my lady
Naturally
Thank you
Today
I think the show is probably the most
Interested in
The most like what
Can you see things on Twitter
People crime
Around and I was a course that Alia Peter wondering what video games you were
Playing in Almased Haiti
Twitter there was a shaman
Oh he did
Great great
It's hard to tell over the phone
This episode will culminate
With Alex interviewing the couch
Great great and I'll give you the spoiler it doesn't
Well
You know what does go well for actually
You get the the cue shaman on the line with Alex
Sounds
Not as bad
Okay that would
The guy dressed like f******
Dan Aykroyd in Dragnet
Alex Jones is ass a little bit clearer about this they both sound crazy
Peace out
Polite
Track that t-shirt
So webreg
This episode let's listen to a little out of context drop it
Is almost perfectly sums up what it's like to live
Explain that
Next
That
Is Alex curity
Do you like that news broke a lot of these programs just
Give you the guys out
I got a story excuse of an explain it to you later
Possibly
So at this point we start on the 7th
And Alex has learned that more people have passed away in relation
Shinto the storming of the
The Capitol Building correct
And apparently he's doubling down on the it was auntie
FIFA narrative
Well ladies and gentlemen we are here at the epicenter where for US citizens were murdered
Inside outside the US Capitol
Manipulated and triggered by antifa evidence is mounting that posed as proud boys so that they would then
I can still make a dead trigger
Part of the crowd hundreds of thousands already messing
Small percentage in side the building
So this is this is the way that the ball is going to break for Alex
The
Antifa
You triggered everything by posing as proud boys
Things office
I just
I don't know we should have had a contingent in every right-wing propaganda is home
Like the day after just ready to slap
Like Jose was antifa
Just one more just one more time one more time said then when he does
Forever
Slap is
Contingent on the person not being able to
Explain themselves
Because you know hey look
Alex is trying to come on Aaron say like 8
Facts are coming out this was a
I'd like for him
M2
But I will believe it's antifa
Intel
I bet you going to repeat
Let me read you some of the Intel
Here in DC
Organization
Promoters always that they would arrest in Trump apparel to infiltrate the event
Capitol grounds
Even arrived to confirm a stage that was set up for the speak
Observation for group of 120 folks
Already assembled
Antifa
Dressed in a manner not consistent with that normally seen from Trump supporters everyone else too
Came from the event
Did the ellipse waiting for Trump speech
Anyway
Arm pads knee pads completely
Sons of congressmen sons of Senator Kaine was
Oh yeah that's great
Another proof that he's laying out that this is antifa is that
People who are dressed in a certain way
I just I don't intend King's son had a felony one time
Through so he was probably
Everybody who's had a felony was proud
Has been like
Just it doesn't
Saying that although they were chanting
Antifa
It's kind of a strange before burning a flag
It really doesn't exactly
Fairly regular yeah yeah
You could say that this is antifa doing an amazing impression of you
Or it could be
People who are in the communities that you running
And it would be impossible to tell the difference
I would even argue with that point behind all of this
They might as well just have joined the proud boys
I don't want
Want them back
Fair
Alright
What's going on though is that Alex is recognizing that like s***
There is feminism
Is 2 real
It happened
I can't deny this we have to lie about it
Because I told people to do this and then they did it and I don't want
Get into that because there are a lot of conversations that are going on around Dallas
Ex's behavior on the ground
You should
Discuss then we will a little bit later when Alex
Get into it
You know he would much rather be like this is all stage there's something freaky
No
It happened
Movie so much better
Don't have to be that like
Oh yeah yeah you know what
Some of our people
Did the end up going in there
Not going to be able to deny that
So
They look they got trick
Into doing it
So that's what I do
They're all trust fund kids sons of US senators sons of Congress people academics
Child molesting sycom loving
America hating
Trash in the planet
When the police got attacked
Police got hit
When the crops all that
Some patriots responded
Play wannabe bully and got suckered into this that's what happened
Offense
Start exposing this
Yeah so that's a
The way the narrative is starting
Take shape
Not strong
So I think that's
Kind of
Struggle
Because aren't we also trying to make a what's-her-face into a martyr
Well Alex that she was really into qanon
And so she can be
Well no she
She is
You know it is a tragedy
And very sad door but you got
Tricked into doing this by queuing
Okay so now
All all open Warfare on Q Horas ionophores
I like this in there I like
Qanon being antifa
It's a little murky
Listen to me
There's one thing that I know
Blowhard
And that is
They like to talk about how they could have averted disaster If Only They had been there
Burg situation
There wouldn't have been a 9/11
We just should have been there I should have been there
Capital
I want to race down and I'll wait for the capital that's my gut told me
We could have told people that's antifa
We would have stopped
So yeah you could have tackled here
If only Alex I've been there
Could have saved the day that's that's one of those lies that just elevator
The point of just
Yeah yeah
Like Elsa I'm so far beyond
The before you started that lock when you started that lie I'm
Just out yeah
Back to yesterday when your employee we don't remember yes. Please the capital Has Fallen
The Patriots are now into hearts
Cancel
I'm interested
In their evidence
I'm interested in what they're going to bring
To the table in terms of like
How are you going
To show that the
FIFA
Sing Theory
Keep in mind too that you know every time we have these events in DC you always see antifa and BLM
Not on the street
They are not anywhere to be seen it in
This week
Because they're all wearing Trump gear they're all posing as journalists they're all just infiltrating all the truck stop
Because they have no
Betnow dressing in all black with black block going around to get their ass kicked by
Cowboys a police are sick of them so now
They pretend to be Patriots they infiltrate
And then they cause
All this destruction
I didn't see anybody who I decided was antiva and therefore they must be the hidden in plain sight dress
Just like Trump supporters
Therefore they are false flag
Are you trying to turn me into some sort of superhero
Vigilante
With a tragic backstory
No because
Is it seems like
This is like listening to Owen
Say that
The day after
Makes me want to like dressing all black and trained really hard and then jitsu
And then just solve problem
So wherever they are
You know I'm not trying to do that
It's like you're making it a
Is it does he
I will say that
You are
Required
What to be able to
Jump between a
A couple buildings before you solve any problem
But it's me doing any of this I will be I will be your Alfred if
You can jump between two buildings before you solve anybody else's problem least 2 or 3 years
You might need a little more than two buildings
2 years that's the rule
The name of the game is
He's getting these talking
Pinpoints out into the world and make
I'm sure that this is the reality that people like
Looks that muddy the waters
Muddy Waters is important
The other thing that I think Alex recognizes pretty quickly
And I think he's right
Is like this is a great opportunity to try and
Cute people back
Some people might be disillusioned by the fact
Through all this trouble and then Trump I guess is
What happened to the plant what happened to the plan
Tell me about those ballots again they were Watermark tonight or no
Steve
We need to talk about talking points based in truth
For the president for America for the world because we don't have any Patriot Communications the president's been caught off basically
The white house is listed.
And it's not because we're powerful is because
Okay
Used great big wonderful
That's what got us into this position
Okay you were cute person
I'm just telling you now that you have to listen to the talking point we have to discuss who was behind this pain to get front of bruising
Nice way to like
Extended Olive Branch
Listeners who might have
Did Mork use an Alex
You know and be like
I'm still come back here you're not doing nothing against you if you
Got into this cuz it's all
Supposed to be asked
Questions
But
Event almost like
Is is like a
A plus one for everybody's media consumption like if you were a cute person you go plus 12 Infowars if
You're Infowars Hugo + 12 Fox News
Fox News you're like
Believe whatever I feel
Maybe yeah maybe there is a a sort of like a toe back towards
I like
Away from the extremism
Memory. Of time
Episode 4 like people on the
Their couches
Buda. Necessarily the people who were in.
Possibly
I haven't had enough time
To see what the actual effect
Activity
I'm about this stuff in that.
It has me feeling somebody who season Opera
And it's an opportunity to give part of that market
Chair that you lost back
Right on folks
To think that he is controlled opposition
And works for the
Mossad or CIA the CIA or whatever
It's so good
Goodbye. Good but that's what you
You should be doing
From a business standpoint
Then now do you see where the Vigilante Park
Comes into this
Because if Alex winds up getting more market share out of this
And no one stops them I feel like their needs
To be some sort of all black-clad ninjitsu master who is trained for two years and could jump
Exactly to building solve a problem
Put the way you would solve that problem is by like
Starting your own about starting your own right-wing media Outlet
Okay
So
To not even like Judo
No you should steal some of that
What is market share
Okay if the problem that you're seeking to
Alright
Okay so I'll just wear all black and have a radio show at night
The Capitol Police
You know there's a lot question
Gyms that are going around about
Preparedness
Their lack of preparedness
You know
6 dates
Yeah we'll learn more
In coming days
Sure Alex has decided that they were understaffed on purpose
Because they were working on this
With antifa or something
Okay
Understaffed on purpose
The police finally pushed back
The police attacked the patriots the patriots attack
Beautifully played we needed to be investigated
State Police
Funded by Soros and they have Soros
Yeah you talked over but he did say empty that works for the
The Deep state
Okay
Hey, right guys
Go do it they're your enemies
As the left
We were antifa
Antifa in this circumstance
Every faculty what the far-right
Wanted
Right well if you look at the responses that we're going on as it would happen
I got to Rio
Yeah I think
I think it was exactly maybe antifa has been your ally all along and it's the
The cops who are your enemies
Very confusing
After this
Saul went down
Trump
Pretty quickly on the 7th
Was put a put out that video
Transfer power
Conceding a great little whoops a doodle moment
Imallexx
I think he recognizes that like
Trump is
Running out of allies
They're people who are like companies cabinet who are resigning
Percent of like
Oh no
Everyone hates this guy now
And I think Alex
These events as an opportunity
What do we do if millions of listeners as millions of activists with talking points and narratives to counter what's happening
What pressure do we put on from
Congress is Trump totally
Ben
Abandon
Tell me on this
Talk about it in the second hour later is
Isolated and increasingly desperate and this is good news because
That does sound right
That's f***
I guess the good news is
Is that we know the vice president will be like hey don't
Send those nukes
You don't need no I don't send those
How that's until Trump
5th Amendment
Do that'll be interesting
That'll be an interesting reversal of Fortune
So I went to Starbucks iced with the 25th Amendment
I'm at stuff and he's decided the Trump only release that video where he may or may not have conceded
Because Pence
Was threatening him
I want the phone
And take calls
Pacific Lee Auto
Trump should do has he can see that you can reduce what you said
Installing
Fraud but I will
To the peaceful transfer of power because they told him he got Mike Pence we got the rest your cabinets are all cowards
Your ass right now the only did that because removing him would cause a bigger backlash maybe Trump
Because
He's going
Not peaceful transfer power because it's a fraud
So they're scared the power he still got
The feeling that I get there is just denial
That just seems like pretty thick
Denial
Alex does realize
Hi this is over
April 2nd
Oh no you
Doing this cuz there's a metaphorical gun to his head is five stages of grief
I gotcha gotcha
Just kind of fun
More anger
When he talks
Syracuse shaman
Was bargaining
Before anger f
Bargaining is VIP
How's the weather at that would make sense that he's always grieve me on air
I will fight the globalist
So Alex has Taylor Hanson back on
Who was the guy who got some video of the shooting
In the capital
Fourth Hanson
Yes
Almost
Almost almost
Suspect that you got me
I apologize I made that clarification in our last episode
Got it mixed up
They are very vague
And were they were on the 6th while they were covering
There are two pieces of video
That are going
Around
And I got the reference
What's wrong on
There's one that was shot by Infowars
Cameraperson
And then there's some that were shot by Taylor Hanson
The reason that I got it confused if they never clarify that
Anime interview Taylor Hanson
Tonight somebody
Who got video of the stuff
Around the time that they're playing the video that the enforcement.
No but yeah
And they're really
You get the sense that they're working on a narrative
Where
Schumer called
Look for the Killer
Alright Taylor Hanson was there I'm Alex Jones Alex Royer
For lady
.
You were there describe you talked to her before she died
What happened what you witness
Oh yeah
Baby feast
I would watch that
Movie
I just
I don't know man
No I don't know I don't find this to be a response
Audible Library
Retaking
It's like trying to imply that Schumer was like
Like killer for blood
Sacrifice
Yeah
It is it is real weird whenever you're like obviously we need
To get all the Patriots
Chuck Schumer
Keep antifa from doing all of that stuff that we wanted to happen but we
It's 88 is really almost like
Nothing after diagram
The points that are trying to
To be made are soaked
Confused
But that should be expected because you know people like Taylor are involved as
Like sources oven
Information and Analysis
Kind of guy
Got into this
Because of Q
Was great seeing when it first started
You know it was it was a way to introduce people to all the evils what these globalists are doing all this time
Pedophilia
All the sacrifices
Let me doing more independent research and I think that's what's great about you is
They do their own research they don't just trust fake news
I think that was a great topic about
Was trust a plan
How do you say people staying home
When Trump himself
Are telling them to come
So he's got it you got redpilled by qanon
The plan idea which is like you don't have to get
Active
Right but then his
Comment was that more people should have come on the six
Apparently yeah
Okay
But what happened was bad
Well no
Everything that happened
Good except for the part where they went into the cabin
Okay
Store bid
So they think that if more
People had been there
To storm the capitol
It wouldn't happen
Cuz it would have seen the antifa
Like every single
Person is a pair of eyes
Okay okay
Alright one mayonnaise
Something like that I don't know where
I'm sure
Great great
Cray cray cray cray
The perfect day that got ruined
Because of antifa pulling a false
Swaggin
Really really frustrating
Freep
Frustrating too because it's all
It's one of the first
Winston says I think I can think of Alex showing some vulnerability like he's just yelling about how antifa
Kick their ass
Catching myself because they were going to fold Flags they said they were so busy focusing on
What in the problem was it was a millionaire
It was a million of us there
He said he does
I'm sorry just left
When you're when you're getting older your prostate
It's all inflamed when you get all angry
Hopped up on
So much fun
Bathroom break
He does actually go to the bathroom
And while he's while he's out Taylor still there
Script which is this like
Bringing some
These Q people into this
This fold
And I know a lot of people are still believe in Kiel
I have a lot of friends
I was wondering the same thing you know
Last night
He's going to turn it over to Joe Biden he's going to be the president in United States
Which is not the plan
People are freaking out already I mean yeah some of them probably are
Kind of being a little bit biased and wanting to trust the plan still
That's not going to work all it was was a plan to keep us complacent
I plan to not keep us on the street
Doing activism
The help
You guys went home
You could have stayed out on the streets
Screw you remember in Portland
They say.
Alex
Stop them
Did tell people to
Respect the curfew
Yeah
Yeah yeah
So
I think it was Alex who took them off
Off the streets
I just I find this all to be really
Sad
Yeah it is a sad posturing among right-wing
Scam artist
Stealing through
Trying to stake their claim on
You know just trying to steak
The Clement people who they can manipulate
It's a bummer shuffling
It's like the tide
But it's also like
Think about that
It seems pretty clear
To me you looking at those candidates
What's going on
I don't know how you could hear a clip like this
And think that any of your like
Preferred right-wing media Outlets have any integrity
How big is that
Gateway pundit
There's not many holdouts out there
The entire right-wing media
Ecosystem was large
Driven by
A grudge for a very long time
Bird
Basically yes
Yeah I remember my dad reading drudge in the 90s
It really warped a lot of the the the media line in shows like Rush
Wouldn't be in the same situation
It was a
Clearinghouse
For the talking points of the the right wing
Yeah and now Alex is suggesting that he doesn't like Trump any more
Trump wouldn't pay him off
What the f***
Do you get it
It know if your if the president doesn't pay you off
For good coverage
Then it's your responsibility as a principled person to sell to see CNN
Completely alter your coverage
Dammit
You don't like
If we suddenly took
S*** ton of money from I don't know let's say Jeff Bezos
Coverage wouldn't change
The I replace you with an echo
Melissa
Can we love your show we're going to give you 20 million dollars but the
That
Jordan we're going to replace it with
Just listen to
That way we
You can turn him off
I do not see Neighbors anymore I couldn't turn the volume
I don't understand how anybody can
I'd like
That they have any kind of
Like
Calling it alternative media is laughable when you're like
Yeah get money from Trump City
The CNN
That's alternate turned on if your alternative Broad
Bitter
Anyway this next clip I just kept him cuz it just like
No fuc
Alex
Some calls and this guy
No way
No
Way to I hear you
And also to I don't know if these numbers were accurate but I was watching
Everything live on your radio show
Yesterday and congratulations
Because it showed that you had one point
Billion Buick
Amazing congratulations man.
One point
6 billion
Hold on I'm writing something down do I need to add
! real quick
It is
Let me see it the first word is
No alright let me and it is
Way no way no way
Two exclamation
For each word
1.6 billion listeners
Infowars
Where
So we are here on this next clip from January 7th
I got to say I found this episode to be largely unlistenable like I really didn't even think it was a show
Yeah I kind of felt like Alex trying to figure out what
The Narrative was going to be
And it's just like alright antifa did this
What does
Bye
Eating and then they went away and all the pain
Patriots got really
Excited
And they had to fight back
Because now the police were attacking them into it
If you don't like that kind of
He's sort of talking
Pruitt to get his bearings about it
It's just a
It's not an interesting
Sing show it all
As a man licking his wounds in the
The posture of somebody who won
Trying to figure out what to do
Which control the what's the angle that we can move forward
Bright and
At the end of the episode
You pretty clear that
Doesn't really have a problem
With what happened
What killed all the babies we devil worship God took his support away we got to fight back and take it back
Capital so evil
Politically
The point is is that we're not the ones Vernon Town police station and killing people are responding to that they start
We're not ashamed of anything come out
So that's
That's her to where we're at I think a lot of people would
100%
Trump if
Osher
Because remember the address that he gave before the riot
I mean the storming of the Capitol building of the United
It States of America a nuclear power
He said all those things that were like I bet it's going to be antifa who's going to take over the Capitol Building in Just A
Too short. Of time
Answer this will prove incorrect
I made it there is enriched
Tradition of
People blaming their enemies
It does seem very easy to do
I think
I think your item and I hate to say that I think you're right they probably could
Yeah that's true
222 a certain audio
Right
Which would be 80% of 4
At this point
So Alex
On the 8th
On Friday
He starts off his show with a bit of a
Different tone
I think he's accepted
This point.
Conceited
Globalist disinfo operatives do not want you to take political actually want to freeze you right now believing everything
Fine it's not in Texas he is surrounded in the White House
It's not a CG video
Concede the election
Yesterday
Last night
So is up to speed with the realities on what
New line
New text messages from the people who tell him that
I believe that you know I I don't
Keep up-to-date fully on
Accustaff but
My understanding that some people were speculating that it was a
Deepfake
Or something
Also by this point on the 8th
If there were picture
Coming out and a lot of the people who were there and look very sad
Suspicious
Well
But they also seem to be wearing like Oath Keepers shirts and they kind of look like a militia
Is like a militia other than antifa
Right
So Alex has to now
Incorporate that into the cover of
Antifa
Which we've established here on the 7th
I will test explain why there's also militia people there
It's tough to explain
He was
You were there
Rest stop
With another contingent of
Probably will end up being a militia controlled by feds and militias are constitutional
Not bad
Delicious
Militia
My friend Alice is almost always exactly
Exactly like what he was saying about like Boston bomber
The body language of men
F*** out of here making s*** off
PB in his absence
Want to get him on as an expletive more than anyone else
Those guys are not okay
Yeah you could give a full-throated
Defensive end organization
Keepers are
Seems to maybe not be answering Alex's
Call
There seems to be a limited gas
School lettuce
The interviewing
BBQ Shaman that would get you to where you are
Episode
Really mad
Accu Staff
On this side this episode
But
He's again
Very much not wanting to
To alienate
The cube people
Sure you can still redeem yourself
Cube made this
This whole f***
What yes
Pull it off at War for the dumb Q people who
Storm the building I want to learn ninjutsu
There was another ingredient wasn't Chester
It wasn't
Josh
Militia
Q
The Air Force veteran a wonderful woman
This is Babbitt
Mother country believe she was storming it under two orders of the president
Behind
Antifa
And that is fact doesn't mean
Like the cute stuff
Esoteric
Rodger dump truck to the Hoover Dam
Free General
There you go
Ansible literally I don't think any of those things
Sad sometimes
And forth Alex would turn him
A villain and hero
Pretty regularly
How's Hot and Cold relationship
I died I just
I don't think you should be allowed to say that wonderful woman
If I know
And you know
In your heart that if you and your son and Gavin McGinnis were around you be like
I know she's dead
Got great tits
So you don't get to say that
So Alex has a
Media
About the fact that antifa infiltrated
Nausea
Hippie rally and
Comes from the old New York
Mo Brooks
I said they were briefed
Was planning a thousand Patriots
As well
Chain
Two people were arrested
They confirmed for posing as
Bank of America great again people to make America great again
So the headline
Quote to known antifa members posed as pro-trump to
Infiltrate Capital riot
Sources
So it's a claim
From source
And it's awesome to like if you just get to the fourth paragraph at the store you find
Washington Times reported initially claimed two other protesters were actually philadelphia-based antifa members
Retired military officer with access to facial recognition software
But the outlet deleted the article after the software company told BuzzFeed news
The story without right
False
Ha
Huh
Kind of an article that has a nice headline for Alec
But it actually means no
He goes on and on about that I like two people were arrested
That are known antifa
I don't know I think I think I hate this just so much
Because you know you like you can see the conversation that
Like you can
Read that and go
Oh okay
Here's what happened
Somebody went to somebody higher up
Who is like
Oh s*** they did it what do we do when we do just put it everything teeth
That's it like they didn't
Think about it
Didn't come up with some brilliant
Game plan
They're just like
You say antifa did it and we'll wait and see what happen
And it's disappointing
Probably
We we continue down the road
Stock from
On the 7th into the 8th
Is that Trump only conceded because he had a metaphorical gunt
Threatened
25th amendment removal
I'll Trump
Yesterday
Morning
Good afternoon
Define your supporters at the crying the whole thing
Morning
We are going to remove you we have the cabinet both right now
Remove you under 25
So this is the way that you get around the fact that Trump was yelling about how like you know I'm never going to back down in the morning
Because otherwise you kind of got to be like he was just
Full of s***
You just
And also it would be
Really difficult thing to just
Survive it like
Why was
Why is he does have evidence
That this was a
False and fraudulent election why would he ever back down
Now he is backing down by that either
He was lying
Open the sort of person who would allow fraudulent election
It does seem like they're not stuff and the only way around that is hey man
Your metaphorical gun to his head that you had a label
Yeah but Pence's metaphorical gun only happened because you held a literal gun
You know
They're not going to wrestle with this that's
But I just
I just it's so frustrating because it's like an eco-terrorist
Blew up
The Capitol building and killed a bunch of people I wouldn't be like listen
We got to like no
You don't get to do that though
I love requirement to ban but no
It's so hard
But at the same time you don't make a lot of money scamming people around the ideas
God I'm so
Yeah that's
House of Cards
He's belts
Can get knocked over
That he has to protect
Play work for him
Scaring people about
So Alex
That was there
At the Capitol building
For a Time
Provably
He was a lot of people were reporting
That he was trying to
Incite a riot
It was my sense from watching the entirety of Infowars over the course of the day
Expressed our last episode is exactly what I feel
He was definitely saying things that look really bad in hindsight
But once
Ship popped off
Real seriously app
I didn't see him inciting people outside of him doing a inciting radio show
Yeah yeah
In terms of what he
He actually did it the capital there wasn't a lot of evidence
So that on the show at
But Alex
Does have video of himself
And he is trying to talk
The crowd down
If this video is too big
Be believed as like
A full representation of his actions
DC
Very much like
Hey everybody
We have a permit to be over there everybody go over there
And I think like I mean
Look dude sucks
But that's probably
The best you could do in that Circle
Sure
And so he plays a little bit of that on the
Alex has
Be instinct
To know in the moment that like
If this gets
Too much further out of hand
We're f*****
Yep this is going
To be something that is going
They will
Take
Problem of right-wing
Extremism
Seriously
If this goes any farther so I have to do my part
To deescalate
It makes sense it's in his character it's exactly what you would do the Gate of gates all over
Obviously I decided that
Said that
Insisted that I do that because I'm so proud of doing that I've almost certainly inspired
Other people to do that but that's not my fault no
To come back from the edge as it were
Are you going to like these
Things this far and you want it
To come back or else
You're in trouble this is all
Contractors
So like I said
At the sense that I get is he just knows this is too much
This is dangerous
No no no
Provocative
Play Store
No no I mean that's
That is pretty remarkable snapshot of what happens when exactly
Been trying to get to happen happen
Yeah I do know that you never wanted that to happen you wanted to live in that in-between stage where you can profit off of
Tension
Supposed to be tantric you're not supposed to come all over the capitol
Yeah it happens
You get on your radio show and you make a lot of money excited
Eating people yelling
We're going to storm the steak houses in all this
S*** yeah
Forever
Yeah man once you're there and it's happy
Bring you get a bullhorn and you yell get off the building
That's how it goes
Yeah
No one knows what that means you don't even know what that means
Swear to God
If I am a person
Who is
In the middle of trying to storm a capital building and some a****** just start screaming USA
Instinctively
Start chanting with
Kill me just kill me
I don't want to be that person
What if you're climbing on the Capitol building
And then you hear it
The Texan
Get on the bullhorn get off the building
You can't tear me down I don't see it being ineffective that but if I'm on my way to the building
Maybe and I just stopped to chat USA I guess I think I might be a follower.
I swear I thought I was
So I went to the Past
To Victory if you wants to explain to his audience
But he can't quite
You know
I need to do a presentation in here
No problem
I'm going to come in here I'm going to lay out the path to Victory
So he doesn't
I don't think he does do this
I didn't hear it
Pastor Victor
Other than blame antifa
Well
Dan the path to Victory
Certainly
Very few can walk
The path to
Church
During one of the breaks
Here's that I like
Either
Did the Orioles claiming
To have talked to Mike Flynn
News about
You're witnessing Satan's full attack and I've been on the phone for the plans
Been on the phone with many others
Especially in a shell
Surrounded
He is basically turning on his supporters
The president of the United States is captured
Buffaloed
He was shanghaied he was Bamboozled is a good way to jettison Trump
The person
You don't need him
Many more really
He has no real use
You've already seen him humiliated basically you seen him turn tail whenever things
Too close to what you want
Where do seller suprise egg
Yeah yeah yeah
Seeing him
Abandoned
To the whims of the people who were saying like
You're going to
Loses electrical you lost
You going to go you're going to leave office
Bellevue office
Here's was going to
This is not the strongman
Next week
We are going to find out
And then this is going to blow your mind
Did you know that Trump had mob ties
Squalo
Yeah we're going to find that
I guarantee you that Alex is going to suddenly discover this fact
That he absolutely never knew before
Oh yeah yeah
Five years later wild wild how did you know that
Connected to a lot of my people I would even argue that bats maybe your way out did you know that Kayla was the mob
Stop the Patriots you know that he was a front man for
The Consortium is on the East Coast
Did you know that with a name like Corleone you get arrested but was Trump you down
You know it's almost like somebody who is already in
Throw two medium Powers would very easily be swayed by superpowers
Probably
So there were like I said some deaths
At the at the rally
ROT Rally
Storming of the
Capital
And there were a couple of medical
Related ones
There were also
A couple of officers
If it was there they those people went to the ENT
Shifa medical 10
Pants that were set up at
Every protest
Step Brothers
That's a great place
Alex is going to lie about
These cops
You had a
A million people in 100,000
What's run the whole thing
I have
The police open the gates they were downsize that day
Patriots got killed at 1
Police officer had a stroke and died
So directly to Cops
The capital who are now dead
When was Howard liebengood who passed away on Saturday
And at this point there's some reporting that
It's calling this an apparent suicide
Is very sad
The other is Brian sickness
Who was assaulted by Trump rioters
Neither of these men die from
Stroke
Deflect from the humor
Switch
That kind of ruining this game that he
Flight
Very sad
It's so obvious
This whole
Like a back
Back the blue nonsense
The police cover
We want to kill Nancy Pelosi let us kill her
So there were only like this
A few hundred people who went into the capital
Roller shoes
Whataburger
Davis Autos in Wharton
Bearskins
Weird Al
About the ones with zip ties and Scotty are Marin
I am to master
I don't think he's a bad guy
Baltimore looting
Criminal
So ladies and gentlemen the time
How long will it be
Dot-com the biggest best company out there
Pretty smooth
Nice add transition I think these people might be a little
You know what I'm since I'm getting a Feeling
That the far-right is trapped in this place where they like
God we want to kill everybody and what happened we want to do again yeah
Can't do it again if we say we did it
The first time is antifa it was antifa but I also have to tell people
To do it another time while at the same time telling people
Not an advanced said it will be antifa
Who does the thing that they do it
Trump will be president
A second term
Really
Concede we can put literal guns to everybody else
You should have heard
The demonic
Cackling
The came out of Joe Biden then
Kamala Harris
Soon as he said I'm sorry I'm conceited
Stop Criminal
You are so mean
Yeah all of you
Voice and Alexa
Ursula was
Vivillon
Mermaid no
As as we know Alex
Prefers the bad guys
In every movie
Maleficent Maleficent Sleeping Beauty
Dude
Look up under people on
And also look dude
I am
Sure.
Beauty that's a beauty I think that's cute
Few hundred people in the Capitol building if you think that's
Impressive
Wait for this
They didn't even really want to go in
Ordered
The crowds in
Didn't even want it
The cover-up
135 and the other fifty or so Orange
Windows outdoor
Yeah man the be there police were told to bring in
A man because you are cover for antifa
The orange hat people who
Are almost certainly proud boy related to require a lot of
Like there's going to be a find a solution in a way out of this problem
Which is to say
That the right-wing is all terrorists
It's going to require a lot of
Diplomacy
It's going to require a lot of compromise
Thought and
Some concession that's going to that's just going to be true
Now on the other
I have watched
A lot of superhero movies
Saying one way is faster than the other
So
We only had a couple hundred people in there right whatever
They didn't really even want to go anywhere near the building
Right but over there
Pianos like look
Still probably hired
Google
I was there are Lister saw it
Popstantot
And it's still low yeah they were there too
The cops the cops
Backpacks
So these skinny jean guys are the antifa guys and they hired a group of goons
Who are much stronger than them because they're not strong
Tired stronger people as backup
To fight again
Against the police or something
Seems like this would be a job that almost nobody would take
Since when that mean the anti-fascists were hiring fascist
It would imply that
Cuz he would have to be like
If you are that group
Of I don't know bikers let's do whatever you want
To take a certain amount of money in order to
Almost certainly go on a death match
That is correct
To get killed
For trying to the Capitol Building
Of the United States of America a nuclear power
Right just doing it as a job
What if I grant no I don't even get 5 grand I'll do 425
Okay I'll take two
What kind of Gone in 60 Seconds
This kind of nonsense is this perfect crime they have all of the family members of this biker gang
Kidnap
I don't I don't know.
Expect asking me to accept
Is a little bit too
The little bit sad
Not for my family Dan
To go buy any old ship
So we do get one person who answered Alex's call
No Steve
China Canal Stewart Roads
Snow Rodger Stone
People seem really important to this moment
Very
Someone who is less important
Maybe that's why he can appear
You're not a lot of heat on him
Is Joel skousen
He is somebody who
Can just come and go as he pleases
He's notably been somebody who's been
Been harshly critical of trump
Is power placement
Infowars world
Over the last few years now we might be seeing it elevate again
Based on his relation to W Cleon
Its sole
He shows up and of course everything's are f******
Can false-flag this guy
Course
Play antifa didn't know what have you bought
He has proof
Anybody you might have got this from another fella we know name Lionel
Well The Tell-Tale cases every one of these people have died
Weapons
Trump supporters don't bring those types of things to
Backpacks
Transporters
Don't
Have
And they don't bring back
Kind of stuff to Rally's that's
Exclusive
This isn't fair. This isn't Fun
I don't like it there mean
It's pretty dumb
Disconnect Clippers
Absolutely
Skousen
Is saying that like
Some really big happen
False flag coming
Yeah Alex suggest
Well it's vacuum
The cute stuffies the fall
False flag that's
Call Matt
Then
Scales and throws Lynnwood under
Hell yeah throw Lynnwood under the bus
He's already under the bus you getting crunchy under that bus now I would suggest that the things that
Thousand takes issue with our very similar to a lot of the things Alex says
The populist movement
What you doing
And I'm just trying to portray
It is going to be more than a truck bomb it's going to be more than Oklahoma City Bombing that's been done before
I think they're going to try to Gin up
Some
Large mass revolutionary movements
Pakistan Tina PLS
Lynn
Texas he's about to order you to launch a military attack
That's right and unfortunately
Linwood publishes rumor about
I got a little cut their supporters
Bulshit
B******* saying that to a guy who said that a hundred times over the last
Couple months and end in between waves
Not not in like a orm repeating the same story
There are no reasons that the Deep state will be killing Trump very
And for quite awhile to because
Durban Poison
They're going to kill Trump on day one
We're going to Nuke the inauguration
Helicopter
Oh man
Is bulshit then he should
I consider the bookings
Insidious
I won't take this away from me
There's a lot of there's a lot of you know you got to give it up
Alex is a newsman
Any does sometimes come through with hard-hitting scoops
And I will say that this is something I've not heard reported anywhere else
Okay that is giving me
He's eating at one sitting five lobster tails
Giant bowls of ice cream and an eating prime rib is Desert and shoveling down
House of Crabs
3 times we normally
Australian Housewives
Heart attack heart attack
Alex's Alex's reporting on
Trump's outrageous
I think it's probably the person that I agree with most
He's not going to last very long
Yeah I do like that as a response to because it's like I know you're making that up but I don't want to fight you about it
Well that's not.
He really shouldn't do that
Scales one of the things I've noticed that he does a lot is Judge
Just make stuff up
List of the 36 people that are looking for none of those were the agent provocateur
If they did arrest some of those agent provocateurs I think they'll be quietly released because
You know the higher-ups will be told you know these are our boys let him go
All the guys doing this
Best dog backpack okay
Just so everybody on the right nose
If you were arrested at d.c.
And then let go you are antifa
Probably let's name them all by name
The problem with a theory like this and a part of the problem of the mentality like
You'll never hear about it
If this thing of imagining happen
Then you never hear about it I'll yok
Vistaprint that theory came true
Amazing house
Didn't have fact that you never hear about it
Is proof of
The reality of this
I would say is it one of the big things
The big takeaways from this interview with skousen
Is like
You did Alex
Pretty much agree in with him
That like it's time to move on
Trump
Useless
He tried to do this like a little dictator push thing
Two weeks
I think the Trump movement is really going to be looking
Poor
New leadership
Cultivator
I really do
But him
Has wounded him severely
And I just think he's going to still be a fortune
Try to act like he can fix the Republican party but
Do it
His kids don't have other the Don Jr
Donald Trump's children about the junior running more
Or anything else I think that's going to be
Play the movement
And
I hate you so much in my
Burning
Not trying I don't think
He's getting better
It takes decades to learn this and just doesn't matter
That's right you got to be in the mood for
5060 years and I have all my uncles background of my father's background I mean it just takes a lot of money to develop in
Instinct where you can smell evil where you can smell the Deep state
Presents
And that's what
We need to teach people to the
How to make stuff up at every turn I call everything I just know how it feels
To be done Junior because I too was a shittier version of my dad and I was worth that
Years and years
Just taking swing
I'm being embarrassed about it over that
You got to be embarrassed for the first year
And then you're free of it and you can say whatever you want
Skylight ninjutsu
Doughboy
Now we get to whatever one is probably
4in what I was the most
Interested in
Episode
Known as
Duchamp
Jake the Barbarian I guess this earlier incantation or incarnation
So he's got the Q shaman
Is the guy who are all the pictures of the guy in the band like
Helmet
I don't I don't
Know anything about this guy except for that he's the Q shopping
I found out about him whenever somebody said that guy
You know about this
I heard his name was cute, he chose that name and was fine with it and I've worked backwards and I know everything
Yeah it's like Riverside Strangler by the river
Does q it's the Night Stalker
At night
Exoclick Alex
Play the clip of him
From the day
From outside the Capitol building
And I don't think Alex
Free watched
Because
He's saying a lot of the same stuff that Alex says
And this whole thing was a setup
That I was going to try and embarrass him
And try and be like a dick to
Unfortunately
He sounds like Alex
100 miles in any direction and you got a deep underground base
Okay
Joker sometimes get attention
Who's ready to play that clip come back from the other side and be like
Can you believe this nonsense
I can't argue with any of that stuff
See this coming. These are the kind of things you would want producers
Is to help you
Powerful Alex
Alex
Yorkie
Well it turns out that the shaman
Nothing but the shop why would he have
Jake something-or-other on route
Citizen oqshom
He's a listener of Alex's show
Just call me Jay calix
It's an honor to speak with you sir
Have you eaten
He was not Invincible at Trump's inaugural
You know I have heard those warnings but you know
I'm going to believe
That Q is military intelligence and I have a lot of faith in the military military intelligence
Okay well I was
They couldn't stop you from storming the Capitol building
Call The Top
And they're all surrounded and cut off the
See this is what I find really remarkable about this
Is that
He is one of
I mean I don't know
I don't know how much of their is like uniformity of belief but a large part of
The cube world does not like out
So he happened
Used to be someone who's fairly high-profile world
Who also happens to like Alleyway and it's trying to have this conversation with Alex right
That he doesn't I don't think he realizes that Alex is trying to be like
Like I believe the same thing
He's trying to use the shopping as a prop
In order to delegitimize
The qanon stuff
Right as part of the continuing
Get people
Back from Q
Here's what Alex
Could have said immediate
Okay
You believe that Q is military until the
Military Intelligence absolutely
Must have known you were going to be at the Capitol building
And did not stop
Write the argument there is that they wanted them
Right
Hugh
Betrayed uq shaman
No not at all kyusha I'm in love is what happened on the
Text
America
Play The General Public
Everything's fine they don't get involved
Absolutely that's why I'm quite proud of what happened on January 6th
Well
First of all
We are talking about a government
That is literally telling people
When they can open their business
When making skiing hug their families
A government that is literally a fat
The way or trying to affect the way that their citizens at 3
This is a problem for Alex
It's because those are all arguments that he himself has made
BBQ Shaman is coming in and explaining to Alex
But this is tyranny and I'm proud that we stormed
The capital
We should fight tyranny which is also something Alex should believe
Alex is antifa
Coronavirus
We're all antifa
We're deep state
Everything is this is really complicated for Alex
The position that I would if I were him I wouldn't put myself in
Because I don't know if there's any way to look
In this in the circle
Thermostat supposed to be
No it's not
I know it sounds fun to yell at David Rothschild don't do it
You're kind of an idiot yeah you're so dumb
Q Shaman looks decent next
Haha
And that's cuz he like
Fix you because he act like
I mean I've totally against
Gemini
Thank you know everything I know about him
I don't support and I think he's wrong
All I know is that he's the cute Shaman and I agree with you on all
There is a consistency to the beliefs
He believes the same things Alex does
To just
Scam people
And that's that
Attention
I mean it can't come off literally anymore like
Hey Alice
You said you wanted the
Yeah
I did it I'm proud of myself for doing it
What's going on with you buddy
Yeah yeah
It's kind of a gut check for Alex
I don't know if he's enjoying it
So Alex is not into the idea of likes
Storming the
The capital
Sure it's an abstract
Idea like maybe a new Declaration of
And the shamans not doing
Do to me that sounds like treason
Dependence
I just think it needs to be done we can't fix things peacefully the right time right place you can see how though
What's the 10-day investigation of probably about to get it
Gorman capital
Well I don't quite see it that way Alex to be perfectly honest with you I think that
Anything we sent a very clear message
The globalist and to the communist
Send a message
There's no
Clarity of that message
Not
There
The I mean there's some elements of it that are clear
What was the other one
I mean I'm scared
I guess that's clear
I think that you know the shop
Man believes that they're up against
The treasonous government
They sent a very strong message with their actions and
Alex
Can play this game where you think
There's going to be a new Declaration of
Dependence
Shawn Mendes
And that you also doesn't agree with the idea that like oh that we work
Going to get
The 10 days that Rudy Giuliani wanted sure all f***** that up by storming the capital
And so Alex is trying to get
The shaman to
Except
Let the Deep state
Who eats
Supposed to be again
They actually wanted every
Here we go
Do you know the Deep state
Boston
This is not good
Well everybody has their opinion Alex and
In all honesty I understand where you're coming from
I just don't quite fully agree with you
Location to Texas
I believe in Occam's razor Alexandra
Things that I know for
Certain I can prove or things that I know beyond the shadow of a doubt a real
Okay I take issue with that but it's not worth getting bugged
It's weird I can almost respect it
Like if you do that
Because what you believe in is that there's a treasonous government
And you were like
I can't handle this anymore
I'm going to go over throw the goddamn car
And then you stick with it afterwards you say I believe that what I was doing was right I believe that it's
Necessary
End
Sure all of your beliefs are based on polish
But at least you believe s***
It's in somebody who actually isn't
Like just playing game
It's terrifying I can't get around the fact
But he's the queue Shaman there's that I knew you wouldn't be doing that kind of stuff unless you were trying to bran
Unless you were trying to like sell Q shaman
And shirts or something like that
Every revolution has color for characters
Yeah but there's no I mean there's got to be a Grifton here somewhere but
It's far different
Adidas outfit
But I'm just saying I would I respect
Tim infinitely more
We have to pardon I do that
Don't feel well respected
Respect is a form of fear
I'm more afraid of
His bulge
Because he's a Believer I wanted to make sure people do
Perspective
Take me to applaud
At least there's a
Consistency
And I don't think Alex is ready for the
Because I see
I think that if he doesn't he's not used to be
People who care
No
You thought that this was going to be some
Idiot that he was going to be able to steamroll
And do you have
Agreeing on multiple accounts
Spitaliks
In a way that is not confrontational
But we don't see eye-to-eye on that
An accident like that there's something about underestimate your opponent I heard that yours
Supposed to do that is that what you're supposed to do underestimate all the toy
It's always helpful
I think that one of the things that I've always felt about qanon
Each other is
Part of Alex's feelings about it or is
Petty jealousy
And like he's Furious that everybody is talking about so many of the same
Things that he always had conspiracies about what they all think
You uncovered it
Think he's a little gel
Barbarian
You're very well spoken.
New World Order secret Technologies all this is real
I don't know about the Cleon skousen
Nobody because the rampal know about it
Beauty College
Yeah it feels
It feels like the intensity of it really feels like it has something to do with the credit
Google
I don't think that if
Like at let's imagine isn't
Fantasy world and qanon
Did manage to over
Overthrow the world government I don't think Alex
To take that as a
If everybody was throwing parties for Q jamun fruit
Successfully overthrowing the New World Order
Alex who
Isn't that funny isn't it such like all I want to live in a fascist
Nightmare so long as I'm On Top
I don't want to live in a fascist nightmare work you is running things and I have to listen to that a******
I don't know yet Alex doesn't want his right-wing fantasy world
If it comes with cute
Absolutely
So this is the point where things I think really
Turn in the interview
Alex starts being a real
It's tough for me to stand up for to shop
Call Kari addictive
But just from
From the standpoint of
Politeness
Very impolite
Had
Pure shaman
Tell me what's coming next time I want to believe it
Where is Trump
You think it's the devastating Victory you just at the Capitol
Explain to me
Bring me up to the level of a q
Shawna
First of all allow me to say that I am not Auntie frying not BLM
I know that there's rumors
Boating around online
Disinformation agents
Information
Askew
The Border qanon
Digital Soldier Story
Galaxy isn't necessarily saying videos
I think what he's saying he's going to buy the antifa provocateur
But you can hear that
You're a shaman bunch of tell me about what
What's going on I feel like I would say it in the very similar Town though but I don't think you would have the interview
Having this interview is a productive
Do thing to do if we were if we were in a bar
And I was like chained to one of
The chairs that have no choice
Bright start a conversation
Eventually I'll get to the point where I'm like
Alright Q shaman
You tell me what the f*** you was up
Yeah baby but I'm on the show clearly
Fidelity
The dude
What are you you are a
Urru a Norseman
Q Shaman what are you
I am a shamanic practitioner
Okay I'm a spiritual Warrior
And if you really want to know what's really going on what was really going on as we are changing the quantum
Spiritual warfare understand that DC is built on Ley lines electromagnetic Ley lines
Show me understand that yes the Satanist
Luciferians
Globalist annihilist and Auntie these people that have been filtrated our government practicing black magic they arguing
Evil stick
Satanic ceremonies and rituals with her sacrifice and children and drink
In The Hobbit is in DC and London and in the Vatican
Like beacons for the slope
Frequency demonic energy
You told us the Trump was invincible
Yeah puterman for whatever
Guess you probably guessed
Restoring the Capitol building
He has a pretty healthy sense of self
Not give a f***
Pretty pretty legs well done
Alex
I don't know if you know this or not
Not but I stormed
The Capitol building
Wearing
Caps
And a helmet
Are you going to interrupt me like I give a f*** about you
Your diversionary questions are not important
Answer the question that was asked
He's a shaman
And
You know whatever I don't I don't begrudge people for
Coronavirus lockdown
Practice you want to have
Would not be the angle I would
Take make fun of
He does
He does think of it
They prayed in the Senate
It's a magic
Because the Washington DC is built on Ley lines
Look on the electromagnetic wavelength of the Earth
When we
Ended up going to DC when we are shouting USA
Homer shouting freedom
Boomershine four more years
We are really upsetting the quantum realm because he's around the fire
Go away
Ghost sounds
Supersedes electromagnetic activity
Okay
By marching into the capital
Bye
Quantum realm in that way we actually took back
The Capitol building for God I said a prayer inside this
Are you saying my shamanic song inside this and it and I broke up all that
Negative
No do you want to talk
No no no no no
Give me a favor and let me finish my well
The Secret of
He is a priest is a religion
Everything's fine
I don't know about all that
I think that he can tell that I was being a dick
See now if we're at a bar I'm still changing my chair and he's coming back with that unlike
Alright buddy
Now we can talk there's some Humanity there more than like
Alex is shook
This point Alex
Really knows how to
Decide to make fun of shamanism as a way to attack
The things that I agree with you
Shamanism is the oldest religion in the world
Are you singing drumming dancing and they use elaborate like
Dress you know the address but face paint
To change the quantum Realm
Sound through electromagnetic activity and
I understand magical powers
No it's not about magic dear talk to you
Are you talking about
You are a shamanic wizard
We get that
Let's just
It's sad
It's not it's not a productive
Conversation for anybody but
Because of a lie
I mean it wouldn't be productive conversation
The cube was talking to anybody because you'd be talked about ley-lines a magical
Magic physics quantum physics
You know what that means
That means whenever and elect
Tron from a single atom
Is paired together with another electron
Then for some reason it doesn't matter how far apart they are
Ley lines
Sprite
I misspoke
My point isn't it
Be a productive conversation with him
No no no Rock but Alex brought him in for the
Explicit purpose of
Trying to
Impune Q
Can't really do anything
Would you think you would be able to like he knows who Q is
He should be like I know these
People
Do you not understand like
You should be able to
Completely
Instructor this easily but he can't
It's the only thing you can do is make fun of this guy's
Spirituality
And that sucks
It does seem like the easy
Just wait for Alex
To go to be like excuse me
Mecu shaman
You listen to my show right
I told you
Two months ago that I knew who he was
I threatened to unveil it and then I didn't
Yeah so
I'm just going to tell you who killed his right now and it's not military intelligence
It's Dick Face McGee over here
I mean obviously he would be like that's not
But then it would just be over
You know you wouldn't have to deal with any more of this
Blimey shaman
B2B any conversation of like what do you believe what do I believe I don't know them they're actually
Pretended to be
Aware of
And to know as fact
He shouldn't be having
Any kind of
I believe
You believe conversation about
This topic is something that should be a settled issue for him tell exactly
Debate
And it's really
Fortune
Listen to Because
It's like the queue Shaman is just saying stuff that Alex agrees with
He has to keep interrupting
I'm asking you what your wizard towers
Why you Grable do that
Keurig iced I was in the military and the intelligence Community disseminating about top-secret information and Patriots and our Republic
Why did you leave Julian Assange in prison when he's the real Q type person
You keep interrupting H I love you dude I love you but you got to let me talk
Are you listening
Zack is
Las Vegas Insider
Dude who was supposedly like the the other Cube
Themes behind what shopping is saying here are the things that Alex talks about all the time
Globalist have infiltrated the government in this is
Exposure
Of the
Exactly
He can't attack the
The meat of it
Without hurting himself
Enso
He tries to distract with questions about like Julian Assange
And then
I mean I would interrupt that
That's feel too though that that was
I'm interrupting anybody who's trying to sell me a timeshare
And if you have rehearsed your little
A bit like that
Do you know what you do if you invite someone onto your show to sell you a timeshare so you can interrupt them
Score points about how annoying it is when people try to sell you timeshares
Kind of a dick move
Yeah isn't that
Sacha Baron Cohen's job
Well there's more layers to it than that but yeah
So
Like I just see the wave
He's describing
The shaman is describing his beliefs
It's just basically a lot of the same stuff that I was pleased with a couple of different
Free characters
Like I was just a different cat
Slightly
Military intelligence
Top secret information to Patriots and a republic
Take that door country from communist and globalist
Some of the highest levels they could bring America down from within
I know about the New World Order
Everything's fine
For real or whether he's
Crazy talk
Any different than most of the subject here on Infowars no way different other than he
That's it that's it
100% the same thing
Wow
Besides the shaman
I hear you man and stay there
All that stuff
Don't know what's going on nobody does
Girl 45 days
It's so frustrating
Just sit there and watch our people wake up but then believe
The charlatans garbage
Again just seems like a petty jealousy
And like why am I not cute
Why am I not as important as
Is Q it's so frustrating to see them by the
Those t-shirts
Q on it
When they could be buying Infowars branded
The pills and they could
Discussing to see people wake up
Wearing a shirt with Q on it
Instead of taking two of these
Goodbye my duct tape that I bought a banana
Totally
Totally what are you doing wearing a shirt that goes over your mouth it's a shirt for your mouth
Alex has not returned
The corner I really don't think
Said he likes this guy at all
It's unfortunate
Because the guys
Very nice Alex's bar
Yeah
But I wouldn't want to clear up one thing
Disease now it's
Taking over the 4th hour
Matt Bracken is also there hanging out
Moral support
Owen wants to know like a man people founded
Acting profile
About you are you at
Actor
I just want us to address you obviously want to know about you is
Profile that says you went to
Acting school so they think you're
Acting
And this whole thing is just an act that would you like to dress that
Reason why I haven't I can cut files because I worked with children for five-and-a-half years and
Children and I got chased out of the home with a knife
By one of the kids that pulled it out of a locked cabinet and I decided that I wanted to do something a little bit more fun
Do I win in the business
For myself I develop my own website my own YouTube I started writing book
And I thought about well maybe I'll give us back to the shop turn a little bit of money on the side
I haven't made any money as an actor I never got anyone we got that we believe you
Use almost
Star-Lord
So close he's so, you just wouldn't worship the devil
He wouldn't
Take too much money for it
Questions go away be
Because this guy said he's not an actor on Alex Jones a show
Alex and Infowars
Are well-known for if somebody says they're not an act
Believing
Alex
Is taking the approach to these sort of trying to shame and belittle
Puta que shopping
And I would argue that somebody who makes
Their business
Going around to protest
Stressed
That ridiculously for the sake of getting attention
You're not going to be able to shame them
You can't embarrass I would be very surprised
Difficult yeah it doesn't work
Your Accu wizard
I'm asking you this for a 12-day
Does Trump
What happened to Trump you knows everything you don't know what Terry intelligent
Well you know what man all I can say is
I think that Donald Trump is
Part of a much larger plan with it at the military plan with that be God
God's plan I think that when you look at harmonics
When you look into the way that energy frequency and vibration basically create and move
Call physical form all matter
Then
We are all playing a part in a much larger grandeur
You're not on stuff
You told us
Meadowlark
What I'm saying and uses you putting words in my mouth again what I'm saying
Is that
Donald Trump is
A part of a much larger plan to help us take back our country from globalist
But Alex has said that to
Of course this leads to its natural conclusion
Which is Alex is going to blow up
This guy
Yes
I just don't
No
What
Like actual difference
Since there is between their beliefs
Donald Trump
Has played a very
Pivotal role
Annex
Closing the globalist and the cabal exposing the Chinese
And the Communists
And the way that they've infiltrated our government away they traded our media until traded or entertainment
Brooklyn
Can't you keep interrupting me
You said he was invincible
Two people after this
Barbecue I can't talk to you anymore
Lord help me
That was
Uncalled for
Response I would say
Damn if he's sick of those witches I think it's time to call Larry Nick
Haha
I think you know I don't know if Alex had the same preoccupation with wonton
As the Q folks he definitely had a lot of about to get arrested got a boat.
Go to jail soon
Invincible is certainly like a
Theme of chosen by God to defeat the Devil Alex has said that a whole bunch of
There's not a lot of light
Between these two ideology
One of the reasons that Alex does do that fake blowing up there
Is because
Like the way he's presented Q
Qanon stuff is very different than what
What this guy is bringing
To the table
And for the audience to become aware that like oh no they're not all crazy the way that Alex wants you to think
There's talk about the Federal Reserve there's talk about these deep underground bases there's
You know a demon
Hey I like that
The elites are sacrificing kids and drinking their blood Alex
Alex is in on that maybe there's a
Alex runs the risk of
Was blowing up right in his face
If you
I see clearly that there
Pretty similar
I think I would also argue that there's nothing Alex hates more than a mirror
Especially one that's younger than her
Like that
Cuz listen to the way he's talk
Walking he's rambling he's saying all kinds of nonsense
He's rattling off bulshit that he's memorized
He's an unwilling to be interrupted for any stretch for any reason he's claiming his SpaceX
This is an
That's like this dude is
Person who loves Alex Jones
Who has
But much of his Persona clearly
Around his love about
It's at least a strong
No one
And hates Alex Maybe
More than out
I know and hates people who like our
Yeah I exact
But you know what
Shaman
Execution
Believe
When they're wrong for the wrong
Smallpox
Ninja
Really no ninjutsu
We got you on the line
So they go to commercial break
And I come back
And Alex is true to his word he is going
Forgive the shaman
Alaska
Sorcerer to wizard.
Shushana
Hopping mad at me
2 days ago
He disappeared for several hours
As
AccuWeather
Good dab
That's the bit huh
Little boy videos right to be really mad at him
Yeah and it's just a long plug
Dog fur like
Is Rumble page
Allowed on YouTube
I got the Von Erichs
Buzzing the UN
I got stuff on her about aliens and their true
The truth about aliens and where aliens come from how they actually interdimensional beings more it just as much as they are like
Conoco extraterrestrial beings
Video on are called just
Take the red pill
Five and a half hours that if you
Really want to know everything that there really is no to get caught up to
Speed here now all you have to do is just watch that one video and it'll explain a whole lot of things that most men
Weatherby things about about you
Cube image completely full of crap
Has been full of crap
Facebook call
After 20 minutes of that insufferable
But he's on lightweight man
Harry Potter
Hocus-pocus crap
All this Harry Potter crap and now I'm going to talk to you about the devil
Dealing with Ley lines in quantum physics
Just can't handle it
No Alex
Give the appearance
XVideos something deeper
But if he was forced to actually talk about it
It'll be like when he's on Rogen and he realize like he doesn't really have anything
Now
That's really a dumb thing to do
Alex is not good at
Confrontational interviews with sincere
Because they are running
Damn that they care about what Alex
The Q shopping
Would like to have
Positive exchange of Alex he looks up to him
Yeah but he also isn't
Invested in the Infowars scam in the same way that all of Alex
His guests are
Yeah Matt Bracken has no other
Like media outlet that will ever talk
I don't give a f*** about him again
That's so he's part of the game
Yeah everybody that
He talks to is
At least in some way
Transaction
Yeah there's a power Dynamic either Alex
Does higher or lower everybody knows where they stand
Everybody knows that they're working towards the shared goal of Griffith
And Alex can work really well in that space
Or at least he can operate there because
People would know not to
Contradict him not to get too out of line if you interrupt you just roll with it
But yeah you got that you got someone like you Shaman and he think
He is higher on the totem pole
He just stormed the capital I bet that dude's arriving riding a wave of adrenaline that is still going
While he's in jail now
I also
F****** flying off the walls
Yeah it's
It's complicated
There's a power in Balance but it
Perception
I think that they're the Top Dog on this golf
Infuriates Alex
I imagine that the
The Q Shaman thought he was doing a victory
You know I just
Got
The most
National attention
Worldwide
My pictures
On the world right now
So Alex Jones is calling me because I'm
F****** famous
Yeah and maybe maybe we have
Some slight disagreement that we can work that out so I'll charm him up top we'll have a nice little conversation
Rational guy we agree with each other on everything
You not take me at my word as a
Sincere person we agree on literally everything
Sing about the globalist
In the blood drinking in the
The Chinese and the Communists
Are you saying that I can't trust far-right media figures because they will cut bait
And abandon me as soon as I'm not useful to them
Oh I might need to rethink nothing I mean
Not for nothing
Alex is far from the only person who's sitting on this dude for doing
Exactly what they want to do and they were told
Kind of
Kind of like the most predict
Edible thing ever
I wonder if anybody had
Had said that this would have
So Alex
If he was there
Things have gone differently
We probably would have tackled
Vacuum shop
Rally Trump
Call the Capitol Police
We should have been down there
Yeah man weirdest
If I and
20 guys
Who are specifically very large I hired them from the same people that
Tony Vargas
20 of them cuz they were busy at the
I mean
A from the 8th
And
In the same way that the out-of-context drop that
I'll get to this next
Maybe
Is a perfect
Like just
Boiled down
Alex
Sure this minute is this is Alex
But Sunday show for 6 p.m.
Sunday live
That's sick.
With only six minutes
Local ad
Gcn where wonderful people
You know 22 last just for locals but I am working on
Just having mobile ads for you folks
How to get to 67 minutes
Adjustable station
I want to watch right now
Play the gentleman we prove it
Call Dad was much as you can learn and earn nobody to control
He's not in control
Tommy is employment government can be Godzilla
To claiming everything's great buys got a plan.
The only plans you just cry
That
Thing there is
Infowarsstore.com though gives you a God create
That's good give it to me
That's the kind of give you an overdose
There's so many awesome layers to that it's
Starts with him talking about wanting to have less commercials on music
Definitely not
Interesting
That
Business relationship
But we do our ads on the show like I'm about to do
He starts talking about how God's plan is
So that was intended to be part of a plug
Futurist God's plan the divorced or what
I don't know if you can amazing amazing
Bookbyte
Definition
Of those would like those words like though there were ten of them
Pretty important to people who love the Bible
Yeah alright
Fairly certain that you
You cannot take God's name in vain
More than he just
I think that's the most you can do
There was some
Vena Stuart a little bit of ignis there
I find this stretch right after the storming of the
The capital at the end of last week
Kind of interesting but also kind of
Kind of
I do I don't know I guess
Google what you'd
I know it is
Is it is at
Sorry I wanted
Sorry to regress for 1 second
But owner next episode I would like you to play
The short clip of him saying we've proven that where the tip of the spear right now
Next to
Go home
Respect the curfew
Exactly. Pepper thing you sent his reporters home
Sorry for interrupting
I would be lying if I said that any of this
Surprised me like Alex's Behavior
You want the ride
To the
The storming you know what the storm exactly
You need that
State prior to conflagration
Make money off of because
Let's say
To the Capitol Building
Back right then
Investigations would be
Very crisp
222 right wing
How organizations militias figures
Keep more people had died
It certainly would be far more serious than Alex
Can't profit in that
Chico's
Systemic
And so obviously this is
You know put the blame on
Somebody else
This is a false flag because they were scared of how close we were to getting that 10 days that Rudy wanted weed overturn the
I'd also at the same time for a showing his ass and so he's too weak
Can we need to look for new leadership
Pizza
It's all very predictable
It's just so brutal
It's so brutal
Tactic
After this
Is not
Cuz it's
It's so obvious
Alright you see the way I act now
And you work backwards new go
Oh obviously he wants to rile people up into a state of constant
Fury
And then that will get him money
Their emotion
Spell connection
We'll get him money
And then when they did something
He realize that that would cost him money
And so he
He stopped
He changed his mind
Quotient
And so
We can't trust
And instead it's just
How about I throw two different types
Cognitive
Dissonance at you
All the time into your brain so much
Open so hard they
That you can't even
See through
Bedtime
Obviously in this for money
Yeah how can you not see through that how could you not see-through when he says like God's plans the only one that's real
What God gave you
This guy's a f******
Assholes
Not that I agree with you but you know
Time is
Peacetime people are f******
Lazy
Full of s***
This was a
2:30
Goddamn storming the
2 days after a.m. to that should be fresh enough in your mind to where you go I got knocked out of the
Headspace that I was normally in and it's just nothing
Yeah
Lisa Houck
Quickly he went
To like first of all calling Sandy Hook a false
You saw how quickly the Boston bombing
Became a conspiracy
Edit make sense
Like the fact that this is a
Giant
Eventually
And I honestly don't leading the Boston bombing and he was at Sandy Hook he went
That's what makes it even more critical for him to make it a false flag
A good thing that went bad because of the
Trickery of antifa
Yeah he hasn't even
Greater
Connection to it
That again
This goes to one of the other feces that I have
And that is that one of the primary ways that I was
Money is by profiting off of Anna
Exploiting tragedy
And this is a tragedy
No matter what
Ends up coming from it and I don't think
That we are fully process
The reality of
The last week
Oh absolutely I don't think you could
I just don't
I-80
It's staggering
And almost
Surreal
Yeah I don't know nothing
It's not good
And that is the kind of thing that I like
Make money
The only thing I would say it was kind of surprised about is
The Turning tax
A little bit
About the woman who got
Yeah I don't
That I felt him martyred building
As much as he was the day off
Murder build
And
Deescalate
You can only
Do one or the other
What you got a murder you're going
There's No Going Back
See my way and I think the fact
Did she was really a
Add to queue kinda
Hurt his ability to adapt to
Create
Perfect figure out of that you can't scream it how stupid
Accu Shamanism then be like this Q believer is also our new
Virgin Mary turn them into a figure of
Of
Empathy and reverence
Yeah
The path that they were going down on the
Continue
I have a feeling
That's
It's going to be bad
This week
If the plan or the
Speculated is that there may be another repeat
Y'all article coming down and will
On Monday if that's the case then I would expect
Expected Alex's go
Can I have some
Choice words
What about that
And so we'll see what happens but I don't look
I don't I don't see by Future prospects of
Relax
Cynthia got good
I do love how stupid
They all seem credible
Who is stupid
It's so
Unbelievably
Ridiculously stupid
To stop for once a
On Wednesday
The president incited a riot
And people
Storm the Capitol building
So
Because of this action
We will swiftly drop articles of impeachment
Which we will absolutely be delivering to the Senate
100 days
After biting the inauguration
But solving the problem with
Yeah
I mean I don't know what else you do but
Couple years
But until then Jordan a website
Go to bed Jordan net worth
We are on Facebook any like that you could please find a local charity to help out people do
Doing
Omniome Lido
Dzx Clark on Daryl run
I if I had
Some guy
I could defeat Alex's Buddy Guy
Well maybe. Probably.
I'm not really much help
Alex
Christian color