Air Jordan
Knowledge party.com
Pray I have great respect for this knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Fight.com
Little bit about Alex
Joan
3rd and Jordan
What's up
My bright spot today Jordan is
You did get a new hoodie miskatonic University
That's a lot of crap
Takes me forever to buy clothes
Like I just never end up doing it
I bet the same clothes
Forever
And I've needed some new hoodies
You know it's winter
Basically wearing a sweater everyday
And so I've added some spice
To my life
This one I got also another one that miskatonic University
Antarctic expedition she wore a shoe
Of Madness reference
I got too much love
Crafted
You're golden dad decide on anything that I wanted to get that would be like I can handle
Some public and it's something that I like
Like I can wear this one would look twice at it but if it was like
Cthulhu or something
People would have to do a double-take and then they be like
Otherwise it looks like it's a college
Make that compromise
That's better than what I do with
With clothes what happens every six months I buy five different colors of the
The same shirt
That's not too bad but I think there's a lot of like
Decision paralysis that you get rid of when you do that
Yeah yeah yeah when you model your clothing choices on Calvin from
From Calvin and Hobbes I think it's
Solve the law
Problems
Before they begin
Yeah yeah
Because then you just like up grab the same thing this one's blue and the other ones
Feel it's a difference
Jordan how about you what you going to start this year they they just ended the gdq
21 they just ended Games Done Quick
It was a bunch of fantastic
Lot of good runs
And they raised over two million
Even in this kind of f****** year so
That's really really cool
It made me happy
That is that is a lot of fun
I'm still wishy-washy tiny bit about watching
Video games
I want to watch some of the people who put up like Mario maker videos
So hard
It's
Almost as levels are the people
That was one of the things this year like almost at it closed it but it was like one of the
Last four runs and they were playing this dude was playing the hardest
Like Mario Maker level that wasn't even Mario Maker it was
Hack music ISO hack
And the previous world record was like 35 minutes
And you didn't
18 Mile everybody's watching that just going like
Tappan man we just saw history
Part of my concern is that like
I think I might get to Intuit
People play video games too much
I can't do it I don't want to enter the territory last I disappear into it
Yeah it's one of those things where I've never like I've never been that good at platforming games
So they've always seemed like a struggle
Whenever I play them
And then whenever you see these guys playing it's actually a very kind of beautiful almost
Dancing kind of feel where it's like
Oh I get it if you just do all of the steps
Perfectly
Could you watch if you're if you're bad at dancing and then you watch somebody's good deal
For sure
It's not how it's supposed to be is the world
Fast food
F****** transition
You're great
It's a mess over here on Wednesday doing a little special middle of the week episode
Because we got to keep on top of things
You figure to be too much
If we wait until Friday
Things would pile up and they may be important
So we're going over January 10th and 11
Today
I don't have anything to say about 21 yet
Nope we'll figure that out
I think
2021 I'm Dan and there will only be Lone Survivor
Snow pretty good today
This is no longer 20/20 okay
Now that's not good
But yeah
Episode interesting return
From somebody who's been out of pocket
For while all right there's somebody who we have not heard
Hide nor hair
Hide nor hair rose on Metro the expressionist
Okay
What we'll see what happened here a hide or hair
Concerned about I'm not entirely sure
The first Jordan
Some folks have signed up and are supporting show
Call me policy Walker now policy walk
Take that
Thank you Nina Z thank you so much you're an alcoholic
Not Finn Balor thank you so much
Experian
T h o m
I like that song
I don't know why
You don't know what if I were if I were Thomas and I went by Tom I definitely keep that Asian then the old English
Michelle h
New Morning Show on in Fort Worth
You're not supposed to walk
Q
The Giuliani braintrust thank you so much
Freakishly large
The both of you are special little shout-out
Wednesday and biscuits
Who are couple of cats
Is it
Apparently adorable that are sweet but I'll take the owners word
Florida
Give a shout out to the concept of Wednesday and two biscuits
I prefer biscuits to Wednesdays
Stripper Drake ever go to Cheddar Bay Biscuits fantastic
Second best biscuits Cracker Barrel
Pretty gray
Biscuits are a couple of cats
People who take care of them I guess we'd them
How's them
Andrew
I got reached out to because last
At the end of last year
Do them typing.
Married
Happy one month anniversary message
Are in December
We can't do this that message now we don't do that missed that message in December we didn't speak to
To anyone know
I feel very bad about that don't want to make it up and I wish you happy anniversary
And Andrew happy anniversary
To get both
Man you should have hung onto it for a full year December we could have been like
You thought we forgot assholes happy one year anniversary another problem with that is I almost certainly would have forgot
Lulja forgot
It'll be around at the end of this year
Wednesday and biscuits
Celebrate
Hope you all are having a great day
Let's start here on January 10th
Alex seems to be looking at the world
What people are saying I'm right about stuff
Aphmau
The internet really
Alex Jones was right
Is
Written on the walls
Festoon to people t-shirts
The Twitter and Facebook accounts
The million today
Honored
The fact that
Get all of this
Now we're getting
Only because I want
People didn't realize that we know
What's coming next
Probably nuking
King City
Experts be honored to have Jordan was right
Him directly next to for a good time call Clara
I think that would give me a lot of Honor
Yeah I know
What a prediction
I I think
I personally would never like
To be in a situation where I'm celebrating something that I said
Being memorialized in a way that I decide to call it fixed
If you ever catch me Slippin and I use that term to be like my words are festive. Billboard
I'm not doing well
Things have gone bad
Screwing into the ground
Claimed on our previous
So that Alex has laid out the
The foundation for the antifa.
The storming of the capital I like I like getting people killed who have nothing
To do with it and it's your fault he's proved
Oh good good. Let me hear it
That's the globalist it maneuvered us to destruction
We flipped Trump in the area valiantly fought
Please keep the country sovereign
Apparently
2 out of a million demonstrators at
Whitehouse the elliptical the Washington Monument the illiterate
All the way down to the Capitol
Elliptical
Identifying
Showed up at active police
And then the police on the other side
Capital open
The General Public
That was very little violence
Very little except for a few people
Along with them
Some useful idiots
Video chat
With
The few violent events to then say
Capital was stormed
By terrorists
Quotes Capital has fallen to The Patriot
And quote
Narrative here and that is basically they
Antifa they started things I'll be provocateurs or
Are working with some other
The big tough guys that the skinny jean Folks at hired
Stuff to make us look bad Manda what's going to happen at the next
Well Alex is warning that there's going to be a lot more
He's basically at this point been like
But also I'm f******
In-N-Out
He was planning on going to the inauguration and now he's like
Hell no
PetSmart
Easy Street
Two-tone quite a bit
It's a doll icon setups in the future
Completely changed his tone the moment he got exactly what he wanted
And now realizes it's time to time to pick
There's a lot of other folks
Who are are coming out here
And
You know
Thera
Make it to my some insightful
Inciting claim
Alright
So you have all these left
The Congress
What's the moment
Ted lieu
Widespread civil unrest
We need to see
Some fires
So answers right to a 32nd
Clip of Ted lieu from 2018 where he's being interviewed by Chris Hayes on MSNBC and is disgusting
Of Robert Palmer
F*** you who do I call for fires and he doesn't actually call for anything he just says that if Trump fires Mueller
Call Larry would likely lead to civil unrest and protest
That's not a threat
The comment in stuff like this is recorded on Infowars
If some b******* this is The Logical result of what this person does their like see you're telling them to do it
God dammit guys your stew
So also Alex is founded antifa leader
He's going to pinpoint as the the villain
Of January
Who said we're going to go there and poses
Patriots
I'll show you who you is
He said it in d.c.
The day before the event in a speech to antifa
A day in advance
Then they drop
The charges on him because he
Did a good job
This supposed antifa leader Alex.
Antifa leader I don't know that means but he's he is somebody who's had some history involvement in
Antifascista social justice active
Sullivan was one of the people who was there and was recording the storming of the capital's supposedly as an independent journalist documenting history
PolitiFact reviewed is footage and there are some questions about her disconnected from the story he manage
H-2b
With him occasionally see me to expressing
Encouragement about what was going on around him
What is a far cry from the accusations
The people like Alex are making
As an independent journalist
Who agrees with all of what you guys are doing I would like you to
Continue
Storming the Capitol building
And somehow I'm the bad guy here what do you talk
The way it looks
Sullivan is a bit of a bad player in the game
He probably felt like he was doing an impartial piece of Journalism document take a Monumental moment but he didn't show
The poison discipline to actually pull that roll off
That's what it appears like
He said that some of his encouraging words were meant to help him blind in
Very well may be the case and pretend to be
I mean they will tear you limb from limb
They did have that kind of scrum vibe
To them from yeah
Whatever the case
It's nonsense to take whatever dubious Behavior selevan may have shown on January 6th
People Eater who is responsible for the storming of the capitol
That is what I would call A desperate attempt to scapegoat
I can't find confirmation that he's been arrested in relation to the Capitol storming but he is facing charges related
Do it earlier protests in Utah that is still going through the courts
As far as I can tell Alex is just making up
The part about him having charges and then being dropped
Related to this
He's doing that because of things like what Joel skousen said on our last episode
That is if the provocateur
Tours themselves get arrested
They'll be let off right
They're in on it with you
And that's just sort of building up that narrative but I I can't I can't
Into that still don't understand how they're getting around the fact that
Regardless
F*** it
Say antifa did
The whole thing
You guys to still realize that they only followed because it
What they want
And what you told them
Well
There's a couple of thoughts on this actually that come up over the course of this
Okay
Without spoiling anything hypnotism maybe info
You know I should have seen that one coming
Mass hypnosis that's what it was
Jets
So it turns out
Alex
Alex has
Trying to figure out a way to talk about it
I like come up with a pale but it's just a jelly bean
Nevermind
Alex is pretending hear that he's like proven everything
Everything
Is what does we got this manager and an unnamed
Fake militia that was going around there working with
Feds
We just finished right before the showing live today
False flag
A diva stage that was some other shadowy
Tomorrow
Comes out they can blame both
So he's got that this is this is how it goes
This is be the way that you
Explain
The fact that there were groups
That look
Almost exactly like
Your buddies
Yep
Yeah I mean you might as well just come out and say if we'd won
Happy that
The Patriots won and if
Since we lost
It was all antifa
Just say that
That was not us. Everybody doesn't like this
That's what we get it both ways come and going
Forward backward we get it
It's fine
Did the narrative here is being set and it's fairly well said I
Fake by Alex at this point
They like
It was
Was just these
Other people it's not
Not me not Trump's could pull some sort of
Visual and audio evidence of
Exactly the thing that I'm saying that I never did it solve the Deep state
Britax and rolls
Q is also deep state
How about Harrison Smith is he deep state
No but he wasn't actually even on air
Deepfake
That's a big deal whatever made that was good
Alex talked about that broadcast at all
Surprise egg
Deep State actors
In the form of
Q
Antifa
But there's another group there and that was the
The drop folks
Be surprised to find out what they were up to
This was meant to bring in
The point with the memo
Because
Football fans
Provocateurs trying to Riot trying to lead this
Trump supporters
Doesn't videos
We're kicking their ass
The cob
And try to break in the window
They got overwhelmed
So now the narrative
Is becoming the trumps people
Light off
Alright
Alright if you buy that b*******
Get the f*** out of my face
Forever I'm done speaking to anybody who's like
No that's what happen
Not only did Trump supporters not try and take
Over the whole f****** country
But they actually tried to stop the Takeover of the whole country
If you say that
To me I will never speak to you again
The constitution in America so much that they were willing to stand up
Fight against these malevolent
Communist invading forces like you
Anon people out and antifa
Protect the Capitol building
That they respect so much say it to my face
Say it to my face
Delta Force
All that we had lots of women were there
This was a fail
Volkswagen
Pipe bombs found outside with Mitsubishi
Hundreds dad
Cute art bleeding at all
2tarts
Hostages online
They didn't
Because the simulation broke
Down once actually got there in the real world
You didn't happen
A lot of the good Patriot
Optimal
And some Shadow Easton
Militia group
What we now know
So that's
That's quite a showdown
Yeah
Play The Showdown
Hellboy
People still doing that
I don't like that at all
It's kind of interesting that Alex seems to giving himself the green light to say that a lot
Yeah
A real
That he's like he's realized this
Is not profitable for me at all
Anymore
Great way to throw them under the bus
And you know like I can
I can maybe get some of the people back in
The same time
You know what
It's feels like to me it feels like
The relationship
Between Alex
And
Glenn Beck
In like 2009 but in reverse
Fox News
Being like I'm not Alex Jones
Not him
He's finally like free himself up to do that which is God's
And I think that actually works on some people like you saw flying
I can't believe Alex Jones denounced
Holy Cannoli 10 effective thing to have some other
And more extreme than you that you can point to be like
You know you hate that more
He's acting like the tide just came in and everything's moving up a level and it's
Unacceptable and I won't
Plucking allow it no
No no
After this storm
The capital
You know a lot of people heads
Some soul-searching
People ask
Difficult questions
And our conversation is going around about like what it would actually even mean and what it would take
Be together as a
The country again like unite and end
Alex is afraid of
About Truth and Reconciliation committee yeah I would say we're probably going to have to do something along the lines of the end of War
WWII combined with
D-BAT
Application
Something like a better version of that for all the white supremacy
I don't know if you know
Conciliation
F***** up if there is it real
If there were one hundred percent real one
F****** decapitating bread and conciliation
Correct
How do I
You must come to communist reconciliation
MTV
And say you're bad
But once you do that
Following a tried-and-true communist takeover
I think that Alex is misreading a headline here
Brennan didn't say that there needed to be reconciliation
I found the quote he's talkin
I'll tell you that there can only be reconciliation with repentance
And I think the single most important thing that republicans in Congress who helped facilitate this widespread conspiracy theory that somehow the election was
And the most important thing that Donald Trump can do in those remaining 10 days is to stop those lies
A to persuade their followers and supporters
The president like Biden is a duly elected president of the United
That was said by Senator Chris Coons on Sunday's edition of Face the Nation
I think that Alex just
Skimmed a headline that mentioned reconciliation and the host of Face the Nation whose name is
Margaret Brennan
I would bet that Alex saw the name Brennan and decided that it was John Brennan calling for communist style reconciliation
8 is
Infuriating to me that
That happened into that you're good enough to figure out
Exactly what happened I think that's
Frustrated what happened
Seems on brand 100% what happened
The host of Face the Nation are inside his mind
Terrifying
You're f****** Hannibal Lecter
Hannibal Lecter and he's the guy from Red Dragon or whatever
Cook though
At least I'm not good at it for frozen pizzas to be there I have no evidence that Hannibal is good
That's fair
I mean you have to have some sort of town to cook a brain and eat it
To the person
Yeah I guess parrot with cat
Barns that comes in
Barnes drops by his entire appearance here on this Sunday episode this January 10th episode
Is that
Hey you suck
Is there to beat up on cue
And she describes it as
A psyop
Which I have some
Some questions about
This is the most
Dangerous times
In the history of archons
Constitutional
Faces
Did Franklin 18:6
Actually kind of
Did they want to impose
Spy a ramrod
That was heavily facilitated by
A psyop operation of qanon
Inagua
Infiltrators and instigators
The thing that I run into is a psyop
One of the things that really
Fuel.
Lately and unless
Like you're at least
Has been Donald Trump retweeting qanon account
Right
And Donald Trump himself giving tacit
Acknowledgement oven support write all of this because it
You know narcissistically feed his ego or whatever I have to ask if
Trump is running asiop on himself
Asiop on you Robert Barr
Obvious
Is the Trump is antifa
Oh s*** that's why Auntie that's who really f****** antifa.
At the Capitol building
If Aunt Eva inspired the attack
The only answer then
Is Trump
Is the black
Sure
You have those people there who were looking real mighty scary
You know
The capital we had the lookie-loo types of beer
These people who are maybe just there to take
Pictures of themselves
Sprite
They're terrifying in a different way
Yeah if you had the real
Militia
Framed looking
In order to explain this Alex has
Already said that this is some
Militia that's working with the feds
But now
We get to Pivot that over and like
That's what the Q people
Yeah right
Sure
That that explains everything
Didn't realize
We're going to go in now
Pelosi and grab the
And ensuring of all those experts all this was done for
Special Ops
Laptop
If you're online
Play the latest
What are the alphabet
But it tells you to go take over the White House or the capitol or whatever
You're being set up for
Just like Arlington Road
Go see Arlington Road
If you're talking about the people that pledge allegiance to Q being stupid
I would ask you what about General Flynn
And his family
Who posted a video of the
Themselves pledging Allegiance
Tequila saying where we go one we go all manipulating the Deep State into thinking
That the Deep state had manipulated
Believing with
The Deep state
Says
Bacon
Run this counter counter counter counter when you going on right now after the first
From
I'm so tired Dan I'm just so goddamn tired they also posted that video themselves budging allegiance to que onda
4th of July what exactly you think is
The difference between pledging allegiance to q and Pledge of Allegiance
Not much
Snow
Dissect that now but I agree patriotism gem go ask
So
Apparently
Drop
I don't know if that's true. Other lawyer will and I don't care because they're
Ethical problems whether it's true or not
Like to be disbarred
Gear is Larry klayman free for this one you might be able to practice
I just love this we heard this before and I just wanted to because it happened again
Alex being like he works
He doesn't want me to tell you that
William Trudeau America
I make mistakes but I believe in humans
Vermont during this election fraud
At the highest level
We're going to put that out there
10 days op
Inauguration of B
You're not putting that out now you put that out a bunch already
Secret snow
Bulshit
Perimeter
Ethically not good
I don't know too many lawyers
Be like
Okay my client is the president of the United
Right I think
It's a good idea
For me to have a radio show with
That's good idea for me to Moonlight
Good.
It's iffy
I will say you know just looking at everything
Purely
Do you know take take morals take
Nearest everything out of that Chucky has him accurate points
That he makes
Tabac you in on which
A lot of people have been saying for a while
The first
He says he's not really one of those
He talks about how this is a brilliant psyop
Which
I8
I take issue with some of that
He has some other points that I think are are pretty good
Who is a
Brilliant disinformation campaign that is unique
If you look at other men
Boards
And posters that claim to be
Do not communicate
Do people who study
Disinformation campaigns very early on we're telling me
This was not true
Conspiracy theorist of people going down a rabbit hole and a random
Message board
This was showing signs of a c
Sophisticated
Disinformation
Psyops campaign
By somebody
With institutional influence and back
I do think there is a point to be made about how different this is than other
What things like
Sure like
Pizzagate got to assert
Point
And then it fizzled out
It's sort of metastasizing evolve into what they say
A bunch of other
Attempt
Doing something like this
Earlier conspiracy times
When you'd have people who would have these
Essentially like
Huge role playing
Things where they would do
No this is like an augmented reality participatory storytelling saying
It reminds me of Gravity Falls weirdly enough at the end of the cartoon
They had a little like statue
That was somewhere in the Pacific Northwest
That's where the show is set
And then a bunch of fans put together all of these Clues together
And wound out find wound up finding out that it was actually something that they had hidden in real life
My best little statue there and they found it
And it was a bunch of people all working together finding out all of these Clues to
Functionally the same thing is q
It's just this time there's nothing at the End of the Rainbow by Usher
Storming
Capitol building
There are some things like that are outside of the rounds of like political
Piercing propaganda
And then there are also versions that are
Conspiracy an internet message
Digiboard base things that could have turned into stuff like this
And made it into an augmented reality
I do I do think that that's fair I don't think it makes sense
Say that it's brilliant
Institutionally
He supported even argues that the main reason that it works is because
Kind of
Stupid
At the level of
The people participating
It's malleable and decentralized you can just
Everything can be anything
Which is why you don't
You don't want
Anybody Within
Institutional control anywhere near
Yeah
I think
What are you said that he had a good point
I think it was basically just remembering
This next clip
Talking about the element of it being like a game
And a lot of people have talked about that about how one of the things that makes it to Insidious
Is the way in which
There's like you're involved in this
Anyways that like their Gravity Falls thing was is actually a fun immersive
Experience
This is IA false
God carrot
If you wanted it on a on a pole
Some people catch Pokemon on the corner and some people
Find out that there's a secret conspiracy on the corner it's at
And barns
Is now talk
Talking about that
I'm about in warning about for a long time
And like Infowars
Perfectly happy
I guess ignore any of these warnings to the extent
But this was possibly profitable to see if we can exploit some of it
All just supporting Trump
So like
Hey let's Let It Be
But now
He's got to go under the bus
So I have got to be qanon
Let's say they were trying to
Something in the sky
That's what it was
Impart reality
A real house where something was hidden there were Clues
Pieces of wood Allpoint
You're part of the wall
And if you liked all that
I can't be a coincidence I must be something behind that wall
In fact it was purely coincidental
They were seeing patterns
It did not exist
Well what qanon brilliantly did
Was use the questioning technique without ever giving answers
Use vagueness and ambiguity
Appearing to get hospice
Pacific
Secrets
Really
Play over reality
Garage
Building
Found people if they told him it was a bridge
Bought the building because suddenly there was a bridge
Overlay
To the Pokemon go
That's exactly
I know that they think that there's a substantial difference
Between what they do and what they're describing
And I don't think there is
I know that it actually there's a
There's a bridge in front of you and then you jump in the fall
Alex just tells people that headlines mean something he has never read the article
It's the same it's the same amount of space that
It's being demanded of he's the ocean of a vague about his predictions he gives you secrets that aren't really real
Yep.
Yep I used to like I used to have bigger tea
But now I just grind them every time we do this
So turns out
Alex
A couple of months
Back heads
Threatened
To reveal who Q it's cuz he knows all of it
He never did do that use all
Just a
Probably it
Attempt to get a tattoo
This conversation becomes even sillier
Knowing that he's
Pretended that he knows who he is and he can expose all of it
Because
Apparently
I don't know if you know this
Hugh
Try to enlist Robert Barr
Alright I hate everyone
And they targeted people who they thought would otherwise be
Potential Act
Good sources of
Support
For crowdsourcing
Independent
Investigative journalism
Acculevel but above that were the Intel group ever with you
Because
Were you actually think you're fine
Fighting for freedom but you're working for them
Exactly
Okay so you are agreeing with
Alex when he says
Are you talking about
Provide us the name you've already said you can throw them under the bus
Yeah exactly would you want it to
If you hate them so much
I f****** hate
Yeah they're terrible little bit of breaking news
In the middle of this broadcast
Breaking news
That's a police officer the Capitol Police who died by Suicide
Alex has decided to turn that into a
News
Police Department
The high-level suicide of the
Police officers death
A story where he is
Is said to have committed suicide but it might be a murder bee
Because he happens to be the cop
Who told the cops to stand down and allow antifa to attack the capital
So he's basically cast this guy in not in this role it's just
Disgusting
Can't imagine
Being
Like anywhere near someone who is
Affected by the Capitol Building like that without
Instantly
Being like does anybody have a template
For how to sue Alex
I haven't heard him say anything yet
Does anybody have like a Mad Libs
For the way Alex Jones is going to need to be sued
There should be like a a whole section on LegalZoom just hold the suing Alex for the
Yeah yeah yeah and Bill fill in the rest for you
Guys family I can't imagine what I would be
How pissed off I would be if I
You trying to
Wayzata someone I cared about
Do I just lost
Just please
Suspicious because he ordered a stand-down so f*** yourself
Who'll keep his f******
Name out of your mouth
I'm not even saying to do tonight
No so annoyed Barnes is still on and he thinks
That whole thing
Where everybody it was like taking the pledge
Like Flynn
It was all a setup
So they could get Atkins
Spira chry was right about that
It's a devil devil, covid-19
Where the
Go to take
Have they have them broadcast
Selves taking these out
Broadcast
Other people that they were take
Basically a future
And then try to motivate
Other ones
To become more and more violent
The goal was to feel
This election was
Everything
Did this was the end of the
The world
So they had to take what
In frustration and fear
Were they would
Really one of them
To take action
How's that any different than Infowars coverage
Dni keep repeating
Inmyhead violence is not the answer because the moment he said
They wanted to make you feel like this election was the end of the world yeah
The only response that I can like I went red
There is flashing lights behind by Elijah's
No I ride you
Yeah but that's
People or run for the fucken devil and then
It's all civilization
No it's not it's not fair to treat audiences like this
Not the answer but sometimes it could
Part of the answer when it comes to Robert Barnes
I don't know I think just get get rid of that lice
You can't want to write moral off
That word specific
Just for the
Not infringing upon freedoms of speech whatsoever
If you
Say that before the election it's the end of the world if you lose it and then after the election you say
These people were trying to lie to you about that
You lose something you lose something afoot I hand I don't care I mean Barnes would just say like I didn't say that
Maybe that's true unfortunately you work
Look for news organization
News organization screamed it on air for
So I don't know
It's not even the pot calling the kettle black it is just both of them are the f****** Kettle in there just arguing with each other
Exactly
So Alex is now got confirmation
Who's passed away short hike ordered to stand down
And I don't know where you got the confirmation from
But based on the other news is reporting
I'm not positive
Gaston
No stuff we don't have to have sources
Most of time you and I are people asking us what's going on
Sources here
Magic torches are
We're smart people we live this Bob
You're smart I'm smart
I have
Confirmed
Capitol Police supervisor the one that ordered the stand down
Has committed suicide there's an internal Bulletin
Overrun governors
This is not
This is real
And there are more
Planet 24 hours
Looks like deep state
I think they're part of an insurrection
You actually bringing Marshall login to Saul
That's why
Detective shutting Trump up
Martial law
Will probably kill Trump
So Alex is reporting that there were four
Unspecified
Governor's Mansion that have been overrun in the governor's have been
Plead
Today is
The 12th recording
What day did you say that
Tents okay
How many Governor's Mansion
Alright so
You know what happened here I think I figured it out so this isn't
Like cute
Some kind of false reality
The president just got an internal Bulletin
I can't believe they kept that quiet
Because I haven't heard anything about these talking about is on the 6th
There were protests
Capitals and Governor's Mansion
And there were a couple of
Incidents where
Governor's felt
That's right yeah and I think that he's taking those bits of information that may be
He didn't know about until this point
And pretending that they're happening
In the immediate that's the only thing I can think of cuz otherwise
I would suggest if you're going to report this
For Governor's Mansion have been overrun
Deep responsibility to name the states
A little bit more
F****** information about it
Yeah
Yeah but it's not reality like qanon
I was working with the president
SeaWorld
Not know why but the real world
We're in the real world we're not the simulation
To only worship the simulation
Very sad
Mansion
A bunch of them
They're using us to go into martial law
They're not giving up with only
10 days left of trump
Because I want to repudiate
Everything he did
Before he leaves
The story
Does not evolve over there the course of the show it is dropped
On Monday
That makes sense
So Alex is not jealous of q but I think a lot of people are saying that he's jealous of you people like
Me I would also say that
By the way
Jonas Jealous
Secure threat
Co-op
Don't believe
So he could have co-opted them if you wanted to
Sears in from a year ago talking to Joel skousen
I was thinking I was thinking I'm just going to endorse it
Because
Sucking up so many good people
Yes are you thinking about using Q like a puppet
He did try that yes he did and it did not work no it did not
Which led to him being
More jealousy
I'm very frustrated
Gets down to the matter at hand he cuts through the b*******
People who are out there
Continue to crowdsource investigative independent
Continue to do independent Grassroots journalism in the
Seven separate from in divorce
Continue to be proactive and productive
Continue to support places like in for
The model for independent information
Any free press
And Free Speech
To stay alive
That's what's really about
It's about transitioning people back
Yeah making them feel safe
And not judged
We're coming back
Back to Infowars
From Q
Because
Q
I know if you know this
Chinese operation
Great
Glad to be here
Anybody part of Q
You're part of a chai, operation
Disowned Q
In return to American
That's right it's it's
2.0
And talks we have formal food
2020 prices
So we got real
Broadside attack on
Thank you I'm at Sunday episode
And that's most of what it is
It's pretty important for Alex to lay this all out
Because he's got a disavow and get away from the stuff that happened at the Capitol
People have got to take a fall for that
Have people that are going to fall are going to be 84 already villains
Qanon is now not just
Some kind of a
Whatever it's not to the same Noah Ki
Jealous of it anymore if they're bad
And also apparently
Some hired
Militia
Who's unspecified
Can get away from that and now when we get to the 11
Just Monday
I really felt like
Alex trying to
Turn
To the direction that he's going to
To be going at
I felt an amazing return to like
This is Sophie
Confirm elier this is like right before Obama got elected released
Pretending
Mirror days ago people didn't
Storm the capitol
Turns out like
Yeah
9 days left till the election
And Tifa
They're going to rule you
9 days from now
The globalist will be swearing-in
They're installed
Later
Exactly
Thanks kickoff
At noon Eastern
20 minutes and he'll be sworn in
The open communist Opera
And I fly from LA to New York
Austin Texas
Where's
Shields and guns and weapons saying
We own this country it is ours
An extra coming to your house
Because by day and by night
The Clinton Global initiative on record
These are the graduate students and students
Your rulers
Most of them pedophiles
So now we just kind of have a more extreme version of how he was trying to scare you about like
Job Americorps
Programs that Obama wanted to put
Yeah it's just kind of the same
Nothing it just feels like
Did you just you just going to pretend that didn't happen
I'm not going to talk to Republican about tax rates
Cuz I don't care
Cuz guess what is underneath that conversation
I want to kill the left
I don't give a fuk don't you dare talk to me about some program and its programs are done
It's hard to engage
Any argument
It's hard to believe that they did it's really what
Being discussed
You want to kill me
Now we need to deal with that and you have nothing like I don't understand why any Republican is allowed on
TV to say anything other than
We're sorry for wanting to kill you all the time
Because I don't give a s*** what they have to say on laws
I don't give a s*** what they have to say on
Tattoos or voting or anything like that
I think the issue is that the ones who do want to kill you
Don't
Feel bad about that stuff
To talk about all Republicans only get to talk about
Now they want to kill us
Sarah.
It's an interesting policy I don't think the video is going to take you up on this
Speaking of media that
It's failing Alex
Texas failing himself
And reality
But the reason that he's able to
I think try
To pull off
But moving back
George Lake
Just making you afraid of Joe Biden
Is the keys just decided that
Metal thing at the Capitol was antifa in q
And like we tried to stop
Where's the good guy
Those are terrorists
I want to be the place
And they're the ones that went
Stopwatch
Trump supporters
Say what
All the sides
How old is it is
I tried to stop them didn't work out they were
The ones who look like they were Trump supporters were just
People in disguise
It's no big deal we're still the heroes where the the oppressed
Worthy agree Bremen Morgan
Because they tried to make us look bad
Yeah there's no moving forward until all of these people admit they lied
That's it
Best you like honestly
There's no change to Alex
Programming unless he like
There's no change to those people listening to have unless Alex has to say
He's a liar
Laura Ingraham has to say she's a liar unless Lou Dobbs has to go on TV
And save the world I lied to you because I want money
Yeah but I don't think that even that would be that helpful
Because maybe it would ruin their careers
It's not going to solve anything but
Nothing's going to change until they
But I also don't think then we can start with others
What's the first step
Media figures have to have some sort of accountability for their b*******
They're the ones I agree that there should be some accountability it maybe they wouldn't be able to work anymore if they
I had to admit that they lied
And that might be a
I would just get replaced by somebody else who's Craven
Eventually you have to admit your life
Well
UB40
Going to enjoy your run enjoy it's going to be alright
Gravy and tells people have an Insurrection what you got
I'm sorry government and everybody
We failed
And allowed you here but
This can't happen
This can't
Well I'm of the opinion that even if those media Figures were to come out and be like I lied cuz I was
Make money or whatever
It wouldn't matter that much cuz the audience would
Ba disillusion Sage
Just be like well I got to find someone knew this person told out or something
And now it says the same complaint
About the Q people
Office
Back and watch
I know you folks are going to go away even once that happen
Because you bought a new Ally
Just like you said the Nigerian email scam
I'll get a millionaire when I send
Peekaboo the 5,000
Appreciate everything you've got to the scammers
You like your family for morning
Move on from that
Galaxy trick Brothers emails
Wow
He is right
They will hate your family for a born-again I am aware
That type of situation
So I always enjoy it when Alex gets in reporter mode
Many reports things were brought to his attention by his wife
Tennis partner
Perry hitting scoops
Next clip we get some
Second or third-hand information from somebody who works in security for Alex
Heard something from his mother
I know Alex is reporting it on air as news
I talked to one of our
Security guys that
Bonded security armed security
We have your mom
Is one of the head nurses a nursing home
They gave all the old people the shots and now a bunch of sick
I just got the shop last week
How many
You're not talk about this until next week then cuz it said number could be zero
Yeah oh no but then you won't spend the next week in fear of without number not being
Yeah but it's so important
Security guy talked to his mom and I heard this
You scared of something that may or may not happen
But I think I was probably only reporting
That's because of the spinner this media diet
Paul Institute website
Is important
And just began
Institute
Who's article is about a nursing home from New around New York called The Commons
Saint Saint Anthony
The most recent report from
Cnycentral is a number of death stare at 32 cents
December 21st
Which is when an outbreak of covid-19 begin
The outbreak
Predates the first vax
Donations
Many residents and staff received the first dose of the vaccine on December 22nd and the second doses I weren't
Be gone until January
Interesting the actual line that Alex's might not actually be factually inaccurate but it's
Still alive
We may well be the case that the deaths began after the vaccinations started but the headline is being used by people like
And like Ron Paul
Suggested there's a
Causal relationship there
This story is not interesting to Alex
Except as a means to convince his audience the vaccines are a deadly plan from the globalist
So he wouldn't be covering the story unless the message was supposed to take permit
Is that vaccines killed the people in the common
And that's just not to
Information is not
They're to be reported
Yeah
But that's why you got to listen to your Security Guys mom
Or maybe
The security guy making stuff up about what his mom said who knows
Spare for the possibility of
Just not going to happen
Nope
I like to convince you even more of that
I can't wait because I have got nothing but bad news on that front
Because
It's over for Humanity
Thank you I will only be lone survivors
I said it earlier
Now that I got them over for that
These people f*** all of these people Mike Adams Health Ranger
Noted rapper
Weirdo Ebola cure
Sure that's true
Cuz he had an approach
To the pandemic
After a while that was not good
Go down to lot of people going to die if people keep saying the s*** that I used to say he joined up with Alex for quite a while in
Doing covid denialism
When's covid paranoia alternatively
And
Then they had a little bit of a disagreement and he was not seeing
For quite a while
Because now it
It's time to just complain about Biden
They're the two of them can do that just
All day
Tom
Appreciate him coming on
25 and Shane crazy agenda
Joe Biden Kamala Harris will push
The election
Mike Franks were joining us what is your big takeaway about
Boy come back next time
I would I would have
Expect if this is happening that the two of them should really get into him
Discuss what their differences were and why he hasn't been on
For so long but I guess
We'll just pretend that didn't happen
Let's pretend
We didn't learn
Who is right
Because he had factually different
It wasn't opinion opinion
Because they were both make
Making everything up
That could be
So
Mike is thinking that maybe
Trump
Sure
Maybe he doesn't want to be present
Again not of America
Maybe
He wants to start a new country
Narrow window of opportunity
Does now but
How is fraulino Trump may have
You may have thrown in the towel at this point and said you know what
Swamp is too deep
Drain
You can't fix that in probably true
To really fix America is to let
The crop system in
Quotev
And Creator and then start
A new system on the other side
You may be thinking let's start a new Confederacy
Kind of sounds like what he would be thinking right now you guys are
Desperately hoping he's thinking
Yeah
I'm I'm kind of the I'm getting to the point where I'm like yeah
You guys should
Call of
Don't know where
There's uninhabitable places in Australia that have happened obuz alot of Republicans
But you said uninhabitable
I did mean uninhabitable and maybe they can terraform it we can send them to Mars and then
Then we could move
I understand there's some of that elusive free market over there a lot of Manpower that were wasting that could be
Beyond Mars leaving us alone
So
Mike is on
He has a little bit of a Time window
And that's because Trump is supposed to give a speech
In the middle of when this episode is on it doesn't end up happening because it gets pushed back
Ramen there's ask
Speech for the next day
Alamo
Yeah it's not the Alamo Alamo Texas
Sure it is all very confusing and it plays out over the course of this episode
We did not have a city version of the f******
Four Seasons
It's not for sure because it's Alamo Texas is also like a Border Town there's a possibility
That that still feeds into the messaging that I drop water slide
The Border
Time in public should begin and end with being racist towards
Southern border
That's great
Also
You would expect that he would want
To give a speech at
Alamo
Yes you would
But just like you would want to give a speech at
The Four Seasons Hotel
Right
It does seem like a pattern
This speech
Mike doesn't think it's going to be any
Think big
Trump speaking about
Isis
It's going to be
Kind of wishy-washy
Because you still got
In a week or more
In office and he
Happened so I suspect
She's not going to concede but he's also not good
Can I come in
Feel sad I'm sad to say but but we'll have to wait and see
He doesn't need to concede and he's already accepted that he's lost
So
I
Don't care what he does
At all
Mike doesn't want
Be quiet it that's Mike Pompeo
No he should absolutely be quieted
Mike Pompeo to
Cease a bunch of urls
Define as long as the other Wi-Fi connection
Vacancies
Amazon know if I want that
I do want to mention Alex's that
A secretary of state
Pompeo
Has a move that he could make
Right now
Back against this big check
Platforming of conservative
Individual
To seize the domain names
Amazon.com google.com
Book.com YouTube
Twitter
Seize the domain names
And
Charge those companies with
As part of a foreign
Cyber warfare attack
On the United States of America
Not go well I think I think that's a good idea I think people would respond positively towards that
I think it would give everybody p
Peace of mind
Happy Government website
As a hostile action I think that's good
Is 9 days before April election is supposed to go out of office
His date
Department is attacking
I'll be good
Maybe awesome I'm liking everything Pompeo
Right now it's really great
I love the way he's trying to
To convince people that it'd be a good idea for him to
Micah Adams
Might not have gotten the memo that I would save qanon now
Because he's coming in with some kyusha
He's got material that he could declassify wheat we know they have
Sidney Powell routinely spoke about
The information
Details from
305th military intelligence
Wasn't
That wasn't just fiction
So Sidney Powell submitted information in an affidavit that was supposed to be provided by an anonymous source
The chief codename spider with a y
Unfortunately she did a bad job of redacting her document so she accidentally docster source
Who's a consultant named Joshua Merritt
He claimed to be in the military intelligence
So working in the 300 fifth Battalion but that's all bulshit
Merritt was never an intelligence analyst and didn't even make it through the appropriate training courses in the army
When confronted about this statement and the fact that it's clearly not true
He basically said that he hadn't really read the statement he signed before signing it which raises a whole lot of questions about who in Powell's Team bro
Does that mean that you isn't that a
Service
Barn door or something
Open contempt
Put people in jail in on Lori's at the
Does 305th Battalion nickname the Kraken
Hydrated the server host in Germany than they've seized bunch of evidence of election fraud and prove his
Like CIA was involved and s***
This naturally all traces back to a Facebook post by some random qanon follower making s*** up
That's the story that Powell's affidavit was look
Going to reinforce
By way of assigning a story to a meant to be an autonomous person in Military Intelligence
The story is s*** when you know that it's just coming from a Cuban on
Facebook account
If you can pretend that there's some real deep inside or named spider
You can make more people like Mike Adams
Buy it
Anyway the point here is the people like Alex in like what whatever benefit they can derive from believing the same stuff that Q followers do
And they want to use the same sources of information that you and Autumn people do
But they want to pretend that they're somehow above it
And it is pathetic
Yeah the only people
Tweeting like I can't believe Alex turned on cue
Believe it
But also what we should be doing is showing as much division between the two is possible
While recognizing that both of them are complete Liars
And full of s***
Q people and info Warriors
To fight on the street
And they will almero
The exact you don't have to do anything
For them to end up at loggerheads
No but it'd be fun to Fan the Flames a little
It's interesting because it really
We felt like there was an opportunity
After the six
Where they could
Get past whatever differences they had
But instead it
Seems like there is now an Arab
Bookaboo
Different
So you would think that until next week when they all decide that there is no
Prince between em and adults
Could end up
Finding like common ground but
I don't think Alex impure going to die going down that road
Mike
He's he's learned that to some hackers
Some liberal hackers
Sure have gotten all the data from
From everybody who's ever done anything with parlor
Be worried about that the I bet
There is credible information coming out today that then left wing
Blackhat cyber hackers have been able to hack through the
Application
System
Ephesians light app downloading
Enormous amounts of data
Parler users
Perhaps including the
Another driver's licenses in metadata location
If people had uploaded
Story right now
I've been getting up from multiple sources
It's my understanding reading up on this that this is not accurate at all this is an exaggeration of what happened
Yeah and it's just what people had posted
On parlor people
The Archives
Not that you had access to all the peoples
Driver's licenses
Church
I did try to sign up for a parlor account because I wanted
To follow people like Alex
Those kind of requirements
Fox now
Absolutely not no why would I
SeaWorld Nazi why would you give somebody your driver's license
Insane yeah it's like the same people who are all up in arms about like gun registration
See also the picture of my driver's license to get a place where I can
Tweet by Wiggly
Justin same I understand why there would be fearing concern about that but by understanding
The point of recording this episode
Is that that is a deep embellished
And I think
Resume that works really well for someone like Mike
Is it allows them to talk about this kind of
They are going to go door-to-door there are going to be death-squad
Under a biden-harris Administration literally a carryout
Genocide against conservatives
Crossamerica
So because they took all the information from parlor they got all the addresses of everybody now Biden
I'm going to take antifa and they're going to go door-to-door
Squatting
Is bad
What happened on the
According to Alex
And
Antifa
Well everything until that point was good though
Now
If you don't want that
I I would say
You would not use inflammatory language towards your political opponent
But if you did want that to happen
You might say that your political opponents were planning on murdering you
Haha
You know
I'm not saying that he's he's a medic I didn't say that he just said hey we should go storm the Capitol building
But if I was
Somebody who believe things like say that
Biden and Kamala Harris will be sending death-squad
To my house
Maybe what I need to do is get a bunch of friends together you've arrived
The thesis of my
Neighbor
It's only five
I'm just a little tense
I understand
And it's weird because like you could hear a lot of the stuff that they're talking about and be like
Do you not
Recognized
What like
What world were living in now
This could have been on his show with Mike
Absolutely and I've got a contact
In Maryland
Today
They are setting up the FEMA operation there in in Maryland
Specific
Operation call and confirm
Caring for gun confiscation
Yep that they are setting it all up
This this is
We're back
We're back to this
We talked a bunch
Over the years
About taking them off the air and whether or not
This needs to be taken off the air immediately
Immediately it's because that is the exact kind of insight
People towards the sort of behavior children
That we saw last week
Immediate
It's so intentional
It's absolutely intense
If you are very clearly setting the stage for another of the same thing that you're pretending you didn't f***
Do you want in the first place
Need to be off the air a media
I mean let's go let's go back to the terrorist
You know it
It's not it's it doesn't work if you let everything go back to normal you've got a
Return to the
The temperature back up
Yeah pretty quickly
Yeah that's what we're seeing here we're seeing the exact same things
But Alex always does
Just as if as if
That event didn't happen
To Alec
It wasn't the natural they're going to put us in
Kabza Go door-to-door and Kill out the absolute absolutely am not at least
Partially
Responsible for the death of multiple people
Selena Alex Jones about because together
Cast of The Deep state
He's
Absolutely directly
Partially responsible for the deaths of all of those
People no no no
Clear about this we don't want any violence
It reiterated everybody here you know
Never initiate violence
We always have the right to self-defense to f*** you
Is there a general
They must be home
I hope the Trump will announce shortly although I doubt it but I hope
We are in a state of War we are now enemy occupied territory and the
Every
Every American citizen
To defend the Republic
I hope that's what he says but I don't think he will
The generals that are running that are ours
Defensive defense
Inoculations are trying to push
Martial law
I'm not about to keep I'm not about offense but all defense is actually are all offenses really actually defense
Violence offensively but all violence will be justified
I am challenging the health Ranger to a fight
No no no no stop stop
I will not sponsor this right
Believe that this is
Is this like
From a 2 years ago they recognized
Look at it doesn't feel like they're living in a world where people
Just
Stormed the f****** Capitol building
I mean you either have to
To completely lie to yourself or your complete
I think it's the ladder
It's just
Like that's just s***
That you can't we can't have this
They're they're doing it again that's outrageous
I feel like I'm losing my mind yeah I know
Mike down for this cuz you're going to feel like you're losing your out
You're going to feel like you're losing your mind about tomorrow
Yeah it is really happening in the anyway you can survive it because
Cuz perhaps about 10% of the human
Population
We'll make it through is you have
Have to be
Entirely self-reliant
Off the Grid
As possible
You need to be able to grow your own food and today
Defend yourself
And and then
Survive the onslaught of the mass
Illegal immigration that's coming
The troops the Chinese troops are going to invade at some
The government
The Titans going to unleash against America
Helpers that there visiting helpers that's right
That's right
Churches just like comments
Try to burn down the churches
Arrest the pastors who don't go along
With the globalist agenda so
If your pastor is
Truly teaching the word of Christ
He or she will be under attack
If there
They will be allowed
2xist
Churches underground farming everybody needs to understand now
We're losing the country we're going under long-term
Pablos occupation
Republicans didn't know what hit him
Gorilla
Is going to be a very big thing smuggling seeds marijuana growing tomatoes growing pumpkins
Growing squash growing
Everything's going to be under the radar
Including money
By the way because the dollar will collapse
Money will move to Alternative systems including
They're coming to kill you
Redbox
I don't know how you could behave in this way after
After an event like
What we saw I just don't
I don't know how you can
Allow yourself
To behave.
I'm just reminding myself of something that the
The great thinker Robert Barnes
BoBoiBoy
Which is that
They made these people feel like that election was the end of the world most important
Thing that ever happened since that's how they convinced remember when Q was talking about
Smuggling covid-19 remember all of those things being very important
Just a short. Of time ago it's almost
Jarring
Yeah I don't I mean I'd I just genuinely don't know how to
I'm shaking
Inconstant
Motion something needs to happen I can't right now I'm listening to him speak
I don't like
How much is a flight to punch Robert Barnes and
In the face punch Mike Adams
Okay
Put them in a line
Alright alright alright
Look I know that you're frustrated with Mike
But I just he just told me
But only 10%
Weco he's right they should go underground
Alright
Dig
A giant hole beneath
Toyota Mall in there
And then just closing
Oh and then the people will
The morlocks will rise once more
You might be mad at Mike but this is the last time maybe
The he'll ever be able to come on in for work
Mike Adams you're dead-on we are not
Exaggerating one
Santelli
Worse
And you even said worse than I could describe
I just won't lie to the public
This is the Megaton
This is the biggest all people better get
Absolutely
Could just say on a personal note
Because for all we know this may be the last time I can ever even appear on your show who knows
But on a personal note Alex
In the world
Can have
Just an inkling of an understanding
Personal sacrifice
Price that you have made
In order to continue to express your voice and
For Humanity
And Trump has made
Other than the greatest soccer
Debrox
Remember you're pretty.
I've had a sacrifice but no music no
You have it I just want to thank you enough
For holding the line
And
Speaking for Humanity
He wants to thank Alex for speaking for Humanity have a Humanity at least
My section of which is my person
Alex doesn't speak for me
Mass
Also like
Bekant
You can't say stuff like we're not embellishing at all what you're talkin about death squads coming
Conservative
If Biden gets into office
You're playing with fire
This is this is
Is not acceptable
Now they're trying to do it but bigger the
Yes we're allowing this to happen
Is insane because
Getting people killed and Jordan they're laying down the preemptive justification by saying it like
Vetiq and antifa they're planning
How to do math why I was going to go to the inauguration on the 20th
Nope but you're planning to do more and the same thing
Now it's just
Now they're there anyone people
As they speak words
People are dying
To to them
We have to deal with that the reality is that
You know
Mike Adams
Maybe
Tiny bit
And if he does maybe they'll get some of things they wanted
If we survive this
We are the real media for America
People's this out somehow that we don't yet know
He
He went down
Surrounded
His Spirit was good he did so much good
He wasn't perfect
Oh yeah and also I mean
Very good
Incredible internetda careforall
The definitions of
And
Doesn't want to see America turned into a radioactive Wasteland
Spell defiant
Yeah man
This is great Mike's like yeah I was Trump somehow it magically magic manager
To get a second term will finally do the things we want him to do
And then Alex you're not the only reason he's disappointed
Disappointing
Has he had
If he was under threat
They're going to Nuke cities
Get the f*** out of here
Grow up man
If Trump hold public office
Does again I'm storming the Capitol building by myself
That's what I'm doing I don't want anybody else there
Just me
Against
The government just banging your head against the wall
I don't care
So Trump needs to give an
Broadcast
According to Alex Shore
And then we get into some secession talk
I think that they want
Good herbal office
He's going to
Power off
You got you must mobilize
You must have a constitutional convention whatever you got to have
We just have to America
He must just tell it like it is
If for whatever reason
He is unable to do that
Then the American people need to make it known
Biden and Harris and others
That we the people
To your charity to your rig elections to your
False flag operation
We do not consent in fact we withdraw
Consent from you and we the people
Will declare a new in the
I believe all across this country
We will set up a new
But maybe starting by storming the Capitol building
Fox I know it's a it's a
Yeah
Every like week
The thing that's really difficult about this is that like we've heard
Talk like this on Infowars of bun
Over the years but never
In the aftermath of something like
What happened last week
Like that should be a wake-up call
4 people
Particularly people like Alex
Yeah that
Chick can happen
You need to be careful
You can't talk like
You can't
You can't say
That Trump needs to get
Intuit like an emergency broadcast where he calls
Biden ad
Terrorista trinese agent
And if not then we need to send a message that we're not going to
Consent to be governed for think of any way to send a message better than
Storming the Capitol building
But I guess that wasn't good enough is what Mike Adams is say
Right Michael there we go
Mike is a real f*****-up dude
Alex is really f***** up to
I mean largely it's about selling food
I'm not going to lie to you
I've already started Lively
As we speak
Good all the solar panel
What's your address
Christ
Why did the Staten 70 years of this
Turn on the other
Adorable Foods
Yeah Alex keeps having very different stories about whether or not he has the
This bunker setup
I don't care
More secession talk when you come back
For brakes
To do is he wants
Texas
Cuz they're cool
You are you are
24 social media companies
To have like a million-dollar fine every time they censor somebody
Don't put them out of business
And also
He wants Texas to make their own money
A Texas could also pass
New legislation or even via Governor executive order to say that any instance of censorship
Will result in a $1000000
Against big Tech
And then Texas could use that
It would practically be at least a trillion dollars
To defy
Deregulation
Texas to launch its own
Currency Texas has its own its own
Gold
That it can strike
Start a few years ago
Directions to launch its own currency so the people in any other state I'm just using taxes as an example
E-commerce and transactions in an honest money sister
Simone by the people
Rather than the
Fake fiat currency that Pineville use
To hand out more bribes
Kickbacks to governors
Great idea let's have states make their own money ever had a situation in American history where differ
Spring communities
Printed their own money he gets very confusing pretty fast
Did it work last time
S*** I think we just didn't
Try it Harden
I think that's what they think
About the Confederacy
Really sounds like they just
Another Confederate
Kalita successful Breakaway
Because of its energy at soil
Consolation of State
Arizona
Call Rana tooth
Oklahoma Louisiana Mississippi Tennessee
Texas country concerts
Absolutely there's there's a mechanism
For doing that a text
This could elect
A new app
President of the new United States together Louisiana Oklahoma Kansas and other states
I want to participate
And then Texas could order its citizens to stop
Paying federal income tax
Access to Washington was done before we can do it right now
This doesn't sound like a good plan
So
So if I understand correctly
I'd love to hear your breakdown
I don't want to hear you break
Call breakdown later
So Texas
Is going to
Declare a new
And then
So so the United States government is going to watch Texas.
Declare itself a foreign power
Yes
And then they're going to be like well course
You can have Louisiana in Florida that's really because you know they were
With that Colorado dry around to join us
And then
They're going to get
Territory and money from a
Oh I meant I imagined trade relations would be really wonderful between the United States
I feel like there's some issues that they might not be considering
There's that point but I also think that there's a logistical issues
Oh yeah they might not be considerate
Blade
No I don't know they're going to be able to sell their oil to foreign powers immediately there's no way that they couldn't
Just immediately start exporting oil
You know there's no kind of United States
Block you from selling this oil
Because it's our
Problems
But you know what they got the biggest issue taken care of already issue and that is who should be the new president
Beetle Idaho and end in Wyoming and so on that are going to really lead I think
The new Society out of
The collapse of the old
Corrupt
America swap
The old Empire
That's just being looted in its final hour
Democrats
When that happen
The new America
With a whole new honest money system for example and new laws
For the people
Are the people rather than
Criminals that are in the Senate and the GOP and by the way I'm now part of the never GOP movement
I will not vote for any member of the GOP
Ever again unless their name is b*******
Only Trump
Bulshit
Alright
Yeah
This is
Bucked up
You know what I was listening to this and I was
Is Mike Adams more f***** up than I remember him being I guess
Maybe it's just because I haven't heard him in a long time but you in awhile really f***** up
That there would only be lone survivors in the past that makes total sense
In order to help sell survival food
Bend it like that makes total sense
Secession in the end of the United States
In the aftermath of people storming the Capitol building
The part that doesn't make sense to me like this doesn't even work for wedding
To do ears are as my vibe
From all of them right now
Which is that
They are a bunch of whiny babies
Who want to take their ball and go home after they saw that they lost
Hi. Fortunately it's not their f******
Ball
Her home is shared
No f****** live there so you have to
To deal with it it's Madden
My politics are not
Divisive Dan
You're trying to murder me
So Michael leaves
And Alex
Complaining about foreign leaders
But not the ones
You think this time
Take shots
The Canada do your in the crosshairs
Global assist
What the Chinese system
We want dick
Gator chef
Taylor liberal there Gooding
Oh Alex has hurt people's feelings easily band
All the idiots
Part of power you're not
You're called useful
Idiots in the words of VI Lenin
Here's what Justin Trudeau had to say
I actually have China
Because there
Basic dictatorship is allowing them
Actually turn their economy around on a dime
Let's hear that one more time. Off abruptly
It's almost like they would probably be some sort of context to they're really cut off
Commentary
What is your favorite politician what's your favorite governor
Oats, does China
What's your favorite government they were on a date
I want to say that these comments were made by Trudeau back in 20
So it's a little older
2nd although they're not great comments and they did cause quite a bit of embarrassment for him to actually say that
China was his favorite
Here's his full answer
You know there's a level of admiration I actually have
For China because their base
Dictatorship is allowing them to act
Can we turn their economy around on a dime and say
We need to go green fast
We need to start investing in solar
I mean there is a flexibility that I know Stephen Harper must dream about having it a dictatorship that he can do everything
He wanted
That I find quite interest
But if I were to reach out and say which which
Kind of administration I most admire
I think there's something to be said right here in Canada for the way our territories are run
Nunavut Northwestern territories in the Yukon are done without political parties
Around consent
And are much more like a municipal government
And I think there's a lot to be said for people pulling together to try to solve issues rather than score points off each other and I think we need a little bit
But more of that
What's on news can now report that I
Prefer China
The end of literally said people are going to do what Alex is doing right now
Cool cool coco call Outlets
China guess what
Are we are we are but prophecy
Yep I don't know if anybody who stutters
These government would
Disagree with the idea that a centralized
Monarca cool Power structure allows
For quicker reaction
Yeah I made it here saying it I don't have
To get a bunch of people together in a boat if you're if you're saying it outside of it being a prescriptive thing like you should have that beat
You're just studying it
Instead of being like well we need to talk to our constituents and we need to have a boat
And we need to write a bill and do all day
Descriptively it's pretty hard to argue with but yeah it if you listen to the rest of that quote
It's really clear
The thing that he's bringing up
Is is that
Phenomenon how they can make their economy much
Maury Co
Friendly
Because of that basic
Dictatorship as he calls it
The government that he actually says is what he admires is the territories in Canada
Completely different message then what Alex wants to give across
Because he's a liar
Not even know
Yeah I bet he doesn't even know what the rest of that quote is
Doesn't give them care doesn't care why would
He just listen to The Sun News Report my lights
These people who was like
Q there f***
Looking stupid because you are
They're talkin to Military Intelligence
And that's what Alex
He keeps running into p
People at like events and they're like
Like Zach
I've literally been trali
What kind of Trance
It was overall
I was like a guy wear a t-shirt
Outside to like you
Now I'm cute
I know you're bad
With intelligence
They're like
Really that's funny cuz
Intelligence
Olive asked me what's coming next and so does he
Those are good
Music
Not fair
Call us
See what we think
Making
Fun of these people for thinking they're talking to Military Intelligence
Patty immediately to start sauerkraut Howie's would want to talk to her
I all I hear him say is just like
I know I'm like
You guys believe
Yeah
Stupid I can weaponize this stuff you guys are following
Of this b*******
You should be giving me money
I hate them
So are you just fed up with these are these Q50
But it's really important to understand that the reason that he's behaving in the way he is towards them
Mad about this this hold
Yeah because he needs somebody to be the people who have the zip tie right he needs somebody
Need to be the people who like
Are scary
Freddy's told his audience not really to be afraid of his EEG wearing antifa
Fiocchi
Argument
Family
So many people
They believed all that delusional crap in it
Control
During the 20th
Which denies us those
Hillbilly
A protest peacefully
They're going to have
Cute cards out there
What does zip ties and their gun
Believing they're about to overthrow the globalist
Awesome magic Brooke
Is the globalist
26 is good
And it's roped in so
Many people there now delusional
Next level
Better
Stab yourself a
Absolutely.
People take
Kindness for weakness
And I just can't believe I've always been so loyal essential oil person
People to treat
I treat them good
Experience
I appreciate the
Doctor appointment 47 years old
Next
What are we doing what are we doing I don't know
I don't know
I wouldn't expect
The Alex would like I finally get it
He's supposed to have known all this makes me want to start bark
Like I almost just broke down and started going
Yeah yeah
It's so it's No Nonsense
Those moments when he's just like
I see everything in the dryer
What next
Level recently
Journal
Yeah yeah
I mean
It does go a long way towards
Explaining how he tells himself he's not a serial
Killer
I've seen something new I'm not a serial killer responsibility for multiple killings
Yeah yeah
I don't know if
Can talk himself out of that one
These two people
They were at the Capitol
And they've trained themselves
The think
The Trump was going to send the special forces in
Right as we saw antifa
And they thought that they were the Special Forces
This is the story now
It was the two people
Under antifas control
The one in there like a group of morons
There's the Special Forces
Right on time
This time
Antifa
What's special forces for Trump
Behind
Waving in the Masters
Luckily
By the blessing of God
Did not go in with
But I saw that
Make me sick
Yeah it's so this is
I guess how the narrative is going
M22 land
Is
People
Not that antifa were Special Forces
I thought they were being directed by the Deep State also like what's going on here
Yeah Dan
What is going on
I don't know
It's everybody's fault but mine
Smile
Excuse me while me and my health Ranger friends try and make this happen again
I told you there be hypnosis
Some thought
And says go to calls and wants to promise me hypnosis
To talk to people who were there one Guy believes this address please
Maybe not inside but at the rally guy who calls in
Who believes that there was a guy on a megaphone
Who is hypnotized
Do you remember the media tower right there
Center
In the back
Yes
There was someone on that megaphone
I know a little bit about
Neuro-linguistic
Programming NLP
Whoever was on that Mac
The phone with literally
The power of suggestion
Hitting all those trigger words
Take it now people
It's now or never
This is China
This is our house
Push forward hold the line they were saying
Everything that would brow anyone and also Alex Jones
I did not say that
I'm here that but
I can tell you what I felt the things that I did hear
So this guy is saying that someone is using
Programming
To convince the crowd to act in ways that it would
But I also think all the things that he saying
Diversant are there exactly what
They would be saying in a bullhorn
Expensive
You guys want this
You're just mad because it happened before you could get enough people together to succeed
Yeah
Angry you're going to be mad when people start to take this seriously
Yeah because real mad whenever you start to get it
For a very long time
Some people have not taken the issue
All right wing
Media and how it feeds into
Extremism
They've not taking that seriously at all
Yeah
Well made
Why we have
Any
Relevance
I think that there is an unfortunate
For them
Trend
And that is where people may take this seriously now and then
Yeah it'll be it'll be good though cuz imaginiff
Somebody was like
Hello
On every TV show just sitting there being like
Bulshit
You know
Yeah but it's
That's that's why I think I speculated about this back in the day and I actually don't think it's a good idea but
If Alex is going to do his show
I have to be his co-host
You have to
His version of net neutrality
So there's some other callers who talk about boring
Stuff about being there at the rally I didn't find any of it to in
Interesting but there's one other color that made me chuckle
It's called magazine
I need to start a magazine to where we can leave it at
Walmart
The freak
Magazine store
Watch all three sounds great
Do you understand
That had 1/1000000 response of a digital format
Here's my solution
Media
I love that
It's called cuz he's like you know we need magazine
Look up Donna Magazine with a lot of money to make any anything all that no one gave us anything about the publishing business
The digital stuff
Lots more people
The college response that is amazing
Digital stuff's not do anything either
Which
FairPoint
We come to the end of this and we need to do Wednesday episode cuz there's a pretty
F***** up
Yeah at the same time it's like
You know if we waited until Friday this would
Pile-up
What's going to happen tomorrow
We're not a new show that the news backs up fast now
Wii Sports
We've already forgotten that Alex interviewed mycslink
Yeah yeah who gives a f*** about that
So
Anyway
We'll see what happens I'm sorry to do this to you
Yeah works up in a tizzy
Used to process all of this and then
The show
And you have to admit it
You know and that's
That's but I'm
Shaking with rage and then I walk away
Haha
Into the Night
Some would argue that your job is easier in that sense anymore.
The stuff for a lot longer
You're better able to emotionally process
I'm a loose cannon
Nobody should take my gun and badge right now
12 couldn't you have neither a gun or a badge
That is true that is a bonus
I need to know it's not so much that I'm able to emotionally handle this much better it's that I steal all the candy that our listeners
Uno campus
Now you're the more valuable resource
Will be back on Friday Jordan but until then we let it we do it
Mileage underscore fight not go to bed Jordan
Please find a local charity or bail Fund in your area to help out people who are
Still doing God's work
But until then
Clark
Alex
Birthstone colors