Alexandra Thurston color
We're couple dudes like to sit around and drink novelty
Doesn't talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Today we have
Aspire Broods
Cherry cran Gourmet soda definitely Gourmet
Prediction prediction
Is it going to be cheery cramp
Or just
Cherry cranberry
What do you think
I don't know I don't actually know what
Applying the word Cola mean
Romania means it tastes like a Coke but with cherry cranberry flavoring
Okay
Or is it
Straight up fruit soda
Let's go with
Colquitt
Let's go with Cherry Coke
Let's find out
The big reveal
Jordan taking a swig
Wow
This is
F****** delay
Yes it is so good
This is the first
It's so good
How many drinks
What is
Taste like
No idea
All I can experience
I will open mine up during our first
Clip but first let's get to an out-of-context drop of Alex Jones let me ask you a question
Oh yeah I forgot about that
Good point
Listen
Can we take that again
Is there
I know a lot about Alex Jones
I also
Riddles with
F****** Frodo in the dark
Weird Troll game
Great
This is the first honorary
For quite a while he sent me what may be the world's greatest female
Sort of lift my spirits
Whatever I feel like
It doesn't matter that we're doing the show
I can take a little look at this email
Alright that's very reassuring I appreciate it very much
To the point where I've been trying to write him back
For about 2
2 weeks
And I can't
And I feel like an a****** so publicly
And give you
An honorary policy walk status
Welcome aboard
Welcome
Don't need to
Email was so good
Dan apparently kept to himself and did not tell me about it which I can only assume
You talk some serious s*** about me.
The show is garbage and it's
Should just be dead too much we just want dance analysis
I know it's gorgeous I was embarrassed through so
I have to hide those things
Anyway thank you very much Brian
Whenever people
Thanks
About Alex
We're going to be in Berkeley
Part 4
Of my investigation into what the f*** happened to Alex Jones in 2015
Recovering the time fan
Of July
Through July 21st
The weird road ahead
But there's a lot of stuff
It's very worth
Disgusting
And I was just being
Very weird
His head space is so f***** up
And I think I started to piece
A few things together
I'm going to give you some of this analysis up from
I think
That Alex Jones
More than being just a
Is someone who
Tricked by Propaganda very
And I think
I like to play the game where there's something Supernova areas going on in Rodger stone is pulling the strings behind him
And that may be the case
But a very simple explanation
I'm starting brick
Scientists have discovered that Alex Jones is a
I'm starting
To get
That possibly a lot of his transformation
That there is weaponize propaganda going around
And he is as much a
Proponent of it as he is a victim
And one of the things that made that click into place
Was I was listening very carefully to James comey's testimony
And one of the things that he was at
Was when do the FBI B
First aware
In Russian
Influencer camp
And his answer was
Summer of 2005
Which is right around
The era when we're talk
I've noticed
Instances of Alec believing bulshit stories
That were
Deliberately
Trace back to
Russian
I don't I don't know if we can
Definitively say that
We can definitely say that he believes
Complete lies
Susceptible
If
He was hack
There's all sorts of s*** that could be found out.
Campaign
It's entirely possible
Someone who is trying to use
Influence campaign
You're trying to use propaganda to sway public opinion
One of the very obvious targets would be
He's clearly crazy
He's hiding
Something
Is
Control he has a lunatic fringe the volume
Like it would be someone who
Obviously wanted
A lunatic fringe dad
We can probably safely say
Proportionally more violent
Send the rest of us
Yeah
So
I don't know if any of this will bear route
But that's something that I'm starting to look at
I'm starting to
I feel is that he just false propaganda
Santa really easily
And we'll see a bit of it over the course
Episode
But first
In July 14th
I looked interesting ride
On July 14th big announcement that he starts the show with
Because I will get
At the end of the squid
I'll explain why this excites the s*** out of me
I think you'll know
I think
Beautiful
Loaded transmission
The first 3 hours
4 hours
Or some station
But I am looking for
Sometime this year
But making the force hour
An intense broadcast
We're more than 50 articles
Will be covered everyday
Boom boom boom
Comment from the people on the panel
Make a call
Go to the next story
How's it going to go with
So first of all
Emoto really
Even for you sir this much closer to John Rappaport
Right within the context of 3 hours
But once the fourth hour comes
Is there a posse
Ability
Episode where he does try this
And that is the beginning
Fourth hour on this episode on July 14th
Yeah Leanne McAdoo
I mean I mean my work talking about like the Roundtable
So like
Bro I don't think
He ever does that
You can't just just the idea of
Alex trying to coexist with three other people allowed to talk at the same time
02 I think he's been able to
Beautiful fire
I think the premise is he's not involved
I've been secretly training
Having them on air that's a good idea Naman are they don't know I'm building
Do something tonight
Anyway
Another thing he talks about is how he's going to launch a TV network
Which is important because he's
Lying about that
Currently
Years later you still think we're about to do is show like through
I think there's reasons not to get to
To freak out
But Alex's
Stated plans in 2017 of having a
TV networks
But if it does happen
Be very worried
Because
Becomes the most
Stood TV network in history
Worries me just because I don't know if I'm ready to allow my tax dollars to go to that many
You remember how likespike
Big TV on
Immediately got sued
Does bike leaves like that's my name
Do not remember
I can't
Say this enough bring on the Rapaport
Yeah I'm excited for that to happen
Lee Ann McAdoo host the fourth hour in this
Episode and she is not ready
It's just very silly house somehow
Weave
We've developed
Weird
Genre
4 cm to in
He's a f******
Miserable monsters
Enjoy from everyone ends
Vaccination
But at the same time
Weirdo monster that lives in a cave
That's part of it
The googly-eyed Muppet druid
Rapaport when he shows up here
I don't know man
The other other rounds
The greater question
The grey
Weather Gandalf
Radagast
The Lords of the Ring goose
So some people have sort of a religious feelings
About Lourdes
Would you agree with that
So take it on as a religion
I'm talking about nerds
I feel like you're leading me toward something
Not a smooth
Tara is really good
Delicious
Hawaii
He's been getting more religious
If you think that it's a complete thought
You're wrong it's like galadriel's water
People contabil
Are you getting more more religious
Babies wrapped in gold foil
China by the thousands
Younger
When you look at when you look at
The borders wide open and El Chapo
Welearn
His wife moved or have her baby so he'd have an anchor baby
The billionaire drug dealer
Even lives off us taxpayers
It's a joke
Find me a joke that's why I'm committed to fight as hard as I can
British Special Forces
Special Air Services
Fortune favors the Bold
What's a hatchimal
But they
Closures
All Peoples of the Earth
I will remember you are special
Call this is
We only see Errol Spence
Just getting the lights
Not seen ear has not heard what God the universe has in store for us
Going to let the globalist
Roloff reality put us in a maze race
Control us dumbass down
Horse and buggy
Buggy whips and horses anymore
We are We Are Powerful
The 41 others evolve
Alex has been getting more religious
Was there actually a reason in there
Yeah it was it was the closest hip-hop
Foxholes on YouTube
They're causing all the oceans in the hundreds of Millions
Billions
I don't know statistics
I don't know what I'd like seven and a half billion on the planet right now
Like
I don't know
100 million baby
And then like
So
If there were hundreds of millions of a borscht
That means that if
He were to stop
Entirely possible
We would have
12 billion people on
CDC
Disease Control in 2013
660 4435 legal induced abortion
Reported
So that's that's in the United States
Is crazy like the babies covered in gold foil
We got a Willy Wonka's factory situation gone there where babies were on conveyor
Conveyor belt
There was a guy who got arrested with like some babies covered in foil like mummified babies
He was trying to transport back
To China
Philippines
I don't read the origin country
He was doing that
Because
I have a very interesting relationship with
Fetuses
Especially ones that
Have died tradition around abortion where
If you get an abortion
Junior supposed to create a shrine to the baby
And worship
The fetus goes
Appease the fetus ghost
Look up food
And stuff like that to help it
The Otherworld
That's like that's like a box
Old Norse
I don't know enough
Speak on why someone would want to buy some
I have no idea
More complicated stuff going on there than Alex is really wrestling with it's not for people to
Eat them
The other stuff is so crazy
He believes in God but then he gets into
There's 12 Dimensions there's probably things living in
I'm out I want to get I want to just
Jump forward to another day's show because
Embarrassed
Playing here
In this clip Alex Jones talked a little bit about what he believes
About something
Specific to scripture
He's not the bad idea
He shouldn't really be
Brain scripture
Christianity that most people know
Hugo
I don't judge people
I can speak for God but just hit my gut level in my spirit
I would personally do it
Strong showing
Assisted suicide and end eugenics
As if it's just some choice
Of somebody
This is about devaluing human life
White
So he's against assisted suicide and stuff like that because he Compares it to a movie
Government
Control
They have some government girls baby
Anime if you look at the Bible 27 people who committed suicide clearly in the Bible
Six of them are called
Specifically Wicked
In the
Further
Job 1:21 says Naked I came from my mother's womb and naked I will depart
The lord gave and the Lord hath taken away
A lot of people interpret that to mean that the Lord gives you
Your life will and the Lord
Takes away
When your life
1st Corinthians 10:13
He will not let you be tempted by more than you can bear
But when you are tempted God will also give you a way to escape at 2
Lot of people interpret
To be either Temptation towards
Or temptation to eat God will not give you more than you can handle more than you
Compare which is
Clearly bolts
Further what reason to disbelieve the Bible that would be definitely
Further one of The Commandments
Strictly speaking a lot of people believe that murder is
Suicide is murder your murdering yourself
It would be against
If God has given you life you don't have the right to
To take it away
That's a pretty consistent theological message
Especially if people who have a pretty hard line on the bike
If you're anti-abortion than the same logic
What you think so Alex is in this weird f****** religious-based either way
I just wanted to bring that up cuz I think you're dumb
I don't know if you know this or not but when Alex is growing up
His
Actually read him
The Apocrypha
They didn't have a
King James
They had a
AB tattoo on his arm
Maryvale
Like 10 years ago
That one didn't exist
Grew up studying gnosticism smarter
You know what's going on with the bar balogh what's going on here
He was boring fan of the Week
He's more afraid of the ones where Jesus
Dragons in.
Who killed other kids for no reason you know the good stuff
CIA
Something really important
Alex is only said that he doesn't trust Trump
All these are things very negative
Things although
He does agree with his rhetoric
Las Vegas
Hates the hits
Does not think it's big
But let's move on
So on this show he has an interview with
TV
Movies on TV
Maybe just a radio host Larry Elder
Who is
Is big
And I think Alex is a little bit blindsided by
Oh really I think he's not ready to have this interview was he not expecting
I don't know I'm not sure exactly I think he wanted just to talk about race it with a black guy
And accidentally got sidetracked
Into
Okay
So what he was
When he was ostensibly doing is
Like pointing to any alike
He's he's got a
Global
Just closes his eyes and points on is like
Find me a black eye
And I will put them on the show so I don't feel like a horrible races
Cuz I'm totally horrible
Conversation
Identity politics
Largely what
He wants to talk about
Globalism
That's why they're now drilling down
Mom
To just kill
Alex
Legal aliens
But he soon well
Indicative of
Exactly what this interview is
Alex wants to talk about the globalist to take away identity
And s*** like that
Of course
Mostly influenced by
Confederate flag
Because of terrorist
Immediately in answering that question Larry Elder
Why would you
Like
Alex
Expect any of his guests
With no prep time
Apparently
Like this cuz you're gone Infowars you're not buying it
I-16 Alex does very consistently regularly
He has gas really hard
Because of course he does
I've noticed this text
You heard it a little bit there
These people are trying to outlaw
Pretty early in the interview
He'll repeat a false story
And get them to sign off on it
As they will know that it's a full story
But they don't want to challenge his authority on the show
Platform
And after that point they are essentially copper
Right so
I know that he does
Also I think
He has a big enough stable of people who are like
On the globalist
I mean yay globulus whatever but did you hear about the
This is the first time Larry Elder
Just that we don't we've not had him on an episode
I'm sure they've a pre-existing relationship where they both know that each other yells about global
So I
True
So
The interview goes on a little bit
And Alex prices
Still doesn't really
Who trust Trump
And misrepresenting what he's
Serious is going to drop out later
But regardless waterproofer world that way.
So that's where he's in this in the middle
Trump Larry Elder you still saying
I don't trust her
But what are you saying
Is true so we had
Defense
Free to find it
Grapes
The logic of a lunatic
Larry Elder steps
I disagree
Recalling
Election
No not about it
Not in globalist line
The thing and then the word means nothing
Cases of legitimate rape
The body has a way of shutting that down
Right
And then the second
It's legitimate in front of rape has
Nothing to do
With
Whether or not somebody lies about
That wasn't
Entirely about all of the like
Well
Legitimate rape is you have
Have to be beaten up
You can't be cold worse
Right
Pressured on it
You can't give in
You can't
To do it you're like well I guess the
This is my fault
Illegitimate
That's not a thing
Then the second
Airport Park
Magic
He said cases of legitimate rape
Magic is
The body has a way of shutting that down
Larry Elders argument is that Todd Akin f*****-up I apologize
Yeah I've Trump isn't making that problem he's not
Probably would have done better
I think that's what we really learned
Again
Dog whistling is for losers
Just out now bigotry
Like earlier early episodes of the show
Trump should not have fired Flynn
The oldest probably wouldn't be happening
Put his dick on the table it was like
No
God dammit
How
Because that's also the
The last time that is really listen to anybody there either
It seems like
Yeah like
Hit everybody was like hey you got to get rid of Flynn this
This is a bad idea
Non-stop from there and
Now anytime they're like hey Trump
Don't do this
He's like
Exactly.
You think this travel ban shouldn't
Call the travel ban cuz then we
It was on the campaign
Eagle
So a little bit longer
Larry Elder supports Trump admits
Good Trump probably is just out for
For his overall Empire
Oh I think it's all of the above I think of Donald Trump
And maybe he'll make even more money
Univision
NBC
But he made a loser
I think overall
My brand be even bigger
The possibility that he sincere
He thinks our deals with the various other countries are we
Anythink
I'm going off the grid for this holiday
I guess
Underage way.
That pisses people off that's the first thing I wholeheartedly agree with
Clearly clearly with Trump in office in the other Republican
Still not doing anything
Group of West Larry Elder is
Absolutely
Conversation we're having is about
Probably f****** around 4
The eat to the point where Larry Elder even says let's not discount the possibility
And Alex because he's putting his business
Things on the line not realizing
So much for abusing Impreza
Oh man
To the point where all of the alike
They are right
About everything
Being a publicity stunt Ma
And an idea to make more money
It just so happened that he got the presidency
So he's using it
To generate more
Department of Justice
Is arguing that you should be allowed to take money from whoever he
Department of Justice in the United
Midstate
Actively arguing
You know that Constitution
Not a fan
Why we're on this like little Trump thing
I loved that moment
From his press conference
Last week where he's at the Romanian president
And there's nothing about waivers but Visa waivers where Romanian
He's like
We didn't talk about it
I brought it up what the f***
Just watch that clip alone
No not not go
Dick everything else away
Very bad
Not good
To trust
My brother was born in Bucharest
So I have no relation to
Miserable
There was also back in the
Please do so I mean that hilarious doing a lot
Better than
Back then
Larry Elders knock
You've got to be involved in two more clips
That are pretty offensive
One is about Charleston and then the other ones just got race this one is wild
Kim
The first person who shot freezone
Yeah
Turning into the argument you could had a nice
Then I'll blah blah blah that stupid argument
It's a dumb
Is the idea that like
Okay
Someone there
Their fault cuz they didn't have a gun
And further its
Society's fault for disarming churches
And it's his fault
That these people died not the person
Not the white supremacist who actually did it
So
Interesting juxtaposition
It's because we
The anti-gun agenda
Supremacist
Cuz he the Charleston
Shooting happened
You got two weeks
Before this
But there's a shooting in Chattanooga
A couple days
After where we're at now
Very differently
You don't
I said that
Jokingly
And then I realized that's
Exactly what they believe
Every time somebody gets shot
As we say
Yep that's
Genuinely
How do we lose to these people Dan
I don't know
These are the dumbest f****** people
Speaking of unbelievable
Who's the blame for races
Oh no
Cold ones
Yeah baby you're blind all the time
Babywipe
People one of the big reasons you don't
Understand races
Because it's
Course you think racism is
In a problem because it's not a problem for you
Do you know really
Expanders
Try and relate to other people's experiences understand just how Insidious
Look at a person and be like hey what did you tell you that you're like
Oh that's probably true
I should respect
Telling you
Your life is
Experience
Is wrong no cuz you tell me your life experience my response
For the 40
We we see just a little bit of softening analysis
Position towards Trump
And we move on to
The 15th
Which we're not going to cover cuz David Knight hosted
But something important to remember
Dave
July 15th
Helm 15
Kicked off
They was real and then later
Do you know if you said it was real for sale we don't have audio evidence of that so let's not make
Good reason to believe
We can't prove it but we can't prove it
But
Then I
Will retract that
We will see
Where is Heather's that a little bit later
What Alex is back in studio
Should scare everyone
Donald Trump speech
Coming up
Spoiler alert
He still thinks he's a shell
Becomes a little
Zoe on this episode
Has all over the goddamn
Klusterfuk of weird narrative
Strange things
She says
But one of them is Mark.
Thank you
Shut up it's just him talking
With the clipboard
This one is about how Mount Rushmore is racist
Roosevelt
No I mean that they took
American Native Land Park
People who stole those American Native
You know what Mark Dice doesn't wrestle with
So this video and I wanted to play this clip just because it indicates again.
Insidious cycle that Alex Jones perpetuate
Wherein he has one of those reporters go out create some
Video that doesn't say what he pretends it says
Drudge links
To it
You know it gets a link up somewhere
And then Alex Jones repeated as new
He's going to say that there's a headline
Then the headline is
That people are calling for the destruction of Mount Rushmore
Is entirely based on marked Isis video
At the end of this clip
Is very short
But this isn't news
Who's up top
I'm in at the end
He says he told Mark Dice to go make this PO
Nonsensical
That's how you tell Fox News operated
Almost from the very beginning
Their trick was always to have their news
People say
A basic story
People would be like
This is what
Is really happen
And then the next day the news would keep
Keep it in the cycle by Staind
People are saying
Are commentators
It's just people are saying
We're reporting on what
They're saying we're not
Verifying a Taurus
Just so happen
The people that said it are on our Network
Where can we have a
Insurance that you have their thoughts
Senior
So here's our reporting on Alex Jones.
Video of Obama supporters advocate
Mount Rushmore
We told you that was coming
Is it
Call Bird
Rushmore
So I mean
Yeah that's basically him saying go ghost
Go out and try and get us evidence for whatever narrative we wanted supplies
It's it's quite literally fake news when he says
I told you this is coming
I told you this video was going to be released
That in much the same way he predicted the people will be calling for the American flag be banned
I made these predictions and then I told my reporters
To somehow justify my stupid f****** predict
That's why he's a hundred
Is that right all the time
All the time long as you make it happen
Call the time
He's Ronald
Now
This
Is going
To get
Bad
It's going to get Mark Dice
Something else happened in July of 2015
That
Is really
Funny conceptually
But isn't funny at all
Is that is that
The Center for Medical progress
And made all those behind the
Videos
About Planned Parenthood people
Selling baby parts
That's right
Right
15 felonies
I believe the sentencing is still to come
Are in big trouble
Big trouble for this and I'll explain exactly why on the other end of it
But I want to really point out
Alex Jones f******
Buy is it
He's so into it
He talked about it a little bit here
Mmbn
Tire show couple days later is all about it
Well that was a
And that was all you heard that narrative
To the point where Noah just like
Just like Obama
The secret Muslim
Yeah
Still believe
They still believe that Planned Parenthood sells baby
Yep
Even though the people who disseminated those videos
Are going to jail they're still like I know that was true there's
Prosecutor because powers
The beer whatever
The Center for Medical progress
His organization
They set up a fake biomedical research company called Biomax procurement services
Under the guise they poses
Potential buyers of aborted fetal tissue in Oregon
And secretly recorded Planned Parenthood officials during the
Videos
Which promoted is showing Planned Parenthood officials
Price haggling over baby
When the full unedited videos became available
Appliance Watts
Not make money when donating fetal tissue from abortions
To scientific research
According to the lawyer for Planned Parenthood Rogers
Biomax proposed sham procurement contracts
Offering
1600 dollars for liver Infamous fetal tissue
I went back and I watched all of these videos
They are
Hey mostly additive
Anyone
You don't have an agenda that this supports
Would be like
The f*** on
It's so crazy
And Alex is so in
Like I can't wait till we get to the 20
Cuz that's when he really tease off
He is so you can't wait till we can
Also the other thing
To point out
Is
Do you know these guys
Umizoomi
Specifics here
On March 28th 2017 this day
And his cohort
Recharge the 15 felonies in
In the state of California
One for each of the people who they had filmed it.
I am really videos where they didn't get concerned
Making it seem like they were committing a crime
And one for criminal conspiracy to invade
Privacy
Now
The thing
Important to note is
That
This is funny
Okay good
Ivory
Now I'm free and clear everyone
The Gate of their client
The Senate
The the house
All the state governors
Everyone invested
And everyone cleared
Everyone investigation
You know who didn't
Set a reminder
Everybody
But this one this one's particularly song
On July 30th 2015
Indiana Governor Mike Pence
The state's investigation
Did not find any evidence of wrongdoing
Planned parenthood's handling of Beetlejuice
If Mike
Pence had to say that out loud I bet her
His babies die
Yeah it's just the number of Investigations that were opened into it there likes
Select committees
The the
United States
Committee on oversight and government reform
Strongly against Planned Parenthood are all like Flock there's nothing here everything
Possible within that invest
So hard
That wasn't
There was even a
Slight Urban likes the entirety of the claim wasn't proven
Catch them on this
Al Capone
Appearing charging Planned Parent
Select Committee in the United States
But the house
Commerce select investigation panel on play a
Was formed
The further investigate Planned Parenthood
Photographer woman Marsha Blackburn serving as the chairwoman
September 21st
820 to recommend holding stemexpress
Business
Did research
Got tissue from Planned Parenthood
In contempt
Failure to comply
Subpoena the six Democratic members on the panel protest before the vote
The committee's final report recommended that quote
The National Institutes of Health.
Stop funding fetal tissue research
I'm at the huge
Health provider Planned Parenthood be stripped of us funding
According to science
Publication
The report contained multiple inaccuracies
Democratic members of the panel respond to or vote on the final report
Released an alternate report
In which they criticized the committee for relying on McCarthy era tactics
And a relying on unsourced unverified documented writing of the report
So
That's sort of some of the aftermath of this
I get that you
Don't don't you like
Not be
Disease-ridden
Are you a big fan
Sure do you want to do you want to continue not being
Do you know new diseases
Can happen
Stroop
Evolve
Don't you want to research this
You want to learn more about it
Not just because you know you're fine now but be
Because maybe in the
In the future there will be in
Information that you want
You're talkin Voodoo My Man Zero play God
Don't blame God
You can't
You can't praise us
Spirit
And keep yourself from getting
Give them science
Do you know what the other thing
You know what
Panel
You don't get any side from now on
It's a 14-member panel six of them walked out
Your phone
Got soaked
You know what
We dip
Land on the moon because you're not allowed to believe
The true comedy of it too is in this video there like this guy
These high prices
That they're going to
Pretty much across-the-board people are like
That's higher than
Repack
But they're haggling
But it's the reverse of what you expected
The person coming to high
Cuz they're trying to make it look like there was a
Tissue scam going on
It is like $50
For samples
Credentialed
And certified Resource Center
Because Quincy
Parenthood
By the GOP
For doing
Providing women in
And help and how
You know that kind of
Making sure that we don't get
Not
Disease-ridden
Bright
They hate him for that
So Planned Parenthood is always
It is always being
So of course
You go and trying
They have
Safeguard under
Safeguard
We will show
Not even the slightest bit we will give them no evidence
Even though when they close down those
At the end of the day we will have been
In within
Perfect
Understanding
Compliance with the law
Well the other thing is
It's gone for good every single one
This is so indicative of what I talk about with propaganda and true
Like this
Still people believe
It's utter horseshit
Still people
The damage is done you can explain away that like editing videos
These people have all been investigated by
Legitimate boards
And cleared of any wrongdoing
Most likely
F****** sued real heart
Now we're getting the clips of Alex
Do you have a couple clips about that
On this episode on this
And what's really important to remember is all the people in the videos are women
A lot of respect and dignity
I'm sure that there will be
0 comments
It's on there
I don't know there are but I'm not sure if I kept any of those in
Because I actually think there's something even more important
Because on
Clearly using coded language to evoke class
He does this a lot but it's
Almost it's almost never this
Clear
Reserve judgement
And that's the director
One of their major directors
Program
Call services
She was the first one body parts
South Augusta
Find
This is a
Picture video that tells a million words
Literally stuffing Spain for Spencer wine
Upscale restaurant
Fortune favors the paycheck
From baby's body parts
They don't get their paychecks from baby's body parts but also did you see how he kept saying
Fat cat
Define bottles of wine the upscale dining
Rich off of
Yeah
Totally
Convincing
They're convincing
Susceptible young women
You know that's who we're really afraid of
Afraid that you're going to
Corrupt
Women can't have you
You do that next
Thing you know they'll be
Better
This
Like this
Thread runs
Throughout his entire coverage
It's so dog whistle
So much
I'm such a huge glass
You in class
2.1
Is resin
Yeah
What it should be
Want to eat via board
Tissue of the billionaire i8
Is that how that works I'm not sure all the time
You did do that you wouldn't be able to afford
Bottle of wine a fine bottle of wine
Oh well I would Age
Is the billionaire
Turn the bat light.
They show this the video
What is a video where a lady is eating a
I don't I don't know
The classiest really can't tell from the video
If she is drinking salad
F****** b******* glass of wine is $7 you have no f****** idea
How much does it cost
That's not in the videos that he
Going over
If it's not from a box
Too rich for my
Carlo Rossi
Pirate jug
So here's even be more more classes
I'm talking about
Fine red wine
Littlefield that's not indicative of the video at all this there's no one getting off there's no one enjoying
The idea that all
It's just dealing with it as like other is a research
Use for this
This tissue that would be being thrown away that is completely legal for them to first of all take
Are they have to get waivers from everybody everybody who gets an abortion
There's consent forms
Waiting periods in there all day
Right
Longer than you have to wait
To get a gun
Well it's cuz
Edit abortion show
Free speech
There's two clips that are kind of fun
Alex has big reveal about his soul-searching about Trump
Yeah
He is in a strange headspace
Videos f****** him up
He knows that I got it I got to work on this
But then he's also got a couple has an interview he's got to do later in the show and then he gets a f******
Curveball thrown at him
I like
And he's just
He's he's on Tether he's all over the place
What century
Human sexuality being a
Is diversity as it is
Somebody
Does get off on the idea of certain life
We know about the most
Is Dallas
Sure they're the ones we find with rent
Especially with all of our weird perverted sexual
Fantasies that
Alex
Thrown in there
And
It's been like
This is awful
Justice
Girl
It's possible
Very strong
Untether
When he has no bearing
What ends up happening is often he ends up bragging
And it does Mexico. This is a f****** weird
Amerigroup
Entre shooting
Assassinate mean
Bedtime
My name
Demographics
You don't know what an extra always hit the mega zeitgeist
Marshalls Creek Barton Creek
On the
Keep in mind he just said I told this story before
Yeah you can tell it again
Tireman
Precise
Thirtysomething
They're real by my neighbor's owl
You have court
Years ago
I want I don't know,
Every group of people that walked
Every
Group
Perrin
We don't see the numbers on the website we don't see it we see huge numbers.
This show is one of the government's listen to it because I'm just a straight shooter
And we have a very accurate history
I'm still alive
Please pray for us
Right now
Very accurate history on the same show
Pictures B fraudulent Planned Parenthood Meriden
It's in Spanish also
Tommy likey
F*** you Alex
But like I love
I love it cuz
You can
Read between the lines
What he's experiencing
He's saying that like everyone pointing at me and saying that's Alex Jones which I believe is probably happen
We're not seeing these kind of numbers
Cuz of course you're not
People are aware of you at this point because of memes
People are making fun of him
And so whenever
That's how they're say
Oh my God
In young nubile women are
Screaming is
I think he thinks it's like John the
Or something like that
Yeah I think he thinks
People's I like seeing him walk around
Jerusalem
The one who prophesied
The coming of Christ
Babe that's what he thinks
Man
Crazy what crazy world
Yeah but he actually gets
Do a little bit later
Explain
Why
There's such a disconnect
Between
His version of reality
And everyone else
Which I'll play for you and I'll see if you
Buy into it I don't know maybe we'll
Is so overwhelming
Completely
Given over
Basically see it
Because it's so alien
To their nature
Fundamental nature
You can't see bubbles cuz they're too evil
Batman
Yeah that's really dumb
Little miss perfect
I can conceive of a lot of f****** evil s*** I can imagine terrible plan
You are awake
Listen to Infowars
I can't conceive of the globalist
I think it's too crazy
It's too far behind me because I am a
Generally
Good person
This is his government listen to me as any for me to reveal
That I started reading the book
Alex talks about babysitter like the foundational pieces of his cosmology
Read none dare call it at
Conspiracy
I'm stupid it's absolute utter garbage
Sweet misunderstanding
A lot and Ivory
List of the great chessboard
Maybe
Only
Non
White American male American
Yeah that's true
Or Derek
Is the big new
The great chessboard and I'll get to reading all of it venture
Complained a lot about the book
Technotronic era
And
It's interesting
It's not at all what he's talking about
It's about
Yep
It predicts they're coming
It's actually called
Between two ages America place
Technotronic era
And first of all I f****** love the book from the jump
Because it opens with a Steppenwolf
My favorite book and like
Alright alright so
It's
I'm I'm not
Turn in the last chapter
But so far what it's about
Is
And it's about
How to
Technology is going to be
Super important in terms of modernization
And the world
So he's off to a great
And a large of the book
Is talking about how
Developing countries
Markets
Are going to have a really difficult time
I'm keeping up with
The technology
Because in order to modernize
General
Stability
That's mostly
It's not saying we need to
To keep them on
Unstable so they won't develop
Like what Obama said
Expensive mama said
It's more
It's more lamenting
The impossibility or the unlikelihood
India
If you look at it from the 60s
They didn't look like they had a very good chance
Of catching up with the rest of
The world
Struggling to catch up but they
They're doing a lot better job of it
Predicted
Pretty good dude
Navigate I haven't finished the book it could take a real hard turn
It's so far
I'm finding Alex
Probably doesn't understand what
I think it would probably
Like you
Even mentioned earlier this
He thinks everyone
Doesn't matter whether it's real
To him though
And so he's reading this book and he's like
Agree the book
Is the globalist
Plan
And I'm the one who
Can see it through this because everyone else
Of the idea that he's writing about this
This sort of
Other weather-based technology
He has to say that
You know otherwise
People would be like
Signaling to his other globalist world
Way2go
Right
We would even get Godzilla for another
10 years or whatever
Oh that's right it was one of the Raymond Burr
I forgot about that that was the American remake of the
Make it more palatable
The bad guys
That's
That's the
I apologize that was a little more extended than I intended
But I am by reading all these texts
Of like
Where does he get these ideas from
And finding out they don't match up with what he is rather
The promise
Service Podcast
Is your view and I will get
To laugh
At Alex Jones
In person
We got
Zbigniew Brzezinski book
Book clubs or anything like that you just giving us a rundown
Policy walked out there go ahead and look forward to the second half
Zbigniew Brzezinski book report
The next installment of the odds of that are infants
I will be reporting back
We have got to run
But for now
It's time
To get to the results of Alex Jones's tool search
Hits of a heel turn
Prisonplanet.com
Well they just came out and they misrepresented
Donald Trump this weekend
Hannah throughout the week I watched hours of Donald Trump videos on
Fox News
I did not
No but I'm actually watching hours
The interviews where he says kill terrorists
Watch the videos where
They said we should have stolen oil from countries
War plunder
We have to watch
All of the interviews where he says
That Putin is a great guy you know talking about how great
By virtue of the fact that you've watched hours of those
You have to be aware of those things
And if you're okay with them
Then
You're okay with all that
And that's not good for you
The same
It's the same opportunities I'm that gets a
To where we are
It is that
That's that whole idea of
I will
Deal with well just just pulled off
Hold on cuz we don't know where he's going
This is that
This is at Cigna
Wait
Are you saying he's not
I don't know where he's going to
Sincerely don't think it's going to go exactly the way you
Willits
Listen listen
Alright
Casinos
You also said
He was like
Hold everything with Ryan
Casinos or predators
The basically with a name like Trump you don't get arrested with one like
Genovese eugenics
Frontman for
Consortium on the East Coast he's not really rich
Libertarian
I thought was sick
And knowing that I was been trumped
Experimentation
Marijuana
That doesn't mean for marijuana
I've done deep Research into Trump
I think he is a selfie
No
He says bomb the oil
Exclamation
It's a proxy
Saudi Arabia
Further
I would really support
Call
You should be
Johnson
We get back to Gary Johnson
7 second
Our problem is basically
Rand Paul isn't big enough
Depress
Isn't crazy enough
Trumpism
Crazy enough of his position
Have the whole thing
Remember
Couple weeks ago he was saying I'm Grandpa
Maybe Ted Cruz
So
Gary Johnson
I really disagree with his political points trying to get
Trump's catering
Trump Donald Trump
Is appealing to voters
Sing to me
Animals amongst them
That's what Cuba did
Where is Eastern Europe
Benefit of a doubt
No loss of money and want some TV shows
Old fashioned a patriotic Donald Trump
The problem is
Donald Trump
I've warned
But now
Thank you for listening
Visit
That's so convoluted
Maybe his gut was right
Yeah
In the wild
But you can't play it now
If you'd listened to our so he could do it the whole time
He can play that you can be like
I got I got betrayed
I got seduced by karisma following through on those ideas
I told you guys at the
The beginning
My gut told me that he was going to betray us
Because he's a secret Democrat
Is too far
To do that
Asteroid
What was it
The middle of January early February when you said I would
Die for Trump
Yeah that one
I think he's gone too far he can't play that card
That statement
Bucked up
Really like I listen to all these videos with
It should have been
This guy's nuts
Instead he's like
Oh he's crazy but I like
Alright
Look
I know he's mobbed-up
I know all this batshit about him
Stop
But I'm going to give him the benefit of
Of the doubt
But verify
That's not a good idea
You should
If you
Don't give
It look if you don't
Trust don't give him the benefit of the doubt
Right
I don't trust you in that car
You seem creepy
But you did offer me a ride
My gut tells me you're going to murder me but I'm thinking it's not necessarily in this case
So Alex now is it this point
Where
Keith said a whole bunch of stuff about Trump up to this point
Now you make this Proclamation
Annie stops talking about
I think I
I think that was
The beginning it's the first debate whenever
Those guys start dropping out
Opposed
The middle just sitting there
You're a prick
I hate you
Super male vitality
Cuz we're going to get back to it
Deliver my heart
Is there any other way
Superman
Is this episode of going to be going over up until July twenty
First I believe it's where
We cut off he doesn't really talk about Trump much at all
What is
We're going to get into it
It seems like
Especially at that time
Whenever Trump
I threw and everybody was shocked
Interview with Jerome corsi at one point which is really boring
Jerome corsi says maybe he's real this time
So there's that they talk about that
It doesn't matter
Around the 19th or 20th somewhere in there
I was when Trump made the
Yeah claims about
Do you like I like to Heroes who don't catch
Alex is responsive that is enough
Because Alex believe
That
John McCain was a trustee at the Handlery Hilton
He makes the claim
That John McCain was never tortured
And in fact was given pleasure women
What
Yeah
He said it's mainstream news
She saying
Can't raise his arms above his head is he got f***** too hard
F***** so hard
He's paralyzed more light
Try and look into that
I can't find
Any verification
I did find
An article on WorldNetDaily
But didn't notice or saying no like references at all
Ice I found one article that I don't know if I can
Entrust or not
Purported to be from somebody who was
Captured along the same
Time is it
It doesn't
Tortured
Sayings
Exaggerated
Story
There were a lot of people who were there and
His experiences no
More severe than any one of the other even John McCain would own up to that
Where are the f******
Yeah
Amazon Trump
Now this is fun
Is immediately
He has an interview with Jesse Ventura
Ventura comes back
Doesn't this clip
Jesse Ventura
Some f****** hard truth about Trump is nice
And Alex
Can't really handle
Oh boy
To give you the indication that
Turn Trump into his we started to feel the need to defend but he can
Jesse Ventura
Ventura
Makes sense
On where you stand
First of all you know if Mexicans come up here the illegals and get on our welfare
Blame the people who created the system that allows that to happen
Which is your Democrats and Republicans
Instead of blaming the poor person
Second of all
I'm off the grid down there I was 900 miles in Mexico
And whenever somebody with the statute of Donald Trump takes us statements like he has
Believe me we as Americans down there feel the repercussions of that
All of a sudden Mexican people scare adults
Student council start happening maybe the federales pull you over more
Whatever it might be
But it does nobody any good
Because Donald Trump is saying does nothing but anger
Mexican people
Because you can't paint them in a broad brush
Circle L criminals in Mexico just like there are criminals here
We are
We have the most criminals will Jessie
That's not the point.
Definitely I'll expand it all Wrestle with
What appointment
Completely f******
That was
No he said don't blame the immigrants
Don't blame for trying to not be poor
Fighting for their lives more or less
So
His response
Here's my
Questions
How are
How are we coming down on
Because is Alex
Understand
And then deliberately Miss
Sleeting
Absolutely incapable of listening to another human being talk
Prior
You think so
And then he just
Can't allow that
It's like there is like they have criminal there just like we have criminals here
We incarcerate the most people in the world so therefore we have the most criminals
Would you can argue with if you're out
So he has
To change the argument
It's a classic debate
I mean it's
Minorly gaslighting
Somebody
Manipulative
Agree with somebody on something they didn't say
I really
I hate
But Jesse doesn't call him out on it
Alex that he could
He doesn't
But he makes another great
Diamond congress's around criticizing the TSA when they showed up and control it
Assault weapons ban
And he said
They're not illegal
We both do the meteors in the entertainment business
The more entertainment copy
Completely irrelevant
Have I personally
People know that I know Donald and they'll ask me and I just say look I don't answer for Donald but I think what
Preposterous and stupid
40 States
You know to have a president that would say things like that about people of another country
You know that's not very
Call Mercy if I pictures
Overall the problem is you
Do you Alex
I'd like
Jessie just made some great points and also another thing that's really interesting
Point out they don't get into is that Alex is also in the entertainment business
Sign directly above Alex Jones
This is about you
Getting out of the first thing that Jesse says
Vistaprint
You're not experiencing the Mexico that Donald is talk
Talking about right now
Most collapse trust you
Listen
You're wrong on
But I'm not going to say it like you're wrong
That's almost like
Because you don't have that
Personal experience
You perhaps don't understand the entirety of their
What Jessie
We can't conceive of the evil of global
Apparently
Even though he's been the governor of a state
Maybe
Kicked out by the
There is why we still like Jesse Ventura
Like
Problem
Jesse's not always right
You clearly was walking around with misleading people
You can't come with stuff like that
I don't think I've ever heard somebody make that
Very simple logical
They're witches
We imprison the most people so
We have the most criminals
Yeah that's that's your
If you're worried about criminals
You don't want Americans coming
Which is always true
We have people in prison for
Bulshit
Definition of what a criminal is
Kind of stupid
Once it's at that
The brand
It's not
It's not you
Committed a crime
It's that you're a criminal
And you're always
Well
Even if you're
Even if your Escape
Keeping your life criminal because I don't know
One of the
Can cartels
Juju and the only way to get out of there was by running
Sing away otherwise they were going to
Murder
So you're always you're never entitled
To do your best
Not be a criminal 10 exactly
So this next breath is really
People are
Ladies
Insurers and hospitals are
Refuse
Treat veterans
But they'll treat illegal
He has a weird f******
Can Siri about it
That even in
Eternally doesn't make
Like even the words he's saying
If you
Grant that the beginning of it is true
The middle
Why is it free
Because the Vets are already here and they're done with you
New people because we are boarded
50 + million of our kid
What is social security
That's true
Lyrics of fact
Is that
We're
Paying for
Illegal immigrants babies to be born in the United States
Because we've
Many of our own right
Prop up a illegal immigrant
We've also already rated Social Security it's so convoluted
I don't even know
Where to like polka
I know I got a few
Veterans are not
That's a big problem
Certainly why are you
Not focus on that
Why is your what is your anger why is your ankle
Like I just like food
Sure thing it's like
We have the most criminals so let's
Boing-boing the system
People don't blame the illegal immigrant
Has to have her baby
Because you can't afford it anywhere else
Blame the system
Keeping the veterans from getting
Coverage for being
Might be a good plan
Why would you do that I want to take a moment to give Alex some credit because
Even though he
He does do it in Dumb ways that rely on globalist
Speak a lot about how veterans are treated well
And he has a he has a good point there
Mount apps
Solutely
Diaz
Some sort of elaborate
Buy evil
Is
Stupid
It is just
What is it
Veterans
Nobody wants
To pay for
For veterans
Right right
Healthcare nobody wants to
Right
The budgeting is so much on the front end as opposed to the back end
Pay for the war but we won't pay to take care of
Globalist plot that's just
People in Congress being
Every
That's the way every
Military is all
Now we want you to
To fight we don't give a
The fuk wants your
Jordan I told you earlier that I was going to end with a curveball
Is it going to end with
Started
The day before this
Statements to make a bit of Jade helm
Heathrow
An Infiniti
You are going to
Elmo's not martial law
Nothing happened
Never said it was going to do that
And I will just sit there and assault
I can't do that cuz I'm not going back through more episodes I'm listening
We may do that investigation sometime down the line
Me to pinpoint when he started talking
Sing about Jade helm
Very very difficult
Get the timeline on for what I can do
Is tell you
Episode
He get the caller
From Alabama
We were already off to a great start
Heat
Random Scholars from Alabama
I'm sure there's a lot of info
Elvis very show his
People are going to lie and say that Jade Helm I say that Jade Helm is somehow real
And they're and they're doing that on purpose
To believe that
Martial law
And then whenever it's not
This time
They can turn me into
To The Boy Who Cried Wolf
That you'll be even more of a sheep
The next
That means you'll be ready primed whenever they're going to
Important things
Keep in mind for those of you who didn't keep up with Jade Helm conspiracy
One of the big things that the internet was going wild
Is claiming that there were a bunch of Walmarts that have been closed down and there were secrets
Military
And UN forces to go on
Use them as like Depot points because their giant building and their inconspicuous
Close so all of these Walmart to close down
That was a big part of that stuff
I was just one of those things that if you're a conspiracy theorist
Seems like a
Great plan
You're like
Genius
I know how genius that is
But then if you're actually
Trying to do it legit
Sickly you're like
We have roads
I just wrote I can only come out of
In or out of the tunnels at Walmart
At what why would we do that another reason that I bring that up as Walmart will play
Call her
Sinister Pointe
Alabama
Yeah that's what's happening in Alabama
And it's just been
I couldn't
Working on and I saw a black
And then I saw
Open until
The truth on this one couldn't get a video of that car on the road
Gas station
Simple enough Alex
You want to just
Put up your stationary would be no problem
Insecurities
Blue uniforms
Is the beginning of any lie
Right
If there's a color involved
He's making it
There were two older guys
We are just over run
Deshawn Walmart
Home business
I was raised on patriotic beliefs
The Constitution with all the men in my family were in the military
I'm in Walmart near the night down here
It was real close to 1 in the morning if it wasn't one morning
I'm walking through these two guys in black suits
Walmart
Now hold on
Two guys in black suits
Talking to a manager
Clearly something the ferry
I'm thinking it's the man in Black
Black suits Comin
That's the theme for Men in Black 2
And I want Parent Trap whatever like I try to take a picture
You in
Badges on their lapel
Go to believe the same thing on their flag was on their lapels they had ID badges to Fort Rucker
You in personnel
Here in America man's they don't they don't want anybody to know as soon as I try to take a picture of the guy
I was trying to the ground by what I'm assuming it's his bodyguard
Arrested by the city police in my phone was taking a still haven't believed you
I want you
I want you to scan whatever email
And we will send reporters
Russian troops training
Secret bases
Colorado Springs
It's
Freedom From War
So I looked at up I read
Here's the bigger question how does he know the secret
Which
Secret
That's what I pursue I don't know it's
Why throw that little bit the secret treaties which are breaking up
You already made up enough lies Alex
Show me the further compounded
Take a break
So I I looked up
The the memorandum
But he was talkin to
About the Freedom From War
State Department memorandum 7777
September of 19
And it is a freedom from war the United States program for General in
Complete disarmament
Peaceful world
So it's mostly in
Concern
About the rapid
Growth
Post nuclear
And
The insanely rapid
Behind this memorandum memorandum
Not a not a law
21 7727
Mamo
It's a little note for note
It's not - 1777
So this is basically
Aspiring towards disarm
If you crazy it looks bad
Because it does talk about how the end goal is getting rid of army
In every country
I think it is I think it is
Type 1 civilization
Would that be better for everybody primary piece of it is nuclear
A song about these
Technologies that are
Wheatley capable
Destroying the entire world
Setting us off on a trajectory that we don't even know what it would lead to
That's the first step of it
Eventually gradual disarmament
Arby's
And creating
Peacekeeping organization
That
And I will be involved with
Mitigating crazy is
Conflicts between states could be hashed out as opposed to war
What is idealistic is
But the one thing that's really important about it is
It doesn't talk about UN forces hanging out Russian secret training or anything like that
And further
Secret memo
The first part of it is not achieved
You know what I'm saying
So like
Pieces of it haven't been to
Successfully implemented
It's like his fear that cloward and Piven plan but brings up over and over again
You can someone wrote about some Professor wrote that if we overwhelmed some people would have to take it more
Seriously
It's it's
Yep it's like
It's like you said
Aldous Huxley
He's the one who knew
I think it would save
I think you would say that to ya
The point is all it's all speculative
Do that
Discern
What is
Like
Do you ever stop and think like
Creative
All of the weapons necessary
You kill all of us
And we just have them lying around and we have for a long time
They're still
They're still nuclear weapons
Songs that use floppy disk
We're just fine
No problem
Absolutely
How is traffic
Would be on board with just a big just like
Hey maybe
Let's try and get two
Where we are not
Age of
Global
I need to study this memorandum a little closer in order to have like an assessment on it but just from my my
I read of it my my once through Reading
I would say it is a great goal but it is way too idealistic to work
Then reality
But yeah or in the near
Taking the memorandum out of it
Why would you want to stop
What vested interest money
Do people have in war continued
Population
Dominance
Call cheers versus bad cold
Pictures Dan nationalism for any other reason
Then to make their culture
Better nationalism
Prosperity
Yeah that's what it's about Second Amendment
Manhole
Jerome corsi
Also also whenever he was like
Take
Tips can the paperwork I was like oh we're not going to
From this fella again I'm going to
As of July 22nd
This is not come
And I guarantee it.
But he does come back after the Jerome corsi interview
It gets real
Walmart
And I
It's incredible what else can you tell us about this what are the police squad car
I don't know about how censorship is on your show so I'm pretty sure I can't call them for bait on butt
They told me that I asked up by wanting to get picture happy with my iPhone and you know I told him I
I mean I could be wrong
Freedom of speech freedom of press
My phone is probably no more but
Your iPhone
When I left the city jail they told me that I could pick my iPhone up when I pick my paperwork up
I know the ins-and-outs of
Supposed to get paperwork as soon as you get kicked loose whether it's do you have to pay to get out or you get a recognizance bond to property
What have you
And they give you your property back
IPhone
At the Walmart
And if they won't cover it will come up there
This is incredible
Describe
What do uniforms look like
Okay that I saw in the Walmart
The gentleman that I'm presuming or bodyguards because they're the ones that pulled
I'm what I'm assuming a Glock 17 to that standard-issue sidearm
Yes he has paid through down on me in Walmart while
Alarm in plain clothes and I'm assuming that they were protecting the two men in the suits with the badges on there
Any harm you know who I mean
Incorrect
No resistance at all because I'm
What else
They detained me and help me on the groundwater Melanie and my back both my hands behind my back
Let It Go on and in the city police arrived and they carted me off
Jail
And you know later on what they say where they were
Espanol
Walmart
Robin
This is not the behavior of someone who doesn't believe in is real
This is the behavior of someone who's looking for a way to believe it's real
But knowing without concrete evidence going to be made fun of
So he gets this hillbilly collar on the air
Just beautifully like what I would say
Something is missing
Because the number of
Keep going up
Just changed a little bit
Two guys in black suits
Became he had bodyguards
Then they pulled birthday cookies phone
Then they pulled guns on us
Episode it's Nancy
I believe
The fact that he just casually references Glock 17
This is like no I don't
I don't like that at all
King something up out of whole cloth but there's some element
The story
He was high
Well police also tell him that he couldn't bring that brown bag inside the wall
Why the f***
Would you be at a Walmart at 1 in the morning if you're not high
I also I don't know any reason to go to Walmart
Ran out of smokes
Alabama
Broad brush
It's time for me to slide right into the South or Midwest
For the 16th
Of the shower
Alex is on claim that he's not buying into Jade helm by buying it
Caller
He has been schooled by Jesse Ventura
But he's also teased his heel turn about Trump
It's very clear that it's only a matter of time now after July 6th
Right until he inevitably does get in
And is it just
The bigotry
Is the fact
That
Trump says
We should hate them
Yeah
That's basically all he
Pretty much
I was going
Cut it off at the sea
16th for this episode
Right but we
Have to talk about
Okay what happened
Turn on the 17th 17th
Is
One of my favorite Alex Jones episodes I've ever listened to
And I will
I'm just going to play the beginning of the show and you'll see why
Broadcast
Exactly
12 seconds from now
Ready
Because we are going
6 oz of information
May actually shake a large portion of the population
Out of there
Is that what Jumping the Shark is I guess so
What a Jumping the Shark what does he think it means
Can use a little bald
Unfortunately
He has literally jumped the shark
This episode is
Embarrassing
So I don't want to spoil for you what
The actual
Jumping over the shark
I don't understand again
What it is we're talking about but I'm excited to find out
I don't know if it's going to work better if I just spell it out of town
No I want to hear it I want to hear it split up the actual shark jump
Preparation
The Binding of
Motorcycle
That's right it is
Yeah it is water
Yeah but you also jump something on a motorcycle at some point
Is held up by
Sweet bulshit live
One of those
Waypoint story-telling
We haven't really dealt with a lot of the
2015 10th post through the waypoints
So we get to take care of like all of them
In one Fell Swoop
During this jumping of the shark
It's amazing
Okay so here we go
Put the first clip
7 Minutes in a couple seconds after the last one
Agreed
Plus percent of the time
Against
Perfect
Stop all things.
Some strong medicine
T'force The Logical point
24 Cinema
Control
And then the American public at a logical discussion
This is a big announce
How is that an announcement they done satirically
It's done
Etta level of logical discussion
Depression is a kanban
So that's the first Waypoint is it there outlawing Brown
Seattle there not this is based on a memo
That's a Seattle
Elliot braunstein the chief spokesman for the Seattle office of civil rights
The city's public information officer
To avoid
Sprays
Brown
Or lunch and learn
According to a memo
Being widely misreported is an order or a van
Now the reason that you did this
Was
Okay
Issaquah
No
This issue came up in one of the Department's and I thought FYI for your consideration
We often use the Expression brown bag to designate a bring your own lunch time of it
We also use the word citizens as
Innocuous phrases right it went on
Not so much
For some people
The phrase Brown Bag calls up ugly Association
The use of the expression brown bag
People's skin color was light enough
Have to allow admission to an event
Or home
Citizens is a different case
We sometimes use it as another way of saying members of the public
Except for all the members of the public who are actually citizen
Come to live and work here
It's basically
A f****** the chief spokes
Looking for the office of civil rights
Issued a memo to
City employees
Then ask them to be more sensitive
Because there is a history of what I've looked into it the right
That's not made up the idea of passing anything that any reference
To racism in America
History even if I have no
Text Shelby
Yeah that's probably too
I think
That this is probably
Stretching a little bit
In terms of
Big descriptors of this bag is brown
He's just saying
You know like
Specifically
With your words
A lot of the times just
Be more specific
Is no more difficult to say it's a no less descriptive so
Ban it was him being like
Skip but it just
The shark jaw
Has been described
Also
The plan that he has
Right is so mind-bogglingly stupid even know what exactly it is
Plan is going to say what is what is outline
His his idea of how this is going to work
Is he's going to say something
Intentionally
So that the media will report on it
But even
Even though even though it's intentionally f*****-up
They're going to take him out of contact
Text
Which boggles the mind
Even further well here's what he's trying to do that will force
Everyone
Let's have a conversation
About how stupid the f*****-up thing he's
Trying to play The Mark Dice Game
AutoPro level only work
Because it's a closed loop
You don't have any Rogue actors in there like the actual me
He's not going to play along with this the way you play along with Mark dice's reporting
And create your circle of propaganda
They are going to take it on its face
They're going
To deal with what you say every like
Holyshit
We'll get to it and even then they could just go back and listen to the first part where he said
This is what we're going to do
The app that is a problem
People don't
Tell people you're tricking
Yeah
Alex is dumb though
So f****** hilarious
Jerome corsi
Please plan
Okay
This time
We're actually going to do propaganda
Corsi buddy
Baby
You're way past that
Dude now
Not a propaganda
He goes on
Segmented I took a break pretty much whenever he got to one of his life
Seattle complete misrepresentation
As we've come to expect
Here's the next one
Girl
As a boy or girl
Someone else
So is this another one of his big Waypoint
Pictures of for one second
Like
Hey
If you can't have your identity
Because it hurts somebody else like Alex
Yeah like maybe
Think about it
Think about how
Your identity
Has hurt somebody else
Olaf
Or somebody else can't have their ID
Because
You don't want to feel bad
You're on a real interesting tip that Alex is not interested in
Grapple
Turn it the other way
It's not even hard
It's super easy like if I feel
And I don't like
That
What if somebody else
Who isn't me feels that way
That's letter A
Removes a little bit of
How do you not just take that little step you like to learn about this point
Alex has been a long time I don't think I've played on the show that nationally
In school
They're telling kids
Yes
And this is because
Boys and girls are hurtful
The trans identifying
Student
He's stupid
But here's the thing
If you look into it
This is based on a story out of Lincoln Nebraska specifically
And there were some materials that were provided to
The teachers by a group called the genders
Which is an organization whose website States
A goal of fostering quote gender-sensitive an inclusive environment for all children and
So inside their materials
Read this
Don't use phrases such as boys and girls
You guys ladies and gentlemen and similarly
Expressions to get kids
I instruct the training documents given to Middle School teachers at the
Public Schools
Create a class create classroom name
And then ask all the purple penguin's to meet on the rug
The document also warns against
Askance
The lineup is boys and girls
And suggest asking them to line up whether they prefer skateboards or bike
Milk or juice
Dogs or cats
Summer winter
Do you mean by who you are as a person as opposed to what your habits
Will this configuration
Creative gender
The document app
Smart
Sounds
Is really dumb
I just mean that it's it has the Ring of like
Like even while
Right I mean I mean that
That immediately have that
Knee jerk reaction of like
Dude
You're going overboard with this let's just
But that makes
Albertsons in the
Just in the form of
Just like that idea of
We're not
Immediately putting you into your blue in your pee
You're like
A boy or a girl I am somebody
Who enjoys that I am
Person first
Feelings and I'm not
I'm not whatever you tell me I am
And I'm allowed on the way that I want
The arbitrary specific of Purple Penguin
Little Greek
Yeah just create
Do teams within the classroom
Getting mad at Legends of the Hidden Temple
Three pieces of monkey together no one could ever f****** do it
TV about that when I was a kid and then
Someone made a group about it on Facebook
Play years and years ago I like you f****** a******. I can't complain about it
L remember that it made me mad
Complain about it because one of the reasons that it was
Was so hard for them
Because they were shooting for like
12 or 40
18 hours
Another reason is both of them weren't tall enough to put the head up.
0 people got mad people I mean
More
So Brenda
Agario the Lincoln Public Schools coordinator for social workers and counselors Lincoln Journal Star
To gain widespread
The materials were provided
Educators to better understand gender identity
And we're not impose rules
Quote
Staff member on a district equity
We're meant only for teachers not for students or parents
And they were not meant as rules
Suggestion
Teachers can make students
Comfortable it also stresses the impact words
Can have on others
If there's a staff member that uninformed and unsupportive
That can be a pretty scary
That can be pretty scary for a family may be struggling to understand transgender issues them cell
Sounds like a really good Progressive
School District
Do you know what it is
Almost
Almost all of this always winds up boiling down
Like I read
I read the
10 million times when I was growing up
And just one of those very simple things is always
Be mindful be thoughtful with your ex
Yeah you just randomly or
Just like think about how does this
Make somebody else feel fart
Instead of
I want to do it so I'm going to
No no
Is worse for Alex's narrative
The Lincoln public schools superintendent Steve Joel pushed back again
What he said was a misinformed reaction
The district gender identity
Binational commentators
It's indeed regrettable for the last week
And a half we had two dedicated much staff time and resource
To address
In fact never once has anyone inside our school
Ladies and gentlemen out of their interactions
Children or interaction with adults
Course
This was about adults
Professional Educators who care deeply about trying to re-establish relationships
There look
4 strategies about how to be more effective in the
So f*** you
Get mad about realshit
What do we
Why do they have to make things up
About bro
That's what I'm talking about that
Is Jumping the Shark
He's accidentally doing what he's parroting
He's going
So this next clip
He actually
Okay he does the jump that he had prepared
Another life
Programming
Put in my mind
Really
. there's
Way better
Be selectively enforced
Discriminatory
And so are all right
If we ever do Muslim thousands a year
Does anywhere from
Name two more country Northeastern Africa like Somalia
Against
For the shooter in Charleston
Been calling for all Muslim symbol
Calling for all mosque in the United States
Calling for all
Self-identifying Muslims
To be deported
Original country of origin
I want all
Muslims deported
Muslims to have their mosque shutdown removed
And their symbols removed
I want them arrested
Because we've got police showing up at
So what
We'll get back to that rebel flags
Assertive dispense with why that argument is really stupid
They're really foundational problem
In order
His argument to make sense
The Confederacy
Worship of
The Confederate flag
Would have to be
A federally protect
The group
It would have to be a religion
So he didn't
In a lot of ways
In order for him to make this argument logically
Actually it doesn't work
It just all the promises
Like it works as a logical
Dumb
Strictly work I don't understand how you think it works
Well because
It doesn't have to be for it to actually work logic
Anything
He's saying
If
Muslims attacking people hurt someone
The Americorps the Confederate flag being hung hurt someone
We take down
Symbols of the Confederate flag
When a Confederate person expired by the Confederate flag
Therefore we
Take down all symbols of Muslim people when a person
Inspired by
Islam
Attack somebody
It actually does work
Strictly speaking
In terms of Aven BB vincie
You see them.
But it doesn't it doesn't matter
Is that is that why
Okay
I see where you're coming from
You're right it's just
The premises are so
Supremacist
They don't
It's the different they're not they're not a one-to-one
Right because
Maid-Rite
Sound arguments you need to have
True premises that lead to a conclusion
He needs to be in the proper form and things have to be true
You can have a valid argument
That's not sound
If you just have bulshit
But as long as it's set up right
The falsity falsity can leave the truth
The thing is
Like I said the really big thing is that
In order for
You to make this argument and make it work
You have to put in something
That makes
Confederacy
Which is
Is a rogue
Failed
Insurgency basically
To be exactly the same as a religion
And if you want to make that argument Alex
You can
But then you have to say
A bunch of stuff that I don't think he realizes
Interesting
I mean
Because if
For a lot of people it does function as
Something of a religion
Geology
Well
I mean the idea that the South will rise again
Very much has those religious overtime
And then the
Fervency of the belief in the
Flag
Belfry
End
Very much a
It is a worship we worship
Past like
Could you
Steve
Confederacy
Ephedra
Federal
Protected religion
The people who believe
Use that we should have the
Confederate flag hanging
Should have to
Agree
To go to church
No ship that
No I don't think so the most interesting about people trying to use logic who don't
Logic
Whenever you make arguments like the one Alex is making
You have a bunch of
They're not really even assumptions but their implied promises that you don't really even realize are in there and when you make your argument
You're actually saying a ton more than you're actually
Getting to
And that is one of
And the other thing is
Like
Like I said
Things have to be
True people were calling
They're used
Sweet naive child
Such a beauty
WiDi.
Please have to be true
Like I said
So he's not taking into consideration we should ban
The Confederate flag
There were just a bunch of businesses that got pressure for people who didn't want them to sell it and they replied
The free market
They made a decision based on what
Consumers were saying prices like Walmart stop selling the flag.
So I was tribute
Well yeah but they're not bringing Pro
Prosperity background
Prosperity
About that battle flag
Secondarily
But people wanted the Confederate flag taken out of state building because
But you're not be
Government building
So those were the real
North Vietnam was hanging United
Here's the other thing
I agree with him if you were me
Which is
Actually I wouldn't agree with him if he was using terrorism as one of the foundation
Premises
If you
People
In reality are trying to ban
Confederate flag being
Flown in government
Write an
Some people are offended by it
Whether or not that's another question
So the
Islamic
Flags
Should not be flown in
Our government State Building
Well yeah but they shouldn't
Neither should the
Confederate white but if he's making
Brett
But he's saying
On their own property
So far
Satirical
He's not literally calling for these nuts
Did the form he's using
So far
Like you just
It drives me up
The f****** wall
I could spend half an hour about all the b*******
You're you're being a pet
Israeli without
I am I am
Flashing into the part of myself that should have been a professional
I looked in
The idea that
People were storming
I'm trying to get
Confederate flag
Confederate flags
Google Confederate flag
Giraffe
I found was
Couple of bad stories
I'll just tell you a little bit about it
Somebody just
Arrested
Confederate flag
Gun at a party
Some charges
Smart because it
Mississippi
Another one
Yeah I know what you're saying
It seems bad but was anybody arrested
For selling the
I did find one story about
5 police
Swap Market
Meet okay
Alright merchandise
County Flea Market was so offended by a vendor selling
Confederate memorabilia
The person actually called 911
Wallingford Connecticut police
We're dispatch to the flea market to
The police chief William Wright tells News 8
The reason no one was arrested was because the items were being sold on private property
Not to mention
Manolo
We're broken
There was a table set up with this material right says
According to the Journal Record
It's not criminally illegal but obviously it offended
Because of some people a sense of being uncomfortable
Certainly the owner could pray
Preclude this Merchant
He said he could
Owner
The town resident called 911 said that there were helmets
The swastikas images of Hitler and other historical Nazi items
I was shaking and almost vomit
The paper
I had to run
My grandma turn on the hits
My Grandmother Had numbers
He said referring to the digits Nazis would tattoo on their prisoners
Confederate items were quoting
Replicas of flags and weapons
He said the seller told him he was quotes telling so much
You can't keep it in stock
So basically what happened
The flea market
Police, I couldn't find any other stories
The police arrested for selling
He's just completely making that part up.
It's absolutely absurd
Well I think his argument would be that
Liberals snowflakes
1 people arrest
1st and Langley
I know those liberals snowflakes who survived the Holocaust
Yeah maybe I don't even know if he would want that guy arrested
Calling the police
Coming from
It's
Look I don't know I'm also I like the fact that at the end
It wasn't even real that's just getting of Texas getting an iPhone
That's a good stuff right there
Alex is not done with his
He has a couple more things he wants to bring in here's one of them
That again I didn't cut it
Just segments
What I just said in contacts
Most Muslims aren't most Muslims aren't terrorists
The truth is
In general
You should stop there
I don't support blaming all Muslims for what just happened
But
Muslim groups
Calling to remove the Confederate flag
Getting into this whole Anglo-Saxon
I'm not somebody else does
But if you want
We know statistically
Overnight world
If carried out
By Islamic extremists
Grant
That's not even close to true
Not even
Clothes
It just to give you a little bit of an idea
So in the United States
94% of terrorist attacks
82 2005 word on Vine
A lot of inward environmental groups
Animal rights groups
A lot of them do you know if you do a little Larson
The councils of terrorism Europe
If you do a little
He talks about how would like all these attacks are being carried out in Europe
There been a thousand terrorists attacks in Europe
In The Last 5 Years
At Wendy's article is written
I am
Less than 2%
We're Cary.
Throughout the entirety of your
By Muslim
I mean if you want to go worldwide and say
Like
You know
Muslims fighting off art
In other countries
Are acts of terrorism
Cvent get into real Berkey territory
What are the big problems with
Terrorism
People use it as a
When terrorism is very specific
Is a group of people
Or I person
Doing a
Relatively small thing
With a B
Footprints
In order to
The influence
That's what it is
That nn
The Charleston
Was not
Terror
It wasn't it was a dude I wanted to cause a race war
There's political implication
But yeah
The government
White people it's this weird
Disconnect between like
Political terrorism but then there is just also trying to
You strike fear into everybody
So I don't know I think
I agree with your
Point
Look it's
Silly
I think
Include
In your in your
Care about
Alex only really cares about things
The West United States
And Europe into that the attacks were done by Muslims
Infinity
Less than
6% in the United States
Less than 2% in Europe
And then if you want to talk about what is actually terrorism in the rest of the world
Australia
I don't know
There was that one guy
I'm talking about
Talk about
He had a knife
I do have a knife
Was Paul Hogan
Well the Crocodile Hunter
There's no doubt about that it's really complicated issue to discuss
Yeah
He says the Flies
Percent of the world terrorism is all Muslims
And the rest of it is just people looking to get ramp
What's up like that's like kidnappings in Brazil
Even if you are saying that you're not
Burnin It Down
It's Muslims and Muslim sympathizers which as we know are big fans of the environment
They love them
He said that that's all
Some people will try to make a caveat
But come out mainstream news was as phony as a three-dollar bill
Southern Poverty Law Center
It's not true
Article in World News Daily that have no source
Basically another Infowars doesn't have
A cool
Angry Texan doing the radio show with it
So it's we're drunk or so used to work
Before you defect
Infowars
So great credibility
Zerohedge
That world
I found an article about it on there that had no evidence and no leg
Anything else
Are there was a claim of
Secret FBI memo
But it didn't linked
To that it didn't have
Any
Secret
18 mm
The claim that it is
Accepted
The only thing I was able to find was apparently
The place the whites
Timothy McVeigh was Elohim City
And apparently they
The Southern Poverty Law Center
Inside
Really
The group and that's how they got a lot of information about the
So
Kind of true and it is much as they had someone
New was doing research
Now
There's no reason to believe that this person in any way influence
He was already prone to two-faced on statement even making
The last ten goddamn years before that
There's also no reason to believe that this disposal within Elohim City
Would have had any foreknowledge
What Timothy McVeigh plan
Cuz even if you have white supremacist group
There's no
Indication that you just an open meeting that seems kind of
Monkey you can't assume that every
I'm a totally cool white supremacist you guys like blowing s*** up I like bloated up
Let me tell you one thing I know about people who are involved in these sorts of
The Fringe groups
What are the trends that runs through all of them is a certain amount of paranoia
A lot of them
I have good reason to believe
Anybody in that group could it be a government mole
Because
It's a good idea to get
These are basically like
Alex you know how you want Intel on what a terrorist group in
Iraq
Is doing
I told you we but also on the ones
Are sleeper cells
Pierre essentially which you are afraid of
So
Look
It's so dumb
If it's just
Again it's making supper
Out of whole cloth
So I don't
We have one more quick
And if this one
Did go on after that
True I don't believe that
What I do believe is we should ban
Again I don't get where he
He thinks
Satire in reality where the line is
Spectrum
I have no idea but I know that what
Is that I'm going to
To say that I call
For the Banning of the deportation of
And then people will take
They won't point out that afterwards I said
Right I'm not saying or immediately before it I said I'm going to f***
There's a logical
Forum
Doves like sort of
Dealing with
Do atoms 30 mm
That's where you take someone's argument
And you point out an example of what their logic
Implies
It turns it into
Italian for our Latin for reduced to absurdity
Yeah Alex Jones at this next
Flip accidentally does that to his own fake argument
A realtor
Let's jump this show
This is the logic
This is what they're pushing
And so
If one man
White person
Again that's Mark Dice
Mark Dice
Let's remove every symbol somebody uses in a wrong way
If somebody runs over somebody with a Ford truck
I want 4 to change a symbol that I want
Every Ford symbol
Thousand-dollar fine
I want
So now
Location of his watch
He unfortunately isn't
It all related to the logic of people who want
The Confederate flag taken out of state building
The only thing that him making this stupid fake argument about
Chevy trucks
That only hurts your fake argument
It only shows
How different that is from anything anybody else is saying
F****** thrown a javelin through his argument
Oh well somebody from
Came over here and committed a terrorist
So we should ban all people from Iran from coming into the United States
It turns out that might be actually like
All this stuff where he's claiming is Jumping the Shark
That way
Like over the neck
Couple episodes
He is like
Now what
It didn't work the way he wanted to
They will be f****** talking about
He talked about how dumb
Not for saying
We should ban all Muslims symbols
But for saying
I'm going to do this as a lie
And then I'm going to tell you that I was like well actually knowing Media Matters operate
Fall for it
I think you're I think you're
I feel your hand yelling at Adam Schiff they didn't talk about how he's clearly drunk
How many episodes they aren't picking up all the
Text or what's going on
But they mean well.
It got jumped interview
Handsome devil gun
Which he actually has in studio
Anime episode with an interview with a pastor whose Name Escapes Me
It don't matter it's just about the Confederacy
Pretty cool
The pastor and this is where he loses all of its credibility
There's never been a civilization in the history of the world that has officially
Embrace
Promoted
And legitimize
Thought that the homosexual lifestyle that has survived
That is simply a matter of historical record
Let me actually use
Use a reducto Adams 30mm
Argument against his I will do it in real time
No cultures that didn't have didn't have Nintendo Wiis have all that survived
There we go
It's stupid
Pointless
If it doesn't mean anything you can't you can't comply causation between accepted homosexual lifestyle
Why did the Aztecs
Fade away
Didn't have
Everybody knows because we
Have
Property
Exactly
That's just like saying
All of the cultures who aren't alive now
Alive Balfour
Yeah the other thing to do is like a buddy there a lot of civilizations that didn't formally recognized on the sexuality
You know
Spartan spot the lot
In the butt
Yep there
Like
If you you understand so well
Well it wasn't like we're in a loving relationship
That was more like if you're a teacher and pupil
Dafuq
Respect
I don't understand
Soldiers.
For so manly we're going to f***
F****** another dude
Viking history about that too
You get a bunch of dudes together in a small and closing sooner or later
Forever
Silly bringing V like
Norse s*** into Exile really know all that much about it but
Bearded man yeah you can pick
Any hundred
Our modern culture that existed
Well
Anyway
We are very
Shorts
Way2go
To get through the rest of this
The rest of the episodes in are stretched to
Are terrible
He jumped the truck and did not get back up he crashed
Remote Landing
The 19th
Because the 18th is Saturday so there's no show
19th Sunday showed
Mostly about how the British nobility or not
Heiling Hitler came out
Like he's been Vindicated on everything he's always said
Congratulatory text for somebody who's always being Vindicated
You sure feels the need to say he's been Vindicated
Really care I don't really
Particularly
All that interested in his feelings about the British nobility
You know that they're their mess
But
We get to
We get to month
Talk more about
Osborne
But he does say that
Is one clip worth listening to here
Personal history
Shark
Is a jellyfish
Jellyfish will get you
He's skinny dip with the babes
And that's what separates the boys from the men
His back then he wasn't
Afraid to Skinny Dip with the lady
So it's his personal history mix
With even dumb masculine ideas
Not true
I don't think
Get through it all
I think it's true
Okay well not his assessment but the
The fact of him skinny-dipping with cheerleaders
Pictures of him when he was younger
Trolls
Okay just built like a brick shithouse this guy
All right he was he was
Fit
When he was younger
It's very disconcerting
He wasn't he was a bad kid
But also was
Traditionally attractive
So I could see him being
One of these bad boys it goes
Skinny-dipping with girls like 150 girls before he's 16
Nobody
I believe
With a couple people
Unimportant
It's more important that Alex is like
This is
What bravery is
Endeavor good girls on your young
I don't give a s*** I don't think it was Brave of me
Anyway
We move on to the
July twenty
First episode where we will end our investigation
Comes up about Trump so the actual investigations kind of over
But he does get back into
This whole episode mostly
On the 21st
Hey there's two narratives that he spending about it all
All talk about
Serious
This is a big new all over again
That they don't let army recruiters carry guns
Army Recruitment and they don't have our
Chattanooga shooting
Military
And so Alex's
Extrapolating
So
Joe Biggs is on the theme
Just south of Austin Army Recruitment Center with Patriots with guns Garden
God
SoJO barbers
It basically
Yeah so he doesn't report to Skype is terrible at breaks up over and over again
Gamma guns
They're protecting people
I have some experience
With army recruiters cuz I
I don't know if it's changed
Certainly hope
But when I was in high school to recruiters were in your school
Yeah oh they were Michael
They were there and their whole goal was to manipulate you into signing up
Cool
Because he was trying to get us into the army
YouTube James Brown
He was awesome
So cool
But
As you turtle
What time when are you start to realize
What my future plans are
For it
Lemon UPS
So
I don't care
Call Zach much about our mirek
Because it isn't
Really
Benign
You want to sign up so you go sign up
Yeah there is a manipulative game with her playing in order to trick people into my account
Like join the Navy
It's absurd to think that they don't get bonuses
Signing people up
It's absurd to think that there isn't
Quotas
You're supposed to reach yet
So
Tristan kids signing away their future
So I don't give a s***
Joe Biggs
I wish I could pull this quote
He says
Joe Biggs not a man to make s*** up
Fast forward Joe Biggs getting fired for reporting on pizzagate
So the other narrative
Of the show
The chicks out most of it
He gets packed
He says
Sum fuk
Wild stuff
Bottom here's the first
So this is about
The demon narrative
Every time you're in protest
And show up
Actually
If something is going on
Restaurant I love Lamborghini
So there we go with more classes
Talkabouttd
Missing something it's important to bring up
Some of deceptive
Conversation
You setting up a relationship where
This Research Center could get
Tissue sample
Every single time that they talk about it
Text sample
They don't
The people making the video want you to believe that what they're talking about is a full baby
Yeah that's not what they're talking about
Liver or an attack
Which is well within the legal
Situation
Like a buffalo
Exactly
The other thing is is Lamborghini
Who's the lady talking
Hi and it's clearly
What do you want I want a Lamborghini
Old ladies making a lame way to live
Well yeah that's
Buying Lamborghinis based on these baby money
Bonita clarify
In preparation
So clear
The visit
Manipulative
The camera of course
Oh yeah
It's crazy
He might have been Oscar the Grouch that's not really demonic as it as much as it is hobo or
Sesame Street
Actually just
Your legion
You saw the movie times
Keanu Reeves
Coronavirus
Glass sword starting Concrete Man
Liberty movies
Another movie
Wine
Classism
That sounds like a lot more fun than you do on your conscience
I don't know I just
Yes,
And it's not what's happening
It's not that they're selling baby parts
With these evil women like
Well I mean based on the truth
Yes
Cuz they're not also even if they
Even if they were evil
Play sound like a lot of fun I like Chianti
Lamborghini
She's aspiring she's got ambition
There is a go
Great moment that again I didn't cut this clip
The time
But
Alex says
Defending Planned Parenthood when these videos come out
It's going to blow back
It's so ironic
Because never
I don't know I can't say for certain
We'll find out as
This investigation goes on
But I guarantee
He never died
I'm sorry that I reported this
I'm still
Portion
Which would be the respectable thing to do
If he was like I'm against abortion
I have principle that even up to the first trimester I don't think it's okay I believe it's a human
If you
I'm sorry these videos were manipulative it would propaganda I fell for it I'm sorry
If you were to say that I would respect the hell out of it
Have you like it's okay
I don't think
Annie
Conservative
Certainly a lot of people in the House and Senate
When they did investigation
Opinion
Splash news media
Conservative
Propaganda
She never
Well guys we got it wrong and
Pretty certain that Fox News isn't reporting to
Too much on the trial of the
No it much like
Hannity is not going to apologize for Separate Checks
So he gets into
This next clip is a bit more about the Planned Parenthood
Important here is the video izle
The videos video song about our lives
That he's going to lie about the LIE
He's going to end
Okay he's going to editorialize and
Aren't in those videos
In order to
Grow
The demonic
So even if you just reporting on the video
That is reporting on Ally
This is lying about Allah
That's
That's like next level propaganda
Multiply -2 by negative
Positive for
That tracks
Pieces
What
Victor's wife terrible actor
Jordan I'm sorry I have to go back cuz
It look you're right you're right
A little bit of what happens after
Cuz it's so funny
You so dumb
Like first of all don't lie on the ground and acting like they're sexually
I don't know what it is
Trying
We've his narrative that he has built up in the past
Did turn them on and have some sort of the sexualized
It's all nonsense but he's trying to make this lie match up with his pre-existing life
It doesn't work if you watch the videos that doesn't match up at all also he says that they are driving Lamborghinis
Lady said she wants a Lambo
There's no indication
M2k
Real Americans drink Pabst
I kind of agree with
I can't stand up
There even none
Cool there's still one cool at the end of the show
He has like I said he does more this go big stuff
It says more b******* about Planned Parenthood so we've gotten all we're going to get out of that
Then
He has
Of his twelve-year-old son
Rex Jones
He does
A admirable book report
I don't want to make fun of him again cuz he's a child
No it was about
Ouija
Look
Because
I have sympathies for him cuz he doesn't know any better
I think you did a great job
For 12 year olds
Doing a news
I know people in high school
Am I broadcast products
Class that did way worse stories
Underwear
But he also had all the Infowars money and team behind him rash
I'm sure you did
It's his dad forced
Really really f***** up
It really really really f***** up
Does this
He has
Exxon
He's going to be even greater than him in the infowar
And it's really putting a lot of pressure on a 12 year old
What what is 12
Sixth grade
That's a lot of pressure to know about global
Yeah well
If your voice hasn't even changed in your already being Prime to fight the globalists
You got a big head
Plays his report
Before he has him sitting in studio be like you're going to be greater than even me or sharp kid I love
Love you so much
Call Tim sweetheart
Very weird
Especially considering it now doesn't have custody
Again
Whether or not he's a good dad he's a f******
Before
Intros
Wreck
He has him sitting there
While he doesn't add
No super male vitality
I did
Looking over today
Selling boner
Has to do with
Super vitality
Is he going to say something like that's how we got you Rex cuz if he does
I don't think I would have cut out I think I would be like
Know this
We might be the most
Progressive Alex Jones has ever been
Which
Is really just
Spell product
Give me a little news flash
Frisky goat weed has different name
But Brooks
Alex Jones
Welcome to the party
That's like
Male or female
Maybe maybe he could
Instead let them choose what they want
Courtney herb
Horny goat weed supplements
Horny goat weed sold
It'll get you going that's why they call it horny goat weed
Then I guess so the end of our
Investigation
Of what happened so far we see little evolution
In his
Except
Hidalgo event and maybe someone told him to stop talking about his mob ties
I didn't speculate
The stuff that he was saying about Trump before this was
Basically vague
Accusations of crimes
You got to stop
Not necessarily in nefarious
Yeah
That
Who touched them and was like hey you got a
No, down on that
Species still says he doesn't trust him and thinks he's going to betray everyone
So there's no Evolution for the rest of the time
Jumpin Fun
Propaganda about Planned Parenthood
Abortion protesters
He literally
And not
Not in a figurative way like
Describe like Hillary Clinton
The demon
Smells like sulfur as a way of
Scribing
You know all of this
He's literally say
It is something inter-dimensional
And that
Protest
F******
Appear out
What is the grout
And if you confront them
They will
Underground
You staying we are lead
And he they are legion
Yeah make them throw up
Spell terrible
Is really bad
It's one of the few times
That I've been listening to the show and I legitimately like blurt last
C'mon man you sense memory you something
So if you'd like you can find us
Internet
At now it's right.com with another
Installment of this investigation
Picks up we are getting close to August
Where the first debate happen
Rodger stone is not shown up yet
I actually want to make this clear
What I remembered
That on our last episode
A little bit
Let me see if I can find the best way
Alex needs to be lied to in order to get on board with
Whole Hog
Because of the things he knows about him and the lack of trust
Sprat he knows about these connect
He knows about Russia connections
X y and z
So in order for him
Get on board what we said is he needs another
Compelling thing which we speculated would be
I
Regret that I didn't point out
Steve pieczenik
Text roll
In the whole car
Steve pieczenik is there to give the
Russia didn't hack this stuff
It was Patriots
Within our government
Okay so Steve pieczenik is there functionally as the cover
Live
Okay that's what I
Alright
I bet it's probably more likely it's
Everything seems everything
It could be nefarious but it could also just be bigot
The entirety of America
True
Serious though is
It's such a wild coincidence that all these people would
Change their mind in exactly the same way it reacts the same
Now United United them
Yeah
I believe
If you can also follow us on Twitter
Look at that bar iTunes
Reviews
That are really filled with
Dammit just hate
Sharon about
I read it Brian I know it's up
Compulsory walk you can
There's a button
Oh no it's right.
Sports magic that I give up
Which means
Rubber parts dealer
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work