Air Jordan pipes sweat it
I have great respect for knowledge like I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Fight.com
Acknowledge
What up
I need a second to think what are you doing
Necessarily celebrate
Anniversary of Maha
While I believe the Edible Arrangements would bake to differ
That was twice
Pics for her birthday
But it has been four years in January
Relative anniversary time. I bought her these I bought her a
Bouquet of South African flowers which she loves
She has no interest in like she would have slapped me in the face
Because I have never met her before
So I got it he's and I got it this beautiful face and she f****** loved it
And I feel like I crushed it I even put it on the scoreboard I have
1 romance Point nice to her 0 right now she's got s*** to do it's a tough year for for most people
Getting that one on the board first of the year get it on the board
Move on it feels really good and she's very happy and it
Awesome
My brakes by Jordan little more materialistic perhaps a little less romantic and we got this box of
Candy
And one of the things that was in it was velvet crumble
What is a honeycomb
Candy
And that sounds more like a exotic dancer but that's up to you. I love it so much
I ordered more of it and I ate all of the stuff
You know what happened to the sea turtles
Go get them, play scary monster ship because they stayed and they were
Lottery
I was so close to ordering more after stop myself
It's so good
I love the crunchy bar which is a fee sort of
The honeycomb
Covered in chocolate
You can get it like Treasure Island grocery store but it's so much better
The Velvet crumble is
So much better
Amazing
Stop sending me candy
400 lb
But I
So a Jordan we are talking
About a little bit of stuff
Address Ruth Alex Jones
I'm done
Hey we go
Blackjack
21 no dammit
Damn this is 2021
Blackjack
I don't know
It's
Something
It's not going to work
Interesting little stretch of time Alex
Just trying to rationalize again
Instill the events of
The sixth not my fault not my fault not my fault bunch
Antifa did stuff and now they're planning more attacks
Assure
Find a little bit annoying
Oh
But
At the end of this we are going to have something remarkable happened okay and I'm so excited about it that I want to get down to business
Okay
Troy thank you so much
Very much
Next I see spiders where there are none thank you so much and I'll probably want
Thank you very much very trouble
Stacy thank you so much you're an alcoholic
Spider Stacy
Not the Jesus Lizard thank you so much right now about what you want
Are you very much did not the Jesus Lizard
So Isaac
Progeny of technocrat
Money off that heroin
Yub
Is freakishly large
Isaac progeny of sin but aren't we all
I believe in the Bible
We are all born out of the first
Indeed
I wanted to say 22 folks thank you all
Show we are incredibly behind
Shoutouts
If you if you have not heard
I'll give you a shout out please send a message
To us and we will get to get that in
It's
I don't know we were you here how many we do up top you don't want to hear 30 of them
Impossible situation
It's a bit and a structure that is really affected with no one's listening
And now it's
Impossible makes us feel sad and I don't want anyone to feel
Left out for
Alias you'd like to send a message and we'll get that taken care of
Timely
Timely joke
Yosser
Also Jordan
Who's very excited today is Friday when this will be coming out
But on Sunday the 17th so special
It was happening I would like to give a pre-emptive shout-out for that and that is
Couple of walks
Eric and Michelle are celebrating their second anniversary happy anniversary
View yes indeed got a very nice
This message
Very cute
About diadem enjoying the show and Eric doing Alex Jones voice
Oh
The shoe to say sweet things
Happy anniversary to you too hope hope you have a great one this weekend to end
I don't know how you could say
You have a lovely figure
Now that doesn't sound right now it's like I'm good
Look at it
Austin 13th
Coming right at you but
He's not a context drop
From Today Show
A little plant
I love you
See isn't that sweet sweet
That is sweet. I do like to imagine Alex as a Georgia O'Keeffe
That's what I open
Secret Garden
Alex's
Michelle predict
Violence
Sure
Because of
Did the CIA
They're running qanon
Declared a National Emergency a particular martial law emergency in d.c.
Program
Across the United States owe
Martial law
But the CIA cooperative
Turtle launcher attacks
Argument is Vicky was like this operation to make
Supporters look bad you should
You should have been
Really aggressively going after the Mongo cuz they were making Trump supporters look bad
Hard know I would I would argue that we didn't have to do anything to make them look
No
I so I think that this is all like basically the preemptive stuff where Alex has a good science
Maybe some violence there might be some
Exit domestic terrorism
Friends with Stewart Road
Exactly
Who's still conspicuous in his absence on the show by the way
Preemptively explain these things you got to you got to make sure that the audience has a
Ready to go Justin
Application for why I like
This isn't a sign that our world is f*****
Right information so you also have to text you at roads and let him know that
You're still on his team and you're just running interference for him so we can commit
Violet
Don't worry Stewart I'm still scared of you this is a smart move for all of us for me to say that you're bad
So what's going on is that there's a globalist revolution that's happening and
Sino CIA running
Qanon in order to precipitate
His violent reveley to the global
What's taking over or something
Did you know that that's all in the Bible
We're in the midst of a global New World Order
Revolution Against Humanity
This has been foretold
What do you believe in God or whatever it is our psychic vision of the future
Is the future of the only two options
Space time continuum
We saw this socket
Becoming
Award
Thousands of years ago
Not just by John on the Isle of Patmos
Yeah so what time
Okay
And so John and Patmos to the Future Trump
Losing
Yeah you know I always thought of time as being more like a singularity
Existing at all times
Simultaneously
Back and forth
Yeah and empty John of course in Revelation you can see all the
Signs that he was talking about Trump
This is disgraceful
Seal was opened and
May was medicare-for-all I'm not religious
I don't care to
Be offended on religions behalf but it's a sacrilege Superbad
To be offended by this
Starts talking about
And then then he
He starts playing on my side of the street
It doesn't want us to declare that and so are you
The thing that should not be
Someday
Maybe even death
Oh no I kind of agree that Alex is what the enemy fears but not because he has any kind of competence
There is a force of Truth or any of that s*** no
Diesel the enemy fears in the same way that a parent would fear a charismatic weirdo trying to convince their four-year-old child that fire can
It hurt them
They aren't scared that the
The b******* of the mainstream media is propaganda about fire being dangerous
They're worried that this negative an insane influence will lead to the harm of people that care about
Fire can't hurt you I have candy in my van let's go
As for the Lovecraft reference
Of course Alex goes with that one
He's such a 101 dudes of course is going to rot something from Call of Cthulhu
Thing that he's misusing and reciting is part of a much
Puzzled over passage from the Necronomicon that is referenced in the story
It goes like
Is
That is not dead which can Eternal lie
And with strange Aeons
Even death
May die
What are the chapters in that story
Call the Cthulhu is inspector lacrosse
Where you hear about a Cop who discovered a group of cultists performing a ceremony and chanting
Thing Louis magnegas
Cthulhu really are
Bomgaars Alliance fhtagn
Beautiful language
Meant to be on pronounce
Human tongue
Blue Springs Loosely translates to
Quote in his house in really a dead Cthulhu Waits dreaming
What are the cultist to lagrasse interrogates
Old Castro
Necronomicon
Is it helps Gibson
Some contacts that are cheap
So the reader can piece together that they worship
Dormant God is in this place waiting and dreaming
And this God will never die
Life span longer than death
Anyway
The point here is that this phrase has nothing to do with what I have to stalk
LOL that's not about death dying really at all
I know that he thinks he's really cool and the most of his points of reference are very sci-fi things he barely remembers but this is a little bit
Get silly
For one thing Alex should not compare themselves
Cthulhu
Cthulhu did not want
To follow the concert
The tution and protect the Second Amendment
It's really clear the textbook Cthulhu was interested at what's that
Those first men formed the cult around small Idols which the great ones showed them
Idols brought in dim areas
From dark stars
That caught with no
Never die until the stars came right again
It will take great Cthulhu it from his tomb
Victon resume his rule of Earth
The time would be easy to know for that mankind would
Become like the great old ones
Free and wild and be gone good and evil with laws and morals thrown aside
In all men shouting in
I'm killing and revelling enjoy
Also Alex is a lot like
Then the liberated old ones would teach them new ways to shout and kill and reveling enjoy themselves
And Oliver quit playing with Holocaust of x
Freedom
I don't have nothing in common except they were both races
The difference
Between them is it Lovecraft got less racist as his career progression
That is true anyway.
Lovecraft death may die is a kind of cool same but no sense for what
What he's talkin about love sayings
F****** old
And we're going to die before he
Call Amvets
That is not dead which may turn Ally Israel
Is basically saying that he's just gone dormant he's not.
No he's been sleeping for centuries under under in really a
Why
I mean why does the Stars weren't right for him
Come back and rain and Terror on Earth
I never liked the arbitrary rules that are given to the old ones or this
The devil or all of these things man if you want. Ultimate Evil buddy install
That's
Fiction
That's why
I was making up arbitrary rules for the devil in the real world
Works a little bit
Silly
Alex was in DC over the. Of time when
The other store mango Capital happen
And
We're getting a new piece of reporting
Do you replace an antifa caused
Dolls are troubles forever
According to Alex
Alex
He almost got swept up
They planned
The SWAT team
In DC and blame me
What happened
We confirm that
I'll be honest I was so exhausted
I just ate a big meal on Thursday
Under stress
Yourself
I did not
Police cars came for me
I'm having told you this whole story
I will tell you all of
Please start using this one
Shows I could drink half a bottle of vodka and a big meals I was like I don't even give a s*** that is 100 police cars
Coming to SWAT team
Talk about Isaac maybe the reason that they were going to take me out and blame me for storming the capital
But then the police would
Go along with
Go fuc yourself to go with the police didn't arrest you because you were right out at the tip of the spear yelling
Runaway Runaway we can't do this this is bad
We get this kind of speech from Alex
Pretty regularly
Haha now I see everything become clear to me
Nlcb entire picture
Almost a subatomic level
Add
I know what your next moves are I know how to stop them I know what's unfolding
Underestimated
2 is 100%
Public intelligence
100% what's left
U.s. government
Use the movement to educate
You're not cute
Mom shooting
Bombings and capitals all over I told you that Sunday
From
DC police
This is a game how he's preemptively
Constructing this narrative just in case there is bombing as in stuff that are done by Trump supporters
You know at least
Alex is
On the surface
Telling his audience not to be viola
Right and there was some
I mean I guess it's better than the alternative in some ways but
It's too little too late and its meaning
Stole the election
So they need violence
Be part of it
It's a lie
The setup
And we now know the LIE
We now know the setup we know
Every
For this moment
Doug and Harwood everybody else has been shut down
It's all the Holy Spirit
The Divine transmission
Receiving
I'm telling you I'ma give you the transmission
Weather
God speaking through him
Fun
Also it's not a surprise to hear Alex insisting the people shouldn't be violent and the reason for that is pretty obvious
Alex knows there's a large enough population of people who work
Completely fried and disconnected from reality going to be disillusioned by the non-fulfillment of all their promise
Fantasies
That they might turn to violence
He's obviously not responsible for all of it but Alex's rhetoric has absolutely been in
Contributing factor to getting us to the dangerous situation we're now in
Ernie knows that
When your allies storm the capital and you make your money encouraging people to do things like storm capitals but you don't want them to actual
Can we do it
You have a few immediate priority
The first discovered with a framework to allow your audio
Pretend to be actual storming doesn't involve you or anyone like you
This is achieved by blaming antifa
In this case there's the unfortunate aspect of the story where a bunch of the people who stormed the capital of public figures and then
I've been very clear that they were doing it for
There's also a bunch of people involved who don't match your characterization of antifa at all
So to get around that object
Now it says Durham q12 the bus which is probably going to be persuasive to some portion of his audience total
The next most important thing you have to do
As what you're seeing right now
If you're Alex
You know damn well that this is not going to be a one-off event
Alex has been friends with Stewart Roads for years now he knows the kind of insurrection is threat that dude makes
And he's supposed to be the public
Thanks for the oathkeeper can't imagine who's
And underneath
I think we should
To kill everybody
And as your subordinate I would like to follow up with
Your neck
Yeah I mean store Road
Is the pr guy and he's talking about like
Rounding people up
Alex knows there's going to be more attacks so it's super important for him to create a pre-emptive narrative
Explain them when they eventually happen
This is achieved by more throwing you under the bus
If in the next 3 weeks
Instances of domestic terrorism in the people carry it out
Lapeer Dipietro
Supporters now Alex can fall back on saying things are really Trump supporters
They're people who were misled by the Insidious globalist psyop it is qanon
Song up there specifically running to make people like Alex
Trump Patriots look bad
Google very transparent it's stupid but it's
Crucial for Alex if he wants to
Continue to be able
Justifies
Behavior
In the face of the inevitable consequences of his behavior coming
Wow he needs to be a
Against the inevitable consequences to stay on
Write make money and not get arrested
I believe this is a very teachable
In the aftermath of the storm the capital I believe that you can see it very clear distinction between people who mean what they say
And people who are primarily scammers
People who really mean it are still calling for right-wingers
To show up in DC on January
People who really mean it are like the queue Shaman insisted that he was proud of his actions on the six
People who really mean it or even like Alex is boring intern Harrison Smith
Reporting the capital
Baldwin and the Patriots were in control as the events of the six transpire
Conversely Alex is a scammer
He has a very profitable Griff that depends on tension to continue
In order for that tension to exist
He has to operate in some distant ways
For instance if you believe the things
He says on his show
Here's what'll happen if Biden gets into office
The literal Christian devil will rule America
Christianity will be outlawed
Everyone will be forced to get vaccines it'll put tracking chips in them and killed them true
The door killing conservative as they died of the vaccine
And Alex will be one of the few to survive long enough to kill his neighbor and feed them to his daughter don't forget.
Mexican shirt that's
Somewhere in the middle
If you actually believe those things in anyway
He would not be opposed
Insurrection immediately
I believe those things that be only
Yeah because this is a fight with the Devil
If this were just about policy than sure you can accept Biden presidency where you try to Lobby conservit
Congress members to push
For policies you'd like to see
With all that she doesn't
Matter if you believe a lie
If I can get them to office there's no policy discussion
There will never be fair elections again in the future
If you believe Alex than this election itself was stolen which has supposedly already been proven
If you believe that and you believe the futility of any action you could possibly take one to Biden gets into office
But it's a natural conclusion
Do decide that you need to do whatever you can
Before he gets into office to stop that from happening
This is the inherent dissonance Alex's nonviolent position brings up
He expects his audience to believe in but if they actually do the only conclusion they can come to his
Exactly the conclusion
The people who stormed the capitol on the 6th
He's basically made an argument to his audience where he demands
The be definitively except
The he's proven every one of the premises in his argument
But hey man I don't want to take responsibility for you
I can see through the Matrix
And I can see that your death
Is eminent
And what I would like you to do
Nothing well or you could give me money
This is how we will crush them
Satan
You understand like this is this is nonsensical this this this kind of behavior
Anyway
Here we go again it's a good thing nobody will face consequences
For this type of behavior that that's
That's really heartening
Thing to know
So we get to Narrative of the six
I just being laid out
Pretty much found his his final version of
Handcuffing
Kelly members of Congress
Lockdown
Happy fuzzishot Force
All in unison
The Patriots
Help the police
This is serious so this didn't work so now they need 2.0
We're going to
It's a storm
If I were officer leaving Goods family I would have
Definitely Sue Alex Jones for defamation
Immediately
Absolutely not proven is just
Making up and then either killed himself or was killed
To cover it up
Whenever there's something that the police should have stopped but don't it's important for Alex to pretend its some nefarious Force ordered
Stand down to allow it to happen
As opposed to them
Just being a Nazi to time it's because of Apple
Aggressively
And again the argument on the other side is they seem to turn a blind eye a lot of the time when there's these
Hard right
Extreme protest
Guardian just had something about that everyone already knew
Which is that police are meaner to the
Yeah yeah
In the case of the storming of the capital A traditionally discussed
Offenses that Alex has decided to just pretend that a man who died by Suicide was actually secretly killed
So you couldn't reveal who had ordered him to order the stand
As far as I can tell officer liebengood isn't someone who would have been in the position
To make orders at the Capitol Police would follow
It's not like he was
The chief or even in the executive department of the Capitol Police
I can't imagine that he would have been someone who could have unilaterally acted in the manner that Alex is claiming it goes higher
This isn't based on anything other than the fact that this man is now dead
The fact that he's dead makes him useful prop
Sprouts using creating disc
Conspiracy
Because it creates a dead end
We could figure out who orchestrated this whole setup
Nystatin as we can't reveal that information
Which obviously would prove alexandrite
The guy is a thing to Alex
That's not a person
I find that
Disgusting
I used to be so rude
What's the
We're at the point now where it's like
If Alex does this I'm I'm almost like sending a message immediately like hey
This can't happen
I don't fortunately you're the only person with grounds
I would love to do a bond like the world should work like this but apparently the law doesn't count
So disgusting
Search
The law won't just be like hey you know he's bad for Humanity so Humanity has grounds I certainly hope
The officer's family is in
Dealing with any kind of harassment
And from
Folks who believe the sort of things that Alex
Based on the past and actions of Alex's audience they will
Able to think that it might be happening not salute
How do I
What's fancies himself
Peaceful
Kind of protest
Forgot he wants a peaceful Revolution
Kind of like Martin Luther King
Right
Martin Luther King
Free
90%
But
What folks think
And they watch them get their heads
People like
Their parents dead
There's a big ass man. Boys not doing
That is a f***** up setting
I don't understand the timeline
I don't know what's going on
Hellboy
Severely Alex's grandparents are black people singing Christian hits
That means like we're not going to be racist anymore no I think they're not going I guess they were all the ones who had the fire
Fire hoses
I got his Alex's whole family was holding fire roses and they were like
Oh I get it they're sick
Yeah
Also I know that Alex loves
The product this idea that he respect Martin Luther King and his non-violence and that's all good and well
The standard line to hear from people on the right thing but I wanted to discuss how out-of-touch he is with his own intellectual turn
Most of Alex's ideas or just reheated John Birch Society talk
Points that is you know
Underpinnings of patriot lure for the last generation
His favorite book the one that woke him up to the New World Order of courses and none dare call it
Conspiracy by Gary Allan
A thing like Gary Allan didn't just write one book
His first book is called Communist Revolution in the streets
Switch is all about how the Civil Rights Movement is actually secretly a Communist front
That sounds like a better dance party
The book was published by Western Islands
Which is the John Birch Society publishing imprint and it has a forward written by W Cleon skousen
Another of Alex's Gyros on the uncle of his regular Infowars gas Joel skousen
The book is a slightly different take on Martin Luther King and goes out of
This way to suggest that he was a violent revolutionary who only said things about nonviolence to appear acceptable in public
In a caption on a picture of Martin Luther King on
Page 1 of this book
Allen Reitz
Although King talks nonviolent many of his alliances are formed with negro leaders who Advocate violence
And give the movement it's quality of revolution
This is an important idea of the ante, no
Set the entirety of the Civil Rights Movement was a communist
Facade and that Martin Luther King was essentially there to trick white people into thinking it was a peaceful Revolution
From page 2
King closed his talk by declaring that of course he meant that should be done non-violently
Many in the crowd last opened
They felt the term non-violent was ashamed was being used by King primarily for public relations
Whether Alex knows it or understands it is irrelevant
What matters is that the system that he supports and all of his intellectual influences who molded his beliefs when he was young
We're deeply racist people who had a particular hatred of Martin Luther King
Not because he was violent
Because he was Christian and Zack him yeah
I guess what I'm getting at is that Alex Jones is a coward
He's not even willing to leave his beliefs the way his forefathers would have totally he knows that it looks pretty racist to be opposed to Martin Luther King
These days
Who pretends that I mean
Someone
To talk about
Standing down
In the face of something and then to talk about Martin Luther
The King Jr very shortly afterwards is someone who does not know anything about Martin Luther King
It's another little interesting element of Disney
Yeah yeah yeah it's like
It's like somebody being like a my my dad was in the FBI and
You know when they murdered Fred Hampton he was like
That was one too many bullets
As for me I'm going to choose
The path of
Peace from here on out
Can I find so fascinating is like how much Alex
Wants to live in the shadow
Of these anti-communist Heroes and like
It's so his worldview all of this is
But he refuses to take
Ownership
Of these things that he knows absolutely
Yeah I can't be against the Civil Rights Act
You know it's it's one of those things where it's like
You can see how
Bankrupt their ideology is over
Time because they just abandoned s*** after it
You don't like just refuse to accept it public
Well I mean yeah
I mean that that like
Martin Luther King Junior is so
F****** revered
That the right
Has to now use him to try and reinstitute slavery they can't like
He's such a great guy
He would have wanted us to own you again I'm sorry Alex drunk enough you would talk about how he's
Sure
Anyway
There's truck bombs coming
But also Alex says
Y'all got to go.
Your Capital sure
Bombs in major cities this weekend or next week
Master plan
It's too early stage mass shooting
Why would we do
We want to be out of the capital this weekend
Gun
What happened
Jesus
Have your video camera and.
Document
Every person so you don't want to do that isn't it kind of contradictory
Maybe just unwise to tell your audience like hey there going to be a bunch of s*** to everybody
I'll be fine cuz I'm in a tank
You guys are good
Fairly certain
That's not
If you think this is going to be like staging as of mass shootings and bombings
I would say for the party
Protection of your audience stay home
Listen
They're going to blow everybody up
Killing you
Left and right
And that's why you got to go
Themes
There were some looking like the people that I'm supposed to tell you are
Antifa
Picture
There was a people who are not answer
See if I actually who were involved on the
Who plays Bob
No that's a couple pipe bombs
You can't miss these at
Antifa
You can't miss
You'll see Chinese
Backpacks as well
They are deep State marks
Core
Halliburton
United
Houses
All of that up
Nothing real about any of that you know what is boggling my mind
What's that is that he literally did
Did say it
And it is
True
They were planning on taking hostages
And assassinating members of Congress
Yes
That was a
Well that's something
Like a conspiracy theory Dan
Did something that is disgusting
Certainly their people who have some suspicions
That that is that was the plan there indications
Of that
Start. To learn more
Thanko s*** that's
Are they have members of Congress helping him that's
Alex
Alex is definitely of the
Mind in terms of reporting that it was supposed to be way worse
Yeah
And that might be that might be the case
There's a lot of details there yet to be
Solidly understood but some of the indications are really really terrifying
You know there's there's some issues between Alex
Some cute
Estranged
Stuff like
Why did
You do this earlier
No no
To get to the point where you realized it was actually the people remember only two years ago
What he said he could
Could see through the Matrix and saw their plan and knew what was
He could read the
The conning Tower scale yeah
Now he understands
But all of that and now he sees why qanon
Trapped him
In the early stages
I'm just going to throw this out the
If
He he said
The same thing two years ago and got everything
Wrong
Okay
Why would I been trust him now when he says
Because you forgotten that he said all that stuff that's why I wish I could do that
You attacked our totally onto and here's why
This isn't my opinion
We know where this is going
We know what you really on
Because you figured out
4 years later
Under orders
Operation
Let's do this so we can put on information Mike Jones books out
Axillary interesting but so nobody gets sued
But it was instantly taken away in three weeks by the group
The Trump campaign people.
I don't believe any of this stuff
But if it is true that seems insanely illegal
Also again
Trump was officially running qanon
Beginning
Why do you keep telling me how shity your
God-king is it doing this
3 weeks
Just steal the greatest f****** conspiracy from the government that's all it took
And how
Password to put two-step notification what what are we doing here
Home
And if that's the case
Bright and all this happen
At 3 weeks and it got commandeered
By these nefarious people
Wouldn't be in the best interest of the Trump campaign to like
Really make sure the people understood that this was something that was a malevolent Force
So it didn't
End up becoming such a
Used part of the Trump base or at the very least
Utilize
The vast resources of the United States government
To take
Back
Oh yeah they could do that to 3 weeks they stole our access to Q
About an hour later we stole it back it's a hardware the government
Yeah
I do love the idea of the other like they attacked because I knew I was the only person
God dammit
Detective only person
Besides everyone else now
God I hate them some other things that are starting
To come to light that are a little bit problematic for Alex's narrative
Namely that
We are proud boys
Who were around the capitol
And sometimes you know there's some indication
Even
Some of the problems might have been there
Regret if they get going
Getting going Park
Say something
Very close to revealing information
Major Patriot group was infiltrated
Ahead of the savanna
Leader was arrested
Global Offensive
Bhattacharjee
But they can also
Command
Mario get arrested right before he's the leader of the proud boys
What didn't you big
Become the leader of
Yeah buddy
Yeah this I'd like this is the way these
This is the way these games died it's whatever exactly whatever they decide but some of them
Working against them and they tear themselves apart
That's that's the good news here that's what I'm
Hearing idiots
Cowboys accident
Counter to the scam narrative that I need to
To keep my money, then so well guess they actually got infiltrated
I just
Hey
How often
I said
Before this all happened
Guys
They're going to abandon you the moment I do something that they don't like yes they don't have any loyalty to
You can't trust
How these things work
Yeah and to see the ways that like it's hard to have
Too much pity for
Someone Like You
McHugh shaman
Community interacted with him after the fact somebody tried to
Play I got a lot of suspicions about it like
You're done
Everything happy you guys told me to do I became the hero that you guys needed and now you've abandoned me
How could anyone have predicted
So this episode Alex is really like acting in a lot of ways that I think a bad
Because as we discussed earlier that like if you take him seriously and you believe the things he saying
Going to kill you
They're coming to kill you
And he just in your home
He keeps banging that drum
They want
They want to inoculate you and watch you have a convulsion
They want to kill you they love hurting you
They're coming
Comics there's nothing you can do except
Face reality
How we beat the
We have cancer he have a satanic cancer
Are you or them
Look at that their race look at Schumer
Look at Pelosi
These are not human
They're coming
I need your brains they need your soul they don't have it
They want to destroy you they want to bring you down
They love Chinese death camp
They're all turned over to evil
I mean
And that's why you need to stay at home and write your congressperson on violence and send letter
And just be aware that's why you need to go put up Infowars bumper stickers and buy
Colloidal iodine fuckyourself man
So Alex is saying here's what you need
When they come to your home
Knock on your door to kill you
And then they leave
Yeah yeah
You flash your Infowars bumper sticker and it's like garlic to a Dracula
Has a really interesting relation
Ship with the events of the 6th
Thunderstorming
And I've noticed a little thing that he's starting to talk about more or starting to
To bring up and I think that one of his primary concerns is that they planned it
Poorly
Will you sleep
Bullet Button
They are controlling the dumbest violent elements to make sure that it's all
Lcq saying
Schumer's house or go to Obama's house or where they're at
Oh no no no
That's kind of sucked up
Yeah
I mean he's probably not wrong
Black if you
Planned it better and used
60 and you f*** everything up then
Trump takes power says that it's all actually antifa
Gets the military on his side starts f****** everybody up who isn't a proud boy or whatever
But instead they did it poorly so here we are
Maybe it's hard to play what if game
It shouldn't be that Alex is like Wildman a plan that s*** for lately
Right right
Resent
As much as
They got tricked
Qanon and antifa
On the other side of the building where you at
Oh no it's okay
He's 100%
I mean we know that
Those little indications a little momentary like
It's poorly planned and they didn't go too soft
Target yeah
Okay yeah
Yep
Now you might think
Let me ask you a question
Shorty
If Alex
Jones
Sees a guy
Sorry I did and you didn't finish yes he's a guy who's got like a really hot wife
I'm sorry nevermind he's a jealous of that guy
Absolutely will he say so
No well actually he will by going on a long-winded rant about how he's not
Horse or something
I'm just glad you're having sex
What the average man I've learned
Just as envious of ever
That's weird
That is a weird thing to say that's a weird thing
Bowser like I'm so glad you get to f*** that in my head I was waiting for him to say some
Something about miseducation like that's the level of you get f***** up I'm
Operating a person's attractive you get to f*** them and have kids Jesus I look at that like
I got a horse
This is not just this is not just a very
Weird way for me to still experience jealousy
Jesus
Alex has a Gaston
It is interesting because this person is basically be
Been shouting qanon
Stuff into the wheeler or weeks
Yeah
Patrick Byrne is a really smart fella
Tell you about where there's a peaceful way
Violent
Patrick Byrne is the former CEO of Overstock who's yalla
Qanon nonsense. Nonsense
On the six
Or the rally before the before the rally
Tell you but if your violin
You're just helping Nancy
Pelosi
What you were doing
20% of America
And then the other thing is
Basically she wants
They keep talkin like they were talk to BonChon in Fort Worth about outlawing the Democratic Party
What are you doing
We need literally word for word we need to get rid of the Democratic Party
And then the Republican Party
Split into two parties one the far-right party and one the right party
That's what I said.
The important thing now is that you don't get viola
Kill everything
Calling for
Not go
Take selfies
Don't want to go to prom
We don't want to do it but if you raise everything a burned-out everything
Kill Everybody
I am
Blinded by the idea that you could think
The guy saying you should toss the Geneva
Conventions right back up your ass and burn everything to the ground along the way
He's a good guy
That confused
This is me Dan
Well it's B
Because
Do you know he's at
He's good
The Democrats are evil and they're run by Satan and what you need to do is not take the moral High Ground
Turn everything to the f****** ground
He's not saying what he wants to do that just did it would work
Also again
Again he would defeat the global cfra
These Patriots did a Sherman's march right and that burned down everything killed everyone around them
But it's antifa who did all the
The violent dial blahblahblah singers
They were proud boys who'd been co-opted by a fan
You guys got to work overtime to say we didn't do exactly what we said that
Headed to do it's a little silly
A lot of people burn
He's got a really simple suggestion for what needs to happen start Overstock too.
Overstock pallets
Okay
These guys
One of the things they always have is like a solution to the problem
Today of a solution that's
Really really simple
But man it is not simple
Insanely complicated
Would be outrageous to actually do but
This is all we watch
Count
Live stream TV by the National Guard
We see what happens if
How does helicopter
Election
Show is 500,000
30 days 45 days they're going to run it
If you want
It'll be most drunk Heights
Ha
I would be
Is it so much to ask is I will I say this to you honestly
I think the only thing that could get
Over ninety percent of Americans to try and overthrow the government
Any party saying let's have another election right now
I think everyone is a little burned out
I'm f****** done
F****** done not doing this not doing
Not doing another election
That will make me want to burn everything to the ground
I like when people like Patrick trying to play this game is essentially
Offering this like
False idea of a simple solution but why wouldn't you accept this really simple solution totally
Bisphenol of Arkham
You're obviously not true
It's a setup it's a trap
Imagine a scenario where an
This world or the United States is like
Yes okay we will do this National Guard hand
Count of these ballots
What would end up happening is the NAT will be used as an opportunity to find a new problem that they can use to complain
Trying
Get this national election
National Guard
Or whatever
Don't just a f****** stupid game
Trying to get sufficient
Adventure they're trying to go on volume something to complain about
Airbnb
Almost makes me long for the days when they would have to actually move the goalposts instead of being able to see that they've set up
Goalpost exactly Twenty Yards apart for
Infinity and every time you reach one they're like
VSCO post
That one over there
Mad annoying
So at the under-12
Trump was speaking in Alamo TX
Which is not the Alamo
Which was totally on purpose
You chose Alamo the city 100% on purpose at work just cuz nobody knew that he was coming doesn't mean that you didn't choose album
Another city 100%
And Alex knows that it's the city not the Alamo building would help and he is also said the people are gathering at
Alamo
There is some confusion
And I think that Patrick
I'm not sure if he knows if it to the Alamo or Alamo Texas
These people
Alamo
It would be
Area
Morals
No.
Questions with people who are at the Alamo
I don't I don't go off
The past Lloris later on
He's going to save it
Both sides of his family were on the Mayflower
Why.
Why not I love it
I was married to Queen but I don't think he's related to Colonel Travis at all
Now anyway we get a revelation about spiritually they're both drunk
True
Bumblebee
Hyperfocal bug
Trivia about what's going on in Patrick Burns
Do people get cold people get fluids but they're calling
The PCR test we have any viral background
Pheasant you have felt
Trying to convince wow wow
Cheese's
Did Patrick not realize you weren't supposed to actually have covid ever
If you are near Alex's show
Yeah it's only imagine that 40% of info Warriors it probably had it
I think I'm not working
I bet the numbers High
So Allie Alexander
Is the head of stop the
Bastille
He was involved in the the rallies
On the six
2 something
Capacity
He has done some live streams or he talked about how he planned
The event
Franco's
To put pressure on the people voting about the Electoral College
Along with
Paul gosar
Mo Brooks
Send Andy Briggs
Yep three members of Congress
Yeah it's good to know in the aftermath of everything he is
Kicked off all social media
Rumors flying around about him being in hiding
And some of that might be a little bit of a crowdfunding operation
The Drifters got a grip
But if they're trying to play this really interesting line about weather or not
He's in hiding
Because they don't want him to be in hiding
Cuz that makes him look like a week
They also
Want him to be in hiding
Because that makes everything really scary
Stop
I'm not in hiding
You know for my own
Protection because of
Tents
Thousand
People that the media has
Inspired
To issue me
Call from my
Maya Pub
Public execution
I am patient
I've had to travel
By unconventional means
You taking a dirigeable
That would be I would be if I would be happier if Allie Alexander did try and overthrow the
Government but Viator Isabel at that would be great
Normal force
Call Bliss will let me get around but I have to look silly doing it I don't know why it's part of their rule
Put one leg on a skateboard at all times
It's not in hiding but I'm also in an undisclosed location and I have to
Travel video
Vegetable beef and sauce
Fox News
Sort of narrative about what happened.
At the Capitol
Pretty similar to Alex I guess
I believe it forces within our government coordinated with the paramilitary arm of the
Democrat Party
Discuss
Inside the US Capitol not everybody was discussing
Okay
Is are
Belmar
What's coming
Performance
They would have breached the US House
What we know is that only
Jake that weird
Your shaman
And by the way
A lot of people don't know this here's an exclusive
Counter-protesters
The last doctor
You rally in Arizona
Stop the steel
In Arizona he's probably answer your phone I looked into this and apparently what happened is that the
Showed up at Allie Alexander's event
Alright
Yeah they did get a speaker slot videos not happy about it proposed a new solution to our problem
Here's my here's my pic
Okay all of these grifter type
Are scrambling to
Scapegoat
Which I like how it's 2020
Are 2021
Too late now it's already happened
There's scapegoating people
Got to do it
Even though they love them
Mx400
Propose
The Thunderdome
Alright Alex Jones has to go up against
Execution
Thunderdome two men enter one man leaves
Are you talking about the place where they now have WWE Raw absolutely Thunderdome
Two people
Enter
One leaves until we have a single ideological group
I mean
Post better ratings and Alex's normal show
I'd watch that
The paramilitary wing of the democratic party it's just
It's really short interview cuz Alex has another
This guy's uncle
Wrote the foreword
For a very racist
Book written by Gary Allan about the Civil Rights Movement
Joel skousen
He has some interesting
To ask about hey we're supposed to admire General Flynn
No Alex did that interview with flying in that interview General Flynn said 100% Trump is still going to be
President after
January 20th
Amscot
How could you be so stupid
How many believe something
But I'm convinced that there's somebody else
Perhaps General in the military
Was talking to them and telling them
I'm a patriot are you know there's a whole group in the White House
No other explanation for why
General Flynn
In the face of all that we know about the Deep state would make a statement that there's a hundred percent
Donald Trump's going to win
Yeah I wish you'd ask him if you have contact with those who was to contact who told him
Somebody perfect
I'd appreciate that
That seems rude I would appreciate that as well I am going to sleep better tonight knowing that Jenner
Errol Flynn is being bothered by the nephew of w Cleon skousen
Ignoring his text make me feel very good
It's nice to know the general plan is soon going to have to get a new phone number cuz skousen woke about fathers
That's what I want out of this whole thing
Epstein
Let's bring him back
Everybody realize that they just trying to
Start the f****** capital
He's dead
Right
I guess
I guess what drives the Deep State the promise that we will make all of your sins go away
Unless you do something
Stupid
Jeffrey Epstein
Exit him
You know you can't put anything past
Gay people suspicious
Whatever alright
There was a video that was going around
On Twitter
I believe that this is what Alex is talking about
Someone brought it to my attention, people actually
There was a video of Alex yelling of Alex
Yeah
It was supposedly like
After all of this
Like Trump conceding Abbey has turned on amateur
And it was
The videos from when Alex
Got mad at Trump for bombing Syria
Messes up his dirty ass it was that same day
Realize the feeds were alive
Okay
And people people like about it saying it was implying that it was
Alex
Thinks it might be a deep
Martial law
I've been through a lot of stress
In 27 years on are probably 10 times I flipped out late at night
My dog died
Dog.
Custody
But there's nothing modern
Jesus Christ
A long time like that sounds like
And it took something I've done
Together their exaggerated
Am I bi a deepfake
Yeah that sounds right
Sounds right it's probably deepfake
Videos nice screaming of Sanity about Trump
Is that the only difference
Between the right-wing in like
Other people is just like
Other people who like hey
I suppose I could be wrong
About something
Not Deepak
Yeah the right is just like
I am going to have
To go with I'm still right no matter what
So skousen interview is not really all that info
Interesting either you sort of going on the same
Tracks that we've already seeing not really bringing a whole lot more to the
The conversation outside of
Glen's number sure and reviewing that Epstein's probably alive
Still
Alex
I'm sorry about
Presidents
This might be the light
President
He's our president he's in a marriage
Probably the last
For the return
Does God gives you the example of what to do right before the fall
This is what you could have had
So Alex is the fourth hour now
Because
Trump's going to give his speech
In Alamo
Alex is
Constantly going on and on about how like
No one else is broadcasting this speech
She's
It's very annoying
But
After the speech he gets into like this really f***** up headspace
I swear he's just talking about how like
I've lived in the fire
The fire alright
The bacon grease
People like Jones are you scared
Theophilus
Graceful
I've been lowered out of it
Whole life
The wave
Because I believe
But I warn you
When you get lowered down into that Grayson your toes hit that
Boiling
How's your legs
Waking up your chest
That you're going to fight
I'm
Betting on
You
Lived in the grace
For decades
I would say physically
My bad is made of Greece
Weird
I don't even see melted Grace either I see they're like solid stuff ever leave it out for a day and then sitting there
It's basically like a sensory deprivation tank
Joe Rogan got me all this information please
What's every two weeks
Crying also at the underwear episode
Nothing will fulfill you like the Holy Ghost
Holy Ghost will fulfill you so much you
Even believe it
Like God demands you take action
Which team scary
Don't know why I be
Salon
It isn't a joiner
It is
Why was I not doing before
There's actually
Guilt
Once you join God Satan is a rotting dead
Carcass in the corner
With maggots covering it
And your Galaxy
How did this ever quite well how is this
Heading you watch civilization falling your people falling
Chuck
Replace Trump
Replace your mother
Was Satan
Everything that song
And everything is good with Ally
Why
What you do that
Alright Alex imma need you to do this again from the top.
That's what Alex
Grape truck with lighter
Are we having for dinner tonight
Batman
I want to wait I can't wait for the inauguration
Cuz I want to see if Alex
The Joe Biden
Pump It Up
I do I do love the idea that you can you can reach Enlightenment like
You think of the great the great Buddha
They managed to pierce the veil and detach themselves by seeing the ultimate meaninglessness of our space at the unit
Instead of like being like I've reached Enlightenment they were just like
Odf
Interesting
So that we get to the 13th
And Alex is in a different heads
Feels doomed a little bit
Ever see the children of men that movie I have
Let people talk about it right now
Divorce.com
How to put a live audio video
We are now in the New World Order
Tune into this emergency broadcast if you want to live
Because when you look at
And when you see children are 23 years old today
They're growing up in a dystopia
That's the last generation
Barely be able to have children and most of them won't be able to
And most the children you see today
Will be
Cancerous
You're all being killed
All the FBI agents to know
Part of the system
I can tell you the people running this
Are not in control
Then are they running it
Advanced knowledge
S***
Aliens
The devil it's the devil alien
Okay
Interdimensional
Interdimensional demon Devils trying to give you vaccines in order to kill you but please don't storm the capitol
I am almost 100
Percent positive whatever you do just spread link
To my contacts
I'm just so sure
There's a promise that you at least won't be f***** over by the devil
Inhale
Until after you die
He's poking you here
I just don't think
The Pitchfork is actually three vaccines
Sharks
Broncos right so so silly whenever they take
Stupid religion and they're like
Now let's add some science to it now that we know about different dimension
Airplane man
Which lowers everything down from like a spiritual thing to just add another f****** thing takes a lot of value away from it
It's like oh you know I understand that lightning is static electricity as you know what it's like
It's not as
Magical is if is Zeus with throwing it at me
Now I know God's just some a****** in a different
Dimension
But that guy
Music by Dimension if you want to tell me what to do and it doesn't reduce the
That like
Once you realize this
Lightning isn't
Thrown by Zeus electrical
You can then create lightning
You can understand it
And if you know it kind of takes away the point of religion
If you bring all this science stuff to it
It's within the realm of human comprehension and then it's not really
Religion at all you see through a glass Darkly
Dimensional travel could if it is X
Dimensional
Then that would suggest that there is a possibility
That we could eventually Pierce our way through into God's Dimension and
Finally kill and overthrow God like we've always been dreaming or conversely Alex does have an actual shot of the
Destroying the death
It sounds silly.
The devil's behind everything
I gave him 20 to 1 odds that's generous
We can look at all this news and all the things that are happening all the insanity
We just said ourselves
Well this is this is
But it's not
We have a fallen nature
We are being manipulated
Dimensional
Creature
What is out of the blue
Spectrum vision
Velvet planet
And has a plan to overtake us play God and then use us and our creativity
To build an escape system
What
We're way more
Seize the creature
That turned against God
What
Bible churches in the Mason
And all of that is to keep you from that information
Churches are trying to keep this Friday
I love that
I want to end every insane things
Everything think I say was just now that's the Bible
That's the Bible
Build guys
Put that one in the book
Yeah
It'll be in to be really interesting if like all the stories about Alex that end up getting printed in the
You know these Outlets
Like they LED with
F*** you how dare you pretend that any of these people have anything other than
Believes nonsense before their name
Who believes that communism is being directed by a literal demon totally
Totally
Staying away from him
Bad whenever you're like oh that
So
In the future
Sick people before
To merge with me
Machines
Sounds right
I'll actually be killed
What you
Have to pretend
That they haven't been killed and these machines are actually them
Or else you will get in
Trouble
Coffee
But if you don't
Understand
Everybody dies
And there's no more children
And in the process of wanting to live to the social credit score
Until you involved
Public ritual
Sterilizing your children
Sterilizing yourself
Resisting God resenting God
Because you're so sick
You got the mercy machine
So you just believe you have a chance to fill live
Do you will actually die
Should be a law
But you cannot
Call
The synthetics that are
Human
Machine merge cyborg
If you say that's not a person anymore
They didn't transfer over to machine it's a fraud why mean honestly that's right
I don't know if I would go that far
Now that's
The Bible
Study just so much and now he wants so far
Levels
Anybody can go away with the globalist and what they
Carryout
But now from my immersion in this since about 7 years old
Great analogy
It's only going to get worse from you
This is a lunatic
Yeah.
The end.
This lunatic here he wants
What's 2
It seems like he wants to distance himself
Drop a little bit
No I can't imagine
And this was one of the first indications of like
Didn't work out
You know if whatever
Hotel liberal-conservative all of you
Trump
Wishful thinking
I thought about this app right about this
I'll explain
I want to come back
The new Motors
Tune into this emergency broadcast if you want to live
Not a joke
God of this world
Wishful thinking
Yeah
What did you start listening to
Starting the back catalog where I was like in 2017 guys
Trump is going to abandon you the moments that it's
Expedient for him to f****** do so
Building up something that's going to eventually blow up
The giant coward
Play also I know that I think
You and I've heard Alex say the Trump is one of the greatest
Christians
However
He's very religious and deeply religious
Got all these types
Actually is impressed
He's more of an energy guy
He's never been a devil worshiper
Undercover
You said he was a secret agent
The energy
You said he's been a Christian since like
40 years
What Trump
People with jet
Control border
Populism
Optimistic
How to say no we want
Evil pedophile
Common Chinese zombie
Trump is a false flag
Tired
Can tires
Wait so tired I know that this is exhausting and it's so stupid
But trust me
The end of this episode is going to be so worth it
I don't know I know that he's implying kind of like Trump is a false flag which is weird cuz
Analyze the last years of your career than buddy boy
Alex is trying to sum it up here on this episode is like
Hey me a call Bubba
I put too much faith in the guy
You do a what do you know
I got two up to
Peach
You see that again
What's the populist movement
It was powerful but
I put too much help in it
You didn't well go fuc yourself
Get to Lighthouse
As much as possible all the
Vista come together
And this is something that I feel like the right should get on board with
These guys just don't
Get to do this
Propaganda Alex doesn't get to go back
And also it would be good for there to be a real moment of reflection for people who are serious and not
Total assholes who just happen to have
More conservative ideas about the way
Estate
Should maybe be organized
Take a moment to reflect on how
What these people have done
To your party
Now we're at a point
Where most right-thinking people
Will not
Engage with conservative ideas
Because
These people have taken over
The premise of your party alright so it's January 21st
Skiatook
Good time for us to start getting to work on the new agenda and now we're going to talk with Mo Brooks
Suggest two weeks ago helped orchestrate a f****** coup
About
Text proposal
F*** that why in God's name would I talk about any policy issue with you if I know your secret plan is
Overthrew the goddamn government
Yeah and it's not fair
For Alex to pretend that is excited about that
You don't get to do that now it's personally mean to me
I got a little bit
Of a feeling of something trying to express something that he's not willing to express
I might be psychoanalyzing too much but
Pushing past boundaries in doing
Really really destructive hate
Predator
Which you are
Respectful
People
You're stealing people's death
You're hurting
The loving energy on this planet
You're not
Good people
Your failure why you're all so scrawny
Ugly fat sick
Because you're losers
Now you call the thing that abused you
You will get so much power from the Holy Ghost
You will be ashamed of yourself and what you were and you will not even know how to deal with it
Infinitely greater than that
So I think if you pay close attention to the words that Alex is saying there I
Think you can hear that
As him ranting about himself
He's saying if you satanic losers he's yelling about herself
Pathetic because they were crushed by a system and it responds
They're buddying up to the very system they crushed them in hopes of getting power from
God will give you unspeakable power
Alex has been pretty clear in the past about how much suffering
Supporting Trump has brought into his life
From the financial hardships
Civil lawsuit
Susan way more trouble than he was before he decided to take on Trump as his Divine champion
That can easily be understood is Alex being crushed by a system
In response he's clung on for dear life hoping that system that it crushed him would give him some power in the end which now is
Becoming painfully clear
He's not the case
But there's a different more important level to this s*** that I don't think Alex even understand cuz he's talkin
In This Very episode it's super clear that Alex is working through some buyer's remorse on Trump
And having to admit to his audience that he got too optimistic about Trump as president
But this is not
The same thing as like you or me being slightly disillusioned with some of the policy objectives
It weren't achieved under Obama this isn't a situation where Alex just like Trump and he wasn't as good as he hoped
Alex routinely said the Trump was a leader anointed by God
God had told Alex that Trump was the way to go
For Alex to now get soft on Trump isn't admission that he was either making all that s*** up or he's actually soft on God
Alex doesn't mean any of the things he says
The constant talk about God being on his side and his enemies being
Controlled by the devil didn't mean anything
It's all just
Extremist talk to make the difference between his side
The other side
Impossible to ever wreck
Reconcile
I get the sense that Alex is beginning to recognize that Trump himself is a dead end
And the price of continuing to believe that he's a god-ordained ruler
Despite the fact
Biden is president
Will believe that he is required to do things like storm the capitol
And he doesn't want to do that cuz then there's no money anymore
Yeah it's in this is just like
I wish I wish the people could see that more clearly
Any audience member of Alex's
The thinks that he has some kind of an actual connection
To the religious ideas that he presents like
You got to get over that
It's not sent total
I just heard him say you're killing people's dreams and then I was like immediately cut 20 and 4 are trying to get a job in media and five
Infowars person that I've seen actually
Make the leap
I think so there's a guy Mikhail Phelan who
For some
I can't remember what Outlet
What he writes for
But I've seen
Bylines from Carol Phelan
Yeah it being pushed around by people who don't realize he used to work at Infowars
I have a little bit less of the stink
Politico
I'm not sure
But yeah it everyone else dreams crushed
Brutal
There's news coming out here on the 13th and end conversation starting to happen
What about this this idea
How to put up a representative Mickey Sheryl about the the
Possibilities there was a Recon tour before that some members of Congress were
We're leaving in this
Really f***** up
For Alex
So he's just
Decide it's not real
Congresswoman
Congressman
He was conning at
That's all I
She is said that Congress members some Congress members giving me at tours of the Capitol building to pee
People on January 5th
The day before the storm
This is suspicious to her because there were no official tours being done at the moment because of covid-19
13 weird to these people to be inside the capitol at all
As of this recording Cheryl has joined more than 30 house members calling for an investigation into the people who were there the day prior in
Proceed
We'll never lot more
As it stands right now if what you suggesting is true things may be way more f***** up
Then they appear
But I do want to call out
Is a bit of misinformation that I think Alex
Is combining with this and that is that there was a particular video that was
Was floating around that shows Allie Alexander Alex and Nick Fuentes
In what appears to be the capitol built
People claim that this video is from the day before the storming but I've actually found that footage posted as early as November
It's from when the three of them were in the Georgia
The Capitol building
For that stopped
The feeling better
Another talking about like if you let the hillbillies decide will lose the country that
Operating videos from that day where they're all in the same year
Alright same outfits right
I think that what's going on is that video was making the rounds now it says responding to that
As being what the representative Cheryl was talking about
And I don't know if that's
Fair yeah I think we're in a
The heart
The hard part of the situation
Is that
After the
The 6th
I just
You can't put anything
Beyond Reason
You know like if you told me like one of the representatives
Had a gun pointed to aoc's face
I would be like
That might be true
I can't rule that out any
I understand I understand that but it's
It's critically important to not descend into the the realm of believing stuff
It's too convenient and that you just want to 100% that's that's what I'm
I that's what I'm saying is there unfortunately now you know a lot of that stuff
You could have just been like
Okay I don't have the bandwidth to investigate this
There's no way that the representative
Eldigan directly to her face
And now it's like if sci-fi see that I have to
Hugo invest
Navigate to make sure
Really could be true
Which is terrifying
But
At the same time you can't believe that right you know well it's tough
But I think that's also
It's the burden of
The modern information space and how you can exist in it as a
Responsible
Consumer information
I guess it does suck but
It is it's enough to drive
Anywhere
Between 30 and 45% of the population in St
Using social media
Anyway Nancy Pelosi
Comments about people taking a statue
You down
While back
She said something to the effect
If people are going to do what they're going to do right
And Alex
Besides
Play this clip and then talk about killing
Well people are going to do with people
Pelosi
People
Throwing it into the harbor
And it's it's a
It is I do sing
Safety standpoint
It would be a good idea
Had to taken down if they can reject appointment I don't know that
Ignition
About a Jessica
Community
Seriously
Would that just old people
No lady
That's not at work
You hunchback
Devil worshipping
God
Vengeance is mine saith the Lord
Products you need
Nailed it
Hitman
James Brown with the sting
So Alex has the Lord's like multiple times
Of that is it sometimes you need to be gods of it
Sometimes
That's what Alex is expressing that's not what
You saying that's literally what are you saying
The intent behind it
Expression conveys to the initiated within the Infowars
The information space
It means
Someone stabbed but it is interesting
Like
Sloth
In the legal C
System is that
Because of the way these people speak
You can't you can't just like enter
Oh see Alex said
Venture
Is mine saith the Lord
So that was a
You know you have to be like okay
Listen to 3:00
No but I honestly don't think it would be that difficult
To say like okay
Vengeance is the Lord's
Across areas
It's going to get stabbed in the neck or whatever
Multiple times frequently you've discussed how the idea that vengeance is the Lord's
What is a riddle
Ryan B actually what it's talking about it sometimes humans have two
To step up and be the instrument of God's vengeance
Would you like to have a conversation about that I think you could introduce that in court and it would look pretty bad
I don't know if it's legally ask
He's a real assholes
Assholes
We have another gas now the baby reporter
Junior reporter and I've got Junior I mean baby in an oversized trench coat
In a silly hat
He likes
The storm
There's a lot to be optimistic about because I'm Erica first is ascendant I think all over the world people are beginning to realize that are pulled
Political system here in the United States is absolutely broken
And I know that you're not a big fan of the protest I think some funny things happened Princeton somebody defecated
On Chuck Schumer's.
And that puts a smile on my face I like hearing that I like seeing that headline I think that's
A small Win For Humanity when somebody does that you're not supposed to think that though Patrick
You're supposed to think it's antifa
I kinda
Patrick is like he just
Get the script he doesn't get how we can make this
Profitable
Yeah because
Hughes
Super into it and he's like this is a good thing
When the Vikings Shaman and these people were presiding over Congress there were no Foreign Wars
Okay we weren't getting any of our taxpayer dollars to Pakistan for gender studies
I'm in the populist movement
And people were inspired by this
Yes it seems to have gone disastrously
And I wasn't there
And it didn't seem like there was any plan or any Rhyme or Reason to it and obviously their agitators in the crab
Basic just the act of civil disobedience
Push the message out there
Americans are at odds with their government and that's a powerful message
Notion
Against the tax
I get it
Okay well I'm saying to you is
If we're gonna launch a war it should be done differently and we played right there hands and I don't want violence this weekend
The globalist everywhere
Trying to get violent that's all I'm saying
So basically
Alex the Saint Patrick
If we endorse
This we won't get our good boy
Let me know
Almost like an abstract
People standing up and storming or capitalize like
We're at odds with the government
Whatever other anti-government violence
The ends up happening
Is going to be seeing as something that we're encouraging
I can't make money on that
I will get
I will end up arrested
If we end up
Do being seen as the
I don't know the mouthpiece the media of an Insurgent Network
We can't do that we have to
Play it smoother Patrick
YouTube ereporter
Grow up
You can
But at the same time Alex said we played right into their
Plan you know like
Okay so yes
Instigators
Sure
But that still means that
All of those people
Did it
And wanted to do it you wouldn't have been that trick by the neuro-linguistic programming on the bullhorn
Tired
Chris probably Q
Person that
You know all the stuff that happened
The people who were the ones who were Milling around and taking selfies who are.
They're all good people all things you would be horrified by what those were provocateur
Absolutely stand around and take the
Pictures outside of the Capitol building
Good if you storm at that
We now get to
To the point that I've been waiting for
Sense
The day
But it all went down
Coronavirus
Psychiatrist
State Department psychological warfare
Help.
He's a real spook spoon
This
Is amazing alright this is one of my favorite doctor
Steve pieczenik appearances
This is psychic
Trauma
For Alex
Does not go well
There's a lot of big swings on Steve's part but I was looking
There's also a lot of Steve trying to hold a mirror up to Alex
Really doesn't like the mirror
Before you introduce is Steve he's really got I like
Okay I know that you said that
Election was a sting operation
Can't really
Still believe
He wasn't saying that he was involved
He was trying to be optimistic
There was some water marshmallows
System why does Alexa
What
Turn this around
Sideways on his take on that
So
Let's get his take on that
I am excited I am excited I am looking I have been looking forward to the biggest
Swing
And that's got to come from cbp's right
Nobody else can swing like in Paul soap
Please keep in mind that Alex has been going on the warpath against
Q100
Now it's Steve
Casey At The Bat
Really just sounding like you and I
We are now if
Ashley in the military
Akoo
What is happen in why I was
Because I've had a history of doing
Soft foods in the United States
What we call hard Cruz
Overseas overthrowing regimes using the military
Hey sweetheart
We call a heart
It was initiated
2 months ago
By our side
Command using Spa
People from
Parts of the
Intelligence community
What's the name
But enough we are about
About to arrest
Biden
Hunter Biden net Romney
You know that's cute stuff like these are been going on forever
Steve
He's not one of these guys who just like this stuff is going to happen
Stuff is already happy
Bend and you might be shocked to hear about
We have already arrested in
Basically overseas we have taken up
N54 over 30 years
Interested
Francis
First of his name
Steve arrested the phone this is a thing that's
It's going around in qanon
Qanon conspiracy theory
It's so funny when the pope tries to
To do like
Very slow incremental a good changes and he's like
We got to kill him
We just got to arrest them we got to throw them into prison forever we're going to get it update
Okay hopefully more details
Less believable but
I don't know
Chorizo Alex believes
That on the 6th
Antifa
Antagonize the police who then got to a fight with qanon people who then stormed the capital until
Groupon Schumer's desk with the false flag
Very far or something
Patriots got setup
Supporters tried to fight them off of course they was a noble but
Much like the 300 at Thermopylae
The capital
Steve's got another angle on this
By the way
There was no rioting in the capital
People here for my town he said it was
Very peaceful
The police took down the barrier
What people do Special Forces
Operators in there
Pelosi
Computer
They were just there to take care of
Mr. Q guy he's just a cute guy
So stupid
So now
This is where the mirror
There's a really really fascinating thing that's going on throughout this
Appearance
And I get the feeling that it's Steve revealing
Himself to Alex as a like
A supervillain
He's like
Alex
I've been using you to get these extremist talking points out and try and start a coup
Don't you understand the vehicle
You're the useful idiot you idiot Alex can't really hear it
Like that
Through which we were able to implement
Cool
It wasn't me
I know what I was doing
Predictive
True
And by the way you didn't
Actual interview
The necessary actions that have to be at
That is very
Put me in this
Ask
I love it I love it
Alex do you know what sometimes I was lying to you because it's
Part of the
F****** app
Yeah you idiot I was trying to start a military coup in this country and and
Did it buddy
Mission accomplished
Of course and it seems like he's speaking real freely
I haven't seen this since he declared himself in open prison
2013 or whatever that was
With the jobs
Security of just being an a****** for Alex
Add
The complete lack of
Actually doing anything I think he's also where you can do whatever you want
And I think that he's like
I think he's a little high
Yeah that sounds right
Do use Alex
But he also has an explanation for why he couldn't
Use other me
He is version of it might involve
Some of them are Jewish
Why would I
Expected
The reason we never use the New York Times we didn't do the washing it
Total control
I knew about the Murdoch family
I never trust
I didn't trust
Family
People didn't know I'm
Fortunately is
Murdoch's mothers and orthodox
And he is at
Totally corrupt individual
Family who brought in
Stations and eventually
Another song
So you were chosen as the
The message through which we could initiate
A military coup
Wild
Goddamn
Alex understandably
Scratch and sniff and you'll find an anti so
Steve's revealed that himself many times
You could imagine
Because Steve is saying a lot of stuff
Very much contradict
Everything he's been saying since the sick
Save we've been doing this for 20 years
How is it that I
Still don't do pretty interviews with you what the fuc why am I like this
So you were chosen as the method
Through which we could initiate
A military coup
Okay well we didn't talk about this beforehand we don't want
I went
A peaceful demonstration to show our numbers to expose election fraud look bad I don't know I don't know about all that
That s*** is about
F****** lunatic you did not tell me this earlier I have no idea what the f*** you're talking about I just wanted to have a bar
Alex started this interview by saying that like Steve said that there was a watermark ballot sting
Time it was a prediction
Right Steve
Nothing much. Still
We Mark the computers
Weimar
Everything that was done was a sting operation nothing is changed
And what was
Dante was done by
Trump
Businessman who understood
The degree of Coronavirus
Among the
Democrats
This isn't just something about
About the world
Control of America
Yes was the
I should stay
Coming in
An ocean of the coronavirus which was not lethal
Fauci another Catholic who was trained by Cher.
What's going on here
Looks like Trump
Got Steve also appears to be quite anti-catholic
It's so funny
Every time that they're like the
The Christian right I'm like man
If we were gone they would be murdering each other in the streets
It's not even anything unique about Christian
Extremism or anything it's a child
Any kind of
Exclusive
Group
Group it defines Itself by exclusion
I will eventually find new ways to exclude people
The DNA of that kind of system
Even the f***
And Alistair magicians murdered each other so
You'll end up like an all white ethnostate will eventually alienate people have different hair
Call this work
Continue to drive profit
So Alex is like a man look we have a week left
Until the f****** inauguration
How's this going to work tell me on this one
Quantify this for me
How is it a successful military coup
Buddy said I guess
Biden gets in in 7 days
Trump's going to get into a lot of time here
I got 150 hours what what do you say is about to happen
I'm about
Biden's not going to be the president of the United
It's going to be saying is that
Massive arrest and what I'm saying into
Baxter's
That we on martial law and we have
A military coup
Qanon real baby
Talk about it that's
Set up a not answer
But such a mirror
Just Alex finally just being like
Oh
God you sound
Crazy
This is where I was like Alex has got to be realizing this dude is
Like out of
It was my idea
There is no globalism
Going to be involved we have
Shutdown
Pakistan
Shut down part of England
Listen for a minute
Did well over a year ago
The reason why he was arrested
Because I'm your show I said this
Corrupt and have been involved
With terrorist organizations 20 or 30 years ago I was
Who's the guy we see traveled around the world in last year
Don't see anybody traveling around the world right now you don't see anybody
What what the f***
Got arrested a year ago but I only
Man
That is because this is exactly that moment that so many people have had you had with Alex is eventually
It's like okay
This guy is literally saying to my face everything I've ever believed is a lie
Or controlled by him
So
I can either believe this
And then I'm gone
Or I have to stop for a second ago like
Ono Ono
Two of them get into a little bit of a
The fight sure whether or not Trump
Is going to stay present
If you listen carefully at the end of this clip you can hear Steve's wife laughing in the background
In 7 days pieczenik
Tell us what's going to who's going to be the president what's about to happen
7 Days let me Jones
It's going to be
It will not be biting
People will be arrested
There will be people who will be arrested
That's what's going to happen
And if I'm wrong
Find don't put me on your show if I'm right
What else you got
You can eat
Quite a bit background throughout this interview
I having a ball
Yeah
So I think
When Steve doesn't
Like
The fact that Alex is trying to pretend that this
Incident
On January 6th
Was some kind of a false flag
You have to blame the left now just own it man
Why why even pretend anymore
I love it
Provocateur
Craziness
But you saw that you guys going
Quiet down a bit
You do not understand what that means
You do not understand how
How long we've been preparing for this
Yeah they're you scolding Isla
Four stars go home and tell your mother you're brilliant
This is a little different though this is almost just like
Mask off time by X
Alex let's do this
We hate democracy
Where is time
Little insult
Mike David is cuz I love this clip
The one thing that they can come to an agreement on
What is the third martial law that's going on right now
Alex
So why are there black helicopters in Austin
And Steve's response to it is like
Call
Perfect
The one thing we are under martial law
That's correct.
Repeatedly you're under martial law everywhere
The state of California over downtown Austin this morning
You're sitting down in Austin
Studio on you trying to sell vitamins
We don't send
Blackhawk helicopter
Why do I see Black Hawk helicopters
Series that begins balls into Alex's eyes
They even answer
Hilarious
Pill
Vitamin zero f****** drug dealer Alex that's what
You are
Alex is not
He's not having a good time with this interview
He thinks that he
He's capable of having the center
Interview and I would say he's wrong
Supposed to have one view on here or one idea
This is all influx we are under martial law
I just think that if you're going to have interviews with people like I say should be a little bit more
Well done
You shouldn't be caught off-guard by him telling you that you have been a 30-year instrument of his
Desire to start a military coup 20 years no free interviews 20 years
20 years I've been doing this this happens
I want every four months
I think that it's like really
I don't think that you know you should have blankets
No
Absolutely no talking to Steve or whatever
Pressure
Who's YouTube
You should prepare
Yeah I can't imagine
Thinking
That
Steve is in park
You know
Like Steve is a loose cannon
At the best of times
I could can expect
For the first time
He burned Alex Slaton 2004
Hurricane Irma
So they make it back
Okay
Alex
If I'm wrong I will never appear on your show again
Every time one of your
Special
Super all
You want that Sarah Wright
That's correct
Alright sweetie
Okay
Add
This is weird to me because this implies that
Steve wants to work at Infowars yes
Why hasn't he been
They just don't have the time
Wild bet
Maybe this is exit strategy Carino's
He's going to be wrong
That business is his retirement last episode
Yeah he is revealing at all the magician cards
Say bye me alright
You are anointed because
This is going to be
The major vehicle
Where we going to go in the next
20 or 30 years
This process you have to remember what is the school about
This is a 22 paid back
Chaney's
Correction cowardness for the
Afghanistan
To Obama who set up the war including
We lost five thousand
Alex do you understand that I have been using you to try and build up a terrorist insurrection
Is payback against my political enemies
Just say that
You should do should know he's going to say something like this beforehand if you're the host of the show that stuff to roll with
Commercial break
Steve somebody who has too much respect
In your universe
For you to just be like oh f*** yourself with anything other than
So you are saying that you have been
Controlling me
You been running a Scion running even
Everything that I've been saying from you
In purpose
One-goal
Not necessarily the truth for 20 years
You have
Harbored this Grudge
I think
Steve
But
He's also
Apparently a failed individual in the world
Show Business
You know your heroics a couple of books with Tom Clancy sure
A ways back
I doubt it was one of his books
Apparently going to be turned into a TV show
But then
Something in Hollywood
Didn't go well
Example just recently
State of emergency was
By one of the major
Presidents of CW Network
Person whom I've known for years and Hollywood said I want to help you out
What happened when he found out I was involved
What happened to all of Hollywood amount American
Jews
Daring confidence
Ignorant
Wow an old white man who failed in Hollywood blaming the Jews that is so rich
Original
Pretty hilarious that you like alright I had this screenplay
CW loved it but then he found out I was involved in a coup
All of these f****** guys
Have a goddamn screenplay
Ybk what are you going to be
Be disgusted by that I thought you'd be impressed Sancho's
Squares how many accuse have you been involved with her
Realizes
Salary
Okay so I took dr. Steve pieczenik vet that if Trump is president
On January 21st 2021
The Daily Show
He's not that bad
But he's elusive
To just go away he has to come back on Michelle doctor humiliated
I'm wrong about that
Humiliate
To humiliate me I would say that
There's no way that doctor
Steve comes back on
For a while
To to be humiliated
Because
Alex is going to want to do a whole
Oh I just sell f****** vitamins
Do I what I do and you won't see him for awhile
But also I don't think it would work in Alex's interests to humiliate him either because
Do you know they'll be a little splash back on the infowar sure why do you even
Talk to this guy why anything he says seriously
F****** liar but Alex is also Petty to the point of throwing his entire life
Yeah it's
Competing forces
This gave me chills
Alex is talking about but he's trying to ask Steve a question is like Steve you're a nice guy
Steve Esther remind him
Am I
I just
We're going to find out the seven days in seven days are coming back on
Absolutely but remember one thing about me
How is a very nice guy able to
Steak-Out
Khmer Rouge without any weapons
Able to
Take out the Soviet Union without any weapons
Able to take a riddle
Noreaga was out anyway
This nice guy
Do you understand
Hey I'm a nice guy
I'm going to answer that riddle. I'm going to go with
He doesn't
Nobody but you
What the messages that is
Nice guy but I'm a sociopath
I was going to go with the message was more I didn't actually do any
Any of those things
Someone like Steve
Would be able to manipulate him that's true
I mean if you can get him to believe that he's done all these
The things geopolitical e
Like yeah
I've been many malevolent Lee f****** with you
The wave
You think I would have if I took down the soup
Exactly
I'm not a nice guy
Now
I'm an ass-whole
Yeah I just told you that you sold vitamin
Dickwad
So Alex wants to know how bad it's not going to be
Specific
I would like
Welearn
Instead
So you can't tell us how this magic going to happen to Joe Biden going to step down
I just said it to you
Separating Alex
I sent you there will be a rest
The Vines
Pelosi
It's going on now
He will not come
To the presidency
I'll be right can we meet your cat
Please
Cute cats and 3.
So because Steve is basically just
Disseminating q-ship on his show
So what's
What's mrs.
It's pathetic feeling like
Like I don't know man would like to
To know what her day today is like I don't know
There's a little bit of curiosity but also I don't care
And I like personalized
Totally I just see them
I just see them both like on the back porch
Laughing about other f****** with Alex
CIA Tom Clancy novel over there just burden floam
And then they both stopped
For one second and Steve just looked up and you just go
Oh my God you have no idea what I'm going to tell Alex
Tomorrow
To be holy
I'm going to tell him we arrested the pope a year ago tell Alex
And she loses her s***
Steve is a doctor
He has a doctorate
He thinks that that means
Either I'm a genius or I just see
Ordinary problems
You're wrong
And what is a doctor really do
He saves lives tenniel
Very carefully
Nice guy
It's what he may or may not be
Low low
Steven Singer because he's a doctor he has me right
To give and take live some people tell you about this
Would you become a
My doctor Dan and the wrong
Sometimes
Things you kill
Pleasure
Or games
Those are the reasons you become a doctor doctors
Get the right
So
Steve
But there will be arrests
For the anaki race
So we got a real clock on that one
Closing, we're going to see some fireworks
Are you not going to see
Fireworks you going to see a lot of arrest
It's going to be quiet you going to see martial law
Clampdown the cities you already seeing Washington
Clampdown
Down in Berlin we clampdown in Pakistan
Clampdown in Italy
And now you will also make another prediction
The Italian government
24-hours
Other than
I've had a wonderful
And I hope to see you again
Go fuc yourself
Italy
Gone tomorrow all day and also
Bucky
I've had a very
Explaining to you that I've been f******
With you for decades
Oh that's
The good interview
It is pretty good I would feel pretty confident if I was Stevie peas at the end of that one and I think Alex is so taking a
Back at all you can do is really like
The spider
Mansion question what is your cats
TV
Timer
Geronimo
What's the temperature
Nona
Meaning no name
Cheap about 4
Well you could nominate known it would be the first female president
You know why
I love you
No I want a really had a real president
For the first time
50 years
The Obamas the bidens
None of them were real presidents
What kind of trying to take back power in the Dynamics
Your cat in it sort of mocking
The resume that Alex has given
Steve
It's ineffective
It's not already empowered
Steve way too much
Steve doesn't give a s*** no try and make fun of Italy was going to be gone to
Tomorrow fire-rescue yuriko
Victor Pope
Has been gone for a year I told you that even though yet you have seen the pope around
You haven't seen any
And this just leaves Alex in a bind
Is it wishful thinking
Hoping
He's so pathetic yeah that's sad
He can't even operate as a sincere person because
To attack Steve
Raises too many questions about his own credibility off and all of the conspiracies that he's based on Steve over the years
So he's stalking alert
Where you at
To be LOL I hope he's right
It could happen if
Steve is what you pay
Pretend he is
There's no helping
Yeah I'm not saying these things like all baby that's nothing
He did it and he's doing
Exactly
End
You're still being used
The fact that you
How could you
I just don't understand how you could let somebody say
I have been using you for 20 years
To your face and not be like then go f*** yourself
Anyways this is kind of like the Nigerian email scam
I think we just
Hit the button in the show is over
After this Alex has an interview with Laura Loomer but I don't really care she's just complaining about how she had a tough time at the
And I don't care
It's
Azure out especially after that
Epic interview with
I can't wait I can't wait to
To see what happens
Bike
Not I don't think that
You know trumps
Sting operation is real
Yeah I think I think the inauguration will happen
And I just want to see how they deal with it
I'm going to guess
Denial
I'm going to guess that they pretend this didn't have
This interview didn't happen if people disappear for a month or two and then he'll come back
With a new narrative
Some sort
Much like a pro wrestler whose character has grown weary repackaged
New character and show back up in Hemlock
I just don't understand see nothing that
Confuses me maybe more than anything else now
Is
Seeing the events of the sick
And how
Trump has
Decided
Tupac
Why would you want to install him as your
Dictator
Lego
What do what you want to f***
I think
Yeah I think that's
Steve thinks it's all like The Art of War
Sun Tzu kind of stuff
And so like
Pretty popular in the Q community
Look weak when you're around getting ready
Expressing a little bit of that
Add stop on the episode until like
Trump's doing this stuff cuz that's what he's got to do to give the
Appearances
You can rationalize that way but that's only going to work for so long
Yeah I mean especially considering the sheer number of times we have seen him pout
When he doesn't get his way
Is a whiny little titty babe
So we will be back
Jordan but until then we have a website
Yep we're also
We are Integra Technologies are fighting that go to bed Jordan
Please find a local charity or bail Fund in your area to help out
People doing
Right now. Will be back until then I'm Neo and Leon dzx clerk I'm Daryl run this IRS
Did the Pope a year ago
Alex
First in color with huge fan I love your work