Goddamn important
I have great respect but knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Jordan
Quick question for you sir
My bright spot today is I'm talking into a new microphone
Forgot I still have microphone
But they're new
I noticed some popping popping and crackling and a couple of our recent episode
Together these new cords and
Amanda's new
This new windscreen feels good
On my face
It's much smoother it doesn't have years of
Other people's faces on it
Yeah
Recover covid-19
Four years were the only one who touched
Say yes it's nice though it's
I try bought a desk
Mic stand as well but it does not attach to the
I still have some work to do on messing up my weekend warrior type
Yeah
For today I love it
How about you
Weekend warrior type project then I have
For probably like
13 years
Lived in
Apartment buildings with
People around me and so when I left
For apartment living I also left my drumset
I miss it you're you're at your guy looks throw some stick around you played drums for since I was like eight
Years old and then I had to stop at like 19 for the aforementioned reasons
And
It is been difficult and
Finally I realized that you can get an electric drum kit for like
So I got one wow
Well how about that it's it's very cheap
Garbage I'm going to break into
It's going to be like when I played rock band
Destroyed those hats
But it is so good to get back to jump
I don't know how it's still going to be too loud for your partner
The last time that I tried
Having a conversation while she was at work
Our rooms share a wall
With loud and I have a tendency to toss language about
Ingest not not fit for the classroom high school students
Heard me speak
So I bought some
Soundproofing shitzo my entire room is going to be turned into a
EStudio potentially good luck with that kind of tough unless you can get inside the walls I'm working on it
Well that's fine I hope you have Some Nights Fun. Dave Grohl ask
Drummond adventures in Providence who hasn't played along to Queens of the Stone Age songs for the Dead
May I have on that rock band
But see what I'm saying you're a drummer and you played along with late Everlong on TalkBack
Fairly
Not on Expert
You don't know your 16th notes bro no I don't very fast
My foot
Get tired
90's rock bands
The sticks do the work that's what a lot of people don't know about drums
You think you got to hit up
With your arm
You just move your wrist and say that it's like a cryptic mystery
I don't know
I loved rock band
And I spent
Hours
Trying to a one-hundred-percent Helter Skelter
An expert okay
I don't think I ever saw
Succeeded by tried it
Hundreds and hundreds of times
Because you getting the cheese method Beatles Rock Band if you want a hundred percent I don't expert
Couldn't get it
Couldn't get a couldn't do it huh
Ringo gacha
Classic drummer
Throws people
I'm sorry I was a lot of the other songs are pretty easy to put powder stelter is a little complex
Also not very good at rhythm-based
Stuff that's that's why I'm sorry if I
That's alright I'm sorry
Okay so Jordan today we got some interesting thing on our on our plate
It's in front of us and we don't really have an episode
That is futuristic
What happened
Was that
I did not want to do another episode for today about Alex
I wanted to push that to Wednesday because I needed personally break from
Yeah I was tired of this b*******
Last week was emotionally exhausted
On
The preparation for Friday's episode of the on the 8th
Yep straight through to present
Non-stop lot it is been a lot of stuff that I
I grow weary
At the same time the payoff of the interview with Steve pieczenik
On the last episode was almost
Who was season-ending
F****** season finale we got
Cbpu given us the f****** cliffhanger
I decided to admit you as the
You go by which I would set up a military coup
Master
About that there was so satisfying
And narratively interesting to me that I found myself
Having a really tough time going back
Italics
I know it'll be temporary I'll be able to get back on the horse
I sat down to try and listen to other episode
I can't do this
Yeah
To do
Naturally in times like this in the past but we've done is we've gone to various other
I online
We could I am so yeah I checked on Kerry Cassidy over a Project Camelot
The storming of the capital for 100 yeah 100% million percent
I got really bored listening to good aliens weren't him
Q and get back into
Space lady wasn't worth getting too deep into
There's apparently an archon alien
A singular one that runs the CIA
I did not know that
Okay that used to be this guy archon right but it's okay
Gary has some intelligence
He might have died
Gmail archive
Unclear
Proof that he's dead and not a shapeshifter
Can't do it
Ya can't do it
Carrie bring it to me
Jim Baker's disappointed
And I still
Still don't like talking about Jim Bakker I don't know why I just don't
Still make me a little bit uncomfortable
I figured I'm not going to be able to go back to that well at 4
I just I don't want isn't going to say God does s*** talk about
Greatest big ass bucket oatmeal is you and I have both read the Bible and eating survival food we can just move on
Yeah so then of course
That was kind of like in a bind as I don't know what I'm going to do got to get something
Together
And then I remembered
So when I was looking at pictures of the capital on the sea
Yeah
I saw somebody wearing a pass the salt shirt
Which of course is the name of Dave daubenmire Coach Dave the name of his radio Ministry
Is that YouTube Broadcasting
I saw that I was like woah
There's Dave daubenmire shirts
At the protest
The people storming there at the Capitol
What was he there
That would be
Who else is wearing a Dave David Mayer shirt
Dave had to have been there right
I am so I went and I check sure
Dave daubenmire was at the Capitol
Not possibly have been there really
James obermeyer decided to go storm the capitol
Football team manager
Win
So today I wanted to take a little bit of a look
Get that but it's not really much of an episode I would learn a lot of time watching
These dreams
For what will ultimately be kind of
I don't know a little bit deflating
Look. If you would like our show tune back in on Wednesday we will have a full episode
Expecting that
Battlestar Galactica
Busy bottle episode we couldn't afford to really do much here if you want to see some spaceship come back neck
So
What are things I have is really funny
Is
Dave is coach
Is a recording
And during the live stream from the Metro
So it's a little bit iffy
Does not great connection is
I don't happen what are the things that he does
Maybe unfortunate in hindsight is he literally doxs every single person
Who's all night train with him
But if any of them went in the capital
His broadcast could be identifying information
It will
8 look
It's obvious
This was always going to be the key
That this would happen
But the fact that the people most afraid of Bill Gates tracking them all the time
Have ducts themselves Soca
Completely
It's just
It's never not going to be obvious going around like
Totally
To do this
Man I love it
Dave gets to
It's the talking about how many people they're going to be there
The only people who are uninterested in doxing each other are antifa
They're the only people who like
Hey
If you're going to video people don't put their face in it or say their real names everybody else is like
Here's my social security number
Are you from Nigeria
So you get to talkin about how there's got to be so many people there and this is
This is big this is not just a proton
Formula
Possibly
I'll be here downtown
Powerful message
No I don't think so coach
It's far beyond that
Once again Donald Trump is not going to call him
Called for this rally
He has a plan
9:00 this morning I believe he is going to
You talk
He's not it's not a pep rally
I do not believe this is game on member we talked about
You know we always have 11 men on offense an 11-minute Nissan Summit Reno
This is like this is like that
The coach turning to the
The stadium
And saying
Get on the field
Now's the Time
I think I might be feeling
Inspired to write a book
Xzibit I feel like there's a great book to be written about
Like all of the right-wing Media stuff
Prior to the
The capital storming
This looks bad in hindsight totally totally
Ultimately the thing is really interesting about it is it's not really that different than the way they talk normally
Hubris enough detail
So there's a guy on the bus there and that Dave goes around he ejects in on
The temperature of the people in
In the crowd hey why you doing hey how you doing
It's now or never
Either now or never
Enjoy the
Blessings
America
And I I just don't want to see
Basically
The communist
That's what we're looking at
Yeah, he's becoming it's now or never got to stand up and fight these commies
Or else you're going to have a capitalist country to live in and have a great time with
I like
I like the reload
Of these guys
Because I recognize how they
And that is exactly like comedy producers
Who have never put on a good show
I think we're going to have about four million people
That is very awesome
I'm telling you I've heard I got so many Facebook messages
Committed to showing up
You should have been here last week well actually it was going to be 4 million but it rained
No one could make it in
Oh no
It's Sunday there's always a good thing
You're so is weekly
Got to know there's football
Football bed
They are a little bit so there's a little bit of Pride or a little bit of expectation
And excitement it's definitely palpable until like they feel like they're getting ready to go
Do something more than
Enchantix or more here for sure
Yeah the electricity
Was clearly in the air
An interesting Lee I mean I think that
The people who are there have a lot more to say than just
Who stole the election
There's certainly some ideas that are big
Graphics on this bus
That are interesting
Trade-ideas great
Highfalutin ideas
Actually what you're doing is you're moving from
The admiralty
See
The land
Soil
It's very simple you just
Remove yourself
You go through the process
The paperwork
Remove your
Yourself as a US citizen
And become a citizen
The state you were born in
Sure enjoyed the Assembly of
State in your state
That sounds great
State Nash
National or state
Citizen of course
There is rumors
Trump is a
Estate Nashville
And what
Have to do we talk about
Seceding
We don't need this
Sasidhar States
Feed ourselves
One at a time
And move over to the land Jersey
And what we're doing right now is
Text to Janna
Gun rights
She's done all the paperwork so that
Now right now or
Repopulating
The original Constitution
So I think Anna's on rights if I recall correctly somebody that I've heard Kerry Cassidy bring up quite a bit
And the screen in the room can't tell those are big old letters
Kick-off left when we got there just basically said
Alright
That
The president
They love most
Is not an American citizen yeah that is a problem with his theory
Because Sovereign citizens are
Higher up on the ladder, at me with Obama wasn't born here and then you're going to tell me that you're
Your president isn't even American
SuperAmerica
Constitution of 1860
That's all just qanon Sovereign citizen
It's a bummer
It's a real bummer it's amazing to me
How important paperwork is
To these people
And how unimportant Rida
Yeah yeah it's
It's fun to because you know you got Dave here Coach Dave on the bus and he's having this guy explain how you become a
You got to take your way from the admiralty not like I don't know about that man
I can't wait to have you on the show again
So it's okay but look this guy knows what he's talking about
I think it was a loss
Do our whole movement is I believe
Who's going to be about
Teaching people how to get out of the
The admiralty
In the Vatican
Xavier
La comes from LA
Land Air Water that's where the word Wok
I'm sprung
The three jurisdiction
The pop figures
The South 13th
Thunder that the only way
The only way to get out of
You going land
Soil and get back
1780 South
Sure
Land Air Water that's what lawmakers are we doing this are we doing this dance
We're not
The pat.
The Vatican
It's the law of the air
Right
And then I think
The British Empire is the land of the law of the sea
Admiralty law
Just everybody
The land the land is related is just the constitution of India
Yeah but not the United States
Individual states
Because we're also
The articles is this apply to people in other countries
There are so they don't have any choice
Figure this out and 1300
Figured what out that law means land air and water
In what language
It looks like an Enderman
Alright
Fire water
Long ago
My father
J.k. Simmons
Element
Equal jurisdiction
Savitar not the not the Cameron bulshit I'm talking I love
Decameron watch
Air powers
I watch the James Cameron movie
Cuz I was
Brought along to it by friend
But I go see it cuz I like fire
I also saw Avatar cuz it was too big to not see
You're not one of those things that I get you got it
Adult there was there was a time when that came out I was OVA
Haters I guess you gotta see this
People are going to be talking about it
And I don't care about that now
I think I did see the last Skywalker
You did
I think I did
Tell me when
What did you get it on DVD Dan
No I think I did see it though
We'll deal with his later
Anyway there's three jurisdiction
We're all under a log
I would like he was Adrian law
Before we go any further
In any conversation with this guy
I want to know a
Exactly the laws of a
I need to know what airline is that the pope has
Control
Yeah if I were to go any further in this conversation with this guy which I wouldn't
Here's here's how it go
What's over there
That move like pretending that he saw something somewhere else and just would walk off
I really admire the hell out of his ability to get away from to
Like party conversations
Four people and the three of them start having a conversation and you're like
I want to jump in but it's just not going to happen
You look over you like all my God and then you just walk away you saw a friend
Keep pulling that off
Like perfectly is that you have to end up somewhere that
It's not indirect I shot of the people you just like around over there
Anyway
Call Davis heard there's a lot to be worried about
There's a lot of
Breck's
Short on the ground there's like a
Antifa
He's not worried about any that s***
I'm not worried
Pepper spray
World War going to war
Spiritual war
What is the physical War
Brake shops
Causa
Boiling
Here
Here's a true work of authority
The mayor of DC has no military Authority not over the National Guard or anything all she has
Is DC police
Grosse Tete
They will step
There's too many of them
So it doesn't look good in hindsight
The conversation certainly seemed to be
What would you call that what's the what's the right word I'm looking for
Is that a way to go it's it's very much like you know like
If you accept the encrypted
If you accept the idea that like
Do they kind of planning on so I can store a little nap at all
Text here before that
They look
We don't want any trouble but if there's trouble there's four million of us cops are on our side
If it's
The capital was the con
Constitution leaves assholes are the preamble
The Preamble was probably
One of the words I was trying to look for and ice
Couldn't figure out a way to make it work
Grammatically
Capitol Police
Troy
And there's not enough of a man
There's just not enough
There's not enough.
Haydel how many
Policeman would you say there are
In
I'm just
Thousand
Jefferson Parish Jefferson Parish we have
We have 50
Officers
That not just officer
Does people who work in the dab
Detectives and everything and that's for a population of a half a million people
Do they have enough
What if
Enough
Decided they're going
I don't know
What was that
What my break
Advocate
Truth of the matter is
Violence all around us
The days of John the Baptist
Don't know
Keno.
Mile-a-minute
Taking a bus for
They're forcing us
Six Flags
Therefore
Travel
The nursing
Masterforce your nephew understand this
Good beats
Same argumentation styles
But we don't want trouble
All violence
Could be seen as offensive as secretly defense
They want to give me a vaccine
It's not great to hear this from someone who's
That presumably a religious leader
I would argue that
Spreading a disease is violence
Stand
Offensive violin
That's an interesting argument that you can make with that
B
And it seems like they are doing Maybe
Yeah you'd want to probably have some
Qualification for like negligence
Sure
Something
Unless you're spitting on people
And then there's that
You're out of line I don't know if you're aware that wearing a mask
Can save somebody else's life
And you're like
You have now committed violent yes but how do you prove the person actually believe libertarian nonsense
Since November
But you would have to prove that the person
Either wear
That
Do masks help
They believe that
And are choosing to not do it
Cuz
The denial could be
Strong and sure
Sure
I don't know if I
Care about denial Minot
Court might though
My but it's
Kind of like a math problem
Like I don't
Care if you think
That math doesn't work
It still does
So you have to
Live by Matt
Steve spends more time on this bus there was a
I think it's bad
And then it goes to the guy in the studio
Studio Amy MS Office
Sure and he's another preacher and he just has some people pray
And stuff and I don't care
Later they arrived
The capital
There's at least
One picture I saw that was of
Pass the salt cellar
They were they were around all right
Angela heads
I'm calling somebody or is it past the salt
Yeah and Dave comes on his show and there's a little bit of reflection
Can going on
We are over the target
Alex Jones said about 25 years ago
Is a nympho War
It's an information War
Boys and girls we are
Dead center
Target
Information
You know I'm just a fly
On the butt of us
I understand that
I'm going to tell you something
We are over
The target
Like we never we never been
So he's just using Alex language
Directly referencing a f****** info Warrior
Man I don't want to be killed by a bunch of cowards like this
I don't lie don't like the idea that this
Extremist
Political communist
Ideology is being so successfully marketed
Under the veil of
Yeah like I really really think
Think that's terrifying I would I I would rather
Be killed in a fight with ISIS
Cuz Isis is at least like I want to kill you
You know
None of this
Wishy washy cowardice from the conservatives just like
I don't want any violence but I'm going to have to kill you guys
And then violent says happen
Wowowo guys we didn't ever want
At least Isis is like I'm going to kill you
Is there is there is a
Terrorist group
Generally do take responsibility for their actions
Stingley
Dave has a very similar take on things after the fact that his hero Alex Jones
Strange part of the information where that's going on and here's your going to be your greatest battle and my greatest battle
Is you're going to have to
Convince
The people that you come in contact
That what happened
Yesterday
In Washington d.c. wasn't this
This was what happened
Storming at storming of the
The Capitol building
The infiltration of antifa BLM
As part of that infiltration
Yes Peyton
Did breakthrough they did break through
And get into the cap
Got a something
Are you listening to me
They lettuce
Listen to me
They let us break
True
They left
But they left
The Patriots blind breakthrough
And then embedded
BLM
In
The group
And all the wicked
Crazy stuff that happened inside that Capitol building
That was not done by Page
That was not.
I love the idea that he's saying
On the 7th
Hey
It's suspicious that the cops let them through when the boarding up
The cops are going to let us through
It's it's it's very strange
It implies like a real change of like
Perspective Alec Aldis actually happen dogshit
Yeah
I just see that so universally would ask these folks that you look at online
I did not expire
We got to find a way to not take responsibility for whoever s*** on that desk
If anybody
Comes at me
With
Listen
To any conservative
I in the media now
No
What do you mean
Protect
Don't even
Like I've can't engaged
This was the moment where it's like
No matter what you do
You caused this and then you disappear out it so go f*** yourself
Alfira coward complete coward
It's you're worse than Isis
A ride for you and comparing things Isis
People is Isis wow
I think that what are things that I found what I was looking at this was
First of all I feel like Dave daubenmire incredibly boring
I don't know maybe it's been a long time since I've looked at any of his actual shows or anyting it just struck me as like you
We're just taking notes from Infowars shows
And preaching
With it
It's a stupid
It's almost like
The idea of covering his show actually feels kind of like drink
Backwash
Yeah you know like
I'm not interested
Yeah but
He was there
This is
An interesting set of
Circumstances an interesting set of behaviors
Be like
Hey Trump is telling us all
To get on the field
You know like
The 12th
I mean 23 Jersey
Something that's just
Good clean fun
That's fantastic that's fantastic literally talking about the possibility of Stormy the capital and have the police will
And then the next day there's a
Conspiracy afoot trying to set us up
Police let us know when they let us in the embedded and matter in there
Doing this
It's really dumb
Bunch of f******
Cowards it's very dumb
And
So was this quality of
I think I said that before
It's just that whole thing of just like really this is who we're up against
Come on man
It is shittiest fascism I've ever see
Yeah I bet all of them have been disappointing
In the in the moment
Yeah
I bet overtime
They take on more of like
Serious character
Stand back and watch
Serious
Documentary about Mussolini they be like
F****** idiot
Yeah probably
Anyway Jordan
Full episode for today episode Battlestar Galactica is over
Breaking Bad episode with the fly as a coach
The fly is just Dave daubenmire Whispering glad a man that's going to happen
Alright well we'll be back on Wednesday with a full episode
Upside.com
We are trying to please find a local charity or bail Fund in your area to help out people doing God's work
Work yeah I will be back until then Emilio and Leo and bcx clerk I'm Daryl rundus
Alexandra Thurston color