Damn important
I have great respect for its knowledge B
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Nike.com
Novelty beverages a little bit about Alex Jones
My birthday today Jordan
Signed us up for the hot sauce of the Month Club
Muff Club
Okay I don't know what it stands for mother
Or f*** your mouth
Well I mean it's
You're putting understand your field
I understand something about your mouth
It's very
Challenger
The sauce
I had some on some chicken nuggets last night would you say it's a real motherfuker
Yeah okay yeah they definitely
This is the nuggets in the sauce
For a good couple hours afterwards
I was sort of like what
Sweating from the face a good bit of a ride I really enjoyed it although
Stomach stomach is all those noises that you mated are do not
Denota joyful ride
Not generally not but I enjoyed it
It was good it was good the first month was
I really it was good it was hot but it wasn't like
It wasn't
A trial
Golf guy had nothing to do with
Really surprised
Good good stuff I'm ready for month
3 already
I finally got my equipment worked out
I finally got it all set up
And I did a little bit of streaming
Video games. Congratulations
Play The Final Fantasy 7 remake
Planet decided to risk the whole game
Yeah I like mst3k but for Final Fantasy 7 that sounds fun I also plan
Attention to playing and trying to talk
At the same time
I think it's I think it's an acquired
It's guilty do you get better at it isn't as you go along
Forward to joining you at some point while you do these video game stream
So did you ever make fun of your
Terrible play can't wait
Look at you using that material realized
Just randomly saying I'm going to start at 2 Central
But it's like I finally got everything worked out so that it would work well with like
Delayed
I'm releasing my book I don't give a s***
Ya-ya-ya schedule eventually
I'm sure some people came in and enjoyed the time so we can get some water
Get to hang out better thing to do for a live stream
If anyone and our audiences interested in it than us live streaming episodes my frankly might be better
Cuz you can be distracted while you're playing a video game but you are more frustrating when I'm distract
Good trying to host the podcast Fair
That is definitely fair
Can't tell can't quite keep up with
I know that's got to be interested I don't know if I completely figured out how to
Set it up so we can all be on there together without the latch
Screwing everything up
But
I think I can always just come over to your house to
You can just come over to my house that's true
That's fair
Jordan today are we going to go over we're back to talking about Alex Jones
Monday's little saltbreak as I've decided to call it
Answer what we're doing today we're going over January 14th to 17th
Which is Thursday Friday Saturday and Sunday of last week in the year 2021
Blackjack baby
I want to add a baby to it I like
I don't know if you like it's 4 so we'll see we'll see
So what my plan is is to go over this. Of time
I meant for Friday's episode we will witness the end
Of Trumps
Lindsay on Alex Jones
Is yoboy
So that will be
You know I mean just
Momentous taibah Sound of Silence
Man loses his mind
Interesting
Stretch
I hear there's some really
Weary troubling stuff
The really stupid
Stop
Alex realizing the
Botanica's
I've been talking with him for 20
Years finally
Thank God
I am looking forward to the moment that I get a Moment of clarity on Saturday
Give it to me so we'll get that business on all this
The first Jordan to take Mom and say thank-you to the folks who signed up and are supporting a show
Rory loves ololo thank you so much you are now if I was you want
How much are LOL
Is Louis by Lolo Lolo
Girl dropped
Very much
Milo Peterson Intel extraordinary
I'm a policy wonk MPI
Next
The Hills Have Eyes
Why is everybody doing the decorative they requested that
Ominously so I did my best ominous reading yet
Morrissey's finger thank you so much right now about what you want
I'm a very much morrissey's finger next Talon from Minneapolis
Look up people donated on elevated level appreciate that
Mbb from Minnesota thank you so much
Ghost Panda of cool Creek thank you so much you are now a technocrat
Heroin
Is freakishly large
Minnesota
Two ghosts Panda about Coal Creek
Thank you very much to the both of you
The Cold Creek in Minnesota I don't know but it is Minneapolis Minnesota
All the connects that are slightly lower
Going to call them sure
All I can only reference I've got if I guess
Prince Pandora
Okay that's all I got musical references
Think I've been
To Minneapolis
You think you have
I have
There are so many cities in the US that I think I've been too but I'm not positive
I got kicked out of a Billionaire's house in really
Who sell hearing aids in the like okay and one of the owners of the biggest hearing aid cartel in the world is
Stationed out of
Minneapple was a prince
No.
It's a guy named Rogers Nelson
The company's name is Starkey
And I we got invited there cuz my cousin has his whole thing and we got invited to his house is like a reward for
People who sold some number of hearing aids
And he and I got way too drunk and we were asked to leave
Oh wow it's a nice it's an experience yeah I peed on his floor I'm proud of myself
I bet were you proud of yourself the next morning
Yes f*** that
Oh wow okay you and I are different
Also and I mean at the same time my boss at the time was my
My cousin so I had a little bit more of a little wiggle room
Floor of a Billionaire's home
Sojourn word starting on the 14th
What's the bad news
Start things off
Yeah the last
It's on a rampage
Lottery search
We had the FBI
Contact us
It's about 30 minutes ago
It was worse than we thought
House
Waiting for his wife
Handicap
So she's been in the hospital
Everybody cease understand that
You need to know that
And they're actively trying to say that
We Mastermind
So that's the line they're going with now
Unbelievable
On the 14th news that Rodger Stones wife was attacked by a leftist activist cute
All over the conservative media
Blockman unconfirmed articles about how they were targeted for political violence
Some commentators a pint about how the mainstream media with covering it up
Turn on the 15th there was an article in the Floridian press That's not the clear things up a little bit
They reached out to Rodger and reported quote
We learned that media Outlets today began to fudge the facts of the incident and asthma
The story was recycled around the truth and what happened was
Distorted
Here's the statement they published from Rodger about the truth of the ensign
On December 23rd my wife Nidia and my Yorkie memes we're attacked by a pitbull
Our beloved dog was badly injured require two surgeries and Lydia Was Bitten badly when she attempted to give it to
Between the Pitbull and our baby
This incident was reported to Beaufort Lauderdale police in Broward County Animal Care
Nydia sustained substantial injuries in the pit bull attack
Last week there was an incident in front of our home when we returned from dinner
Amanda bicycle recognize being started screaming numerous political epithet
Which are not fit for a family newspaper
While there was a scuffle mrs. Stone sustained no new injuries in the event
Report said she was badly beaten or hospitalized are incorrect
This event was also accurately reported to the Fort Lauderdale Police
Seems like Alex is kind of embellishing the story a little bit
For dog pee probably should have reached out to Rodger for a comic
Considering how close the two of them are
How to report a completely false story about Rogers wife on air
Galaxy Golf
So
I would say this is not good and that's what story about Laura Loomer I'm going to need season evidence before even
Don't start caring about whatever is going on there
And even gets reported about her on Infowars as an attempted a publicity stunt
Until proven otherwise that Rodger himself is on a rampage
And has been dressing up like a
Only thing that makes sense to me
He's attacking people left and right dress up like a pitbull day drinking is involved
Now we get to the new framing of
The storming of a capital back on January 2nd
Alex
Some historical parallels feel like we're on
We're on like the 5th new framing
Other events that
Doesn't need any new 408 we're going to get a couple ones on this episode we going to get a couple frame this is frustrating
Okay good
Infowars.com is confirmed
January 6th
Was
2.0
Dog
We're going to be covering
When we come back
Riding that printer
Snuggled in that warm bread
Is
What happened
Price tag
He was very popular at Sonic stolen the election
Firebomb that
Match
So
This is
Good
I like the idea that something
Didn't print it out I'm excited to find out what that's going to print it out it's got the little hooks on the hours they got a
Perforate the thing and then a tear it apart
Yeah
I would say is a couple of details wrong about the reichstag fire here
I think I'm probably most important element he's completely making up his at the fire happened after Hitler won an election.
People thought was fraudulent
That's not
I like to say this because he knows that his audience is gullible
Ball and he paints a one-to-one comparison of Hitler and
It's dance to scare them more and drive more profits
Infowars
In reality the reichstag fire occurred on February 27th 1933
In January of that year Hitler been appointed appointed Chancellor of Germany's government which is still under the control of the country
Paul Von Hindenburg
The structure of the government was at the president was the elected leader of the country who would then appoint
Chancellor
Who would be responsible for introducing legislation to members of the reichstag who are also
Elected
At any point the president could dismiss his Chancellor
You know that he was
He had control over that position
He thought well
According to the Smithsonian Magazine Hindenburg reluctantly appointed Hitler as Chancellor on the advice of Franz Von
Poppin
A disgruntled former chancellor who believe the
Conservative parties should Ally with the Nazis
To keep the Communists out of party
Man I heard something like that so frequently pass
Fear of Communism leads to aligning with ashes every time
The reality of the racetrack fire is that it was an event
I almost certainly committed by the Nazis which they blamed on communist
This allowed Hitler to use the event as a rallying cry against the Communists
Justification for why the government needed to assert dictatorship level powers to crush
The threat they pose
There's no other way to put this on this
Why what Alex is doing right now is attempting to be same political maneuvering that the Nazis engaged in 1933
Yes correct
Terrible event
The drove home the sobering reality to a large portion of the country
I'm a terrible event can be in
Incredibly useful
You can blame it on your enemies
This is why Alex is now
On-air fudging details
About the reichstag fire
And if you did it
It is wise to blame it on your enemies otherwise people will think it's your fault
True
That's certainly true of the present situation
You don't want people to think it's your fault though
So Alex really has a bad handle on history
I've heard him that mean like you know the fake quotes R1
Something
But like man
He's way out of line
Alex Jones
Narrowly won the presidency of Germany
Von Hindenburg was not
Powerful position in
Republic
This is crazy not true
Hitler had not wanted Alexa
Compare the presidency of Germany
He was Chancellor beginning in 1933 at which one of the maneuvering to seize more and more power for himself in the knots
Tea party who had a great showing in the reichstag elections in the 1932
Election
People like Nazis
Hindenburg died in 1934 at which point Hitler dissolved the office of the presidency and combined its powers without it
The chancellor
Essentially making himself both Chancellor and president
A1932 election Hindenburg it's soundly defeated Hitler but the Nazi party itself like I said have gained a large number of seats
The scenario that Alex's painting is 100-percent revisionist history because he needs his audience
To think that their living through a direct
Parallel to Hitler's rise
Power
Paul Von Hindenburg
Chancellor and there was not a contested election
For president to the way that Alex
Cuz describing
This is just an idiot making stuff up because his he knows his audience doesn't know any better and won't bother to look into it
Not care either way
This is one of the things that really like to drive home to anyone who may have some inclination
To take Alex Jones seriously or think he knows what he's talking about
If he has this little a grasp of basic facts
Acts like who was in what office when The reichstag happened
And he's so willing to
The confidently assert really fundamental and accuracies why would you ever give him the benefit of the doubt with more complicated
Ever if you can't be bothered to understand like really simple arithmetic
You shouldn't listen to him about like
Geometry or algebra trigonometry
He doesn't know how to add
No no absolutely not he doesn't have a basic grasp of the fundamentals of it
Existent
He doesn't know grammar don't let him tell you how to edit your paper
Whatever you like
You don't know if
If you don't know the building blocks
Upon which understanding can be built right
Your
I feel like one of the fundamental things that he doesn't get is that some things are
And some things are not
Everything seems to be fungible there but something's there was some things have to be yet something's have to not be
And the things they cannot just be whatever you want them
Great and if he wants me to take it all seriously the idea that he knows this secretive
Information that
Hitler was set up or all this nonsense that he throws around all the title is revisionist WWII history
And he doesn't know who was in what office staff
That's embarrassing man
You can't do this
You know what is
Blowing my mind
And it's just going to be soap
Painful
It's going to be so painful Dan if you recall
Do those early days
Open 2017
Whenever you would call it
A Nazi
And people would go you can't just throw that word around
That's a terrible thing to do it needs to be used correctly
And now we are about to begin a long stretch
I've literally everything Biden does
Not making him a Nazi
That will be screamed at us
From all corners of the world including the ones who screamed at us to not call compliment
Exclusively from those poor
Come from Alex one of the good things always fall back on his he knows
Literally nothing about WWII
One very smart
And was blamed on
Asianet
Lisa's not pretending it was
Yeah it's almost like he's
Trying real hard to thread the line where he's like
The Nazis were the good guys
What does he say the election prior to the fire was in April 1932
Your prior to
To the fire 360
After the there was an election for reichstag members scheduled for six days after the fire but that's
The opposite of what Alex's describing
Alex either knows nothing about WWII history and is pretending he doesn't order
Or he doesn't know what the reality is and he's Willy fully lying to them in order to
Make it more closely match this scenario also to scare them you betcha
You really should see
Stop
Congratulations though Alex you have a real depth 100 books on WWII 1000
Books on behalf of
Alex's
Just slander sir slander
Interpretation and their things are like that are like
What
Was
Who was where
In what power alignment
Yeah that's what I'm saying it some things are
And some things are not it can't just say that that's had the
It it's embarrassing for Alex and he never has to pay any consequences
Like even in terms of embarrassment for like
Not knowing any of this s***
So sad
So Alex
Mentioned earlier that the FBI
Are called
We might learn a little bit more
Twilight Zone Twilight Zone
What in the world of Twilight Zone
Imagine what people in Twilight Zone Twilight Zone
The Twilight Zone
Regular challenge
You don't know Madman
Your people in the military
Cornerstone
What you know about what happened
I'm guessing that Ike first of all you write Twilight Zone in the Twilight Zone will be just normal life
Cancel each other out
How about anything that would be the version of the show they watch of the Twilights out consequences
Anyway Alex keeps talking about the FBI contacting him
I think I might know why that is
You remember that he said he had an employee who was there and got footage of the woman getting shot inside the capitol
Maybe an employee who was illegally entering the capitol
That sounds like something the FBI would look into his employees Sam released his raw footage of entering the Capitol building
I was going to play you the minutes where he actually walked through the doors of the building
Thereby committing a crime
If you can see any reason why law enforcement might be interested in talking to Alex
Enough
We're not going to take
We're not going to take all your food
People
Be clear that voice is the cameraman
Bedroom
All the capital
Here we go
This is the first time
Steve
Dumbfounded
I don't know how I made it out of there
Butcher Boys
This is not this is not a peaceful protest
Want to be accurate about that but whatever that means
You heard
What does Guantanamera mean
Where we go
We are
Over there
Nickelodeon movies
Hi
Chewy.com
Infowars store
Dot-com
We got sales
We got sales for days
Please
It's because of your support they were able to get into things like this
I show you the real news that the media won't
Disabled
Tomorrow
You're going to skinny
We are
The plug
I just
I just said these people need to be babysat I don't even know if we need to start working today need to be punished or if they
They need to be babysat because
Literally have no ability to process
This reality
Force.com
I'm going to add back to my quickly growing collection of things that really don't look good in hindsight
This is
Import
You can't
Really we do like this I got to assume that you know there's a lot of people who have been arrested
For breaching the capital even people who are just recording people who didn't break anything at your illegal entry that is
True I don't see why Sam be arrested
So
You can't arrest him
He works for Infowars
The FBI's afraid
Pissing off
Should Sam be arrests
There might be some interesting questions about do you work it in fours
Why did you
Record going it licked it Alex
Send you there on an assignment
That Infowars continues Capital that little clip of video
Keep that he was there in an official capacity would suggest that as part of his duties
While promoting infowarsstore.com he committed a crime
That might be something that people would want to talk to Alex about I don't know through the Looking Glass here Dad were in the Twilight Zone
Ensure
Everything's normal
Anyway Rogers wife
Going through some things
This is the real world you cannot
Amman
Ran over his wife
The Rodger now is going into hiding
This is a joke
Why does my hospital had emergency surgery
Because a man
His wife up
Condo area Nobody's around random
Walking the dog
If I were Rodger ibp
It's about that would be really not happy about Alex's Behavior
Don't f****** embellished stories about my wife in order to make people scared of the left
Cheesy dick
I know that's the job
Yeah yeah
Come on that I hope someone
Scream cut
His dick off at Rodger Stone
But I'm not not
So if I were a dry be mad about that also not be thrilled about this
Beating up
Seventy-five-year-old whatever she has
How old is wifey
Oh my God
Beautiful women
Wow
What are we doing
What do we do we got to do that we don't
To do these things Alex
We don't have to
To say
His daughters hot we don't
Well I mean it's it's
An interesting why he was trying to recover from saying that Roger's wife was hot
Is child instead
That'll make it better
What a good save everybody who's why isn't everybody reaching up for i5
5 going on where's everybody else is I-5
So we get back now to the the reichstag
Backfire
And I
I was so glad that this paid off
Cuz I was worried that that stuff that he was printing out wasn't going to be
The opposite of check-offs
Printer print out
This is 2.0
Jose
Government
The capital
Glen on Monday the 27th
Versace
The chancellor of Germany
Hitler's
Government
So
This is the wicked
Pedia article about the ricetec
If you create yourself Malik does any work please call this image
He doesn't do s***
He has his intern spring Wicca
Pedia Paige's room
The fumble his way through blindly reading
What do you say
German Fire wikipedia
The German word for the fire
Confused Alex Wiley was cold reading Theory
Is it pathetic
Hey white more revisionist history about Hitler coming up
You you assume a legitimacy that somebody essentially from the internet doesn't
Pickle papers suggest
We at least did the work
And then you find out they
Just printed out the internet and that
That's 10 times
Is less interesting
The newsman of days of your might have
Desk papers looking at
You know
I don't know I might maybe I've only seen this in sitcoms
But like somebody comes running in with a piece of paper
Transcriptions because you couldn't even do s*** like that you have to read it out loud like a man
I think I was just trying to emulate that to give himself some kind of like the appearance of that and it's just Wikipedia articles
Here's more ride b*******
Hitler first only got two left
Wasn't enough and then it was
Weimar Republic
Hitler was not elected president prior to the rice Chex oir
Chancellor by Hindenburg
The title fewer didn't really even exist.
Set the timer to guess you was a few or the Nazi party but it wouldn't come into being like a state role until after Hindenburg
Has a president of Chancellor into a new title
Fuel her and rice Chancellor which eventually got shortened to fuhrer
And then they got shortened to Senate majority
I hate to sound like a broken record here but Alex is making s*** up about Nazi history for his own benefit here and then pretending with the nerve
Berg trials back him up
The thing that I think is most transparent respect
Alex
Damn well in that moment
He's making this up
Yeah he knows he's making this up
That's why you say teaching to something like the Nuremberg trials which is absolutely useless as a rat
The beach part of the tribe how many months-long years-long
Exactly came out in those trials even
Pull the thread to determine how reliable a source is being solid to go other than
Thousands of pages of testimony
And you're not even really sure what you're looking for to approve Alex right or wrong
That's a big part of Alex's game
One of his favorite things to do is make absurd
Completely false claims and insist that some impossibly long text actually proved him right
He's never read those texts but it doesn't matter cuz he knows that his audience hasn't been won't either
That's why he'll constantly just point it thousand plus page books like
Tragedy and hope or ecoscience
He just insisted those things
Actually proved him right that's all in there
It's a way of trying to Railroad criticism and make it impossible for anyone to actually engage with the things that are being said unless they
Read these really long book
Pretending to have Ray
I would dig through the Nuremberg document
Disprove what hour to say
He gives up his right to be taken seriously when you completely fabricated history like this
But I couldn't help it so I did to grab a little
Distance from page 110 of volume to the trial of major war criminals
This is spoken by Justice Robert Jackson the chief us prosecutor at the Nuremberg trials
The burning of the symbol of three parliamentary government was so providential for the Nazis that it was believed they saved the fire them sell
Certainly when we contemplate their known crimes we cannot believe they would shrink from Mere arson
It's not necessary however to resolve the controversy as to who set
The fire
So I guess if I were to sing that came out in the Nuremberg trials of the Nazis themselves at the fire that
Chief us prosecutor doesn't seem to even making that indictment
In the Nuremberg trials
And in fact
Though it's generally accepted consensus that the Nazis did
Probably start the fire
Come by even today
Even the US Holocaust Memorial Museum says quote the origins of the fire are still unclear
I mean
I think the prosecutor really makes a good point which is just like
Just Amy you take it off at it it doesn't matter anytime
It doesn't even matter
He did was
Horrible enough fire is not
Anytime anytime somebody is engaging in WWII revisionism where they're like
Changing a little bit of the of the story away from
Nazi Genocide
Is it to me like that sign that you're eventually going to try and get me to think that
Even if there was a problem with Hitler
It wasn't the genocide or the fascism Park
I see you coming sir
They're Alex's Alex's really f*****
Weird on this thing
This really struck me as like
This is unnecessary
It really is
Disposing of a
Either
Complete and total ignorance
History on Alex
Does Park
Or
A willingness to lie to his audience
In any way to make history look like what he wants
What's the present
Look like to them in order to convince them of a lie about the present
Either those are pretty bad looks
Yeah I mean what's that old saying he who lies about the past
Controls the present
And then becomes
Senate majority
So
We get
I guess
At this point on 40
Is Guyton bush
Haha
He's the Batman Batman
Cast on the show much
In the in the reason
History Sol
People who just discovered our Show recently probably won't know of our obsession with Jon rappoport
Follow us on Twitter for 400 episode
And then
Go to the knife
He is a guy who is a quote on quote
Investigative journalist
Ism hiv-2 nihilus
Is a real dick
Monetizing Alex
Alex has an intense emotional Reliance on him
Sometimes whenever John
The 4th hour Alex will do 5 minutes within where you
Just like Johnny Lee Africa
We love you so much John Rappaport tell me I'm a good man
I just needed to hear that have a good man
Through his interviews not really all that great
It's kind of just about how like
You know there
FIFA did not ship through the Rolodex of Infowars guessing we're like
I guess rapaport's the only one who hasn't been documented as saying we did it
We took over the Capitol in a positive way there are there are a fair amount of like wow they're back
Like Mike Adams was bad last couple episodes
Rapoport's here showing up later we're going to get the
Steve Quayle is f****** back
Who here was against the cuckoo anybody raise their hands anybody Ole Boy Oh not a lot of faces okay
So here's a little taste
Who is this guy
Standing next to him
Well he was arrested
All of this comes tumbling out
Sebastian Inlet go
He was released
You know
It's like Keystone
Alex is referencing John Sullivan
Then who's not by any stretch of the word
Initially Alex I've been saying that this dude has been arrested and let go and he's making us both
Since Ben Sullivan had been arrested but he wasn't really let go
You released from jail without bail but whenever Alex brings that up he fails to mention the conditions of his release
Concluded surrendering his passport
Having computer activity is monitored being not allowed to go on social media and being under house arrest
He's definitely still in huge trouble but the phrasing that he was released from jail is being misrepresented by people like Alex implies that
The charges have been dropped when that is not the case
Yeah the legal system is not really there
Interest in portraying a
Accurately out
Capital letters and stuff
Although I don't know all the details but Sullivan's not someone who left-wing activist seem to
Hey them
There's an article in The Intercept that's like the number of activists from the west coast to a raised concerns about him longbow
Before he went to DC
But anyway
Weirdly you know where I actually first saw John Sullivan for the first time
It was in the footage
From inside the capitol that was shot by the Infowars employee Named Sam interesting
Gear Sam talking to John Sullivan just after that woman got shot
Trying to get the footage
That John Sullivan headshot of the incident
Okay
Infowars.com
A couple of interesting things here
The first is obviously hope ghoulish it is that these two are so interested in talking about how good their footage is a woman being shot so soon after
So close to where the shooting happen
Voyeurism on display here that I think reflects poorly on them both
Yeah seems unaware of Infowars
If you were really an antifa provocateur who's there to set up the Patriots to make them look bad
Strange city with sound
Completely unfamiliar with the name in 40 supposed to be the Patxi's in Fall Guys with this whole thing
Conversely if he really were left-wing activist seems unlikely that he would be unaware of Infowars in that circumstance to
Given that there are media organization that is proves that poses a very real than relevant threat to left-wing Act
It was community
I honestly don't know what to make of their exchange and I can't possibly imagine how difficult it would be to process information after seeing someone
Get shot so like not recognizing a name Cody
Sofia brainlab
I have no idea
But I do think
Pretty funny to look at the Dynamics here
On the 6th
When Alex was on his own show
He was touting this footage
Said he'd gotten from inside the capitol of the shooting
Footage was shot by Sam Lloyd
And John Sullivan was the other footage that Alexander
Booty I was not turned out to be an auntie for agent
I honestly wonder if Alex even realizes that the person that Sam got footage
Trump to send to Alex was John Sullivan
I bet Alex doesn't even realize
Another Gaston
Online right-wing talk show host
The show before
You might have been I'm not sure if Pete Santilli
The same tailor lace
I couldn't help it
I don't like this guy but I also am not interested
January 20th
Commander-in-chief hasn't called us to a peaceful
Protest
Auto Washington DC he just said wherever your
I believe that there are setting the stage the FBI said
Forewarned
Replace
There were going to be some agitators coming in
Because
For the FBI
Let
Polices.
Operative
In the window
Obviously
The emotion involved in just
Years ago
2018 from 2015
Headline Infowars was Obama
Plan martial law in Maryland
How'd that go
Jimmy trigger
Is document still aren't real
There's still definitely just something that Harrison
Smith family was cruising around 4chan
X-rated besoros Sunday
Pizza in Philly the guys like a radio show host but he's only relevant at all because he was arrested at the malheur wildlife
Refuge occupation
The charges ultimately were dropped against him most likely because he was both occupying The Refuge and pretending to be a journalist
So didn't even want to f*** around and try and figure out how that
First Amendment needle gets threaded and I got there like
Jesus Christ either that's just too much
It's too much it's too much
He's a dumb dumb
And he's on just to try and help Alex
Convince people that
Said said
People up and going to like
Coming weekend
It's all going to be a mess
Who's going to be the agent provocateur deven
Mass shooting
Bombing
And now that we're here recording this on Tuesday
I think it's I think it's fascinating to me just because
In in Subway's
This is
Kind of the only way that these people would be able to try and
Keep their
People from committing
Mass acts of violence
Cuz I can't come out and say
We were lying
People be like
No you weren't
Or you're lying to us or it doesn't matter we still want overthrow the capitol but if you say that if you go
You're going to be
Torrid and then blames that's more likely to cut
Through the
It's like a it's like when you're talking to a child in pretend land
You have to talk to
To the pretend land child not the regular
Yeah because you just say
Something along the lines of like complete denunciation of violence
Is a certain amount of your audience who will think that you've sold out or something because that is how
Information is filtered
For a lot of these communities
Yeah you have to be like okay yeah you want to do this
You're right to want to do it
The Trap and you'll be a symbol that'll bring all your brethren down holy that is probably the only way you're right
Yeah it's it's
It doesn't really work for everyone
I don't know
This was pretty fun
Pete Santilli has one big message
And it's like yeah alright I believe
What I want
Do you understand right now
You're most
Trusted people that you have around you
Are going to be the ones that you will
You will be shocked
Actually working
For this app
There's trillions of dollars at stake
Your security person may be paid a hundred
Thousand dollars
Just set you up to
Information
In order for you to
Make a steak
Turn on recording
And essentially be used in an adult
Repeats messages nobody in the right-wing can be trusted
Listen everyone or everyone was solidarity
The moment that it is expedient for them to do is yes
You could afford
Did you guys ever hear about
Stalin's closest politburo friends and all that stuff
Did you ever notice how they backstab each other all the goddamn time will guess what that's what fast
Well I know that Stalin bird of the reichstag
Right after
We don't have time to figure it out dad
Makes a bit of an accusation here that I found two states
I believe and we're getting
Information now that there were maps that were put out
A guy named John Sullivan
B0m
FIFA
Activist
Just so how
Happened to be press
How she was able to determine that
Going through the Labyrinth
The hallways in the
Halls of Congress
How she was able to
One particular spot
Or Secret Service would be
I'm sure was provoked by John Sullivan
She's very emotional and
The window
She goes up
She gets shot
I got to say it feels kind of like defamation to just randomly imply that just because Sullivan was an ear Ashley when she got shot that's
Somehow he later there
If the standard for making that accusation is that low then it could easily be said that I was his cameraman Sam must have led her to where she got
HotShots Infuse right there too
Flag-burning friend Taylor Hansen was right there too so he must have been the one who lied her there
This is a very serious accusation that Pete is making based on nothing
The only reason he's doing it is so that he doesn't have to feel bad about being an active participant
In the media
Ecosystem that missing forms and radicalize people like Ashley
The point where she thought it was a good idea to storm the capital
He can't take that really hard look in the mirror so the best way to
But that also has to come up with a convenient story where someone else's bad guy who actually secretly mcenany
Add Aleve to this
Yeah at no point in time can that man just say
Wait
I think it was me and my ilk
Except let her
I can our Real World come out
I don't know if I have the reflection I have to change my behavior or recognize that I'm a villain while I
My profit off it
Good luck.
So Alex keep lying about Roger's wife
And we don't need to hear more of that cuz basically just the same thing over and over again
Videos of mother Gaston
Okay Isaac
This guest is listen to our show
It's as relevant from Rebel media and I really think
Tell me if you know why I think that
What happened
What's your view what's coming next
Look up we all noticed
You know the phrase
News
And you can battle Freight
Fake news on a daily basis
What happens when cat is
Cement
When that cement hardens
And it becomes
Straight you can't even
Argue or dislodge
I'm not saying that I came up with that metaphor
It's something that I've used in this very specific context
Many times he uses it multiple times
In this interview
And I was just sitting here like you mother
Weaponize my own s*** against make that
Liquid sucks
Not very interesting as an interview we're going to jump
To the 5th
So 15th of Friday
He does listen to our shows
Can find out how little
F*** about it
Go cry to Tommy Robinson about Samantha
Anyway so we had some vaccine possibly related death
Norway and Alex's covering that story
Just on this little
Bissell.com
Which is Scott links to
Reuters
23 dead in Norway
They said that's okay it's going to kill something
I'll just normalizing the day
That's just
So this is an instance where the headline can look pretty scary but the actual story might not actually be as much of a cause for alarm
As It Seems
The first thing to be clear about is that these deaths that have happened in Norway are obviously being study
At the time of this episode there's not been any causal link
That's been made between the vaccine and these death
Switch
Mail.
If Alex would actually read some of the underlying
Information that the centaurs article is based on
From Stephen Evans professor of epidemiology
At the London School of hygiene and tropical medicine
Evans told the UK's science Media Centre that when people who are at high risk of death get back
Made it there will be a certain number of
Coincidental.
That's what occurred shortly after vax
Destination
Regulatory bodies across the world are closely monitoring these fatalities Ivan said
And are able to calculate the exact
Expected number of deaths within various time.
We do not yet know but it would seem that the observe numbers of deaths
Is not notably above the numbers
Expected he said
Adding that there was quote
No need for anxiety but complacency is equally mistaken
If we're vaccinating people who are going to die soon some of them are going to die soon
After we vaccinate
People who happen in high-risk categories may have a higher XP
Citation of coincidental.
To be taken into account
Also the possibilities brought up in these articles
Minor side effects
Possibly being much
More serious issues for people in Moore
Anyway
I think that if you look at
Get something like how this
Guide
Stephen Evans is explaining the situation
I think it sounds very responsible
Yeah because he has both
Both side sort of reflect
Kidero just like
There's reasons why this number would be there were people looking at it will understand this better
This is not a reason to be super worried but it's also not a reason to just be like whatever
You know I hate
I remember when I was when I was young
When I was little
They had kids Bibles
You know that were Illustrated and they simplified a lot of the stories and they left out all the rapes
And
I think that's what we need for like science news journalists we need to give them like the kitty version of
Real science
And they can disseminate that so people don't get
Get to scared
You know cuz they we can't be having people with her
Headlines like
Vaccine involved in two deaths
B23
Apologies
True no it's not
23 people died after getting the vaccine
It's related or connected
How many of the cases it is
Is unclear
B is the headline itself can be weaponized so easily by people
With the wrong
Information be good message messaging is is critical
At this point with the medical information I think
I would change that headline to tens of millions vaccinated without dying
Unsurprisingly statistically relevant
But unsurprising so far at this
This point in time 23 like let's go back
To the old track
From the 60s
Start writing R1 headlines
Okay
Another headline
Suicide
Drug overdose
And more
I can tell from
The phrasing of the headline that Alex is reading there that it's a
Post
In an outlet called the Dhaka Tribune
I didn't know that I'll accept up with you Bangladeshi media
I guess one of those interns just has a Google alert for lockdown studies and they're going to hit the filter
This is an article published on January 11th about a paper put out by a Canadian doctor of Pediatrics named Ari joffe
The paper is called covid-19 rethinking the lockdown groupthink and it's not been published by anyone
Nor is it. View
Odd also it was written last October
I was absolutely didn't read this paper what does interns just sent to the headline from an outlet in Bangladesh covering the Canadian paper
For the no one cared about 3 months
This is trash at work
Now
Alex gets to a point where
You kind of think
Maybe we got to move on
Maybe gotta move on from Trump
I think he's starting to have those those feelings of like
We must move forward
I could Snap My Fingers
Come out against Trump
Tails because it's private
Things are done
Message works
Illegali
The minions
What's the Second Amendment betray America
Make it so easy just come out just a little bit
Red flag laws or or
Come out
We radical Islam alone
Jones you come back here
Greg
I never been your fault
I don't want to be in your phone
But that's
Where are the sigils
Truck settings for that
Trump said that
Talk about something
Why he thought he did the right thing I'm so you can get
Pizza Hut
We failed to do the right thing when it came to
And now he knows that
We move on
Now it's Joe Biden
We will never accept
Who's going to come after us
Because he runs a globalist
Find family
Dropbox
Rubicon
Unbelievable
This dude so mad about qanon
Check is what we just started real
There's also there's something interesting in paradoxical turn on Trump
Only for him to then and his ramp I think we can move on to fight Joe Biden
Turning on trumpet leaving that season of a show behind me
If you're Alex you don't go
Get to do this
You don't get to whip your audience into an apocalyptic
Fervor but a trump was appointed to be ruler by God and this election is a spiritual battle between Trump and godliness in the literal devil
Then when it's time to move on you to say we move on
The devil one
He's a good dude I guess we talk
Talked a little bit he's everywhere
Alex promise the end of days
And a f******
King devil if I can got in and guess what
It's probably just going to be a slightly disappointing government
A bunch of money yelling about f****** b*******
Also I want to point out this thing that Alex has been doing a lot lately that I find really offensive
He keeps talking about how he could join the globalist so easy
They want him on their side and any minute he
Be one of the elites
This is meant to be heard by the audience
Like an abusive spouse yelling about how they could do so much better
The message is really clear that Alex could join the globalist whenever he wants
Because he's special
But no one listening has the same offer extended to them because they are not spare
And you should be glad that I'm not joining these globalist choose to shine my light on
You a******.
It's it's
Stark
Yeah it's a really narcissistic and and gross
I don't enjoy it I would prefer he didn't do that or exist
Well I mean like if you didn't exist
I know there's at least two people in the world
Who
Woods
Miss him
I got the wrong clip here thinking real hard
I got the wrong clip-on okay
Later Alex says the two famous people told
I'm something this is a clip where two people tell him about one single famous person
Rewind
Didn't hear that part there's one person
Does Woodbury
Who did I say
Christopher Walken
But the video where he's admitting it all
Houston employees like a man with a gun to his head
Blackmail
Weird
The Jack Dorsey
Jones is always right
Famous Hollywood producer
Music producer
It's like their Guru and then he's like Berry Gordy all the time
And this is like a while back and I'm like okay alright
You can't make up the weirdest level
This is right before Phil Spector died right
I love me some famous music producer
Yeah man I don't know
Let's imagine this is
True
You got something better to do with your time
No he does it
He looks at me like I'm
Guru
I'm really really done with anybody
Treating a rich person like there
Real like
What's going on with Jack Dorsey
What's going on
Money
I don't even care about Jack Dorsey I want to talk about Alex Jones being his Guru
Alright well then that still makes sense money is the only thing he cares about I mean
I must have felt terrible to kick your Guru off of your own platform
Multiple times
Absolutely
I believe David Knight on
David night is my night light
I just think about this like you get kicked out of a bar and they're like later you like the bouncer tyminski
Gyro
And loves me
Guy f******
So I hope his heart
Kick my ass out of there
Alex didn't tell that story
To be powerful
I didn't tell you that
Jack Dorsey Story 2 Channel power Fuller to Loma Portal Hollywood only part of the wash
The power structure really is true that you cannot register or fathom
Popular Infowars really is now
That was all God's plan
All of us together
Almost all these liberal talk show host attack me
They actually listen
Mike cernovich visiting year
So don't you know they all love you and they all listen all the time and
Don't you know all those
Big people
But I appreciate
It is awful
Don't believe anything Mike cernovich
7 / 2
Man this is sad
Is bad
You know what the only people that I could really make a solid case
I really dislike him but do listen to Mir
That would be
Alex
Is
Confusing man
In many ways grade
He has certain taste
Disgusting once he has a
The crush on somebody
This really happen
Remember about a year ago visiting my
Whatever you're mine my wife's mother
In San Diego
And so
Craft little
Country Club Plaza Hotel
Fairmount
Beautiful Hotel and golf course with a walk around the golf
Or stuff I'm rich your Nike
All the typical spring
Nobel prizes and it's been going on
It's always okay
View
I said man I'll have a website or a podcast
I told my wife to called
Chemtrails and Country Club
Beautiful country clubs beautiful pool beautiful statues
Five star hotel
I never stayed somewhere that nice
Everyone
Everyone so then
I get about 5 a.m.
That's it
Fishpig Popstar
She must be
New album is called
Chemtrails
Over the country club
Playa del Rey
Alex continues
Lana Del Rey
It's about going to Lana Del Rey
He is so into this Chemtrails over the country club
Eddie can't even enjoy it you can't even enjoy it
He loves it he loves
And he can't publicly
He has to spend a f****** 10-minute Jag on how famous he is
Goddamn
People can't even come out and say he loves Lana Del Rey Alex I would like for you to challenge yourself
Explain to me how much you love the song Born to Die
Hey Alex what are you watching the national anthem video about that
Samurai Dr from the Artists Den
Are they are they just so great it's so great
Like the last two albums
Just decided I f****** love like
You don't need you don't bring It Up all In For This americana's
I guess maybe
Another Tuesday 10
The cop or something
I don't know I don't know exactly what it is but it is
Really weird that what we should be doing should we should the antifa focus more on
Biplanes and crop-dusting mind control
Over Resort town
I don't know
I think that's a good idea I listen to this this Chemtrails over the country
Country Club song
And I don't know I still like Lana Del Rey I'm not but
I think I might be a little bored
Good songs on Norman f****** Rockwell but like
As a whole I thought that song was really
Kind of just standard Lana Del Rey stuff
Intrigued meme
Got it kind of felt a little bit
A little safe a little down the middle
Is this
Alphabetically
The sequel to Bombs Over Baghdad
Yes
Moving on Alex interviews Larry Pinkney
It was a black panther back in the day
And today
More just about how the FBI is running at Tifa and black lives matters.
Alex get back to talking about Rodgers wife
This is the next big mouth
This is the 50
Teepee still talking about Rogers
Watch got beat up
Tell him
The front yard
Got up
Overtime
And she knew the Rodger
You're crazy so she just had a guy hit with a bike
Hospital
He's so upset he can't even come on the air
74 year old
Okay so
Crazy
I need your support
Appreciate your support
Wow
Alex
You can make up s*** about my wife
But I'm not going on your show to lie and please just whatever you do don't use
Good stories about my wife to sell pills always predictable
Just
You at if you meet Alex
Talk to him for more than an hour you have to sign a waiver that says he's allowed to say about your time to
You're probably you probably right
I'm going to lie about that
Soylent is another Gaston and it's Steve Quayle
As I noted weirdo
He is someone who has he is a long history with Alex
Coast to Coast
He's also a gas
Start Jim Bakker Show
Israel's president for a while books
About
Giants
Usher
Shark Valley is another book of coming out soon about Giants that Alex
What's that talk about
We're not talkin about centers within the NBA
About the angel who fell in breeded with
How to Big Dan
Alex
In the past we listen to episodes from like the 2009
Sierra around them
Steve quayle's around a bit more
How do I keep nose stuff ahead man
He's just really right about stuff
That was asked him how he
Pino's
The stuff that he knows I'm interested in finding out
I don't know if you could predict this and it's not a good answer
Simply this
I went from the gutter most important
I got was Wild on Montana State University
Jesus
And I accepted Jesus in my heart
I was living in my mother's house
And
10 10 blocks from University
And Jesus literally and I noticed going to play
He gave me a panoramic history
And told me he was calling me not understand
I just found out
What's the date
Best spirit of God convicted my heart but here's the thing
He gave me a panorama of his
The future was just imagine
Pizza Steve
Going to
The things from you
Until there shortly
To come to pass
He told me he said I want you to prepare
Are My People
The End of the Age
I'll bring people to tell you what you need to know but you must be
Good morning
Oh boy
You are such a good medium
You do not need to do
Do voices
The reason that you don't know things is because I'm going to hide them from you until
I have appeared to you Jesus from Beyond
The grave why I'm not explaining things to you
Also if
You know the Lord came down
Steve panoramic view of History
Probably explain to Alex
That Hitler was elected president before the right text
You know Jesus did left out that part for some odd reason not everything's in the panorama
Everything about history
If you're seeing a panoramic view of History
One that's a lot
To take ensure how long was he there for
I mean a day to God is 1000 years
Totally I feel like if you are there at like if we had some scripture
Remember neck if it's the name of a ribosome
Oh the Places that you learned sure we see through a glass Darkly
None of us have the full play
Picture but the Riza has a clearer picture than the rest
Let's drop
So
Steve
Talk to God
Who gave him a panoramic view of
Of History
I told him that he was going to leave
God's people
Or something
Nylex had if
Visitation
You got a visit from Jesus I got a visit from the other guy
Why'd you get a visit from Jesus I got a visit from the dead
Because I was serving the devil
Wholehearted
And somebody somewhere
For me because
I was totally
Why did I get a visit from the Devil
I got the other
The other guy
Even Jesus was Tim
Either one of us
It's really important
This is a spiritual war
I don't know I feel I feel like everybody who's ever been interested now it's Jones
Once again should have lead
All their stories
Alex Jones
,
Guy who believed the devil visited
Yeah
I I just have a heart
I want to know the rules of this universe it's really getting annoying
It's like whenever it's like when you're watching a superhero movie and then it the deus ex machina somebody already out all the sudden
Has a new power Heroes
Set up the rules for me exist within the rules of space
When they started to get to the blower that could give people powers and heroes is like no we can't do this anymore
What's going on with that Eclipse we can't do this
Stop at stop
Nope you can't just everybody's claiming that they got visits from superpowers and she had no come on man I got busy
The day by Hephaestus God
Good person that you got visited by the devil and that I was a bad person that I got visited by Jesus
It's like yin and yang but we don't believe in that boat
Yeah
That's the kind of conversation but stay complaints
Boy this show is
Dog
Cowboy Steve's got a prediction that has nothing to do with Giants or visitations from Otherworld
Like this state
7 years ago
Even if you don't
Allows China and Russia to destroy the United States in a nuclear attack
Bugs going to reveal the sins of the leaders to the people and
And a People Sims before a holy God
SOB's on a planet
Those are sons of Belial
As if we've seen it we're seeing the Deep state
I guess get a bunker
I prefer the Sequoia and Bilal
I thank you very much I don't know I guess
China and Russia going to Nuke us
Yeah why
I don't know they heavily invested in
I think they want us to live
Anyway
Steve
Is
And insufferably
Annoying
Weirdo I love him 7 years
He's at Visions if I wanted
Just hear somebody talk about like being visited by God and how do you know Bilal is going to Nuke the
The Earth or whatever the f***
I could call my wife
I won't listen to that same person tell me about antifa
I'm just not playing that game
At anyway we go on
16th and that's Saturday
Okay what Alex has an episode on Saturday must be an emergency emergency emergency episode I think
Dogs that little bit of time to think
We got a new reason that the six Pappa
There will be another reason
Don't come until actually Sunday
But on Saturday Alex
Pink
Think he might not be feeling good about
We all know the false flag
When is the scoundrels
Ace in the Hole
Duration
And now they played it
What is a good cover
Vernon sever their racist
12 Wok
I didn't do it
And then Ashley pieczenik on
A few days ago
Chortling and
Celebrating
That's right
But not in the way
He said
But see that's the thing about the globalist mindset
As the terrain changes and they
Flipside
Gauging Machiavellian Behavior
They think that's intelligent
They think
Cold-hard social-darwinist stick
Where they carry it out
Proof of their righteousness
And it's not
Stevens global
II
What's going on here in this world
Play out as a it goes along
He was traveling but not in the way he seemed
The way you seem to be chortling was that Trump had one and everything is totally fine
It should be pointed out that our episode of mocking the s*** out of Steve's interview with him came out on Friday
Friday so I don't know it's baby
I don't know if that's what led to this
Emergency episode of reflection
Probably not
You stalking about 1984
Emmanuel Goldstein is a is a setup
But other characters
In 1984 and how
How they interact
Torture came in the courtroom
They thought
Friends
Cuz I couldn't leave them in car
Just like in 1984 O'Brien
And it's all just a fictional account
This
Is
But but he still thinks O'Brien's are good. He's like
O'Brien they got you and Brian come to the jail cell
O'Brien they got you
I got you two years old they got me a long time ago Westin
The differences with somebody like me
I know pechenik shuttle Bryant
I'm just observing him and watching him I'm not listed Smith
Oh boy
Subway
Okay
I'm not getting manipulated I am the master manipulator
I am observing him as an excited
Experiment
Just say whatever bulshit that he wants to have
But I was observing
Closer dad
Cool versus sad I am glad I'm not a narcissist
Really you know what it would really f***
Wake me up for a good day or two
Need to create a mythology around it I be like
I got had
And I would learn from it and I would move on with my life
And then I do and then you would bring up the Nigerian email scam before
Happened before
Alex is still talk about 1984 any cuts into talk anymore about this Emmanuel Goldstein
Being character
Here is Emmanuel Goldstein
Goldstein is a
Fictional character in George Orwell's
Dean
Dystopian novel 1984
Is the principal Enemy of the State
Go to the party of the
Oceania
So he's reading the Wikipedia page for Emmanuel Goldstein I'm not sure I was watching the video all right
Reasonably pauses there when he says the 1949 novel
Is because on the Wikipedia page it in accurately says the 1984 novel 1984
Or they have the year wrong
Correcting that she was
Tristan his analysis of 1984
Anyway
He's he's he's bummed out cuz
On the one hand
They got false flag
Are you pissed off
Welcome
He's experiencing.
Biden's going to be
It's
It's tough times all around for the Patriots yeah sure
And there's literally only one solution
Thank you so much for joining us on the Saturday evening
The only way we stopped as well. Eration
Boiler storm
Doctors
Is by you taking this live feed and the archive feed for Bandit video
I'm telling everyone that they've got a martial law plan
The next few days and then only getting the word out to stop it
We need this report to get 10 million views by Monday
Get your email list
Get your text message list
Tell your neighbors to watch it
Run down the street
Will the sign saying watch
The productive solution is just
Get me free publicity
It's Dom
Man
Brutal
Great
Fern emerging
Cynthia episode
Alright so we're going to be told how we're going to die
Okay omigod
Mike Adams is so goddamn dramatic
The owner of it's over for Humanity there will only be lone survivors is dramatic
He's like a Junior High student this guy is going through some things
Writing poetry all day
Unbecoming of an adult the way it's Maudlin is over-the-top
It's just
Not cool it's like how you imagine Edgar Allan Poe in high school you're like Jesus that guy must have been exhausted
Annoying probably
Who's smaller head
Soma
Mike wants to explain why there's so many troops in DC now by argument would be that a bunch of people storm the capitol
I don't understand
Did
Existing threats
Sand you know continuing
People saying they want to do it again men are universally nonviolent
That's what I've heard from them
Another explanation
30,000 troops in Afghanistan
3000 Throop
American
This is ten times
The size of America
Cannon to kill a fly
Rights
Nation of this is just for the inauguration
Complete nonsense there's something else happening
I've been sent photos
The Patriot missile Banks being set up
In other states in America
I'll be no there there is legitimate concern
About Chinese troops
Chinese troops in Mexico concerned about Chinese troops in Mecca
Mexico does not sound like something I I believe
I don't know why they would be in a massing of troops in Washington DC who is in the
Border but
I don't know
Yeah that
Argue also one of the reasons they're so many more troops
You know how hard it is to get 30,000 troops to Afghanistan that's all
Long way away
Where does Alex and Mike's narratives shouldn't use that as the number
Mike has
I'm somebody
Who sang the Trump is going to win
Their CIA show
I think he's talking about Steve
I don't know though because he won't name names
There are some
Bad faith actors
That even in the last 24 hours I was able to even laughing midterm
A particular bad fact I don't want to mention any names but someone who had fooled a lot of people with online videos that were popular
Saying that no you at Trump's going to be sworn in on the on the 20th
That person is a CIA operative I've been able to acquire his
Is the ID number
Working at the CIA
So that's it that's a no
If you had evidence
That somebody was running operations
Definitive proof they work
For the CIA
Like you would put that out
You would have to put that out you'd have to think that like
Super dangerous for me to have the
Alex would say right you have to get it all out
Yeah I mean it's not a sin Disturbed Mission Impossible if you are
Jennifer aydin undercover operative
The biggest things that will get you killed until you release that information
Who is coming out with that information
So I think this is about Steve
Pennywise
Some pretty serious things on the horizon
I'm sure there's possible Chinese invasion
I also another threat
Consider
I'm very very concerned
That the Deep state
Is going to set off a dirty bomb
In the u.s. city
Going to blame that on Patriots
And that's why they're desperately knocking on doors looking for somebody to recruit
Somebody who actually has a history
Of appearing on videos and end podcast and so on talking about guns
Or chop or what have you
You
Yeah
Yep
All of this stuff is you
You realize this is you are you speaking to a threatening to dirty bomb made
I am I am loving all of these I'm concerned about what they're going to say the Patriots
Because part of me is like
Do you guys think the Patriots are capable of building a dirty bomb
Cuz that concern me I think they definitely are I know what that oath keeper guy was arrested a couple years back with a napalm
Yeah I think I think what we're all really hearing from these people is oh my God I'm worried about what we created
It might be out of
Is an
Controllable
Completely out of
Lime group that we thought would just be
Fun
Yeah unfortunately
All of our fanfic about history didn't warn us about what Real History would have warned us about an uncontrolled
I think it's kind of like me starting the year the seltzer
I thought it would be good fun and I thought that you know we just have Seltzer's and I try them
And it got out of hand
You picked you went
502 b and a year is too long
It's an unwieldy amount of time it's an unwieldy amount of sell turmeric
Commitment that had it for a long time
. not saying it's over I created something that I thought
And it was fun it was a lot of fun
A lot of momentum
For a while
But it was uncontrollable
Flagged a little bit and then it came back
It's still back
Controllable thing you can't just force
Set me up for doesn't work
But neither does democracy apparently
Cuz Mike has to tell you
Country is Father's day so dramatic
The rule of law has collapse in this nation and whether you're arrested just depends on which side you're working for so
If
Patriots
Are you going to be considered guilty no matter what you're doing
If you're a radical leftist you can throw Molotov cocktails and set fire to Federal buildings and burn police cars and shine lasers at Federal
Agents in your mythology
Apples in 24 hours by a George soros-funded
A district attorney
In your local city
We will now enter the era of complete
Lawlessness
There is no
Controlling legal Authority
That is legitimate in this nation
Which means the constitutional republic Has Fallen
Damn
Wow that happened
Yeah
Big news
Huge if true
I love all that is no legitimate legal Authority in America
Game on right now
All the things that would stop you from
Doing things like storm
The capital that would be
And there's no legal
I guess if you will Mica saying smoke them if you got them
It reminds me so much of all those 2021 articles where it's like
Cops
Have been proven to hurt leftist set
Three times the rate of
White nationalist
Seems like guys
I'm glad that you have
New hard data
But come on
This is America
We didn't need a new Guardian article in 2021
We had
Guardian articles in 1914 saying the exact same set but it's good enough
The more articles but you could have just put up like Apple
Picture of the
Flag been like see this is what we
Fair enough
Now
One thing you're not going to see an article about
Is the evil eye
I don't think
That's true
I want star documentary about this guy who actually had magical powers could hypnotize people with his
Narrated by Vincent Price
No it was this really rich guy great mustache
Haha
Mezmur
I remember that in one of his employees was little guy who would watch films right and then review them
Poorly
The guy whose film reviewer night
To the UN School
Doctor Demento
Please tell me that you know what I've done
Was that
The critic man I forgot about the evil eye
Oh s*** look into my Triton could do that
That's what I would have
Evil eye
Is a real thing I don't want to have a George W bush moment with you where he said you know I think
I looked at it
Everybody knows it's the eyes are bloody nose
It's a wonder the show
I look at your eyes and I see a serious
Intelligent
Focused person that's really concern you look at my eyes
EBay CC the same thing
I look at the eyes and itching
Increasingly worse
At the grocery store or in public
And I'm sick more agitated
Crazy looking people that look like skitzofrenix or demon
And what you put a photo of a composite
Democrat leaders eyes
And it's not like we're cherry pie
Every
Photo of them they look
Like
They are from another dimension
I mean I've I've met somebody people I've been in rooms with these people
And
What is it
About the eyes what is going on
Do you study
Lely medical issues that the 5G
The GMO all of it
What is what is causing people
Tow truck
Looks like this in interact like this
Medical Windows cases
This is not a medical issues a spiritual issue they are demonically infested
That's no joke
Exaggeration that there are actual
A demon
Are demonic entities that are
A possessive
These people and then what happens is the body
Play the physical body
He begins to mirror the internal
Dark Spirit structure
This is the health Ranger if you don't understand what led to the situation on
The six that you created and f******
Can cause
This is what you would say
Your political enemies are literally demon-possessed and the constitutional republic Has Fallen
You are not fighting responsible rhetoric
Bananas
I just think it's funny that this guy runs a natural news like alternative medicine site me sitting here on are talking about how people
Bullseye's can tell you what their Demons Inside
That's another thing
Lead every article about Mike Adams
I need room to look at me I have a cross-eyed like what would you think about me
Sorry is the sign of the deep
I Was Born This Way
With a demon
Sorry
These people are stupid
Don't wait out starts talking about Steve and I would say that he describes
Steve kind of like how you might describe a lunatic
We'll talk about Steve pieczenik here I'm interviewing him for 19 years
He is a Big Smoke
He was involved in one of incredible stuff
He did help write Tom Clancy's novels
And he has a twisted syre laughs at you and says you know
We Co-op
You'd he's adoration you know does all that condescending stuff
But he's a lot of good things you're supposed to 9/11 an inside job and
Wow
Alright
Have you fired David Knight
You dumb motherfuker
Really has not
Are really has not
It's such a
Great turnaround
Time to go fast
It's like a goddamn Twilight Zone
If they were night wasn't so boring like this could be a
Huge
Boost his career
Now his credibility would go off the charts if anyone were still list
I did actually list
Listen to a video of David Knight talking about Steve
After
I believe is after the 6
And I was like
Pac-Man Steven stuff
So boring
Couldn't even get
Eclipse from
Fired him because of Steve
Andy says Alex doesn't care about anything except
Traffic
William
Damn
Hamilton boring
Thanks for speaking the obvious to power
So Mike and Alex get to a wrestling with the idea that Steve made this fat
About the election
And like how if he's wrong it doesn't matter cuz any kid never come back on the show again
1910s people discussing like
Well if she is a
Which then unfortunately we're going to have two burner but we don't know yet
I notice about that he made a bet with you
At and you were going to offer to employ him if he's right and who's going to offer to never come on your show again if he's wrong
What was no downside
For him to offer that because
This is this if he's if he's playing us it's his final play
He will never want to come on your show again
How many demands he come back on
What he said does it come true
Well you know fine this morning he can you can just say no and what you going to do you no go find them and put them on camera no no
Why the final play Steve will be back in like a couple of months
Of course
Fernandez didn't happen
Done this Rodeo too many times
I guess this is a little more severe than other times though because I
Alex's feelings are hurt
Feelings in the past I just haven't heard him be like
When using you man I know that was too good that was just too good a day clips
Four stars for sure
Not as busy though not as much as that's true
Is it was worried about a dirty bomb worried about Chinese Invasion sure
He also is worried about anyone going
Protest
Do it alright
Listening do not fear
Participate in any of these Capitol protest
Not that there really any
Actually being organized by Patriot
But don't participate in those
Don't go to the capital this is all false flag operation to being set up
What you can do
Is legally and lawfully
Prepare to defend your home your family and your local neighborhood or community
Against the any kind of aggression that made
That may happen if the left
I believe they can carry out a a local Uprising and go door-to-door killing people like
What happened in the cultural revolution in China
And that's a very real possibility this guy is so dramatic
This is this is painful to listen to
Do these people not hear themselves like I know they don't care about what
I know they don't care about the words that they say
But I cannot imagine listening to somebody
Who tells me
That my political enemies are literal demons
I'm breath
Tells me
That I should
Protest
Don't
Do anything
Barricade your doors
Don't do the protesting cuz at the Trap but you should be ready to kill people who were coming door-to-door
Skill conservative something we are going to have a
Dearth of Jehovah's Witnesses if they go to the South
So no that wouldn't do it
Alex is worried about
Migration is worried about immigrants
Camiguin can just changed immigration right now
Interesting Theory by interesting I mean absurd
Motivated by racism
You look at Europe in the model they want here
Everyhome a Saison
How to take a African
Or middle eastern migrant
I did not respond your house at work for the UN
So they can do whatever they want
Further breakdown you're home I mean this is literally
The Takeover civilization
That's messed up
Why you'd assume that any immigrant that you allow and agree to have in your home
Out of the charity
Hardwood baun spyware
Cool you could just say
Okay well first off
You could say no to
Imagine
Second
If you do have somebody in your home
Don't they know how insanely hostile you are towards
Is unsafe or even the government was like okay we're going to put you in all of these
But not
This one
Those people
Are going to
Kill you
It doesn't it doesn't seem like it's in anyone's best interest so it's not paranoid
Of white nationalist types like Alex and that
That's that's all
Either you want to buy though
Yeah we can't
Quarter soldiers in our homes
God dammit you better mind
Cuz that might come back natural
I was just sort of going down this path
Gets distracted by thinking about Steve again
He doesn't like it cuz he was laughing at him
Show will attract this together
What could be the final
Final shows me you heard my
Like like you said
This could be your last time coming on
The quail said that but I thought it was funny
About all y'all just don't worry
But I won't be coming back on your she'll probably get haha
Because
Thurmond Eye Optical
I don't think he's delusional
And I think he knows something really really big
It's coming up here
And then he wants to just put the
That last Lafayette
By-the-way Jones
Thanks for helping us get martial law to have the Kappa
I think that
Steve was laughing at Alex
Spanky's also.
The problem with the way that exclusive nobody offer someone like Allen
Septra because
He's built up Steve over the years
Far too much
To sort of penetrate the facade of like the fake version of him he's presented to the audience
Which is really easy for someone like you or me
Very smart delusional person knows
Forrest Gump himself into every single
Reinforce his credibility over and over and over and over again
And now
It does look so good
Yeah it's not like Steve is a pathological liar that is aware of his
Pathology
And he's laughing at you for buying anything that he says he might
Nikolai araiza pathological liar
Who is laughing at you for not believing his lies
And you know what
Steve wasn't like laughing it out when he said he wouldn't come back on his show
He was being dismissive
He was like Rob's I'm wrong I'm not coming here shortly but don't have me on my
He was a certain confidence
I think it's so funny how
Much
Alex condescended
To the Q shop
Who is a fan of his
Who believes almost identical ship to
Steve pieczenik
And then how much you got his ass hoe
Spicy Fortune
Who is supposed to be his
Like I'm making you shaman
I'm going to prison maybe that's why
These people just exist because they it's not possible for them to have good relationships
People like they simply cannot do it
What they believe is friendship
Is exploitation and what they believe is love or affection
Is actually a secret plot
Let you know I'm calling Pete Santilli here you know everybody and the right-wing is
You further right bitter taste tell you out
Ain't that the truth
Ain't that the
The truth so
At this point
On this
Emergency Saturday broadcast
Alex gets into what I described is
Incredibly familiar territory
My goal I woke up about 3 a.m. this morning couldn't sleep
I know you're so clear like 3 a.m.
Literally got like three and I was really clear
The backboard Shield
The Met
That's what I need to go on there tomorrow
If my last show ever
And say that
Add to people and then I forgot to do that
You just said that
EXO
People download this to hard drive save it
The show next week show literally
Social Mike
Speak to that behavior gone all at my messages if it's my wife she'll because
This is the knowledge now
Future they're going to win
This is so frustrating
Yeah you know why because it was a running bit on our show cuz he kept
And then on November 24th
He actually did it
And it was sad it was a failure
What you want to do it over
But it's just so annoying
Nothing nothing matters
We did the payoff for this joke already you are you doing it again why are you hurting me this feels like it's personal
That's the personal attack I'm not a good enough comedian
To pull off doing this joke
Again we already did the season we what we like
Look
I I had one joke
Good I told for longer than
3 years and even that was a little bit too long
Was this is over
We move on we write new material we got to go Alex
You are a hack
You know where
It is attacking
It's like
Okay
You're a writer for home
Right I don't know why the
This came into my head maybe it's cuz Tim Allen.
Conservative
Tim Allen is the star of the show so there's an episode that you do
And like
A season later
He insist that you do the same story
Pretends or seem to not be aware that you've done this story already
And now you got to try and find a way to make this episode happen the second star and what
Funny again
This goddamn fake Last Broadcast
I'm Fury arable
That is terrible
If it does work and is really funny
It might have them just taking it
Very seriously cuz he's very dramatic and dramatic man
He said he's like it is such an honor to be here
You fuc
It's it's really silly all right
This goes down
Right when the fascist
State that comes in
Put us all into a bind
That folds
People like Alex
People like Mike
Any info Warriors will be needed to rebuild
Society
The evil
Fascist regime will eventually
Call
It will fall under its own arrogance will fall under
Its own mistakes
Under its the weight of its own deception
It will eventually fall
As many evil regimes have fallen in the past you have we defeated
The Third Reich
The USSR
Fell
This
American
I tried to call American this globalist
Coup against America
Will not last forever
It will fall
And when it does fall
It's people like you and I
And the listeners to the show
It will be necessary to rebuild the neck
Text Society
In the
The image
Of Christian principles and values
With added
New freedoms that weren't in the original Bill of Rights
Such as health freedom
The right
To always say no
Two medical interventions to say no to vaccines to say
That right
Which was I
I think dr. Benjamin Rush wasn't it who wanted to put that in the theater
Initial
Bill of Rights but it didn't make it in there we need that to be
The third amendment
For example
The First Amendment freedom of speech
And and religious expression Second Amendment 23rd Amendment
Freedom Health freedom
You always have the right to
Control your own body
The government can never Force anything upon you
I mean this sincerely I don't know if Mike Adams knows there's already a third amendment only agree with you
100% believe you that means he might not know about the other one
That's f******
Scary I'll tell you the one that he definitely doesn't want to know about
Anyone that involves
Some of those later ones
He's probably a little bit if you are
That was weird
I don't know what I mean like I understand the key dwells in a media space
Basic really obsesses about the first
I mean the Third
Is pretty important to that's at quarter results reflect really remember
Steve is the problem whenever people like him say stuff so insanely confident I have to be like
I swear to you
I know what this is
Question for 1 second
Can of like maybe I just mistook it maybe I could be wrong it could be the sixth amendment maybe I don't know.
In this extreme right-wing world like there was a real long stretch of time during Obama's presidency were they were obsessed
How about states rights
All that nonsense
I'd so like I don't I don't understand
It would be so easy just to say we need another amendment
The people who have spent so much time
Slapping accounts
Intuition
Telling you to read it and putting it in their pocket
Have never read it
Yep
I couldn't understand it at
Also I think that Mike's imagine Health Freedom Amendment would guarantee access to reproductive Healthcare including abortion
Guarantee the right to not have a kind I know that he's considering that
It's like a thing where the government can't force you to have medical things done
When you also want to make sure the government can't force you to not have any medical procedure you think is necessary done
That seems like an important element of Health freedom
These people are fundamentally stupid
I just can't stand it
I hate I hate this dramatic
Some weirdo this guy is so weird
Evil eyes exist I just
Isle of the Dead
Just
Junior High
Guy going through puberty kind of like everything is so serious kind of delivery
They're going to dirty bomb us yet it's an honor to be here with you Alex on your lap
After the fall of the American fascist
Say people like you and me will be needed to rebuild Society
Whether tis nobler in the mind to suffer the slings and arrows of outrageous
So
Dial Alex is supposed to be doing his last
Episode thing here
Robert Barnes
That would be the last episode
Just talks b******* about you
But
He's talking about
Okay so brought Barnes is laying out like what
Qanon dead
They targeted certain group
If you listen to this
It sounds almost identical to
The Infowars business model
They also
Targeted
Three groups
In particular
Qanon targeted first people that otherwise our crowdsourcing Grassroots
Castigated Journal
Second
Are they targeted
Soldiers at
Ex-soldiers
They targeted cops and ex-cop
And people that also were religious
Tell your people that are accustomed to believing in a source of authority independent oven separate from the state
Incorporated references to religious rhetoric in
Incorporated references to
Bible verses Incorporated
Princess dude
God this is not Gnostic Roman cults.
You're describing info
That should be his last broadcast
Because it's Barnes explaining what Alex
Unreal or less unreal
Complaining about the FBI
If is what Shakespeare he would give that Soliloquy and then immediately Beast
Esbi
And he's made a big deal about how they're like saying that
He caused the uprising
Are you playing
The storming of the capitol
He comes clean a little bit about what they actually had questions
Myself
FBI contacted our security people want to bring them over to talk to him
Oh we don't care about Alex going to talk to you
Oh okay
I don't worry about it we just got false reports that you guys were in the capital
Just tell us you weren't the Caballero
So show Sam was
Aya your cameraman was
He's doing a plug when he went in do you know how he know that
Ateez being broadcast
On your website
I got it from bam. Video
Also if I were the FBI to would be like
Let's talk to your security people
Not you you lying piece of s***
I've seen your deposition
Do not help
So hire Larry klayman for this one though so it'll be great
Alex talk to Barnes about how bad Q is for a while
And it's annoying
And then he gets on his own
Any
Reeds
A fake Cicero quote
Okay
And real
Quote
His favorite quote
The man in the arena
The Teddy Roosevelt quote
Dogma bystanders and the reviewers they mad or not
The man in the arena he falters and that is okay Paul Wright
Kind of s***
So much
I think it's the only thing that Gives Life Meaning anymore
Then
He goes a little bit of
We got Roosevelt
We got Cicero
Oakshore
This
That a friend of mine City
Text message this morning
Subject forwarded from a friend
A man named Tom Nicholson post on Facebook as account
Sports car that you just bought
Now I'm an approach to told him that the money used by the car
Go to bed
Thousands of less fortunate people
Industry of the
Stop the tractor
Her dumbass
Also built the desire for people to have nicer things
But then to build the desire for better medicine a better technology a better future
I'm sorry I'm not ready when he said
The response the man made in
Internet
Read a story of stated on Facebook below
I got it looked at my
Corvette
I wonder how many people
Could have been fed for the money that sports car cost
I replied I'm not sure
A lot of families in Bowling Green Kentucky who built
Prepare the people who made the tires that fit the people who
Are the components
It said the people in the copper mine and mine the copper for the wires
Alex is reading a chain email that your grandma would send you
Yeah I believe this is the meme this is Valium meme that's like
Military man was in the professor's room in the professor was like
Military man stood up
It was like I hate liberals and then
I was like
I don't know
I thought this was supposed to be your life broadcast you're reading a chain email what is going on
You know I said I just made my last broadcast really good but I
It's just too heavy of a subject that was my last broadcast from here
I'm just too tired already but I'm going to write some notes tonight
Tomorrow Sunday show
For 6 p.m. and give you my view on the world
So Sunday I'll write a note
To your dad it is
Yes
And that's why we have to
We're not done with Saturday yet
Saturday a.m.
It just a remarkable way
Anybody who really thinks that Alex Jones is like
Sincerely religious
Enjoy
So I will end
Transmission with the Lord's Prayer
Our Father who art in heaven Hallowed be thy name thy kingdom come thy will be done on Earth as it is in heaven
Give us this day our daily bread and forgive us our debts
We forgive our debtors
Temptation but Deliver Us from Evil
Last Kingdom
Power the glory
Forever amen
Alright I appreciate the crew
I appreciate their work I would just ask to Lester's
I don't know how long to be on there
We got baby. You need a lot of more Baba sell-out wintersun for your immune system
Monticello
I don't know about the Lord's Prayer going back quickly into an ad but
The f*** out of here I am selling T-shirts
And we have asthma shark
Designed by one of our better and Friends
I said Trader Joe's is. Joe Biden
Was China and Russia in
Ukraine and Iran
Trader Joe's at the Fun shirt it's fun enforced
Dot-com
All sizes
For adults and children
And so I suggest you get the shirt
Infowars store
Thomas limited edition shirt
Adolescent
Dictator
They're installing
That's why Steve pieczenik said I was my last show with you cuz it's
The joke's on me thanks
Or he really believes what he's saying anything's going to
Job here
Somehow
B lasagna
If that job moonshot
Anyways interesting guy but I think he's a little more on the devil side of the Angel side
Don't tell him that
Play top down.
People the way
They're in the cyst
That's who I'll always be
That's my job
Okay again brake jobs
The crew seems really mad
I hate
How comfortable
These people are
With demons existing
On airplane
And running
Thanks
The point where you would
Be like
Here's a fun t-shirt
About this
Demon
It's running the world yeah yeah it is it is a little bizarre for him to be like
We made this pun t-shirt to kevil fun with the dictator
Nhr globalist dictator
Very weird that's that's so annoying
Central threat
And you're like I will make this fun
We're onto Sunday now
Final broadcast this bit is finally going to be put
Well Alex can't get to it right away because there's news
And he has a new
A group
To blame know what happened on The Clique
Told you that
The day of the event
After I told you who the operator was where he came from in Utah
Towelette / 102 Hood address of trump supporters
Elmo videos
My employer
Look like
You know that.
I look like I employed them
Actually
Pat's Steaks
Potatoes
Fight
As sure as hell we did about who they were
They were telling the crowd they were probably but
They were boogaloos
No Boogaloo boys
No
Flaps
Got to throw throw the Boogaloo boys overboard
About man
I really like how Alex said boogaloos
Really really hit it really did
So apparently this is how he's going
Going to get around
The fact that there were a bunch of people who
Where
Okay for sure man
Yeah I assumed you were roads isn't on this Sunday broadcast
Be making up a story about Stewart Rhodes wife
Getting run over dog
In hiding
Anyway Alex has a new video
Of the Boogaloo boys
Sure
I got this is so funny
Alex
He's so bad at this this whole thing
And it's just so incredible because
Try to get this out on Pussycats out of here
Gateway pundit
Mary Claire
Wait what went on the water
How much at the first big one
She told you about
You can bet your bottom dollar you'll be seeing this one
The first one
But
Those are inside
Nightclub don't talk about flight
Mommy as Rolf
Flight Club
Lafayette Club
I sent him so he chose me
Why wait that's
Exactly against the rules of Fight Club
I just
That's
Alex Jones
Then Tucker Carlson sent me this clip I'm going to leave it there you just said everything
This clip was sent to you by Tucker Carlson
And if that's true
That tells us all we need to know about Tucker Carlson
To get a comment
From Tucker on that because I would imagine he would not
Admit
To sending information to Alex being a source
On account of Fight Club
Being ruled by still talk about Fight Club I would imagine that he would say no idea
An hour to have to wrestle with wife
No one will be publicly associated with him
But they'll have his employees on their shows
Anyway
At this point
We've not decided that the Boogaloo boys
Are going to be blamed for anybody who appears to be
Write a right-wing whatever
Feel-Rite wig and we got blue glue for people who are gone for people who are weird
Even though
Sure
So now that's settled
It's time to go back to familiar territory
Over 7000 strong migrant Caravan
And this will be hundreds of thousands if not Millions like it you're up at the UN plan as soon as they knew the body would let him in
They began the
Guatemala
Here it is
Migrant Caravan narratives are back
Just
It just do it
Take 4 years off
End run reruns where you just edit inviting over Obama it
It's got to be the same thing
A lot of similarities how much time you can take off if you're just going to recycle the same show
Just run reruns
I really hope that you have
Drafts of all of your
Articles from the Obama days
Yeah man my grits are
Coming to America showing their plan
War doesn't look like it did in Vietnam War
This is Modern War
This is global agency
Take your vaccines and roll over to die
Remember
In the next two years
I mean
Almost kind of feels like you
Say have a good answer be destroying the cap
Yeah yeah it does sound like we are at War
Yeah and the enemy is
Demons trying to bring it immigrants
That sounds some suspiciously like white nationalist talking really feels like that
Oh really
Just part of the Great
Replacement
Uses people as a weapon
They turn their food off the trailer jobs off
You just think you're staying home for
If you monster
Vacation
No it's collapsing the Border
When you become poor the third world starves to death
When the first world collapses the third world dies
How many
Time did I drill that
And now in Europe
Everywhere
Borders
Collapsing
Giant
World populations that don't have jobs
And don't have any structures are coming here to do what
Collapse the infrastructure
Do not go to work
Forget you to say you're not essential
Amistad Street
Then they come in
Tell you
That you got to open your borders up
Because the third world
And then I get here and they're organized
In the political weapon
And political groups
From the beginning
Year and a human
Refugee camp in Marxist
Venomous ideology
Projected by Mark Zuckerberg
Projected by Jeff Bezos
Rejected by all them on record commanding
That's quite a sentence
Yeah you know.
Concerns that it might not be awake nationalist thing
Yeah I wasn't really made it pretty clear there
I would say over this territory so many times in the past
Best when he's gotten
Into the the past Caravan there it is now
This is is very much
Watch based on a white
Identity Sierra Toyota
No
I would say
Do behavior that he's engaging in
And the way that he's framing a lot of these ideas
AR
Very dangerous
They're the sort of things that I do think
Sound a lot like
Insight
Violence of people that you suspect might be Emigrant
This is the Takeover this is Modern Warfare
Using giant third-world starting horde
Starvation or invasion
And the un's got to manage with the lap every damn bit of it and they're going to swap your bread city they're going to swap your
Military
Attack
I don't know what you would expect the outcome of that to be other than like
Rank xenophobia
I am the possibility of violence
Directed towards people
That are
Determined
Tubi
Immigrants whether or not they ask
We are followed by a sign at every border that says whites only
Yeah it's it's pretty bad
It's not on
Familiar territory for Alex
Certainly
But I just constantly end up getting in a position where like
The world is really like
Serious
You know
I just don't understand how Alex cannot be living in a world of reflection about how serious things are
And how unhinged people are
And how how dangerous we are in a Miss like a misinformed
Populous
People are living outside the prism of reality
Don't believe
Leave
That he is a committed believer of the things
That are distorted reality
Absolutely not
He's
Monetize
Exploiting
The fact that other people living in to take reality
That he preaches
You wouldn't be able to operate
If he actually believe the things that he say
He wouldn't be able to work
You wouldn't be able to do any of that s***
He would be dead by now because he would have
Storm the Austin Capitol
10 years ago
It's not
8/8 it's nonsense and I I I just constantly
I think like wild that will take
Take it seriously and you just never does never does
It's a mean yeah yeah
It's hard to
Say anything you know when you ask like
How do these people not take it more seriously and it
It's just like scream
Mother
It's mine can't matter that much though
I guess so f****** much I guess
It's talking about how his enemies are ugly and they want to kill you read about this
I don't know
I would say this isn't safe
It's all weird disreputable
Creature
That's all they can get
Cuz they're such a
But no good looking no well-spoken no honorable man
Will even serve this
But it still doesn't matter
Men don't take the
The field
Because you didn't join the fight
And the fight is informational is cultural
It's spiritual and it's about information
And it is about
Non-compliance it is about symbolism
Won't matter if they're going to hurt you so bad
Because they have a nature like a child molesters got to write the child
Or murderers.
Have the drive and this desire and they thought I
Power over you
Their stock go up at Amazon
Now they just got to do it
Put you down
And they're going to go and go and go and go and go they can
Will you stop that
I can't stop until you stop them
Wild
It's not it's not a good look
Overall
You know what I've always thought I've always thought that the Democrat
Secret where
Could be
Governing the country with
And they refused
To do that
For the same reason Alex refuses to take the
Like seriously
If you material improve the lives
I'm just running my
I'm losing my mind
I understand
And if you think that Alex is
Solely driven by money
Then I would
It suggests that this must be what everyone keeps telling him to do more
Humpty Dump
Brian stelter 100000
He later bitching no one watches me
You are one that I mean
You molest the truth
Filter problematic
We have to be clear-eyed about what is a domestic Terror threat
But also very careful not to exaggerate
There's a domestic Terror threat it's called your speech
I-24 Americans at the Capitol who's Orion a small riot
It's the worst things in Pearl Harbor
You're a child
He plays all these games
Let's go back to the shack
The pot
It's interesting cuz it was supposed to be as fake last show
Entire segment
Complaining about a Brian stelter
Peace on his fake last show cuz that the time capsule
He's done one of these where he just plays a Brian stelter interview that Justin Smoak this paper
Just a completely normal I was listening to it on like
I'd like first of all he's not saying
Is responding to it is not a hot take it is a pretty
Soft conversation about misinformation on
You take Brian stelter do and just a regular old like hey how have you been and turn it into a 10-minute logs
Scary so scary
The truth look at his eyes
For Old Times Sake here's a minute
40 of Alex
Just getting really mad at stelter
We have to be clear-eyed about what is a domestic Terror threat
But also very careful not to exaggerate
Overstate
Undue fear
In this country right now
I think that's actually very careful here.
Just because someone may believe that other
President did not win
The election are the
Did not win or that someone believes in qanon
Doesn't mean that there are
Going to go
Go pick up arms
It's like I'm questioning election we don't put them in the FEMA camp right away
Did he say that
And them all weekend
Do psychological scripture reading
Super predatory Superdry
Super Evil
Continue
Possible counselor ever be a solution of real clear. Listen to this
Information crisis
Is there a final solution enough
But how do we deal.
People
You know saw them with suitcases
Georgia
Closing things
What's a comeback I'm going to be nice
Play the clip on a
It's hard to look
What does it matter
They know that the global is word is through stelter
And so here is this this this this
They call us that
Brian
Uebelhor
I'm not saying that he's not at a public
Figure oriented accomplish anything I'm just saying he's Brian stelter
Brian
The Voice
The globalist
The voice of
The globalist stelter house small potatoes everybody who's a big deal is
I am I just
I think it's fascinating cuz you know like if this is the pretend last show
Make
Since I mean like
Alden
Hates Brian stelter
I can't
Figure out except the Brian stelter has mentioned Alex a couple times and he comes off as a less
Then
Alex's definition of masculine man
Exit that bothers Alex
On some level
Right
It feels like he's been emasculated by a less masculine man in Alex's eyes and just say
Alex is a dumb
Bill because I don't think
Alex leaving his mind
Where has Alex
Is clearly thinking about the times.
All the time
Is Brian stelter so much
You see this like
Just it come out on the show if these these outbursts is amazing
I'm so glad that I've passed
Customer friedersdorf
And now it's a process
Unhealthy healthy
So Alec
It's comes back from break
He promises
Knocking interrupt
And they're just me this is so
Text TI-84
And you're just watching these criminals
Talk about it
Play
Few minutes of this I'm going to try to shut off.
Have to work on the broader disinformation problem
Turn down
The anger see from that huge percentage of Republicans who believe that the election was stolen
But yeah
He's on
God is so much stelter
He's talking
About
Halak
We're at War
To not be enslaved
There comes a point when powerful organizations and groups
Poseidon
No matter what happens
Committed to the fight
We are now under globalist attack
I tried to warn him over decades
Barry Goldwater Cleon skousen so many others warned before I was even born
They believe that we were so strong
We could not fall
From within
Fact of slavery
Ambassador persecution
And the full thrust of the globalist attack
Level never-before-seen
That's why tomorrow I'm going to do a special transmission
You
Because everyday now is precious go f*** yourself man
Not good I can't believe that by the likes of you I want to start fires I don't want to
Start building fires I want to start large brush fires in the street I understand to let everyone know
What is happening yeah
There's too many people who are unaware
He is doing this again I need someone to know that he is doing this
So annoying to because
Like he did nothing but waste time on a Sunday show
There's so much just like
It's the Boogaloo boys that's
That's who we don't like now
Tucker Carlson's Mysore swoops bike club
Yeah
Helter Skelter hate dudududududu
So tired dad
There's this
Last clip here from Sunday's fitting cuz it's kind of how Alex wraps up
I will say that it is exciting for me because now on Friday Orr show we will find
Finally get his actual
Alex goes out on the 7th
Just perfect
I'll just recap what we started the show weather for Henderson
Information
We know the boogaloos leftist group with Aunt
A few hundred people
Stacy attack
Only the Q folks were dumb enough to go into get media attention
Andrew
People that went in non-violently to be set up and arrested
When they've arrested
They both are released later
They did their job well they said
America
Trump knew his supporters were patriotic
He didn't decide anything they went down there to say we see the election fraud we have
The number to Shallotte
Fought back he did the right thing
Key
Didn't roll over
He didn't submit
Infowarsstore.com and get t-shirts books film
Got a bunch of stuff about to sell out
Your body X2
X3
Vitality of DNA Force Plus
They're all there
Infowars store
Dot-com
Separately
This is New World Order this is 20/20
A reading when I was 21 blackjack
Hey Google show Wrecker
I was into that stuff
Again
Here we are
Every generation go through something every surgeon original something really big
We're going through it right now
Job
Amazingly
Important report
Major pop artist exposing chemtrails
And tell Bob
Don't do it I hope that you will share
Supposed to
Pennsylvania Lottery
Delray's video
Freaking trails at the Country Club
As a report
This is very important report this music video
Okay
He is a lot of words to say that the Patriot movement is filled with stupid
Affordable Towers
It's 5828 didn't understand why you tells his version of the story
It's far more exciting than saying that the Patriot movement is a bunch of stupid double Towers
Spotswood Pizza until he would say
Man
I love like I I want to see what the most
Trivial thing Alex would call it important report
Fighting demons
Who are overthrowing the United States Republic
Destroying the cons
Constitution
We need upwards of two amendments now
And I will tell you this right now we're going to go out to our special reports
That's right
It is a Looney Tunes cartoon the here we go
For my new reporter here at Infowars Lana Del Rey
Jesus
God what a ride what is
Happening
I don't know are we are we fake or is he
I can't tell anymore so no
Yeah I just don't know
Don't feel like I learned much from the strip
I'm glad I got the benefit of his vows
Dozens of books
Totally it's nice
Toosii
Multiple in
Instances of him just reading Wikipedia Pages poorly
God this is dumb
The show is so dumb
Excited for Friday though
Well I mean
Can't wait for the second broadcast broadcast
It'll be better then
The November 24th
For sure I would hope so
Yeah
Multiple.
Yeah I just think it'll be something interesting on the day of the inauguration like
I I hope
Did everything go smoothly in the world now we're recording this on Tuesday comes out on Wednesday
I hope I hope it's a
Uneventful day by and large
I also hope that Alex
Prize or something she wear I hope it's
I hope he throws a hatchet or something like I hope it's not just moppy Alex
There's potential for likes
Some real
Performance
And I hope we see something as opposed to nothing
But I hope that the something we see isn't this like
This sucks that Sunday show
The like
The hard shift into like
Immigrant bashing is really not good
I know that's a normal thing for Alex
Absent
For a little while or at least on the back burner
Really don't like to see a coming forward again
It's really annoying
The full
Let's direct our attention away from all Democrats
Directly
Towards
Minorities of any
Shape
Specifically ones that aren't White
Is is
Normal but it was
It was nice whenever they just wanted to kill us all equal
You know
There wasn't there was there was a feeling of
Hey I don't know
Jordan we will be back
But until then we have website
Where on Twitter
We are inviting I go to bed Jordan
Girls on Facebook
Doing God's work
But until then I'm going to go
Hyundai CX
I'm Daryl rundus
I'm telling Mike Adams
Grow the f******
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color