Air Jordan
I have great respect for its knowledge B
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Acknowledge
Ceramic novelty beverage isn't Just a Touch about Alex Jones
Smoochie
Go so far as to say pepper in a recipe
Sprinkle or perhaps
I'm subverting the Forum
I like it I like it how it how are you doing I have a question
What is your brights
My bright spot today Jordan is I first of all I accept this already.
F****** I don't care.
Sucker for like Lovecraft
Themed
Storytelling that sweetie
Eternal darkness is one of my favorite video games
Sohal time course
It's great whenever we played Mansions of Madness together you get greatly into insist on holding the iPad
Voice narrator
I love it
And I was I was looking
Sitting around for cheap
The game
Video game reviews
I was looking for something like $5 rain
Is that was trying to expand my son called Lovecraft untold stories
I'm a mark
I'm buying this
Barbie getting 5,000 in return
If it's a letter is not from a Nigerian prince but it's in someone in innsmouth
Miskatonic University would like a donation
I got it and I was really enjoying it
First level of it was
Pretty fun
And then he got
Absurdly hard
It got like on
Farrell Evans apart
I actually looked into it because I was a kid to Camp rewrite the reviews online
Unfairly hard at that is like
Not balanced
And it's true
Yeah but it was also like not
It was just really hard
Am I kind of I was playing around with it a little bit
Here's the bright spot was that I didn't
Back down to the
Call Tay
I kept trying and then I learned
I realize like this is kind of video games
Like if you playing Mega Man to his f****** hard
It has that sort of difficulty it's just like
It's really it's
It's what I enjoy anyway I
Did beat the second level
Do something that I have not felt a ton
A video game
What are these open-world games that I enjoy are like
Yeah you get things done and maybe you beat a castle in
Monastery in Assassin's Creed
Difficult it can be yeah
Yeah do you know
Achievement
So cool
How about you my bright spot Dan may sound counter-intuitive but I mean this wholeheartedly as a bride
Okay my bright spot
Is failure
I think that's kind of a share this
As you know I started trying to stream a little bit of video games on
And it is
Gunn disastrous people had asked every time the address
Twitch TV j.b. Holmes 3209
Okay. That was the important thing
Disastrously everytime
The audio issues
Really it's really fast because it's fun to teach myself new stuff
At 33 like I've never touched the software on this before
It's fun to learn all the things that I'm terrible at and
Require new equipment for and all that stuff
And it reminded me of when I started doing stand-up
I've just like
I failed
For 2 years straight
And as I'm doing this I'm so frustrated cuz I couldn't figure it out properly and I felt like I was disappointing the people
Who actually came to see it and I was really grateful to them and I wanted to do a good job for them
And I failed miserably
And then I remembered
I can fail so hard
Persolog
Eventually I got good at it to the point where I think I can do the same thing here failed the equator
Play the Wild streams did not always go
Appreciation for why I have such a
Difficult time with my being like that let's get back to doing livestream headache
But I wish you luck with that I know you'll get it figured out and it'll be great before watching the Stream
Because it
It also means that I'm trying new things
Good out of the gate at new things
That's true really good and humbling and I've appreciated it a lot you are second level of Lovecraft
Challenging
3 year old people anymore on supposed to be able to use
Computer app
So Jordan
Today
Yes sir we have an unexpected
Twist
Yes Alex is out of studi
No
We are on our last episode on Wednesday I had said that today we were going to be
Listening to the end of trump
Presidency and Inauguration Day
On Alex's show and I cannot deliver that
And I'll explain why
First reason
Alex's
Fake last episode thing
Carried over into this episode
I know you knew that last episode we talked about the 17th Alex tomorrow will be my fake
Could not
Follow the thread up
Then it turned out
That on inauguration day
It was an all-day affair
So that's going to have to be on Monday
Origami covering January 20th on Monday today we're going to be talking about
18th and 19th
Blackjack no
No baby sorry
And yeah it's rationed on Monday I just need a bit more time to prepare that good
A lot of
A lot of stuff
To go through
A lot of disappointment
Harrison Smith
Posting
I'm sure a good bit of that I don't know no
Before we get down to business on today's episode though are we
The last
Proper shows
Trump died
The last days when Trump could
Do something weird is on air before we get
So first Nathan asked thank you so much you're now a policy wonk
Next door's donation Drive
Next Nicholas leikola us
Remind money probably the Best Buy linotype.
Nicklaus
Thank you so much and I'll probably want
I'm a policy wonk
Text Thomas Bean
Very much Tom eb800 NWA
Thank you so much you and I'll probably walk
I'm a policy wonk
Picture very much 1 800 MW Hogs
Very much so
Derek and it's spelled darrick money the second best way to spell Derek
Sebastian
I think it's much of an hour technocrat
The waffle witch
What's the business
Money off that heroin
Are you can blow people's minds
Is Waffle
Yes that's true they are to make delicious too
Waffle iron
Got five bucks
Probably
Also wafflewich
Should be in a Miyazaki movie if not already pay a lot
Does level four
Super unfair
Contacts drop
From Today Show
War with these people not just on their eyes
I'm not special
He always sounds exactly like the
People that he says they're demons
Yeah
I just
You know I don't take someone seriously when they're like I'm fighting
Demons all the time
Now it's a little silly
Non-Stop
Demons all the time
It's brutal not fair
So we start on the 18th and of course on the 17th Alex had decided he was going
To do his last child
What you again already did last November
Between his food and fifth last show somewhere in that range on Saturday
That he was going to do the last
Broadcast
As he was in the middle of a
So human Mike Adams is a very dramatic
Oh yeah
On that Saturday Alex got distracted by Robert Barnes lawyer extraordinaire coming
Tell you all about qanon
I meant Alex realize I got I can't do it today or tomorrow
From Sunday came in
Did not do it
Decided to point the finger at the Boogaloo Bois right for the capitol storm
And then he's like I can't handle it
I'll do it tomorrow
So the 18th Monday is in
Supposed to be
The last show ever
The final broadcast
Great
We're doing it
Is a restart
Jersey
Jim
Courts of the state just seized 150
Thousand dollars every dime
The company
Payroll
Adipex
Build a building and to pay for the insurance
Close
Cash donations
Only God knows call themselves the church or BLM
It'll be protected on the First Amendment and all of us should say
You're part of the Church of freedom
I really think I'm an incorporated Church
Believe in Freedom
Okay that that was inevitable
Time
Basically
Literally s*** all over the sickness for not having a church in they shouldn't have the protections of the First Amendment
Really screwed up not doing this
When Trump was in office
Because Trump wasn't going to process
Churches for 501 c 3 violation
But that might
Games that might go back now
To where you can't do
Political organizer
It's basically the game here and finally getting around to it
Church
You never did the Church of blade
Because I would have joined the Church of
Sure
I don't know how Alex isn't already at church
He constantly talks about God and
Like this show is
Deeply religious thing where he's fighting demons all day
I don't either science-fiction or
One of the two
Both of which could be a church news and politics AFL Ron can do it
So Jordan I don't know if you know this but America is dead
It didn't die
Inauguration
And that's only cuz Alex
You can definitely put
United States of America
Born July 4th 1776
Side of satanism
January 21st
Whoops
Still writing gelatiamo still write in July on those checks
This is why you got to double-check before you put the death date on the tombstone
Course so that's all I'm in Rock
Yeah
Before Bernie had to drop out of the race
Also get a real socialist to kill America
I know that you were taking issue with him saying you know Merrick was born July 4th 7
And I don't to parse that right now
What I do want to talk
About is it this seems to imply
The Alex doesn't believe that life
Begins at conception
It seems to me
This is an indication
Bertha is looking like if your pronation your pro-choice
I think that's the reality
To celebrate the Independence Day the day when someone came up with the idea
1617 somebody was like man I think we can do it or maybe a thousand years before that
Erik the Red is out here man I think that these states should be more night
The beginning of the the protesting
The crown began in the colonies
Then I don't know anyway I just thought that was kind of funny
When it became a
Twinkle in the eye of subreddit
Missionary by Alex at the beginning of this episode
So Alex decides to
Talk about the one ring
Sure
The globalist
Apparently they all want power in the Rings
Naturally I give power to the
The Ten Kings
Louboutin rings
9 rings
Whatever but there's one to rule them
But there's three for the Elven Lord right
Seven for the dwarf Lords
Alex gives himself chills
The globalist
That that that is why
And there's only competition with global it's about who gets the AI take over
Usai
10 rings
Christian allegory
He specifically said it was not for
The Insider knowledge
Went out of his way
When they
Heather's 16
Split ring that controls him all that sing
Spirituality
Got you
I believe it's 9 rings given to Mortal man
Doomed to die
Literally in the poem
You make a good point about token really resisting allegory as well
Nuclear bomb right news like interesting
No yeah
You did say that it was a religious story
You know it was a
The Christian story
Unintentionally at first and then intentionally upon reflection
Who is Jesus
I think that's a good answer
Yeah I just I love it anytime Alex is like talking and he oppresses himself or he freaks
I'm self out man I mailed that
I absolutely got that one
Solve that problem
Going on about how there's a
They have been in the riot
Capital
App for the storming of January 6th
Who might be inconvenient for him right agent
But you can tell
Alex can tell he has a special sense
Are you got you got FBI agents in there running
It seems the video you showed later other people in full camo and full mask
Definitely
Weather
What's going on
This just makes me think of the time that we spent listening to the immediate aftermath of the Boston bombing
I totally whenever Alex was like I can
Tell who everybody is just by looking at them I can see the way they're standing and I know this guy's Hast
Did you rescue team all over
When do you don't know shitt
Alex proves that the the blood of numenor has grown thin
Alright
How many more do I got I think you got way more but I don't know how much basically.
Oh boy
I mean like
People that he's talking about I think
I don't know what the video he's referring to but I assume based on the
Prescriptions probably the oathkeeper
Folks were there
But now a Joe Biggs
Former employees employee grambo
He going to prison hilarious is going to
Do prison
Hard for a while
He flips on a lot of more important I don't even know I don't even know that
Going to do much I do I doubt it
Who's more important than command of The Proud boy yeah that was pretty easy to take out
What if I mean I assume he can flip
Congressman
On account of them committing the crime
Hey I don't know
I don't know what he knows or what he's up to but
It's interesting to see this path
He's gone from
I didn't gone working at Infowars trying to I get pizza gate going
Ted Cruz to finally go to prison
Also just
Before we got on are here today on are what the f*** am I talking about
There's a new story those breaking about the William W
Who's the guy
Who had a big beard pictured at the Capitol with along with Q shaman
And love the headlines really stressing that he went to the Capitol because
Alex told him to
And I think people are making more out of that then they should think you can do
Much with that no I mean like
I saw some people tweeting
To be effective like Alex ordered him
Indigo sure even though
Star the rawstory article about it the freezing of it was a little bit iffy
Because as far as I can tell from the actual information
He just said that he knew that there was a rally at the Capitol
Because Alex
Brightside meet there at 1
Write what you got to assume is Alex
Wanting people to go to the stage
You Wiki
Conceivably going to be having a rally at it would be nice
People ran
With stories
They would at least like send you an e-mail
I mean I imagine that the reason they don't is because you would be like
Hey could you add more nuanced and maybe like more Nuance means fewer clicks so we're not going to talk to
I mean I don't know if I could even be of much help with this but I wish people would recognize that like the more
You put Alex
In the crosshairs for this
Toad when it's something like
What you see in those stories about the
Just got the mower works
Alex's favorite holiday
Yeah you just shouldn't you shouldn't do things like that they playing into his now you wind up you wind up not just letting
Off the hook
But
Doing a
I would call it pulling a Rogan
Where you accidentally give him more
Credibility that
Bye-bye NTB
Also write him a new narrative
Yeah I mean really this is this is like
Sam kind of stuff where it's like you can't blame the dog
You know what I'm saying
Or was that him
Yeah I'm pretty sure that that was Satan and stuff
The ring
Why I hated the beginning of the show it was very boring
There's nothing going on
And thankfully about an hour in our and Alex
Condenses
What he's been talk
Talking about for the last hour
Last hour
Is confirmed the Alex Jones story
The Boogaloo boys
Beyond the Southern Poverty Law Center 80 on the FBI
No
Capital
It's been confirmed Apparently that is a fair
Condensing of most of what he spent all of his time talking about but he didn't
Is any of this you haven't confirmed any of it
He just believes that
Saying something repeatedly is the same thing as good
Confirming it
How about this
How about fuckyour William Watson
Article
Alex doesn't get to do this
And all you do is
Go through what he did on the 6th
And how he lied about it immediately and how he's lying about it now and how we don't get
Get to let this go
He doesn't get to go on and talk about how
There's going to be problems and everybody's going to have their balls cut off
He has to say
If I lie to you
And I was full of s***
And everybody should Braden article about that
And also there's writing article that in the weed mentions that he believes he's constantly fighting demons
Yeah
We have the FBI in through the Southern Poverty Law Center in the ATL they were running a Boogaloo boys
To do all this right get the get through storm and going
Weird they were buddies on people who were Patxi's apparently
They were just there to be like
Buckle
Usher
And to be killed
An end to be arrested
A sacrificial
Dummies just like in Spies Like Us
Yeah
Spotify
Sicko free
Disgusting
Who's weird
So then you're saying that
They did it
I don't know
Are you saying that the real people at the the Patriots
It's did everything
Spies Like Us recently
I think maybe his kids are coming to such an age that I got to get in some of those classic comedy there
That's fair
Yeah
I think
That I'm noticing about Alex
Around this time is that
It's pretty much just
It's very Doom
It's very much
Dude the country is no more the devil has taken over the United States
Yeah but you would expect it to
BMV
He's been yelling about it for a long time instead of kind of comes in this form it's like
This is just
Going to inside people to
Violence
Want to come back and talk more about what you're witnessing there in our former capital
Global control we are now officially occupied
Joe Biden will be installed in about
46 hours
As the first dictator of the United States okay
And it will all be shut down after that
Should we think SBR was the first dictator of the United States manage to avoid
I appreciate that I was going to go straight at you
No DC's the former capital we're now under complete occupation or riding is a dictator
Call Ray
Okay well what has your show
Cahiers
Suggested people do when those circumstances are achieved
I think you know
Couple days left for Trump
To be an officer
He's got he's got criminals to say you
Can go free well actually I was a prediction about the house
Straits of action
Massage tomorrow
I'm predicting that right now
My gut tells me the trumpet good
The final Crucible
Snake eyes
Came up came up just short on that prediction
You don't get to do this
Alex probably very disappointed
Yeah why did he think that would happen
Alex's get we heard on that Sunday show he's getting back into the migrant Caravan
Fever Bass
Narratives
I've noticed about him is he has a
Absolute
Inability to estimate sizes of groups he will say like
100000 people is 10 million
Gumballs in this jar
He guesses a million every time or 7
He's not good at estimating he's looking at a picture of like a caravan
Of migrants
And he's just
So many more people
And if you don't administrative America it will be
By admitting run
Admitting This Is Love
Jamaica
Hundreds of thousands that Caravan here a few years ago that Trump stop
Look like
Insignificant
What's going on
Newscast about the 7000
Thousand let me give you a news flash
It
I've seen footage
That's just the first group of you and Friends
Imma go to your phone calls but that's what's happening
Prove it
Look
Are you notice this
It sucks
Thanks
These sorts of stories
Really get under Alex's skin more than a lot of other ones
Really mad
Chunk of this episode of the borders closed
Who is home and he's
PNC
He's really really
Like
Down in like freaks out
And more Muslims and I'm used to supply shocks
He addresses the idea that this was going to be his last show
Downhill for plants
Alright imma go to 137
Call
Michael
Steve John
Christian Houston Scott
Easy Richard now
Quit quit
Broadcast
And by that I'm going to keep doing shows but
You understand
I believe they're going to shut everything down the next few months they're going to blow up Federal Building
They're going to put poison in the Water Supplies I mean it's over
You understand your only shot you got is realizing that we're screwed
EVS bossing Intuit
We're a trained group of monkeys in this country
We're not what Americans used to be
Constitution
We're a joke okay
He's in a bad mood
Yeah bad mood has started
Covering this story about the migrants
Yeah
Turns
Pretty f****** extreme
I mean he's talking about blowing up federal building poisoning the water supply
And like
Just candy asses
No and it was the rock hookah because you apologized
I apologize for not getting famous Republican The Rock
Alex goes from there now they're going to do all this
This s*** we're all just going to let the rock get away with that
That right everybody's just agreed like I don't worry about it you're the Rock
Endorsed all of the horrifying things but will still let him be a movie
I mean
Sure I don't know what his politics are anymore and I don't know I don't know how I
I look
Vince McMahon is eluded
That is true
I don't know I'm not going to I'm not going to sit here and defend the rock but I'm also not going to say that I know
I'm not speak at the RNC
20 years ago
Anyway Alex gets deeper
Into Doom
Fantasies
We ever beat this
Believable
They just begun
Pension fund
Power off the oil off
It's over man
It's over it's all gone it's all over
ATL forces
I wish
And deserves it
Good they're not God glad just let them have their way now
All your games are over
All the TV watching all the laziness that joins over
It's over
You don't care
There's so much
Yeah there was a jarring shift into that commercial
Yeah so I guess we should
Not storm Capitol building the senate for
I don't understand
If I recall
I do believe
But Alex said
God appointed him
To defeat Satan
And he was the only person that Satan was worried about
Yeah and that's why Satan tried to recruit him when he was younger
With all the hot cheerleaders
So
I mean now that he's done I assume saying
Bike
Dodged a bullet on that one
I guess God isn't that powerful now is
Wow you look don't blame God for Alex
The only person you can play
Is there s*** I don't believe God at all anymore damn I do think that if you take everything out too seriously
Then yes
He has been defeated by the devil
By extension so is God
Yeah but also
I could see a world where God
Sitting off at the size like I didn't tell you to do that
Keep my name out your mouth
Guess who you've been working for the whole time you idiot
You're controlled opposition for the devil
False flag
Alex believes
Everyone
Play the news
Like all over
MSN
Everyone's calling
For people to be thrown
Champs
Fans just people who like
What kind of people who are
Bad w
FEMA FEMA
5 years ago
We have one clip
I probably saw 5
Eclipse this morning
We need to arrest all three of them right now
One Clip 5
Nobleman
Car polishing
Or their jet boat
Caring about this
Don't you have both
All the successful man
Keep Their Heads down
Makes me sick
You're not successful
You're the one
Again Alex is furious that rich people are
Doing more
To support the Infowars
Or something
I think you can
Read between the lines a little bit on that we've heard this this chorus
Before
I do think that this is him
Trying to do like
Posterity last
Last Broadcast
Play Cafe class broadcasting he's getting really mad and I'm trying to get is Howard Beale moment
Mad as hell not going to take it anymore
Kind of thing
And it's really
Really funny
Because
He starts time-traveling
Is mine started traveling through time
You brings out a story from 2008
Excited
This is this is it folks
Just makes me mad
Country
It's Kismet
Literally sucked into a black hole
Literally
You understand they are announcing shock collars
And shock bracelets and bracelets
I have vanished
Pump It Up
To show your covid obtaining attracts you at
Actual meaning about having a shocker in it
I love my shocker
I'm not joking
No but you're talkin about a thirteen-year-old news story about something that the DHS was
Considering and didn't Implement there is that
So sad is that
Yeah that might be an issue Yelp
Because we heard him talk about that
Episode
And the problem is Dan
Liberals don't have any memory
But I also heard him bring it up on
This episode
He talks about how they were going to do that for you remember
And then he incorporated into the present
Yeah he's the worst yeah so
Content warning
I guess about this
This next clip
It's pretty gross
Alex freaking out
He's now Superbad
He's losing his mind
Shock collars at Justice
Explain what is happening with climate
Mister shocking collars Amazon
They are like
Garish
Their colors that are just
Yes people are shocked you're still wearing them
There's more talk about shock collars here and then Alex brings in a little bit of his
His fears and disgusting
Stuff about drag queen story time
It's been awhile
That is a predictor
Communist China
Homeland Security
Is having meetings about
Around your neck
Daughters and sons
Directions
Little videos
I can't even look at him
Custom
You think you're safe in the world
Maybe
You think they're safe
It's all gonna burn
You're smart you're part of systems you can manipulate those under you
Come back on you a trillion Pole
I will not
This
Well not Summit
Call SimpliSafe sales a
Social distancing sweater
How can I go to your calls
Show show me homeland security video rework taser
Bracelets
Sounds fantastic
I'm not why
Is there a solution
Oh I'm sorry the flight attendant don't put me in a real Education Center
Put them in a re-education camp
It could be your last chance
Joseph
Qx30
Really drives home the Rarity of that entire
They let him Tire red like really feels genuine and organic and real
It doesn't feel like a performance at all meant to heighten people's emotions
With a minute suggestible State wherein they might be like all know I got to buy this t-shirt
You know I think this is why I really don't care like I've seen a lot of like a lot of those takes where it's like
You need to feel for the Q people they really believe this is real and that's
And that's why you know I know you don't think that they should read
Pac-Man
Get it
I get it
ICare
Because a child believes that the boogeyman is under the bed
The child is a child
I'm going to do I'm going to be like oh there's no Boogeyman under the bed
Let's do this
You're an adult
I don't care
I don't care if you believe that the boogeyman is under the bed I just don't care
You're an adult
Many of you people are middle-aged or older
Stop believing that there's a boogeyman under the bed
Yeah but you're not taking into account nearly enough how belief that there's a boogeyman under your bed gives you security
And feels an emotional hole that you need
Build can you don't realize that it's being filled by something
False
I am nonsense
That's cool as a boogeyman under your back and realize that you may you're not I don't feel like you're empathizing
I'm not
They're really not
That's okay and that's your right
I disagree with you I understand that
So
Like if we're pretending that this is Alex's last show
Things that he would obviously do
Is put off going to call
And not really get around
Successfully do that by screaming
About all sorts
And then he finally does get
Pickles and
In normal color fashion they're kind of a bummer
This one guy
Who calls in has been in the in the capital
ABC since the six
Not the building.
Excuse me
Okay and
He's really struggling to understand why
Trump
Go away
Why would you get on an airplane and give up on being president
If we know the election was stolen right if we know these people are demons dry why would he do that
It's tough
I got the call from
Only president to be here on January 6th and I'm still here
God bless your brother what do you see there what's unfolding
I see a lot of a lot of buses
A lot of Buster's
With the tenant windows in
I'm hoping that
There are true
Real troops
You are Soldier
One thing that you're not
Mentioning it all is
Where's Trump
He doesn't
Say something
Start the Insurrection actors
Oldest town
This will be worse than the
That's what I'm saying is he's surrounded
No one is the
Supporting him
Human wisdom
Like people think he was invincible
They set us up
Comicextra demonizes
Trump's going to leave
Those troops
Here's the weird
Sing the troops
Fox news reporting
I don't either so who knows what's going on up there
I miss your crazy brother we're about to find out her
We the people know what the truth is we know there was election fraud we know covid result
We know there's a pedophilia going on
We know Epstein didn't kill himself
We know we didn't suck
Send help for the Benghazi soldiers
We know that you're biting
Senile
What the heck how can a man get on a plane and fly away from all this
He also said he would never surrender
I'm here in the belly of the Beast
Waiting for the command
So sad
They just really bums me out
That's a guy who's
Except
Internalized all of these these narratives from right-wing media
And he's really he has the right thought but he's not reaching the conclusion
How could
Trump if he is our hero
How could he know all of these things and allow it to continue
Take the next
Step buddy
I would imagine that the next step
Is
Making up a reason that makes him still be the hero yeah or or just turning it into
Trump was set up himself
Alex's doing surrounded he can't do anything
But that's not his fault or God's fault
Somehow
Another caller calls in and Alex gives him some bad advice that if
People are listening to a show and taking him seriously Alex could like be costing people
Thousands and thousands
Thousands of dollars
Coming from a blue state
Populated area we go
Square mile easy here
Is the time to go
Hear it yeah yeah
We we continue to
Downsize your life
Cultural goodness of God
It's worth everything
They're designed to totally collapse and bring down the entire
United States
So I guess
Listcawler he does mention that he's like his family has some land
Someone who's listening
Uprooting your life
It would be very very expensive
His family has land
People who were listening probably
Is Ray believe what I went to saying in like they're coming to kill you they want to chop you up
America's over
It's time to flee the blue city is cuz they're death traps and they're meant to collapse
Like
He could f*** around and ruin people's life
In a way that we'd never hear about
You never hear about these people who would listen to Alex took him seriously
I decided to go to Idaho
I'm sorry to the people of Idaho that that's the exact like I often come up with
Oregon
I mean but a penny that they're spending on moving to a remote location is a penny they're not giving to Alex
Said true except
Scenario not as they need to stock up with survival food
That's fair you got that one
Literally
Amazon for people who
So now I have gas.
It's Jason Jones
Show me the guy who didn't like
Covid restrictions
Directions and came to Alex's attention
Director YouTube video I think
Anyway
He is there cuz he was at the Capitol on the 6th
This is Beast
Planing about how the
The media is gas-lighting people about what happened
This is so funny
Mike down for this if so hard
You know it's one thing to
It was all I was all quite
Horrifying Alex it just students me
We have to double down
Spider commitment
The freedom of speech
Freedom of religion
Free and fair election
And
You know we're not we're not going anywhere we're going to keep standing up
Oh I thought out you still here
Okay so yeah
That that's what I got it thank you though
Algebraic
God
That's good
I love it
That beautiful just beautiful
I don't understand how
Trump could just leave you know knowing everything of nose
I don't understand how drunk
We could just leave remarkably me Jason was saying like Alec
Lexi was addressing Alex
He later said that he was walking around with a headset bikes week
He can hear everything that Jason Jones
Man that is that is profoundly rude that is
Love it doesn't matter how much of a dick Alex's does it matter
The other platform keep on,
Somebody who used Alex's platform
Maybe for nefarious purposes
Steve pieczenik
And Steve
Might have turned evil
According to Alexander
Okay eat seems to be implying that Steve
Flipped over and started
Supporting Q cuz he turned evil
The problem is that is General Flynn now General Flynn
Pledge of allegiance to kill there's that so Alex tries to thread this needle here and it does not work
The movement was exploding Q came along and take control of it by with intelligence Ops
We now know that well-known intelligence Ops that I know personally flipped
Because they were controlled
General Flynn the great guy he is
He's a good guy
He's
Control an army
How you don't know
I don't know.
Controlling an army under false pretenses
Makes you less of a good guy or bad guy
Love you know lying to all these evil people in order to turn them into an army that he can use to overthrow the
Yeah.
The problem with qanon
According to Jason Jones
Is you know they use
Vague information
From Anonymous sources
Why you listening
Do this just remember how many times Alex's reference
Vague things that lieutenant
Colonel told him
People have
Such faith in
Q
I've been startled the people in my life people I love and know from
High school with college Westerville
I'm getting inundated with these tax
Listen
For now please stop sharing this information
Anonymous sources
It's communicated in a way that the ambiguous
And you can verify what they stay
When you have
An ambiguous statement from an anonymous source that cannot be verified
You can't support it or refute it
All that can lead to infighting and mistress
And
The structure the very structure doesn't matter even a content of what they say doesn't matter what you say
When it's from an anonymous source
Sway
It cannot be verified or refuted
The only thing you have that is argument
Animated
What
Who made Jason might as well be explaining what Alex does
System ya-ya-ya
I do like whenever
Self-awareness of 1
The evil is allowed to sublimate through blaming someone else
That's good that's good
So earlier this episode we heard Alex
Pretty bad
Without freaking out a little bit
They're going to kill you
It's going down
Naturally poison in the water
Going to kill you
He was also very viscerally
Responding to things easy easy pretty mad
That's why this is really really funny
You have been
Probably
You should write a book on maintaining inner peace I agree
I very much agree
Pretty through the nose very much agree
That I have
Often been lacking a
Zen and the Art of screaming propaganda this position called a sun salutation
Nevermind
Please say
Just going to start to matter all real quick and then I'm going to yoga
Adderall then consents Weber date
Since yep
To keep the vibe the real feel in the house
I always have a glass of tea
You know
You know what's fun about yoga is whenever your right leg is
It makes it more difficult
Interview stupid I don't care
All right so now we're onto Tuesday
The day before
Communist
Joe Biden
President
Snow White no real
Real trouble at the inauguration
25,000 uniform
Troops
Probably is a pretty good tutor
Deterrence probably
He gave his speech and it's sort of flew in the face of all the he's senile he can't to
Can't talk for even a minute kind of
Stuff
Bob
So is Alex's is still living at 8 in the before
He does
No
But that is what
Biden is going to get in
Unfortunately almost half of his audience
Believes
Have a lot of people mad at me
But you won't be mad tomorrow
When you see that I told you the truth that we got a pole on infowars.com
Tens of thousands of people
And over 45%.
Everyone's being Nash arrested in Trump to the standoff
Absolutely
What may be part of that is because of the people you talk to me
Absolutely incredible
My audience after
Stormy telling them this
Would believe it I mean haven't Gaston who I've over-inflated their credibility
Saying they are do everything know everything they overthrow countries
Toppled governments
Yeah for I don't understand why we would believe
Couldn't one
Exactly
I think that's indicative of
I mean I don't know how scientific these poles are on
Infowars
Assuming a third of his audience
Let's say I believe the
Steve is right
And that Trump
Magically remain president
If I saw that number
For our audience
I would think I'd failed
Problem with my audience
I feel most I would almost say that would be a reason for us to
Quit doing the show
Yeah that's for people Alex doesn't look at it that way
Kind of excited for them to be proven wrong and everything right
To the little people who give me money
There's a there's a loose
Thread
Dangling from the 6
And that is what Alex has repeatedly
And on microphone
Trump personally asked
Tim to leave the mark
Yeah wrong speech to the Capitol Building
Does not
Turned out
Alex was set up from the inside
He wanted a million people in DC to peacefully demonstrate
We were sure we had more numbers and they didn't couldn't
Coming to speak at a stage
That stage was there the night before
Broken down by the time we got
Are we were totally setup
We walk completely into a trap with people inside his administration we know now
I told him
All the stuff
By the time I got there I saw what was happening and tried to stop it
This is the real world people
Trucks
Menstration
I would imagine you would really want to name names alright big news
I think everybody would give you a lot of attention if you could name names, on Alex
Does not doesn't
The globalist plan
Also by the way I realize now that we've
Move.
What's the 19th it didn't really do a last episode on the 18th
But he also didn't say I'm doing it tomorrow
So I assumed that was meant
And it was just that out
Any just got distracted you just did an outburst
Started yelling
And hoped it would be kind of look like Network
Kind of the feeling that I get I think I think his last broadcast being like 15 minutes long would really be great for
Hit his last broadcast
Being talking about migrant Caravan
Over over exaggerating
There
Sphere
Not after you should have for them
Mmm putting him into a mood where he screams about shiting I get all going to die
Overbearing
And then puts off going to calls
I think that's fitting I think that's pretty good. That's about right
And now I'm going to say all the slurs that I've wanted to since the beginning in alphabetical order
Also
Here's what I think about Willy Wonka
I watched last night and I've got a 20-minute review
Horrific racism plus Syfy reviews
Beacon Syfy
Did you know
That
H.g. Wells
Formerly was
The head of the bad guy
I did not know that I learned that
Mobiles24
100 years
You can debate
1850s I had the bass
Lander Dalton
Wedgwood and Hawks Lakeshore
Grandparents
Aldous Huxley and Julian Huxley
And then bye
HG Wells is leader of the Illuminati
Ultra Vision
I just got 24 years at everybody
Because
Publix
Wow
Alex strong word
Strong words immediately following I think that the dead authors podcast by Paula Tompkins is real
You shouldn't
Probably have that position I seem to
Seems
Badge I think it goes against everything that he said he wanted in the past
For saving people in the light it does feel that way also if
Like the h.g. wells was the leader of the Illuminati but this plan only goes back to the wedgewood's in 1850
Illuminati started in 1776
Sure
Before 8
Who knows this stupid or the new Illuminati is like the Illuminati died
Brought it back in new Illuminati I believe
I got right
Anyway
H.g. Wells
Not just an author
Head of the Illuminati
Cool
Alex doesn't have a meeting with him
But he might have a lead a meeting with another
Illuminati
Stop 11 next month
So I will be entertaining
Snowing
What did you just say
Your soul
I'm not going to sit here and debate
It's all out in the open
Alex is going to have a meeting with the
The top globalist
Bill Gates
I have to be something
Cancel cancel
Maybe maybe it's possible
Could be Klaus Schwab could be could be could be a secret
I think it's one of the ones that we've never heard
The mystery Rothschild his brother who's not in the group
It was it was it the Kennedys who supposedly had a relative that they kept in the
Attic or something like that
Oh that's right they actually did holyshit that's real weird
I was just talkin about a Jonas brother who didn't get to begin with the truck and you're really sad
Memphis
I don't know who Alex is talking about
But the globalist
Except
Their plan
In order for them
Let's get away
With what they're doing
Alex Express is this a little bit
Humanity is starting to wake up and actually be
They should be
Play the social darling
But if you don't recognize for doing you don't have it
Open
Dialogue
I talked to them person-to-person and say
I know what you're doing
I'm going to resist you
Then they have no respect for you and will run over you
They better physically meet you
To acquiesce and submit
I always have to leave you an escape valve
It is a rule
Alba University
Follow these rules
If you want make a spiritual cultural
Economic and
Physical
Decision who you're with
Then you are
So the religious stuff
30 adds on to this is
But whatever but
I like the idea that if you don't know their plan and
Specifically fight back
Like he is just taking that from that fake document
Silent weapon
Which was chapter 1 of Bill Cooper's book
Behold a Pale Horse
We covered this in-depth in our episode number 381 on this podcast I want to rehash all the history
Read that again but if you're interested in how fake that document is
Don't listen to that
On Page 6 of that fake document there's a
Particular
The Bill Cooper repeat over and over and over again on his show
So to the point where like if you were a listener you would definitely have that implanted in your mind
Is it really a board
Quote
All science is merely a means to an end
The means is knowledge
The end is
Control Beyond this remains only one issue
Who will be the beneficiary
In 1954 this was an issue a primary concern
Although the so-called moral issues were raised
In view of the log natural selection it was agreed that a nation or world of people who will not use their intelligence
Gents are no better than animals who did not have until the
Such people are beasts of Burden
And steaks on the table by choice
Can consent
This is where I was his idea that if you don't directly fight the globalist
That's equivalent of you consenting for them to do whatever you want that
They want to do to you
Beds that if your
If you can get away with taking all your stuff it
Zelda silent weapons for quiet Wars
I would hurt Alex reference a document before I know he was a huge Bill Cooper listener
That's all that's all this bike
Mythology about the globalist
Meeting you
Do consent by not fighting them
Stuff comes from fake
I assume he's
For saying that he knows God's plan and he can see it
And he's part of God's plan
And that
And he's apologized for being wrong and he said that
He can't see God's plan and maybe you know all of his
Ideas of what God
Controllers are
Now what's this is all still part of God's plan God's plan is now for him to
The fight Joe Biden
Politically and make a bunch of money telling people to head to the woods
Thought he had already told me that God's plan was for him to defeat Joe Biden in the devil and Trump
To take over
And create a lasting 1000-year long reign
I don't know I don't know if he was ever specifically Thousand-Year Reign but it did certainly have overtones of that
I don't know I don't know it
One of the things about profits
Is when they're alive
They're really slippery
Their prophecies quite a bit
Yeah you got a real talent for that
Long form improv comes from
Long form improv rearranging prophecy
Form Improv
Tobias disease games that I was playing with his like prediction
Decades-long
But the globalist their plan is
Hundreds of years old
You can debate it
All right maybe it's maybe it's Mesopotamia
Baby experiment
Call Natalie
In his hubris filled mind
She's going to talk the globalist out of their plan
Don't take enjoyment
Screwed up
Falling apart
Mariah
The plan is to make Humanity so dysfunctional
That those of us that aren't part of it are going to
Suicide
Globalist
Because I mean why won't stand up
Yourself
That then I can't help you
I'm not going to join the globalist
Open dialogue with some of their
Top-level people
I had some dialogue with their top people
And I want me to stop
Yeah that's going to work
I don't believe any of this stuff but let's
Humor a I can imagine that he's going to go into
The meeting with Klaus Schwab
You gotta cut it out man and they're to be like
I have not heard this information for
Are you serious
This is bad for Humanity photo I'm talking to the devil
I can only his horns and the fact that I could never see him through the shadowy fire
That I agree might have been a sign
I should have figured this out
Can't believe it took a
Weird sex
Some guy yelling at me.
Hold on Alex
Just real
Are you telling me
That when I sold my soul to the literal devil
He was a lying to me
Alex is also said that these people act impulsively and they can't help themselves so I don't have anybody
The other also not human
Anymore
Parlay is going to do
Call such stupid
I guess an order for him to enact
What his plans he also has to get
Veritasium
Consent
Because it's a rule of the universe if God's plan
No because he's not doing anything to them
The globalist only need your consent because the things that they're doing
Affect you like Chemtrails over
Country Club
Usher
That affect all of us because of our passivity and not fighting them on it that's what that's consent to have right rails
Dropped on us I mean if you're going to
Defeat the globalist I assume they're going to lose all of their money and power so that's doing something to them
Yeah but
I'm just saying if it's universal law
He actually has to get the
Consent of the globalist
Before he
We can defeat that fine I guess Sports Camp exist
The consent to be beat
You have to sign a waiver before you play the game
Consent to
Disney
On this episode here on the 19th and it's not an interview I'm really interested in all that much
It is
The brother
Of John Sullivan the guy who got arrested for videotaping inside the Capitol building
And Alex has decided is the big antifa leader
Write out who who caused all the trouble
We got Mike Flynn the third cuz Mike Flynn and my junior are not answering my calls anymore
Jim Sullivan is a guy who has some right-wing Tendencies or is the brother of John
I just I heard this I was like
Tell us about yourself
Brother
You're very well known in Utah
Just popping up for a while
This interview is deeply irresponsible
A lot of it ends up just being James talking about John's personal life in ways that I don't feel like they belong on Infowars
And was it kind of left me feeling gross
Send uncomfortable
I know that Alex really needs
The build-up John Sullivan is the big antifa Boogeyman in order to
Precarious conspiracy theories about the storming of the capital being a false flag
Super inappropriate
The whole thing is Alex trying to get James to give some details that Alex can use
How to build a deeper narrative
He's asking me probing questions about like it
Did someone put him on drugs or
Do you know what who is Handler might be
It's okay it's really gross
And also I don't know if
James
However much he might disagree with his brother
I don't know what kind of
Potential damage realizes could come to him
By virtue of the way this conversation goes
The super Super Bowl the 1-yard line
Understanding I was being set up and all this and I did
Korean
Call Julio mobile things happen
Accused
Call Matt thing
I bet he didn't fumble at the one-yard line
He scored and won the game against America
In the super Super Bowl
It will be your brother
I don't know
I don't
I don't know if he realizes like
The kind of conversation
But they're having here is a
It's really
The kind of thing that could
Potentially put a Target
Mr. seller misses real quick to kill your brother I just want you to I just want you
Agree with me that all of this is your brother's fault
He is killed
The country
And
Of course deserves
I'm going to going to politically this dude is saying
Buddy who is along
Filming John because
There's been making a documentary
About him and his brother like the two of them are both like
Opposite sides of the political aisle shoes
I don't know what's going on here don't trust any of this I don't
Caribou
Yeah I really do
It just really really really uncomfortable but
I will say that
James doesn't realize what Alex's narrative is clearly because
Counters
Seeing him wasn't really that much of a surprise after few was
Remove from Eutaw cheewit to travel to Kenosha
California to Portland
Trying to get into since you two communities and they would kick him out to seeing him here wasn't really
A surprise
My brother saying that he keeps getting kicked out of there
Antifa groups antifascista groups
Alex
Stu then argue that he is an antifa leader
Yeah
Seems like they're both
Run in a game
That's what I am not saying that they're running a game but it does seem like
They're running
I think
A lot of their comment
It's about John
The sense that I get there is sort of an attention
Seeking Behavior pattern
Yeah kind of
Disregard for what other people are doing
That are productive thing
Maybe maybe I'm just so cool
Just so
Conditioned to believe anybody in that sphere is running a game up some
You know the thing that I think is the most worrying is the idea that there
Someone was making a documentary about the two of them
Like that to me is like okay
If one of you one of these brothers is
Someone who seems to have a clear pattern of attention
Behavior and the other brother is
Happens to be directly on the other side of the political aisle
It is doing a documentary with
It seems like this is all attention-seeking Behavior actually does
And the fact that you would go in
Talk about your brother in such a weird way on Infowars of all places
It just it would grosses me out
There's too many human elements to it
I wouldn't I wouldn't like this this
It's kind of conversation to be had
Don't see any
Like
Either they're like the okay so they could be running a game and this is f*****
Or they're not running the game
F***** up yeah
You know like this is f***** up
We have not interview people who know Alex for a reason
Yeah cuz it's uncomfortable
I wish I looks would do the same
Cuz this is weird
Any more of that
Does though on this episode
Get to sit talk about how he doesn't want bike
Dead
But he is going to put him in his death pool okay let's
Deadpool
I don't think he's going to be dead
In the next year
Do you watch power though
They put him in there cuz he's so weak
So Adam
Talk about stepping down
When
Once we have our installed present our first dictator
First dictator get those when he was vice president if he had a fundamental
Prince with Obama
Difference
Situation then I then the current
But whatever
Biggie
He's trying to say he's putting him in the death pool
I put a death pool on you
Do we have another guest here before we wrap up the 19th
This episode was not good
This was a slug today
Get through
Nick Fuentes on
And
It's interesting
Because
We have slightly different viewpoint
About the storming of the capitol
Alex is all false flag
Nick has been pretty it
In favor
Calling it the end of the world
I think it was
System what they wanted when they broke in quoted the media
Contact
Appreciate them coming out
Thanks on the founder of the broilers
Volunteer popular talk show
Thanks for having me
I want to play one thing here that sort of out of order because I think it it did
Is alright
Responsibility
Later people falsely
They claim that I breached
Wasn't true
There were people who were claiming that nicotine test was along with like baked Alaska in the capital
There's a picture that definitely look Tate
Horn like Nick Fuentes
It was quite
Believable
And I
I took that as proof
But he was there cuz I looked
A lot like him
It appears that that's not accurate
He was outside
He did not go inside
That is the case
And I can't find solid evidence
It's outside
Of that
Picture
And so I willing
To believe
Is is Sabin
That I was wrong when I
Repeated that he was in
Hannah Capital so
Anyway he
Yeah course
Which almost is more evidence I think that he didn't go into
Yeah I am
Under arrest
That's right now he think a lot of people who are getting arrested probably are not like
I'm a big deal with the pumps right now I'm a big fan of the we got
Carried up in the moment argument
Hey man it's
The crime of passion Dan don't count
Well some people look at it as a crime of passion
And some people would think of what happened
That day
The entirety of it as
Culmination
The stop the steel thing that Alex was a big party
And when we got there the entire time
Awesome site
Because
You are there as well you are traveling the country in Phoenix
The voter fraud and everything
And so to finally see hundreds of thousands of Trumps
Supporters
Capitol Building demanding
Bat-Mite pants
For the Republican Senators take action on voter fraud
The Fulfillment of the
Two or three months of stop
Steel protest
And to me it looks like the America
People were waking Uprising off at all of that
Everything else was a fulfillment of it too
Everything else was The Logical extension of the the movement that you all have been pushing down the road
Anyway
Make a little bit of a softer view on qanon
Then then our
Alex is pretty mad and of course a large portion of it always comes down to he wants
Scratch
And that is also where this clip is go
Going to go
But Nick
Kind of has a position more like it woke people up the Normie
Types of the Suburban
You know they they now know about how
All the people I don't like are Dracula's terrified
We're on our way to Victory Maybe
Need to get those people back into
A profitable Revenue stream
The good thing about you and I always thought was that
I got a lot of regular people
Do believe the right things even if they were believing
Conservative
Who believed that usual stop about
The power of the elites and the evil and the corruption of
And kind of his International thing that's going on with the government
I didn't, Siler City
Did
Became futile 10-q knows about this
Papua
The general public was just now waking up
To get into it
See the thing that I liked about that
Pissed off that he's not getting credit credit to not sound like a super Petty assholes
You like you've been around a while
22 here silver he's a veteran he was there at the storm in the capital there's no rookies in
Any more Dan he was in high school or the 2016 election
I know I heard him debate it was garbage
Ya Ali and the storming of the capitol
He's not been around awhile if the way that Alex is pretending
Can the day your 90 trouble
It's our last clip here
Is it just talking about out right now the globalist
Sphere Alex because he has
So you can reach people
But what they feared about you and what they feared about Joe Rogan
Is that you have your own
Totally independent infrastructure
Broadcasting
They want to control everything that people here they want to control what's on their phone
Want to control town.
TV on the radio
Nick is still verified on Twitter
Still there
Psychotic
Punctures that
I don't know I think I think it's
Everybody wants to
Control how everybody speaks and all that
And more
Yeah they're certain platforms that just don't put up with certain behaviors and you guys have
Cross those lines
Dude
To the point where
People going to take it seriously
And I would assume
We can show that they were involved in XYZ
Report that they will be bad they will be kicked off
Alright
I don't know who he's talking about so I can't even text you
I can go look for every account that has
#Boogaloo
Then I have to go through hashtag big igloo
All the weird ways everybody
Spell things
Can't do that now
Making a nonsense state
It's almost like Vega information
Yeah man unknown source
It's hard not to hear them saying like
Okay well we used to never have to think about how people
Fulfill
Then they started asking us to think about how we feel and we stormed the Kappa
And now they're demanding that we think about how other people
Will feel and they're giving us consequences when we don't
That sounds like exactly what they're saying right
There's there's a some overlap
I
I find
This to be
Sad
This was not a good
Couple of days for Alex
Yeah it wasn't even like
Maybe he's holding back
For the dinner with the long
For the marathon gas the inauguration
But like
I don't know
Is the last 2 days on the key
He mustered up his fake last show on the 19th or the 18th
Wasn't anything it was a it was a real disappointing crescendo
I just got nothing
Yeah
I mean it's not
You know you had that day where you know that at the at the end of the week you're going to have the worst
It's like longest day and
The day before that
That you're like you know what I'm going to take it easy today
I'm just going to do my job but I'm not really going to
I'm going to yell a little bit
I got I got a lot of things to scream about I'm going to lie but then I'm just going to take
Take it easy man
Imagine maybe he's been
Too busy writing a book about inner peace
I do think even if
Everything
Sucks
And nothing is really going on here
I would
Haven't done this episode just
For that clip
Where Alex is gone
That's so good I just want that there
I will say this I will make this pledge
If Alex does write that book
I will edit it
100% audio book of it in my Alex impression
That will be absolutely that is the one thing we will do for Alex in our career
Will be back
Jordan
With the inauguration
Spectacular 2020 because Alex
That's what's on the tube steps
Will do that on Monday for that but
Until then we have website we do have a website it's not right. Calm we are also on
Please find a local charity will be of undergrad help out
Until then Emilio I'm Leo and bcx Clerk of Daryl run cuz I'm constantly fighting
Holding
Alexandra first in color with huge fan I love your work