I have great respect for knowledge B
Knowledge fight
What's fight.com
Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Something that we need to put ketchup on
All right back we got something in the mail box
From
Hannah out in Erie PA
Pennsylvania
And I need to make good on this
They're great
Hannah Santos
Some chocolate
Erie Pennsylvania the pride of Erie
Candy
Romolos
And what is this other one it's Stephen something-or-other
Please
I haven't had to do that that had to put it
Between two families in Erie that are chocolatiers one
Makes a chocolate that is deemed
Quote better than the other
I want you to do a blind taste test between the two milk chocolate sponge candy
Until we did that before the show
Chewing into the mic
Discuss
So I we've tried these and which one is the
The classier one or two considered
Equalizer 1 and I say it's definitely it is gondolas
Mobile
Gondola
Vibrate
Pretty sure I'm right in advance
I'm not saying that you're not I'm just Airi were talkin about this exactly
Start a recording as we're eating chocolate
Your reason
For choosing Rivaldo is almost oppositional defiance
Local thing it's
Don't know too much about these arrival chocolatiers
Hatfield
Koizi
Sure I just assumed that
One of them if it's
Better it's the less
I don't but I don't think it's supposed to say
Say is not as good I don't think either of them were bad
Don't know they're both delicious
They were both fine I just think the Romola was a little bit
The chocolate was a little dry
A little thicker
Doesn't melt in your
No absolutely not
Anyway that's my breath button
The rare triple bright spot for the cycle absolutely
First things first
Somebody reach out to me sent me an email and they had done a better job of
Converting my terrible PDF into an Epub and Mobi
Could ever do
Citgo as he would like to
The formatting of your book left something to be desired
It's just like
He didn't amazing job
Second
Was going back to my I've been writing about music
Music for a while.
So I've mostly Taylor Swift
But I've been digging through all my old crate
And stuff like that and I finally read listen
Shinto
Spiced version
Lover's Spit
Broken Social Scene
Beehives or something like that
So good her voice
Manages to be both sonorous
And breath
Happy at the same time it is
Okay beautiful and then the third is something that you just gave to me
Physically that comes from the what was mine again
Meriwether
Male been what did I have I don't know it's not my job to remember your pure passive-aggressive
I just thought you would be offended Enough by them that you
Anyways
I was sent
From Amy Raptor princess copy of I believe the first English
The first American Edition
Of The Long Dark
30 time of the Soul by maybe my favorite book this one and
So long and thanks for all the fish
My two favorites
That's really awesome
Rival heirlooms
Seed vault
Some socks
Little known facts about the Dan
I'm a crazy cat dude and Houston cats on it
And the other one is a pro wrestling I love it
I was going to
Get to that on our necks
Text many episodes
Nike I have to hand it to me and I need to tell the world because it's incredible
It's a very excited
You might have to Stop & Shop
Simulated right now
Take some breaths
I would we got some stuff to go over tonight
Jordan we're going to be going over inauguration
2021 blackjack
Blackjack
Dial debating so fast
I know I got to race you
Going to get weird
The rule is you can't
Start saying Blackjack until 1
Gets out of its traditional
Jeopardy you have to wait until the sentence
Is the question in Spanish
Destiny have like points
001 seconds at Buzz Inn
Click
Now you don't have to buy
We'll figure it out as we go along
Anyway we're talkin about inauguration today
Set out to do a marathon
All day and part the reason for this is that he was expecting a false flag terrorist attack to happen it not happen
Turner Falls
Pull-A-Part
The idea that being a marathon naturally pretty quick
So today we're going to be doing is we're going to be going over the American Journal hosted by Harrison Smith
Some other issues about Harrison Smith
Then Alex Jones Show
Until Jon rappoport takes over the 4th hour
Should I was going to also do the war room but by that point
This thing had ground to a halt
I got I got no interest in this
And the American Journal honestly think was a bit more interesting than I expected it to be
That we really need to talk about right about this
F******
Comparison
Also I'd like to say what could have been one of my bright spots as are all the stories that are coming out about
Alex losing his
Supreme Court oyez
We are aware of that but inauguration must be taken care of before we
Jump down that road to a deal with that later in the week
For all those who work
For us to get to that
Before we get down to inauguration though
We've got to thank some Joe Biden donors
I don't know that to be the case that I don't know if
Does departed it signed up in our policy wonks
The first Elliott Morgan take us about two and a half hours you want
I'm a policy wonk
No
I don't think you made it
Grifter Heather
Text Andrew
Corey and actually Corey made interesting request
Estimate is
Like to be known as a policy knock
Congratulations Courtyard policy knock
Thank you very much
Call Athena Corey
Dog
I'm a doctor in my time is precious thank you so much and I apologize
Thank you very much and we agree
Wake me up
Mr. muscarello very fine fellow thank you so much
Thank you so much
Why not mr. Toad's Wild Ride what's his what's his role with the Koreans Wonder Emporium
Elevated
Appreciate that very much so Judy see not Jodeci
Jody Jody
Speak yet
Lord sub Waldo
Was the band Lorde
And
Read my name when I became a policy walk thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Heroin
Freakishly large
Thank you so much
Whatever
About it as like
This is
Immediately is in Subway's
Extortion
Yeah you got to get up to technocrat if you want to jump tazelaar
Don't know what the joke man was
I don't know I lose neck I get contracted to stuff
Anyway Jordan we're going to jump in here at the
Beginning where it all started
In the beginning
There was the word
Buffon
And then okay
Harrison Smith
And America has fall
You're watching American Journal this is a dirge of sorts a
Funeral song for United States for the Republic as we know it
This is now
A wartime broadcast
America the Republic
Has Fallen
Donald Trump vacating
The office leaving the White House
And taking Air Force One while you still can too
Florida these people are intensely dramatic
I like your
I think I start to realize when I look through the prism of like
People
I similar to Harrison or to Mike Adams
Are just overly dramatic
I do realize that Alex has the same
Except
Manifest isn't like this weird
Over the top modeling America has fallen in heat
Little bit less like
Obviously like
Really
Dramatic
It is a little bit like
What's going on is these are all the
The theater kids who are so into masculinity they could
Join the theater program
And so they're trying to get all the cedar kids stuff out I would have been a Theatre kid but they were too inclusive
100%
I tried to bait
Yeah I had to I had to play football because I was
Do not play football
Theater kid too much
So
It's going on throughout most of the coverage
Hiiraan
The 20th that is wrestling with Trump's Legacy
In the last hour of his presidency
Harrison come solidly down on the side of
That dude unfucked
Anna I got to be honest
Donald Trump
Completely fail
Utterly
Totally
Felt
I'm having this debate with
My dad yesterday seeing you saying you know Trump has probably the greatest president in my lifetime
It doesn't matter
Avail
He left us
Not
With any lasting Triumph
But with
Ash
You got some ass
I'm going to take a lot of people probably predict
Did this
What kind of person would possibly have predicted this remember when he was elected president
We were
To give him a
Ciara
Yeah it's
Stuff I guess
Aspiring
Authoritarian
Dictator servers
Sad that they don't get to
You know what their guy wasn't
I'm strong enough to eat them
To the point where they could be a servant
I was hoping that the
I was licking with strong
Powerful
Ineffectual in a grifter just like my boot I can't believe that my tongue made it all the way through that.
So quickly
How many licks does it take
Take to get to the center of trump
I will say this about Harrison
Was that
For all the like a trump has failed to kind of talk
He's a big man he's a big man
He's big enough to admit that
He was wrong
Okay so this clip is only 34 seconds
We thought he had What it Took
To do what was necessary
To save this country
I guess you would feel
Embarrassing
If I cared about that sort of thing
I'm not
Admit that we are wrong
What wrong really he could have could have done if he just didn't
He just didn't do it
I didn't do it
He didn't
Have what it takes
Wow we are rugs
Actually nevermind I am not
Late-breaking news
That's pretty amazing
I'm a big enough my Intuit Mint actually I was right
You like videos
He's completely missing the point of being a big enough bad
Is the the sense of like
I am an adult
By immediately undercutting it
It's my experience
You talk about it like
Being big enough to admit you're wrong
If usually the byproduct is like introspection
Wrestled with or like
Oh wait what was it that let us down the road to thinking it was going to be our King
He'd heard other people say I'm a big enough man to admit when I'm wrong a lot
This is supposed to be the thing that I say and then he's walked
Sit back because
Is he doesn't understand it what's
Is right now course
Anybody who's listed are shows where this there Greeley Ematic you
Nicki Minaj
Is also there
Expression that you keep
Using
Politics is war
Referred
But
Sherman
No longer exist
We never lied to you folks
We have never
Put a
A friendly face on something I was horrific
We've never told you to trust the plan
People working behind the scenes that you needed to do nothing
Oh real always
Shot straight beard Infowars
Am I to do
Today
You try to do it in a way that doesn't
Give me on a list
Of some sort
Cuz this is a Brave New World
This is a new situation that we are in
We've been discussing it
This entire week really ever since the 6th
Drink some coffee is no longer safe to
Hurry it up
Express Yourself
Believing that the First Amendment
Will protect you
He says broadcasting is
Not the case anymore whoever threw some
Major stories to show you that
Don't share that sliding on a Tuesday
Ranch
Alex Jones went on yesterday
Leidsa
Fairly well
Is this is
Award
Politics
Is
War deferred
Politics has a
Replacement for war
Where people
We elect
You are fighting for us and Halls of government rather than us
Brawling it out in the streets
That
Is no longer the case
I don't like his understanding
Politics
It can't be War deferred and also a
Placement for war
Elevator
Delaying tactic is if that's your description
Democracy we have a real problem
It's troubling I think again this is just like him repeating
Thinks he's heard sounds pretty good if you're not paying attention
Okay
Tyler Texas War deferred sounds like something someone strong would say really funny
Introducing a report from Alex
He's going to play that
Sure what's really funny is it at
The end of that rant
He throws it to a Harrison Smith
Peace
And so at the end of the video that Harrison played Alex references
Video
So it's like an Ouroboros of b*******
But this gets Harrison into thing
Thinking about how like hey
Pure white
Hey dear Young
It's going to be bad
If you're yeah
Yeah
Calm down this is going to get really bad
If you're like 50
You can just go out to the woods and wait it out and you'll be fine.
But your children think of
The children
You're over 50 or whatever you might be able to live the rest of your life
Off your meager retirement
Enjoy it
Have a nice little place in the mountains
Watch the sunset
Drink your wine
Listen your old music
But your children
And your children's children
Are going to be a despised minority
With no rights
No future
No ability to make anything of themselves
Robbed
Constantly
And the money given to people who hate them in order to replace
So you can't just
Ignore this anymore and if you do your part of the problem
You need to be involved
You need to be aware
And we need to fight
Not
Politically
Literally
I'm not calling for violence I'm letting you know
Violence is upon us
Implemented through the state
So you're okay surgically
Supercilious mean
To be very little difference between that mentality that Harrison is expressing and the tiki torch wielding Nazis of the unite
The right rally
Jews will not replace us
I listen to Infowars a lot and even from my perspective that was a
Very explicit overtly to White nationalism
Real blunt
I was wondering what was up here so I went to the American journal page on banned. Video
And there's a pretty mask off
Stuff going on over there
Perhaps most telling video title you'll immediately be confronted by
Titled
Stop white genocide
That is a name
Intensely direct title for a video and
Scripture really says it all
Quote Harrison Smith explains why migration is the
The choice weapon
One of the elite
When trying to dominate and destroy a population
Hoof
It stopped to be more clear than this
Harrison Smith
Explicitly disseminating white nationalist narratives
On the Infowars Morning Show
Which I recall correctly it's supposed to be
Entirely phone calls
I do remember that being the
The plan this is not something that's just like
Tacitly supported by Alex by virtue of the fact that it's on his Network
It's just a more explicit recitation of the taco
Complaints that Alex himself spouse
Constantly
Steve Doocy
I didn't want to just point out that Harrison put out a video.
Decrying his fears about white genocide and then say that the work was
Was done there far too many lazy commentators will react to titles of things about looking at the body of the Peace
And I strive not to fall into that trap
So I watch the
The structure that Harrison is going for is to make the argument that the treatment of white Europeans in the United States is the same as the treatment of
The weaker people by the Chinese government
Are people are comfortable with saying that the treatment of the uyghurs could be called genocide
Harrison's well within his rights to claim that white piece
People the target of a genocide here and in Europe
In order to bolster this claim Harrison
Pretty predictable false equivalencies that the Chinese government is accused of forcing uyghurs to be sterilized
Kaiser be required to take birth control
Here's some then claims that this is the same as the US offering people first
Control and that somehow Decades of propaganda are responsible for people making Family Planning
Choice
Is a completely insane false equivalence
And I don't see a good way for Harrison
That flimsy a spanking is arguing
Just said it
No I don't think
I don't think there's any way not to
Hear him say this
And think what you're saying is
White men are going to be treated like white men have treated everybody else
Send this country and that's worthy of
Killing everyone
Harrison gets to the point in the video where the argument pivots to immigration
Because at this point
The beginning is laying out this groundwork
And he saying
What is the same as
The treatment of the uyghurs
Short nonsense
Harrison primary source that he's reading from is a July 4th article that was posted.
MPR
Here
Harrison discusses his contention that white people are being
The subjective
As the government and get this send this if this is a genocide I don't know what is
The do you don't brought millions of Han Chinese settlers into the region with Promises of high salary
Jobs in Free Housing
My God
Ethnic migrants
Economic migrants
Coming into a region for high paying jobs Beth genocide obviously when it's in China
What about get versiti here you have to understand the distinction folks
Do you support giving birth
Back and happening to you it's a good thing
It's diversity it's our strength it's what we need when it's happening to uighur Muslims in China it's just
By God
What about you
I don't know I mean
Hello
Hello come on but wake up
Dammit a couple of important points here
The first is that the guy who was interviewed by MPR does not say that the form of immigration that Harrison is
Discussing is genocide
He says that it's a part of
Policy of ethnoracial domination which is still bad
Person stops reading right before the guy says quote
The reason why that this has changed
We do need to probably call it a genocide is
Quite simply because the evidence now for
First time specifically mean
One of the five criteria set forth by the UN
Convention
The punishment to prevent
One of the crime of genocide from 1948
Which specifically says the suppression of
This guy's clearly expressing that bringing the Han Chinese to replace weaker workers doesn't meet the
National genocide
But now that there is evidence of birth suppression
Oh that does meet the definition
Harrison is completely misrepresenting his researchers words
Because his agenda is to yell about immigration to the United States and stress way to Griezmann
Not to cover any of these issues in a meaningful way that helps the audience better understand the world and hopefully put his public opinion
Better policy
He's trying to make white people scared of non-white
He's trying to use the prop of the Chinese State oppression
In order to justify his shoddy argue
None of the complaints that Harrison brings up here rise to the level of meeting the UN definition of genocide which is the
The standard
Oprah conversation as presented in his primary source
Article to the UN convention lays out the other five Acts
How to do genocide
And what makes it even more difficult argument for Harrison to make is that says quote
Genocide need to any of the following Act
Committed with intent to destroy in whole or in part a national ethnical
Racial or religious group
The word intent
Is going to be a really serious problem for Harrison
The argument
He's setting out to make requires that he's somehow demonstrate that immigration of non-white people into the United States is being done with it
Intention
Of destroy
Going in whole or in Part B
That's going to be really impossible
For him to do without slipping into
Explicit white supremacist or neo-Nazi
Conspiracy theories
I mean I I would just
I would just have to
To say
Manifest
Destiny and if you want to start pulling some s***
Find start giving land back to the First Nations
Otherwise shut
The f****** because
These are the people who celebrate manaphy
Trust destiny
As the greatest thing that ever happened
I had something to do with God telling
So Harrison goes onto complaints
Some more in this
This Beast we're taking a little side door into his
Stop white genocide videos from the inauguration
Today
But I
I got really sort of curious when he was talking about your ancestors being a hated minority
And all that is like
This seems like code
I understand a little better and then I found this stoplight genocide piezoelectric
The United Nations convention for the punishment and prevention of the crime of genocide from 19 and 48 specifies
The suppression of birth
As one of the
You know primary
Attributes of a genocide
Now
If I was
Some sort of insane conspiracy theorist I might point
To the ongoing
Attempt
Buy mini mini mainstream Outlets
To suppress
Birth rate of white Americans
Say white people don't have children you shouldn't have children white people
It goes on and on and on we seen this headline over and over again
But that's not genocide that's
A good thing
Is remember white people bad
I don't think that makes Harrison sound like a conspiracy theorist I think it makes
Harrison Smith isn't seeing the media constantly saying the white people shouldn't have a kid
It's because they're not
Easy things like interracial couples represented in commercials and sitcoms and he's experiencing that isn't attempt
How to say the white people
Shouldn't reproduce with
I decided to check out what happens when you Google white people shouldn't have kids
Looking for some headlines
Looking for something to look into digging around
Can I can I guess
That's just real quick
You are you are going to find roughly
Reactionary right-wing
Articles about this
And very few
If any
Not so much I found the first eight results are just about raising children who are capable of talking about race
Issues they don't say the white people
Your nephew is a 2017 article of the independent title.
7 reasons people shouldn't have children according to science
There's nothing to do with white people not having kids
It's more of an exploration of the research into things like changing friendships at 1%
21 pool quotes
Non-parents tend to lead healthier Lifestyles than parrots
Was that the one
Okay that was 2017
I was interviewed for that one and they reject
Did mine which was white people don't have
Oh maybe early version accidentally talk to that one
Go back to being about 280 people being able to talk about Ray
With children
Closest thing to get really calm
Closest a really complex racial issues nearby
Is it there's a couple articles about like the Dynamics of
Adoption
Yeah Transit option that real huge
But that's not what you're talking about
Of the search results actually even find an article that
Actually about people advocating the people not have children
It's not race pace
Is a 2019 editorial piece in the BBC about a group called The antenatal
You just want no one
There's also the voluntary human extinction movement they are but that's not racially-based either that's
I assume Harrison also looked up a lot of New York Times articles and the like
From anywhere
Between
1878 n1939 whenever everyone with navigator for black
People to voluntarily not have children ever again
Okay I don't know either I would like some
Citations
I don't think the Harrisons making a serious Point here I think this is just a white identity talk
I'm going to being presented as if it represent
3 hours
Sucking Grouch
I would like
More ideas
Concrete example
Of what white men are going to
Young white men are going to face
And I would like him
Did you put those up on a wall somewhere just so we can refer back to them every time
One of them
People like this
Present like this idea like we've seen all the hundred
Articles telling why people not tempted
I haven't named one
Pick one
And also
It can't be something that's clearly said
Can't be something that you say that you don't get the reference
Like I said this entire argument really just hinges on Harrison trying to make the treatment of white
People be equivalent to the Weger
And other minority treatment in China
I want to
Continue to layout for white genocide I guess is what I'm doing here because
After all these years
Nutty
I have this weird consistency
I think the genocide of the uyghur people in China is bad
And I think the genocide of European people in Europe is also bad
I don't understand the complex
Geography that goes into
Yes I agree
Determining whether one is bad or not I just I'm just such a simple guy
Tumi genocide equals bad and I just don't have
Didn't fit the college think in the University brain that's necessary to understand why it's good when it's against White
Why people in bad when it's against the uighur minority I just
I just am too dumb I guess I don't know
I don't think Harrison is too stupid
His problem is it stupidity or not under
Understanding is that he's outrageous lie racist and he's also unfortunately smart enough to know that it's bad for business.
Just admit that and live open
That's why you have to make you strained comparisons in false equivalencies
That the experience of being white in the United
In states or in Europe
Is an anyway comprable to being weaker in China
That's a ludicrous proposition and
It's why I used to pretend that allegations of force
Sterilization in China
Are the same as the availability of
Give birth control here
Any right-thinking person to hear that argument recognize pretty quickly how stupid it is
But that's because of
The crypto
The argument or the false equivalence doesn't actually exist to be taken serious
It's only there because Harrison knows he can't come out and express his true white nationalist positions without consequences
I wouldn't say the genocide against Tweakers is bad in genocide again
That's why people is good
I would contest Harrison
Point that the situation leads group are facing or in any way compromise
And that's where her son's argument would completely Fall Apart
I know that because I'm
Was listening to a
40 minute video where he's trying to defend
He's failing embarrassingly and really letting his racism show
That said the lonely Shepherd by zamfir slaps okay
Alright
The king of the Pan Flute
A couple decent music choices
Because I'm good
Accuse that heard from other info
Shepherd
Yeah I mean I was going to be a little chilly
It really does
That wakes you up
Zamfir
Branded himself
King of the Pan Flute as if it was a crowded space
The bombastic something otherwise
People aren't going to
The king of a flugelhorn
Don't give a f*** with his title
The Children of Sanchez such a good song
Good soundtrack
Sorry anyway
Harrison
It's two guys going
Keep going
1948 convention on the prevention and Punishment of the crime of genocide which has been ratified by least 149 countries
Define genocide as any of these acts committed with the intent to destroy a national
Ethnic
Racial or religious group
Killing its members causing them seriously bodily or mental harm
By-the-way vast
Vast majority of suicides
Vast majority of
Medication
For depression
Lawn all on white people
But
That's a good thing because white people are evil
Even assuming that everything Harrison just said is true for most of tistical perspective it's still meaningless in terms of his argument
There's a white genocide going on
Again he's using this 1948 un definition of genocide that includes the word intent
Is it really important element of the definition
I mean Harrison works for Infowars we probably shouldn't even care what the UN thinks about the subject but he's operating off that definition so that
That's the conversation that's being hat
In order for his argument
To carry anyway
Harrison is going to have to demonstrate and prove the following
But there are in fact disproportionate medication and suicide rates between races that cannot be
Explain by other factors
Like income inequality and War access to healthcare
To that this
This is the result of a concerted plan by some group as an attempt to
Destroy white people
Harrison can't even come close to either of them
The best you can do is suggest that mental health practices like psychiatric
Medication or attempt to kill off white people
Because someone's out to get ripe
That's all he can do
Because there is no
There's only enough
Appeal to emotion only an appeal to fear
This is an attempt to get racist people listening away day
Express the racism without sound
Also a recent paper from the division of vitals
Statistics
Lcdc reflected in
Once you adjust for population the group with
By far the highest rate of suicide
Is non-hispanic American Indian or Alaska native women
I eagerly await Harrison's coverage of that
Oh I know I would
So in order to bolster his claims there's a white genocide going on
The case of Ireland
He seems to think that their entire population is going to be replaced with immigrants because of a need to do so in order to make their pension
System work
Here's be profoundly racist
And idiotic way that his segment on white genocide ends
You on the other side
Why this is
Very dumb
I don't like what's happening to the uyghurs in China we should be defending
These people were being systematically eradicated
By there
Governmental organizations
And on the other hand
I don't want the people of Ireland to be systematically eliminated by there
Super State governmental organization
I don't think
The pension system is worth
Replacing every single person in your country with a foreigner
There's plenty to go around
There's more there's more bangladeshis in a single District of a single City
That country than there are in the entire nation
Violin
Maybe we can help out Ireland maybe we can help increase the birth rate maybe we can stop this genocide at least in Ireland
Maybe expand that to the rest of the world and recognize the white people are a global minority the least
Elation of any
Racial Division if you want to take the big ones Asian black whatever why do the smallest and they're being J
Decided and that's the headline stop white genocide
Harrison is working off a primary source it's an article
Independent out of Ireland
The article is closed Ireland needs for million migrants
To sustain state pension
Harrison takes that information combined with the fact that Ireland's population is only like 5 million
So that must mean that they want to replace everyone with immigrants to save the pension system
Yeah that sounds like the Irish
Problem is a Harrison didn't do any work
Like even reading the article
The first thing that jumps out at you if you do read the article is that the idea that the country needed for million migrant
To make a pension system work with something that was used as an illustration of the problem
The country was facing
Regarding having an aging population and meeting the pension
In a meeting of the pension
I wasn't being suggested as the plan to fix the fence
System they were saying goodbye 2051 they would need 4 million new people paying into the system
The balance out all the people over 65 drawing from it
It Harrison wasn't such a
Adobe racist
He would have kept reading to the park
Have the article where it says quote
But the statistician and commission members say it's unlikely that net inward migration will reverse
The current trends
Migrants would become pensioners themselves
This article is about a discussion of why this wouldn't be a solid plaintiff
Fix the pension system
Because if that were the only approach taken could end up creating more net problem for the pension system then you fix
The article goes on to say quote
Irish physical
Advisory Council chair Sebastian Barnstead tax
Some spending would have to adjust a van pension
My pension age would need to rise
Social protection Minister Heather Humphreys spoke at the first meeting and made it clear that a reduction in the amount of state pension
Was not to Beacon
Considered
This article is not about Ireland bring in for million migraine
Engine system but the headline is written in such a way that it
Easy to use it that way
The four million number is used as an illustration of
Imbalance little exists between those paying into the system in those drawings
From it because the headline is poorly written in because
Harrisonville lazy Craven races
His article can be used to justify an argument that Ireland is engaging in white genocide in order to save its pensions
Harrison knows what he's doing
He knows this article isn't about bringing in 4 million mi
He also knows
That because it looks like it is he can mislead his audience it.
Thinking that it is
Heidi's racist agenda behind that
Impatient
Anyway that's the end of our side door through Harrison Smith piece on white genocide
I can say with a
Fair amount of confidence
That this special report was
Quite possibly the most
And most
Julio argued racism I've ever seen on Infowars
It's the racism equivalent of Harrison saying that the capital of fallen and Patriots were in charge on January 6th
He's not hiding what he is
He is eight
Yeah this is
Cuz what is he saying whenever you says
We can stop the
The genocide of Ireland is just
We can make sure that Ireland remains a white Nation
And then we can save everybody else
So Europeans for European nation
I'm looking for African Asian
Chinese people Virgina
Sing it all the primary source that he's working off of for the circle is a headline that he's misrepresenting it away
Way to use as a racist
Call Joe
Like it's it's outrageous
I mean it's
To be expected
On sublevel
It's pretty
It's like using story math problems as a like
Okay it's the migrant Caravan is racing towards the Border it's 60 miles an hour but the white nationalists are going towards the
Border from the opposite direction at 50 miles an hour
People will be exterminated
I don't like this quiz
Bad quiz
I started to wonder about this and I ain't really one of the things that I think is interesting is that like
Yeah I mean a lot of the same themes are exactly the same as what Alex talks about the crypto
Way
Wayless close to the edge
Because he knows that there's consequences right
Right people will treat you in a certain way
He'll lose his ability to argue all everyone says I'm a race that they all lie about
Made that kind of s***
His Wonder
Makes me feel like there's two possible Dynamics
I want is that like
Alex's thinking f*****
Let Harrison do a show that
Extreme as hell that's the white nationalist Waters Market
Going to punish us for this war
Is it the case that
Alex's run out of
F****** steam to the point where
A bigot like Harrison is
Taking over yeah
We're not taking over the whole thing but I can't Resort
I don't know it
Outrageous those like
I I think the Harrison might be a much bigger problem
Then he appears Harrison isn't even smart enough
Have to do the
Dumbest
Easiest
Thing that you can
Can possibly do
Which is immediately do what Alex does f
After saying something that the
Explicitly white nationalist
Now I have you know me I don't care about white black Hispanic coronavirus red blood doesn't even bother
Other to do that
New
An a******
Prelate
Back to inauguration
Sorry to take that but I felt like it was
Import
You got to know when the whites
Well I mean I really felt
Like that was
Something that's my argument for white genocide you got know when they're coming
I felt like that was something that was behind the clip of him talking about your like
Your children will be hated minority
This is kind of think you
You talk about
And then I'll get back
The 20th
This is a scary thought
Do we know how fake the news is imagine how fake history
You see this play out in real time
We see the truth with our own eyes and then we hear the lies about it
Is he the truth
Of the path at Dak to us
Imagine how false history is
That is so scary
That mentality is so scary
Especially considering a week ago we had Alex
Presenting a completely false version of Hitler's rise to power
Infowars
Does so much
Historical revisionism Antics surrounding very serious issues
You know that the
Hey we've created an alternative reality for us to live in and we say that everybody else is lying
Can you imagine how much
More lies are going on with his
You weren't you're basically yeah you're absolutely right like
Hey we've defeated reality in the
Present are only way to go now is
The past unless somebody invented
The Time Machine
Well isn't I think that's been the project of a lot of fascist types for a long time
Revisionist ideas about what happened in Germany
Have any influence over text
Textbooks well whatsoever
You're not going to get a real history
Revisionist ideas about the
Confederacy
It's not too surprising how many people learned
That it was about
In school
How many people probably Allen million
Millions
Maybe even the entire country in our elementary school
System that is designed to
To teach you history and for you to take him to the world they lied
Straight to your face when you were seven
So Harrison is is going on here on Inauguration
He's talking about how
Did the mainstream media msms the globalist
They've taken
The people who believe that Trump won
And they've turned the idea that Trump on into the big lie that they're being misrepresented
This is just nonsense
District only the big lie
And they're saying
Even pointing this out or people trying to represent their constituents were all calling out
Saying this was fake please for the love of God you're supposed to be our representative
Please say something please stop this deal from going forward
They are now being portrayed
As racist
Fascist
Implementing a new Jim Crow
I mean this is
Abor review
This is beyond anything we've ever experienced before
And at the heart of it
This is a war against white people
That's what you have to realize am
They are making a concerted effort now they're out of the earth couching it
Any friendly faces
Phrases they're saying
White people are bad must be destroyed must be rooted out
Must be ripped out by the roots
Must be eliminated from this country
But this point I got a little bit worried
I was like
I'm moving to I-10 was just checking in on inauguration day I got a little sniff
I don't think I thought maybe Harrison was a big and watched stuff
The war on white people
On the way
National is literally tried to overthrow the country
They've declared war on all white people
I was like okay
What when I sat down to prepare this episode I was thinking
Alright a breeze through Harrison's dumbass get to Alex and that'll be went like this episode
This is going to be half the episode probably talking about Harrison
Terrible
These years
Hugh
Biggity
Remember
That the evil global
Star now.
Declaring war on white people according to Harris
Even though last year
Only a few months
Citgo
Their plan B was murdering everyone
Well plan B is not to be remembered now cuz
It's not the profitable angle
We've got new sales flowchart
So he also wishes
The Trump was a little bit more authoritarian
Of course he's talking about this
In the framework of
Optic
Differences
Is between
Trump's inauguration and Biden
He's being really dumb
I'm here
Donald Trump won
Dooley like to nobody expected it but he did it he pulled it out you pulled people through
He got elected president of the United States
Everybody was
Very very concerned about
Authoritarianism
Open 2016
Before the Trump
Inauguration
DC was filled with 65,000 troops
And there were people going
On TV who are heads of the
Army saying
We need to have
Purity test we need to kick out anybody that doesn't adhere to our
View of
What it is to be an American and
Reality
Entire National Mall was covered in Flags because they weren't letting any people come
And the entire that idea Washington DC was lockdown like the green zone in Iraq you tried to throw over
I would have thought oh God maybe this is the authoritarianism there warning about
Course I didn't happen
None of that happened in the slightest I wish it had been more so
I wish she had been
More like the the
Monster that they portrayed him as maybe we wouldn't be in the situation we're in now
If he actually
Used in Iron Fist
What is shock someone who works at Infowars revealing what they wished
Trump is a dictator
If they sink
History is a lie these mother f****** can't remember two weeks ago Clear Lake
Turn me about that like
That description of the inauguration is like you're pretending there's no cause to these effect
Did that damn it
I could be wrong
But I don't remember in January of 2017
Liberals
Overthrowing the capital
No that didn't happen that didn't happen in that kind of effect this inauguration
Smaller crowds
Pandemic
Bi flag
Also about a memorial to those lost
Bring up the flags as if it's just like a way to fill space
Because people could
Be there soon though there was a symbolic
Meaning to that I wasn't
Committed or where I mean
Some could argue even a genocide
With intent to kill the poor
If you go back and look at
Kushner's f***
Can statements
Ml in terms of like the screening of service members
That is also
Because somewhere involved in storm
The capital
Yeah so I meant like I think
When you have a situation like that
It's
Not to allow yourself to
To give in to the impulse go on a McCarthy ask witch-hunt
The conversation
About extremism
An extremist infiltrating law enforcement and
I did the services like that is something that is long overdue
But you have to retain your sensibility about it
You can't just be like oh this guy donates to the heritage
Foundation
Therefore he's an extremist
You can't go that far
Need to be careful
But that's a conversation that you should never pretend you can have with someone like Harris
Yeah I know it wasn't like in 1863
Batman Lincoln was like
12 course I need to have a
Confederate in my secret service
Detail why wouldn't I have a
Confederate soldier in my secret service
It would be discrimination for me to get rid of this
Literal enemy of the United
Midstates for my secret service
And then I would also like to say just do it in the same way that like the screening of things is like if a sensible reasonable
Then you can understand why would happen but you have to resist
Going too far with it
Of course I would say that the presence of
Security forces in and around the inauguration
It's something that I don't like to see it's not good
It's f***** up
I can be again
What's that at the same time be enough of an adult to understand
Why
I can be against the militarization
The police
Storm the capital of
I understand that you're like oh no there were so many
Troops there I understand that but you need to
1st and there were so many there because they're worried
There a lot of you wanting to overthrow the United States government people online
Empathy
Lior sincerely
Discussing plans
Sims 4 other
Probably if it was it was more than two weeks
Between
There might have been a better solution that would have been available time
Crunch kind of situation we never overreact to Scituate
Valid
Directions to have
Absolutely not something you should ever find common cause our allies ship within
Central Warriors about cuz they're not sincere
Happened
Any why do underwater literally said the capitalist followed to the Patriots
Pretend City didn't
You don't get to do it
You shouldn't
So you may recall that Alex's said that if they hosted the American Journal doesn't take calls
They will not be hosting it any longer that is true
There's nothing to take calls immediately but he does
Get to some calls
And these calls
Those are not good happy
People whole boy
This is the Renegade Patriot in Ohio
I was just calling in
Because I've been listening for 11 years and stylist
But I prompted me to make my own YouTube channel
That was inspired
Partly by Infowars
And by
Political prisoner named Charles Dyer started childbearing notice July 4th Patriot on YouTube
In case you're curious Charles Dyer is not a political prisoner
2012 he was convicted of sexually abusing his six-year-old daughter and send
To 30 years in jail
He's been turned into a hero of the extreme right-wing who curiously call everyone they don't like pedophiles
Because he was a member of the oathkeeper
It was the type of the
Extreme right-wing militia guy they where his house was searched
They found a f***
Open grenade launcher
How do I get a whole lot about a fella when they call in to Harrison the show say they were inspired to start a YouTube channel because of Infowars
Charleston
That was solves most problems
Yeah not great
Yeah
Nothing compared to this neck
Text Colorado that's not good this caller is an Escalade
After
Analyzing the
Top 10 high rank
Pics
Providing
All 10 of them have dual citizenship in the state of Israel
Do you know
Don't try this best
To get that
Support from the Israeli Lobby and
Really he was basically the best president for Israel a diamond that's actually true
Yeah it didn't even work
The border now
And all by biting their man
Before but when you hear a right-wing dum dum like this color bring up someone having dual citizenship with Israel
It's an expression of deep anti-semitism
It goes hand-in-hand with
The Holocaust
Didn't happen this guy wants to complain that Biden has Jewish people in his cabin
Everybody knows that that looks
Bad so he
Tries to couch things to try the couch that hatred of Jews and language that ass
Concerned about dual citizenship
This is a classic Neo-Nazi talking
Complained that the Jewish criminals
I believe Run the World they don't care that what they're doing is illegal
Because their Jewish Heritage gives them right of return citizenship in Israel so they can just leave there in a void being held accountable
Then I saw Die Hard 2
Diplomat
Community
This is what's at the core of this collar and what he's expressed
Same here and it's been an Insidious anti-semitic Trope for decades
Since Die Hard 2
This color incidentally is just responding to a meme that went around on Twitter from an account called syndrome of a Down
Claim quote
All 10 of Biden's high-profile appointees are Jews
That's right
Every single one
This is a company buys
Screenshot
Intent Biden appointees next Israeli Flags
Unsettling
This is a really simple game this Nazi is playing where they just
Cherry pick Jewish people Biden has appointed to various offices that assert base
These tender the most high-profile appointees
Whatever that means
But it's suspicious
These people are Jewish
It's super transparent and anyone who's calling into Infowars to repeat this.
Is absolutely an empty semi till proven otherwise
Warrior show Harrison is hosting here just full of white identity Bass
Beer colors
Is inspired by Patriot pedophiles and potential neo-nazis
A interesting fact
This guy
The meme
Oh my God
Joe Rogan fact-checking here yeah he'll you making a lot of good points I have
The image here that's been going around all 10
Abundance high-profile appointees are Jews and dual citizens with Israel
US Secretary of the Treasury Janet Yellen attorney-general Merrick Garland
Secretary
Real quick there
The meme that he's reading off of dozen
They are dual citizens of Israel
Yeah Harrison is added that because he realizes don't want to do it oh boy I got to hit that J too hard
Soft in this a little bit otherwise
As a medic as it is
Homeland Security Alejandro mayorkas
Director of National Intelligence
Avril Haines white house chief of staff
Ron klain
Secretary of State Anthony blinken
Deputy secretary of state Wendy Sherman
Secretary
State for political Affairs Victoria nuland
The office of Science and Technology policy Eric
Lander
Director of the Central Intelligence Agency David as Cohen
Call me crazy
I think the people serving in our government serving in the American government should not be dual citizens with another
Country
Crazy for thinking it might Auntie Adam height
Yes sir
Super Saturday
Exactly what you are really really bad traffic
It's Super Bass
Except in terms of anti-Semitism in
I can explain one of the reasons why it's really obvious
Harrison's complaint is that these people are dual citizens in the United
Satan is real
Having dual citizenship in this
Case is divine
Define solely as these people being Jewish
Interesting the people have dual citizenship by being a government is suspicious or wrong is really just a way for these people to say that they think
Jewish people shouldn't be in government
Something so obviously
Harrison isn't an idiot he understands this dynamic
Fully well
Beautiful lake with big
Who knows that Daddy Alex will fire him if he speaks to freely I suspect
Do you do stuff like this this is outrageous
Yeah
Can't be like
Iru I was I was
I was aghast
This is not what I expected on inauguration day
And yeah yeah
Expecting that sounded cuz you can't say that they're going to kill everybody now
Yeah
Well we've seen
Not quite as a Jew should be in the government and maybe it's a function of Harrison
Smith being like not a great broadcaster
Castor
He's being this
Yeah yeah
The chops to be less race
Man this caller
Remember there was this
Nice sweet little Jewish lady who came on to Oprah and said that within the Jewish Community there are people who are not Jewish
You're hiding
Under Judaism but they're not Jews
They don't follow Moses they don't follow the Torah
They don't follow the ten commandments actually followed
You're not the problem when I talk about you
There are people who hide behind is Judaism and she
Openly admitted they are
Breeding babies
People who you can until they're pregnant
Satanic ritual that went over after
Why you doing this she goes
Power
Like it was an obvious thing like you should know
So I don't think these people are actually juice
I think they're part of a
Organization that is satanic that is hiding behind you
Wow
I was listening yeah hard on the anti-Semitism and listening to Harrison be
Completely open to it and not shut it down at all
And I was thinking I wonder how long it's going to be until we get into blood libel
This Oprah sacramentality collar is bringing up as from May 1989 and it was a
Huge embarrassment for Oprah
What happened is it there was that whole satanic Panic going on in America
The McMartin preschool trials and it's like 60 year and lurid stories of ritualistic satanic abuse
That was drawing ratings
Oprah tried to do an episode of her talk show about ritualistic satanic abuse cases and one of her guests was a Jewish
I told all sorts of insane stories
Butter family performing a ritual murder since the 1700
They was prevalent
Two Jewish families
Didn't do anything
Oprah
The frame the conversation by introducing the gas to someone who's quote mentally Disturbed and under psychiatric care
But I think that's
Good enough
A better move would not be doing this kind of interview someone you have to
Preemptively introduces an unreliable source of information
Just so everyone knows I want you to say that this person is not
Set to be on TV
And that we're going to exploit
Putting a mentally unstable person in a position where they're being exploited for ratings
Fred deeply dangerous accusations about a religious community
Either way
If this happens nowadays open
F***** everybody awesome
It happens kind of a scandal over a meeting with
Leaders of the Jewish Community apologizing and responding to criticism
Should never have happened if you're not
There's better been fired
30 years later was stealing your hearing about it that's how good it was out from
Nazi colors show
This show is absolutely mind-blowing and how expensive it is
There's American Journal
Harrison Smith seems way way more committed to or just willing
To broadcast
Explicitly racism and anti-semitism
Doesn't the audience
Yeah I was
I was I was taking a bath
How how
I have
I mean you know why I would say I think that is just a simple x
Explanation which is that Harrison is
Isn't Rich enough to A1A
Money more than eight
Anybody who's not white
I can't imagine that he has a more lucrative offer than what he's doing at Infowars
But I can't imagine Alex pays him anywhere near what David Knight.
That's true but
I also
I would imagine that if Alex wanted him to Kirby's behaviors he
Maybe and then he would get an alias and write a blog
Probably trail start a YouTube channel where he wears a
The mask is everyone wishes
Take another call and what needs to happen
Is a
Infowars
Obsessed with the idea that there are no go zones all over Europe where the Muslims won't let people in
Absolutely
Conoco zones in a
America Bank you going to move into a very new
Dynamic and I've said it before I think
Geographic proximation will suddenly become very important I think you need to find
Like-minded people that you can be near that you can protect each other that you can
Actually put up a substantial force in order to prevent
The American forces from coming in and
Robbing you of the rights that you have as a sovereign individual
I think
I'll personally maybe I'm a little biased cuz I'm from Texas but I can't think of a better place to gather Patriots and say
Everybody was out there in America I know it would suck to have to leave your home and and go to a different place
But if we stay
Just separated if we stay
Urbini small Pockets around around don't come one-by-one and scoop us all up you have to
We have to gather in a single place
We have to defend that place we have to create areas of land
That the
The powers-that-be cannot break into cannot get into we need to have our own autonomous zones
Around the country
Okay
All I heard was
I thought Sundown towns were a great idea and I don't understand why we ever stopped that was there something wrong with some done Townsend
This show gets really weird I lost
My taste for it
At a certain point
I have a conversation about getting people to move to Texas to secede
He has a South Africa
Can call her lady
Seems to think that apartheid didn't happen
Couldn't make sense of what you were saying until I don't know any clips
It's kind of all over the place
Yeah and so
Here is how he goes after break-up
Before Alex join
For a little
Spirits show on the American Journal
This is
Directing agencies to review their actions interracial Equity Everything To Me based off this
He's talking about like some advice
Racial equity which basically means robbing white people and rewarding non-white people in order to basically
But do a genocide on white people I mean it's not that let's not mince words here
Everything that the Chinese are doing to the uighur Muslims are exactly what
The plans are
For the Biden ministration for white people I mean when you say
It's a good thing and we're we're making policy in order to decrease
The share of the population that white people hold
That is a genocide apart policy let's
Let's not mince words let's not pretend like this is something
That it isn't
This is a genocide policy
To essentially eradicate any
Anybody from standing up against these people
And I'll have to do with the fact that
White people historically
Actually puts in Freedom into their governmental organizations and that is mostly based on the fact that
Christianity is a European
Religion so
Third hour begins on the other side
So now we've shifted into white suit
Supremacy
Straight up there
No arguing that
I will say this is not I will say this
I think
Harrison has
Is absolutely succeeded when he said earlier he is going to lay out the
The case for white genocide
Calm down calm down
Alex
Comes on
Stop by the Journal
And
I was
Weirded out by
By this actually
You're watching American gentleman infowars.com Harrison Smith joined by Alex Jones walking out
Diane I'm just popping in for a segment here to invite all your wonderful viewers to have our live coverage coming up
Erin just about
49 minutes of the inflation inauguration of the kind of Chinese five Biden
Why is Alex coming
To promote his show on Harrison
The white nationalists are tuning in Dan
Get the sense that maybe
Alex sees a different audience
Yep appealing to another audience that might not
Stick around to watch Alex
Yes he's coming in to promote him
Himself to them
Cuz otherwise like the only place you're watching the American
Journal his on Infowars extreme yep
Which would automatically start playing Alex's show afterwards
I'd like to welcome all the Red Ice listeners to Harrison Smith show and I just want to let you know that the Alex Jones Show is up
I am
Alex
He thinks the people thing
Donkey sauce
Does he accept
Is the Trump is going to be leaving off at
Nashi Naman infowars.com thing I'll dare you say he would leave today
You're a traitor you're agreeing with seeing it as it was I magically
Said he was going to stay
We literally talked to the present
Okay
Dr trailer's lawyers I'll talk to somebody else right close to him
Last few days and he was going
As soon as he capitulated the day after January 6th
It was over
What happened January 6th
They sabotage operation
That was a last-ditch Hail Mary to begin with
I was listening to that has like it's
10 AMU South
F*****-up sounds not good
Yeah yeah yeah
He probably just woke up or something
You know like I didn't I wasn't sure but I was worried
I was worried the way he's talking is not normal Alex Jones
Are the dog I think that's what I'm hearing that's kind of what I thought
Explains what's going on okay
So they don't want a big Mainline debate about this they want to have it be esoteric
They created a secret society
The inside group
Military intelligence
And that everything
Was going to be fine
Celebrity pacified I move on
From Hewitt
Set point
Talk about what vitamins do other to strangle this country
During inauguration
Afterwards
I do not have covid-19 thing I have to do homework done
Add.
Infection
I don't want my tonsils have been to see the doctor localized spine
Dime-sized bottleneck my throat
But I thought I never take painkillers when I don't think it was right now
Okay if you're on painkillers
Good time to be at work
Do surgery I talk for a living
What you got to do then
Wow
Alright let's play The Show Must Go On
Nearly as much as
It could have
So it's not like you super f***** up
Just here like there's hope there's something different
It is delivery in that
That explains
So I think that
They thought
That
Biden would be giving
Is getting
Sworn in
On Alex's show
But the time it doesn't work out
And
You know
We get all that
While Harrison is still hosting
And Alex has left there for his show
Tries God bless him he tries
Joe Biden probably wondering where the hell he is right now
There's a baby that knows what's going on tell ya
That's great
That's great work
Harrison just plays Biden
Speech is acceptance speech
Kind of limited late because I think
He's just hoping that by no make a big flow but then you can then respond to the whole narrative about biting on Infowars
Is that he's senile and he can't form sentences so honestly I think this is a bad strategy
They're literally
Earring evidence that he
He can speak and make sentences essentially debunking one of their big talking point
And that is how
The journal raps
We closed the book
I assume he's a big enough man to apologize
For saying that Joe Biden is not
He's not there so to pretend
Never said that he didn't say the capitals fall into Patriot weird
So Alex
Comes in and
He knows what to do a little bit better then then Harrison Harrison just let's buy talk for a long stretch
Alex Alex tries to Mystery Science Theater that s***
Many centuries ago
Saint Augustine
Ashamed of my church
Road to the people was a multitude
Define by the common objects of their love
Define but
What are the common objects ways Americans love children sinuses America
I think we know
Opportunity
Security
Liberty
Depopulation
And yes
The truth
Back for watching a speech on Infowars
Yeah you don't know how it goes
For somebody who thinks that Biden is senile he got his speech patterns
Pretty well down how much time he has
It seems like
Venice Beach
He proposes that his First Act
Will be a moment of silence for the America
Has lost a covid
It's interesting because we know that from listening to his show he
Long stretches of dead air
Recycling should be no big deal nothing
My First Act
Who's president
Are you ask you to join me
In a moment of Silent prayer
Remember all those who we lost this past year to the pandemic
Most of them died of something else
Dan's husband's wife son's daughter
Wuhan lab that your buddies Obama
Becoming the people and a bit
Rescue
What's 7 motorcycles for by the Democrats in the um trichomes murder
A most violent year
Do that already impatient
Alex pretend
Except for this moment of silence because of radio restriction
That sucks nonsense
He just has to interrupt a moment of silence
To like not allow it to
Two are some spiritual explanation for it in his head
I can't I can't allow my mind to have a spiritual moment on Infowars solutely not yeah
That's the really weird
He has stage
He can't now.
You can't let it happen
So this next clip is maybe the only real moment we're on Alex's show itself
Those pills my
Be affecting you
A new and better world or children
I believe we must I'm sure you do as well
I believe we will chill when we do
Will write the next great chapter
In the history of the United States of American American airborne
A story
And I found something like a song that means alot to me
It's called
American
There's one verse
Where am I
List for me all the calls it goes like this
Working prayers of century
Have brought us to this day
What shall be our Legacy
What will our children say
Let me know in my heart
When my days are through
America
I gave my best to you
Let's add
That's outside our own working prayers this is a frontman dismantle things are great nation
Statues
Then when our days are through
While they burn down syndrome children
Children will save us he says that he
They healed
At the beginning where it just seemed like he was making a lot of sense interjections
I don't know
Makes sense
I guess 5 a.m.
OVO
Still messed up
Alex
They've been talking about how they were going to be commercial free
Because
Inauguration
14 minutes is what happened
Now that's fine go for hours
It Isn't So
We're not going to commercial-free I guess until
Tonight we take calls up until 10
Pamela whole rap
Special guest here
Alex it expected this inauguration to go all day and realize it's going to be a ceremony
Real quick
Didn't realize that maybe
Trump's rambling
Speeches
Art
Normal
The wedding ceremony part of the wedding is
Is usually
Pretty quick
Yeah the reception is what goes on
Takes awhile
You have maybe someone who's officiating the wedding was a blowhard
Either way
Good bait Alex expect it'll blow hard as a president
Cuz last time
And 14 minutes and he realizes
Oh no
No just going to be a rambling nonsense speech of God
I am I have no commercial
Not good look at those commercial breaks back
Guys I don't have anything to say.
Doing this commercial free
He gave me
14 minutes of content the even listening to it I had a hard time riffing over Jesus
Commercial
But Alex goes to
I didn't listen to the commercials on
Infowars
Itself for a while
Cuz I generally listen
Through the the speeds
Genesis Communications
Commercials on them
Here's what Alex
Commercials this blew my mind
Okay not yesterday and announced a global government corporate Alliance to redistribute wealth afraid
Planetary Universal income to Global corporations will control to the apps on your phone
Finally it's all now completely official part of the UN great reset
Schwab all officially written about it hundreds of books
Agenda 21/30 gets here and the only gets worse like they said into a wood chipper
Brittney Griner
Spiritual battle and stopping abortion
What's going on here
Am I supposed to watch this show or musical cues are
Sophomoric
Their amateurish
Yeah I don't
I don't know what's going on here
I don't know what he's talking about
I think this is old
Because the Pope
When is Easter letter last
Steer
Disgust Ubi
Yeah but maybe the world is approaching
Single-point where are Universal base
Something, something we should
To be considerate
I couldn't for I don't know if there's a double down on that but that was like a big story in April
Yeah
I don't know I just
I thought the music
Really dark and like music
Is that a cup
Is that a commercial so much you're just a
An interstitial
You think there's a product that he's selling confused about supposed to listen to Infowars
Because you be I might be coming I don't know
I can't actually remember
I was caught off-guard by that left turn to like abortion
I forgot the
Previous part of the commercial might've ended up in like a body's commercial there's other
Anyway we get back to Alex's coverage of the inauguration
In which is now over
15 minutes into a show
I thought you got to you got to do what he does
I assume you didn't listen to the
The Poets
No
He do anything else
I mean maybe in the evening
Coverage they went over the
Play Party ice bath
Lady Gaga a little bit
Yeah why not Alex has a Gaston
Who we've been curious
About his whereabouts
The FBI might be as well okay
On the road I'm on on short notice
Obviously don't get your tag on what's happened how people that were delusional about Trump being Invincible how they're going to handle it but
Cashew
They're clearly saying domestic terrorism is here
They're clearly preparing to wind-up Baraka
You're an arrogant American people
Spiros
Founder of The Oath Keepers
Been wondering what he's up to
Interesting Alex doesn't
And start with
Haven't seen you since
How was the sixth time what happened hey Stuart Rhodes you're on the road
Road on the Run
Yeah definitely wasn't too bad I'm not done nothing but he want
Anything but
F***** up dude
Here
Is disappointed
In Trump
In very similar ways
Is the Harrison Waters
Everybody sees right
These are not
President vice president
These are tricon agents
Roosevelt ebird.org
Your view on all this
Realized
Is that you know Trump actually fail
Is the pop
Consider it a dereliction of Duty
And frankly cowers in the face of the enemy I'll be blonde
And we were calling for him to use Insurrection Act
All through the summer
You did not do it
And he
How you sound
I mean
Responses like
As expected as it you could
It could be
Disappointment
He has been
Very clearly calling for truck to me wanted to overthrow the government
Institute
It's to deputize him and all of his buddies the militias
Tell them up to
Restore order in the country
Of course he's disappointed
He was really excited
This is the closest who's probably ever going to get
President being like yep you guys are my Army now
That's about as yeah he wanted a nuke
Confederacy and he almost
Got it man now we said no
Symbian like
Hey the line is it wasn't
You guys
On purpose
And he was like
But I want to tell people that we should do it again
Well he does he has an interesting
Take on what happened
A little bit but Alex certainly doesn't want to start
He wants to start with
A fake leader
Tell him because he's a fake leader
Stuart news
Constitutional
Scholar
You went to Yale
Can you imagine how many lies are in history
Stewart
He's just like f******
We don't have to follow laws now
And all kinds
Who sang
It's the same excuses we've always heard
We were surrounded by bad people whose fault was that
And he's still
The commander-in-chief had any responsibility Step Up
Refill the do that
Whitehouse Nidoqueen Audi
Illegitimate
Eating pass
A so-called legislation
Rules are pretending now
I got three Supreme Court just
Justices who don't count anymore
That's how we're going to do this that's how this rule works.
I get to choose who I think
Is the government
This is not
The way for a cohesive Society to work
I mean
Makes sense because
Their goal is not to have a coherent
Incohesive
It's time to declare in
Independence
Amazing a truck
Our country be stolen like this are governor
So we
We still defend the Constitution but they're the ones of the Earth
And the vile
I didn't get stronger your community be raising local militia
You need to
The nullify
Refuse to comply
Schedule together
Okay
Okay so commit
Crimes and kill cops when they try and arrest you
Man
What pretend laws
By this point I'm at
I would like to know specifically which ones are pretend and which ones are not for
Anything that has Biden's
Signature on his Hancock on it
That's fake
Look
I
Can't
Say enough house
Stressed out I was
But I was looking
I got really caught with a left hook out of nowhere by Harrison
Over racism
Anti-Semitism I was surprised by the way
Going through his shed
Much more of a
Slog
Then I expected and it made it
Like it was it was taxing
And then it's the same time
Filled me with all kind
The thoughts about
Alright
I guess the Morning Show on Infowars now is just like
White nationalist happy hour bigot time
And that seems like a bad
Things to be gone
Let me get into Infowars
Is itself like Alex's show and you got store roads coming in
It's just like
Frank discussion
About like the
The government isn't real
We need to secede
And this is doubling into talk on Harrison's show about creating these enclaves where
You can protect yourself from the America
Sundown towns great
Eats
F***** up
Don't they already have white nationalist compounds in the Pacific Northwest
Tiger some around here
And everybody's just like it's the Pacific Northwest I guess you guys do
I don't
No enough
To know for sure but I believe I've heard
Artificially there's a place that has that character
So one thing that Steve Stewart is clear on is that he's gotten the memo
I've got a s*** on qpp
The only silver lining in all this
Finally shut up
Cuz all they did the entire time
Oh no
The bad guys
Delusional nonsense
Who was an absolute psyop
All done one
To get you all be lulled into a false
Security
And just be asleep
That's what happened
For Years yet
People sitting on their hands
Doing nothing
Waiting
The plan when is this miraculous day
But never came
It was a master
But now you going to wake up smell the coffee and realize
Now you got to do with the heart
You know who else was sitting on their hand
It's doing nothing for a long time
People like Alex and Stewart Roads at like
You know these people who
Thought they had something to pick up game from qanon it's hella got to a point where they realize nope
I can't gain anything from this
And now they sound like people
Who we are associated with like all of a sudden
They're pretending that people who have
Maybe more left politics
People like the guy the qanon anonymous what haven't been like banging the drum for a long time
Talking about the dangers and the
Misleading nature of
Qanon
I have no patience for that
You guys have all just
Jumped onto this now because you realized
Well
That's our
There's a good chance
That we can bring in some of the people
Anyone who has
Already
Decided that Alex Jones
Controlled opposition
Because of qanon
Maybe we can get them into our revenues rain
Isn't the end
Application of his argument though that he wanted more people there on the 6th to overthrow the government
No because then
Biden had been inaugurated
Hahaha
Well you got me
Is that cute people because they were lulled into a false sense of security did not show up on the 6th in order to over
Throw the government like
I mean I think that you could read
His comments and maybe some of the even like Alex
His comments that way
I don't think that's a totally fair Reed
I think it's a possible reading
But I think it's
Like the way that they intended
He's more like
There's organizing that you could do there's
Information Warfare you can engage in that you were who are into a false sense of security about you thought Trump
Was bulletproof right
You could have been banging on doors in Georgia
I think that's what they want you to hear
There you are
I am very much unfair and I'm telling you right now
He wish there were more people on the 6th
Anyway I speak no sex
I was trying to get around to asking about that
Hobo
Give me your take on top of the Capitol
I mean we got set up there bad
Wilshire ice bus tickets
I think it's I see it like this
Yes
Actors that made sure
The doors are wide open
But
For all of us.
Use the rhetoric of the left
Deb
Storming the castle were storming the capital
And and
You should disable
The most ever trespassed
Rhodes has a lot riding on people believe in the people who were at the Capitol just trespassing
You see I'm like antifa The Oath Keepers are a group that exists
Instant road is the head of
Website where you can donate to them and everything and they have an online store we can buy official merch
Ethan actual group
It kind of looks bad
Three members of the group get arrested after storming the capital
And they're charging document lays out how they planned for weeks in advance in order to eat
Kill members of Congress it took a lot of planning
Sing 2 trespasser
Thomas Caldwell Jessica Watkins and Donovan Crowell are all of Keepers from Ohio
And they're going
Going to prison for a long time
According to an article in The Daily Beast
Caldwell stands accused of organizing a group of 8 people to aggressively disrupt
Desertification of the Electoral College
The group used Facebook
Buck in the walkie-talkie app Zello to
To communicate with
Which is really f******
It's stupid because now the FBI has all that s***
Including that messaging with someone on Facebook who is apparently encouraging them to kill members of Congress
Sing
All members are in the tunnels under the capitol
Silverman turn on gas
Bill Gates is going to inject us all with computer chick
Tips to know where we are at all times so we need to protect ourselves by using
Did apps while in the capital
After leaving the capital Caldwell posted on Facebook quote
Probably scuffled with cops and drove inside to hide
The doors one guy made it all the way to the house floor another to Pelosi's office
A good time
We need to do this on the local level
Storm the Capitol in Ohio tell me when
In this individual case Stewart
Personal hand maybe clean
What are the messages that the FBI had in the charging document was Caldwell saying quote
I don't know if Stewie has even gotten
Out his Call to Arms but it's a little freaking late
This one we're doing on our own
Will link up with a North Carolina crew
Oh man Stewart read that would like
Yeah
I guess you can take the best-case scenario for Stuart roads is to say that he's responsible for
Restarting a decentralized right-wing extremist militia organization that he has so little
Control over
But now it's being used by members
To plan militaristic takeovers of
State and federal capital building
Also he might be in hot water because the charging document
For those Oath Keepers does include a charge of conspiracy
Explicitly alleges that they quote conspire together and with others
Whose identities are known and unknown to law enforcement
At this time
That's not a brief Glimpse to see when you're the head of an organization that these people who are gone
Going to jail for a very long time working
Spider-Man
What I'm saying is
I would still be worried if I were Stewart
Even though that
Good of the Stewie thing is pretty good for him
A lot of our generals
Flipped
And I
I just good
Is this good or bad
It's tough to be concerned about it it's probably his best play to pretend people are just
They were just Chris
It's no big deal
A few members that were in there
When they
Defense fund
Picture of a
They did not do that under my orders they did that
Contrary.
Always.
But I'm not going to
Has horrible people or Traders Rincon.
Too many on the right order
In the same
Police open the doors after a few people knocked
Some of the windows they were ordered to
Does sucking enough people to have a crowd
Stewart don't you understand we already have the narrative
You have your own personal issues and I understand are you don't want to throw your people under the bus but they are going to jail
I feel for you
Infowars has a narrative and I'm not going to
That all
Yeah hateful your ass hey buddy
You can thread
Define needle of
Could they overthrew the capital but it's bad that they lost
I wish you the best I have fun
Have fun
You're also probably going
Jordan
Stroger some interesting ideas
About cancel call
That hard
Apparently I don't know exactly what the
The route is
How you get there
From 8
See
Right but you start with cancel culture
Okay then things get out of
Control are we going to get back into white genocide
Masquerade
People Dead in Ditches
Don't play the good cop in say
We come in peace
They really come for war Stewart Roads
What do you expect
From the left
Are going to follow through with cancel culture
Tenzan into the ditch
It's worth going to end
If you don't stop it ends in a ditch full body
Throughout their history
Tattoos of State Rep
From the Mexico those calling for all of us
You were Trump supporter
To be tattooed Wildomar
Visible
They will know who you are
We need to understand that we're
Or worse
Citation needed New Mexico State Rep
So if I understand correctly if
Tubing can't rub one out in a meeting
We're all going to mass grave
Yeah you remember how Mi got rid of his political opponents by bringing up blog post
Yeah that was that was the
Main source of issues for the cultural revolution
And I'm pretty sure
God
I just can't stand this overly dramatic
Person
Making these
Petty complaints
Simultaneously being the leader of a f****** militia
Where people did storm the capital on
Seem to have pretty nefarious
You know like when you're so used to having uncontrollable and impenetrable privilege
Your entire life
And the lives of your forebear
The idea of equality is threatening
Sure but
Let's just remind ourselves
What's that
Best from abiding presence
Didn't see we're going to get
A little bit more
It's not going to change too much
True
And I think that you'll see more coherent
And more
Sincere aggressive critique
And action
In front
Hundred percent organizing
Against or in order to push policy for Biden
From the last
Then you will from the right culture War nonsense
Yes a bunch of
A Griezmann
And you'll see
Anytime
What's 2
Four more coherent
Yeah policy
You find it
Hard to
Think that
You don't like watching
Portland happen
Just recently
Reacted
It struck me
That
More likely what we're going to see from the capital riot
It is not that
People are going to go back
DC but the cops
Going to f*** people up at
You know like the DC overthrow is
Is going to everybody
80 minutes cops
F****** people up video
I think I think it's entirely possible and I think there'll also be the other day
And that is ice
Think that there'll be a lot of people who end up going
Going to prison at least get charged with a bunch of stuff
And I think that we may or may not here follow up
Saint a lot of a lot of people
Be jammed up for that
And I hate
3 bummer Stewart Roads is militia members
At least it's unfortunate that
The people who created
The
Conditions are absolutely not going to
Rico
Anyway store believes that
You know that guy
Left
Sitting president who was real
Alright that's it there is a potential for future election
Future elections
Began go Wells
But there's something happen for these elections
Let's go out
That is
Paper ballots
But also
I'm happy with paper bag
Hold on hold on
That's with the beginning beginning there's a second step to this
Is Ludacris I don't know how I feel about this
30 seconds
We no longer have a legitimate
This is
Actual sitting with legitimate president
We will see if we can ever have one again but snore choir
Any local elections you must insist on bigger balance
They won't do it
Hold your own parallel election
Prove
Make sure you have a way to prove that
Bottom up
So you take it back
That's right Stewart
How do you how do you do that
I do have a second election I think the funny thing the funniest thing about the
Is that the only people who would be
Furious at the results of us going
Two entirely paper ballots
I have zero doubt in my mind that if we were using paper ballots Stacey Abrams would have
Open governor of Georgia
Zeroed out
I will I don't know
I don't know
Maybe
I don't I don't
I don't know what I
Think entirely wood
Change
Cuz I don't believe that there's rank
Corruption of
Electronic voting
I think that there is
Problems with gerrymandering and access to polling place
And I don't know if that would be fully solved by paper ballots
I would say that you know
One thing that would be
Befriend more helpful than paper ballots would be
Having a holiday for life
Having multiple days the people can vote people are doing
We were making progress toward totally and also expanding access to remote voting
13 Republicans away from how many polling places are allowed in let's say majority-black neighborhoods
Not and not letting people like
Stewart's friend
Hang around outside
I like that more progress than paper ballots but I will say the one thing that is stupid
Is the idea that what you should do in you can't have paper valid
Is run a second election
A parallel election would
People a lot
About
How you would want to
Here's a really good processor
Could get some verted and you'd never know it
So you're running a second election sure
How would you ever know
Well because they would also be run by the Georgia
Or why would they ever do that because right-wing nut jobs wanted
No
So dumb I think they should have the UN coming to observe the results of the election I think these guys were
Middle of it
Alex
Earlier storage said Trump is a disappointment he failed
Step Up When fruity called
Yeah all these people are going to be going around and saying that he was surrounded
Excuses for
Who like Alex and Rodger Stone and Steve pieczenik and Jerome corsi
Immediately after
Inspector Road BLK Percy was on
Alex Jones Show
Last hour
You really failed
Department
Bob Marley
What's the lawyer for trump it was in some of the meetings
They were planted in the military arrest Trump if he did that
Even though it was lawful
Totally surrounded
Oh. Sounds like you're the kind of person who is Stuart was talking about has a note
This is just
Clip of Alex being a narcissist
Head-on inaugurate
I'm just an always try to steer you as accurate as I can with the best info I have
With real research
We love forkel
Understanding a
Quote sources
I'll tell you about the time I do more than my forces
What
Pentagon calls me up
CIA called Meetup
That's what I said
Thanks
Not the other way around
I have a good political
I'm doing this a long time
Sabbat train Hitler
Feel hard knot
As an organic
Patriot citizen wasn't praying by the cyst
Matt is seen by the system
The proof
I'm someone's real
Route
Pull themselves up
I'm not telling you that
Powerful
Telling you that because
Fellowship years in the Lady Gaga
Those pills might be kicking it in the Lady Gaga
They really do respect people who pulled themselves up
How did Alex
What's good as first showing
His dad bought an ad
Radio
I think it's really funny
Is like this imagining
Any others
Show where like somebody interview somebody about like a Medicare policy or something like that
Commander like you know what I know way more about
Rest in peace to Larry King if only he had a few broadcasters just like
Man all these people that I talked to her f******
It's stupid the government calls me anybody
In any context other than Alex Jones
It become so rude
Or how rude it is
This is the kind of dick head that he is seeing if you have an Mo for long enough people will just be like 5
Find also speaking
With Larry King
I was reminded on his passing
A lot of people post
The clap
And if you have it
CNET go go check that out
Larry King was on with Dave Rubin
They were doing a live broadcast
And Larry King answered
To call from his son
It was
Incredibly rude
Beautiful
Forever bee-utiful
Lovely
I love it so Robert Barnes shows up now call we got to have some
Constitutional law to tell Rosario
Oh that's right
That's right he's just basically there to sit on Cube War I think that's
Barnes's
New thing
His new branding is anti Q guy
He also has an idea
Trump needs to do
I think
Oops a great skills as marketing
In his great asset is his brand
And so he should Leverage
Both
To look at independent news media Network
Independent information
Distribution Network
Independent social media platforms
Maybe look at independent Banks and financial institutions
The realities are
There's going to be huge demand
For all of those things
Some people that are Trump supporters
Because of the censorship
Campaigns
And the blacklisting campaign
By the institutional media by employment institutions by
Financial institutions
By the social media oligarch
The only way to counteract that is to have our own
To do to replicate and repeat
Infowars
Build an independent
Bran
That's not
Depended at all either
Corporate donations or sugar daddy billionaire
But also isn't dependent on
Wake Tech distribution platforms either
The Infowars
Is the model in the template
The president tumiran
Unfollow in a broader context
Text of Industry
I'm not sure that I would want to be involved with a bank that's
Modeled after Infowars
Like I don't think I would feel confident have my money held by people who work
Constantly ranting about the devil and how they might be out of business next week
I don't know
There's some good financial advisors
I think that those business models are
Especially ones like
You know
A lot of that has to do with confidence
That's what was one of the things that will go a long way
Depositors not make a rush on their money trying to get it out
Is a
Maybe here's what I want to do
I want to put my money in a bank that's
Screams at me about how the government is going to take my money away from that back
Wright also is this
Independent Bank don't be involved in the FDIC if you're telling me that you want a social network started
Trump without a f****** daddy billionaire
You know what it's a little incoherent
It's all a little
Functional is like his plan is functionally let's secede from reality
Tireless
We can't leave the country cuz we a flan
But our brains cancel
We will create
Media ecosystem what you've already done a lot of a
Lake work on with
Infowars
And Trump has
Certainly elevated all these things
What creates
Online spaces for us to
Interact
You know what this would remind me alot and I don't think Barnes would like it
If This Were an actually enacted
I think it would remind me more of like
The mining towns in the 1890s an early night
1800s where
The guy who owns the mind also printed your money for your home
Ran everything there
Printed the newspaper I'm not positive that Barnes wouldn't like that I mean that's not a musically libertarian Fantasyland
I think a lot of people would love it if they were the owner of the mine
See that's that's what you saying yeah and that is
I'm going to get my own mind
I think people like barns
And Alex are at 11 of society where they view themselves as being okay
Be the person who runs the mind or somebody who's an associate of the person who have to buy an ass
Reminder
Obviously that's
The society that they would like
To see if they would like to build
I'm going to tell you right now
A society built around people who don't
I want to work in the mine but I'll want to own
Not a good one
It's functional
So Barnes said most of it is
Complaining about qanon which is
Becoming annoying
At this point
Until he leaves and Alex
He said this like a pretty excited
There's a short compilation
Compilation limp calling for
Reprogramming re-education camps of the American
People tell Alex is going to play that compilation
You know I was curious
Cuz I hadn't heard him play those clips
Somebody keeps talking
About it so I decided what I was going to do is I was going to look into
To each
Clip to it
Here's the deal
I took this compilation clip by clip I found the contacts for
For each of them
But none of them really had anything to do with pudding
Conservatives in camps or anything even
The clothes I was thinking like what the f*** is going on
I spent a long time sorting this out and then at the end of the compilation it didn't matter cuz Alex said this
American people
Go fuc yourself I wasted so much time
Sorry
Sorry it turned out the compilation that I was talk
I think about doesn't exist that's the equivalent in my world of slipping on a banana peel
That's Lucy holding the
Ever and ever
But but
Charlie Brown
Alright
So many
Brainwash
Educate
Chill
Firing squad
Reprogram
Show what are the clips about re-education can
Abigail's.
Harvard now what is setup
Kind of weird
Education camps and moral rehabilitation centers
And institutions for wedding people
Who had the chutzpah to work in the Trump Administration
Criticizing
Glad post
I got to be criticized
Barnes is still around but who cares
Alex breaks into the air interviewed say that he didn't find the clips but unfortunately
It's not a life they're saying they want to play
For conservatives and cap
Just another right-winger complaining but his fear that left
Yeah this is noted Epps
Steven lawyer Alan dershowitz complaining about Harvard
I'm starting a petition to encourage the school to not hire anyone who work for the Trump Administration
This doesn't help Alex's point and guess what that's a clip from November's
The durrschmidt allowed on TV
I don't
I don't know but that's what I find really interesting about that is that Alex is supposed
Italy in possession of hundreds of the eclipse
He breaks in
With this clip
After playing the wrong compilation
I don't know if he has over here
There are not
Cuz they don't eat
So Alex's
Kind of bored
Because
Inauguration really isn't that big of a
And also was shorter than he thought it was going to be half but I didn't make any real serious gas
And Alex has a little bit disappointed
All right I didn't Air Attack should happen any time something happens turn your phone on brother so much
The others should have been
Text anytime
Pretty sure he's very disappointed nobody attacked the capital or around the country if some other
Or something
Pretty much like
That's the whole reason we were going to do an all-day thing as I thought
Volkswagen come on man
So it goes on a little bit longer Alex's spinning his wheels there's nothing really going on
Is very boring
Volkswagen
On 20th
Stopped it from happening b b
So what's so awful
Alex's Matt Bracken
I noted race war predictor
Matt Bracken
Noted
Shawty diagram fan that bracket
Noted ebook about race war salesman
Matt Bracken
Yeah he's on the two of them have a largely unproductive
The conversation
I think Alex is so bored that he just leave
Safeway is during his interview with Jason Jones
You're doing a half hour
You take care of this until Ojon Rapaport shows up
That's great and I don't give a s***
John Rappaport shows up to host the fourth hour
And this is where I turn things off
Okay hello everybody John here
I thought I would celebrate
Lady by Janelle duration
Bye
Putting myself in a virtual Loft
As you can see behind me
Virtual City
Betty Jean virtual locked
Down
And my refrigerator is stocked
Virtual food
Because it was
Of course a virtual
Inauguration
After a virtue
Election Gala Zoom background
Riveting stuff
I can't believe how boring
The most bored I have been
So fast in the shortest
This. Of time
35 seconds for him to explain me to go to zoom background
Brutally bought
Terrifying
It
Yeah yeah it makes me it makes me mad
Yeah
I think that I could have probably kept going
And listen
To the war room
Although that's not a show that I normally listen to
Owen Shroyer is basically a less competent
Broey version of Alex
And I just
What are you
Got to buy the end of Alex's show was this
Sort of sense that
They're all disappointed
There's no real new talking points being developed
In terms of like
What happened on the 6th
Yeah president
Wooptido this is all exactly the way they've been
Going
I didn't I didn't have any faith that is looking to develop a net
Anything interesting
Simultaneously
Did there was any chance
That Owen show could be any more defensive
Then the American Turner
I don't think that there could be anything
The top of that in terms of
The dangerousness
The offensiveness
The bigoted nest
Banality of it
The banality of it was such a
Terrifying part it's always the scariest
Just like
To kill millions of people
Like it just tossing it off
Yeah yeah
And so I kind of felt done
With Inauguration Day
Outrageous White
Nationalist
Supremacist flash neo-Nazi
Be content in the morning show
We saw Alex
Disappointed that his
Bombings and false Flags
Didn't come through
And therefore he had no content
On his own show
I just
Infrared showed up
So I was.
I think we got what we need
Needed out of it
I think Alex
Definitely didn't get what he wanted out of it which was no a lot of terror attack
I do think that I was
He was kind of hope
Open for
You say we're going to do
If you're Infowars
And you're saying we're going to do a live
10 hour Broad
That's not because you think the inauguration
Going to go well
Do you have legs
Some analysis or
Find the setting out for any
First hundred days you really want to get down to the nitty-gritty
You want to get in the weed want to be a policy wonk Toledo policy wants to know that
Firefighter show
Girl
I don't think he has the ability to nor the interest in it and his audience
Be at all motivated by an Infowars we want spectacle
Everyone explosion
And apparently
We want
A dork
Yeah I guess so
Will be back
Probably on Friday
I think for another episode maybe a bonus little thing on Wednesday
But
The Fallout of Alex losing his Supreme Court in Texas
Appeal
Which I think will be
Maybe interesting
Open tell them Jordan a website on
We are important I was just going to go to bed Jordan
Please find a local charity or bail Fund in your area
To do
I got bad news for you Harrison Smith
You have attracted my attention
Alexandra Thurston color