Damn important
I have great respect for knowledge B
Knowledge fight
What's fight.com
Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jill
Jordan
What's up
But bright spot today Jordan was getting to join you on your stream of your video game
Channel over on you started playing Final Fantasy 7 is a lot of fun
I'm 22 and have very little to say
You are very offended when you do not have a sincere and large body of research with
From which to call Van challenge for me too
Tear
About every guy
You judging other people think I'm not judging you I'm happy for you and I fully support you in this and all your endeavors
I do
Can't care about watching the stupid video game
I understand completely I also don't like it being exposed that I probably didn't beat the game though I thought I did
You can close
God
Happy for you and
Congratulate you on the launching of your
You're a side project hair
Absolutely great how dare you act like you were so terrible
Bored
I will keep my mouth shut light romantic difference
My bright spot Dan is today my partner is getting her vaccine
Teacher she didn't even have to try and cheater way in or lie to everybody
Anna getting her vaccine at the right time and I'm really happy
Relations
I hope that continues
Be able to get a 2020 to get around to podcast
She probably low on the list slowly
Play Fade Away I figure a teacher like you said obviously this is
In that in that line
Much less so podcast
Jordan
I'm glad I'm glad I wish you the best on your new
Exploration of
Midgar you will remember me
Jordans
Something to talk about
Episode 27
So fast this is Wednesday
Of this week and the reason that we are sort of jumping ahead in time or last episode was about the inauguration
And Harrison Smith peeing
Yeah
Oh and the reason is hey I'm Alex Jones
I'm sitting around I'm thinking
The devil just got into the White House sure
The Supreme Court has just ruled that I can be sued by the Sandy Hook families
I'm going to go on vacation man
Leaves for Utah which is a strange place to go but whatever
I like that
The only tie every time he threatens vacation
He never takes
Vacation is when his lawyer that clearly said
If you are on the are you will say something that hurts Ark
You need to chill Utah
Rudy gobert
I don't know what he's doing in Utah doesn't seem like I've nothing against Utah State I love
The south-west quite a bit
Sorry I retract that is a good place to go on vacation
You know too many places are dry
Alcohol
Do that too
Slough dry county a lot of dry county
I thought you meant
No I did not
Studio and Owen Shroyer was hosting for
Number of days and I just don't care
I am so considering maybe like let's chicken
I just do
Smith episode Wednesday Alex hosted a good bit of his own show
With Owen Shroyer riding shotgun
God no no in the studio and something happened that requires our attention
And so we'll be talking about that today
And honestly I think that there might be a sequel to this
On
On Monday's episode of our show
Is this appears to be
Something that might
I am going to fight a bear on Friday this week
Take away the bear
Charity boxing
There will be a bare-knuckle boxing match
How do I just go
There will be a bare-knuckle boxing match Challenge and vendor attracted
Okay
Alright weather alert
There is like a feeling that I have
Let me recording some Thursday and
I have some awareness of what happened on his show today but I
This is a narrative that scan
Continuing continue into Monday show
Without giving too much away everybody was listening already f****** knows what I'm talking about
Anyway let's take a little moment before we get down to business Jordan say thank you
Stouffer's
Doctor
Can go like
Open go
Next Bruna symbol
I love you
Whatever you want
I do dried rice
Leland
Thank you very much my favorite of the
Just a clam
Next Love's your podcast
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much devron from Sweden
Thank you so much trunk of the tiny hands of fate
Journal about
I'm a policy wonk
That's a little of Mystery Science
Your hands up
Fake designer hands
That's to go along as a another plug
Which channel
Mystery Science Theatre cutout already embarrassed
That's the goal
Doing something is a terrible idea.
That's trying to smother you with embarrassment
Sojourn
Start off today on the 27th like I said this is all going to be on the 27th
Sansa Alex opens up the show
And he teases
What will end up being the reason we need to do this episode
Ladies and gentlemen thank you for joining us on this January 27th
Wednesday broadcast Blackjack and we are going to have the
Coming up on the broadcast today
Daddy is appreciate what you're done coming on after I said some
The founder of
The founder or the leader of
The first thing that Mike Danna does when he gets on the show is correct Alex about this
Is like the disease of the book
I wrote down founder of the Boogaloo boys and then put gel
Scare quotes around
This this is something that's a little bit
Murky
I don't think this is a good idea for Alex
You'll see why
Cuz he agrees with them on everything exactly like you did with David Duke
And this guy is a twenty-year-old Who
Is
Really
I would say he is more consist
Stephen Alex really tough to argue when you're out
Ends up becoming very embarrassing
I would say that we'd have not talked as much about the Boogaloo boys
Who's on this podcast
Because
It doesn't intersect with Alex as much as one might
Alex leaves them alone for the most part
Except
A couple times he tried to use them to scapegoat things that their right-wing militias have done
IMDb situation with a capital
January 6th
Is so large
And so important that it's
Slide 28
Critical mass of throwing them under the bus
Employment papers and such don't come under attention
Right he wouldn't do too much
Too I guess
Point out
The people
Who IRA
Basically he's running stochastic terrorism
You know like he's he's the one who's both giving them back cover of Life
These guys aren't
Part of what we believe in while at the same time stoking
The ridge
So you don't want to be also like
Boogaloo boys let's pay attention to them
It would be unwise
It's complicated for him to because
There is a lack of uniformity
With a lot of the Boogaloo community
He's right there is an embracing of antifa sometimes black lives matter
Or at least a loose accelerationism being the goal regardless
Some would say potentially performative
Collaboration and an acceptance of those
Indeed wing
Any that would be really difficult for Alex to explain to his audio
He's made such a
Supermarket off of
Globalist devil bad Alex Patriot God good
Go to
Have his audience understand
They're going there because
Bring some people in there I know I've called them all demon so they're trying to bring in the acceleration
I've gotten
Some messages
In the past
From folks
Who are into Boogaloo stuff
And they
Implore me to understand that
You know it's about guns
And gun rights
Sure
Feelings that I have that I come around on it
Is I'm not going to judge any individual based on their
Liking to wear Hawaiian shirts in protest for the 2nd Amendment
But I'm also not going to trust them
Avery associate themselves with
A group like this
Part of the reason for that
Is there have been enough instances in the past
Of people who associate with Boogaloo
Iconography ideas the movement
Doing things
That are meant to acceleration
Protest
You do make
Who's that that guy that that's sergeant
Who shot shot a cop
And then rub Bogen blood on his car
He was walking prior to this by using left-wing protest using the energy of it in their anger
For their purpose
There's been enough instances of that there's been all that discussion
And then
Let's just f****** deal with the fact
Boogaloo is a reference to Electric Boogaloo
Break into yes which is a Trenta
He was a mean back in 2012 about a second Civil War right
The organizing Central thing is a joke
What about
Alright we're going to have to have a second Civil War
Boogaloo is
From Alexa
Civil War 2 Electric Boogaloo
If you are someone who just
Cares about people's Liberty and rights
And Second Amendment
And you also like to be goofy and wear Hawaiian shirt
I would implore you to not be associated with
The group that's name is derived from a joke about how we need a second Civil War and has spawned a bunch of
Incredibly malevolent actors
There's nothing about this Hawaiian shirt
This intrinsic
Take to the thing
That they seem to want to
Push for
There's nothing
It just I don't know
It seems it seems like a bridge too far I just can't imagine being in 2021 and taking anybody
At face value
Says
Anyting Simba
We don't take them at face value anymore
Maybe you're a good person
Yeah plenty of good people who are Second Amendment people tons of
But if I took any of them at face value I would be an insane person
That's simply not a thing that we get to
To do anymore with Second Amendment
I would bet
That there are
Many individuals who consider themselves
Keepers that are decent
Family
Caring
That considerate people that aren't
The type that whatever Napalm bomb
Right right right
But
Still rare
True
That said even if that individual
I could see if possibly a decent person and I can probably get along with sure
I would not
Align myself
With them politically
Right right to know that they were associated with the oathkeeper
Because that's a deal-breaker
And I feel the same way largely
About
The Boogaloo
Yeah I know I just background check everybody
Just go back through their Twitter feed just going back to the
I don't believe I did that
So Alex does not want
A violent revolution
But he has against
The Boogaloo
Which makes sense
Are gearing towards like the inevitability of a second
Kind of
Music makes no sense
Those are you out there
You're always the ones that are asking somebody else to do it
You're always the ones asking somebody else to do it
The weekend after the 6th
Alarm rcdc they'll arrest you for that
We didn't see the bugaloos show up armed
I don't know
I just don't like this thing about Revolution
And then.
People say
Okay will you go first
There's so much in that clip there that just
Contradict
Alex's entire branding
He's saying that he isn't going to go first but he also spends so much of his time on his show yelling about Aries
The tip of the Spear of beer
The barbed wire to make sure it's safe for everyone else to charge
Filoli if you listen to Alex's show and believe a word of what he said
Also opposition to the Boogaloo idea of having our marches makes no sense
I went to the gun rights absolutist in the past he's been pretty clear that every American has a right to carry arms peacefully ever
Probably approach
The idea that a certain group is being told that they'll be arrested if they March arms
To be a huge violation of his concept of the Second Amendment
And yet here he is saying that the Boogaloo types
Because the state told them not to
This is where it's important to recognize that Alex has no real concrete
Principles that he's working off of or else
His position here would be have to be
He doesn't have a principal believe in the right to gun ownership because like shooting guns a lot and he found it was a really marketable Niche to be a guy
Dial jelavic bread store support for gun regulation
True at the moment business requires that he actually be in favor of people you would normally called gun-grabber
And somehow this doesn't seem weird to a large portion of his body
Yeah I mean with your when your ideologies and your strategy is
Something weird happens and yeah you're going to get into some real uncomfortable
It does appear that way
Someone else was uncomfortable situation
Is Donald Trump impeachment trial coming up
And Alex has a pretty good idea
Iblog what he needs
To do
He's lost over 60 other platforms so he can be silenced
Silence ahead of
And during his trial
What the presidents lawyers put on the defense
On the witness
And let them know about him
Always got to do is have a hit list
Exhibits
He puts on and it will destroy them
Perry Mason
The whole system on trial please just please
I would like that please take that advice
That is something that I would want that would be the first time that I have ever watched an entire
Asthma trial
Keep on going man
It's a
I think it's Sound Advice We like Let Your lawyers represent you
Has a fool for a lawyer
Alex is really getting into this idea of a trump needs to get up there and low Bass
The the entire Congress
Right out of the real footage
Activities in a lawyer says have you no decency
Annihilate
Really
This is their Waterloo
But of course
They're always aggressive globalist
We always we always act
Where's the bad guys
We're on the defense
That be great the idea of trump
Like having Alex as his assertive representative in court I thought it was going to be the best you could be with
Trump representing themselves but now the idea of trump
Represented by Alex Jones
Has one-upped it again goddamn
It would be a zoo
Everyday I just I don't I don't even even imagine I would love
Zach famous quote you no sense of decency to pull out
That line was spoken by Joseph Welch
A lawyer who is representing the Army in case against Joseph McCarthy
McCarthy
Accuse one of the young attorneys working with well to being connected to the communist
And that is what prompted Welch
The question McCarthy's decency
The beginning of the quote is actually quote
Until this moment senator
I think I never really gauged your cruelty or your Reckless
SMS
This hearing was being broadcast on television
Send it the most essentially it destroyed
McCarthy's career
At least in part because it clearly exposed how much of a Witch Hunt McCarthy was engaging in
Alex loves Joseph
McCarthy and thanks at the house on American Activities Committee was absolutely legitimate and they were doing the essential work of rooting out,
Alex shouldn't celebrate the lion have you no decency it's really confused
Towards the guy
That's what threw me for a loop
Okay so he's saying he really could have
Taking it to
Joseph McCarthy
See if you saying that
He couldn't be that lawyer right
Saying it to like Nancy Pelosi Chuck Schumer cuz I sent it
He doesn't understand nothing
Things work
Easy volcano
Something that should be like a deep wound
Atlanta communist
Psyche you destroyed the guy who I think
Or
Could have solved all of our non-white problem
Xscape we get one of the more unsettling
Ideas but Alex has
About
The Boogaloo
Types
And this is something we've heard him Express before
And it's kind of
It's a revelation that he
He kind of can
Tell whether or not a group is real or not
By who they target
Okay that's great
Because they believe they can tell our free society and submit their take over that way
That's why they're going to leave paramilitary groups there either
Unknowingly control because of their low IQs
Lunch
The globalist
Please deadly vaccines
Battery populated states super unpopular top Global is Klaus Schwab
Bill Gates
Notice you never
About
Call the Secret Service from the president
To make you think they actually run time
Seem disappointed that people aren't making runs at Bill Gates alright alright
Stone as a quote
I'm not
Kill anybody you know
Yono
That's words that mean kill people
No that's it
Kill people for the messages
Absolutely clear
I'm not saying kill anybody
You know if you said if I'm not saying
Kill anybody I'm going to say I'm not saying kill anybody... And that's it
Not
,
Because nothing that comes after that, is going to be anything other than Felisha guilty know the next Clause is generally going to be like
Or at least delineates like circumstances where the first caused by
Alex has called for violent revolution
Just feel that way
So he's calling for even more is the Trump needs to turn this damn impeachment trial into a circuit love
We need to get that message from that message to him
He needs to go on the offense
Call the ostinato Biden
Omnipresent
He needs to
Just demand
Dominates
You can literally turn this whole thing around against them
If he doesn't
Bye-bye that he's been defeated I can tell he he he doesn't feel defeated
I'm pissed off
No they're not
This is like the same s*** he was saying
4 years ago
Yep
They're saying like call just leave this alone and I will leave you with all that now there
It's just this is so
Boring
I'm talking about his own feeling I know I'm disappointed to be in reruns of reality right now
This is really a bummer
You can almost feel it the way he is
Did the manner of speech
He's just
Coming up with things that he Alex personally feels and applying them to Trump
Jack would like to yell at Nancy Pelosi
So strangely enough my advice
Trump is to yell at he should do what I wish I could
Good deal
Yeah
Big Cowboy news
Sure oh so it should be pointed out that Alex was
Jumped into the proud Boys by Gavin McInnes on are on what awards
Technically
That is true
Well Gavin was giving a little silly punches
Yeah I think that's
Action
Rufio panman
Based Stickman
Gavin McInnes Alex Jones
Rambo Joby
What a
Murderers Row shitbag
Haha
But there's news about one of the other members
The left is not create
Proud boys
The left doesn't know how to make memes as well as I do
Yeah I'm the meme machine if they called me
Yeah
Alright great
There was news that came out that
In the past
Enrique tarrio
I-Ready
These stories and I'm not sure that I see
C&E concrete
Indications that he still is
Bright
And I can see that going either way
I am going to withhold any kind of
Judgment
Or any Declaration on what his current behaviors are
Now I would say viralix
I might be worried
Because Enrique Torres been on Alex's show a bunch
Winter time
I would say
Metallic
Might have
Or Joe Biggs might have
Said something
But you wouldn't want to say to an informant
I don't
They probably didn't text
To to each other though dad
I don't know if that's the case and like I said I still need to see further
Indication
To heal
At least
You know like convince
Vicki was
Like snitching on the Proud boys or whatever
There's a problem for me this is this is what I'm talkin about with higher classes
Alright boys are also a really
Really bad at being a gang like
In Chicago
If you get taken up by the cops and you're in a gang man they just assumed you talk
It doesn't matter it doesn't matter if you talked or not
You can't take that risk
Sure so they can't you of course you say Enrico Thierry Andre guitario is an informant
You got to get him out of there you think if you're doing like security put probably yes
I understand making that likes her to safety position
Right I understand that
This is a gang
Punches you and make your name cereals to get in Idaho
Getting the message what I'm trying to say is that what I'm saying maybe our expectations for how tight a ship
They run
To be adjusted
They do not have a Stringer Bell
That is for sure
They laugh at Gavin McGinnis his jokes
Not a good group
Now that's not
Vaccine news also you have the vaccine news
But you mentioned up top I have good news yep I was just some other news
Hold it to vaccines
Major health problems are bad reactions
Both
MRNA vaccine in their regular
Those have been pulled they say it doesn't work and it's dangerous and you shouldn't take a vaccine
If they know the House of Cards is coming down
Alex isn't wrong about the underlying story
Free here and I didn't think the Bandit
Attempts to create to experimental coronavirus vaccine to this week
However the message of the stories
Completely misrepresented by Alex into being anti-vax
In reality a story like this should give people even more confident
That's about the vaccines that are widely available because this clearly demonstrates that there are some vaccines that don't make the cut
These two that were developed by Mark are not the same ones that were made by Pfizer or Butternut so pointing out that
Story of the way to make those
But that's exactly what I was doing
Houses also just lying when he says that Merc
Decided to stop pursuing these vaccines because of bad reaction
From NPR
Marcus Holt
Development of its covid-19 vaccine candidate saying that while the drugs seem to be safe
They didn't generate enough of an immune response to effectively protect people against the Coronavirus
So they're just didn't work
Mark spent a ton of money on developing these potential vaccine then ultimately it didn't work
The fact that this happens pretty regularly is actually an indictment of Alex's fictional worldview and it was really interesting to see him report
Working on a story
Huge problem for his narrative as if it's somehow validate
Yes weird
Yeah but the narrative for them is
If the system isn't working
The system isn't working
System is if it is working
Then the system isn't working
Because if it's work
It's trying to kill you maybe idea I'd like I think it's more just like a sleight-of-hand thing where
These vaccines got recalled
How can you trust this completely separate tracks
I meant also just making s*** up the obvious thing for him
The obvious problem there is that is it
Many ways is
Essentially the free market
Working the way it's supposed to
They don't have a product they can
Can sell so they can't sell it
But Alex would believe that even if they did have a product that was ineffective because everything is about money the Run
A hundred percent right they still sell it even though it wasn't effect
Thanks so much money into it
Jesus.
Incoherent world
Anyway
Alex is going to get to interviewing this Boogaloo
Gentleman
And
Interesting
Because
I can't quite figure out where to place himself
Cuz he's like you do have a responsibility to over
Overthrow a government well he already said earlier I'm not saying kill anybody but you know
And that he may develop later I believe that this makes no sense
Sax to me
I believe in Declaration of Independence believe that when we have a destructive government that have come after our freedoms and our rights
It's not just our right as her Duty
Defrost
I don't want to do it I don't want to be lead
My idiot
I don't want to go at the wrong target
Exhaust
Every
Form of
Artificial Warfare
Politics by other means
Bismarck
Pen is mightier than sword
Warriors
Can't win with the pimp
You're not going to win the Pandora sword
I just
I don't understand what you saying other than kill my enemies
Yes because
He's saying that they like I don't want to be led by the Southern Poverty Law Center the abl that's meaningless that's just nonsense
But
The problem that he seems to have is that these groups
Aren't doing what he wants
That's a real issue
Because he says
But you have a responsibility to throw off his government once it reaches xynz point
His show is essentially all about how we reach xy&z point
Ninety-nine percent of it yes
Also the left is on create
Those are its base
The two themes
He makes a career out of arguing that we have reached the point where it's essential to throw off the government
And then you have these people who are like well
Well you have a good career out of it or reactivate a career out of it you would be more
Christian people actually do
Yeah probably
Cuz there's not a money in that
Navigate to the point where Mike Dunn
Boogaloo boys Jordan Air comes on
For the interview
And this note that I have right here on this clip is just as this is a bad idea
Usually people who disagree with or no come on
Mike Dunn is a well-known Boogaloo boys
And so I will try to get them before the Restless
Log out my questions of my comments so you wants to
That is straight
All about folks that want to start a straight
None of that is accurate
It's funny to whenever
Owen Shroyer who's also their timing in periodically he
I was complaining about these other people who were too cowardly to come on it's like
Brian stelter
Also maybe the reason that he's coming on is because
Cuz he's not yours doesn't disagree with you
Stop saying that you guys are wrong
Maybe
He recognizes that you are very usable
Yeah you are platform that is exploitable for his purposes
Which he could have learned
Is a lot
Easier than he might
I think if you would listen to our
Plated out exactly
So easy so easy
So Mike starts off like I said the first thing he does is correct
Alex about the leadership
First things first
I'm not I'm not
I'm just someone who's in the movement
Alexace
But I just want to get that straight
Buy me a time.
Leader of it
Simply
I control a large
Portion of it isn't interesting
I control a lot how long
Is the guy who there was a vice article and video
About him John
I believe last year
And it did sort of traces some of his Brute
From being a Virginia gun rights
Militia type
Which if you were calling your guy Alex was
Super into
Loved it I've been through that he fell in with the Boogaloo communities and what-have-you
Michael started with Mike Dunn
Dot-dot-dot or Mike fun
?
Understand
Hawaiian shirt emoji
Yeah it's so
He was involved
Prior to getting into the Boogaloo stuff and just a lot of stuff that Alex
Super
Super into and capitalized on
The gun rights rally in Virginia that Alex
God talks about all the time
Some of the malicious stuff that that Mike was involved in was involved in that
I know it's almost like a lot of these
Far-right guys are are
Almost giving these like exit interviews with these people like hey you did a great job
But we got to cut you loose
And I cut you loose I mean blame you for everything that we've
The flip side of it is like kind of don't meet your Heroes kind of kind of lesson
People are coming onto Alex's show
Second I saw you like that I thought you were great Alex but unfortunately
Oh boy
Mike
Mike is
I think he can tell that Alex is trying to set him up
Because Alex is trying to be a dick to him and I think it might knows that and
Easy Millennial gen Z kind of guy
What's the weather called
But he's using you
And he's a he's a
She started with a quote
I want addressed as well
Find yourself here some other fudge from you 1776 the answer tonight
She also said it just
People
Be what I believe in
If they got motivated
And stop
Giving their political ideology
Figure
They will figure out what they
We have been motivated
Figured out
What we wanted which is freedom from tyranny
That when you say 1776 is the answer to 1984
And your involvement in the capital
I know you can
Inside in the Bible
Allison blah blah blah
Feeding into the media narrative
See what they're putting up
Let's not putting articles up right now
Alex is giving him a lot of
I think it's scary over here listen to me when I talk
You're really not supposed to come
Back at me with things that I've said before you're definitely not supposed to use my words and ideas to justify your beliefs quora
Fractions
Because
They are my words
Sound exactly like oh boy I'm in trouble now
I imagine that's his thought process
Is just like
Oh no he used words
I wouldn't have done this interview is over Alex
I think this is a bad idea
He can do these gotcha moments like the Bill Ayers interview or David Rothschild
Just he's so bad at this
He's really good at steamrolling conman
He's not good at talking to people who are the actual
Beliefs I don't agree with Mike
And I don't trust him
I don't think he's being
Necessarily
Aboveboard and fully honest even in this interview
But I do believe it has beliefs
More than Alex yeah I didn't have a problem handle it
Schlitterbahn almost certainly inspired by Ali
Yes send
He is aware enough to recognize the Alex
Doesn't actually have those beliefs
That's not good
March 2nd Americans begin
Battle
27th we had the Battle of Long Island September 15th we have another bloody battle September 21st
New York City
October 11th we had another bloody battle that's just one of the many
Ancestors all 1776
I feel like you just for the merch
Tire
Lost Ark
Avenues that
Politicians who were there for the money
Hot dog
Infringe
It doesn't matter
Is it
People
Even you
This is
Or Alex wow
This is not good
No this is a terrible situation for him to be in because he's being rightly confronted about his
Using Americana for Merch
And s*** that is a valid criticism to be levied against Alex
But he's also
Being scolded by somebody who stands
What's 2
Deeper radicalized perhaps his audience
Yeah I'm interested in that
Push and pull because it does seem like they're Twisted motivations here for Alex
It's like one of course he has
To be Top Dog
But to he does want to give these exact ideas of Platte
True
To me is part of why he
He's not interrupting
Yeah it's hard for me to tell if it's like a way of
Painting this person has the Fall Guy but also at the
The same time as message
There is a part of me that feels like maybe that's what's going on but I also
I seen enough interviews on Alex's show that are just like he does not prepare
A tall idiot
Who didn't know anything
Lake house
An awareness of Alex's career
Didn't have an ability to stand up for himself
Like I would bet that he's like I'm going to
Talk to at
Queen
I'm a man
Yeah it is
Really funny
How how
Completely clueless old people are
Considering the fact that I believe that
90% of 60 year olds are savvier and probably have a better education
You know like 123 I'm terrified you have powers
You know you guys don't even know what kind
Play f****** Powers you have yet
Yeah and if you're not going to lose an argument to Alex f******
Punjab snow that it's pretty clear probably some
This this guy is not
What Alex
Expected I don't believe
Now that I take issue with other thing that I'm worried about is that this is a guy who
Stan's two
Be a negative influence
On Alex's audio
Stroking so much as there are people who are like
Gavin McGinnis or
Nick Fuentes or Michael Jones
To come on Alex's show
Handstand
To take audiences on a different
Pass
Take them from this
I mean it's bad but there's
Kind of a
Like
Hi guys like
An exploitative vampiric nature to Alex's just like
Keeping people scared and then selling them dumb pills they don't need
Like I hate it it's an awful thing but it is
It's kind of
I don't have a vested interest in them not going
Too far for the merch
Yeah yeah
Falling into overtly anti-semitic communities
Starting to watch the American terminal
Things are dangerous and I I don't think
He is the right person
This Mike making these critiques of Alec right that are
Justified in finger
Hey what are the reasons is like
Mike believes a lot of the same stuff that Alex does like that the election was a fraudulent one
We also watch Brave
We all understand
We're not Chop fans we're not fighting
Is that we understand that but
Stability
We see it as they're hot
Rebelution
I just want to come to that
Justin Lovelace the people
Previously
We see that as a way to say hey
What do attorney and we're going to stand against it
Where is 3%
How to say concerning
And and what we're about we're about freedom and liberty for all people
Discrimination
The Constitution
So I did this is a chance
It's to launder and sell this
This group as
I don't honestly don't even understand why he would say that as if it's a good thing
On Infowars
Discriminate
This whole thing is about
Discriminated man we're looking for
We ran out of boot
Now we are hoping
Somebody will come up who will El Paso
Suppress the people we want to
I don't
I don't know if I would agree that that's the vibe I get off mic
Sure
No I don't get that well
I mean
I guess
I guess it's that kind of
Always
Getting to that conversation
Should have like you guys just don't realize
Because you think
Think you're going to be the mine owner
You don't think you don't think that you're going to be
Under a different boot
You think it's going to be some sort of
Utopia where you get to do whatever you want
What to do and all you're doing is establishing
Someone else
To f*** you over
Probably worse
Yeah and it's also
Mystical reasons in a disconnected World why the Civil War in the United States in 18
60s didn't
Really lead to
Complete destruction of America another civil war to break out today
It's not like what
This fantasy is worth one side will fight the other event someone to win and then America
More in the
An actual Civil War do you think
Thought that would work
Look for the other Global powers
That are like
Tied up and talked to me it wouldn't work majan that China and Europe
Naturally they do
Have a massive investment in the United States continuing to function the same way
I imagine they would stand on the sidelines if all of the sudden the global economy where to go
Two groups of morons were addressed Road Blue on f******
Playing running at each other with knives
We need the economy in the entire world to get back online
Far range in consequences from this this this
This
Yeah
Sort of Fantastical idea that they have
A real
Lack of Interest
In accelerationist ideas is like
Anyway
I really don't care I don't care for this this guy is kind of ideology
Or maybe him personally I don't know I don't know anything about him
As an individual except for
What keys
Put out on like vices
But like
I don't know
I don't that
Yeah I find it hard to believe how many people
Still believe that
Like
A war in the a Civil War in the United States would have
Two armies
Opposed to each other
With two generals
All choosing which troops
We're right as opposed to regular beating like there's no middle ground in a war in the United
They're like
Street battles
In every United States city or explosion
Everywhere
I like there's no like just
We're going to go fight you know and you know the quickest way to get the UN here to is prostitutes at
For you at involved man I'm sure Alex would love that
Baby grape
So
Mike and Alex
Talkin about
Alex's ideas
Our kind of
Behind
What Mike is doing
Alex has a really tough time with
I'm just trying to figure out
Are these could you mention this
Because I'm smiling
Civil Disobedience I believe
Defensive
Japan
What's the score
You're saying listen to my work my energy
You're taking from that
The idea of Revolution or armed conflict
Yeah no s*** that say that it took it directly
I'm just saying that
That you carry
Sometimes
Look like
You're just there to create merch
And not ask
About you do peaceful protesting and
Listen to Growing Up
A 1776 Revolution
Or the
I figure out whether
Talk show with your axe
Understanding
What will my Gillespie Harper Sinclair
You're better believe I sell t-shirts and I sell product
They want to shut us down
They want to kill Art Online
You guys were
Your shirts
Hawaiian shirts
Infowars
I'm a capitalist I'm not ashamed I didn't get gym point six billion
Dollars
Democrat daughters in George Soros
What's matter
I don't get any funding
Oral-B Atlanta
Are the Boogaloo boys volunteer for my security
I paid for my security
South Shore
Meccapolis I am not ashamed of selling products
But to be clear
If we get to a point
I think I got to be violin
Then I'll do what I have to do that's why I'm fighting so hard
Call John
Yeah that was good
Suction cups
Abandoned house with piano wire
No we all know Ali
Alex is a paratrooper he's going to get in that parachute and he's going to land directly on top of the Capitol building
He'll his way down I don't think about Alex Jones and that is he is a man who is not unfamiliar with stealth
Where's the where's Rider made
Yeah that's a little silly
I do think that Mike has a decent point though that Alex
The way he engages with his rhetoric in the way he behaves on air
Does lead to a point where he has to
Be honest with himself am I just being me talk show host
Or am I actually trying to rile people up to 1776
And we've heard Alex when she gets too hot music
No
Shadowgate comes out of the auto do any this year
Yeah when the country is stable
Or at least more stable than it is now
You can get away with 7 theater to 1984 7
1576 everybody gets that it's a metaphor
Now
It's automatic four
You can't say it without meaning it
Because it's happening
Yeah and your use of it as a metaphor is part of what normalizes now
In the same way that Mimi jokes
About
Boogaloo Civil War Electric Boogaloo
Well people actually want
To engage in ways that I could set off second Civil War like a jokes
Can lead to action in
Maybe jokes replying
Yeah. Now we can't do this like
Nora what I really meant was
No specific
Be careful in your language
And make sure that everybody's f***
Troy
It would be helpful
Guess what
Hundreds of thousands of people are ready for 7
Maybe milk
And they're surprised that you're not exactly
So now this is the point in the interview I think Alex realizes
I better be mean to the
This guy I've got to condescend to him
How do you see this thing unfold tell me tell me
General George Washington 2.0
I don't know I thought you were the
And revolution
Tell me
Freddy with a bill of particulars of what we want and then we go to war
Tell me tell me what we do General General done what do we do right now
Go for it
It does
Papers in order
Plan of government
And actually get it done is start building forces
I think that Alex thought he'd be cowed by that yelling
I think that you thought you'd be intimidated by L200 outburst
Okay well let's get a plan in place and take a right
Oh no
Oh I thought you were just going to be stupid Mike is saying essentially
My part in this is right rising up in bulk
That is what I have been doing
Great
We need those bills of particulars
Why are you doing
Yeah yeah absolutely he's like
I guess Alex was expect
Acting him to reveal himself as stoop
And reveal that
Look at all your stupid ideas that don't make any sense
And then when he didn't reveal himself as stupid he has to try and portray him
Stupid
And now he realizes that
Eats in pattern
You know like
This is a generation well-raised on my generation zirin
Destructive
Well it's impenetrable for Alex also because
The only way to penetrate it is to
Sort of
Also puncture your own mythology and your own
Worldview
Are you to say like We complain about is b*******
Wrightsboro reason that you want the bill of
Particular is in a
New government and all this is nonsense it's all eyes that we've been spouting for years on the radio
Now that you could do that and then
Devolve into a completely different conversation
Mike is essentially Bulletproof on a lot of points because he's talking
Alex
He clearly knows Prophets
You don't put it on a certain press
And he would stand to lose those profits
If you were to do the
Thing that would
Deflate this conversation I don't know why people who are going to absolutely be
Beat the s*** out of Alex in an interview
Do not bring a hype
So many different lines in there he said where somebody should be on the call to be like
And it and this would be a good place for it actually cuz in his next clip
Like kind of choose italics Outlook
They say
Strawberry salsa
We disobeyed it
If they try to wrestle
What are use the Second Amendment the way there wasn't
Where did you do this
This is in Richmond Virginia
So we go there for
Still
To make sure that things are peaceful
Andres
Disobey the law
We stand against the tyranny
And what we see
People like you Alex
Have you talked to her
Speeches but y'all do actually sending this morning as a Young Man
A young American and someone involved in the Liberty
Equalism
How am I not standing its tyranny
Evil legislation marching
They're going out having a bit
Because you because you talk
Disobey
We we stand there or we're not
Like a lot of
Republicans do we actually stand up
That's what I want
What's the revolution look like
Well there you go
Austin
Civil disobedience
They decide
The do something
They will Santa get
When I say hey
You can open carry
Disobeyed
Walnut
Repeat that was so weak
Alex
Sinatra but I don't know
You can you can honestly imagine somebody who likes Alex
Text hearing this
And it's shattering some of the illusion you have about Alex
As him being a competent confident
Strong force
This guy is
Mirroring back a lot of Alex's rhetoric
Better pointing out the
Places where
It's clear that Alex is
In contradiction with himself
And it's so
And he's hammering the fact that he's in it for the merch
Utah
You talk you talk for money
That's what you do
Likewise
If there is to urinate then
I'm halfway waiting for this to end
You like about molyneux
Declaring himself a white nationalist warehouses just like well
I guess I'm a book a little boy too
I didn't know it but here we are
Good like you said I mean you could tell there was a little bit of submission there are out show Das
Dollar
And so Alex has to retreat to try and get have got your moments
So he brings up the capitol
The Strategic blunder of rushing into the cat
The Strategic blunder
Of the selfies in the cute art stuff
And all the rest of it dammit
You think whatever the capital was a victory
Or Fiasco
I definitely think it it was the right thing
Thing for the wrong reason
I think it was good way to make government to the people again
It was nice
Members of Congress
Fearing the people
I think it was right thing for the wrong reason
So you know wish that people wouldn't have knocked on the doors and Awning
I Wish Your Heart
Percent that
So that's a little bit so f***** up yeah
Yeah there is nothing quite so terrifying as a zealot
Urolift
A lot of historical problem
20 year olds
Kia
Is also limiting his own personal involvement with the capital
And the storming of it
Boone article in Reuters from January 8th
Groups of loyalist under his command
Help
Storm the capital this week amid a Motley mix
Writers who supported President Donald Trump
Attempt to overturn the results of the November presidential election
Well most boogaloos are Libertarians who largely opposed Trump done said the group embrace the moment to strike
Against the government
So I don't know like it if this
Reuters article is wrong
He downplays his own involved
And there might be some disingenuousness on his part
In terms of his exact action
I just don't think that you can get away with commanding
Sing people to
Overthrow the cap
It seems it seems like this Reuters article if true is a
Yeah
That's I don't know
Yeah I don't know
I do know that that is a point that Alex really hope
Would show some sort of weakness on Mike's
Point Park but no he stands
Sperm donor
What are you got a consistency
And I'm not saying that it's a positive thing
Yeah yeah
Owen Shroyer is there like I said and he pops his little head in
Say hey
The Bible
He indicates that stuff
I like it I like it
Should we could do it later
Alex you can tell is getting a little heated
There's no doubt that we have encroaching Global government there's no doubt
Out that the government out of control
At the biggest
Crooks in America are in Washington DC
90% of Americans would agree to that
Here's the problem though
And ended my God I'd like to get you responsive
We're not in
A 1776
Colonist versus the British government time
We're hiding in the woods
And we got the local communities and and they don't have a World Tech
Technocracy
Set up against the us or a federal government set up again
I've been to jail multiple times for my free speech you know that
So I mean to sit here and say nothing cuz you didn't stand around Hawaiian shirt with a gun
Hello
Alex
Alright I'm not going to just let these two young dickwad
Talk around me without me just starting some dominance and Alex's being a real dick
I feel bad too bad for Mike but like
You know I can tell
He's being rude being rude
I am not winning the war of ideas
Invited this guy
I was just being a dick to it because
He's failed
The upper ground
And in this argument as usual he's pouting and throwing a fit
Return to this team's like if you were real
You would kill my enemies
I'm telling you
The target
Boogaloos are real
He's been calling for the Council on Foreign Relations
Every member
Ricardo
The last thing I want anything
Original Australian
You are
Not endorsing
Him
But you are saying
If you take out my target
I like you I will consider you real
Expected of being sprockel run
False flaggers
If if only you did Kill Richard Haas
I'm not telling you that I want anything bad to happen to Bill Gates
But
But I am going to use
The same
Visual metaphor
That was used
In the war on terror hey you know you you said
I asked you what the plan was and and you came back with it should be my idea and my ideas
Is that you should take out these Target Osha Thai minute aren't I
Oh no
So
The proud boys
Under the bus
Does not
Look like they are going to be heroes
He saying that he still supports
Cowboys and Levi butt
He is a proud boy
He's now lumping them in
With forces that might have Act
Did you know good
Enrique tarrio
Time I want exposed the federal forces that are involved in this
Identified boogaloos identified problems
Leaving me attack on the capital thank you
All this out today before this broke about tarrio
Google is Wesley Chapel
Ugly boy
I'm going to ask you right now
Building
DC is the capital
Capitol building
Okay
Alex's big gotcha is
Is a tweet or maybe it was both on parlor I'm not sure but it's Mike saying that they have for fireteams
Ready capital
And
Well I don't know I didn't actually see the tree but
It makes sense that his explanation is ouimet the country's capital is not the building
Sir sir there to where I know they are homophone
Yeah they sound the same
Four teams inside
The building we were talking about Bain Capital we went to the wrong build
I am really sorry about that be how quickly that guy
Gets resolved
I was talking about the
Yeah and he was correct about it too we didn't find assemble he was just like
There's a difference
But Alex has blamed
The bugaloos
People
Who were the ones that like the zip tie them to the ones that are really scary
Capital the Patriots
Vicky
Prove these things he's not just
Because this interview isn't going well
Alex kind of reveals that I I'm just looking
For someone to blame
Decided it was you
Here's what we're going to find out who these guys were in camera that mask on
Is on trial in a week and a half
We're pissed off about it
He wanted to put peaceful pressure on them to show our numbers
You hear the headline
Po-boy
Yeah
That is not what someone would say
Nope I approve it it's a bungalow boys and we're going to find out who did it
And I think they work for the FBI
We're going to find out we're going to get to the bottom of this if I ever told you about how I'm a psychic based on
People
Body language expert but I can tell from skills photographs God gave me a vision
30 years ago that laid all of this out for me Mikey or not really fitting into this vision
Confused
Did you might be working for the Devil by
I don't understand why he doesn't end every interview that doesn't go well with like obviously you're working for
For the devil sir
And I must have you off
Obviously this is a challenge to the devil has thrown my way and I just
The devil took Jesus into the desert for 40 days and 40 nights it on night one Jesus said
Now I'm out
Did you know that the devil is actually a book boy
I did not know it's proved that
That's fair
So like I said Alex is claimed that he's proved all these things when he's talking about it on his show it's not like
Spitballing ideas
Talking about we have Define
Trinity proof
That sources have confirmed
The document everything that it was antifa and booger
You folks got tricked into going and taking selfies and the Patriots were doing the right thing
But they got overwhelmed
Oh yeah
So
When you hear clip like this it
It's just like
This is not this isn't congruous
How to say it
I said this
I don't think they're racist other stuff
We know they are probably not wearing their outfits not wearing their you
Perform
We have tweaked by you
And in other people saying they stop
The capital of tack
That was the right thing now you're kind of
Halfway back
Cool
The question is
I see this doctor
4 Gold lady
Hi-C
Brandon straka
They're doing nothing
Freaks me out
Clubs
That's my big question
Alex if he knew what was going on and he had the information that he claims to be would not be trying to
Figure out who the provocateur groups are
Do not be having the alleged leader of the book Amazon
And being like well we're just trying to spit ball and figure out who did what
Also there's video of Brandon straka inciting a crowd to
Casteel a cop Shield was doing was nothing
Pikachu
Barely anything
What is it look if he was in my hometown
Princeton Illinois
Nobody would be bothered by it
There is that that's hard to understand cause and effect
Brandon straka go to prison
You know cause and effect
This is really just the way we perceive entropy in the universe
Self sure
Yeah yeah
And I think that
At this point interview you can really tell that Alex is done
He's been defeated
He's bigger than have the energy it's just no good
Doyoung
You can see Mike Dunn
I'm a little concerned I see this going on I'm worried about
The idea of your movement that anybody can send her a Boogaloo it's like
Are you for anonymous
Ru42 anybody's b-42
Don't you worry them are you frantically that's what it came from
Are you worried about being taken over
What is actually happening here
Audiology
Boogaloo
Several people started
Liberty is for all and we're done
Yeah and it's a joke meme that turned into an ideology about
Be need for a second Civil War
So
I don't think
I don't think we can sort of
Eliminate that and pretend that that's not a p
Piece of piss
I think that's fairly important but
Alex signaling defeat there just being like well you know look I'm just
Trying to tell you that your group can be co-opted
That is an attempt to trick
That is a
False
Move backwards
Into AAA proposal submission
It's a sidestep more like yes because then Alex
Tries
To get him
Do
What's it called what's the pleading the fifth
Open Chrome Alex is trying to get him to self-incriminate
Here's my issue
Are you guys putting on a Manifesto of Target because
Directions to sheet of what
The people should be in control of
What about Bill Gates what about
Tell me
Why who's the extra space for you guys
It would be a courtesy here and released a Manifesto
The real evil King
Malicious
Golden people understand
Oh baby
Listen what I'm telling you is I want to save this country
Okay this is the Spider-Man
This is Spider-Man
The bad guy or the bad guy
A stupid idea I'm not going to do that.
What you are
Oh my
That is so funny yeah
Man
God bless
I mean like God bless
No I don't have a appraisal
It's a it shows some wherewithal
Look for Mike to recognize like
Talk like this
He's a good I would say next move
Sure if this was Bobby Fischer vs. Kasparov
I'll be like nice move in or it would be an unnecessary error
To continue the chest metaphor
So Alex
Pink
He also
It makes it a little too obvious in this conversation
That this is person
Like this really feels
Personal
In this clip Alex is going to express that by way of being like
Hey I'm the real person fighting for Liberty Shore and you can prove that be
Because
A bunch of people are suing me anyone suing you
I want to save this country
Running around storm and capitals
Either intercourse
What's the country
Do you have 50 lawsuits
What's again
You have the Democratic party financing
Why am I under so much taxes I know nothing
I'm this coward I do this cuz you were piece of s***
You're this cuz you are all the gun
Oh my God
Fall down on my knees
It's the fact that you
The only thing is
I am not doing
I'm not Democrat
They're scared of it
People swim cap
French Revolution and I always will
Alex is trying to again incriminate him he's trying to get him in this thing where it's like all you told people to start
Like afterwards Alex can still use that for his narratives if you get them into that box right and not least of which he wants the
This guy emoji
Yes he wants this guy to be like
Did tell people to storm the capital of being like that all you guys aren't you were engaging
Taking the same sort of s*** that
Achieve any of the goals you professed to have
And we're going to force a revolution
Not that idea there is the accelerationist ideas before sir evolution
He's not
Something that
Is it it's not what goes well with
Public facing idea of
The Boogaloo
Types
Want you to think like all weird
Just here standing around making sure nothing
Gets out of control
Because you want to force Revolution
Yeah
Like something to go bad
Right and people start shooting
I think one of the
Most difficult things for Alex's he doesn't understand that their agenda
Begins with Rebelution
There's no like
I don't think they care what
Brexit
If it was a left-wing cause they would be like yeah let's go
The revolution is what their goal is
Yeah you can't really be like
Oh see you're so stupid it's like no
We just didn't succeed
The goal is still a revolution
We're not changing our goal because we lose
Yeah
And I would say that based on this reporting and Reuters
If accurate
Is counter to what Mike
Is presenting
Here
Some question about that I don't
I don't know what the reality is I wasn't there
But it does seem to be like at least a reason to be like I don't think that you're above board
I don't think you're being honest
Now
Here's where things turn a little bit more hot
Alex brings up
That the Boogaloo types
We're trying to get a
2nd March going
After January 6th
Norm's March in DC
Alex conflate
Boogaloo types
End bike personally
And is
Accusing Mike
Of trying
To get people
How to do an arm March while they sit back and watch
The chaos happen
You're pulling a me right
Bike called Alex a liar
The boogaloos Supreme leadership
Whoever they are
Go to DC the weekend for the 6
You guys didn't show up
Other people
Coming to DC
Just said that
Is it the word
Brother
Oh I thought so you're not going to respond
I've gotten messages from you
A printing them out individually
Charlotte wheatgrass
Will you said you're not the lordship
You don't have any problems the ATL
Are Southern Poverty Law Center headquarters
So Alex is now
Like this is
This is falling apart
Yeah
Alex's conflating
Other Boogaloo people
And this guy personally
The guy calls it out that you're saying that I did this
If I didn't do that
Alex realizes I got s*** I did
I just got called out on that slider
Hey if you were going to the splc tangentially
Quiet that you're an agent provocateur
I'm not even going to say it I'm going to be like
Hey you ever been to these places
This is
Giving off
Weak tea
Week 2
So Alex now goes out to break
He thinks he's wanting a little bit
He thinks he's got some win back he says he's made some suggestion
And then he also got Mike to say
That an armed march on DC a week after the
The capital would be an unwise strategic move
And somehow this is hypocritical although I think Alex agrees
I don't know what's going on anymore
I have said that
Oh good good for you I remember the Boogaloo said
You just said
I'm a coward
Fast action
Wise action
Police Department
Told me earlier that we should not follow the law you said I'm a coward I follow the law
You don't fall off cuz you're a revolution
City Council
We Belong
Local cops are issued
Lordship
You're that laughing cuz Alex thinks like you've got a daughter
I finally got them
I don't think so
Don't think you got anything there now I'm very I'm very bored with this conversation
Yeah I'm annoyed by it it sounds way too much like I owe you f******
Philosophy 101 course where they're like
Essentialism
And it's like you're both
Stupid
I don't appreciate
And this is even worse
Because you guys are not arguing about philosophy your life
How do we kill all the
I think I think that I can relate to what you're talking about in that I think
Stupid
Santa frustrating
Conversationalist
But I do still think there's an important
Okay well we were talking about how to kill
You're also seeing just yet another example of how
Ecosystems that have been
Spawned by people like Alex
Have now out ground
Them to a point where
They
AR
Able to embarrass him
Yeah
The Young and the Old Dan is always going to go it does feel a bit like that
Play theme of that
They come back
Is that Mike did not leave
After hours
Routinely insulted him
Suggested that he went to the splc
And pays the favor by blowing up one of Alex's narratives
It makes it clear that antifa was
Not at the Capitol
What I said was I would not incur
Inconsistent
Who's the guys in camo are that Lidia
And then get a few maybe 180th
Let you know there are
Not going to show you that
They were not in
Somebody point fingers at
You're failing when your point
They were not
Oh I'm sailing even though they arrested antifa leader
He brought 100 there I saw a bunch of skinny jean guys
Helping do it also this was Altra paper
That is it called
It's nice
Oso
Okay so should Trump be arrested for inciting this
Probably
I think there are a lot of other crops
So have you ever met
Livertox
A lot of people like
Oh and you want to put both hands on that I mean
Dude giving up
DF
A second time
Have you been to the splc you talk to them
And I just
You got anything
See now that's
The problem with getting that brief moment of victory
It makes the gut punch loss
All the wars
Yeah
Doesn't do much better it starts talking about now that Trump is out maybe there's stuff
If we can do now we can organize against war and this actually makes
Brings up Mike having a decent point and that is like
Could have done that before
Surveillance against
Let me ask Lord Boogaloo do you agree with that Lord Google Earth
You're cool with it
Tyranny if it's a
If you like which would be
Rebelution
Said somebody is in
Weather
I just talked about all of us unifying is forcing oculate
You said for the buried their own
I didn't stand around with up with a with a gun in front of stuff
Another cheap shot mister
William fireteams in the capital wing wings
Come on
Don't get mad
I want to complain about cheap shots and he keeps calling him Lord Boogaloo and like
Mister Dog.
Oh mr.
Now that would have been too far
Wow you ended with mister
You're dumb
Beer today talking about
Unity and unifying
I'll get together with folks and we like
Fight against the war and all this
And Mike
Which point is
Pretty fair that's like well you had no interest
In reaching
Out to any other groups when Trump was in office
You weren't concerned
With what inroads
You can make with cooperation because that's
The Tyranny that you enjoy
Yeah
I don't want coming from
Do you know
He's essentially saying your belief system is in Coke
Did Alex is proving it and Alex is trying to say his belief system is going to come here at
And he's proving that it's not
Is there
They're awful
Yeah all of them are awful
But when you have a coherent belief system it and you are in an interview with someone who doesn't
They're going to be like a wave on the mountain
You know you got enough
Totally misses the point
Mike was trying to make about how like oh yeah all this stuff
These real problems that you could have found a common cause with some other group that may be politically disagree with
You know inter
Person any kind of unity before but now you do
Yeah because Trump
Is not at office anymore
He completely misses.
Republicans across the border people who identify as
Is that your offer
Administration
French
Mike Mike
That's exactly the point that Mike is make
Exactly
How can you both call for Unity now and then proudly say
I would never work with black lives matter
Because I haven't we what was I saying
Boogaloo
More more pejorative
So
We've already seen a couple of instances of Alex trying to paint
Mike is a Southern Poverty Law Center
Collaborator
What was that the question
What comes next in the Boogaloo universe or is there no
First Urology
Who creates is the high priest
Who creates the audiologist
Does it just flow forth from where
It's autonomous and the next thing is Unity unifying the
Bodysuit
Running to us through our
Government officials
Is unify most people and getting ready to
And physically
Liberty
Well
Yes I have
They like asking questions at all
That's all and I don't like giving a mess
Ask yourself
If that pays good picture for you.
Well I just think what happened
At the Capitol
Ruin the great thing we
I was really hoping to blame you for it wow
You have been to go in circles around me
I guess you're an FBI informants or maybe you're working
For the FBI Idol
Do you think Alex
Expected some caginess or some non-answer when he has to talk to the FBI
BFDIA
Coming for me
Voluntarily and loudly calling for a revolution
I've talked to them and the only reason I've been murdered
So Mike
At this point has
To clarify
To Alex
Because I was just trying to pretend
They they are
Global anti globalist
Because they don't Target the same people that I
Driver killed Bill Gates
And told Mike has to clarify
New World Order
And I miss goes
Way off the rails
The capital is a symbol of us voting justices be
The New World Order
Bill Gates
And Klaus Schwab and the Rothschilds the new
They would be having the HRT swaps teams will be coming after your ass
What about Cedric
I need to control this.
What do we stand against
Assistant
But these people are legitimate
Netgear people
Their people
Different
But they don't work for the CIA
CIA sources
We are legit
I'm controlled opposition
I'm control
That's why you
Anything besides
Pizzaland
Legal
Awful wonderful
Dory ways to protest
And then there
Literally
From which is not the
Look at my
I take orders from God that's it
You fired the one
That was David Knight
Opposition
Ono Ono
Once again
Bad HR decision to come back to haunted house
I never thought I'd hear that said and seriousness
Twenty-year-old Boogaloo boy coming over like you're controlled opposition cuz you fired David
Boy
Eboy
Yeah
A man if only if only this is the one time where is he at
Just listen to that
Cbp's broadcast he could have just been like
Steve literally said he's been manipulating you this
Entire time
Yeah you're so easy
Horse your control.to opposition
I don't know I think the term
Is loaded
Oh yeah
Take the term controlled opposition is so loaded because
Implies
Like state
Control or something
I don't I don't know I don't
See compelling evidence
But Alex is like working for the feds
There's something like that
He is
Unreliable
Opposition
It maybe not controlled opposition
But he is
Persuadable
He's influenceable bye-bye people who play games with his ego and protect
Regular
His sense of self-importance
Closer things that
Are real
The real soft spots
For him and
Steve such a good
I would be interested to know if we discover a new
Thing that he's so we
Week 2 which is
Being
Belittle
Being forced to like
Like do you think this is going to make him
I have to be like
Wolfine I will act more aggressively in order to look all these idiot
I don't know I mean like
You would think that our show would be a part of his is psychosis
Made a career out of it later like him
He's not trying to he's not trying to impress
You know it that that's something I was thinking about
Particularly dangerous about this or something that makes
Is it more difficult for Alex
Is that like if he had
Somebody who is like an antifa person on he could berate them and humiliate them
Bike hit the pause button
We can't really do that
That to somebody who
Has
Credibility in the right-wing world in in quotes
Like somebody who
Might have access to an audience
Of
Right wing
People
They could like Alex
Yeah I mean
It's a weird
Weird thing from
Pop up into my brain but I was just thinking about how
In World War one of the big issues with
The
Chinese command was that
The higher-ups didn't want to lose face
In front of there
Subordinates
It's weird driving
Overall policy
By having this hardcore stands
That was imparted upon them
By the leadership and then the leadership realizing that
They were f*****
Couldn't then say like okay we're f*****
Because the subordinates would be like you got you guys are a bunch of
Cowards
So we created this kind of
Feedback loop
Run more extreme elements were
Even though I sensibly they were under the command of someone else
They were the force that was driving Thomas
That sounds like a right way
So Alex has been called controlled opposition and he did not take kindly to that
This is Owen cute
And
He tries to a guy
Say we're all friends here we all went out of the silent Revolution
We walk
Fast but
We got to do it later exactly that's his older
I've been arrested for my peaceful protest
I'm calling for
We have to awaken 50 million 100 million 200 million American
Before you can ever even think about doing a finger like a violence in this country
And have a chance of victory
That's all I'm saying
Doesn't matter we done some good radio
Well-spoken person
What you're saying
And so we'll continue to watch the situation I was in.
That's all I can say but
Hilarious
I'm independent
Independent
You're mad
Also I like the idea that he's
I'm not going to take cheap shots after an hour of cheap shot
I'm personally offended by
Him saying that they did great radio
Absolutely
I will save it as somebody who listens to ton of Infowars
I think it was
At least
More interesting
Sing the music
I don't think it's
Good and I think it's actually really dangerous
Negative thing but right we'll content
Looking at it as somebody whose external and recognizes nefarious motives on both sides bright
It is interesting to see the
The Clash
Of agenda
Which is
Humiliated me like crazy in front of my audience.
Confident at the end of this and I
Probably extended
Too long
Because I thought I could win in the end Drive traffic
Maybe I'll
Yeah so now Mike leaves and Alex
I guess now is aware of other things that he should have brought up they took for an hour
He lied in front of everyone
You disgusting little rat
What
Not challenged him to come back on the show tomorrow
Oh my God
Because I meant to go
Get to this I forgot about a while ago
Yeah okay so
Alex now has other post
Since it is I should have brought this up you had a f****** hour
I forgot I forgot to get to it I forgot to get to it
Twice if you start to the splc I printed out a stack of
Single tweet per page
And I just forgot to get to all the
I frequently brought up how he should be killing Bill Gates if he's a real but I forgot to have my
Evidence that he's a dirty little rat
I don't I don't know exactly what Alex is even bringing up in that context
Nor do I particularly care
No I don't necessarily think that Alex is wrong that he wasn't
Babe totally good faith actor
His interview Mike was being a little bit disingenuous
Why Alex is being
Disingenuous
Well I mean that you can't trust Azela tazel it has every just
Navigation for lying in the service of
Well there's one thing you can do with his out
Boxing match
A 4727
Do you think he's so freaking time all day long
What do I get the money chair
I am so sick of all these wannabe tough guys
Look I don't
Care one way or the other
But
Alex
That dude will murder
Will absolutely
F****** murder you would take
Is a little bit of ducking and dodging
Hands up
Hard to fight
For a long time and in my longtime I mean 30
If you're 20 years old you're boxing a very much out of shape Alex Jones
Like 47 year-old dude sleep apnea
Apologies
Okay you don't want
Connect on the first shot that if you dodge
The first couple swings he takes
He's done
This isn't this isn't a four-minute 40 situation where you can still go 10 Rounds
This is a dude
Who will absolutely destroy you
It would be it would be satisfying to watch
Alex talks to Pete Santilli
Got arrested after the Monday or know the amount or standoff
Cuz he's apparently
Now an expert on FBI infiltration
On stuff until Alex needs to sort of
Feel better about himself after getting
Clowned by this
Boogaloo dude
And afterwards Alex realizes I
Now right
I know I don't want to box
The first hour
I just see of fertile
And you know what fire by wants Revolution do whatever going to do
Call joke about my
McDonald's box
What's his name
Don't show
What's it called
Logan Paul and the other Paul guy
Logan Collins never get the other guy's name
The joke
Okay
I don't really want to fight you you. You're definitely be made that'll be really embarrassing
I probably would have at least a black eye
Knock out all of the teeth I've been grinding
I could use some new
Cooler heads prevail
I do think that I see the boogaloos as a way for the FBI in the
The man to set us up now granted
I've been spending weeks on my show using them as they Fall Guy
Part of the storming of the capitol
Just kind of the same thing
I literally tried to get one to commit to a
Cargoloc lemonade himself
I'd happily and repeatedly that he works for the globalist secretly
I failed
I guess we'll be fried
Friends now
So embarrassing
What did
Ineffective
Bad
But there's nothing good that can come of this I don't even know what Alex expected
In terms of like a positive outcome / list
I do think
It's really
Really funny
But Alex is doing this like
I guess, has got a prevailing we got to be friends with these people that I have already said
Are awful
Wow the intro music that's playing Isidore's don't play with me cuz you're playing with fire and everyone
I hate everyone
That was an intern
There's an intern who knows what's up
He medically that is really funny
Like I said this is sort of going to be a two-parter into Monday right now one of the reasons is
Because I do know that at least
Someone
From the Boogaloo
Folk is was on the show
Thursday I did not have enough time before we needed to record in order to get that already
For Friday's episode was that will be on Monday
Will will be back on Monday for part two of this
I haven't come up with a good pun
Like
The Caravan ready projects
Trust Me by Monday
I will have a great Bond
Was there a
Break-ins
Let's find out what's a good question
I don't know
Breakin 3
Rubber Boogaloo
I do not break a Breaking Bad season 3
Hyundai brake
We're having a great time
There was no date
Yeah they're going to get this game one of these days
I think I think that there's some fun to be had by listening to this
In terms of seeing somebody
Mirror lot of Alex's s*** back
To him in a way that Alex
Can't really deal with can't really respond to
Itsfunneh
You hear him say hey you're probably controlled opposition implies like
He thought that at the beginning of the interview
Is weird
Why even go if you think you could
I don't know I mean why not make that the thing you bring up
First I think
Because if he brought that up
First he wouldn't get the chance
To defend
Yeah the broccoli rabe
It would immediately become like
I'm not controlled opposition coloring
The beginning of the interview
The Poise that he's
He's showing or the kind of lack of concern with
The way out
Is portraying him they come from a place of like
I don't even believe you're real
Yeah I mean I could also definitely come from a place where I mean obvious
Paisley he had a
Quotes from Alex it could come from a place of
The preparation if you if you believe that you're going on a show that's
Controlled opposition
Yeah I imagine you'd be like
Okay
Then I have to find a way to defeat
That otherwise there's no point in going
Or or failing
Defeating that
Assistant place in a way that I can
Achieve my goals
Well not falling into the traps
That will be set
For me like
Hey do you work for the splc
Absolutely yeah
And I think that he did that and I actually think that's why this is dangerous
Because I think
B Mike successfully navigated the terrain of Alex Jones is shity interview Style
And I was given
A place where
He could appear to be the person who
Lives Alex
Jones's ideals
And I would not be surprised if I was not an effective recruiting
Mitul ya to anybody listen Galaxy
Alex should recognize
Intentional or not that is the effect
That disorder
It's okay
The boogaloos should pay Alex
Well and then there's just that
Known
Psychological exploit and Humanity
He sounds so confident
He sounds
Like a true belief
Fever and he's laying out
Stuff in a way where you're like
I guess revolution has to happen
Somewhere that Alex
Can't receive the exact can't disagree with it
The best thing is like what later
Later
That's a dumb argument
Do you have it
Opposition to Orange exposition
This guy who you saying I used to look up to you you were my hero
You're not
The Alex Jones but I grew up listening to you know
Creating that differentiation
Between the Alex Jones I grew up listening to and
This person I'm talking to who is Alex Jones in the present
Is dammit
It's
It's hard
The Clown
It's hard not to look at that like
23 and under generation and not
Nazi people who have
Who are burst in the misinformation age
You know like like we we live
Through it they were born of it
You know so this
Misinformation
Information era we live in
Like they're not going to be cowed
By old media
It's just not going to happen
And Alex is old media
We'll see what happens on the Thursday show will the bare-knuckle boxing match that has been canceled happen
Wait for Breaking Bad season 3 to find out
Jordan
We are trying to raise is going to be and if you could please
Please find a local
Call Charity Fund in your area to help
Emilio Emilio mdzs
Cork Darrell rundus
I'ope
Sometimes forget that I'm Daryl run.
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work