Damn important
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Knowledge fight
What's 5.com
Around novelty beverages
Alex woo
Pedro
Whatsyourprice
Well this morning my Bright Smile Jordan is
But he's understanding the weather in Chicago was such
That the recording last night would have been a
Unnecessary risk
In terms of
Transportation
I'm antibiotic right spot I guess is that too because of that little scheduling
Mix up
Shake up
I was able to watch a little bit of the Royal Rumble
Okay so I got to
I love a Royal Rumble we know who we know this 30 people running every 5 minutes or whatever
3 minutes timer
Who is the who is the person this time and within less than 5 Seconds
I don't know if it was less than 5 Seconds
But the sort of joke
Illumination
10 person was always at the hurricane
Okay character who's a superhero
Carter
There's a guy named hurricane
Add yeah he he's a sort of Goofy character who
Is the superhero
You are and yeah he got
I don't happen
But yeah I love a Royal Rumble I do enjoy this
The the pace of it I like the idea of
People just keep coming
Theme songs Kik
Thursday
Exciting returns and end
In that structure
And I enjoyed
Hydrated
Probably asking if I have thoughts about it
I don't have thoughts just was Hurricane was my favorite character
For sure
It was it was it was fun though
Who's nice is a movie called
Gigi colon
Psycho Gorman
And it is
You guys you guys listening cannot tell the door very hard
There is a serious
It's one of those movies that was made by
Just somebody 450 bucks or whatever
And it is
A live-action cartoon that is
Very occasionally incredibly funny
In a dry deadpan way
And also incredibly terrible
But it's one of those movies that I'm not going to recommend anybody watch
But I'm so happy to
This what year we talkin
In about an hour
Immediate
Is recidivism
Okay and it's just
It's just
Wildin out there and I'm say it's one of those things where you're just happy
Is it something like that is real you know if it didn't exist I thought about willing something like that and dig
Existence before possibility of becoming
Cult classic
I do know people aren't going to watch it
It's there
Manuel
High Praise
Absolutely feel like I understand exactly what you're talking about and I have no idea what this thing
Exactly
Jordan today episode to be talking about the time span
Supreme January 28th
And 31st
When do you start loving to go
Black
Bacteria
About
The 29th on Friday cuz that was a travel day for Alex
Coming back from Utah vacation
I'm also not going to be talking about the 30th cuz that was Saturday
Although I do have a little bit of something to say our special report
With the Stuart roads
Pompeo keepers
In studio
Where they did running commentary over a documentary about
Lockdown or something you are
I was watching it and maybe we'll cover this but it's just
The two of them having
Kind of a casual conversation about secession
Great
Cigarettes not really
Beyond just saying that they did that damn that Stewart Roads is standing by
These keepers
The capital
I imagine he wakes up every morning is like a didn't get me yet
That's it
The other thing that was worth pointing out is that the roads were saying that like what you should do
Is throw a big Rave sure and then when the police come to shut it down
Basically was on your right to live
Relay it man
Sorry I'd started off so here's what we do we set a trap for the law
That's basically his version of civil disobedience
And when they try to arrest you
Start fighting
Before
We dig some trenches right outside the way
And then puts
Spikes in there and then cover it with leaves and when the cops come
Have you considered
Qwiksite
Instead of
Spike's I find the quicksand work better
Destroys the evidence Derek actually came up with mote and but
It looks too much
I love notes
Now have you considered this
I know a guy
Ike's to hoist safe
Can I get a pulley system going
Hanging
Caswell
Dropped or safe
Also we need to have two people walk
By holding a very
I do like the idea that sat just turned it to Looney Tunes
Someone walks through with bunch of pies
Yeah it's
It's not a good
Special Report by any means
It's not interesting
And it's very long
And 7 I'll be cover
Jordan this episode will get down to business on it thank you
Spectracide
Recording the show
That's good idea
So first
The bosky thank you so much and I'll probably walk
I'm a policy wonk
Text Aaron
Text Heather Watson
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you the Watson that the little buggy
Zach the axe
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you Zach
I am also
New donated on an elevated actually bequeathed
There's no doubt that I think is really cool
Your
Wanted to give a shout out to Chicago Bond. Org which is the Chicago
Community bail fund
And I know that we've brought up you know like if I donate to local charity and bail bond in your area
Two specific one here in the city of Chicago and
Pointing out a specific may be helpful in terms of like
A recognizing
People in your area there is an analogous
Guess version of this
So please if you feel so inclined to check out the local in your area
And I guess your Taco Bell Fondren
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
Things about Tom and the Chicago Bears
Community bail fund
And then another thing we should take care of here up-top doing
He's got a couple of walks out there who are celebrating
The rotation around the Sun indeed
First Matthias got in touch with us
And wanted us to give a shout out to
Who had a birthday actually
Sunday yesterday recorded it on the day of your birth
So happy birthday either way
I hope you have a better 28-21 2020 blackjack
Kevin Nealon
Sister subliminal
Maria reached out and wanted us to wish a happy birthday to Eric
Eric with a
Can a
His birthday is actually tomorrow February 2nd
Eric
You're listening
F****** work on your thesis it's work on your history pieces
This has been slacking off too long to be positive
Ask that we wish him luck
Yep
I've decided to school
Absolutely also good luck on that
Happy birthday to you and also to everybody else who celebrate
Birthday here in 21
There's one car
There's one birthday
From David
Who says that every song should have a recognition of
As well
And I hit song for happy birthdays happy birthday
Do you
Happy birthday to you
Did you know that the rate of prostate cancer in men over the age of 85 is 100%
So there you go happy birthday
What a downer
Burn in hell you Satan
Wow
Quite adequate
Michigan Biden
By grouping that's a list of the to luminaries
I think of Nietzsche I think of biting someone I think a bike I think of
Of course
What is vitamin with the Ubermensch
Indeed
Theory start on the 28th
Alex has
I figured out that at this point
Avoid
Smokey Perez got arrested cuz they stormed the capital
I got to figure out how this works
Worth straight-up Oath Keepers and with a lot of these other groups
He's sort of been able to figure out how to thread the needle
Qanon it's like okay
Yeah it was all a setup with the proud boys
Obviously I hate them already there so
Soros Soros
Keepers are a little bit more difficult because Alex is
Longtime friends with Stewart Road but he's been a huge promoter of them
And so
Kind of has got to be like that if somebody infiltrated
Three of their group
Indicted
Before going in
Capital
Performance
Training
A month before
Capital incursion who knows if any of that true
But the point is is that
They are sending
Infiltrators into every major organization
So who knows
Could be anybody
We're always were always infiltrated strong take
So I was I was kind of confused when I
It's launched into this episode cuz the day before this Alex had interviewed the Boogaloo boys
Mike Dunn
Episode
I realize that we missed
A real
Great opportunity for a Mike Dunn Mike down
Did we miss a great opportunity
UK opportunity
It was there on the table and we we missed it has been humiliated
Browbeat
By this guy
Okay
I know that he's going to interview another Boogaloo dude on this
That Junior 28 episode
Okay let's get to it to the market to it
Instead
This kind of seems to be where his head's at
Let me just lay out what I think
Biggest and first and foremost
Trump if he gets off
Off defense could be
The president of the world as Chris reading
Very important
Chris Ruddy
Views as of this morning
Honey says Trump Canal because of the world that's actually a true state
What the f*** are you talking about
Okay so if I understand correctly Trump
Can become president of the world
Power and popularity
Hey man I got
You're just got to be the president of the world
You got it solutely there all
Aggressively against there are policies and I think you're a toxic influence
Burma now is that how this goes
Command mark
Whatever it's taken over by junta
You making it
Sandpoint
I would say the first president of the world doesn't exist
President of the world Buena position implies world government
If it if anyone could be a global issue would be president of the world
I don't want
Like Obama to be the president of the world I want Hillary to be the president of the world remember
Lot of time spent Infowars where Alex was talking about how Hillary was going to be the president show
Brandon bill was going
To become the Secretary General of the UN and then they would be
Together the president of the world
Alex's
Excited about Trump being the president of the world which
Again doesn't exist no
Proof
Hellboy very dumb
Which street is it
Easy going
How to get the whole world or border would like what is he going to do with the whole day
I guess conquer them
Yeah he would have to
There's a lot of stuff that goes unspoken
I know about Eritrea they're not backing down
Switzerland
Neutral
So
High-minded
Concerns
In the possibility of being the president of the world
Certainly
Very serious
Also Alex is a little bit Petty
She has to read a teleprompter speech
5 *
In that very short
Shortest route
Yeah
He shot her so she doesn't know
Planet
He is on
Is it possible that trumps was too long
Wyatt is preparation the worst thing a human can do in Alex
That is so bizarre like
Yeah oh he took it seriously
You know what I'm going to go I'm going to go crazy on Alex let me tell you this
I've got
Maybe 45 minutes of material
10 years to write that way more than 5 times performance
Is oftentimes
Yooper
Hair
Here unprepared
How to prepare natural I don't understand
You have to say something a million times to make it sound like you're saying it the first time there was a very big
Big difference between somebody who is
Desperately unprepared and off-the-cuff and somebody
Who is able to do things off the cops
I don't
This particular instance to is very bizarre to me
Because it's the inauguration speech
That's
Probably one of the most
Important
Highest
Spect the speeches
A big deal that you're going to give especially in the early times of your president so you're going to set the course
Maybe give a thesis for like what you want
I to achieve in your time and all that
Atone
I don't want somebody just being like a f*** it I'm going to wrap
I think it would Alex is saying it's a bad thing about buying this a actually a really good guy would argue that someone who gives 8
10 minute speech over someone who gives an hour speech is always better
And
Maybe
The preparation allowed him to parse it down to 10 minutes maybe trim the fat
About getting rid of stuff
Yeah
So now that Alex knows that The Oath Keepers were there
And arrested
And that's going to be
Maybe
Stewart kind of adjust
The Narrative a little bit and what I think is really funny about this
Is that Alex
Keep changing the narrative whenever new groups of right-wing people are proven to door
Open mail
And arrested
If we just don't let
The music Apple event
But they clearly infiltrated Patriot groups that used
Delete the chance
People from
Large Patriot group
Boogaloos
Quasi Patriot
Owen Shroyer
Rolfing
Controlled
Organization they really remember us being together by Noah Troyer
Of course you got
Proud boys that
Orange glitter Albany
Infiltrated
Reviewed all the footage
They were boogaloos they were proud boys and there were
Keepers
Deadly
Last night this morning
This morning
How to watch The Wall Street Journal report
The show Zoo
Sweet Frog boys being instrumental break
Outside
They're not all sad summer just useful idiots
Got caught up in the mob psychology but
Like the media
Why
It was all staged
If some of it was
People being foolish
Woody's trying to imply and does on this episode is that like the people who are leading
The charge
There is a couple people from
Each group that they had got set up right
To make everyone in those groups look guilty
This is complicated
So
Every single right-wing group
Was infiltrated
And then led to the Capitol
To overthrow the government
Right now let me ask you this question
Why was it so
Easy to lead them to the Kappa
Is it maybe cuz they wanted to do it
I mean obviously
It's not entrapment even if Alex's
Complete nonsensical conspiracy is true but also none of that is true
No you won't you guys tried and you failed
That's it
You've tried to overthrow a country
But you're not a user
So you failed
Yeah and also
I don't feel like Joe Biggs would like this kind of
Atone for Myla
Because it implies that it best
Computer useful idiot
Yeah he's calling everybody what it this is almost like
The Revenge of Stevie peas
Dammit
I'm still standing
Joe Biggs is got at like
I got to imagine
He's going to have
Some complicated therapy in prison
About
His relationship with Alex
He gets fired from Infowars cuz of pizza
The gates. Or he leaves he tries to start his own news Operation of go out
Kind of
Is associated with but it's like I don't know keep it an arm's distance probably show up
Besides I'm
Jumping in
Both feet why not
He rises through the ranks of The Proud boys becomes like
Really high up in the problem
Make the name for himself in the in the
Aggressive dangerous right-wing
Community
Batman storm
Capital
Wow it's so crazy that when it be
Sounds convenient they just cut loose
Scalp isn't it so weird they don't have that loyalty or anything like that
Who would have guessed man who could have seen that coming we seen it happen with all of these groups
Alex Ernst born in Moore
So someone who is loyal to a fault
Someone who is
Trista
Just
You know true
True as
The day is long I don't know
Rodger Stone
Okay
He kind of wants to imply that everybody history
Is a secret life.
They want to erase this Wrecker
Impeached
Nixon impeachment
Impeachment
It's not right and it's not fair
And we know that history is written
The historians are left
Pearlstein
As
This story is there a story ends there
Again
We can't let this happen you see I think this last fine
For the price
For his legacy
There is this battle of
A historical
Pushy
Yeah that you see that that is that is a really interesting thing that seems to be
At least subtly behind a lot of these these right-wing figures
But I find this very interesting
Alex believes in
Lower
Beating real
And
Completely false version
History
Rodger is attacking nestorian to
Yeah
I'll be in the problem is
History is left-leaning
The more you read about history the more you like
Oh those fascists are bad
And the more you see the fascist you're like oh in the modern times
The people who are doing the fascism
Are Rodger Stone and his bill
So it's
Kind of does seem like it's in their interest to portray all of history is
History is unkind to those who want to
To cling to
Biases and bigotries of the past
And
I mean
Pretty clear
Is that what's to talk to Rodger about
They
Impeachment trial is
Foremost in his mind
And
He really want
This f****** thing to be a circus he really wants Trump
Out of order
I don't
I wonder what would be
The most
Sort of politically useful thing
For this or the policies that we would like to hear would it be more effective for it just to be sore the quiet
And go through like
Process or would it be effective
I think if it's a circus it's
Probably more effective in splintering
The GOP
Yeah I think that it would
Lead to
Such
Embarrassing
Showcase
You know people in the Senate would have much more
Baggage
But for not
Ludington
Oh yeah
Absolutely think that maybe that would be politically useful but I'm not positive it would also be
A pretty embarrassing thing
Just watch
I mean for the concept of
Justice
Which
If you don't have
Kind of Sherrod Elementary
Justice
Society
So the idea of holding like a two-day little like
Hey Trump your evil
Your
Acquitted itself after
Expensive to the concept
Justice that it's like
Why
White believe that any punishment will ever
Come to these evil
I'm not even trying to
Predict or talk about like in vic
Acquittal
I'm talking about the strategy of
That's what I'm saying about a two-day trial or something like that that's so offensive to me of like we have
Evidence
Is incontrovertible I guess I guess what you're saying makes sense
It's like a 2-day trial with an acquittal
Or whatever is kind of
Whereas whereas
A week
Two-week trial where Trump is going crazy
Screaming nonsense conspiracy theories
And then an acquittal could be toxic to the people who voted for acquittal here's the biggest
Here's the biggest reason
I don't know how long Trump
Be quiet for his lawyer
True so the shorter
I think they all quit
Well I be
The five quit and now we got to like yesterday or some
Great lawyers
Oh yeah that was
Like
The longer it goes on the more likely
Play Trumpets to be like
I've got something to say
And once we get there then the fireworks start
Men left and right he's going to be born
Doesn't it
I Feel It In My Bones yeah
I can't wait to say good job Barnes
Bars is going to try and impeach
Be so good
Trump needs
To go in there swinging
Prolon order
And the guy that was she'll try to expose this election fraud
Use that as a place to
Put on
The evidence of election fraud could be able to tell him to shut up
This would be
This would be the ultimate
Reality TV show
Mini Scholars
We could get up to
2 months
Hell yeah
Degree up front
A few lawyers representing
If he does that they're going to hang him out to dry
You can tell him
Coushatta
Wiccan someone is being completely uncooperative
Just being like out of order
You can try a minute
Haven't you seen like I haven't you ever been to a quart
You know one of those quick traffic or it's where they go all day
You're allowed to just scream for as long as you want
22 months
And they can't do anything to you at all
Stopped in the Senate a crucial loophole that we refuse to close never if you just misspelled
Court
Can you wait about
People say tubal-cain
Some people just wait about
Filibuster
I don't think it's a good idea
I do like I think this is dumb
In terms of the goals that Alex has I think it's in the real world it would probably be unproductive
And I think there's another idea that's going around that also would be unproductive to the bowls that Alex has also
Because I'm against those goals
I think that maybe they should do it I'm not entirely sure
I haven't I haven't
Thought about or considered the the logistics of the possibilities of this
Idea of the Patriot party
Party splitting
But just
From
Basic View
I think what you would end up doing is
Completely fracturing the right-wing
The conservative vote would not
Be unified and Democrat
It probably it run roughshod
Attleboro
Seems like
That would be a really bad decision
In terms of the rice
Electoral
A two-month trial
For Trump to present his evidence
They would have to talk
Real slow
I think Rudy could handle it
Rodger is against
This idea
Of the
The Patriot party which I think is probably good political in
Instinct on his part
I think
I think that there's a lot of dangers
In terms of like were that party to get rolling
Any kind of
Actual
Foothold in power I think you could end up with
A pretty
Terrifying Overton window
But
In terms of
Fracturing electoral power on the right
I think there's a
It would be dangerous for them
Yeah Anna and Rodger realize
Globalist
Fun 3rd party
Because they don't work
English
Just give it legitimate shut off our energy supplies
Green Party
When you pull back from taking over parties you want to do is Soros and the globalist have taken over
Democrats
The comedy Chinese are taking them over
They're putting in their DA's are putting on their attorney general
It's a nightmare
We need as American people to control at least one party
We almost got there with Trump
Landslide
That is a nuclear option
Down the road
Just for him to run for president or something if he had to
We think that
He should run for governor or Senator or maybe he should run against Rubio
But I really think we need to get
President-trump
Back in
Back in DC that is
What we need to be the real leader
I don't
Fucken understand why you think he has any interest in
Running against Marco Rubio I mean maybe for the campaign you have fun with that you are sure I want to be in the
Good god no
Imagine imagine
Call God that
Terrible
Nightmare that
It's not all about
Trump
Cooperate
There's a minority whip tells you what to do
On the phone all the time trying to get donations and s***
Imagine that
Yeah
You imagine what kind of bills he would write in Cran
Brutal
Absolutely brutal
I've been able to
Provide
Senators in Florida with free fast food
No and it's a b so right
It's alright to be like 9 or we need to maintain the two parties
Sister because as long as both parties are awful
They can keep passing the ball back
You know so that means that they can still be owned by a billion
If any party governed effectively
The other party would be destroyed
You know like
Democrats already or like I know we promised 2000 but let's do 40
1800 you like
Guys
Really are we doing this
Okay we'll see the Republicans into years
Thanks buddy
Good work
Yeah
Stupid
The bomber
But Trump will not be a senator or governor
Why would he run against desanti
If he runs for governor there's no way the state remains
In the union Trump is governor of Florida he is the president of the United flooring
Lago de Texas
There we will take our second
That's not the Alamo ship
The Border
So Rodger is
Weird
Because he doesn't want a third party
Party is a bad idea
To give me the f****** money to the RNC f*** them
Trump should be president of the world
Republican National Committee
In the Infowars audience to follow
There is no chance that money is being
Amazing point
Please go back to
He said about Trump can merely the
The president of the world
Nationalism
Patriotism for Papa
It was a better trade deal
How would you be the president the world for nationalist
Very weird
Saragarhi where
The world
No one can move
I think it's probably a politically
I don't know
Active
To say hey we shouldn't have a third-party we got to take over there
The party but also give the Republican party any money
No no
Let's make sure we don't support them but also
We had to take them over
Yeah we all got to give money to the right
So
Alex
It gets mad
Here he's a Rodger
Takes off cuz he's
You said his Beast
And
Gets mad about Nancy Pelosi
Because
She is not thrilled
With there being members of the House
Who sings
Seem to have hostile intentions
Marjorie Greene certainly has said some things that would make me feel unsafe and
Work environment
She's not Nancy Pelosi is not happy about that
Good for her cuz I don't think
She should have to put up with that
Right then you have the the Lauren boebert
Of the world
Also
Making you feel super safe
Xog in an interview said that the enemy is inside
You know Alex
She's not thrilled about that not thrilled about that
Chandler Bing
Hey lady it was your supporter when the shots delete the tried to kill 18 others you lying sack of garbage
Spell Pelosi
That's what I mean by that
Sing about that clip is it's one of a number of times Alex has to over
Clarify
Elisa B
Alright
So everybody is getting caught for doing the thing
To do I better be real
I better redo it
Gloves you're going to burden Outlet by that I mean I believe that God has it out for you and
Your soul is going to have trouble and in this circumstance I'm going to put you to Romans 12:16 because nobody gets mad
Troy has been sitting along
He's theoretically hosting a show and Alex
Who's co-hosting but Alex
Doing the everything
Ideas what he wants to introduce
To the proceedings about how
Popular Joe Biden
I have some primary evidence
But I think it is
Stupid
But you know getting back to the Biden issue here Alex I was looking at this today
And I just have one little print out here just really work for the
The printout
Google search
Friends
The crew wants to do this they can do this I was looking at Google search trends
Biden as a Google search Trend was almost non-existent
In the year 2020
Almost non-existent Trump on the Google search stranded like
Number one
Overbite had the most votes
Ever
And then the other thing I noticed Alex
Two of the top
Word associations with Vidant really trend
Is this what we're doing
And dementia
So wonder why this diet
And by the way later
Because it doesn't really look good on a printout
The things
The Seminole
Because
This is huge
This is huge huge
Yeah
Google
Trends
Trump put out an online poll where
98% of people said they wanted to be president
I don't understand how buying one
Possible
98% of Americans want
Yeah this is
This is an instance of
Taking something on it
On the surface
Appears to be making an argument that Trump is
Is far more popular than
Not to the larger issue that there's
Since very dumb
So we got some guests coming up
After Rodger
We got a couple of
Big big hitters
But I want to let lister's also know Stewart Road
The last 30 minutes the next hour
Another one of the Boogaloo leaders
Joining us
A song about really happy
The capital
Ocir
Bad
I get from his four
But only because you can't swing a stick
I'm looking to Enrique tarrio thing
Bad guy
I like it what but
And it just goes with the territory license
What
Wow that's weird
Is
If he is a bad informants
A literal demon servant
I like that guy
Hays good guy
Look I don't I don't know what
Natario was up to I don't know
Now maybe I still haven't seen concrete evidence that you was informing on the Proud boys
His perspective he has to think that he was
It makes no sense to be like this guy was a scary dude he was infiltrating the right-wing groups in order to make them look bad make
False Flags
Demon servant good dude
Good dude
Jarring to hear Alex be like
Look up doctor this Boogaloo guy said I was a f****** inside dude like I was both controlled opposition
I understand I'm saying the same thing about him
And maybe he's cool you guys are doing great work together
Together
Man that's some
That's a
Really fast
The Boogaloo boys were supposed to be his
You take it out of this and now he's like
These guys
We're all
Chooses
Sort of distorted views of what Unity
Is possible or is
A suitable
And Owen Shroyer seems to be really on the
Unity care
We're outside
Project
He's talking about like reaching out to Black lives matter in
And folks on the last certain I saw I heard him screaming
F*** BLM
Positive that there was a
I think they burn the flag
Puerto Rico
Okay good
And Alex
It's kind of like yeah
I'm supposed to be above partisan politics
What happened
I don't want to fight with
All demons
We get soap are described them as demons
I got to take over the populace
Liberals
What do you think
I think
The reality of what Alex is talking about is
Some people on the left were tricked by my opposition to the Iraq War
I miss back when I could yell about George Bush and I could be beamed
Not an incredibly insane extreme right-wing zealots there was a time there where I wasn't
In the pocket of somebody whose mood I was
I miss having the facade of rationality because I was to the right
Is George W bush
This is this is silly
Yeah I will I will accept it
Unity
From these people when they apologize
Publicly and make amends for it and correct their mistakes then we can be unified again
Until then go f*** your
Speaking of unity
Owen believes that he sees opportunity in the GameStop
And Robin Hood situation
In order to bring people into the fold this disillusionment right with the proceed
Fairness
Of the stock market is something that he believes
That they can use to bring people into the rec
Of the Infowars universe
And I believe that that is
False Unity I believe that
The kind of thing that you see constantly
With anything that galvanizes people put
Pic-a-lilli online
You'll see an attempt
Infiltration of it by
Right wing
Demagogue
And I can see a bit of Owen
Seeing an opportunity there
Although
I don't think
That it's going to be a fat
It's going to be something
It's going to be even discussed on info about it too much cuz it's not
Not really a big issue and it also is something that
I just see it as being like
This might be a wedge
This might be something we can use
And Owen just doesn't have the shop
So we get to the the Nextbook book a little boy
Who comes a nice guy named Magnus pen video
Music
He is the Buffalo boy who was recently interviewed on the Jimmy Dore show seems to be somebody who's
Sing the round
A bit in terms of like being
Someone who people will interview
Sure and
I can understand why because he doesn't
Sound crazy
Which is
I mean A+
For a public face of a group if I was going to be the public face of a group whose main goal was
The second Civil War
Come on I'm a good dude I'm smart
Conversational. I like all sorts of people
And he has a different approach
Sort of a good cop bad cop kind of thing with Mike Dunn
Where Mike Dunn when he was on
The day before
Was kind of being brushed
We're the ones who pretend you do
Alex is taking that long
And also now has softened so much
Yeah, lip balm
The salvage or feel better
Give us your view on what the boogaloos really are and what you guys just did
What just unfolded
Activate the boogaloos
Yeah we're just kind of a Libertarian Anarchist coalition
Kind of a militia more of a movement
We started off
In the lockdowns that makes
Expanded throughout the whole George George Floyd
Once and we just continue to be operating on the ground is
Kind of a moor
Unifying not right or left
Armed movements
F*** you
Like that actually I want to get the left involved
Isn't the way
No no
I I think that you already see a contradiction between with Mike Dunn
The saying and what Magna
Message saying
He sang we got started in the lockdown this girl out of jokes about a second
Civil War I am not going to be told lies about your own history by a fish
Accountants sounds like
Ifucking accounting damn you're just saying that cuz the release the Boogaloo is there a real dork
Joke to start off an account
Alex
Really
Making
They talked
Here you are and in a lot of ways he talks
Talking about how like
I had this bad feeling about Mike done but I was wrong
Maybe I've been
Have you guys over all do have a good goal
Are you guys acceleration of do you want a revolution
I mean
We have you not only that A revolution is inevitable but yes we want a revolution
Form that takes
Peaceful
People's Revolution is he
Ignorant
Got to go after that they're going to try to
The Destroyer
On the offense
So I just think that he's steamrolling Alex
Letting this guy
Haven't have a
Very
Friendly platform
To present this exactly how he want
And it's
It is
Unaccept
Diebold assembling
To be like we want a peaceful Revolution
But
No
.
Now if you want to continue that
Thought and say
We want a peaceful Revolution
.
We believe that there is going to be resistant
To that we will fight that
Peacefully
Then that's cool. There's there's two kinds of
Approaches
That icbing
Possible
We have something like this group that is really interested in
Gunma concern
And what have you Second Amendment
Stuff that you can have somebody who's like okay I disagree with oppa
Open carry restrict
So we're going to get people together and we're going to have an open carry March
Right right
There's two things that can do to purchase you can't
Take one is that we expect we're going to get arrested and then that arrest we will accept
And we will use that to try and
Change
Public opinion by virtue of
Are arrest seeming unfair to most people
Or you could take the approach of we're going to do this and we're going to threaten people with these
Arrest us
Someone might get shot
I think the first
Might be
The first one is something that even if I disagree with your position on the open
Open carry laws
Are you Siri
Problem with someone doing a demonstration in a protest like that
When it comes to like
Someone might get
That's that's what we're in dangerous territory
Eating their their b*******
About unity and all that stuff
I I think immediately to a Fred Hampton
Like Fred Hampton
What is
A person who went into the Second Amendment groups these f******
Militia groups and was like hey
This is a class struggle this is about us
And convince them
And they joined
And then they act
Did peacefully and that's why Fred Hampton was murdered
Because it was that moving to the left
If it's the other way around
Yeah we're in
So Magnus believes and expresses that the man is trying to get everyone
Each other right
Sure sure
Alex
Okay cool
Cool
But a
The cops
What about you guys
Okay
He does not get the answer he want
Right now is
Is trying to get everyone to fight
And kill each other instead of coming together against
They want all of these groups they want
Antifa they want 34
Centers they want all these groups to
The other side
Evil thing in the world and it's
Secretly
Destroy them
So they can laugh
All the way to the bank
Kill each other
But there's no doubt that's going on but I mean
Local police
At this point I find it hard to believe that the local
When you look at Gunn
Station
Police are just going along with that and
When you look at
Lockdown
When you look at a rest
Asking people over
When you look at
Austin protest
Whether they be right-winger left
Task very aggressively and laughing about
Obviously I'm not saying that officer friendly in a small town has never done
Anything wrong
Some horrible individual
When you look at
The institution of policing
Bastian Tire
Bape forsaken Liberty and all Direct
Interesting here is that
Magnus is coming in with a complex.
Alex
Can't really deal with
Well he started with
People are trying to divide the left and right saying both sides are the most evil people on the planet
So they can never communicate with each other
And while they're doing that they're laughing all the way to the bank
Remind you of anyone
Connect individual comes to mind
The exact person that he's talking to his all of his time talking about how
Methhead demon-spawn
Whatever
Leaving that aside
Like
I I don't agree and I'm not going to side with
Magnus
Issues with
Policing
Issues with police
And Alex can try and deny that kind of stuff as much as he wants but
Magnus says he has a more interesting perspective
Savannah on
The police then Alex
I would counsel
Very hard
To remember
This m*********** is lying
He said he's making well
Making good point maybe in the service of
Lies maybe not lying cuz I do believe that he does have problems with police
That's more I think
What is
His attention to know this is
This is absolutely a f******
B******* way of being like see I listen to the problems on the left and we're going to pay attention and when they
Join us
We're going to team up and solve those problems
I don't know Dan
Have we seen what happens when
Let's say right-wing grifters find something no longer used
8 oz
But I would suggest that if you were
Thinking about
Them having good point
You remember what they
They do whenever
You're no longer you
Yeah and
I mean not for nothing
In the wake of this dude being on Jimmy Dore show
Some people did
Look through his Twitter and found him
Supporting Kyle Rittenhouse
I don't know man I don't know I don't know about this
For Alex though the question comes back to pretty constantly as it did with Mike
Kuiu Target in
I want to ask you about
In a revolution and what
Your goals would be of that Revolution
Will that do Declaration of Independence
Big Tech
Nether
Tweakers attacked Apple they would have legitimate
I'm just saying all the time or what
Are the local police
That sounds like a communist takeover of local government
No time for him to respond to that diatribe
And again it just comes down to Alex like is his
His two issues seem to be like
This isn't being director
Goodbye me
And you're not targeting the people that I want you to talk
Yeah yeah
My biggest issue
Is
Why isn't everybody doing what I say
Belkin b as X
Is Italy anti-global is very clearly like I am against global
Globalist
It doesn't matter because Alex doesn't see them blowing up
Can you imagine that's what Trump in the Senate would be like he's like why is everybody doing what I want to do
That's the whole thing it's a quorum I am a narcissist
I can't spell quorum
Soccer notes quorum
Quokka
Alex
Do you know he is problem
Seems to be that like
They have a revolution in mine
Revolutions probably good
It's not my Revolution and it kind of is a problem
Annie Bakes
An insane analogy
We had
But you're done on yesterday
Really thought about after the interview
In the world
And if they can successfully who that be great
I'm just really concerned about
The goal
General
Respected lawyers and
The Confederacy
You're literally describing the Confederate
That's 100%
And so we will reform our new Union and we have that right
I just see what happens
The capital
Which
Those two burglars bragged about
Don't try to walk that back whatever
I wouldn't call it a salt
I would call it a
A pissing contest I would call if you like
That's what you call it
Wow
Dan
What you see
Movies like Animal House
Walking off of lectern
In the door there was some ass Justified
It was wrong
Not a new Pearl Harbor
Your mouth is open as if in
Surprised
But what you don't understand is that the storming of the capital of was
Is basically like you know how like an old TV show
So so what
Is that the Patriots
Jump the General Lee over the capital bill
That's what we're describing here basically it's
Blake tpn
Yeah yeah lot of cops.
The right-wingers just egg
The capital what are you do we were throwing a little prank come on
Let me put the capital
Wow
Just while they waited until the capital passed out and then they put shaving cream on it and tickle the capital with a feather
I just don't know what to
Juon
And someone would
Try and say that
Like I just
Caesars
What is just
I want to get a white
Glove and challenge him to a duel I don't know what to do about that
I would say that
If this is just like
Slightly above
Brett pranks
Why are you talking about it so much that's a good plan
Also I don't remember
Spending days and days trying to scapegoat a frat prank
Anyway Alex is seeing the interview with Jimmy Dore
Did this guy did
And he loves it
And even before I even went on Jimmy Dore the only
I could even get on with
Which was a small decentralized
Yeah and I'm so happy for him to have me come on because
What is given me the ability to do is to break
Through all the mainstream media lies about us because
Bears
Extremist experts and journalists
Covered us all year long
Buckler eight-year-old
A video in
Text evidence showing what are movements about
And it doesn't line up with the with the main
It has all
These extremists
Work for DC
And quote them on certain parts
What time is this
Yes we work with
Dlm
Those parts of their report and
And run us all rough
The media and I feel the same thing
3%
Yeah
F*** you
The criticism is that the mainstream media Lacks
Some sort of nuance
Staying reporting on groups
Particularly like
The bugs
Sign
Great
I don't know if you're broken
I'm through that by being with Jimmy Dorsey
Say no I would argue no but then you know this
This is going to wind up with
This dumbass being all over
For the place I imagine
Jimmy Dore
Assertive
High point of it will be him going on Tucker
But I don't I don't know if
I don't know if he has the Escape
Trajectory
To get out of that bubble very much. I mean like
It does
It does indicate
Kind of
Places
But he has access to
Includes Infowars
Jimmy Dore yeah
At that should
How to put pause in a lot of people's minds
It's not a good sign
No
So everybody
I'm going to go out on a limb
And say that most white supremacist
Would deny it
Oh yeah I've been emptied the issue comes down to
The group is
The character the group itself is not white supremacist
And a lot of
I mean obviously there
Probably are
A fair number of white supremacist to fall under the Boogaloo category
Fair enough
The group itself is not white nationalist way to supremacist
Dim character
And that is something
That's the nuance
What's that is kind of difficult
For people who aren't
Engaged in these things
The relief to really
That's where clunky conversations,
The white supremacist Boogaloo group
And then
Kind of blue look
I'd like you don't know what you're talkin about
It's difficult even for me
Definitely understand where exactly a lot of the lines are
Alex tries to
This conversation
Far nicer
Then the one with Mike
And
It's weird because
The territory that Magnus is getting into should be really hot
Stole stuff for Alice
Like
Magnus
Is defending a
Alex Jones
And that's weird secured
You believe in free speech antifa doesn't
Is funded by Soros on record
I mean
The police infiltrated
To cause chaos
False flag
Some of those same
People that were at those WTO riots in Seattle
Are the same people that I
2 today better part of panties
Going to get really disillusion when they hear things
Just like you they hate
They hate
Goebel oatmeal Corporation
Free speech
Fox News or something
The camera on one guy that has a
I speak for all of Auntie
Global
This is a problem for Alex
Because he has contracts
To remember the things I say
Well that's a problem but also
If Alex actually believe that the quote-unquote Soros antifa contracts at Harrison Smith out of 4chan
Document should not be compelling to him
This argument to be like
Do you understand I have contract between Alexander Soros
America
You sir
Don't know
You're being trick
By the people on the ground who are
Who are all time, yeah
Magnus ver magnusson or whatever your name is
Let me tell you this right now
Everyone in antifa had to sign a contract I've got the document for you right here go ahead and read through the old
An idiot aren't iPhone 0
Stuff up because Magnus would laugh in his face
I supposed to think
It would be embarrassing that's why Alex is derrida's fall apart because they're built on nothing
Alex himself doesn't believe them
When presented with somebody who probably isn't going to play along
This is what I keep
Coming into is that like
Alex
Should not
Engaged
With zelle
Yeah he's a pretend Zealot and he's going to get found out when you go up against a real
And that's why he can't bring out his real narratives that he uses all the time on his show because
We'd be punctured so fast he's an instant disadvantage and somehow he still believes when he has these people
I can take care of it
The great reset is the problem
Or something needs to be a revolution
Probably Alex to work with
Antifa
We should be able to unify everybody against the great race that is literally
A corporate takeover consolidate power
Mentalism
Universal income
So they can dictate the terms of our surrender we have
Got
To get everybody mobilizing
What is your view of Magnus about
The great reset
I agree and
Because I had this conversation with an aunt
Remember they agree to it's not that
That's the idea of like Alexa
System everywhere but they are perfectly aware that
People that are pushy
About all these multinational billion-dollar Banks and everything
We need a reset but it's not this recent don't you this is a horrible reset start
There's a difference between a reset that involves rethinking our approach
To climate issues rethinking our
Approach
To what
People need to live
Kind of thing and reset that involves
A civil war
Those are very different and if you talk about them
Revolution
Not just like us your buddy in the water is in a way that is incredibly unfair
And that is
When you engage in that kind of a disingenuous
Sleight of hand
It leads me to suspect
Maybe a lot of the stuff that you're saying is not
Since you're not genuine
And that's one of the problems that I run into with Magnus
And in this next clip I think we really get to see this
Pretty clearly
Actually I was just on the phone with the woman that was at the WTO riots and she said she would be willing to
Come out and talk to you so
If you want to talk to him
Antifa member
Talk to an antifa member
But I never one
Like obviously the
The dictionary definition of acceleration
Basin is imbibe
Be correct
Everyone is calling
Think everything is
Fundamentally flawed and it will not change without radical change then literally everyone is
Acceleration
Acceleration is Rand Paul's
Accelerationist
Everyone acknowledges
Totally
Destroyed
The board
Exactly sold like a lot of people say like oh you want a revolution your acceleration
Everyone wants a revolution right now
Talking about it
Twitter
This
Is another manipulative sleight-of-hand
The accelerationism that people are talking about when they talk about Fringe right-wing groups
The militia isn't isn't accelerationism towards
Shooting violence
Ethan accelerationism that's rooted in
Heightening tensions and
Highly tense situation
And protest that
Have the potential to
Spin out of hand
And prove to be an inciting event
In a conch
Between supposed
Got it size of a civil war we see the water boiling and we want to push it over the edge
Accelerationism
That he's
Trying to make
The same
As accelerationism where you have people who are saying
Climate change is
A problem that cannot be ignored any longer
Yep we need to
Elect leaders who were willing to
Explore ideas
About regulation
Okay
It's not the same
Recognizing that our system
Is flawed in many ways and we are pasta
The point possibly even past the point
Where we can
Totally fix all of the issues sure he's not the same
Is thinking everything is f*****
And we should hope for a civil war
Because
It's going to happen eventually so why not do it now
That's dishonest
100%
I I mean yeah I understand this guy and you're you're 100% right good cop bad cop
Bulshit with these two
But God I prefer
The a****** from the other day
Cuz he and also he's just going to be like
Yeah f*** yeah
Blow it up
You know like I don't like this lying piece of s*** coming at me with his accountant I think that Mike was still lying to
It was still trying to put on a Pioneer
Facade do what he actually is believing
In promoting
But yeah this
This is
Just intrinsically unfair
Yeah yeah yeah
What do you presenting
It's intentional
Because
He kind of understands that there's a lot of Alex's audiences
Probably pocha
And it's hard to like bring up AOC and all I think of is
Ted Cruz being like being like hey you tried to murder me go fuc
Yourself
I get it you can bring up how antifa and BLM are also against the
Bad or whatever it is you want you tried to murder all of us
The other problem too is that I do
I do think that there probably are some accelerationist types
On the left
You can rationalize I'm get away to that issue of like
You can
Find Eco fascist
Find eco-terrorist
That's not the mainstream
And I'm ghetto
I would save it probably
The Boogaloo boys are a little bit outside of
The strict mainstream of the right
But they're closer than eco-terrorists are to the mainstream of the lab
Mnm comparing
You know I don't know I don't know if he would do this
By comparing like
I don't know
Gun-wielding accelerationist to protest
To Greta thunberg
I think it's unfair comparison
AR to the UN I remember that didn't she do that what you gave that speech
So Magnus wants
Peaceful option
Again do you leave a public representative of a group that isn't
Hayirli based around
The fantasy of a second Civil War
To the point where
Listener pointed this out to me
Bring it up on her last episode
Wearing a Hawaiian shirt
Is about Civil War it's
The gate have to get around social media
Big luau instead of Boogaloo
But everything is about you anymore
You got
I think that he is one Alex over to an embarrassing extent
And we need to keep trying
Peach blossom
The armor to BP
They continue to
One after another
If they keep doing that
Keep denying people
Redress
Then you're going to have
And it's going to be really bad for
For them for us and for everyone involved
I'm really impressed
I'm glad
I love to have you on with the
The lady
Reach out to these folks that I understand that
We can all drink
You're not drinking to mainstream media Kool-Aid it's your Kool-Aid
Magnus has got Alex so on the ropes
But he's willing to work with
Antifa
I mean China run antifa it's hard not to see that like
Oh well you're just nicer to Alec
You know like he healed course he agrees with all of this s***
Theoretically in his mind
But
This guy's being nicer than my done so you guys might have a good point you're being real deferential and I do
I don't see you as a physical threat so who knows
How this would have gone if Magnus was the first one
I don't think this interview can be seeing
Outside of the context of
The prior one
Very badly for 100
And it's not like I made you have to be delusional to think that Mike and Magnus don't know each other
Yeah you're probably right
About Alex getting
I'm going to go on
It was cool
All you got to do is say that he's a good dude and super smart
This is embarrassing and Alex
Is
Just
So bad speaking of
Interviews now Stewart Roads of the oath
Keepers comes Andre could work into this idea that some of them got arrested
And took
Shifting gears
Constitutional lawyer
Award-winning researcher
You name it
What awards
Nonviolent
Defensive
Keepers
Arrested party
Members of Congress
What do a very good job there in the capital just run around Lihue
Any of that
Y'all when we woo
They were like Jeffrey Osborne
Junior
It is
It's kind of astonishing
Quickly
Hand wave
A literal violent coup
Yeah it's Astana
Well it's so important
For people like Alex of people on the right to do that because
So indicative of
The sort of danger that they present
X2
A civil insane Society could say that the enemy is within
It's very important
That's the hand waving have just don't understand why people who
On the other side
Don't
Keep stressing this
Really aggressive
Cowardice
Money
I think I think maybe but I think also just kind of like
We all are just exhausted
That part
Go to bed
A lot of the time whenever I'm
Lionel getting an episode ready Alex will say something like
Yeah and then I have to like
Deal with it
Sometimes in life
You run into walls like that news don't want to deal with it
Maybe some people don't want to do
With veteran hand-waving is a good way to do it
I mean when you look for Alex
It's it's an existential threat
Recognizing that his worldview implies this
Is is really dangerous crap conclusion of what you say
This is not some like infiltration this is not some like
Oops we were meaning to do this and then this happened this is what
End goal was and you did it stupid and you lost
Unlike Jeffrey Osborne who won
Trying to do it. I was just
Talking about in terms of awards Stewart Road
I don't know what
The case is here
You what he was at Yale he apparently one
An award for paper on enemy
Combatant status
But he wrote
Think I was able to find the paper
Any flaw
I didn't read all of it but I read some of it in as I kind of seems like college paper
It would have been a
Pink 2000
Conveniently
Yale
Their records online come out 2005
Oh so weird
So I was able to find the recipients list of pea shooters
It reminds me of Mumford the movie Mumford
Oh yeah yeah
It's being a psychologist everybody who could verify his time in college.
Daiso weird so weird we've we've met some people like that in the past
So
Store
Is kind of like a
Where the situation that our founding fathers
That's what we need to do is set up a ton of a cities
I think okay
Make sure you do with the doubters to
The reunited
Mutual defense and also for
Grassroots
Politics
Separated themselves
Even before
Smuggle
Underground let's jump
Let's just
Alex is currently in a luxury resort in Utah
He has an iPhone in his pocket
This is this is ridiculous
God damn I hate
These people Selma
It's a bit of a mess but not as much of a mess
As Alex's narratives about January
Yes this is a huge problem for him
Because as we've seen he's had to gradually expand the narrative
Based on
New people who get arrested eration of this narrative
One of the reasons for that
Is
The people that he's tried to blame
The Boogaloo boys stood up to him
And he got embarrassed by two of them
He can't
Throw The Oath Keepers on
He's too connected to them
Stewart Road
This is good buddy Yep they're they're tight
He can't do it
Cowboys
He also probably can't throw them under the bus completely Joe Biggs was like the second-in-command he used to work it in full ride
Enrique tarrio they were independent contractors that kind of stuff that those people
On the show before he spoke Alex's c-pack of honey
This
Alex could be like I was in bed drunk
It's too difficult for him and so now he has to kind of like
Do this
Founder of the OT bridge is here with us
Worried about this
12 hours or so self-styled militia members in three states begin
WebAdvisor capital
Breach USC
Well I sure didn't bring the weapons and I sure didn't do all the things they supposedly
It was the Q phenomenon behind the scenes that also secretly Trump's giving orders to storm DC and all that
Honest having
People demonstration
Calling for a senate investigation
Ted Cruz is calling for
When you get the demon
System
Weather
What is the capital
Ellie got a few problems you get a few boogaloos you get a few
Keepers in the mix
This is the new Pearl Harbor
The Narrative now is just
So intensely complicated and shifted so far over the course of the last couple weeks
It's
Continuing to go along with this is
Just embarrassing
Cuz Alex
At every stage is that he's proven all the thief
Yep and then everything
Things shift so now
Hugh
Is the Q movement is the real villain Shore
And there's a couple of people who I guess I would go probably I'm going to guess soon he's going to say sheep-dipped
You going to call these people shoot
Yeah there's going to be a couple sheep-dipped people in each of these groups
That were there as infiltrated provoke
Contours all these groups are actually good
Just had a couple people who are
Apples
And those groups were actually globalist
Plants
Busy
Too complicated
I guess I guess he has too many Q followers that listen to his show but if it were me I would just go
Hardon cubing controlled by the globalist
The whole way
I know he's hurting the cube
Turn all the cute people into global
Snow that's kind of where he's at
Right but I mean like straight-up
Queen braids
Everything is their fault they're the globe
Sure
You know
I think that's interesting
I think
Can you be difficult
Like argue that all the people who believe in queue are aware of a globalist Plata but they're apart of
Kosher
That's okay
He's he's saying
Accu is globalist
Intelligence and
Like that
But the people who fell for it and we're in on it
Or do you not like that the followers
Weirdest good researchers who got taken down the wrong path them in with all the people who use eight
Francophile Democrats
Are evil people there just been caught up in this whole thing you know you just
Depends on his mood
Yai
He don't know I strive to
Yeah I keep
Any kind of
Through
We are through line or belief that Alex
Someone is to blame and it's not us it's a fake group is controlled by the global
Show up against a Boogaloo boy and they're like you're like
Accu s*** man you are the stupid ones you are being controlled by The globalist Who Run cute
I don't know
I think Alex realizes that the new generation
Not going to put up with his b*******
Stewart Rhodes
Is not like Outlet
In many ways
He's scarier
Terrified
But Andy also is not
Somebody who throws people under the bus
That's true Alex is willing to throw anybody under the bus right
Immediately
When it's convenient
Yeah I imagine that military service will give you more lawyers
Loyalty to your comrades in arms
Radio host
So one of the people that was arrested
Storming the capital
One of the three of keepers
Stewart Rhodes knows for a fact
Is an oath keeper
And you won't deny that
And he also spent some time on the show promoting her crowdfunding caved
GoFundMe set up or not to GoFundMe
It's on rally today
The fundraiser for Hulu
Actually remember who was involved in that
So we can always sit behind our people
So there you go
But you aren't part of this
Nachle na
I'd never do that now I am going to
Try and help fun to defend somebody
They're my people
That is
A kind of loyalty that is
Foreign
Infowars
Are you saying the cheetah thing that you personally think was
The bad idea
But you're still going to Defender
What if you threw her under the bus
Then maybe you wouldn't have to deal with it all your money
So we are now in a situation that is exactly the same
Identical
What the colony
Saw
In the colonies
Okay
What do you spell
He's deteriorating
Extremely, he looks like
Walmart
Blue Bloods
What the hell's going on here
It's you should look at this as DC is now the green zone
From communist China
And we're the same exact position
Exact position
Explain to me how they're the exact same position
Storages Deadman
I disagree
Stronger
Stewart is he's not an acceleration is
Siri said we're in the colonies and I'm pretty sure that what that required was that a literal Revolution
Before that they had people writing pamphlets
And stuff
The Oath Keepers are very similar to Thomas
Pain
What might
Were they to be Stewart Road might say that
Stewart's
He's trying to
Have this like
You know like that it's not time for action or whatever
But he does
Give
A little bit of a contradictory message
Pier
And It's upsetting
That shows our weakness because
When they when they try to give orders to violate our rights
Territorium George
We're
We can't wait too much longer
Because
Confederates
You have to do something
The timeline
Globus tours
But we've got to do
I mean folks nobody's happy
Panther
I told you that was coming back
3 minutes
Before you let out literally
You have Stuart saying that there's a sweet spot
I think we have to do something before the military is done purging
Also the military has started that put the clock on it
QVC we're not into acceleration what we are saying is that it's going to happen shortly
Anybody
4550 minutes
Yeah that's not good
The 28th wraps up
Snopes
You're so good
Alex is like I said on the road
He's come back.
30th
Roads are in studio
They're talkin about this dumb documentary
Talking about how they got a seed
Very stupid
Navigate to the 31st
Sunday
Episode
Open Alex's
Basically describing how where in Revelation
John the Revelator the Isle of Palm
Patmos
The Beast
Looking forward to it
That part wasn't in the Bible
Is Drake Marvel
World government cannot buy nor sell that a marshmallow out of the hand
You Must Destroy every genetics you must kill the Earth
Are you will not be allowed to live
La pelota
Believe
John was the greatest science fiction writer ever 2,000 years ago it was not for whether you believe he was
Inspired by God he was not
It is not
So
The old Chinese proverb says
13 *
We certainly aren't
Fishing times
Armageddon with the dragon
Folding
Go get your pop
Cuz you got front row seats to
Is it 10 years 100 years hours 60 minutes away
Being an hour
Dragon might be here in an hour okay
Okay so I'm not fair I got to pitch for you
I heard the Grapevine
Let me get the character
Okay so
You've got the Book of Revelation
You've got this whole like Heather the hand on the mark of the bee
Butcher of the devil
And you realize
Everyone has a phone
So do you get around being
Higher Book of Revelations if you just never attached it
To somebody's hand or forehead
He just win does he win if everybody has the mark of the beast in there
I mean it would certainly seem to indicate that the prophecy was a little bit
Pittsburgh
What about like
I don't know that there's so much
Any of those prophecies like
Like why
Custard
That's true
Existed
What am I trying to think.
French fries
They did not have those
That true they can even have friends
I don't know what I'm trying to get
There were some things that were missing
From the
In terms of it being a wormhole
I don't know I think it's unfair for Alex
Looks to be like could be a hundred years could be an hour
Get your popcorn out you might die before it starts but
Do you have them up already
Or in 100 years
So big news
Yes on Sunday
And it's that Australia has ended
It's covid development program
I'm about to go Australia suspend Nationwide their entire vaccine program
Now ladies and gentlemen
In the world
We are ending our vaccine program.
House not work
We believe you cannot make a vaccine
That works to cure the common cold and that's what this is
With even more mutation so it's even more impossible
Alex's editorializing on what the
These companies are sad
Problem
There is that like the one in Australia was developed by the University of Queensland and a biotech firm called CSL
And the one that mercury
Different
Don't say we're working on
And those are also different than the Pfizer
Anna Madonna ones
They're all fake
Tall fake vaccine treating them like they're all the same thing
It's a it's a syringe with some liquid in it Dan it's the same s*** it's very weird
Perspectives doesn't understand anything
Actually that's not the news
Breakfast for the news
The big news has to do with Emmanuel macron
French president
Who came out yesterday
Chronotope
Globalist
Understand
Metra crime you'll be torn limb from limb
The riots
All the signs are coming out
As opposed to the other
I told you months ago
I talked to the head of a major biotech company
That's real gene therapy
They also sell pillows
And he said you're absolutely right
Giant Total Takeover
The vaccine will destroy and sterilize women
Kill your immune system off the charts and give you cancer
Too bad for somebody with knowledge
Potentially save
The world
Billions of people seem like he would want to get that information out there
I guess
He's not responsible for
French president macron said that the Oxford AstraZeneca vaccine appears to be
Quasi ineffective in people older than 70
65 excuse me
Which is a claim that scientist strongly rebutted
What about the top
I don't know who that what that mean
Did not come out against the vaccine or vaccination nor is he trying to save himself from being torn limb from limb
Also this
Is not the same vaccine as the ones put out by Pfizer in moderna which are the ones that are currently available in the United States
The claims that Alex is making our
Surd and it's super convenient
Big Time specialist
With magical Medical Technology won't come on the show
But honestly this is your
What do you think that's the most I'm about this
Good enough
The AstraZeneca vaccine that macron is talking about season 2 in mRNA vaccine
If you were a member of the Infowars audience you would think that all these vaccines are getting developer all the same thing
As if a company is racing to finish the same recipe
But that's not the
Case
These are different approaches being taken of varying levels of success Sunset back
Alex doesn't understand
The basics of the topic
Pixies cover
Cuz work
It is not meant to reflect reality it's meant to push an agenda
And this is just really sad cuz all his
His ideas are about mRNA vaccines being different than vaccine
And that's why this is particularly evil Hema Kronos that
And that's why he's getting rid of this Oxford AstraZeneca vaccine
But it turns out isn't an mRNA vaccine
But Alex doesn't know that
Macron claims
Prezenta is almost in effect
Over 65
Alex doesn't know s*** he doesn't know anything he's talking out of his ass
It's so this is how arguments get made
So
Australia
Does not work
Not work
That's it
That's the level of shitties bring into the compelling
That is compelling I remember going to
The mighty first year
I didn't Ridge
Start out in literature I originally started out in audio production
And I was there and I was looking
Clipboard
Going through all this stuff and I remember my teacher screaming at base
Yeah
I think that's part of the game that's being played here is like
The audience
Is obviously humans
They
I think that if someone is yelling
This
Repeatedly over and over again
So definitively he can't possibly be making this up how could you be this
Confident and make something up at
The same time people can't do that
Possible.
Simply inconceivable
And
Unfortunately here we are
So
Staggering
Statistics about this vaccine that I would beg him to
Demonstrate
To the vaccines killing
Not just the famous
Baseball
The vaccine
50 year old 6 year old
Dodge
Before they even leave the clinic
And then have a convulsion and bye-bye an hour later
Bye-bye
Absolutely
They all report
Putting in hospitals and nursing homes that
5% of the patients are
Dying within a week
The MRNA
Holyshit
5%
Fatality rate
Alex you need to demonstrate that
That is a legit like there should be illegal
I mean that's it
Insane you could need to somehow demonstrate that like
The him saying that people believed it and it led to harm
But I do
Don't think that
Like I don't know how you'd prove it but I believe it like I believed that causes harm absolutely
Without question
5% mortality rate
Out Quest
That's outrageous
F***** up
So f***** up that would be the number one story in history
Culmination of all of Humanity's knowledge about infectious disease results in 5% of
People dying immediately
And I don't think that you get to make claims like that
Willy-nilly
And yet
If you can't yell fire in a crowded theater you can't tell you it's a lie everybody that they're going to
Die
So the vaccines are a bio-weapon
Apparently
I would like to stress this important point
That I brought up that
I don't think Alex knows or cares
These vaccines are all different vaccines
And somewhere not mRNA vaccines
The closing and everybody down right now
Nest
World leader starting with d
And starting with senators
Come out and play
What do you think
Kronos
Do you think the Australian snow
Suspending their vaccine program
Because it closed
Does not work
Quotes
Work macron
Work Australia
It's a f******
No weapon
The MRNA vaccine 14 Serebii
Make train your body
Well one of them at least
That you were bringing up isn't it Mr
Placentas nonsense but there is that
I just
I don't know
This is desperate
Anyway
We don't have time
Ester all-white
The inevitable thing
It's going to happen as has always happened
Is it Alex says something it sounds silly
And then twenty years later what do you know Alex is right
All the way we are living in
Exactly what Alex predicted we would be in 1991 if there's one thing I've learned
From doing this podcast
Best hits
Don't
Ever doubt out
It stands up to scrutiny true
He's he's right almost all the time
Even when it contradicts
Other things he's almost always right about
Be very prestigious
Yeah never believe
He's very dumb
Mostly it's just talkingshit
Remember the s*** he said
Abu don't have time to wait for him to be proven right we need to act on the things that he saying now and just trust that in 20 years
Yours will look back and be like that God we listen to Alex I just don't trust people who make me want who say I should do that
Very very dangerous types
We don't have time
Or here later
How to get that song about who's right
The enemy has written plans
It's so easy to beat the
Operation lockstep Rockefeller Foundation
Online
We just bring in a planetary police state
Buy disease X something like a weaponized cold virus
Control
Variance would show up all the time so that
Lockdown
Just making that s*** up yep
I don't know anybody that's actually has adamantium claws
In 20 years will look back and be like
I can't believe
That this was okay
Did this guy got away with this ship
That's my prediction
So if you want to
Now think about like
Okay you think that you're going to be proven right about everything
Here's the kind of shity
This is an exact
In elementary school in German
Play the actual train videos
When you're seven-years-old you should have to marry a Muslim
Muslims will be the future of Europe to Christianity fat
I would like to see those I would like to see it
Very funny video to share on the internet
Where
The Germans are teaching
Elementary School
Behind if you're not dating Muslim by fourth-grade eleven-year-old what are you doing single
The Old Maid
Never get married at this rate
You're in sixth grade you should just get some
Some cats and I love my cat there's nothing wrong time cat
Yeah this is the kind of s*** that Alex says
Horribly bigoted nonsense yeah
Anyway the globalist
Yes senor
Always
Might just be a few years behind
What about Plan B
Plan B never said that
Stop
Didn't happen
Find
Listen to Iowa
You were supposed to have a whole internet shutdown
Independent Media left before they did this they weren't planted launches for
They want this early
Nearby schedule
Ketchup
By launching early
What future plan
What
Everyone hates them out
Call Schwab
Boris Johnson
He's talking about like the releasing of covid
Release the covid-19
Brothers chicken
The idea that he's putting
Fourth is that the globalist or a few years behind and so they had to pick up sometime
Super Evil worldwide organization that is orchestrated everything
Still a few years
This is a plan that goes back to the devil
Beginning of History I do appreciate that the devil cannot keep a timetable
Bright
Just behind a little bit in the song He's behind
Kicked out of heaven
Realflow Face outlet
This plan that is
Millennia-old
And has to do with Trump
Seguin office
Or something sure
They're behind on it
This evil plan
And so they decide to release covid a couple years earlier
What's the point of a few years
Honestly if you have a Bolivia old plan and you're only a few years off 6000 years later what
That's really efficient. No one's going to remember though that
Really official
A few years in this scale at time is meaning
You got your ID of work project it supposed to last a year and you're 3 months behind people are furious at you
Get my pickups
Sometimes
Hey guys we're not ready yet for this plan that's going to end the world
I figure we just go for it
We got a 50/50 shot the problem is that Alex is still on the internet
Crackdown
Time that they released
This thing right
So
Yeah
I didn't get a reason for why they should problem why didn't they shut down there
Can they not
The goal in the motivation is to make up some lost time but
The plan that they're engaging in requires that the internet be shut down to be pulled off successfully
Why would they do this thing to catch up on time but they don't have one of the essential pieces in place for
Right so dumb
Okay so here's our plan it can only be stopped
If we allow Independent Media to reveal our
Plans Ryan stop everything
I'm glad we're having this meeting
Crucial first step
Terms of us being able to pull off this in a barbecue it's the only
We can take
If we wanted to go early I'm glad we're only
I'm glad we're all on the same page
Alex will destroy our planet
Movies that back to
Devil's eyes
Our plan was to go
Rewrite on this evil
Atlas is about to Marvel at our great beasts and then he's just going to go back in in the seals are going to close again
Cuz we forgot to shut down the internet
F*** dammit
You know what this is on us
We can't claim ignorance on this one
We knew that Alex was going to f*** us up there are exit interviews for the higher-end
Sorry guys this one's on me
My bad
I'll take credit for it anyway this is
Catalog this in the Alex's plans of the globalist to make no sense
Yeah they're real bad it what they
They're real
Bad guys almost like he's making it all up
So
I got everyone really excited and over the weekend was there was a piece of Wall Street Journal
About Alex being involved in the funding
King of the
Bastille January 6th
Yeah yeah yeah
I read that article and I don't think that Alex comes off looking back
Terrible I mean
It's just
Organizing and fundraising
Alexander Augustine looks like way more of a
He's a real dangerous lunatic
Somebody to get my radio show and then maybe the profit incentive will keep them for being too much of an a******
Possibly hair
Alex response
Do this piece in the Wall Street Journal and I think he responds exactly how I did
And that is
I said all of that stuff on air
Hundreds of articles
TV shows
Call breathlessly saying
Rally funded by
Help
Jones organizers say
Forward what I said
Rally the 6th for the money
Got to secure the venues
Authorized
Porta potties
Well-known
I was planning
To try to do all of this
So that we could storm the capitol
From my perspective I think Alex is kind of right
Yeah but I think it's this reveals a couple of really funny things
First of all like just beat the idea that he's like why are they
I said
Yeah yeah
Constantly said the lot of the stuff that's in my Wall Street Journal article to sort of Revelations
Are things that you would know if you listen to Infowars
The thing I think is really funny
Is
Like let's say January 8th
Alex has been talkin about
Paid
For part of this rally there's that
Wall Street Journal would never report on that cuz it's just Alex saying that's fair
That is fair
Alex is an unreliable we believe anything this guy says
Alex Jones and I don't believe a word of it to someone else
I don't know I think that would almost be something that
Alex should be called as a witness at Trump's impeachment trial is going to be
I mean he did just say that Trump told him you know I didn't have a hard time putting himself in the center of a
Metrology
Because of this Wall Street Journal PDF
Don't never call me as a witness because I tried to stop
The storm
I'll call you in a minute
Only way to make the impeachment trial board Ludacris would be to invite Alex Jones
Can I remind you you're under oath
I don't even know what that means
Yeah that's why I think it's really funny that
Like a lot of the underlying information of this article is
Stuff that was public
Prior but also
Maybe bulshit not Coronavirus
It's not proven
I thought the second thing that I think is really funny
Is
That the article says quote mr. Jones personally pledged more than $50,000 in
Seed money for a plan January 6th
In exchange for a guarantee stop speaking slot of his Christ according to his funding document outlining a
Bo between the company his company and an early organizer that pay to play of course
To get a speaking slot
That's wild
That that's kind of embarrassing it's in the article it is
I'm paying for Acts
Yeah there's there's money and you don't have clothes
And there was no way that I was going to get a speak inside of Trump's actual good god no
So I mean I figured
He did speak tonight
Before that might have been what he paid for
Yeah kind of a bummer
But I do think that those two things in the Wall Street Journal article are pretty fun
The unreliability of Alex even speak about his own life
To pay to get a speaking slot weird how you can both fall so far and you
At the same time Inspire Rave literal overthrowing of a country
It is
Interesting up-and-down kind of scenario there
It is interest
So we end this episode now Jordan
Evidence of why Alex should never have to pay
To speak somewhere
As long
As he's forced
To speak over assert
And song
Understand
Is there ashamed of their power they don't want to force their way to the front
Humble
They love their man
They love their friends
Do that
You belong in charge
You belong in charge of your life
Your family your destiny and if you don't take control
Corrupt system
Call Amanda follow the basic code God wrote on your soul and it stopped
Because they're not following.
Falling the Fallen one
Absolutely
That's why you
Say that
That was not the best work he's done over that song
There were moments
Flickering
Passion
I would listen to
Cover album of him sing talking Woody
He thinks the lyrics
The songs are
I don't want him to do that
Although I do think I'll be interesting at the side
I want an album of just that song 12 tracks
Just that song
But different days
Alex just
How old is Drake freestyling
Whatever is on his mind
This is like a great thesis at the beginning
I know about powerful man
Go from there
Go for it
About Alex
All he does
Does something to him
It doesn't it I didn't hear much of what he said I was too busy singing a lot
What is a sultry a sock
Grapes
I mean it's a the lonely Shepherd
It clearly
What's Alex into some kind of his own without like
Blowhard
No narratives right now I'm just going with straight inspirational f******
Clear Eyes
Full Hearts belong to this I can see the right hundred percent
Absolutely a bunch about like being able to kick himself into a psychic State and I don't believe that but
That song kick him into something
But something
So we come to the end of this exploration Jordan and I'm left with
Sort of a bad taste in my mouth for Alex and his
January 6th to narratives
I think I'll be interesting to see as we get closer to the impeachment how Alex
Probably trying to egg Trump
Into
Turning it into some kind of a circus
What ends up happening with that will be
Fascinating to watch
Alec Steele
I do worry about his malleability
These
The fact that he can have
These people the bugaloos
But he decided where afbi cutout group yep and he said he'd
All of this
Women have two of them on
To manipulate him and embarrass him in different ways
So easy
It's it's
It's a mess
Yeah
Yeah I imagine that
This is
I think what scares me most about this
Is how easily
They are hand-waving away
What even Alex
It was like
This is going to f***
You know Alexa
Aluxes Isla I got to back away from this this is all
This I know this is bad for me
I know that this
January 6th
Takeover of the f****** country is bad for me but it takes
Two weeks for people to convince me that
That's not good cuz he's trying to have it both ways
Trying to retain that this was bad but also like all of the actors who were actually involved in
There were just a
A few people in their organization to her secret globalist we're trying to make them look bad
It's too late
It's too complicated are you still trying to run interference for people who are
Going to do what he wants them to do is going to steal fundraise
For his housekeeper folks
Who stormed the capitol
Alex is making it very clear
There
If you
Kiss the Ring sort of or if you
Play ball a little bit
I will
Pretend that all the members of your group
Who do bad things
Are not really part of your crew
Yeah exactly
Stupid
They expect
Sorry episode will be back with another upside down to the weekend until then
Also on
We are also on Twitter that knows I go to bed Jordan
Facebook Facebook
What is iTunes ended
If you could please find a local charity or bail fund
And in your area
Back but until then I'm busy explore come Darrell run this some the juiciest
Dice Cube
Holding
Alex