Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
But sit around drink novelty beverages in a little bit about Alex Jones what's up
My bright spot today Jordan comes in the form of a series
Decided
Make a note choices on cereal right
It is a Dunkin Donuts
Flavor
Mocha
No mocha coffee.
Hard pass
Throw a spirit that box
I stared at it for a while because it was like well
I'm drowning
But there's another voice that was telling me
This the novelty that's going to get you burned
Right right
Honestly there was also when there was a caramel macchiato
And I said that looks gross
That is definitely going to burn me
It's is right between those two
Perfect greige
2fa
Yai
I got it it's great
Ecorse shockingly good
It takes like a mocha coffee so I thought they were going to taste like donut
Type they know it and it's got like
It's basically the texture of it is there's like little marshmallows and then the
Cereal itself is basically just like Cocoa Puffs
Okay
It's just a
I don't know I mean
It's not great it's just
I expected
To be a real dangerous proposition
Imagine Dunkin Donuts probably won't release cereal based on my coffee
3 flavor which is
Black
Just a bird
Terry verdict
Black
A whole pot of it
Hosted going to come out with a full Journey
No cream I don't foresee that happening
Drinking coffee
This introduces an actual interesting problem was that bad is that if you're having black coffee flavored cereal
Do you put milk in there
Absolutely okay
Brood
Silly
Haha that's a that's a red eye
Not Material
What about you with your brights on
My brights is the new album by madlib sound ancestors
Very very good okay good it's all music that was
Made by madlib over the span of like
The past two years
You do you do Mad Libs
You know how all he does
Just sit around and make music all the time
I got that sense, I don't know him personally but yet it seems Seems like he likes music
He's like one of those guys who's just like
I know what I do
How do I make music and everything else
Yeah that's that's basically like me and looking at Alex Joe now why I'm drawn to you and
People with your weird committed people
Because I'm a little late
R5
Is arranged by Four Tet and it's
Really really
Really really good
I'll have to get that out of spit
I've been getting back on the bike a little bit and I've been needing some more music
Throw into the rotation I've been listening to a lot of Polish ambassador
Enjoy the Polish ambassador
Skype
You think I don't know we'll see the Polish ambassador
Listen to
While I enjoy there's an album called
I got it
What album are you talkin about actually pull it up here cuz
You forget names of things really easily
Do you know it's like within the last like 5 years or so something's albums
Mario
Vocalist that have a group called wild light
Amanda even album called
The tide
Coming to that's really
It's good for a little bit of riding the bike cardio Stout
Check out that madlib album to just going to end up drifting back to like Carly Rae Jepsen
Girl with mixing a little bit of that
I can listening to Sky I'm never going to hear the end of it
I got to be trouble
I generally if I have that feeling I only listen to the Sami Zayn intro music
Cuz that's great
Batman also Christian
Supertones
I rarely ever listen to other Scott stuff on
If you listen to Chris
Skin scab
Backwards is that like running away from God
That works
So Jordan today we talking about February 4th
Sucralose
Stuff happening
On this episode
Requires our attention
This is Thursday's episode so
You know it's right hot off the presses yes indeed
Ride to get here and we'll talk about that as we start
The first villain Jack
Ewok
I'm a policy wonk
Lego next long-winded thank you so much right now if I was you want
Thank you very much long-winded hear the spiritual connection with anybody was aliases named long-winded I've been accused of be
Someone who uses back
15 * the words
Next I guess murder Hornets were just a filler episode you and I'll follow siwa
Next time tamarine I submit to the globalists thank you so much right now politics
Thank you very much camera
Mr. Jim
I think you took a people donated on elevator that would appreciate that very much so first he's a sandwich
Call One Work thank you so much you're now technocrat
Take my money you filthy animals thank you so much right now it's
Technocrat
Money off that heroin
Large
Which name to because
The gotten into some aggressive arguments in my time about whether things are or are not sandwich
Yeah I've heard of people doing
Disconcert to me babe
It's people that have strong feelings about sandwiches really introduces a philosophical question
About what does
Constitute
Sandwich
Hot dogs
Is classic
Thing that will cause people to come to loggerheads
A divisive topic
But once you start talking about that you enter the world of taco
Is the Taco thing
I know see that's what I'm saying once you start getting into that
It's dangerous
The slippery slope only trust
The word of the Earl himself
And he is not
Spoken regarding hot dogs so I say that it's fine or it's not fine it does not matter until
Alright well
We will go with that
So Jordan today this episode like I said we're doing February 4th and
My path to this was
A challenge
Because I was trying to get myself really motivated
You know
Talk about Alex on Monday Monday
Cover the week
And then he started talking like this
I can't handle it
Transfer
All of the
Resources and jobs
Overseas
The public's got to go into a conscious mode buddy gets really unconscious
Just trying to accept what's coming
I love him to death but I said if Mike Lee whatever sticking up
You got to tell me on here
Open your eyes look for problem
I got a booger hanging out of my nose
They will do it
I called her second straight up
Don't work
But it's going to take
Yeah I was now wow
Load up
Okay you basically having an HR meeting where you scolding the crew for not telling him that his collar was out but in
The guys of talking about how when you're unconscious the globalist composed
Seem like he's turning what is a very Petty
You guys should know I'm incapable of basic hygiene
And take care of me he'll tell them
Talk to your staff during the breaks
Make your points
I just wasn't like this so
Stupid I can't even
Wild yeah it felt like walking through with knee-deep mud and I don't need it
And so I decided you know like maybe I'll go
And try to find some Project Camelot
Indeed
Nugget
Not great so we decided we're going to a time travel episode to go back to the past
I listen to episode from 2011
Alex trying to get really excited about the Bilderberg
And it made sense
Everything
Use really excited about this Swiss
Holocaust denier that he didn't realize of the Holocaust denier
Jordan
I heard
February 4th the year 2021 and Doctor Steve pieczenik
Musically really appreciate it
Power number 2
That is
Catnip
There's nothing we can do
There's certain times in doing this show where you just got to resign yourself to like well
Steve's back on after saying Trump
Still be president
After January 20th or I'll eat my hat potentially
If he's not president then I'll never come on your show again it right if I am you got to hire me
So no one is happy
Interested
I'm interested to see what kind of big
Swing is going on here is a lunatic
I don't know babe you just never know what to expect
And
I'm hoping for a double down
I'm hoping for him
To come right out and
Say it
Trump
Still Perez
I am going to say
Completely unrelated to what you want
Sure don't take this as a sign whether that is or is not going to happen okay
I'll say that I was a little underwhelmed by this
Interview on both of their paw
I was a little underwhelmed by Alex and by Steve although there is some hilarious stuff it happen
Should have been screaming at each other constantly this should have been a knock-down-drag-out
You have been lying to me since the beginning and I then
Stevi B's we like
Of course I've been lying to you you're a bull ride
Not that Steve agreed to do it or if he did he doesn't
He does not give
Ward Park
It's nuts that Alex
Clearly doesn't have more of a plan
Obvious
It's just
Instilling
So Alex Sabaton the second hour
I got to get
To some other news in the first hour
What cities are liars and I'm going to show you AOC caught in the LIE we talked about
Look up where offices
She's a junior member of the House
Actually been there while she was a congresswoman tits are scurrying around the halls
He wasn't even in the damn capital
This woman
Is a congenital
When I get to that in a moment
Launch about
While
Good stuff good
She didn't claim to have been
Cynthia Capitol building
But her building itself was also evacuated
I don't know I understand that the right-wing really desperately needs
To try and minimize the
The human trauma
Those experienced by the people who are the victims of the
Consequences of their rhetoric
Are we tried to get you guys murdered but you're lying about
Yeah I understand why people like Candace Owens eject Pacifica really pushing these things hard and Alex
Now jumping on
This is well like I get it
It's just
Dumb it's
It's awful.
Toosii
Denying
Denying her her
Experiences is
Yeah I know it's more f***** up things I can think of I
I'd like it if I
From an empathetic
If I put myself in their shoes I imagine I too would scramble
Because I would not want to reckon with the idea that I am essentially an attempt
4ukey
But I don't think that they have
I think they're just basic
Psychopath
Tonight like what this is what we got to do to protect the
The grift not that I don't care I don't care
Murder
I think part of it is protecting the Griff but then also I think a part of it
What
You know it is something that is so essential to a lot of these narratives is the
Inability or the desire not
To feel bad about anything
Yeah
And that would
Penetrate that bubble pretty hard recognizing these are human consequences
These
Fiercely theories in this this b*******
Get paddled
And to recognize that would probably introduce some bad feeling
Do you know that
Not in their interest now that would hurt
Yeah
So Alex
Just Mayo see shared and then he flips into an ad and like he doesn't entire segment
It's just ads
The entire second segment of the show is at
It's just unbelievable
It's toothpaste so I can hide more money in his company it's a drag it almost feels like Alex thinks that announcing that Steve's going to
To be on the show is going to somehow boost ratings
How many does extended commercial
The message
Then he gets back to teasing
Steve interview
Dr. Steve pieczenik we have to clip a planter in a few minutes
Has the courage to come back on the show
Here a month ago before
January 20th
And
Talk to him
Can't wait
Man
Here's the thing that I take issue with with a comment like that what Alex is doing is he's framing Steve's commented
He shouldn't be prediction prediction
Yes
Steve's
Been saying he's involved in
Predicting something will happen no
Doing
It would be a completely different show and people would
Take it as seriously if you just like
Hey I don't know anything I'm just get out here's what I think happened
Intelligent
Expert with all of his connections if you're just going to ask him for random ass predict
Yeah when he says I'm involved in this s***
Then
You know your brain is like oh he must be talking about something
If he just says I predict this is going to happen even start to recognize all his predictions
He's not doing well anymore
Might be a bad idea
Experience
Completely different to a listener when you presented as like
I did this I put
QR codes on all the ballots
You know what I what I don't understand about alley
Is that I feel like he was missing that
Golden opportunity
Of like
When you when you can cut ties with one of these assholes
It's like getting rid of it's like when you're playing Go Fish or Old Maid or whatever it is where you can like
I'm discarding this card
I am not losing the card I am
Giving it up giving the bad thing away you know like
When you cut ties with a Stevi B's
You can throw so many
Bloated narratives on a
Like just toss all the s*** that you don't want anymore out
Exactly be like. All that was all seems like you'd like
Go all-in
You land it all on him don't matter you wouldn't be lying
For the most part is fluent
Stalzys Naked and Famous
Play I don't know I think it's Steve
Because of Alex
As built up
His own organic fanbase
Is a threat
Italics
If
If he turns out Steve to
What a goddamn moron
Basically are just like pointing guns
They're just sitting there like an impasse
What are we doing
It's a goose builds up these
No-win situations with these lunatics
And then here we are a man who is more dedicated to
To hoisted himself upon his own petard
Seems to work I mean profitable
I'm also I forgot about this
I forgot we we need to give a shout-out to someone whose birthday
Alexis sent her an email and told us that Sean
Celebrating a birthday happy birthday
Just wanted to give you a little bit of a happy birthday happy birthday
Mandy Moore
Birthdays
No it is not
Nobody asked nobody which
Shih Tzu more birthdays than you would die sooner
No they don't want you to have no more
Kind of a guy but the more birthdays you have the closer you are to death
But if you do cuz if you have more it's further off something here alright
What you to race closer and closer to your end
Dornier literally making no sense
Because neither desire
Text
All right here's the bottom
Let's hear the bottom
Most of the first hour is spent with Alex talking disgustingly in
Grotesquely about child
And we're not going to listen to any of that
And I have my reasons for it
And if anybody takes issue with that I will say that we've covered some of that stuff in the past
It doesn't add anything to
Demonstrate these things at over and over again
And I
Believe that the way that I look
What's Carrie's himself
What has the potential
To be re-traumatized
Two people
And I don't want
To be a part of
Bringing that to our audience
And I want I want no part of it
If you think that is
Hey Ben
Inappropriate decision on my part I would encourage you to start your own Alex Jones podcast
We've had out many times has he been on the show saying that s***
Go back and listen to it
Saying the same s*** it happens a lot
Singularly grotesque
Example of it
And I only have two clips that aren't actually about that but are about like
Little things that he's saying
On the side of
Those conversations that are kind of stupid and maybe a little bit
First one
Is my cannabis
There are a lot of currencies on the planet
The Establishment operates.
There's cash
Digital money
There's a derivatives
There's art
There's drugs
Their sexism
And there is
All sports
Pleasures
I mean a big one is eating dead.
A lot of establishment people really lie
I'm from morgz and stuff
Dead kids and people
Watching blade
My dad told me all about it
Guatemala news
That's how I know this is nonsense
Wow whatever you're Alex Jones me like I'm a big serious expert on the New World Order
Dad told me people getting eaten
My dad said one time that I need a person
I would say that if you want to be taken seriously
You can prove these claims you don't need to say my dad told me when I was little I discovered
While you were sleeping if you would love to someone will break into your home and brutally rip it from Bonneau
Need your pillow
Will they leave something behind I don't know
But I read it in the news later on in life it's been
Confirm
So Alex Jones's dad scary bedtime stories notwithstanding
Detail with the more we learn about his dad
The amount of the f****** dude f***** up Alex a f***** up.
Except you.
So the other clip that Alex has here is easy
You know
Whenever you like
People get rich
They start to need more
Exciting thing
The mundane pleasures of life sometimes
Are not with a
Sports cars
It's an escalation problem the moment you've achieved your dream now you have
How to find something else to
Bright Alex discusses a little bit and I should tell you this
This is a family show
Very popular first album
Eat big bowls of fresh PCS
Right off of woman's rear end
I just want you to know
What we're up against and what we're dealing with
Alright Alex
Okay
Fine
LOL
Here's what I saw
Nancy Pelosi
Sitting at
Much like ours right
Like I like it
You're you're fairly close to me if you were to stand up turn around and just start shiting into a pole
I could grab a spoon in
Eat as you s*** out of it that's what I saw Nancy Pelosi
Is that what you
I didn't have any mental image except for Alex just like his brain trying to be like what can I say that's gross
I mean look
Humans are not
Good eating
From a nutritional standpoint it doesn't make sense for people to eat human
And there's also
Nutritional issues with eating feces
It's not I mean both are great
Particularly
Pleasurable
Sometimes I order Chinese food tonight I know it's not maybe the most healthy decisions about the
Pleasure of
Eating
I imagine the same thing as Trooper
Eating s*** coming out of a woman oral fecal transmitted
Or I mean eating humans
You can come down from with
Alex gets around to the Steve interview
Easing into the introduction
Coming to you live from the 80s
Broadcasting worldwide
I'm not going to try to rehabilitate
He did leave the CFR and say 9/11 was an inside job
Paul the real perpetrators out
We're actually involves orchestrating
What
I thought he was buying into the whole Q8 Chan deal
Here is a problem
For me
If you believe that he's a man
Expert inside person
He should not be
Like at all persuaded by Q stuff
If you have for a moment
The inclination to think
Steve pieczenik
He's getting it
Influence by stuff on a message board
You should very seriously question whether or not you should take anything anything seriously he is supposed to
To be behind the scenes
Which would be behind the siop that you have argued Q must be
So how could someone behind-the-scenes unless you saying that there's a
He behind the scenes
By the other behind-the-scenes people
3Q
Oh no
What are you doing letting him behind the scenes if he's going to get tricked by other people behind the scene
Started is too good It's Tricky
Please shut the f***
So Alex is gracious
64 coming back and my note on this is just like why are they doing why why
Appreciate
Steve pieczenik coming on
I am
Amazon
What's punch that up
Is this the beginning class Center
Why I just I don't understand this doesn't serve anyone's interest
Steve is going to have to go even
Further
Out on a limb in order to
Retain any sense
Credibility at all
Alex is going to have to either
Confront somebody who he clearly does
The fortitude to confront
Or he's going to have to get persuaded by Steve to wait and see
Whatever
Situation for anybody except receive nothing to lose
The Alex's insistence on
Not
Preparing
Coming through immediately with us
I don't even remember what date it was I wouldn't
Promise to me
The world would
Oh my God
60 sucks and I think he's a real liar and a menace
But
That being said
I do think that
The first question that Alex asked
Is on
Okay I do think this is not the way even there
This is not how you want to start interview
Tell us a joke
Are you in with a few guys were you part of the setup or were you really
Believing this was going to happen we really appreciate you coming on
Number one eye
Enjoy coming on the show number
Is the ad hominem comments
Disgusting
Yours
Thanks that I lied for in some way
Gave them false
Promise
Table turned on you in a
You don't get
To do this
You do not
Alex
Alex tries to frame the interview
With three options for Steve to pick that are all bad. Steve says I like coming on her show
We're going to say is that you
You're disgusting are you this bunch of assholes who keeps saying bad things about me
Wild
So pathetic
Yeah Steve takes control he only texts
Just none
You can see it even at mediately just like now you're
It's not even in over your head
You don't have the wherewithal is it here's what here's what you do whenever somebody does that one
That is a shity opening question
F*** you
Steve comes back with
I don't appreciate you say hey
F*** you Steve you f****** lied
I would suggest that a better question is not
Three possibilities
That are all things he can't possibly accept
More open-ended question that is leading
To the
The f*** is wrong with you man
That would be a better opening
If you are wise you will allow Steve to hang himself right if you were the one who maybe prepares you to have a question
Guide you towards where you want to go as opposed to one that you're
Person you're talking to
Wheatley reject
Yeah
Volvo of all the like
So simple
Judo
Principles
To be put into
To be demonstrated right here
Alex attacks with overwhelming Force
And Steve just
Get out of the way
And then once Alex's horse
Has gone past him he turned the back
I came on the show again
The basically say to you
I will double down on the military
And the reason I'm doubling down is that
Right now
It's taking more time
And I don't directly deal with military operatives
Yes I had in the past when I went over
Received
I still have faith
In my side
I have faith in my special
Forces
I have faith in the generals
You don't have
Special Forces theme
I was right I was right he did double down that is what I was expecting
Yeah maybe
Not the not the point it
Yeah
Yeah it's not it's not as big as willing as you do but it is
Is cool
I mean like in terms of like
Now what are you going to do Alex yeah
Yeah
Steve was wrong he came back and now he's telling you he was right
You almost could have predicted this coming seeing as how he has had no interest in whether or not reality
Conforms to his
Bulshit Stevens
Absolutely gaslighting the s*** imagined that he would baby come come try to me
I'm sorry for lying to you also you're not even getting to the under of the underlying emotional problems
Which has he told you
He has been using you
Yeah yeah they don't get into that
Surprise
Everything is going according to Trump
Plan apparently
Only one person in the media really understand the gift
This subtle thing that's going on and that is
Is the Trump is being quiet
Maybe
That's because he's got an impeachment trial coming up and kicked off all social media
One person
It's it okay
This should piss off Alex but I think
He is distracted
So what I'm saying to you right
Now is
What you're seeing happening is it
Free what Trump wanted
App
Music
You got to remember one thing us
Elsa 20.
And by the way
He is remain silent
Only one
Individual
Repeat it
That's Bill Maher
HBO he hit it right on the head
Why
Is Trump
Silent
When India's history
He has never been silent
Insightful
Alex's big anime
It's just
You know who they watch all the time
By how much they reference
About how much they hate them
Free time
Because you watch Bill Maher all the time so you
Can hate them eventually says something weird like
You know what this bill Mark I might be right
Cuz you guys are f****** chill
Toddlers you can't
It's just two seconds of Lego I hate him I love him and I'm not going to say that this person doesn't exist but I don't know any
Anyone I like who likes films
I don't know anyone I like who likes Bill Maher either person may exist
And I just don't know it
And I wouldn't judge them for it
But the only people I have any evidence watch Bill Maher are people tweeting stuff
Yeah
Alex and hoop dance
Yeah that does sound right
Is the old is Bill Maher just
Maybe that's why you going so far with the racist right nonsense it's just he's like oh I guess the only people who watch my show Arbor
Is Dennis Miller and you might be dead as melaragno
Goddamnit cowboy
Equally on funny
Trump his whole plan right is to tighten
Show his ass
He's going to show how incompetent
He is
And this is where Steve begin
Things to drift into
Possible antisemita
He's showing you how corrupt
I said to you before
Text
People who aren't
Confident
And Coronavirus
Primarily
They were Jewish I have a synagogue
Going on there with blanket
With all kinds
The people in there
I've never met
What's a rolling company
It's really be
Paola Marino the point that people are do how
Wow it is you you are I wouldn't have even thought of that is something to bring up unless I were saying
Nazi
It's so weird the way he speaks to just that like
I've got
I've got these people in the government like
I think he just designs trading card.
I genuinely think that he just draws like magic the Gathering cards
And they have like
Nancy Pelosi
Deep State operative written on them any just
Begin to wonder
If he's not like
Severely Disturbed
Like
Weave
Talk about him I think it one of the reasons any may not come off as that is because he's in the Infowars fear
And Alex portrays him as like this really
Serious
Character in
It's really funny when he sniffs at Alex
There's a part of me that
You know it has to wrestle with like
He actually think that he's running like
Special Operations teams
Does he think
He has sway within the government and he's got these
He's 11 Jewish people who he's never met working
In various offices Mecca
The problem for him personally I don't know
His wife laughing in the background that clip makes me really
Think that he's aware
She laughs about some other
Up to
Shiza
Maybe she's on this on the same boat she's in the front seat of whatever boats
She's not too thrilled
People either
National Security Council and the state
Department
And Wendy Sherman
I got a two on top that has never been in
Flower gorilla 45 minutes
Are the Galaxy there cuz you realize like this is going too much
Don't say I got to do on top ever
Outrageous
Outrage
So in this sad this next Cliff they get
To the heart of the matter which
Got anything
You're actually more correct
At the heart of the matter is that
Steve reveal that he's been manipulating our
Feeling getting into that cuz they don't the issue is
He said the trunk
Still going to be president
After
January 20th
I get a little bit snippy
Alex gets snippy
Steve-O
Let's just go back
Let's just go with your scenario
Doing is anti-racism Stand Down
Military coup
You're saying there's military coup what's going on there
Dodge right on the 20th
He was going to get inaugurated
I said that he would still be president of the United
What's going on in Maryland
Oh no
Psycho
Hang up
Steve thinks Trump is still present course he does what's going on in May
Exactly.
Hang up
Out like
Now na
But you have that
You don't get to be angry at me right
You don't get to do that
You don't understand what's Happening Here
Alex
I guess
He just has to put up a
Put Steve saying like I did things going to get inaugurated I think it's to be president
Todd Brown
So Alex tries to be a dick
Attractive
Reclaim some sort of like
I don't know Authority in the conversation
It doesn't really work and then we find out that Steve also hates Mormon
We already knew that
Talk to his cuz you're so smart
Like I said
Tell us then what's what's going on here
Telling you right now I said it's
Do you understand
Indiana Matrix
V-neck
And he's showing it to you
Party
McConnell
Total wastrel
A corrupt individual
Mitt Romney Mormon
He reminds me of the days of the
It when they slaughtered Christian
And I didn't do it what
He warned orbit I've got to BECU you wore these must have listened I warned them
You don't want any more massacres on your hands
Holyshit Wild
Also interesting to recall vets
Steve also said that
The pope got arrested like a year ago
At the beginning of the first wave Steve claimed Authority was to say I got your audiences been
Crawdad homonyms
Yeah you're a liar
A little bit later Alex realizes that he called the audience
Disgusting
Flip your disgusting audience
Are you in some people that said disgusting things about
The most naughtiest
Unfortunately I don't even read most of
Let me be very
Frank I'm not interested in what your Aryan
I don't really listen to
Text Ami on the Shelf Cooling
I don't even know who Q is I don't read that nonsense
I have nothing
Or anybody else
You're the only show I go on
This is
This is outrageous man
There's no point to this
Just be me and the only reason you would do this interview if your alley
So you can
Throw away your baggage on C
Well you do that dude recognized that like
He does bring up repeatedly that their last interview got a lot of traffic
And one where Steve was on with Owen saying that the election was a sting operation
I got a lot of traffic and so I think that Alex has that motivation
Motivation
Cuz of course
Yeah it's Alex will take like a little bit of this if it means a couple hundred thousand
Views more
M-theory
Forced Steve to hang up on
On you or if you just
Steve you're making everything up
Steve if you always been a second and I will listen to you
Only on the answer the question why are you such a f****** liar Steve Steve you don't give a s*** about what my audience thinks great
Why are you such a liar liar get in there
And because I was scared do that Steve's with running circles around him
You specifically
Let's just get this straight
If people understand if you were wrong about time are whatever
You legitimately thought
Propaganda
I didn't say you be on the 20th
He will be in the United States
He won the election and it's important not to recognize by
What is your view on what's going to unfold how long will it take
Cialix is just
Supplicating
What are we doing
Trying to find ways in which you can accept the things that Steve is things still the president
He's trying to make excuses for Steve Turley
Which is wild cuz
This is supposed to be like Alex's
You were wrong damn how old is he
He do this
Who is this
Possible
It's it's
It's just I've seen it too many times
How can one man never learn
Is it busy physically incapable of
The active learning
It makes you wonder if Steve's not like
Independently wealthy in like
Paying out
There's some Dynamic here that just doesn't make
It's really easy if you just see a couple examples of it be like Alex is dumb and gullible
And maybe that is what it
It's such an extreme level of like
You just get burned by this dude over and over again
I'd like Sith
Fluoride levels of like you know he's trying to kill you all the time right
What are we doing here man
So you you're seeing right now the exposure
Of the Biden
Corrupt
Incompetent
Government
What you're seeing now is the exposure
Jima
Biden
And all his people
And what it really is
It's not on
It's an indictment of a
Obama and Brandon
Close to the heart of the matter
Obama is a
Homosexual
Nobody
The CIA operative and Brandon was his
Control off
Alright alright okay
So instead of
Accelerating Steve for being a psychopath
Liar
He is instead allowing Steve
To be a raging big
Yeah back whatsoever
Yes I agree
Although this next Club does get into territory where Alex has a problem
And that is Steve is like
I love Brian stelter
What does your narrative
Aren't real
Like Alex
The two of them were arguing about whether or not the
Action was stolen
How incompetent
We have
Michonne in order
Extol
How do you know they stole the election we are the numbers
Coming in
Double triple quadruple in Battleground state
Completely
I think that's over
And you think
I am a witch
That's why I come on your show
They tell me the country
Bombs off all of the country
Very well they haven't said anything
The splc and I play golf on the weekend what are you
Talking about
You're saying that the sblc did Oklahoma City and they're planning bombings what are you talkin about
Also Alex the only people threatening to do bombs in
All that stuff we're on your show
Associative
I think that's really funny because this is not threatening to Alex
Except
Because
Steven
Seen as a credible voice
It's because of
Alex's action
None of this would be a problem
I except for that Alex can't discount him as a crazy person
Too high so I will have to jump
I know the splc
What election
That's a solid swing I like that response
I like that response
So the election was stolen
What election now we've got a whole new Rico and do a little lunacy
So what does it mean
The devices by which
Steve exert
To control over Alex is flattery of course
And also patronizing
He treats him like a little baby
But a lot of the flattery is in service of a patronizing Eliza's haircut
Cycle mind
It's a it's a it's a weird it's it's interesting that we start with
Alex being like
My dad told me this when I was younger so I'm going to believe it until I die and then we get cbp's coming in here doing it like
Oh you're a good boy now stop it don't you do that but you're a good boy you're a good boy
Alex knows that
Because
Not in the middle of this interview they start arguing about whether or not Steve is patronizing him
Which is really sad
Just sad
And now here in
Florida we're not listening
Fauci who by the way was
Isn't that interesting
Trump
The New York Times
And the Atlanta
About wearing a mask now you don't wear one nasty with
To match so take it easy Alex
Listen to
What's going on
And what I want to know
Did you actually believe the stuff you're saying and talk show host and people like you
You want to show
Patronising dude I'm 47 years old around the block a hundred times
As you are being serious
What do you want me to say
Exactly
What's happening
Am I patronizing you
Am I seeing you wrong
I just
This show is f***** up
Like this is supposed to be a show where you talk about
The politic
Fixing the
Workings of the New World Order
Hours of grotesque
Discussions of imaginary
Child abuse fantasies that he has
Second-hour is a psychodrama with an old man who's been manipulating him for years
Popper right now
It's a little bit. I'm not sure what's going on
I think the second our Alex. He was going to come in and be like
Hey Steve
You f***** up
You know what you get some right you get some wrong answer that could build the next
SpeedFlex truck is still president how do you not
Durag how do you not see this coming because Steve is a wall
He's not somebody that's going to move and he doesn't give a f***
Exertion can you put upon Steve to make him move
Oh you can't come on my show anymore
Clearly I can
And Alex seems to have gotten
That realization
And he starts
Kind of trying to help
Steve make his arguments more I hate him so much still president
At the mara Lago and what-have-you share and
He's going to come back
Which coincidentally is another q narrative
I don't read that stuff from this website this website
This website and this website that I don't read suspiciously
Most of the stuff I say has to do with the things that are popular in Cuba
There's pretending to disagree with Steve
Alex is trying to help make that point
Trump's going to return
He's getting more popular not less that
Actually has credibility with Chantix Chang
Siri is
Watch yourself
Have you asked your mom today
Periods at a Appliance Factory
In the Midwest
I'm still up to Big Pharma
A while
Is a producer
Roddick
But the middleman
For the rebate that I'm doing punched out the middlemen and reduces costs and the
Money goes back to the beep
People purchasing
The drugs
Do I have a lot of enemies out there this maybe the list
Time you'll see me for awhile
Lot of very very rich enemies but they are not happy with what I'm doing
But I
Figured we have one she has to do it and no other
Going to do what I do
No other president
It would do
Nations
A rebate
Dubai from Other Nation
Much less
Call nobody
And they're a lot of unhappy people
And then he said at the military base before you got on the planet flip my laundry shed
I will
I will be back so so that adds something there
On Trump why are you doing this
Why are you doing this
This is outrageous
There's no reason to do this you're supposed to disagree with Steve not go out of your way to find clips of prompted
Seem to backup wood
I just
I'm just
Just jangle keys
Is that what we need to do do we have witches been jangling Keys wrong
Has that been a problem is that why the right has been allowed to
Flourished as we haven't found the right
Color of keys to dangle outside of their vision
So they can get distracted instantaneously
I don't know man this is f****** out of
No
You don't let people get away with it
Eclipse
Hear from Steve Zander there's more but these next two are just sort of like
I got lost in the incoherent
Pointlessness of this interview
Interesting to listen to for these social dynamic
Text between these two dudes
Private show he's ever done he's putting America
He's literally showing you the American show
Which is massive
Corruption
We didn't have it with Bush Senior
We didn't have it with Nixon
Jimmy Carter he was corrupt
Okay.
Trump means well he cares about the countryside.
How to get us he was
The president that pissed him off
I was there
With almost the whole Lighthouse was gone
The capital
And he literally pointed me and I led the people out I was like oh my God this is really happen
Then we got set up
So just the idea that trumps got all this
. going on
This sounds like a reboot
Politically what you're saying is happening this is destroying by the Democrats worse than ever
Levolor sun to level in Napoleon level
I mean they're destroying us there their they're coming after
Well he's isolated right now
The point is what
That is my question to
That's a good response because that was incoherent it was a whole bunch of different
Spaghetti strands
Yeah I think you might as well just said I'm not going to bail you out on that one
You're going to
You are saying what now
They're talking about being isolated
This goes on
Bickering
Trump is like
Mr. spacely in the Jetson
He needs to be out the public fight and he needs to be
He's totally caught off a bunch of cowardly lawyers down before ever shut up
How do you know he's
Totally cut off
I mean
What is this
Trial
No it's totally fake
Are you understanding Roberts
I think you should go into that Briar Patch and use that to expose them
But he's already
When did you ever hear besides
When I
Said that John Roberts
Supreme Court Justices we've ever had
He's been in
All kinds of
Problems
Adoption
Did you ever hear that
The chief
List of the Supreme Court
Is Sakura
And what day it happened
Chief
Was somebody killed by the way was he remember this
Supreme Court
What are you doing now
You're a f****** liar I can't tell if he's going back to Scalia or if he's
He's talking about like a current
What are they
Ruth Bader Ginsburg
Mega game
Court right now
That's kind of is indicative of how lot of this interview goes
Spike there's just
Two delusional weirdos
But with slightly different delusions that neither is really willing to give up
Alex's commitment is so much weaker than
Steve's
Answer you find him
I'm coming around
Gods of War
So he'll kill your God now
Yeah I don't I don't care
I don't care if you're arguing about imaginary not then you might care about
They made it back
Bats
Then that is that Steve was correct
He would get a job at info
Correct
If Steve was not correct you can never come back on again
So the bed is now meaning
Swell
Here's an interesting question
Nothing
Of who is right and who is wrong
Well
Steven sister Trump still president
That's fair
So what happens then
That's a good question thinks he's won this
That is
That is a fascinating conundrum we have found ourselves in
Suggested middle grounds that I don't think anyone is going to go for
You did come back on the show so I appreciate
But he eventually hire me.
Only because the show with David
On the other side
Hot show actually
Okay for me to go to break
Little people
That might seem a little people
Time Bandits
What wow
Listen I got to pay some bills
Yes I will I don't know I don't know if I could
Could stop myself from at least two and again to see what David Knight and cbpu show would would be like
I don't know these people personally but I find it
Very difficult to imagine the David wood
Ever agree to that I would love it
He died I don't know if Steve is allowed boorish nonsense Peddler and
David Knight is a
The quiet stated moron that's why I think David
Do it
I don't know he hasn't he's been out of work for a while we've been out of work for a while sometimes you like I'll take these boring as hell
And we're not into him
That doesn't mean that there isn't an audience
That came along with him he's doing his own show
True on something
Maybe
Shoot I don't f****** know
But I bet he's making something off that
I don't know
And I bet
That Alex gave him some money that is almost certainly some shut up money
I do like the idea of zalak suggesting that he can have a show co-host David
Because
That is a f*** you David Knight huge f*** you to David
That's the only thing it is.
It is a way of him saying
Everybody knew
I think it's actually
Steve Sanger East
You going to hire me haha I think that's one of the few moments of weakness
So you kind of see from Steve it is actually
He seemed interested in that
It's weird how so he really does think he's right
Well yeah or at least he thinks he can Gaslight
Imagine
Imagine how gullible the employees at Infowars are
If you can trick Alex
Something Wild
I would say you know Steve
Needs
Someone to help him
Turn on
The Skype
If I were him Mia maybe you would want to get a job at Infowars
The Producers there
That's true
Anyway
Steven the man of many talents
What's
Getting out getting Aldo Moro killed is one of them
Blind alley really a talent
He was really good at it
Scale that Alex brings up and that is
Poetry reading
Coffee shops and read poetry in his off time
He's
Reading poetry
And and
This is a call dependent chaos by Steve
Credit Union
I'm I'm getting
Sun
Lucifer come in what what is this so
Is this a love letter to Lucifer Steve pieczenik are you
For the devil
No I have the Hartford
Angel
It's simply NY go on your show
You're the only show I have a go on in
Number one
Incredible
Intelligence number
Incredibles
Sense of humor
Let me let me let me let me translate that for you my religion is f****** with you
The only thing that gets me out of bed in the morning
What I got to do
This is a new poem
A rat done bit my sister Nell
I think it's
Steve the weird dude
The idea that he's doing poetry readings is
Interesting
Makes perfect sense to me
Emerald sublevel yeah
It's nice that he has hobbies that are harmless
I don't understand
Why Alex
Westwood
Respond to a poem that ends with a Amen to Lucifer
As if it's just a
The joke when he takes his very very seriously
But anybody else brings up the devil doesn't bring up the devil
The devil I would argue
What's up
After this
I can't tell if this is a joke
Or not
All right but Steve
Literally refers to himself as a son of Lucifer
Now as Lucy
And the son of Lucius
Kohl's back
When 9/11 occur
Ostracized
Ace of the sexual
Pants
DCI whom I couldn't
Meijer at all I thought he was
Operation
Basically warned me not to do it
I almost guarantee that right after 9/11
Steve was not a high priority
Steve's going to run
Areas between the first and the second
They were like real quick we got to make sure Steve is out of there
Escapism Steven been waiting to do a coup for no reason
Now we got something
I I
I think he might have been joking but I was
I was blown away that Alex didn't you refer to yourself as a son of Lucifer
Should we be talking
Dan we are Alta
Play the sons of Lucifer Lucifer of course the lightbringer in Michael the the demiurge the two of them
Together without which
It's none of creation would happen
I find it weird
Okay well that's also
You kind of ends with Alex
Steve
Being buddies
They're just sort of s*** ago David Knight I hate them both
I'll bring it back
If you host
David
An issue
David neither you or me
All I'm saying is I wanted
Neosho
Say it to you okay where's my
Opposition
What I thought you said it was a budget plan
That's weird
To take this attack but it's not because I love him very much and I definitely haven't been attacking him this entire time.
Is it seems to be also sort of thinking of David Knight is a Fang
You know like I'll bring him back or come back
I will make him dance
Swith you while
Cannot
I would
So
So fury like this about wouldn't even insult me if I was David Knight that would have felt
Steve is back
Wouldn't help me more than
Anything I could have mentioned I probably be considering
Speaking to a lawyer to break my MBA
All right well now it's time to talk about everything I know
Yeah I know you can't do that fired me because this guideline
And then you called him on it
And then you brought him back and now your buddies again
F*** you I think the problem is
Steve's a good guy
I think you meant what you said I don't think you did it out of meanness or bad that's what my gut tells me
Toshiba.com
Come back on next week
We're challenging David in studio
Well that was a powerful interview is going on I don't know what it is but it's crazy the office
Is going on
I don't know I don't know what
Needs to happen other than like
Permanent dunks
Thank for these two idiots
There's no
Place that they can be allowed in polite
Society without being a cancer upon the rest of us
Other than in a permanent
Dunk tank
Where I can throw apples at at Target
I mean I understand what you're saying and I hear I hear you
I don't under I don't get it
Now
I can't imagine like I've listened to the show so much
Search for so long
And
Legitimately
There's just a reality
That is being denied by Steve
And I would have thought that I would
Good stand-up for basic tenants of reality anything
Anything
I can't I can't believe this interview went how it did now I've
It's outrageous know I'm Fury
Curious I didn't know what to
Expect when I heard like Steve's coming in he's got a face the music was like that
With rage
Onida
Guess Alex's behalf
Alex can't decide whether or not he wants to like
Say Steve is wrong
And push back against his s*** or like
Play clips
So Trump saying I'm going to be gone for a while to try and help Steve make his argument
Both sides of this fence
And you can't
Nope nope no sense
One of them is
Well actually both of them
F*** it
You want but you're a monster and an idiot I thought there would be a point where Alex would just have to be like Steve we've gone too far
I wish you the best
Have fun in Florida
I'm not talking to you anymore
I know we're buddies now
I I just I really makes me wonder like what happened after the Las Vegas shooting
That made Alex stop talking to him
A good like 6-8 months
Better legal advice
Maybe maybe get more to protect then or maybe maybe David night was more of an influence then
Could be
I just
The judgment
Just lie back a little bit
Snap this is
You're ready to be speechful
Because another gas
Call Nelda third hour
And he's a big boy
No
I don't
I can't hang
He has Magnus Pangea backhoe
It's offered to get this antifa person
For Alex to interview
The fruition of that
It's not really that interesting outside of saying that like
Alex is clearly down now
And Magnus is still full of s***
Yeah just having people talking to each other and
More and more groups kind of
Reaching out and
Got wind of this and a lot of
Progressive and liberal YouTube channels that have
Talking about hey maybe Unity hey maybe we should work together with
Trump supporters
They've started to get demonetized
That's really convenient
They're saying the same thing they've been
Saying all last year but the moment they
Try to be like hey maybe we should work
Porter's maybe we should
The more you guys want Revolution
You don't want a civil war right
From the very beginning
Wow
Okay what what what
What's the weather is the Boogaloo meme
Yeah like
Just like oh yeah you don't want you don't want to Civil War okay
Yeah
Do I wearing a Hawaiian shirt
No don't
The downtown by Igloo on it
To war
Come on dude these people need
F****** around
Out
Unreal
Need to be honest and that's one of the reasons why these interviews are so weird is because
There's deceptive
Business
But there
It's clearly
Like deceptiveness
For the target audience
Deceptive Misfits tailored to Alex's
Audio
This is more infomercial
This is not an interview this isn't
F*****'-a
New show this is an infomercial for why you should be
Be cool with the Boogaloo boys
Yeah that's what I'm afraid of is that they want a civil war
Easier said they don't
Now he doesn't want a civil war
Does want is a war against
The government
What about is the Federal
Never a me made or a postmate about
Going out in
Fighting Democrat
Information
Has ever been about that
Everything you always talk
Talk about is the copper
In particular Thief
Federal government
But always been the Apollo
So it's never been a civil war
And we've already most of us have stated that if there was some
Republican vs
The Democrat
Civil Warfare
Participate
Cabins in Into the Woods
Try to stay out of it
Go fuc yourself but also wow this is so disingenuous cuz he's pretending that he has this idea of this war
Against the federal government
As if the majority of the country wouldn't
Side with
The government over him
That's the part that is the real imaginary world bulshit that he's trying to pull off
Yeah we don't want to hurt anybody like what about everybody who thinks
The government
Shouldn't be overthrown by force
Oh well I mean
I've never end up having to hurt
So what'll happen is all of the people in the Earth
Obviously I assume that the people who are paid for by or paid by the federal government you know
There's what
345 million people
There's a lot of people that would probably
We join the Boogaloo Bois
The Federal
Wow
It's I mean
Usually there's a lot of dissatisfaction with the government there's a lot of people who want
Structural fundamental changes that is not the same
People who would say like I'll take up arms with you
Against the federal government
This is outrageous that is
The disingenuous framing of what their agenda and the goals are
So outrageous
Yep and one of the things that
Is it seems to
Maybe the real thrust of these PR campaign
That Magnus is doing
Is did you want to be a living example in this embodiment of how the media lies about all these group
And maybe you're getting a different version of those groups than actually exist
Picking up steam and a
Particularly like
People are starting to look into things and starting
The question whether you know they
False beliefs on all of these
Different movements or even if
Didn't have false beliefs
Their feelings on them were exaggerated
By the media to an extreme to get
Get them to the point where they dehumanized
And I have
Is Colorado
He's talking to a guy who says that all the Democrats work for Satan
Yeah I don't I don't know I don't know how to I don't know how to listen to this damn I don't know how to listen
People judge how dare the others are people are both full of
S*** to each other
And acting at all
With any kind of
Decorum
Navigate reality in the internet era it's very very difficult
Listening to these two assholes talk
Knowing
In the back of my mind
Let no matter what
These guys are saying
They are dreaming of Watching Me Bleed
That is what they both
Desire
Watching me personally
Bleed to death that's because your blood coming out is not really a pain to you
It's really more of a demon leaving your body
More that this guy talks
The more I just
Like that
People are hearing that the media lies they've been telling about that's all you're saying is one
Your b******* is work
You are doing this in service of Watching Me Bleed
F*** you
My name is gets to
Continuing
West Point and some people
Some people act like they're their opposition is
Actually literally
Evil
Like the person he's talking to right now
You have people that literally view like
Everyone in the opposing party as
Like some evil District
Parking for staff
Physically removed
Get to that Nacho
You don't hate
Your neighbor like that
As just a regular human
It's totally manufactured
Is totally push
The media to get
What do you think
Yeah Alex has to Pivot and change the subject as he's talking about
Exactly what I was
Anything like all this isn't real it's not
It's not organic it's manufactured by the media that you were talking to me
Before I've said that they are all in service
Is of the literal Christian
Are you saying that the other side dehumanizes their opponents because if they do I sue them for intellect
Will property
The end result is just
No I
The media
Has a vested interest in making
To the media and their enemies
Do you want these groups to look
Scarier than they are
Right
But to remind you before we listen to this clip
That Alex Spencer
Most of the first hour of the show talking
Grotesquely about how his imaginary enemies
Abuse
Kill and eat children
In ways that were so graphic
And exploitative that I refuse to play them on our show
I'm not defending White supremacists
Now some of them
But seems like what we're hearing about each group is not actually what's going on
Because they intentionally want everyone to look scarier and more dangerous and more evil than they actually are
They don't they don't want you know
If you go back
It's very much kind of like
To Kill a Mockingbird
Bird Indiana the whole thing with Boo Radley
They just wanted
Take someone who might be a little weird or might be wrong
And they want to make them look
Look like a demon they want to make
Devil's cancel route
The KKK
Black lives matter all at a barbecue
At the end of it both people befriended that was still people trying to start a fight
I would guess they would not necessarily
Befriend
Yeah
Yep yep I think we just proved Karma isn't real
Huh I don't think there's a God I don't think there's any punishment or retribution or Justice in the universe because
Two guys are allowed
How to speak on air
There's a part of me that really sincerely Wonder's as I listen to this
If Magnus
Wasn't
Saying these things
As a sort of
Pointed Thing 2 hours
Yeah there's a part of me that wondered
If
If he knew that this is what Alex
Does
And was saying it for that purpose
It's weird because
These two guys
Magnus and Steve
Are both manipulating the s*** out of Alex
I'm using techniques that Alex
Can't really respond to he doesn't have the wherewithal
No
And it's interesting to see like the old generation and then the new generation
Just abusing Alex's
Dumb dumb
Use him for all he's worth
What an idiot
Remember who's going by a pseudonym
Sure on along with with
Maggie
Anti-fascist
And I don't I don't care
I don't really care
I agree
What
No actually I just listen to Boogaloo boy lie to my face or even though I know they
In his heart he wants
To see me bleed to death
So I really don't care what the person
I'm sitting next to him says either
I don't I don't I'm not particularly interested I don't know who this person is they're using a fake name they're wearing a mask
Ask when they're talking
Oh well then it doesn't need anything at all
And the stuff that they're saying is like really not very controversial and it doesn't start a fight
It's just like yeah we're against
Corporate that corporate world corporations
Whatever
It's it's very mild
And Alex doesn't really
Like take issue with much
I don't know it was just pointing much like
Steve interview
Alex's finals
Suggestion
News online
Cuts to the heart of so much of Alex's politics
Being meaningless
He would love to
Sia Summit between the proud boys and antifa because he thinks
It would go Vive
How long
What month
Mark February what year is
You said it before I finished 21
Dammit
How long ago did violent fascist try to overthrow the United States
Couple weeks
Okay
Now
I'm going to go out on a limb here and say that the
People on the right who are saying we should have Summit
Are doing that more for their benefit
15 hours
Yeah probably I'm going to go with that
But even beyond that Alex can only see this through the lens of like what would be
Attention grabber
Steve
Did you do show with
With David Knight not because that would bring anything to the world. Because we would get any
Greater understanding or information out of that dynamic
Because you guys would fight and it would draw attention
Yeah be great
Everybody loved it I saw this Boogaloo boys I get interviewed on Jimmy Dore show
They got a lot of attention so I reached out to him cuz I wanted some of that attention
He personally I've always thought
That
The best form of governor
What happened
Annnd WWE writers room
So naturally I assumed
Dictatorship see what happens is
The government should be a giant spectacle
That never accomplishes anything
And resets to new narratives every now and again but I don't think I don't
I don't think I took a WWE writers on this I got to get
Stickman hitting everyone over the head with a stick and saying no
Oh so you is so that would be very similar to what it is that happened when the
Professional wrestler
Sling took over the
Somewhat
Weavile we come to the end end
I feel disappointed
And everybody I feel disappointed in life
People in the world but
Everybody that I'm looking at here
Random antifa person quote on quote
Magnus
Alex
Steve pieczenik
The only person I don't feel all that bad about it Steve Jennings wife
That's cuz I don't know anything about her and all I do is hear her laugh when I say something
I'm sure I'm sure if I knew anything about her I would
I would have some issues
She's just there for the
You know when you get when you get older it's
You just like being around
I live alone
Damn I just wanted more
But we
Pieology
I would like an apology
I feel like that's not unreasonable to ask I don't think it's unreasonable
But I don't think we're going to get it because
We've entered like an event
It's not even disappointment is disorientation
Cuz I think on some level this represents a new level of not reality we're living in
Beyond not reality creating a not reality on top of the not reality that didn't happen not real
Reality to Infowars and Alex Jones is narratives about the world
It's one thing to kind of
Like see like this is Alex trying to maintain that. Reality
Now you have Steve introducing the secondary layer of non reality on top of Alex's non reality
It's disorienting and you would think that Alex would want to fight
To maintain control of his non reality
But he doesn't
He doesn't seem able to
Weird
Yeah I know that's actually my new position my new and major position
I will absolutely Reach Out across the aisle
When I get an apology
I would like I will happy to have a happy happy to do that
I don't I think that most people
I would like a direct apology
From every individual
I don't think I'm going to get that I would like one
But you know the audience is going to get another episode
Your bail found in your area to help out those doing God's
Omniome Leo and bcx Clerk of the guy who's in charge of telling Alex on his collar
Alex
Birthstone colors