Jordan
I have great respect for its knowledge B
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Alex Jones
What's up
My bright spots that I don't know this may be a little bit of an unconventional brightspark cuz I don't know if it's bright but
It's been giving me a little bit of
Mirth
Okay I noticed that I have
Constantly
Have this thought
But it it's almost sounded defensive in my head
Or almost apologetic
Hi I love my cat
Excuses within my own for
Very open emotional look I love my cat
Sorry everybody I love that
I apologize for sharing my
I'm burdening you with my emotions of Love toward no one has expressed any negative feelings
It's because she does break a lot of stuff around here
She makes a lot of messages torn up my couch
Yeah
My dog is an absolute nightmare
Understand your feelings there there's a little bit of pets having that requires you to make some Apollo
Pieology
Outloud to a lot of people who are on my street
Usher
Today Dan I have
Rare double bright
White spots
Chapel bright spot first
Dad I don't know if you remember
It's been a while back we wish somebody a happy birthday from analects
I believe that was our last episode
Now what
Apparently happened as people have not been
I'm taking our advice which is you are somehow accidentally the person who gave a birthday wish
Let it ride
Believe it's that the name was wrong
CIAA difficult to pull this subterfuge off
Quick little
Audio adjustments to the
Let me think about how many names I've said over the course of this show could splice in
Absolutely we have to do this is almost an admission of laziness on their part
I just like they were becoming Delilah
Song request
Hey where you coasting tonight and where you Coast
Anyways have a birthday
Flash
Harden My Heart good love song
Happy birthday to Jared
Yeah from Alexis birthday and if you happen to be a Jared
Just if your if your partner's a Jared's absolutely screw up the name
And then of course I have to witness
Witness eyewitness
By observing disdain I make it real
Or watching my twitch stream
It turns out they are having their 18-year anniversary
Kind of
They both discovered our show and they waited until their anniversary to reveal it to each other cuz and now their 18th anniversary
Marriage can get a department absent
So they have real names but I refused to believe it okay
URS weakens 85in magnanimous moose
Mary anniversary
Happy anniversary anniversary
Jordan we are doing too many more of these requests
I'm so torn I really like it on the one hand I mean
At a certain point do we do everybody
I don't want to be the one who says you know what
You're the last one
Sorry that's where I'm at I don't want to be that long
Mine is the scariest I want to I want to break up with
Relationship we just text every other days I know our habits in our patterns we will
Just feel like
Birthday shoutouts for sale
Today we have an interesting episode to go over Ruby talking about a little bit of action
From
February 7th
You are so good that is really fat
Super Bowl Sunday turning and looking up there having a thought before you finish the blackjack
Very recently before we started recording
And I'm
I got to be honest with that
Not a lot of content
Not right lot of stuff going on
And I think that one of the things that is that like why we got these
Trying to figure it out
Alex is really confused now that he likes the Boogaloo boys and like when I can't really pin this on them
Don't really know exactly what to do s***
And I think he's biding his time a little bit cuz tomorrow as we're recording this on Sunday
Monday
Is the trial in the Senate
Excited for that
And
So we're going to do an episode on Wednesday and Friday this week
Yeah but this episode is still going
Tubi
About that Sunday show
But I have to tell you that
Jordan
I found a new genre
A new genre a new genre
Okay we're haps my new favorite thing
Alright refresh
Genres
So far
What classical
Countries are naturally
Genre is Alex's weird infowars.com commercial read
Okay alright cuz I generally listen to the show on the gcn feeds or whatever you know
I'll just hear the commercials for
Like Ted Anderson sponsors I haven't listened to the show like on Alex's own feeds for a long time
Back
And it's all I want to talk about those are f****** up
Let's do it so we're going to talk to you about some of the commercials are played during this too shall pass
Let's say thank you to a couple folks
Two signed up and record this year
Do first
Danny thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Monkey Turtles odd
Mature now
Real before Lieutenant Colonel called me about the
Some info Intel
Next
I'm a policy wonk, chimera
People hates the most commies and chimeras name
It is what it is okay
Thanks so much poop Feast 420 here now policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Next I can't stop adopting cats
Thank you so much you're not a technocrat
Heroin
Freakishly large
This episode happening before a lot of stuff
During the Superbowl would have happened
And so if anything was particularly Masonic
Devilish
Alex didn't have any comments on that during
Michelle said we were going to have to wait
To find out
About that
Will handle what Superbowl
Commercials
There are people are going to talk about
It's almost kind of fitting that we talked about Alex's commercials on the day of the Super Bowl the thing that is known for its commercial
I wouldn't say that's almost fitting
You're just saying it's accidental
People think this is weird
You says it a totally normal fast yes it's one of my favorite things
I'm not weird
People started this is weird
I'm touching my nose with tweezers
So here is just
The first taste of one of these commercials
That's just
Let me set the scene for you
Alex is sitting there
Bookshelf behind him with a bookshelf behind the other side there's like a
We can't see much of it until he's sitting there
And he's like looking at the camera if I have just been injured my ears have perked up at this visual because this
This is clearly a law commercial right there are visual similarities
Office commercials have
Their uniform books on the Shelf Alex's lacking bat
Thank you for the laughs
Huge Juma but was competition
My goodness
I could have been braced you
And just my shoulder
I got to pause already commercial
Exactly
I just feel it literally
Takashi
And I knew she was control I knew was putting up
Shoes with giving fake dates
Show me black people
Believing in some magic trick
Still president
We're going to have to save ourselves
How to restore
Admitting the truth there's a lot of positive things the world awaken to the New World Order
So now we know the truth and now
Every product
You hear me on here
Future orders
They were having trouble with
I think you might now a start to understand why I
Completely fascinated by this
Amazing
Understand how to
To keep content and Commercial separate
During commercial break
Because I was always like you know why he does this
Because he can't do it in his own commercials he's selling other stuff so in his in his show he's going to sell you stuff
I realize this is just
I just sell it when he's talking to his kids
He's like Robin but you need to go to school you need to get good grades
And the best way to do that is with my Suite of products
I think it's a mixture of that and I think it's just habitual I think like he's gotten so used to that being
How ads work for Ira
Who sings like okay this is a commercial spot I need to talk about the product
This is a commercial to try and get you to buy at
Alright I'm going to complain to rescue
Alex we're just going to be just want to cut one clean one look
You can do that whole thing we just want to cut one clean one as an alternative if it just
In case we need to stay here for a little while
The do that the first minute off that just go ahead and
Let me ask you a question
How does the you had an argument with
You relate to the selling of The Prado
Hey it's what he was on his mind was f***** up and they sat him down and he recorded rambling
Tim Tebow for the Superbowl commercial
Confront the bookshelf
They're like let's see what we could use
Christopher Guest movies Atlanta listen we're just going to roll tape and you yeah
That was weird
Nothing
Born at pivot commercial you do apologize to anybody in a commercial
You don't need to point out that you never lie and then equivocate on it
Commercials
Commercial
There's no
Plug in the ghetto product wait there's no plug in the commercials but I can't watch the show without hearing plug-in
Imagine a world
Without
Imagine being buried alive
Coffee Limited
France
Maybe 5% of
First of all what numbers show even higher second of all that is not where the term dead ringer come from
Of the person Six Feet Under
What I'm getting at here
Barry alive if we have any chance to metaphysically without filtering out
Ticketmaster Sherman
Providence to get out of this
Admit the globalists are trying to bury Us Alive lockdown
Remember
Product in there
He's selling God to you
He's giving you a good old sales pitch forgot that's why we got to turn to God
It's so bizarre
It is unpacking the weirdest unbelievably bizarre
That's weird
I mean it's not that bizarre that he has this weird fake etymology Academy
Balaji of dead ringer
My dad told me that that's where the turns from a repeated to you on it
Ship that goes on on Infowars
Just like I saw this in a meme one so someone decided
That was a
Clip
Two are
When he's take
They scored it
Music under her eye but that wasn't a joke
Somebody was like we got to put that on
Because it's important to have an interstitial
Like if you watch the video of it they have found b-roll of someone scratching at a coffin love it
Yes please
Absolutely.
This is so dumb
How long are they
Commercial spot I mean it depends
Do they run like for commercials in a row
It depends
But how long how long the commercials are the first break of the hour is from about 25 minutes
36-minute mark
And so that one's usually just like one
Sharaya man
The other commercial breaks be kind of very but there's like maybe
And it's all just him talk
Wow
But sometimes it's multiple of the commercials
Like one of them is done and then another will
Surreal
I'm just blown away by that
Just really wild it's indicative of a lack of anyone wanting to give you money to advertise that's for sure
You don't even want to give you money for advertising because you can't afford to pay someone for a good ass
A newt
Jody Watley advertise your own s*** if it's talked about dead ringers and such
Blakemore
Random
Not true facts
In my commercial
Wow
Alex is your guide
Sick of this Geico
Gecko nonsense I want the Geico Gecko
To tell me that geckos did not evolve in they were actually from a different planet and then be like by the way
We sell graded
That's what I want
The first hour about of this show is a lot of it is about Alex's disgusting like child abuse
You stuff and so we're not going
We're not going to let any of that
And we will instead get to some of the content
In the 2nd hour
Well first of all got to say
Ali Alexander breaks his silence
Did not realize he was silent
Yes
Get to bed in a little bit
And the fire 12th generation of who is responsible
For January 2nd
Yeah and then the rest of the time is kind of
Treading water
I want to say this can't censor truth
Dot-com
URL app
The fancy
Call EE. Because I was spending a lot of time this weekend doing research
Amanda
Shows watching interviews watching
Videos are pugs
Is there
My pillow guys to our report pretty good
Pretty good it is on there isn't it yeah
First order of business
I take great umbrage with someone saying I did research on banned. Video.
Research
You're killing time watching your employees
Merriam-Webster can do research into his own book but beyond that nobody
Alex did post
Mike Lindell MyPillow his documentary absolute proof
Which is hilarious
Because it's supposed to be absolute proof
Of the election being stolen and Alex says it's
Pretty good
It's pretty good review shouldn't be pretty good absolute proof
It won the palme
Plumbob
The thing
Is I got inundated with messages from people asking me to cover the documentary
A little bit earlier
Socially
I was I was trying to find a way to make an episode out of it cuz
There was public interest in that but it just it was going to happen
It's so poorly made
Did There's jump Cuts all over the place
There's no new information really that I saw
Yeah I'll be brought to the table it's just not interesting
I read that he made it in 6 days working 21-hour days
Pray that's what I that's what I read
And my first thought was like well that's a guy who's clearly
Pumping himself up being like look at how great I am
The way you described it though
I could see Yoko Cattle Man being up for so weak make
Do something that bad reserve for muriatic
He's
Cabeza
That's behind him now OK Google pillows
I don't know anything what makes his pillow so good
I don't know anything about the guy and I don't want to ever make fun of someone for having a
Addiction
It's just a bad documentary crash
I just
I resented watching
The only thing that I felt like at all
Okay about was like well
This is going to be played in court
2 hours
Yeah
Is 2 hours long
2 hours long
Yeah good movies are about an hour
Yeah
It was a it was a struggle.
To get through I was very bored
So I'm sorry but who really wanted that
Apparently you want to watch it I took video letter about that
But
LOL
So
Alex is pumping up
This
URL
But he's got
That you can't censor truth
Dot-com
A lot of comments
We can't share banned. Video
I do website
Probably stopped
20 of those comments
Different
Everybody doesn't care about your comments I read them
Nazi Nazi Nazi
This day band
The term Bandit video about a year ago on Twitter Facebook Google
You do all that
Just a URL
Assistant week
New York
Link
To the very database
And the very same videos
Like a disease
2020election center.com and
Some of the other
Maybe about 6 or 7
Trying to fight a disease
Dot-com
This is a loser strategy that Alex keeps gauging in any he's very open about his band of Asia
Strategy
To the point where anyone paying attention could stifle this
She is
Eventually people quit playing whack-a-mole is they never hit the bowl enough
You know
So he's he's got to be like this
You guys know you're not never going
So just
I think that is the implicit threat yeah okay yeah I've got can't censor truth
And also for other ones I haven't started promoting yet you're going to knock this one out already
It seems like a waste of everyone's time
So what's not a waste of time
Is ads
Let's get back to this
Commercials cuz they are way more fun
I shall stop them
Because they work
The real
Powerful
That's for reason
34 reasons
I know those are two reasons
I love your idea that you didn't even gather his thoughts before
This is
Pure stream-of-consciousness yeah
Even down to the like
I don't know if this is an action movie line or what like
I sell products for two reasons
Because I came here to chew bubblegum and kick ass now this is not available thing
Alex
Not writing things down
So here's another commercial that's not a commercial there's I don't believe there's a plug in the shed at all
The world is awake
The world
Understand the globalist
They are discovering the global
The elites
Manipulation CFR
Bilderberg Group
Damian bro
Club of Rome
The quicker picker-upper
They had to come out the open
Human freedom
Because they're actually losing
We have forced
Then
In the open
Humanity is winning in the plan
That isn't Dental
That is
Cereal
Awesome God
We'll Never Back Down
A deck this is a wrestling promo are you just telling fear are you just telling Yaya
I think this is a tacit
Admission on his part on some level that like
It's so much more profitable to make
The audience feel things into the direct them at product totally
Make them feel like this visceral fear but that's
It's matched
With
The globalist are secretly losing of course
OnCourse
That combination is just like
It must be
The most potent
Market
Getting two people terrified
Then save it by giving you money
They're going to feel better
So you give them money
And then he goes
Hey we're winning
But you got to say terrified cuz we haven't
One yet
Right then you give him more money and you feel like you're safe and so on and so forth
Until you forgotten your own name
You know what name you'll never forget though blackjack
Ali Alexander I will forget that name I promise you
Holly Alexander is on
To say that everyone is trying to get him
I guess yes
If he doesn't get away and then scream Ali Alexander free I'm going to be pissed
I think he does have actually some valid points about like people
Posting on Twitter video of him Nicola Tennyson Alex
At the Georgia Capitol was at the
Washington Capitals
Yeah that's that's fine people you want to complain about them getting that wrong
Go for it
Little bit
He's also know our people lying on the internet
I would I would say that some people probably are but I would bet that even more people are just
Yeah just don't know that they're wrong
Where is Ali is actually a liar
Grifter
But he has some thoughts about
Why
They're coming after
The GOP and such
Christians are all in
Republican Party
We control the entire Republican
Can party can't have that because
Does bringing people who don't believe in
Technocracy really people that gave
The world
Federalism Brother people that gave
Local isn't that work really people that stabilized
The Republic when the pagans in The Barbarians even if
Western Civilization
Mute the Christians first
So that week
Can't Inspire the Republican party to take
Meaningful action against
Is technocracy
How is the Wild and Save
Bebe
The notion that all Christians are Republican means that you have a very
Skewed version of who a Christian is absolutely
I don't care for this guy much
Didn't realize how much I enjoyed him being silent
It is interesting to me
The way you would put
Did the way he puts that
Of like
It's good thing that the Christians stabilized us when the pagans were around
Remember something about
What was it that the pagans got done to them
Oh that's right
A massive genocide
Wow he's just like
It's a great idea for Christians to genocide people
We're doing it now with this might be one of the reasons why it's
Tough to get swan
Eat stuff
And that leaves Alex I like he's got to do all these ads himself
Again all shot in front of his bookshelf
Totally they just let him roll some of them are really long
Listen we're going to we're going to cut all of our commercials for the next 6 months
We're going to do it in a 3-hour shoot today Alex
Go
Here is a long one
The number one question
Is Alex
Love your show
You really mean the things you say
Well I mean
Incidentally that is kind of what I do for a living
I will say that is not
Okay so you do not fight
But he's right that is
You don't
Need
Just sit there and put
Or your face is
The Dalai Lama
Or your face
The private Federal Reserve
Or your faith
You just have to have a memory
Remember
The things I've laid out
I have
There's nothing
Not because they were away
Not because they were supposed
But because
They had this feeling of
Invincibility
And this feeling everything's go
Because they were just going off
Dottie you I can
Address
London Guardian
Show you
Portraits
I can show you the
Catholic Church
Quiznos
There's so many article
Convictions
Just on that subject
The focus on
Jose Jose you for real
I'm as real as a heart attack
Girls getting hit by bus
I'm a realist Trainwreck
Time cover
System
Pacific
Games
Wild
While that I've ever heard by Tire life
There's no way that he could have ended
Did that with
Please buy Infowars store Prada
There's no way he did
Go to Infowars store don't need the 2-minute ramp-up it's a commercial people expect
Also
The only way you can make this more Cerritos if you're watching the video when he says I'm as serious as a heart attack I mysterious is getting hit by a
Airbus cutting video of a goat getting hit by a bus
Video of like in Connecticut security cameras
The windshield
I don't know I think you could easily drive a human being insane
You at 4 one day one person YouTube just chose
And they're like no big it's just get bad today
And it's only AJ's ads if they could drive a person insane instantly
This is not real and I also was kind of thinking like
I think
I'm coming around to the idea that maybe he's on drugs
Like 8 just might just be a drug
Could be
Weird Behavior
Yeah no
Holly Alexander
Are you okay are you on methamphetamines
Coffee
Really upset about
Set me up in prison all over the news
Long has President Trump who's on trial starting tomorrow if this is serious
Well I guess that settles it I mean he said he's not on coke
Style
Yep
I don't have any evidence
Instead he's ever pissed clean so many questions immediately come up to
Do whatever seems to say hi there are you on drugs
Are you lying are you
Hey Alex I'm the devil
But like I said
Alex can say all day long that he's not on drugs
But I don't know that he's pissed
Queen
That one time
Madison Security
Years ago he Gosa
This man you were totally down tired
Because you just came right back
I'm back on breaking Exploder you on drugs
What do a drug test called a portable drug test here
In a cup
No drugs I said you see that he said yeah see that
People think
This is weird
When you're under attack
I feel like this sounds like someone on drugs
Your energy switch is just really off-the-charts I was just wondering did you take any drugs in the bathroom
No I didn't say that why are you give me a portable drug test immediately
Savannah protecting is on what I will I will say I'm suspicious
So Alex and Ali get to talkin about the six
January 6th
The day of the
Storming of the capitol
There's two interesting take
Is here the first is the Alex seems to think that they were right on the cusp of getting that 10-day investigation that Rudy
Giuliani water
So Close All Things Considered
Pretty peaceful rally
Why the hell we have the motive
21 Trump
Had them about to do a 10-day investigation we were just showing our numbers why we screw ourselves
Where's the motive
Iran
We still made history
January 6th
What's teaspoon
9% of a million people
Totally peaceful
We feel that our election
Installing
The first
Human history
Okay wow that is a big cell that's a big cell
That is an interesting angle Ali Sid
I'll tell you this right now real estate
10 years
Nagasaki is going to be huge that's all I'm saying
I'm saying people aren't thinking about the good
Things that happened on the 6th
Interesting prism to see things through
And I do like Alex's attempted making it like
We were right there we were about to get those key rings that you wanted
Because that's
That's a good way to to really make it like
We couldn't have possibly wanted anything like this to happen if you were about to get our way
That's what we were
So there's a new narrative
It's going to be spun about the sexual
Has to do with
Somebody
An Insider in the trumpet
Campaign
That it set them up they did them dirty
Course
They got done dirty course they did so what ended up happening
Something like this Rogers
Not entirely clear
Somebody
Play a video with Allie wanted them to play at the ellipse
Ali sobh some instruction
Something I don't know
Laundromat
He was on safe flight 93
He's just concerned that they didn't
Play the saddest video so people could know not to break again
Play it's a good video
And we walked right into a trap truck watch Regular trips to go into what you know
Are you ready to release her name
Maybe she didn't mean it maybe should have BB know it was a command of everything
We know who remove the Jumbotron directives
We know who I mean I mean you're a million people with no Direction
So we got that the person has taken the Jumbotron directions down
Don Alex
Denali dirty
You're like a guess on who this is you know what you're up to email
Okay
Sarah Huckabee Sanders Huckabee Sanders is incorrect
Are you going to release which already thought already told my people
3 weeks ago
Yeah I mean I managed to say it to Trina Pearson is a campaign advisor
A quarter million dollars
On the Trump campaign
Advisors to do nothing
The president in November we caught her recalled her out
Me and several members. Bastille
And she was behind this to
Ditch out part of the
The Coalition at the Olympics
And that
Leadership
What the mass is when we walk into a trap set to us
And I think that's
The president
Archer totally distance himself
This is getting a little bit
Too much
Little little
It's a little thin
Guys
Okay
I am just going to have to stick with the simplest
Explanation which is that this
This is what you've been
Telling people to do
Then when they did it
You were mad
Because
It looks real stupid now
Now yes yes and it's pretty easy to look at your rhetoric in
Contentedly
Conspiracy theories that were being thrown around
Kind of got a stop the certification of the election
No matter how and
So wait, let me ask you a quick question telling me that
Getting your video up on the Jumbotron that would have saved everything would have Influence People what you're saying to me
Broadcasting somebody's words
Can cause real life
To happen correct
Suggest that you guys are aware that
Well yeah
I think
I think this is just dumb
Like you just
It's too far it's too far to walk like to make this make sense
So we now come to the end of our content
And we just have a few more commercial
Lovett bring us home
Just as the beginning cover commercial
I just
Can't
This isn't how you started commercial
Look
We got to come along way
What
Look
You need paper towels
You look is how you start a fight
You're at a bar if someone's not listening to you
Everybody was pretty good luck
Nope that's how Alex is started reflecting commercial
My pillow
Buy my pillow
Commercial
Look
AB
Populism nationalism approaching the future
Watch repair is a surfer
Whether he is a traitor
Deal
Strongman
Does it really matter
Ocean
Liberty this
System of Freedom these
Was a great man
Dollars
He paid a mighty price
It's easy to play Monday Morning Quarterback
Taxi driver
Okay
So
He Rambles a bit more and then he makes this metaphor that I think is a little strange
Give me some good news
Big
Royal Flush hit
You'll get that and every
But as for national
Freedom
Trump have in the election
Call the martial law in all the tearing is a sign
Yeah they stole the election
Yesterday
Because they're weak
I'll get the message needs to be like really stressed hard that like
Tyranny is upon us but that is a good sign for the meat or women
You are dying
No it's going well that's that seems to be just like the through-line
But also a royal flush
Aunt BB
Yeah that was a little bit frustrating today that's bad metaphor
And why did he lose
I mean you could probably America
Katai
With the dealer if you get blackjack
But
I mean
Yeah
You still can't lose
Brutally
This was the last commercial that we got in this one is exit I thought this was pretty funny
This might be my favorite although I will say it's pretty tough to top
Are you going to look because Luke has a subjects which is
These assholes always look assholes very similar
Exactly
I'll bet this one is great because it makes no sense
Is very stupid
And it reveals something
We're already on the 2nd
Um contact tracers
Your house
People have their doors
Shakedown
This is all
Trying to
Globalist
But into an age when I call Chad
Realcomp
Decision
Being awakened
An awesome new age of
The understanding
Every product
You hear me on-air advert
We haven't stopped
Every product
A couple days
What's yours
That second part is the
Smyrna Park
Same Parts just adding Rose Wilder just added it on
Everything in stock at the end of a minute of Ben rambling commentary in the new age but
Pho challenge
But also
I like I like a huge selling point being
Our products
Exist
I can show you where they are
They're here the store in the store room
Yeah I'm pretty amazed
That like I really do think he probably just sat down.
Has to
Together it's 100%
I am
I love I love that he's like
I like
Talking about how we're getting into the new age
Bethany realizes that new age of the same little too much
NuWave
The difference
I do appreciate how either
His audience
Has made it very abundantly
We cleared to have with all of their Quest
They do not understand basic
Sickly anything
He
Hats to reiterate
Things cons
Silly Tay himself like
People say that they're worried about cuz I said and then
We all get how
The supply chain
Alex I don't know why
Explain
How that works
In-N-Out
It's because I think that he would
He thinks that he's talking about the supply chain supposed to make people
Feel I need
To act now right but I think that he believed that his audience interpreted as there isn't any stuff
Also because he does do a lot of yelling
Cooper is it like
Yeah so I would understand why the audience might get that impression need to clarify
It seems like
You may pour choices if you've gotten to that
That's what I would
Explain why he starts
Commercials with
But I tell you you can't
Was it not the most serious episode we've ever done
We have paper towels in stores
Piranha man
It's always Super Bowl commercial special
Wednesday to discuss Alex's immediate response
To the impeachment trial and see what he's up to
Damn right to the occasion come up with something
We'll see
But until then Jordan we have website
Barro's on Facebook if you could please find a local charity
Doing God's work
But until then Emilio Emilio mdzs
It's Clark I'm Daryl rundus
One-time Jordan and I were doing a podcast and he's like I said give me a cup
I pissed in it
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color