Airjordan.com
I have great respect for its knowledge B. I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
3rd and Jordan
Jordan
What's up
My brakes Jordan is something interesting I learned something
Bindi I was unaware of this
I was valid to lots of gas from that guy
Honestly I had every reason to know before and I don't know why I did
Quite frankly but as it turns out
I only know when things come to our PO box
Because I get an alert
From the store
Sure where the box is
Dido
Don't send you alert
When letters
Discount
Oh
I didn't know that and unless
The person who's giving you the packages check
The mailbox
You'll never know
That's not fair
I found a bunch of letter the last time I went to pick up
Packages
And also weird
Way behind on Zeppelin of the mailbag around
22 opening some of that up
In the near future by
On the last trip I went down there got these letters
And I got a particularly amazing letter from someone who I just want to call dr. Justin that's what I was
Going to say.
I don't I feel like this letter is delayed because I have no idea when things
The mailbox
But it was just getting more us
Then did not know wedding mail
I appreciate it so much it meant a lot
How has been just tears
Just tears
Non-Stop
Thanks for sharing that letter with us
Things on your
Dr. Ness Hellyeah
My bright spot then is I have finally finished
2 months long project
And I've done with Taylor Swift
Okay
Listen to the whole catalog listen to every one of her albums
Nmd
I'm done
Is Amazon pretty proud of myself how do you feel
Find
That was perfect
I am even tentatively not read anything you've written about Taylor Swift cuz I don't want to get mad at you
Just got this before I don't want to
I don't want to pick a fight I don't want to
Look I love blank space I don't know what I don't want to talk about it
I understand
Irene Irene
Tried to pick a fight I was trying to go so far over the top no one could possibly imagine
Would be fighting
At a certain point I insisted that
The guy who wrote Bloodsport was the writer of one of her songs do you understand
The audience wants to know what your next extended exercising misogyny will be
Maybe bunches articles about Mariah Carey not being as good as April
Well that would just be impossible because Mariah Carey is exactly as good as everyone thinks
Maybe extra series could be about pink
Now you're just now you're just
Fighting people you're defensive
About Mariah Carey election
I don't know lifetime
See I met some big haters in life
Well congratulations on finishing a project
Yes let's not talk about it again
Jordan Tillman we are going to talk about is Alex Jones
What's today
Episode
Moving I was like
I knew.
Easypro like me everything happens in slow motion
No matter how many times I've
Sit there and think in my head I know he's about to say the date
Yeah I'm still caught by surprise every time it's also not quite Fair because I can just keep talking
Has one word almost even
You're you're playing at a disadvantage but I'm also very good at it
The double whammy this is Monday or talk about the day after the Superbowl right there
Some thoughts on that imagine so now they are there
Some thoughts on that there's a big Broad
Push that Alex is at engaging in
That I think will be the direction
Of content
In the in the near future
Amanpour get down to business on that episode and folks who signed up and recording the show
So first call me was oh thank you so much
Thank you very much, was overseeing the room
That's well he wrote the marks
I believe
Have you ever seen the room
That's why I want to see it
It'll actually make you sad you won't like it
You will not appreciate it you'll be like this guy was trying so hard
I need some bad movie
The I don't I don't know if I will I don't like I don't like everything that I've seen surrounding it so I'm not
Interested in what
What germinated all of these plants that's fair
That's fair
Dictate a letter thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Very much Bagels
I'm hollaback girl thank you so much and I'll probably want
What country are going to write a serious by Gwen Stefani
Alright tomorrow's warm flat Seltzer thank you so much and I apologize
Next next
Just ask what the hell do you have against accountants we're not all Oogie Boogie sympathizers thank you so much you are now.
I'm a policy wonk
Account
I'm just saying that you can't be
Bolton account
And I feel like
That's right
The end might be very cool for an account
I think you took a people donated on elevated level appreciate that
Grim squeaker thank you so much right now technocrat
Heroin
So good
Freakishly large
Oh yes thank you so much
Joe who Skip the intro and a grim squeaker
Did you watch the Super Bowl I did not
Grateful for it
I meant because of this episode I watch the halftime show
I did not know I did hear that weekend did stuff off of House of balloons in the f******
Spoons with his first Italy po
Where is Seattle
About doing cocaine and f****** stairs that song like I can't feel my face when I'm with you
I thought I don't know that
Just think I've heard that somewhere
Read it that for sure
And then I Starboy except like
No they were all about that
Put the chorus is I'm a motherfuking Starboy he is a motherfuking Starboy
It sucks
Halftime show and we'll get to that at the end of this episode
A little bit
But the only thing I was thinking was like
I can't believe
Did the weekend is this big of a star
I've nothing against Texans like a talented guy but I'm so disconnected from pop culture
Wow
There's no surprise guest
There's not like I remember the days of halftime shows what it's like 15 is not allowed
Five different bands Aerosmith going to be there
Hitman Nelly's going to parachute in this s***
Comes out of the floor at the Super Bowl
Math yeah it was just a weekend it was a fine performance
I didn't like all the songs
Maybe it's somewhere a little bit boring
But I'm not about to talk to Remo
Although
Give me time
That's about all I thought I saw a little like a couple of
Like Choice plays
Look at Mahomes passwords falling
I don't really have any strong feelings about it
The game
I guess I'm from Missouri so I should love to
Cheese
All right some friends who really like it
The Chiefs are good for them
Anyway
We start
With Alex
Contact drop
There's a rare situation where I'm going to give you a little question ahead of time
About this out of context drop
He's telling somebody to burn in hell
And I'd like to try and guess who he wants
Supernanny
That is
Out of the lot
They hit the gas
I thought you were going to be okay
Etsy
And this is after
Do the Superbowl I am going to go with
Why not
Bill Gates
Springsteen Bruce Springsteen's going to burn in hell
Bruce Springsteen doesn't like the far-right
Ephesians learned that to born in the u.s.a.
Commercial
No one explained the song
YouTube
He resented the commercial
Where I guess it was a General Motors
Commercial where Bruce Springsteen was doing the voiceover talking about how
There's a purity
The middle of can
Right in the middle of America
We all is hard to get
The middle that boy oh boy
It's about that pissed off Alex ugly where Bruce Springsteen going to burn in hell everybody should burn their Jeeps
I'm fine with that
Whatever
Is that more or less carbon in the
Atmosphere
To burn your Jeep but Alex thinks we need all the carbon that's true
Start off the show and Alex is in the exact mode that I like to I like him to be a
This is what I know like okay this is going to be weird
Okay I tend to get up here on the Arrogant really side
I'll get to all the points I really want to break down
Try my best
Yesterday
To just
Be calm and then we'll see how long that lasts and just cover all of this but it is becoming
Extremely
Extremely clear
Exactly
What is going on and what is
Unfolded
This is all just too happy this is all too insane this is all too serious
Okay okay
Come in and out of the gate
Brought a lot of energy
We're going to calm down I'm just going to get
Through this I quit
I am not going to be here for any longer I'm done
I got to get out of here
He doesn't actually go to rebroadcast buddy does play
Some special report
But not before teasing a little bit of what's coming up on the show something interesting because of his
Jay Dyer is going to be in studio whether she's a great author
And researcher noticed
Easton
More deep research
On the globalist endgame but even I have
Because
Did you make a movie about two years ago 20 years ago 10 years ago
Another operation butt
Hehehe
Going back as well
Hundreds of years but then
Reader's Digest
Was there show the things he does to go
Please book she's reading my everyday new 14 there
Terrace Apartments
Brain damage
Sterilizer
Piranhas
It's hard for me to read there
But he doesn't
Probably just said it's hard for him to read
Apparently Alex doesn't read primary sources anymore but pretends to pretty expensive
Except
Jay Dyer
Say yesterday I do all my own research
And then say today I can't really do any research so I just read this guy
Yeah that's not
Fair and then I accept whatever interpretations he
Carly has a bad
How about primary sources that he probably didn't read either are you kidding me this man
Claims to read a book a day or how could I not take everything he says at face value dance certainly
Excited
I can't wait to assess you
I've heard him been on the show before he's boring
Stupid
Well alright I'll get excited for that
Alex is in a bad mood
He clearly wants to storm off the show
He's got this guy coming up that I think I can
Sick my teeth into
Instead Alex just like
Easy plays the special report about Marjorie Taylor Greene
Okay
It's this weird
Weird thing where John bowne
One of those employees trying to make an argument
That Marjorie Taylor Greene having these committee committee appointments taken away
It's somehow it purged of all conservatives
It seems like a dumb argument to make it seems like a ballia
What year what you're doing is essentially equating whatever you believe in and your rhetoric with her and if you believe
Leave if you want to
If you want to make that Association you're more than welcome to yeah I think it's illusion or it might not work well
Extends to like what we need to do
Is we need to get
Committees
Try
Find that's called being reactive you wanted
You can do that you can post your phone on thing whatever.
The dumb video
Anyway I got bored of that
But was not bored with
Is there somewhere
Okay
Last episode
Commercials
And there was a big hit
And I thought we need a little more of a taste
Of these
Because I have not heard of any really
Stand-out commercial
I think we won
I think we had the best commercials of Super Bowl Sunday
Yeah yeah I think
Can't think of whatever like an advertising publication but I think it would give the crown to Alec
Oakley commercial
Small town
There's a small town that's how you do the light
This commercial might take the
Okay
I think it's my favorite
I have to warn you
4 minutes
Nautica
This is a special report
It goes
All over the place
Hey ladies so mopey
A bummer
So was 4 years ago
Lawyers
Like 10 years ago and I dressed up like The Joker do anti
Prozac at
Prozac
Classic
Frogs
Antidepressants
Admit
Lawyer
She's playing with Joker
Crews are just like Jack Nicholson
Joker
That's not really all show
This was actually a defense of introducing any video of Alex on Infowars
But you did say that it would be like
Compare
Playing The Joker correct but it wasn't just about a specific video
But Alex is referencing where he does have Joker makeup on
Trying to complete those two things
But yeah I was like
Hello this is
Just like the first minute
Avisca scrambler
The commercial aspect to this will get to it many commercials
Begin with of course I was in a custody battle four years ago years ago
Or is it something weird
Surprise me at all my kids taken away for me and my lawyer need to make a
Really really desperate argument
To keep my public
Persona out of court
So not to answer for why ice cream but how my enemies are demons and literal travels an hour
Because I'm a performance artist
What you my audience to think that right
Sales pitch won't work
Have you tried, that's the preamble to a great
Commercial
Yeah
Jones admits
Character
The most unscripted personality
Research
Instead of
Fireflies
Why do prabhakaran
And then I
Sometimes
It's all
Huge stuff like
World
New World Order
Eugenics Agenda 21 agenda 2030
But you and biological
Open Pandora's Box
We are not 2 minutes
This is not a commercial this is a voicemail on his like Xbox
What does somebody drunk at like 3 a.m.
At four years ago alright I was in a custody battle first minute is about the custody battle stuff and how I'm real
Sometimes
I got real excited and I just yell s*** whatever it's tied to deliver information I kind of forget what I'm doing
Probably cuz I'm a drug
If you would like to re-record your message to begin again at the dial
Show me the time I have here just be really straight with all this
One stop
Continue
Because my body
Exhausted by my spirits.
Expedia
Godspeed
Exaggerating
Psychotic anti-human
Paradox
Continue
I've had to rely
Basically purely on people.
Hollister today
My time
I'd rather be on air
What's happening
True that
Add
Really helped a lot of people there.
Quality
And on top of it our mission
Is absolutely clear
Reach Out
Do people
Amazing products
Where we are and what you've done for this operation
In advertising
They could break down
How this is
Active calls action
Here's what I'm here's what I'm seeing in my mind's eye
End of season 1 of Mad Men
Don Draper is looking at that Carousel and he's thinking
I'm going to say everything Alex Jones is saying in this wood right here look I'm not telling you what to do
You cannot by Kodak don't want to see these pictures
But some people don't I mean that's fine I'm a proud man
Ascertain
Saudi qualification silvery concert like
Listen you don't have to
To do this
I heard that
And I thought
Who is in charge of
Quality control
Could of God
Here's what you could have done are you so desperate for something to be
Before minutes long
Exactly fit like
In a break only the only explanation
Because the only explanation I was a lot of fat in there there was not a lot of substance
And you do what you can do
You can edit the video
None of it
At the end
Relates
20 set at the beginning and he's called to action please go by from Infowars store
Do you need the added contacts of 4 years ago he was in a custard
Nor nor do need the second minute
Cool I think he's having
Problems with employment
I think maybe he does not have the most
Capable hands on deck
I think maybe he has very few in
.
So we get in this mess
Alex getting actually down to business and
I think I think that you see hear him complaining about like Maxine Waters and Hillary Clinton
We also see what I think is going to be the Direction moving
Forward and how Alex is going to try and
With the end of
The really like the Trump season should I guess
The only way I can
Express it really is I feel like we're back
In 2009
The Union
Psychology of the Shadow onto you.
Maxine Waters likes her evil ugly ass no
Weather
Watch this evil ugly ass no
Hillary likes her evil Twisted but no
Exit on you
Because these people are not retrospective
And they cannot look within themselves
Wow
Alex
Knowing thyself
Used
Highest order
Alex
Loud exhaust
But if you don't know yourself you don't know anything
Know thyself first
People do not know who they are they don't even know where they came from or where they're going
They just want to pull
Down everything good
Just as night follows day in day follows night
Massive false Flags in this country
Play knots and they're going to try to move against us they're going to do it
Because they never got
Trouble for all the things they did before
The corrupt lawyer run just
Apartments
You so full of pedophiles and corrupt people
They literally existentially want to make a run
American gun owner on the American Christian and they're going
To do it
There's an overwhelming Sense on this episode of feeling like
Exactly like the narratives of 2009 they're coming for your gun
It's just
It was exhausting
Cuz it's just like I feel like I've
We've been here before
If you are somebody who is listening to his show like I don't understand how you wouldn't
Be like hey you
You played this song before
I mean you know can you end up going hard on hating immigrants
It's now too so everybody's everybody's trying to step back and be like
Remember when we could just be racist for fun come on guys this is going well
Yeah
I think that there's a difference with Alex though and that is that he's playing this game
30 play
Before with
The same intensity before
And it didn't come true
True
So
Or
What if he
He just said it did
Have I guess I didn't option
So it's
It's going to be psychic Warfare they're going to show US flag
Cordless corrupt lawyer run just
Department is so full of pedophiles and corrupt people
They literally
Existentially want to make a run
American Christian and they're going
To do it
They're going to do it first or psychological operations
And it's going to be bad
It's going to be rough
And you better get yourself ready for it
Are you better now
What the different scenarios are they're going to unfold out of this
Call coverall we come back
We're not going to be on here unless we have your
Plus we've got great products
Everybody already
Needs minutes of a rambling nonsense commercial but I mean that commercial was great
Did you hear that that was
What 10-second
It goes on from there
Wintersun being awesome
False flags are absolutely coming or they're all going to take a run at the gun owners and Christians they hate all that is good
Yep
It's just a classic at Vivid business it's just not fair
They're just shouldn't be allowed to just be like okay
These past four years we had a grand old time
Ran roughshod all over your b******* killed a lot of people in
Destroyed essentially anybody's faith in
Democracy anyways
We're going to go back
To just being mad about regular stuff now is that find it we're going to
Seem to like us
Right
Crawl in a little hole the angry tea party typos again
Does everybody like
The stakes being lower I guess
Pretend to be escalated
I thought Biden was the devil
Devil I thought the whole idea of him getting into office was an existential threat to literally everybody because he
Cold by China which is controlled by the devil and God also the devil's controlling whole bunch of other things
But like
Alex
Reveals how he and his staff talked about
Biting ants like
You wouldn't talk this way if you actually thought he was the devil
And so I remember
On that same conversation on January 8th with
The managers
You know what's trumps out everybody didn't think everything's fine
More letters to people are going to hate by
And I said you mark my words
As soon as I can ovulation Tovar
Biden sworn in up there
People are actually going to give up
They're going to ask
Ashley Fall Away
That's okay
We've got a bigger number than we had 20 years ago
Or even ten years ago even five years ago but
All the sunshine Patriots aren't Winter Soldiers they're not going to be involved
They wanted to be part
Of the
What does it matter
So Alex and his managers have a conversation the conversation goes along the lines of they think it's going to be
Business divides in office and Alex's
People are going to lose interest
Yeah that's the way they're talking about this
Behind the scenes that's how they're processing test
Whether or not this is good for business
It has nothing to do with their
Pretend nonsense about buying beans
The f****** devil Neville that is performance
Anybody who thinks otherwise
This is
I mean
Duluth
Now at the same time there is a real-world implication of a lot of this stuff
And that's where this discussion of how there's false flag
Coming up
Where is that
Becomes really important
And I have some thoughts about that
Guaranteed
Hundred percent confirmed
They've done it before
They stand to gain from it they have a history of doing it
They have the motive
And they are now pre-programming at 11 I haven't ever seen
Even before 9/11 IMA for Oklahoma City
Even before other events that right-wingers
Going to engage in Terror attacks mass shootings bombings
Everywhere
America
Pro-gun
Or anyone that pro-life is a terror
And they're going to try to get the
The general public then in Mash
The same ones that wear the mask
They want to do what they're told
2 then literally anomalous Revolution
Not work with us not talk to us and actually physically attacked us
I've already beta-tested the whole thing
When Alex talks like this
Generally what you should take away from that
Is he recognizes that he and his entire information economy
Formation space have made things too hot
Yep they've got things too hot and stuff going to Bubble over Amanita preemptive
Justification and narrative for it
That is all you need to hear when Alex says
I guarantee
Tefal swags are coming
That means
Hey
Trump has an impeachment trial starting on Tuesday
It's probably going to be some
Fuckedupshit
People have
Has been radicalized to the point of no return
Thinking
He had the election stolen from him
The narratives that I've Been instrumental in pushing
We need to make sure
That all this is fake
It does happen
Very sad
It's it's not just added
I mean
Perhaps not legally criminal but at the very least morally debate
I would say so and it's awfully transparent to you when you watch enough
Of of him and you see these behavioral patterns such as becomes really obvious that
I'm not saying that like Stewart Roads called him and said I know someone's going to do that
And and and
And very irresponsible
But I think that Alex knows well enough to read
Do you know the sign
They're out there
Chatter Alex's Alex's plugged into enough chatter where you're like
A lot of this is too hot
I can see you somebody out there doing read the comment
To be some indication of some people are
If he even does that right but even if you don't like you don't even need
To go that far to say chat or you could just say like look at the scenario look at the world
Happening happened a few weeks ago
Are there was a bombing on Christmas morning
Yeah yeah
Oh yeah
Anyway
I think
That is what's going on in that is the big push
Then I was talking about being like what Alex
This content in his
Stuff is going to be moving forward it's going to be a lot of that
Like return to 2009
And then really really
Stress that
If there's if there's false Flags coming
And
That's just to do preemptive damage
Image control
Four people in those pro-trump communities
Anyone
Take violent action
Absolutely
So all the other moves
In the past the bubbles have made
All just leading up to this move
This move right now
The false flag that will lead to the Civil War that will lead to
I have quick before we go any further
What happened to plan B
He didn't say that
The Harrison Smith doesn't work
They're making their big move
All the other moves were probes
All the other moves were test
All the other moves were just
Beta this is the main assault
They're going to blow up federal buildings are going to shoot up colleges Church
Why didn't you tell us all the other one in lakes in in Reservoir
Attack on terratech
As the globalist try combat combine text America down and causes of Civil War
So all the other everything was Prelude the other ones all the
Screamed at you
For 25 years being very most important ones that have ever happened it turns out
All of them we're just
Probes
Alright. Mine's my tasks
Is it possible that you're wrong this time too
No no he's only been wrong every time for 25 year
Is it possible that you have a currency bias that you think whatever is happening now is literally the most of
Ford thing
The Domino's Jordan
Essentially
False flag tips over
Right
Sure
That goes off
Hi Penelope used to make Patriots and right-wingers look bad
We need help with that
Teams were done that after the storm go to Capital play
That goes down
Babe there's a civil war
But the Civil War is only two like collapse
The United States Shore and then
Death camps
This is all men
To trigger the Civil War that's the goal
So the false flag triggers
Pictures of Civil War and the breakup of the country in the end of the dollar
What's a plan to have done in a year
Has the symbol of America
Who will carry it out evil
What's America collapses
What about 1 year out from the end of the country completely unfair
Where are you
Year away from death camp you just get to step down after you've destroyed the country there's no like
Fanfare he's just like that I'm out of here guys mean I'm sure it wouldn't
You know the smoothest exit
I got a cab but I'm going to get out of here to go I got to go
This is a s******* by the way
Yeah I think this is nonsensical and it's also
Deeply irresponsible
To tell you're already terrified of paranoid
Gullible as audience that you're a year away from death camps
Because of f******
Jill Biden
Why in God's name
Would somebody bother with a false flag
Whenever you just said
That you're a year away from
Death camps
So you should be out now being like we got to terrorize these people otherwise we're going to be in a desk
I mean
It's it's
You know terrorists edging mixed with terrorists free
Rationalization and denial
But there is other folks
What is a scholar on the matter
I disagree
Killer got into power
19:33
He wasn't
Finding people
The death camps
Oh wow
Businesses
How did
So Alex doesn't know anything about Hitler's rise to power is he fully demonstrated a couple episodes
Call tisserie is
Is really upsetting
According to the United States Holocaust Memorial Museum cooked the first concentration camps in Germany were established
Soon after Hitler's appointment as Chancellor in January 1933
After the night of Long Knives The Purge of the essay that took place
Between June 30th and July 2nd 1934 Hitler assigned a Heinrich Himmler to formalize
The system of Campus
That was going on
The camps that they were primarily for the purpose fully
Of extermination, later
But even if you want to give Alex the most
Generous interpretation possible
Operation T4 started in January 1940
Who does anybody systematic killing of people with disabilities in Germany
I was just playing with the Nazis weren't sending people to death camps until 1942
Probably just him knowing
But that's the year the Operation Reinhard began
The Nazis attempt
Did you kill all the Jews in Polish
There's a larger picture that he's unaware of or weirdly ignoring
And this should be another signifier that Alex has absolutely no idea about the reality of world history
Nor does he have any respect for majorly traumatizing and a traumatic world events
You should never be taken seriously as claiming to know
Anything
Yeah
No and it's not
Just that he's
And it's not even like he wants to remain ignorant or he doesn't want to learn things they they
It said he actively wants to go out of his way
To learn and propagate things that
It did not happen in order to justify his b*******
Now anything he says about history
It said entirely to be like
Totally okay for me to do whatever I want
Today
Has nothing to do with any
It's and it's false
Depictions of
Of like a very very serious thing
Expand its I mean that's just
That's just wild. f*** him
F*** him so you know how Hillary Clinton project
Sahara Shadow her Union Shadow on people she doesn't like her but
Important thing that I've heard madler and Maxine Waters all don't like their butts
So they project this Union Shadow on you
So they think that you're bad cuz that's their Union Shadow that they see on you but that's really them
For Alex to say somebody else's
Projecting its
It's very rude Alex
He protects his shadow on people too and that's why he thing
Pigs that everybody else is good at f******
I think people are powerful in
Amazing and have incredible ideas and
Have any credible
Sexual prowess
Amazing
Dynamic
Build civilizations
I love freedom and Josh
I've learned not to project
What I believe
William
On dollars
I can only hope
I love myself
We know
I have written a poem of myself to myself
I've learned
I have learned not to project myself onto others I can only hope that everyone is as good at sex as me
There is nothing wrong with masturbating you are very good at
It sucks you masturbated what a doofus
What is boron
Unreal navigate to one of my favorite types of moments
But I think it's this
What's a good stripper
His projection is understanding of Union Shadows
Comes down to
Maxine Waters doesn't like her but
I have a huge I think metaphorical but
No I know I understand but metaphorically speaking literally talking about his sexual prowess
The but she doesn't like her stinking but that she hates
The metaphor with wine at the literal events
Maybe it is
Next clip is is my favorite kind of s***
This is where Alex like kind of forgets what he's talking about
An incredibly depressing story
Any story that makes him look
Pretty bad just not kill another.
NOCO dog Kelly
Coming to somebody and saying hey
Need to go home
We just
Got a call
Answer your phone
Your dad
Just got
Car rack
I don't like
Call
Remember hey
Grandma's dead
This was already really
If using as a jumping-off point but hold
Hold on hold on to your horse when he doesn't like bad news
It's been like to give it doesn't like to get it done like to do as unfortunate
But
It's our job to do the
And if we're not honest
Yahtzee my grandmother probably 6 months by Dad's Mom
Josh I guess she's been gone
What's up with two years old he's 18 now
I guess she's been gone
Do you want your math always 17 + years
So close
I called my dad
Porsche.
We got to go see Mima
Because you don't funny you said that I thought we could go see her
And then I was on coke
Stadium
Elector in the morning
My dad got there like 7
Ready set let's go
Atlanta in the bed
In my house
Younger I could get out of bed
Start now
No problem
Renaissance Ticketmaster
Doctor Donna Donna
Finally got up
And I had a beer for breakfast
I have one more for dessert
Cuz I was really tired
What is happening
Then I got in the car on brownie stacks
30 minutes for I get there
Because then I just got there when she died
Seesaw
There's that
Invisible internet
The enemy knows about
Spiritual
They're so pissed they wanted to do it they don't they'll never Domino
What the f***
Is going on man
So let me break down that story cuz first of all he wasn't joking when he said he was drinking with amorphic
Get the f*** out of here just realize it like really bad
Whoops I better another one for dessert in another Woodford desert I've been I drove Jesus cry
What is happening
The real the real like headline of that story is
I missed saying goodbye to my grandma cuz I was drinking in the morning
The answer to that is your dad at the house if you want
But you decided to stick around and have a horrible to while you drive
In the morning
Looks bad Alex it doesn't look good now just don't tell stories like that
At all now
I don't know how to connect to an invisible internet that everybody has
And then she died coincidentally it is they were like
Oh we just got this
Psychic idea that she was going to die soon
But even if that's true
Alex
You were up
And you just
Drink beer in the morning and then drove to visitor this is a story about you
Ignoring psychic
Hours
It would be
Yeah
Ebi story about you believing that your psychic powers were less important that your desire
I have a breakfast beer
Listen
Play said I had a rough one I stayed up till 4 I got to drink a Guinness in the morning to get going
Nori was
Two in my ear off last night
Talking about ghosts or something
My God
So anyway that was a little bit weird
But now we get into
What I'm going to call Alex's May and breakdown of the Super Bowl
I forgot this
Super Bowl app isn't to talk about the halftime show or any of that stuff nearly as much as you might think
Cuz there's another thing
Too obvious
Sleep satanic
Uno
I don't think so. There's another thing that's a little more important
And that's Alex
Is
7th Super Bowl and they're just calling him
Cross between
Hercules and Apollo
Worship
But again it's only a game at the end of the day but we understand the human compass
Petition and inhuman striving is what makes us great
Men competing against each other women competing at each other
But onto this they add all the globalism they had the prop
Opaganda they had the anti family
The racial
Separation message
What
Do you hunger for this competition
And then they show the so-called black
Quarterback
Arkansas
Team
Kansas City team
Is about as wide as I am
And the media says it's racist to Tom Brady won
Ronald McDonald
He's got curly hair
Oh boy
Absolutely not race
Sister Tom Brady won
Was racist his put on one of his famous hats
I get to decide
People's race at
Suppose
Wow
This is ugly
It's a goes on quite a while that's wild
The media didn't say that the game was racist
Alex is just pointing to a bunch of anonymous people on Twitter who posted jokes about a black quarterback losing during Black History Month
And then pretending there's a serious argument the video maker
I granted a lot of people rightly don't like Tom Brady
Cuz he's a dick
This angle that Alex is taking you stupid
Play Space on literally nothing any
Deeply
Speedway race
Prairie
It gets so much worse
Yeah if you are if you are like I hate it when the media points out
Racism in the wrong way
But your defensive that is to get more racist
I don't think the first part happened at all and I think you just want an excuse to be racist
You'll feel a lot like that feels like you just really don't like black quarterbacks because of one cow
Colin Kaepernick
Can so any chance you have to be like
The media blows what I think that's oversimplifying it
Even
Greater oversimplifying
Go to the f****** huge race wow there's definitely that
What about Kaepernick
And also it has to do with vegetable
All of it is the attempt
Temperature
Checked on the anything and everything
Going on
Racial division
Remember
AOC said don't grow cauliflower she saw cauliflower
Growing
La New York
Community gar
And she said it's
White
Cauliflower from Africa you dumb monster
What does it matter what color it is purple
Or black or brown or green or red
Nutrition
But that's
Total mental illness ladies and gentlemen we talked about this before but just because it's relevant here's the full quote
Quote what I love to is growing plants that are culturally familiar to the community
It's so important
So that's really how you do it right
That's such a core component of the green new deal with having all these project makes sense in a cultural context
Text and it's an area that we get the most push back on because people say
Why do you need to do that that's too hard
But when you really think about it when someone saying it's too hard to do a green
Space that grows Yucca instead of
I don't know cauliflower or something
What you're doing is taking to Colonial approached environmentalism
That's why a lot of communities of color get resistant to certain environmentalist movements because they come with a colonial lens on
This is not about cauliflower being white
There's nothing to do with that but
The thing the reason that I read that quote again even though we've talked about this
Is because you wouldn't
Cover this
That way
You wouldn't cover this the way Alex is covering it unless you had a vested interest
In trying to create a white victimhood argument for your racist audience to enjoy
Oh yeah and that's
Kind of exactly what he's doing with the Superbowl to in it
That I mean it's real bad
Look at all of these things
Because
It's it's
Soul
Awful
How old is people think
Because just like
There's no way that this thing could be racist
Silly you're just making a mountain out of a molehill you know
But if you actually just listen to what people are saying and then look into it you can find like
The tiniest
Things are built on a f****** mountain of racism and if you look into it if you would be
Be interested in if you would be
Curious about it you might find
Holy s*** there's racism under all of this stuff that I would think of
The penny you think the pennies racist
Hippie you probably look at you in your pocket
You don't like it's that kind of s***
Am. It might not be but you should take people's word and
Be interesting
I think I think of a lot of folks
Are guilty of this I mean it's the sound biting of
Subculturez
Information transfer share
Bye
People
Do it out of laziness sometimes and out of racism sometimes
Name a bunch of motivation
Intersection areas that Alex's
Racist
And he's also super lazy
Cuz that he's really just reading a Paul Joseph Watson article has call Joseph Watson nose
That his audience
Eat this stuff up
Today
The thing that I kept thinking while I was listening to this is like
These dicks thought this was worth their time
I saw Paul Joseph Watson article this morning and Infowars
Dot-com
Tom Brady winning Super Bowl as races are this is a joke
Read about 20 tweets by black people saying it I didn't believe it I went to their account
They were serious and I read hundreds more
They said it's so insulting he beat a black man
It was a lot of black men helped Tom Brady win that
Super Bowl
Telling you they were black
Folks
Quarterback I guess it's a gimmick
Cadillac
Who's the leader one of the founders of black lives matter is totally White
What is happening at the other white lady said she was black
What are we doing here insane do you think you're winning
Cuz you know Brady had at least like a half white team of the New England Patriots is all God it's white people winning
Easiest Buccaneers teams almost all black
What the hell does it even matter what color is
But this
Is
The mental illness
I thought the tweets
Had to be a joke
What it's all about
The fact that he wasn't ashamed
President Trump was a fan before the Press
You seem to be the one who's upset you seem very upset
Very upset ridiculously over-the-top upset
Berry Racine want they slaughtered the end of it
Because it was just such a
By the other team
And they're like look
The black quarterbacks losing
That
Other quarterback had wider skin than I do
I just
I guess I'll curl my hair and Sable
Doesn't even matter it's like what the hell does that have to do with anything
What color is quarterback hit
While
Tom Brady was a black guy
He would be just as famous or probably more so
YouTube
Call my skin
Pink
That's mental illness
Colors I like
There's what
My dad knows how to get me a green watch
When I got up
Purple shirt on folks and I like purple people I got Bland
This is mental illness ladies and gentleman I got a black microphone what does that mean
I like Outlook
What
Don't know what's going on anymore
I don't know what's happening
What was that
I don't know if your uncle started yet at a certain point you put roles in your uncle's mouth to keep him from talk
I am honestly confused by his idea that everyone's ripping him off with
Black microphones
That is all just about Rush East have a gold microphone
And Alex is trying to like
Be like I was
Something I don't know
Step2 startlingly race
Displaying that
Wow goes back to
Comparing Mahomes to Shaun King
And Rachel dolezal
And Japan this is just
Izanagi
God no
I know you all know that but it's the way they
Projectile what's that idiot
Shaun King
No
African blood
We just look at him
Black people singing
And who's the other lady
LeBlanc related
Prisoner hair out
Rachel dolezal
I mean it's sick
Fox
Absolutely sick
But I'm digressing almost at Thomas Eggman
I wanted to illustrate let's keep rolling it
Tom Brady
Knows that it's not as bad as a fluid ammonia
Knows that it's a hoax
Refusing to wear his mask
After the game
And they're so mad and he did that on purpose
That makes me like Tom Brady
Way more than the fact that he has
The greatest of all time
No doubt in the NFL
He's now the greatest of all time
Not being a coward
What's the other
White dude posing as a black dude
On the other team that got his ass
Hanover
Maybe if you had a black quarterback
Not loss
Quarterbacks
Text bright
That right there is
The towel that Alex is racist troll
Oh yeah he's actually pretty pretty good
That's the that is the signifier
But my point is me like
Has Rachel dolezal or whatever the hell her name is
But this is all the global of trying to get us to in fight with each other
Yeah there's
Quarterback
Do you know he's looking at
He's getting that curled folks
He's in there hours a week getting all like that
But you can say he's black
What was the great great great great great great great great great great granddaddy
This is where we realize that Alex doesn't realize it Mahomes
Who's dad was a professional baseball player
Now this is wildly racist to a
Just
I'm out of amazing that you can keep going I feel like you already nailed your racism in you you're done
You know like he said he might as well
Just be like
I don't believe it anybody's black
If I don't want them to and then you're done Alex's why you finish Alex's white insecurity and is white
Vanity.
Really alarm
By people making jokes
About Mahomes
Losing during black history month and the only way that he could deal with that is to do an outrageously Ray
Racist segment on his show
On and on
Where he tries to be the Arbiter
I'm saying that he's not actually even black
To what end is this
I am confused
I am very
Confused
I don't know.
What is the continued existence of the universe
In a certain to a certain
You know like
Spider-Man's like I don't understand how this country has made it as long as it has if it is rewarded this moron so much
You know like there's
There's a fundamental confusion I get from listening to this
I've just like how
Who
Why
What are we doing
I don't know
Of Joe Biden
He had a little message
Before the Super Bowl
Sorry
I have this is what I this is what got
This is what I realized was screwing with my head
Apologies for interrupting and
Derailing this entire problem I'm fired I get it
No problem
I remember
Something important
Happening
Right now
Very sophisticated
News political show
Would talk about
And that is not
Tom Brady
Fifth president did he fix his God is being impeached
Have you seen have you seen Mahomes hair though
How to beat
To talk about it
So by then gave a little bit of a little message
I to covid-19
Super Bowl and Alex has a video of it where
Fighting
Sure it's unclear if his video is authentic
Because their other videos
But don't really have
You know it there's like
Crowd noise
But who cares
Yeah I don't give a fuk I don't remember Alex reporting about how
Everyone Boo the s*** out of trump at baseball game now that wasn't a big deal
I don't care but they discover that neither
He gets into his analysis of the commercials
Mostly just Springsteen
Bruce Springsteen
Riding around
He supports cutting your gun
Esports pregnancy support transgender
Oh but now he's a good guy going to bring it together he's Bruce Springsteen
Spirit of America
Here is this disgustingly
Condescending at
4 years ago I was in the middle of the cutout battle
There's a chapel in Kansas
Standing on the exact center of the lower 48 it never closes
Call are more than welcome
Morgan Brittany here
In the middle
I don't care for that add myself
And I don't think Alex has any right
To complain or critique commercials
No it's it's a little bit of Knox
Alex
He said he's going to take some calls
He gets around to it but
He comes in from break and the
Or maybe whoever it is
Trizomal glutathione
We are just
Countdown here
Countdown
To the false flag
Shower
The proof of them coming for you and me
He doesn't
Another coming
Emergency alert level prepared Masa false flag
So this Elvis song that is not little more A Little Less Conversation little more action it's just let yourself go
Alex into a little bit of a mood and he starts rambling you know he's been mad about black people in white
People playing football so it's nice to listen to music whenever white man stealing black people's music
Call the same.
How's it going on nobody's scared no more
Those people
Better Diane
When the killers come
Dying starts
Mommy start
Don't look like the left much ready for a war but they sure won't one cuz they never been in one
Metal bumper music
Play some Elvis I apologize for ruining your we got cabs are we got Pastor Sam we got hairy we got Tyler We Got Talent
20 something dollars and I said I want seven on that board
Cuz I don't want to keep people on hold but let's just
Go to him now
Probably sit here waiting for that big old
Juicy false-flag terratech
Galaxy might had a meeting with somebody in the bathroom
If I got a little bit of happiness
So his first collars again causing all the time a pastor Sam
One of the things that I find really interesting but Alex
Does techniques with callers
Is he creates false conflict
To tell Martha
Whenever they disagree with him on like a minut point
He'll creative false
Fight with them to hear the frame of their position in a certain way
Then he can respond
To that doesn't allow the nuance
Of the matter to me
Dealt with in this case Alex and made some comments about how
You know if the gun
Compass catering
You don't want to be at home
You don't want to start a fight with a
The police cuz that's you know that's how the old Civil War is going to start
If you end up the
What to do with that no you got to Target the
The high-level globalist
And Pastor Sam's
Proposition is more like
They're coming to take our guns
Pain
It's it's already past the
The point you would think
And that Nuance is dangerous for Alex
Text to have
Well
It would
It requires that
Use actual positions
Sound a lot more
Like aggressively and immediately violent that he wants them to
And that he thinks can be profitable
So he starts a fight
Don't worry. Patriots thing it's time for war
I see you strongly disagree with me
You know Pastor Sam I didn't say a lot out
I said if the cops are coming
Your house
It's a good idea I'll be waiting for him until
Because they've been brainwashed
Identify certain point it's going to start up here
But up
Lying down I'm staying with Target
Is it the police
They get the police
Become frog gun
I'm a big boy I'm a smart boy
Then I would want to go after which I'm not saying do
That's what people that were running the show
Can I say is better
How to be a man
Tell me how to do it
I know you said that
Dispense with the nice
The first I'm going to tell you that I called yet
I'm going to tell you that I love you and that I'm a prayer partner for what you doing
I followed you
You for 20 years
Yes I Alex's 80s created this phone
The artificial
With this call so there's no hope of any point actually being discussed
It just goes nowhere
Sweet goes to another call and this person
Has a very
Very easy to answer questions
You're on the air welcome
Hi there hi Alex how are you
I want to make a point about the January
Trump supporter
5 years there was a counter-protest at every
People in those
Communities felt very strongly that it would be too dangerous
People from taking part
Because
They didn't want people to more people to be killed
Yeah they were like hey
Stay away these people are violent Trump supporters might kill people at this thing and then
They were roundly mocked
And then
Trump supporters killed people at that thing
So
Yeah I made it super easy to answer question yes
This is not the first time that this is happening there were
Greatly diminished
Counter protest thing to happen
At the gun rally in Virginia
The the one that Alex went to they try to be very insightful at
Inciting at happens sometimes
The counter protest
Folk
I believe
Prioritize
They like to live
In a lot of time supposed to be a little bit more responsible
And in the case of January 6th
Are there was pretty
Pretty consistent messaging that I saw
From people that said that I'm aware of it this is not a good thing
To go counter
Demonstrate to know
What I'd like to know is where were the counter-protesters
The thing that we said was going to be a violent display of our power the implication of courses
Is that they were
Mixed in the crowd that yes babe that's all bulshit
So I know Alex's gallery
Doing this fake fighting with his calls and I'm like
This guy is f***** up
I think he's I think he's doing speaking
Agree
Why are you starting another ad
If people are always asking me out
Decent chance without drugs
And when you go on Joe Rogan show on Joe Rogan
You told him that you got a problem with adderal and it's a little
Well
Stop that one's a little bit more like
The pictures are starting to picture starting to come into Focus
Yeah we had a real rough
Start of the show and now the energy is
Why am I
Throughout the day you get
More tired
You know and maybe
I ain't had this happen before have you ever been working for like
Like six hours right
You know you got some more work to do but right around that 6 hours
You just so tired
And you just really use a
You know sure you go get a cup of coffee or
You go to the bathroom and you snort some rails do what you got to do to make it through the last 2 hours dad
Saying but that is really coming around on the idea that he's on drugs
It's a lot of sun
I think the fact that Rogan asked him a question really
Really makes me
A bit more open to the idea because why would Rogan bring that up if
It wasn't something that Alex brought up with
With him
It sounded like it was coming from a place
Genuine concern
French
Yep
Hey I don't want you to keep hurting
Turn yourself man
Yeah
And yeah
And Alex
Keeps
Saying that everybody insists on
Take a little Coco
Big little math but you do a little bit of
V-eats that way you don't have to do as much give me a call
The beginning of this I got really excited cuz I like said he's going to have Jay Dyer
Yeah and they're going to talk at this guy is a guy who's the primary source reader in all this
I immediately lost
All respect
What would you call this.
Time we're in right now is it's pretty clear
Forget they're saying
Patriots are terrorists are going to arrest us all
State air attacks loser getting right Estates terror attack
What would you call this. Of time or in
And what are you doing to get ready for it because
Every few Generations goes through some real tyranny we're about to go through a
This is the age of transition
Brad this is their phraseology
Before how we go from the way things were during this
Christian. Of the age of
You know Pisces the age of the fish
To the
Aquarian age which is what blavatsky write one of the
Esoteric philosophers that the elite
Always like to look there she called this the external ization of a higher heat polish it go tell Kerry Cassidy about
No s***
Now by worldview is based
On this woman from the 1830s who thought you could do magic
My fear that other people have learned to do magic
You know the problem
He's a moron
Problem that I'm having is
Jay Dyer is a great DJ name
It's not bad great DJ name
I would love to be
That's so good
Jay bilas great Jay dires great it be awesome
Have a collaboration with
Ghost
Cuz apparently believes that those goes conductive
Through David Wilcock
Spirit
You do not need
You to do any voice
You don't need to do scratching on the records
Okay so
I don't really care about him and I are as interview it is
Dumb whatever you when you start with Helena blavatsky
I'm out
About Dad
Are you going to phone conversation
Things with friends about these sorts of things and you know week
We can talk about stuff but
When you want to make me scared of your big bad guy at a magazine and insist
But they follow the
The teachings of Helena blavatsky
That's like
That's one step
Further than if somebody's like you know the Unabomber did make some good points
I'm just look
I know there's stuff
You know
I think it's a little more fun
Cuz at least there's Magic
Anyway
So Alex gets dark in about Trump
A little bit here
And he says something that I find
Unaccept
Okay love you listen to this clip
Can you understand Veronica sing
5 years of Alex's life
Have been
Wrong
David meaningless
And Alex has been an instrumental part of the globalist
Plan to bring into urine
Does he know that
I think Trump meant well he was a Nashua City America's being screwed over
But that the establishment let him win
She did win by landslide
4 years ago
Because they know they can run circles around him and use him to energize
The last eventually commit any crime
And then support a total police state
Abandon any values they had
Clearly evident
Active
Other than sophisticated level we were all
Play
Wow
So you are a useful idiot
Exactly like you claimed you were not
To a guy 3 days ago
Yeah I mean there's there's really no other way to interpret that
Cuz I mean I guess the life wouldn't have been
Turned into whatever this is that would facilitate tyranny of Clinton did wanch
So I guess the only way to reach the point where actual tyranny Could Happen Trump had to win right Alex
Many many times the Trump wouldn't have won if it wasn't for it for like that
I doubt also heavily implied that Rodger stone is working for the globalist
Hell yeah you know Beavis
Bully pulpit for Trump
Yeah I'm at you know what I could
Could believe that
Or maybe Alex is making all of this stuff up then other stuff up my just be making it all up here
Spitballing and nothing he says means anything
If you were being serious
He would then have to the next. Should be
I know I should shut up
Because you quit cuz clearly I make all the wrong decisions that lead us to this but this is my fault
I'm blessed half a decade I have been leading you to tyranny State and I made multiple.
Matarese with police state in the title
Supposed to know better and not just that but you followed me. Get to where we are meeting I am
The reason that we are where we are and I am a bad leader and you should not follow me
Getting bowled out for years ago I was going through a divorce
Okay well now I
Maybe
Wait around for three minutes.
We got one last clip.
It's like I think everybody kind of
Expected there to be more talk about the Super Bowl halftime show
As opposed to Alex
Being racist sure but every time
What do you think he's going to Ziggy's on
That's what he does
You talk about the halftime show tiny bit with Jay Dyer and like
This clip is just titled
Stupid talk about halftime show because this is stupid
But you are venting to me
Did you see that halftime show and I
Watch Super Bowl because it added Tom Brady wouldn't be wearing a mask on it I like him I watched
They're all
Skull mask
They're subhuman but the one guy has speech
And they all like puppets do what he says
This was very sick
At a subconscious level that means you are robots
In the fastest event you are skeletons you are dead
I control
Exactly what I think is going on here some bulkley speaking it began with this choir of robot
Drones race everybody's up in the in the
Wire with the weekend guy they're singing
And they're all just for doing what they're like
El Papa is like there are there on a marionette right
I just
My response to all of this
Kind of conversation is like
If you guys are just high kicking around it like a hacky sack and this is a conversation you want to have great
But if you're adults on a presumably
Grown up
News
The world events radio show that you have very seriously this is
Coming this kind of conversation is laughably stupid
Who you're all drones and only the weekend has a voice
And the only people who should be allowed to publicly discuss the semiotic
Save this event
Would be somebody it would be like Umberto Echo to put this in the context of all of this
But even then it's a f****** Super Bowl halftime show, go to bed. I would have been here's the thing that I want
I asked
Is a rhetorical question
These types of things have been going on forever
Talking about the symbology of halftime shows in the supply of Jeezy's music videos and all this s***
I want to know these motherfuker
People like Jay Dyer
They pretend that they study this stuff
Actual field of information
I want concrete examples of things
What they read in music videos at halftime show it's all around you
What
Look up your window daddy that's why I wanted to be rhetorical
I just want I just want to know what magical like
Psychic revelation
You get from
Also they took off the mask
September 2nd song
In the performance
Who cares
Yeah I just I find this stuff really dumb I used to really enjoy reading blog
That would talk about like
People have cover in one I would be when I was young
All the time
Has any how many Super Bowl halftime shows are even memorable
And none of them for their semiotic
Janet Jackson mix
That was not the semiotic of what she was wearing
No
The prince hologram on a couple years ago wasn't there
That was kind of bad
Give a s*** about the halftime show
It's a people we talk about people like Alex care a lot about every year for
Day and then we're done just let's just not talk about it for that day
There's a lot of potential for psych interesting performance
I think that it's
You know cut God bless people who are really really try
Geographers are gray
Just aged out of the point where I can get too excited about a lot of the musical acts but I appreciate like
I get it
I can watch the weeknd's performance I can be like this is not necessarily for me it's not my favorite thing but I get it
The hell out of it shirt
Yeah it is
Fodder for people who have a tough time coming up with things to talk about
A people like Alex you just need to be mad at something
The Super Bowl such a perfect
Thing in that wheelhouse rally
Do you have to be like
Sublimating of mail drives to war
But you can complain about whatever symbology is in the halftime show he can complain about and apparently
The race of people
And whether or not
They
Attitude being black according to Alex Jones
F****** disgrace
That is really disqualifying as like
Allowed in polite Society ever again
Well you should be shunned
That deserves a shunning
It would be interesting for someone to like
Sit down and try to explain to Alex
Exactly why
Play with self
Flagrantly race
Understand I think it just needs a good
Universal shunning
Everybody shun him
I think most people have gotten that message
I think so too
We need some more though.
Put some crazed up the shunning sure
We reach the end of this episode did not enjoy the Super Bowl
We're going to get to the impeachment trial stuff today but
Because it was Tuesday got started sure
That will come Friday episode will I check into Alex's handling all that stuff
But I do think that this is this episode does import
To go over because of the incredible racism
Wow and because of the clear turn towards
Really aggressively being like also I go, they're going to happen
You can't read that any other way than preemptive damage
Control
When it's coming from someone like Alex
So invested in Terrorist edging
Yep
Remove the back on Friday
Impeachment business
Indeed we will do it today cuz I saw some tweets
Bruce Caster is
I mean that was one of the most
Fundamentally disgraceful things I've ever seen in my entire life bad argumentation
No argumentation
Just rambling. Call Barn
You know what
Being a senator's pretty cool you know
Extraordinary people
You know be great like
Trump's lawyers are doing
Terribly right
Out of nowhere you hear glass break....
Mayotte
I-5 and republicanism Barnes kicks him in the gut
Larry klayman coming from the sting spot and drop
It's downright of baffled
Swcw
Eating and Hogan okay okay rock I just got it I got it
But
Please find a local charity or bail finding Jerry to help out people doing
This site for years ago
Holding
Alex
Birthstone colors