Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
Because I am a complete Nutter
So grateful you forgot it
Discuss a little coconut water with little jokes
Dreading that two episodes
Would have been
Nightmare
Maldonado
Without talking about Alex Jeff
Alex Jones
This is not your grandpa podcast
I don't know I don't know
What the f*** is wrong with that guy
Yo
Today
What is
Monday
Monday Monday June 12th
Okay
It's sort of the culmination
Of our last
Control
About the Megyn Kelly interview that's
Coming out on Sunday
Obvious
Like there's some damage
And he's gone overboard
Attacking Chelsea Clinton
Quite a bit
Does she
She got involved
She started talking about how big and Kelly shouldn't have had Alex Jones on the show
You know there's a lot of people who have been going around on Twitter and saying that she should not be giving him a platform
Absolutely a valid point disagree with it to some extent
Because that work is done
The interview has been done and it's going to air barring
Bring some sort of crazy sponsor.
And we can
Which I'm assuming Alex Jones
Somehow Lobby and go sponsor
Twitter and said like oh JPMorgan
You're not ever really actually has done that
What's the f****** shelf that's a win-win
Oh yeah
The liberal Twitter
Don't put
Maniac on there which makes his followers even more maniacal in their support for
Whenever you have
Sponsors pull it cuz he doesn't have sponsors
Pull out real
He doesn't have that concern
You then
Because I'm so dangerous
Everything plays into his hands
Except for one
Very specific thing
That I'll be laying out over the course of this episode
Because this is innocent
The third installment of our
How not to cover Alex Jones
Continue until he's penniless
Tumi VI
Idea that everyone
If I don't give this guy a platform
Right understand the issue there
You just do it right
Gym in
Hockey and mundane ways
Playing into his hands
Set down the other night
Twitter thread
This is a major opportunity
Are people really want to make Headway against Alex Jones
There is a path we can proceed down
But no one is doing it
It's hard everyone is just getting mad about Sandy Hook
And I understand why
It's horrible
We've covered it extensively
If anything I've done
His denial of the death
Of those 20 children
Yeah
It is
Monster
It's unconscionable
Airline the damages done to their family
The lady who was getting death threats
Included
Yeah that was in the article
Was that you can't listen
Wow order deprogramming of a cult
Yeah
So all that is awful and I get why people want to focus on
Even in that
Scenario even if
Colonel
There's something
So much more
That we need to
Like
The issue that should be pressed on Alex is not
Why do you think that nothing happened in Newtown
Because that's a question he's been ready to answer forever
Yeah he's been
He's been preparing for that one absolutely
She's going to do that Buckley sat him down and was like dude I'm your cousin
Now you listen to me
That's going to come up
And stop marrying my third wife
I like the ongoing marital Troubles of Buckley better based on nothing
So the question that Megan Kelly should've asked
In regards
Sandy Hook and maybe she did I don't know
Who interviewed
So I don't I don't know what she has
And a lot of
The things that we have to go on it
Assumption
Past history
Of TV News special
Trailer
The question T-shirt
What is
Let's talk about your position on Sandy Hook
That put the traps down for Alex to walk
Because his narrative trailer
Is B we had debate
We we heard both sides of it sometimes for Devil's Advocate
Aldi's
So you say that
Then play him
VSCO
Use a synthetic
Completely
What actors
Fractured
That they clearly
Used Acura Sunday even ended up using
Photos of kids killed in mass shootings
Shooting
The sky is now the limit I appreciate your call
So you play that clip for him
Which is why are you lying
About what you said in the past
It's not about Sandy Hook necessarily
The important question is
Why are you pretending that wasn't your position
It's very publicly available
He's not ready to answer
And it's not
It's not a question that he can answer
Without
Stepping into a huge pile of s***
There's no conceivable answer to it other than
I was lying back then
Right
I was caught up in propaganda back then
And I think there will be consequences
I didn't realize how bad that would look in hindsight
He would have to say
I found evidence that it wasn't
Fake and I'm an idiot I'm sorry I said those things
Know his position would have
To be I was playing devil
What do you want
You have to listen to that go
No
Unequivocal
He was explaining
What he saw the reality as
To his audience
He was directly saying it to a listener who was calling in and everyone else was the third
Yep they were the surrogate callers were being trained
And taught in the Macabre was that
In that clip he's
He says
I did
Believe it at
And now I do
So tell you can't call that Devil's Advocate you coming to a realization
There has to be something
It's not to get to like
Why are you a monster
How could you deny Facebook
It's why did you lie right
Or are you going to apologize
What is the nature of your deceit in this case or are you going to say
Your
Wrong or I'm dumb
I fell for this
With that sort of a question
You ask him
Why would you do that to those families
It sounds like there's going to be an emotional resonance
It's to it but it doesn't work with him
He's not going
He's ready for
His feelings and emotions
He's better than everybody else
No he has no feeling
Because he's never laugh
He's never actually left
Never
So we're going to get to this episode there's a couple of fun things
We're going to deal with a lot of damage control about Megyn Kelly
Getting
Then we're going to get to some really f***** up stuff
At the end of this
I'm going to play you a clip
That I think indicates that out
Our last episode back from 2015
Alex Jones
Quote-unquote jump the shark
In not in his conception
In this episode and validates the last 20 years
This career
So we're going to start at the beginning
You don't have coconut
Henry stop drinking wine whoever takes out the window
Alex started out the show on Monday
June 4th
Infowars.com Studios
Alex
Absolutely dominating
The treaties
Coordinated MBC this is all PR
Freshly out of Megyn Kelly
Chelsea Clinton
We know that you hang out with
This is incredible
Kelly
Trump says better watch out
Add
I just knew I was walking into a trap
Because no matter what
Zombies
Everybody else then just reminded of the show so it grows even fast
In the WikiLeaks
Patients dying because of your foundation how your mommy
Airplane
Alcohol
I kinda already know too
What the format of it
Who's going to be
Essentially the same attempt
Gotcha
There's going to be a mobster
Of course he knows we all know
What do you eat with the answer
Cancel the interview will be
Chelsea Clinton
He really
Stop bringing up Jeffrey Epstein
Flame
Does Trump was on it
Whatever he brings up how Clinton was on the quote-unquote Lolita Express
Trump but did to they were friends also
You can't
I'll just ignore that part of it
Fiesta frame
The interview as a hippie
That's important to his
His narrative work
And maybe that's fair
I don't know
I mean
You think there's no other way.
Organize
Is it right
How would you how would you do a puff piece on Alex Jones
I could do a piece that wasn't a hippie
I think I think certainly is it safe
Forgiven
Interview Alex
I wouldn't be doing it as a hatchet job
Destroy them
To drop that because I would also
Speak to
Here's what I would
Seek and Destroy first off by
What is my Approach Kelly should have done
The Sandy Hook stuff alone
Do something we talked about the beginning
Do you have to bring it up that's the approaches
2X
Explain to him and to illuminate to the audio
The link between his past
And his propaganda
That's what I would speak to do if I were doing
A story on him
It would not be a hippie
In the sense that I want to
You know like
Score points off ever
I got but I wouldn't
Make clear
All of your toxic masculinity
All the things that you have about
All of that is very easily traced back
To your relationship
But your mother
That you've explained yourself on the air
Lathe
Further I would lay out God that would Blindside him beyond belief further I would lay out your
You're a bigot
I know you don't want to believe that
But you are
You think that you've been beaten up by black people more than
Martin Luther King has been beaten up by white people
You think that you're the new Martin Luther King
You have real problems
Grace
Maybe you don't say the N word on-air or maybe not even your private life I don't know
But that doesn't matter
You embody horrible racism
Now look at your pants
You think that you were beat up all the time by black
When you are a kid
Not realizing
World problems
You were a f****** s*** head kid
Also how many
How many Comas do you have to
You put other people in before it invalidates any before you look in the mirror
Yeah
Betsy I would take those stories that he's told on the air of being like
Targeted for his white
You realize how
The way that you deal with race now mirrors
That childish idea that you had when you were a kid
Do you realize that all of your anti-feminist ID
Kind of root
They take you
How to be a man you can't be a mama's boy you don't get love anymore kind of stuff
That's what I would do
Just laying there
Let's get in there what do you think
And hopefully there'll be some Opera mean he would just scream at me but
Like that's the way that
You would have to
Because because that would
Do the thing that
The
That the thing that he would hate the most
That would amass
Well
Far more damaging to his listeners
Because they're in
Like will not there but his audience as
Noted in the past
Is mostly White
80% +
Percent dudes
Yeah and
The most damage
His listeners be idea
Percent White
Instead of
Instead of trying to catch
In Ally
Or catching him in
In a
Evil
Are you really just
A p****
Did you ever consider that maybe you're a coward Act
I don't like that phrase
First of all the p****
See stuff but also
Using
Anything else I appreciate where you're coming
But here's the distinction I would make
I would not be seeking to emasculate
But he would feel emasculated based on his own twisted worldview
I will be seeking to actually
Give him a more robust
View of race and masculinity
Better much more integrated into the realities world as opposed to
His abused child understanding of it
Play clearly
I don't know this is
This is f*****
But clearly something happened
And it arrested in his development
Yeah that is what happened
Very simple to see
So all his understandings about the way people interact
The way
The world works
Is childish
Globalist
Is walking childish to begin with
And you take it you take it further
That's what I would want to get out of the inner
I would just do the psychopath test with
Call boy
Hey you scored your a murderer
Are you a murderer probably knock
Memphis be like like
Did you f*** Buckley's wife
Either questions we need answers
Less emasculation in more infantile
But I want to be able to connect with
The child the child version of himself
But he clearly is acting out with
Cuz it's
Don't you think that would make him a sympathetic
Figure though
No because
The damage is done is so severe
Daddy would take a tremendous amount of work for him to ever become zip
Pathetic again
Because once you get through that part
This is the route
Oh so much of your bigoted
So much of your stupid position
That you have
So much of your twisting of the truth is to match
Be there in five
Open tile ideas about the world
What is that
Then you can pile in with the
Why do you feel the need to lie about Sandy Hook
Cuz then you can
Like you
Destroy him
You can get in with the
Okay what about this do you realize that
Deep state of the conservative movement
Right now is going to take away healthcare for women that really need it a lot of it
Totally your fault that you played a massive role in perpetuating at Planned Parenthood
For medical progress
Platypus
Merida propagandistic Ali do you realize all the damage
That you've done to our International standing
Two are actually caught me once this bubble
Starts to go down a little bit justify your cheerleading for
Do you understand
And then he said that he would take take away a lot of
Sympathetic
Yeah
It's such a
To watch
Watch this
Reaction
Based on this
This entire interview
It's just that
Like you say something inflammatory and then you get out right
The outrage goes bad
To the other side and you just
Outrage
And nobody ever actually
Deals with
The f****** problem
V to some extent
Because it's a ping pong the game where used
Play yeah it's a traditional
Structures at
Unit like you said you get you say something f***** up I get mad
You get mad that I'm mad at you and it just goes back and forth
A media and a number of the players make a good amount of money
There is that.
That is really really
Customary
Even even though Alex
Themself as such
Alternative media figure
He's still very willing
Play that game
But the reality is you need to not play that game
Can't be played with someone like our
Like he's too
He's only
He's only yeah
Now the whole thing
The whole thing is a mess
You just described in your interview something that TV news
Witches
Just play the clip
Make you sit there
And listen to your word I would love to watch Alex
BB jelly and sweaty
Adjust
Probably better interview is
Alex Jones
Can't handle something could have your
Immaculate Alex Gallagher moments
And that's the whole thing again you can dish out all you want because you're a boy
Bully moment you get challenge
Runaway you're out
Is a
Withal
Sincerity
I wish they would have let me
The interview
It would be
The greatest
I would be in the background just
Barely barely audible just giggling like a lute
Yeah
Anyway
41 Clifton
Is Alex explaining
He thinks he was lied to
About the premise of the inner
Purview
It's simply amazing to see them
4 hours
In the morning till 10
45 at night
Interviewing me
They rented a barbecue place they rented out in my office
So they can edit it down to 11 minutes and then
I know he's ended questions together
Villain lighting
Villain
Maybe you just look like a villain in any lightning
On the phone with you
I know you're a lawyer and a hat
Sandy Hook
Those things
So she can try to get some answer she can stick together
Amazing
So let me read between the lines on that
You look like you want to yell something
Megyn Kelly
Told Alec
Means that what she actually said was
I find you fascinating
Or something like that
If you're crazy person
I also probably like
You know go get some dinner I'm coming down to Austin
Show me some
Call wife
Let's let's
Get comfortable talking to each other a little bit make out a little bit
Sup the other stuff
TheCHIVE
Look that villain
It's just kind of a standard
News interview footage
Is really dead
Terrible
Is product even later
The other thing
Cyberghost
She kept asking me the same question over and over again
We know why
He didn't just
Service question and Ike
Continue to not
How do you feel about all the
The damage that
You've done to this
Coming
How do you feel about that
About as bad as the Sandy Hook victims
You keep bringing this up
I mean
Cuz I think our listeners interviewers want to know Megan this is our profession
Alright I'll change that
Uber how I look at it
You know what I just realized to
Pet Megan is gorgeous
She is beautiful
What team may end up
Humor
He left January with the secret
Presentation of what the interview is and her setup of it
Is very
Wrong
I would have got it was wrong
Clip is Alex trying
Explain
Why the demo
In the world are mad about his interview
Flagging show
15 minutes
So that she couldn't sit there and edited together
Unbelievable credible
Take 5
Why would you do a villainous laugh
Sing about your village are you talking about
The Trap
It also like
That strikes me so much
Yeah you're stupid Network
You're mad that I always win
Doesn't mean that you get to
Are me down he was that kind of f******
I don't actually really want to bully
That is actually
Goodnight clip
He said one thing that I
Kind of do agree with
And that is that a lot of the outrage about it is serving
To get more hype
For the interview
Intentional or not is another thing
I don't believe that there's a
A plot on the part of NBC-2
Hey let's anger people
Maybe there is
Guarantee guarantee
How many people watch
Sure
It's going to have very good rated no s***
Why
Probably do a lot to the extreme
Like
You would watch it
Yeah
We do for our work
Haywood Road
Are we going to cover it
Tech news
Yeah totally you have a built-in audience
A couple hundred thousand people listen to Alex regularly
Cuz his body was not nearly as big as he thinks it is
See Clinton
Get more yeah
The people who say Hillary should go away
Hillary should not
Go away the avatar for why the f*** are you white
Hating on women so goddamn much
Chelsea Clinton should go the f*** away
I don't need any more political Dynasty
I'm done with the bushes
I hope they all go
Done with the Kennedys
I'm done with where the whole point
If not to have
A goddamn monarchy
I think the Kennedys are done
For the most part
Second I don't think
Chelsea is necessarily engaged in electoral politics
I don't know if she's been asked if she's intimated that perhaps he'll run for office
She said no
Oh did she go
The few I've seen a few where she
She's like at this time
Am I to have milk
Either one
I don't think it's fair to
To say
Here is a person
Who is entire adult life
In the realm of politics
XM is gotten involved
The nonprofit NGO organization
Opinions on things
I don't think there's any reason to tell her to shut up
I don't like the idea of her running for office
Necessarily because
The same reason
But there's no reason for her to go away
Coppell
I agree with you completely
Okay.
I disappointed cuz I want my I want my the bushes are a much bigger problem
F*** off
Yeah
I know I know I'm wrong
I know I'm wrong but I have this very visceral emotional reaction
2nd time it's like
Oh
What is Mike Huckabee's daughter have
I don't buy a f****** car I don't care
He's way better at this
Maybe he was the problem is Sarah Huckabee Sanders is talented
Anyway
I don't know
Diamond Caesar bad that's my point my point
It might even be okay
But if you're going to run for president I would not be
Be against that
Yeah well
I'm against
The Senate is
Cox out
Talk about how great he is
Which is
Pretty standard fare
Yes
Cancel him don't show it
It's so hard
Controversy
Don't go watch it
A literal Passion of the Christ
That's how the Romans got criticized
Operating system
In the dark
Running around
Ivanka Trump had to say
I mean you're screaming was super vague
Soft supper maybe the
I checked into the small business
Optimism index
Even in the article
Specifically says
It's mostly because these companies are not going to have to pay Healthcare
I don't like that
Being high
That does not bode well for us the Christ is the top-rated movie of all time
Yeah no
It's number 30
Haven't you ever seen
The reprisal
No I've never seen
Does the direct
YouTube video sequence
Number 30
Number 33 is
Secret life of pets
Right around there
What do you mind if it's saying is it set of box office record that is beat
Been beaten
Superfair
Number 30 is Lord of the Rings
Return of the King that came out in 2000
Second work number 24 is Jurassic Park
It just doesn't work
Lion King is 18 Again
Never was even close
Probably not even in the top 50
Yeah
My parents
When it came out my parents were part of
Church movie where the
We have
To go see the patch
Ports to support
Christian values
In the world
Give me the wildly anti-semitic characters that's okay sorry
Sorry
Actually
My dad is a religious studies professor
He wrote
An opera
Camp
Where are we living
University of Missouri
I was walking by The Secret Circle
Which is a place where
Free speech
You have protesters out there a lot but basically was just for
This insane preacher in a brother Jed
The scream at people already big Pandora
Already
Real fun for a day and then Super annoying after
I heard him screaming about my dad
This article about
Really what I like
You can expect to find truth
Institution where religious studies is
Professor Friesen
Mother
Whoa
All right my man like every got done preparing Civic notoriety I like it
Cool down.
I walked you know like I was curious like
Screaming about my dad
Just wondering you know
El profesor freezing it
Play From Me Spotify
Catastrophic
Real Passion of the Christ fan blow
Also Alex
This is way smaller than
If you really look
Numbers are
Mini skewers
I recently checked back in
He had been growing at all
Not really at all
His profile
You're such a
English
Number of
People listening
Extol extol
This much
To the point where he
You can be
Indians
Higher National concert
He is in the zeitgeist
Nothing nothing we can't get there
I don't even know
Anybody can get there Beyond
I don't know
Christ
MB
Jim Caviezel
He was a movie with
No
Nothing
Really nothing
And somehow he's turned
Super small
Into a
It did just like
The constant
Left
Do you know the reason I think is because his actual audience
Is much larger than his
Going to his website
Actually listening to him audio
There are a lot of people who don't listen
Who are
Did Leah Greene
Yeah
I'm so the damage being done
That's being done by his
It resonates
The people who don't listen
But are already on that page
Yeah the biggest of the world the white nationalist time
Nationalist
Somehow
Very high
Steve
Athlon TVs Hillary for prison or whatever it is and immediately that is
Extend his reach
Through yeah I get it
Having him on
Megyn Kelly NBC that makes the most sense
Is that
There are late
Bigot
Who will be exposed to him
It's backwash
It's all bad back
Yes
The the
Main piece
Pf2 Resistol
In this episode as a massive rant
In the middle of the episode
Just because otherwise I'll be like 7 minutes long
This
Is where Alex is in
Mulan murder mode
He is prophet
Deciding his own demise
Oh yeah of course he's going to die but this is where
I'm talking about the
Damage control
The so far has been like
Kelly sucks
Ryder shows
All this stuff is just
JoJo stuff
This point gets to like
I got to make sure people know that I'm
Laying my life down intentionally.
He knows that they're like I was telling you before we started recording I have a very strong Theory
The Heat
Bentley said something
On camera that he knows he
I think that he exposed himself in a way
That make Kelly probably didn't realize
I bet he wasn't what he said
I'm going to guess it won't be
In the actual interview but if I watched all four hours that raw footage
Check 37 I'm certain
He knows that he said something
And he's worried that it'll be in the actual
Not to the extent of like
Or something like that
Just just one in one clip like
We're playing the game here come on
It's nothing like that
But
Pretty certain based on his
Veggies
He knows that he's in jeopardy
I believe
Chelsea Clinton
Hates women I'm not trying
To get out of this alive dumbasses
Saratoga restaurants in to get out of this a winner in your system
I'm here
I'm here to make you pee
Dewar's analyze and the corruption and the Clinton Foundation
Missing the main calculation
So I want and the Clinton Foundation
Charitable organization regardless of a very bad book title
I want to do I want to deposit right there because
I agree
Not with any
Except for what he said right there at the end
That is
This is why you missed
The calculation
And I agree that everybody who covers him
Missing
What his priorities
He is
To ascertain
A kamikaze
There is a reckless abandon about his public self
You don't give a fuk
If he's on NBC talking about how he doesn't believe in Sandy Hook
He has a thin for it and play
What
Terrible
Is is much different than
Would you care about is
The deconstruction of his ego
Remedy Construction
The globalist
Those two things would really put him in jeopardy
The everything else
Was just nonsense
You want to bring up 9/11 to him
He said 17 here 16 years
Really really puts
Varnish on that beat
Piece of s***
He has
He has it all.
Conspiracy stuff
He's Ironclad
So you do miss the calculations
Whatever you're approaching
That way
Just because
Right
Megyn Kelly in the Greater Media at Large
Is still Bound by a lot of
Things
And they can imagine
Somebody
Completely
Unbound by
Like even Fox
Clings to some of those old ways
Some of those like
We have to
Berries
Sliders
Have some sort of underpinning some sort of
Fact
Some sort of small little thing that we
We can kind of glom onto
Alex
Does not care
Natto
Hilton
He will just make sure it up you can catch him in that making s*** up
He's going to make sure it up about that there's no
You think
EBay normal for a normal media figure
Sooner or later
There's going to
Be a break
There's going to be
Where you have
Something
To to hold on to
Alex
Alex's
F****** Smoke on the Wind
Here's why
Smelling
Mail
The toxic vitality
He has a width of Axe Body Spray
In all conventional news in almost every other facet of people who are
Pontificating
Or whatever
They have forces to keep them in check
Like sponsor
Like the network like
Lake
He probably does have some sort of a
Billionaire benefactor that's backing him up
There probably is something like that you'd assume
Beyond The Zone products
Breitbart
There's got to be something like that behind the scene
Do finances can't work otherwise
But be that as it may the rest of it
Is he sells his own product
But he
Warehouse that ships everything himself
Sponsors that would ever betray you
Indicated by a
Basically just Alex
So he's not going to abandon
That's who Cash Cow
Nothing
Deleuze either
Never heard of good luck radio stations that are under arrest
Control but if those go away
He's not getting paid for that there's no syndication
MP4 Infowars stop
So he's not losing money there
If every single one of his radio Affiliates got lost
Tell me the best thing ever for him
He could claim that he's the biggest victim of censorship in the world
Who caused Mass migration to his webs
Such a great
Swell of like the globalists are coming
I need you to buy my products
Do doesn't lose any money
Spider-Man
Uvideos do all this stuff because
So all of these other people even Sean Hannity
Rush Limbaugh
Very serious Market pressures that stop them from being out and outliers
People can boycott their sponsor
People can make threats
Things like that
The free-market can touch them
Alex really can't
Except by
The people who have been tricked by him
Stopping buying a product
And the likelihood of that is very low
So
Again cult
C programming
Like you can't
You're much more likely to get a mass suicide
Yep totally
So if you come at him with like this idea that you're going to
Shame him
And Subway is that you would to somebody who have the same Market pressures
Your delusion
Never going to crack
He's only going to crack the threat
Who is masculinity threats to his ego
Or threats to his
Globalist Smith
Cuz he could just start yelling about a bunch of bulshit that probably isn't real
If it's like
It's like putting a psychopath on trial for
Like 30 murders
If you can't
Definitively
Prove
He's going to deny them
Yeah
You can put them in jail
He's just going to
To deny them because no matter what
She thinks
He's smarter than
Thinks he's better than you and that
You are less of a human being
So it's
Yeah
Yeah I'm trying to steam a psychopath is mind-boggling
Like you just don't
Understand that the Shameless
Necklace
Trump has never been ashamed of any
Nope
We're like find like Alex called to the deep and Trump
Within their souls
May precision-guided
Coming in on top of you
I don't like you getting away with what you do
You make me sick
The barbed wire
Doberman
Yeah
No and you can't hold it back
You can destroy leaders you can destroy me but you can't
The signal of Americana
Americana Renasant 2.0
Freedom prosperity
Apparel
Will County
Compassion
Friendship
Globalism
On your power trip
I'm going to need that explains
Together
I love Humanity
Because I'm so selfish
I believe it because I know it's me
And if you and us together
And you have no idea because you don't know God
This is where we'll take our first break in Atlanta
This gets back to his
My ancestors Army
Who cares about that part of it for right now
He does talk often about how like your offspring are just
I don't like
Erase memory and stuff like that
That's true I believe that he thinks that you live on
Through your answer
I think that that is
Okay this is
The new fund
I think that might be what he's getting it's hard to tell with Alex often when he's talking metaphorically or literally
But he's brought this up enough times that I think
When he talks about like
I'm being selfish
Selfless
Please continue I'm being selfish
Because I
And I don't think he means my
Gene's will carry on
I think he thinks
My great-grandson will be me
Or something along those lines
There's some sort of a reincarnation thing
Going on
Alex's believing in
Spell it out cuz that's not too weird
Espouse
Ostensibly Christian
Beliefs
Ostensibly not really
God damn it if we know what he actually believe
Some weird facts
So the other thing that clip it's really important
You talk about like
Notice the
The talk-radio is beat
The president has become
Me
And it's not
Fair
It's not real
It's not true
He's become Bannon
Yeah I think that is I think you're right that's a much better way of putting it was a late
Bigot
And he is in our investigation in 2015 we flash back to that time.
He never says Americana
He never says Renaissance
2.0
He never talks about any of the things
But he talks about now
He's a completely different person
In terms of the day like
The catchphrases the men
Does it work
But he throws out rid of those little speech meme
But he has
Completely different
It all changes with Trump
He did not
Everybody is not
Become him
He has become part of all that
Now unfortunately
Homogeneous to a certain extent all of it
Which is
White
Nationalism
These people have that in common
Their priority is great white
Christian man
That is what it like
That is the
Thread
Ties
Between the
The rebel media The Alex Jones the zerohedge
The
And that's another thing that and we were we were texting
I have the specifics
In front of me
They were they will never actively point out
This is a white
Nationalist
No
The white Nash
Those small groups
Right
The entirety
Yeah it is not
Small amount
It is not these Fringe groups
Yeah
Those guys are out
That's it that's the reality that my hypothetical interview with Alex Jones would also take on
Is that I would like
To elucidate to the audience
That he doesn't care about the
Conspiracy theories nearly as much as he cares about white identity
Really really cares about when he gets
To work
It's usually about those things
So to my estimation from my
Now
Six months of intense research on him
You poor bastard
Operating
Like Theory
Is
The conspiracy stuff is intention
It's a glittery seductive Ella Mae
Map to get people to pay
NSYNC
But he's someone who tells the truth about
Hot stuff
Then once you're in
All of these white narrative start
To come up all of this victimhood narrative
Everything about how like
Estrace
It all come
And that's the main funk
What you doing
Tricking people into buying a survival Goods
Fort illegal
And then now also
Lee radicalizing dudes
In2white National
And whether that was the case years ago I'm not sure
But it absolutely is now
The problem
Yeah
The Sandy Hook b*******
Symptoms
We should
Why are you
To Sandy Hook
Or why are you f****** ruining their lives
Like not to minimize that at all
But the larger issue
The thing that nobody
Is white
Primacy
Because
That is
Just to make it clear that I'm not
Just talkingshit
I pulled up
Statistics from quantcast
Of demographic breakdown
Of all of the sources that Alex Jones
Respect
He doesn't really site Breitbart article that much anymore
I don't know what happened between them but there is there some sort of
They're not
They're not on who
Is regular rotation
But Infowars probably stop Trump from
Or maybe
Alex's cross about it
Is 78% male
22% female
Credibly disproportionate today
Demography
Pics of the America
The America
If you want to look at
Abnormal breakdown should be very close to 5050
If you look at represent
Specifically Appeals
Further
Is 83% White
3% effort
Population
Give me something to the effect
13 /
Percent African-American
You expect something much
Closer to that if it wasn't
A massive operation
Not beyond that
The audience
Is
Something to the tune of
60% over the age of 40
So weird
Just got that before in the past
But that's an update
The numbers of changed
The tiny bit
Now you look at the sources that he trusts
Any flights
We have World News Daily
74% male
26%
86% Caucasian
4%
African American
Papa papa
65% over the age of 40
So slow
Zerohedge
88% male
12% female
83% Caucasian
2% African-American
Something around
55% over the age of 40
Drudge Report
Which is the most popular of all these sites that I've listed
89% male
11%
Jesus f******
Write 90% Caucasian
1% African-American
Wow
73% over the age of 40
Course
These places
Did Alex Jones
Credible
And I mean
Just because 60% is over the age of 45 that doesn't
40%
There's nobody
A massive
Demographic block
A plurality
For sure
Of the audience
Every
Place
But Alex Jones
Credible and not part of the fake news
The dinosaur media rat enemy media
All of those places are heavily
Older dudes
And that's not a coincidence
There's a reason that all of these places are networks together
Unfortunately quadcast doesn't Publix
64 Breitbart
Pretty much
So I mean like
You understand what I'm getting
This is
A self resonating Echo chamber of white narrative
Especially white male narrative
And they realize that they have no danger
In spelling out those
They're totally fine to be
Is flippant and dismissive
Charleston
As a shooting
Because who's going to
Already agreed 9% male audience
87% white audience
Is probably no one's going
The worst
The worst they could get out of that is
Somebody saying well I'm not going to
Rye or you might have someone who's like Alex is getting be a little much for me
I may Drift from the fold but they're not going to be drudgereport
Right
UCO Mark Dice video out there that Alex
Who's playing today
And now you're back in the psycho
It's
It's completely nuts
I don't know how else
To put it
It's one of the old-fashioned voice club we don't allow women golf
This depicts about Infowars
I saw that
Checks out
Yeah
Is really scared because
A very
Is that
Incredibly similar demographic
Patterns
I realize that a lot of people are probably the
Call self-reinforcing
Cuz they play the same stories
They play the same narratives
Well
Alex
Confirm not realizing what they're all in
Together it's all a mess
Propaganda
Campaign
Targeting White
Fragile
White male fragility
The same as I said
Yeah it's going on here
And the only difference is that Alex is dog-whistle about his calls for viola
He is really desperately
We're trying to get people to start
Because when he is
2 / 2
Things happen
Like the guy who showed up a comet ping pong with a gun
Pull-A-Part
Constantly harass this
Hook victim after Alex Jones
Stuff about Bohemian Grove there was a guy who tried to sneak in
With a bunch of guns
He was going to kill everybody
Bohemian Grove
If he's too overt there are people who follow
What he says
And those people
A real Danger
So you think if there is a
If there is a white nationalist suicide bomber
He will not say
Oh he's a hero
He's a martyr
What
Yeah
Yeah that's what I'll do
Drugs
What's that south of South American drug that you
Zombie
Girls like you
Of course which is the story every time
Again as we discussed
He still has never
Apologize for insisting that it was a Muslim who shot up that mosque
Yep he is not at all he said
I know that it was a Muslim
IEEE just doesn't
Whatever I say
He's a racist
And this show is about white
It sounds crazy
Two stomachs
And I understand
Because he doesn't say like
The n word
It doesn't say black people are stupid or anything like that
And he has Faith Harbor because of
It is testimony said
President-trump
Didn't tell me to stop
The investigation
But there were all these insinuation
I hope you'll stop
Play I'm not racist
I say that we're all humans with all Red Bluff
The trappings of it
The way
Deals with
A white death versus a minority.
The anger that he has towards trans people and anything that's an aberration
From what normal
No
We're that he's a bigot
Anyway
Alright
So alive it's unbelievable
Stand it
You fallen monsters
Cellular level
I'm not with you and your damned to Hell system
I'm good
Know what that way
Ascetic
Duh
Let It Go near me for 4 hours to edit it together
And India blue Shelbyville was really sad
No idea what that mean
Or how that would work
Or what you do I can ride into a trap
Victor winner
They think they're invincible
Trying to put me down the mud they have a victory over busy shoving me down in the mud everybody's over-running
Am I making it safe for everybody else to speak
Just like Tom stealing Hannah much bigger scale
So when he says that he is
Telling the truth
In some ways
He's making it okay for people to
Speak out about
I'm freaked out by Muslims
That's the third thing that
The anti-pc stuff that he's doing is an actual like political correct
I'm making bigotry okay again
That kind of
Agree with him
That's why we do this show
Trump campaign
It was just all out now
Because it's like
It's not necessarily bigotry to make fun of a handicapped reporter and s***
That's just cruel
Ableist
But I don't know if
Question now is a good time for us to do that one little gate that
Why they sell the hopes he's falling sell the hopes that he's a criminal
Enron
Good or bad
Island
The winning team of the mainstream media wants you to lose once you pour once you are there control
She wants to empower you
Be a winner join MSM
Lame
And complete test
And then make you believe that you're joining the winning team by going against rockets
If you look at things
We're destroying them in this way it's the next wave that will completely
So
Test is really bizarre
But we have to frame it to his audience
This life is just preparation for the
So this whole thing is just a game
Yeah he's using
Trump to be that
It might be slightly sacrilege
In undertow
But beyond that
I don't understand his
Conception where it's like
You're either with me or you're
With the mainstream media
There's a middle ground
There's a Nike and I can reject most of both not anymore
Wholeheartedly
The choices Dan
Training your ideas
How big
I support the existence of the media as opposed to the existence of Ally
I would tell you that
Counterproductive
To save it
That's it
Stupid but there's
At this point there's nothing maybe that need
Needs to be more protect
You can't have cameras
Recording the GOP answer
They won't show you the Builder
Because quote
We're not stupid
Exactly
Quotes
We might as well be the f******
Is
Keeping this
Pictures of really good reason the freedom of the
Press is in there
Is the
The First Amendment
But freedom of the
Is a
Big deal
Because in countries where they don't have
Like ones that have influenced our
National Security
Journalist murdered
For reporting the truth
Yep and that is
That is the point that's the danger and
Buckhead
Assistant
Sounds it sounds
Hyperbolic
It really does to a lot of people really
No America still has
Protections in place
We don't
Rule of law
God
People were saying
Even before the Alexa
Trinidad
Principles that we have are only as strong as
Is the people
Door
Play
So apparently
This whole idea of like
Norms
Maybe we should have written that s*** down
Yeah
What was the thing about the press to is that like
People don't believe that psychopath
People don't understand
Psychopath
What these guys are
They have no feelings I have no emotion
They don't give a fuk about you
They don't pretend to know
Like this this game of
Oh you know
A general belief
Humanity
In the fundamental decency
Of the people who want to
Hey you don't run for office
Power
Because you think
You know the people you know
The majority of us
Goodbye
Why were fascinated by serial
Killers
Because of this like
I can't
Believe
I can't believe that a person who looks
Like a human being
Is not
Watch documentaries on the world right now
Aruba
Healthy
Democracy Republic whatever
It can contain
A liar who's not funny
Like Alex Jones can exist within a free speech
Free Press
Paradigm
Very easily
And has for 20 years
Did for the nonsense
She's pouting
But we can't have
People who are legitimate reporters being demonized
The fist
Implode every
So we are watching
The other the other thing
Into this is the reality of it
Jones's game
Can't be screwed
Like it came
Really survive people actually paying a
Intuit
So he has to demonize the media as a self-preservation
Because if people start paying attention
If
We had funding
Legitimately do this everyday
Document what
Are you saying
Create this database that I'm working on
Of the narratives that he's pitched
Complete lies
Over the years
He just be like he'd be laughing
If the mainstream media really
Took their critical comb
Did they wash over
I think that mother forgot to wait for me
If they
If they scrutinize him the way they scrutinize real stories
He'll be screwed
And that's why he has to create like
It's all it's all it desperate
Self-preservation
Preempt
Damage control
Put on a large
NeverEnding
Scale
But you want but
Okay do you want
Oh no and I think you just learned the word Gorga
They think that will boost
I was
Obviously
Little bit
The Gorgons
Medusa's Palace
By going into the Gorgons pit
Survive
I survived going into that layer
What it's all about
Are in the dark when she first got here
Let's play some of that with audio for coming into the studio last week
Now he plays eclipse
From Jason and the Argonauts
Monitors on the wall
Teen
What's what what's a bold woman
Good cold as ice willing to sacrifice
Our luck
Surrozen
Studio
Everyone that's not sick
You don't like the whole person
Fruitealicious
Give us money
He said Gorgan 6 times
Itsfunneh
That was
That was a fun dumb little
Philly
If it's an indication that he doesn't have much
Like
Even in the middle of that
She's a key
Keem
Bow
Borman that was him going into his Arrow sheet
And finding nothing
Couldn't come up with archer
That's like
I mean it's Patty
He's trying to say that she's ugly
Elvis
I don't
I'm not down with that but at the same time that's just our
That's classic Alex
We can all have fun with that cuz the rest of this is
So if he wants to attack
Liberal I want weird-ass Jason and the Argonauts Alex
Yesterday
Also I wanted to cover like the most
Sedate Megyn Kelly stuff
I am.
Tuesday while recording this
Owen Shroyer was host
So this is the most up-to-date
Ever recorded
Owen Shroyer at work that's never going to happen
The whole thing it's tough
Ocho Rios going to make a brief appearance at the end of our episode today and it
Okay but this next clip
He gets
Really self conscious about
People thinking he's being
Using dirty words
Nope
You'll see
But then
Spirals out of
Control into
Talk about how Liberals are dumb
Did they claim
They're awesome they're not they're bunch of drooling
Mystery
Boobies
Poshmark
Is there a South China Sea multi thousand-year-old name for pirates
Booby trap
I don't like going to settings
Your soup truck when elections are liberal
Intellectuals
America year old
Go to Publix coupons
You can't talk to me
Running around foaming at the mouth
Video emerges of Chef
Questioning
It is
But
I love that you got that
Probably my biggest
3 year old
3 rolls
Knowing teaching anyone's XX
It's cool 3 year old sex act
I think that the only like
Might be taught in school by
Tears
You know what I mean like there might be like
Like your friend might tell you that or something like that
Teachers are not
Broaching that at all
From my experience
Been public schools
There is a sex ed
Health Plan
Mine was very
Anti-sex
Siri very much are
People is hell
I remember there was a girl in my class who was like laughing
It's something and the teacher f****** freaked out on her
He was like
If you keep laughing you're going to be taking notes
The rest of the class
But she was trying to
To keep things really on lock
I got to get through
Talking about
Is f****** middle schoolers I don't want to do this
No one's happy about this
Like I wasn't three
No one's teaching anybody anything
Is Doctor
Sikorsky has big
Breaking news about
Can we not do that guys
Guys
Let that one go here's why they really should have let it go I'm about to
To play you a video that they play
You know maybe you could decide if it's if it means
Okay
The election for Bernie Sanders
I think
I guess we've looked at as an ounce
With a vested interest in training
How do we get better access to
Heart catheterization
Develop better training guides
Can one of the election officials speak to any work you've done with either the parties or other groups on the phone that type of information
That's enough
That's not
You're supposed to be an expert that's
Nothing
That's an absolute zero you talkin about provisional ballots
Trying to better train the public
How to use provisional ballot which is a good thing to be asking about
Because it is
We're complicated issue
Quite frankly I don't know if I would know how to send in a provisional ballot
So I wouldn't mind some education
Could you explain why both get rejected
Is an amazingly good Quest
And that has nothing to do with
Some sort of a set up against Bernie Sanders
That's nothing to do with even questioning the Integrity of voting
So they're just lying
Let's just do
I want a flashback to a little bit earlier in the episode when Alex Jones was talking about I'm still alive it's crazy
My discernment is better than it's ever been
How is your discernment allowing you to report on this video is something nefarious
You understand
That's insane
Yeah that's bad discernment
So Jerome corsi is on and most of it is about
To listen to board
What's the rapper
He needs a more holistic
I don't
I don't not support that
Corky's on
How Alex is the victim of a propaganda campaign
And how Megyn Kelly is doing her job
Like I'm going to assassinate the character of Alex
Couple of big things happen
The first
Is the Jerome corsi finally says meme correctly
Then f*** it I'm back on inside baby meme I mean meme
Then about five minutes later it was a conversation with somebody like
You just being like hey
Not five minutes
Stop f******
Idiot
Oh that's great
I was I was referring to earlier than
Jump the shark
Yes and this clip Alex Jones invalidates
It's his career
What should Trump do
Well the presidency as normal Power
Start using it
Better start realizing in Washington
Don't wait till the end
Get rid of all the people
In the administration to I've been there from Clinton and from Obama get rid of them
So far okay
Also get rid of those people
And then bring in a bunch
Sycophant
Who will tell you that everything you're doing is right
Still not the most insane thing ever
I think it would be unwise and probably lead to a lot of trouble
But not the worst thing I've ever heard I do like Jerome corsi
Infowars studio and in d.c.
You can hear a motorcycle wrestling outside
Acoustics
But now we get to I want him to have a pic
Better be the best yeah yeah that was a weird little
Easter egg across like a director has the same little time could be his little Winky
So this is where
Call me
Clinton and the other
Counterattack
Absolutely
Horses
So they're Alex Jones
In one
Invalidates the
Entire premise
His career government
Take military action against
Hypno against its own enemy
Which conceivably would be some private
Cuz they're talking about people who are
Pushing this Russian
Propaganda
Directions to Fizz all fake
I think so they know it's not
Totally but here's the thing
Sing fire all these people
Is okay
It's wrong but it's okay
Him saying
We need to indict call me
Clinton Obama
Is an abuse of power
The President telling the f
Bi to do this
A
Gross
Nation of what the price
Relation
Because I have a sentence
Kind of in the
Wheelhouse
Brielle hold off
Cuz Alex Jones
Legitimately just said
A military coup
Cleaning out
Acting on
The people who are against
Trump with the military
She is made
Documentary film
Called the road to tyranny
Things will
Everything that he talks about is a
He's entirely
His entire premise
Is that like these globalist
Are going to have some sort of a coup
Counter counter counter
It's not okay
It's absolutely not okay
That is in later in the episode but
Since I didn't get to it
He absolutely didn't say that flipping
He meant it
Now you did
Demon
That the military needs to get involved
And
I don't know what the military would be doing first of all act
Acting within the country's borders
I think that's part of what he was really afraid of or not Jen 31
I'm literally Caesar yeah that's quite literally
What Cesar juicy power
Yeah
So if they everything is well with the military do
I guess you loves and kill them
Like
Abu ghraib man
There's opening
Guantanamo Bay is one of the most expensive things I've ever heard
Megan Kelly style interview
Your guy
Having a military coup
Why
That's what he called for
Yeah
That's not that he said military action
But
Singapore news people physically
What do you want
What up what else is there to say
What is there
Set
That's so
That's
Crossing a
Huge line
Yeah
Now thankfully that's not
Free market all of this
Like less government is all gone the moment you want a military coup
And you want a military coup to stop
An investigation
It has a lot of evidence behind
The idea that you would do that is only because you know that eventually something is going to
He asked you
2015 he knew he was mobbed up in 2015 he was the frontman for a Consortium on the East Coast
He knows all this stuff launders Russian money
Yeah he knows that
He can't pretend he doesn't know that
That knowledge that he had 2 years ago is still in his head
He's just pretending it's not there anymore
He's pretending he doesn't know these things
Talks about like
This Russian thing is fake
Dino's it's not
I'm the idea that in order to stop it
You would want
The president to order the military
To act
Physically upon his opponent
Is
That is treason
That is wishing trees
Yeah I'm not saying Alex's committing
Destruction of the American Republic entirely
In the name of protecting
Which is I mean that's what all scoundrels
That's what the cultural revolution was
All of these authoritarian Powers will always say
You don't need these rights
We're going to protect
Yeah we are the ones who can do all of this stuff
So you don't need
Because these other fake people are trying to take me out
The countries in this clip
In case you're a nerd
He put it another way
And the next one
The desensitizing
Republic
With this assassination play with.
Hey course he wants that big story
All of the
Get rid of the Obama and
Clinton
That was for the nerd
Kill the Jedi
If you're keeping track
Order 66
In the Starwars universe
Revenge is what destroys
The entire
It's the Clones
Hilton
Alex
You shouldn't do that
You know
You know those movies that you love so much totally about a horrible restrictive empire being too
Defeated by a lovable group of rebels
Really love the empire
That's the real message
We got the whip
Palpatine was just trying to do a good job and defeat the Universalist
Small business number two had to work on the desk
So many oh my God
Free market
To keep costs down
Pay those contract probably not
In this episode there's three instances and apologize I don't have audio of the third one
Symptoms of Alex legitimately
That drop needs to militarily act
Act on his enemies
If that's where the rhetoric is at that tells me a couple
First this interview is
The damaging
Damaging
Forgets keys in panic
Check mode
And second
If the rhetoric evolves from here
Serious trouble
Like
I don't know where else
Chicken Go
If the military
Where else does it go
If the military won't do it
Patriots have
That's where it goes
I think he can probably say that legally
For a bit but if he gets too descriptive or two like literal
Then he really answer is into inciting violence
Yeah but I think
You can still say if the government won't do it
Patriots
Should I think you can still say that legally
It's murky but I think I think it's free speech
A man that sure seems like
I'm against it but I think it
It's illegal
Yeah I know
So I really think that Alex Jones abandoned every single one of his principal
Span of like 3 minutes
The show's not over
2 years
Which was not over we got a couple Clips laugh
Cuz I what ends up happening a little bit later on the
Michelle is that robbed
And Owen Shroyer
Went up to the mark
Is over the weekend
F***
And the way they presented is that Muslims
I've teamed up
Always Auntie Sharia people are being attacked by the Coalition of Muslims and communist
Also
Probably some of the people who were
Protesting the alt-right publicity stunt
Probably worse than Muslims
Anarchist
Probably some communist
Diverse group of evil
Bigotry March
If you are if you think people are for Sharia law
Communism
You've lost
You're f****** poor people protest
Sing the anti-sharia March workpro Sharia law
They were just
Holes
I'm talking about Sharia law
Oh
If they're pulling that narrative
They think that
Sharia law is
Compatible
With,
Well that's the Communists are the idiots were going to bring in the necessary circumstances where Sri Lanka
Then the Communists will be beheaded
Do not exist
Sentrilock
Pictures from the marches and demonstrations and they were
Hilarious
Yeah there were just a bunch
Like armor
And like like nights are her not like
Not like for real night not like Teflon
Crusade
Straight
Holy Roman Empire garb
Just tons of people with guns it was f****** in
It seems like Civil War reenactors got bored with reenacting the Civil War
Back to the Crusades
A lot of them were like a modern-day dress just with tons
The guns
Like that
But yeah I think it is probably
We need a gritty reboot this is a Batman Begins
Civil War reenactment
Discuss their experience
I want
Also
Shroyer's been playing
A clip
During the commercial break
So whenever they go to commercial no not yet that's for tomorrow
Don't kill the Younglings
You'll be no better than
John podesta
You do not want Trump as your emperor
Palpatine
No
At least Emperor Palpatine
Teen was evil and
Negotiated his way from being one sip lured into running an Empire pretty impressive
He didn't even inherit a lot of money from his dad so real story
Americana
Whatever you're watching it on the website or on the livestream they don't play commercials that would be played on the radio
But the times
They play like 30 second
And reports from their their reporters
It has been talked about how
At these Shreya marches everybody are bigoted against
Bi-Rite
Water balloons
It's he's like
A balloon full of urine
Hit him
It says him
Way2go
Lauren Southern
Him well I did some looking into it
Okay
It turns out that as a Goose
Lauren Southern protesting the absurdity of transgender
Change their gender
She became a man
No one cared
She became a man legally
What I understand
People very supportive of that kind of backfired
Good for you
No one
The backlash
So I don't know is that
I don't know if that's what Owen Shroyer is like
Like referring to or if it's just a mist
Speaking
I looked at
That's hilarious
That f******
Hilarious
Studio
Right around
His shot down the appeal
Trump's travel ban
Travel
A second
Somalia
How did they get here
He has that the imams are going out passports that's not true at all
Some people are able to make fake passports but
Entire country
Official Somali passports have biometric indicators in them
Chili fake
As of 2012 Somalia has
Two airports have paved runways
Airport
What else might be talking about
Is that there's a Civil War in 1991
In Somalia and Airport closed
Air Flight Services
Experience route
Are there like
I don't know
Probably enough
Situation they're like
How many people are in Somalia
There are nine airports that have commercial service
And the other ones are all decimated populations
18.3 ml
Yeah so in Chicago we have
Two airports for three million
Airport
Commercial traffic first
60 million people
Spread out through a country
Airport
In Somalia
Depopulation
There's a large barrel
Sweaters that they about
There's a lot of rural areas throughout the country
Have no use for airport or other than bringing something which is the other
51 airports that have
Which if you think there are dirt Runway airports in America your f****** insane there tons of them
Runway Airport
St-charles
Out west
Like it
A population of
People at
And Alex's
I know that he thinks
It's going to go to the store
Recording everything
Going to be okay
Possibly
We're going to close this episode
Just racist as hell
Stupid
But also kind of endearing in a small way
Alright
Confused me in so many different directions
I don't want any
Explanation before just doesn't sound like
Okay Alex Shroyer
Is trying to do his job
Rob dude kind of adorable
You just have to put up with these two goddamn
Chicken dip
Is jabroni is over here
To won't let him use me
Eddie's trying trying to college bath
Can't
Cuz Alex Jones has got to get racist
Amateurism
Mike down for this one
All these countries
Are these nuts
7/2 seven-year-old Hillside passport
I think the proper response in italics
That's not Gallows humor that's racism
Saturn
That's a minute-and-a-half of just out-and-out
Pleasant
Wow
Yeah. That I have about that first
They have to pitch this narrative that adult Manor being
Classified as children
Because otherwise the official
Statistics about rap
Ugis don't match up with their narrative
They say that all of them are military age men
Of them are women and children
In order to get around that
There's adults with children
Be classified as children
That's the game that they're playing
I do not
See a large differ
Between what we just listen to
And let's say I don't know
70 years ago
Someone being like
You know what
Look not all black people are bad
You know like doing something like that
There's really not much difference
That is as offensive is that
Stupid
As childish
Reality
I pray to God willing
Too promising also
Pray that that sort of thing that we can see
See right now in the present day
That's f****** racist
I pray
Twenty years from now 5 years
You can look back on that sort of behavior
The same way that we look back on the boat
God we don't do that
F****** idiots
Died
Thank God Alex Jones
Didn't do that yesterday
I hope that interview goes well on Sunday
Not going to
Oh yeah
Although not disaster
To the level that we wouldn't
Disaster in the
Orchestrated
Spread the word about the show
It's it's more like
Telling a lot of people
Yeah
Absolutely
To somewhere to
To follow us at where would you go
That's where you would go
Lowe's on Twitter
The score fight
Acknowledge
Score for Augusta
I'm seeing it happened a bit I'd like to reinforce the behavior
You see people tweeting about Alex Jones
Just f******
Get in there getting their replies
At those assholes
And tell him
To get your perspective right
Yeah get in the knowledge fight
Don't play this reactionary
Play this reactionary ping pong game of outrage in the actual knowledge fight or we can
We can make Headway
Champs Alex we can
Not necessarily take him down
But week
Play a game he can't respond to
I don't want
I don't give a f*** about the cult leader
I want the
They're the ones who are going to be
And that's always the case
Yeah support Alex
Are only getting hurt
Buy the shirt that they believe it they're the ones who Trump is f****** over
These are the
People who are actively destroyed these are the people
Who are just like us
Struggling their asses off
And instead of engaging with reality
And doing their best
Kind of fight again
There
Regret
SeaWorld
Where they don't have to
Furious any of this response
Difference between those people and you and I are possibly too bad choices
Somewhere down the line or maybe even their choice
Pressure
Like
If you were real a shame if you were raised in the same environment they sin
Entirely possible
You would be an Infowars you might be a victim of the
Alex Jones
Absolutely
Real clean
Hate their wives
Cuz their wives
I have stopped enjoying that hard
Let's just robbed
Also if you want to appreciate it
There's a button over on the show
Become a policy wonk or if you'd like
Donate
What was it
Time travel episode
Slightly as I go through my 2015 investigation but we will pop them in as well as we can
Who's been I've been fun but you know what
This dislike
Alex
Sort of narrative that
This interview is a trap
And that he's going to come out
Dead
Yeah that is a doornail
But
But what is one guy
Is it
It's Batman
Redbox
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color with your trip and I love your work