Air Jordan
I have great respect for its knowledge B
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Acknowledge
A little bit about Alex Jones
I got that
It is expanded from that
I am off.
I don't think that be possible
Difficult but I've tried the number flavors
That I've been able to get my hands on demand
Not mad so good
It was really tough for me was that I had heard of I'd heard such
Startlingly different reviews
Worried
Category but I loved it and it also I didn't realize it but I
It just takes me back
A bit too
Like things that I had in Hawaii growing up
And it makes total sense
You think that it would
It's great I love it to another dessert
Another f******
Sweet thing for me to eat we need it at the audience was like what other sweet things
I'm going to become obsessed
What will capture dance sweep do today
Good news is people will be mailing those
No that is true thank God
Text again I think she just comes with dry ice
Dry ice and then just melted one
Emoji how about you
This week Dan is the sword
It's a Korean movie
I don't know it's really good it's about three swords when they do stuff
Swordsman plural know the movie is about
Singular
Like the Highlander there's more than one Highlander or I'll go there
No there's not more than one Highlander there's only one
I mean there are many people who live in the highlands
I thought there was
These and Mortals and they have to kill each other of course they do but the Highlanders specifically refers to that he
Highlander isn't the group of them
English movies from just appearance in conversational style alone
Sean Connery is indeed Egyptian in that movie
The original bar
What's today
Reverently things we googled just before getting on the show
So Jordan
Interesting thing to go over we have a talking about February 10th
I like to have marijuana
Go to events
I know it's still late cuz I'm halfway waiting for you to say it first I am disappointed in you
Because you have the open Lane Car Stutter Step
Anthony Davis
In the black man YouTube
I'm feeling, you just know you're not going to go for the layup cuz he's going to swat it away for me I decided to hang back and just see what you have
Is Wednesday and Thursday of this week and the reason I wanted to
Checking on this is because of course
Trump impeachment is going on
We'll discuss some feelings about that
Both of us have watched a bit of that
Yeah I blame you cuz I wasn't going
And then you text
Send me about it
I watch a little bit of
Oh my God surprisingly engrossing time I'm like this is stupid
Very conflicted about watching it I have
Feels important
It should read it feels like it's way more important than people
Everyone's like this is our second one we've been here before we all
You should have been done in the first one so
Let's get this over with cuz these people there f******
Talk about some of the specific
Shipped into the episode but yeah
It's weird
Took before we get to the business on that episode self let's take a moment to say thank you some folks who signed up reporting show
Text Connor Vig
I'm a policy wonk Caroline h
I'm a policy wonk
Thank You Caroline
Sweet Caroline
No papa
Sorry
That I'm seeing I guess not you're not bossy one
Text Becky
PCS
Your black jacket
And finally just mean it about juvenile policy
I'm a policy wonk
Do you organize those cuz I feel like our last episode was
99% fake joke
And this one just don't seem like normal people
Prepared a little bit today where as sometimes I will end up
Fairies
How much
Time I have
You're a busy man
Before the episode I need to be better at organizing
And stuff but
Yeah I know I read an article recently about how podcast
Don't really need to do much work in the money is really good
The job site
I assume that that's what you're up to
Yep Jordan also
Very special Delilah message
We got an email
Simpson lady
You got an email from Mike
Haha
He wanted us
To play I'm Holding Out for a Hero
Haha
Little bit of James Ingram
That sounds right
Human having a real tough time coming up with songs
Insect
But he he reached out and you wanted us to give a little bit of a happy birthday message
Whose birthday is actually yesterday with asthma coming out alright
You know something about a birthday week
I know I hope not
That's not fair that office in a long time remember birthday week
Remember that they were birthday we remember people who would just be like this is my birthday weekend
Thursday
But it'll be Tuesday and it be like
I choose to believe that we are not dealing with people who manufacture a personality based on their birthday
These people are great
Lauren happy birthday happy birthday you can have three days
Not a week
I'm sorry Mike that I couldn't
Improvise a better song
James Ingram's named Holding Out for a Hero
Nevermind
The only James Ingram song I can come up with right now at the top of my head is featuring Michael
McDonald's
Jordan
Impeachment
Yes what about it is upon us
Yeah
You know
So watching that watching this stuff
Blaze is Castro look
Solid with a beetle
Oh no Joaquin Castro better with a beard
But all I got is his twin have a beard
I don't know
We should call
I have a twins
Try out facial hair styles styles
No I think you are talking about a clone
Yeah I just think guys beard
Look good
I don't know
I feel like the image that's going to resonate with me is that video
The officer running down the hallway running past Mitt Romney Mitt Romney turning around
And running the other way paired
With all the video of
Protesters talking about hanging Mike penson
GPD imagining what could have happened
Had that guy
God Goodman not
I said good you know
What the other way
You know they just the idea that someone
Who's a very
High-level politicians
Very notable in politics who ran for president who is impeached Senate
They probably would have killed him
There was a little bit there was a little bit of me that was watching that part thinking like and then the next
Thing you should say is if it weren't for him
Mitt Romney would be dead guys
45 senators are going to vote to convict
Say you want Mitt Romney to die or shut the fuk up
That's one way to put it like that
I think that's pretty much the only way to go
It's it's it's a really surreal thing
To be seeing
This conversation that's happening
You're trying to persuade our like
You know that
They're chanting
Kill
The vice president who they elected
You understand that the Intel
Moments earlier
They were fine with the idea of
Supported my pants be subverted
The Constitution
You understand
Your name is very replaceable with that they are looking
See the problem there is
Is I think they thoroughly understand that witch
Why they will be voting to acquit
Yeah I don't I don't know the Dynamics
It it was
Pretty it's pretty
F***** up to
Did you see the information presented
That way
Is it
Coherent it makes sense
Spend
It's is almost
Hilariously over-the-top
Comprehensive
We're like I was watching yesterday
I meant today and they were talking about how
This is almost guaranteed this is guaranteed to be the shortest in p
Impeachment trial in history
And after watching those two days I was like
That does make sense
In a normal real-world situation because you'd watch that and go
Real good it's open-and-shut
Fairfax opening statement
What was that Caster is
Being like
Are they made some good points
I don't know why you're all August members of this body I just want to
Say you guys are all great
I love you now obviously the prosecution makes some good points
My client's guilty
But I want you all to know that your spec
Spectacular people I thought we were going to bicker about your addiction
I am not prepared
Boy it really does look like he's committed those crimes
And all the all these sort of defenses that you see throwing around or like well
Trump's rally couldn't have incited this because
Do people are planning for weeks
Tah-dah
Exactly
A e
About all the stuff in 4 weeks
Is it
Are any
Conclusion like I don't have any faith that there's going to be
Conviction and I also.
There's not going
And to be also like I just
I see this
That
Yeah yeah yeah
So I wanted to see Alex's response
To a lot of this
I figure if anybody is going to be
Mad
About this
Alex yeah
Key for the sense theme
Peach mint as impeachment has come around
Has been really really insist
Sent the trumpet
To get up there
I put the whole system on trial
That would be great
To get in there and insist that he won the election it was stolen from him
Alex is not happy that that is not happy
I'm so we'll get into a little bit of his response but first
Here's an out-of-context drop
Today Show
Ashley worship
Ashley know everything about everything about Joe Biden
What the hell do I have to always up my ass
Yeah man
That stuff really shouldn't be looking at Alex Jones either
But but we have to because he's up America's ass
Can't not look
Alex discusses the UN building
A little bit
Have the show here on February 10th
He's talking about how he made that to documentary endgame
Reviewing building on the front of it
And
He wasn't supposed
Beyond air
When this stuff was going on now you know all the stuff that message
And you can either believe that
Or you could believe that all that stuff you were saying about they have plans
Take me off the air when they're plans
Come to fruition
Was just nonsense
We're not supposed to be on there right now supposed to be shut down
A green Mist on the cover
You will notice that I specifically said
Bio-weapon stimulants
Practice a lot
And then
Launch
Successive wave
Posing as the saviors
What will be the United Nations it launches the attack
For Global enslavement and click images
Bookshelf
If the UN building
New York City
84 Rockefeller
Rockefellers
Strangely enough
My story
Of course
Sold it
We Are Family
That's right
New York
New York New York
Digressing sorry
I agree
And you can
Go and decide for yourself if that
The documentary is actually about what Alex
Think that I believe he's literally asking us to judge a book by its cover
The DVD
I love the idea that Alex's you know he's making this physical land or the UN building sits into a personal issue for
But there's a couple problems
The relative that Alex is talking
I'm about your is a guy named David Ayers
Who is he and his family were the ones who Colonel Travis
Left his son with
Exclaimed
To be related to came to Texas In 1832
I also Colonel Travis didn't like adopt his son to them like Alex likes to pretend
Hi son just stayed with The Heirs family to attend school while his dad drunkenly pretended to be a soldier at the Alamo
The sun only stayed with the family for 2-year
It's not like
Enough to build a bond I will I'm not going to get no problem I'm not going to I'm not going to
Arizona
I think that's fine but the way I was presented is like
Colonel Travis
Also David Harris himself actually wasn't from New York
He was from Morristown New Jersey where is born in 1793
According to the Texas State Historical Association David
Came to Texas to buy property and build a home
Prior to that he was a merchant in Ithaca New York
Ithaca is what 200
30 miles from New York City's I had some doubts about this whole story
Of him owning the land of the UN building is on
Keep his fight with his imaginary enemies personal
Live family's land that they you at brother
Think about that
If that's what you want to do
Okay I have a claim to that land back from the 1820s
Then you also have to acknowledge
That maybe somebody else had a claim to that land in the 1500
Nope
Why not
Alex's property rights
Began in 1820
There's this
Sing it in life
Square
Stuff happens gradually
Alex tries to discuss how
Taking covid
Seriously
I will lead to negative consequences
Is much like
Taking the clan seriously
Leads us to
Trump off Twitter
This is one of these a here this way
So the first Domino was the
KK and watch the premise most probably lost her in the ATL
Pablo
Alex Jones
Gougeres leiteritz the president of the United States
No I think these are all lumped in with enough since 1415 house for 15 days
Sounds reasonable
Have you seen outside your house.
10 years in prison
Outside your house when I tell you
The problem with the argument that he's making is that like
If there is
Behavioral similarities between the
The clan
Alex Jones
The president I don't understand breaking the terms of service of ascertain
Platform shantham getting kicked off
Isn't it's not like some kind of a dominoes falling situation it's
It's more of just a
Consistency of the rule only Nazis would expect just
This to be applied fairly dad doesn't make much sense
How many terms of the evolving
Situation with covid
Didn't do any
Any of those things
People some people didn't
Two large enough extent
That those were not effective as effective as they could be
Provide
Material support to people
To enable them
To do
These safety
It measures
In a way that would have been meaningful
We end up with we end up with a situation that gets worse and worse and half
The medication you would prescribe for that
Become
Larger so it's not the dominoes falling it's just
Does not taking care of a problem
Not just that but mitigation efforts that were already planned for an In-Place that Jared Kushner according to witness
It says denied
Specifically because it would only hurt Democrats more
Making it more of a genocide situation less am just awesome that out there
So but if you're outside your house are going to go to prison for 10 years
Okay
In the UK
This is nonsense actual story is about how the UK government has rolled out new rules
Swear if you're returning to the country after visiting a country that's on the red list of high-risk
Countries
You're required to quarantine at a government designated hotel for 10 days
Would cost approximately 1750 lb
David discussion of a 10-year setting
People who knowingly lie about where they're returning to the UK from
In order to skip and skirt
Public Health measures
Andy require quarantine
Everyone can still go outside their houses out
Just trying to scare people
And I am positive
That you know that is a high figure
For a lot of people
But also
I would assume
Dead people who
Are coming
From these countries are people who are coming in
Provocation
Do those countries
Possibly
People who would be able to afford the quarantine
And I would also assume that
If not that there's probably
At least some sort of a program in place to help people who don't have the memes
Step forward this to think of Public Safety
It's not that I don't know
Anyway download bulshit
Alex is lying
Oh yeah so
We know that Alex is a violent
Jap
From all of his words and deeds
Yeah those would be how we identify as regular
His existence
Encouraging people to be violent his behaviors in all of the stories he tells about a casa
Sing people is oh he's
Superhero
He's not
We're right now
Buy Wii
I mean Alex and his audio
Yes
We
Are in a rip
Tide
Interview fight
When you're the riptide you're going to drop
So you can't fight
I don't know anything about Riptide
No Riptides were part of my girl.
Quiet
Yeah there is there's a certain amount of truth to it like if you get taken in an undertow
Or something you will generally end up like
Just kidding
It's not cuz you're just going to stay under and drown
It can't be it can't be very bad.
Been through similar things
In my younger years
This metaphor doesn't quite
Quite work the way Alex wanted to
Because when he's sort of saying is like we're going to take some bulbs
In this Riptides and then will be spit out
From the riptide and Beyond safety it'll be scary
But you can't fight
Cuz if you fight that's when you're going to drown
But then at the end he also says that people are coming to kill your family
One of those things
I knew what to do when it's stuck
Hit me up
Well
Let me just tell you
Already
This is not negative
He's going to get so bad within a few years he's going to be totally Blown Away
Mass suicide deaths
And then
All the college games
Jobs going to have government paycheck
Uniform
Coming to your house
Call Minister coming
So we shouldn't do any
Okay
Or should I be worried about the armed, he's coming to kill my family would seem important to you
But they're not coming to kill Alex's family so we need to just
Sit tight and we'll get through this
T-Rex can't see you in the movie is going to sit still and relax
Spaghett see you
I just can't
What do you also have to have blue ribbons
Why does it always go to be every time there's a new email
I was there I did all of the stuff the best of everything at 3 today
Close enough to like
I could believe that I don't have any problem with that I just have a problem with this is yet another in the long list
Things Veritas is up
I want that title for most specialist.
My buddy
Yeah so that that's an incoherent message that he sending his audience there because
At the end of it I
Feel like you'd negated a lot of the ideas that you'd want to be
What do you tell people you're in a Riptide relax
We're going to get out the other side of this
And I feel like you
He's telling you to fight that ripped
No no no see cuz he
He said Relax
First yeah it's it's
These Clauses are dependent on each other so first
Get the riptide and then die
What do you know about Pablo Escobar
Not
Good you're not watching narcos
I did not watch
My calendar.
I think he was at at elephants I know that was in the movie Blow
I just figured as a character in the movie Blow
All-time great mustache
Pee-wee Herman with Elsa
All-time great Moustache by the way
I learned
This is not only did he have elephants he also had hippos
Yes Alex
Cuz I'm very long
Ramble about the dangers of Hippo he was voted best hippo in high school
So Pablo Escobar had these hippos
And they got breno now they've bred and now hippos
I heard somewhere where they should
Weather now
Speed sensor now people want to call them
This leaves Alex to saying that there may be some good arguments
Perfume I'm calling
And I'd like to remind you he is a noted eugenics
Dislike her this guy allergy
Theoretically
Pablo Escobar in South America. What was it for hippos
Something like 40 years ago
Thousands hippos run around
Grizzly bear
20 ft crocodile
Throwing around
Pablo live
Now they want to call
Hippopotamuses
Don't come from there
I don't need to be called
You noticed you're telling people this and they don't care
That's because they're not conscious they're just eating food
Bad and they're breeding lead to get rid of
Donation
Stop playing God is evil
That's the problem
God
Real document
Artificial intelligence Singularity Godlike
Dissension
I just find it really interesting whenever Alex has these like hypothetical
Go conversations of globalist
The dog listen listen I'm not saying it's a bad idea it's very weird
Practice it can go wrong
Yeah I would say that if you're branding is the such
But at that Alec
Puts forth
Should never
Say that there's a
There's an argument to be made
Dumb people that's not a race
It's never been used in a way that's not racist
There's a track record of some people may be using this for their own race
Hey Alex
You know how you see some people is dumb
Is Ezekiel
That's it's playing God because
Is God had already done the Noah thing
I don't know baby
So is it so he's almost a little mad at God
I was like what are you doing you should have just gotten rid of the dumb one bright we could have had plenty of fun
Yeah, let the Dum Dums on the boat then you put all those goddamn hippos on the boat they're everywhere
Classic
Mustang
So Alex is not afraid
He's a strong strong boy
Was only slightly afraid of Riptides
Who's afraid of
His former employees probably
How I'm doing
Have no fear
I know I'm way past everything I'm not worried
I love my family but I just had turned over to God
Rodger said hey it's okay
I'm not mad at God I appreciate it
Future anyways
Can you watch
That first lawyer that got up
Gravel
Pulled over and pissed all over itself
You're so powerful Schumer I love you sir you're so much better than us great job with your presentation on trunk
Because there's not men in this country
What about you
You talked about the dimensions in chess
Quite a bit
F****** pretend yeah that transition was as jarring as it seemed in the foot
Yeah it felt a little weird
Happy's lawyers being soft
Right right
Universally agreed that cancer did a real s*** job
Great lawyers
This is a little bit like
Touch N Go
On the
Material yells about the lawyer being weak a little bit
Doesn't spend too much time
Talking about it yeah I kind of halfway assume that today we will be talking about a secret migrant Caravan and they wouldn't
Even though the appeal
Dancing around a little bit shoes to the impeachment like
The fact the Democrats all have Chinese spy handlers
In their office that sounds right no not only that
They all have
Handlers
Nobody knows
The name
Of the Chinese
Spy agency is called
Chinese spice
Intelligent no secret the name of Chinese intelligence
He's not even know
What is it
And you all know its name
What is everything in Plainview
Like what
Is the red white and blue
China is the Red Dragon
A what
What's the name of the
Diablo
The devil
Don't talk about some positive news
We're just doing word association game
But the real kicker is he over B the devil
Especially the the ministry of State security
The dollop
Diablo couldn't come up with old scratch their I think he's probably pretty pissed in the moment
Come on man scratches way better
Anyway
Alex is thinking about the devil
And so
This clip is actually just titled
This show is stupid
You got the whole blueprint folks
Global enslavement at the blueprint for Global extermination
Malaysian Daniel
You decide
But you don't want to be part of its decision
You cut yourself off from Satan
You got to let me in
What you got
Steal your will to steal
Irritability
God
And your free will
Touch that Satan's all about
Animatrix
So he can fool your soul the only way you can win because he's not a god
He's a fraud
Wake Tammy wins liar
KT impact filter yellow that the devil is a devil
I can actually come with a more upwards
Inflection that passion
Seems so fake
Tumi
Just so boring
Cookie
Declutter
1 things are exciting maybe another bright spot is a cat has jumped into my lap and is insisting on being very
Affectionate right now
A few
Little guest appearance there on the bike
I guess she probably going to swing in probably heard some devil talk
So actually she was trying to delay the inevitable and that is that I need to tell you about a couple gas
We have on the show
They just got kicked off Twitter
Jim
Jim's brother hop
I can't remember
Brothers Pizza
Maybe something like that
Yeah they're the brothers
Coffee Brothers Hawk
The Gateway pundit
The dude that got kicked off Twitter
And so they come on to complain
About that
And I don't
We don't want to listen
No not really but no
Jim hoft his main point seems to be that
This isn't the cult of personality about
Okay you know we're not going to have another candidate like that
For a while
Wake up
And I think it's also imperative
Populist candidates in the next
Primary
Are we have to get rid of some of this deadweight
Looking party if you don't want to sound crazy
I would recommend you not say
Whether or not a candidate in a future election is
Pro the president who is no longer in office
I would say he's a real designation of a crazy person
Personality Dan I just want everyone to agree that a single person is the greatest Hume
Human being that ever lived and we should do whatever he says
Yeah
If you were running a Democratic candidate
And they were like this is the pro-obama candidate
And I would look at that
Also as weird
If you're very weird
Variable
So Alex is going to be talking about how like a note
They've stolen the election
And then we know that
What makes us
Not vote
And that makes it
Easier for them to steal
Is it goes out to break with something
Really upsetting
Blue States the most City people get
It makes it easier for them to cover up
I was talked about
Basalt
We'll get to that in a second
Is it
Cartridge box
So you heard that the end
You can't hide
Assault
Alex's commercial here
Is a little while
I'm now back to listening
Started off great I'm listening to this episode on the DC entry
This is a commercial that would have been played out on the radio
And I will tell you it is a very
Different tone
Then the commercials reads that we've heard Alex gear
Oh no reason episodes
The little bit it's a little bit more f***** up it also sounds like he's jacking it
Okay
Good listener discretion advised he sounds we maybe to Banning by proxy
A grand assault America is about to have a Synergy cut off its borders
Is dollar
Are you on the right team that you are
All of you who are awake at and love
Oblivion fear the enemy is about to expose itself
Enemy comes to kill steal and destroy
We should but once it comes through
Dominating us and raping us attacking us
America
This is the truth of this just the infowar
Wow
Quite a bumper
Hey Alex it sounds like your voice is a little bit scratchy l a t that usually have
Promos today entire pack of cigarettes
I'm a 3/4 drunk
Objecting off
Papa Haydn
From my wife recorded under a blanket
Cell phone flashlight
It's supposed to be like a billion-dollar operation
I think I think one of the things that's going on is I think he's probably f***** up
But it is also like trying to really do that movie
Yeah
Because I
I think this is tailored more towards
A possibly random person
They could be listening on the radio
Peak their interest
What is this
This is exciting
Like he missed the mark though I need to know more
You compare that to the meanderings random
B******* it's on me like actual forward speed
Rubinos attacks targeting his audio
Yeah it's
It's pretty clear I just think that the
It's really funny
This is what he thinks goes to that like wife messed
Yeah yeah
It's remarkable it is it is you know I like to imagine that you know I'm not if I fail
Held in a different Arena I would be aware of it
I wouldn't just be like
Yeah I killed it I can do literally anyting
Wow hits
Done who gives it
Yeah right
So this is a good strategy for Alex a try and get new listeners in
Just do these
Creepy jack off commercials about the end of America
Alex this sounds
I only do what
You're not paying me for two
Good strategy
Another good strategy might be Paul
Paul Joseph Watson
My oldest friend
Promote my s*** maybe I'm not mad
About it
Please remember
Everything the enemy.
Infowars.com newswars.com
Call zaida summat.
Not mad about it
What is in it for Paul to promoted 40 reason
It's really in his best interest to play Down sorry connector
Nothing else that he can get out of it
Other than like
Not making Alex
Mad that's the only thing that he has to worry about he's gotten
As much publicity as
Could come out of Infowars
That's why the band on the Titanic
Cat playing is cuz they didn't want the captain
To be angry well I guess this is where we die I don't want to piss that guy off
Yeah
It only hurts Paul to remind people that he worked at Infowars for 20 years
If I were him I would do the exact same thing
So Alex is mad about Trump's lawyer being
For the most part I mean incompetent
Two more mad that he
He's polite
About his presentation
Therein
The chamber's obsequious
Sure
Decorum that comes along with extreme directional speak
Edit all set with literally just storm
Do you refer to people as the the gentleman or the lady from New Hampshire whatever the f***
Alex is mad about the
Swell
Stitches show you with enemies
A white male.
So you look at just this this this foppish
Meaning
Just classic BS artist lawyer in there ingratiate himself
Groveling Chucky shimmering all Shimmer takes out his weakness
Congratulate
You later if you do it
He's just mad out of analysis
At all
Big thing that he's mad about in terms of the conversation that happened
Throughout the beach
And stuff is that
Did defense
Is not arguing
Did Trump win the election
They're taking as granted that Biden won
And Alex is pretty mad about that
Because
That's the only thing you could really get people like
Distracted
That's
Stupid arguments
That you can't but the reason they're not doing that is cuz that doesn't belong in court that belongs on
Infowars
Media Outlet
He's a little bit upset that that worldism
I'm being like taken over by his
Right his s*** right
I mean it is
Maybe
Maybe it's their best
Honestly after after looking at the the opening arguments
Maybe their best defense would be like
We're putting this
Whole thing on trial
Actually
Trump is president
Find that everybody did this in your doll the one who should be impeached
If you want a gum up the works
Can possibly create new problems for yourself
I think casters already gone far enough he might as well
Jump off the edge
Edmund is a
If you want to be interesting yeah probably that's the way to go
It would be a disgrace
It wouldn't work
Probably not
Has gotten a little bit used to the last
In 04 years
5 years is like politics
Descending
To his level
Concrete instance of
Not
And that probably be pretty frustrating
And then at the same time you have a funeral Biden
Comment so if you know Alexa
The Senate has an important role to play in
To do their job
Stay above the
The Fray and trying to
Keep himself
Yeah it removed from the processor
And that's got to really piss off
I would imagine
Sup
So you got the only thing that he knows how to do and that is
Talk to Akinator
He has a comedian
Let's see if you know who this guy is
I have heard
I've heard the name
It's funny cuz I'm banned. Video
The segment that he's on
I believe we're first team is atopica Media
That's not good
Usually means they're not
Apparently Jose
Co-host
With Anthony cumia
Anthony cumias new show
I'm shocked that I didn't get a call the co-host on that one too for that
Are you comparing me to Anthony cumia
Cuz you better not forget
I don't think that is
Dave Landau is on
And tries to make a few jokes
Alex is not a good scene partner As We Know
I only have one clip here cuz I don't care about what Dave Landau has
What to say about cancel culture I do particularly care about his perspective on
Impeachment cuz
It's not that interesting
You f****** co-host
Show with Anthony cumia
I got to go
I have very little interest in what anyway comedian has to say about
Cancel culture Strike 10 show that you're on Infowars
Strike three
You said this on Infowars
It's not even so much taking that big of a stand it's just telling people not to be completely blind
The only
Thing that most people are really saying is that this is going to end in some kind of bloody Civil War
And whether it's starting to look I can see that
I can see their point
Just think if people just
Down and stop
Turning on mainstream media
Which I just can't imagine what it's like to sit in your house
Sheritha television
Fear I'm sending you
Yeah totally unlike the show you're on
Terrifying
Kind of monster would
Force people to watch
Search for straight hours of fear-mongering
I feel like you really
I look like a like a real ding-dong
When you say something like that on Infowars because that either means that you accepted a booking on a
Platform asthma
And notorious as Infowars about having
Do diligence
About the place you're on
Or somehow you don't see what Alex does as
Rank fear-mongering
It's really simple what he's doing he's just asking people not to be blind
And that's all he's doing mainstream media that's pumping
Fear into your blood all the time by reporting
News
I would think that anybody who works or any kind of mainstream media Outlet if they behaved in any kind of way
Close to like with Alex.
They might be in jail
Would be sued
Over and over and over they be fired
It's just it
Before they would be Brett's
That's also a possibility
That leads me to believe that maybe this Dave Lent
Guy is not incredibly sincere maybe a little bit disingenuous with his
So
The temperature was
Do Brothers Hospital
Yep
Weird comedian yep
Surface-level fairly certain that one of the big deals of
Stuff is happening right
On the 10th
You mean impeached
Yeah
He have a lot of that stuff
Hearings on the 10th we're happening after Alex
It was on it
Metro that's true
Some of the stuff he had he didn't have any way of knowing
Got until the next day the 11
Anthony's on air
That is still the little service
Live Oak
These nut
It's October
Nearly as much
I mean because
From Alex's for sale
Perspective that makes sense
The election was stolen according to
This is all b******* it's all imaginary
Engage with the substance of the thing if the thing
That kind of seems to be where he's at spleen to me how
Alex seems to have a more cogent position on what he imagines is imaginary and how much we should talk about it then
The rest of us
I won't
So are you starts off on the 11th talking about Bill Gates
Cuz of course
This is the most important news of the
1 *
It is official
TED Talks
Call for on.cnn 3 clips of it the last few years
Falling
The euthanasia of old people because we quote can't pay for the Aging population
In Europe the United States Australia
You can hire 10 teachers and that's not
And you fish for a life.
The moral thing to do
Everyday
Nursing home
Where is the employees notice all of the death
Say something
Mostly places know to keep it quiet send it out of something else but
The cdc's on website
Some of them died within 15
Minutes
Carlos is claiming that someone died 15 minutes after getting covid-19 vaccine and then be presented that as evidence of the to work
Causally connected
That's the level of work he does
He just dissociates two things and insist
That you had been proven that they're connected when he's done no such thing
Alex good legit show me a news story about someone dying as they're getting vaccinated and it still doesn't prove the claim
The vaccines related to that person's
There's an unfortunate reality here
That is that Alex either doesn't understand that Dynamic of reality
Or he understand all too well how easy it is to trick people into thinking
The correlation proves causation
I think the latter is probably more likely
I also killing all people who could hire teachers
It's easy to misconstrue his words that way but the conversation he was having it out so it takes out of content or context is about
Exorbitant
Medical cost
And that what can be done about that
Literally most of the world is
Dealing with right now as population
Explodes like it's not unique to anywhere it's like
Oh s***
What are we going to do
Does f****** baby boomers wrecked
It's
It's easy to look at that conversation to Bill Gates
Public forums
As being like well
Mathematically if we just
Kill all the old people we can
Tyrell
It's not it's not the conversation
That would be officious argument that I would make it a
Debate where somebody's like
Oh well old people are trying to be like
Kill all of the old people that you could sarcastically make that argument against
Alex and win
Totally he is he's got a lot of nothing
Actually that's a really good idea
Alex is now more mad
Are Trump's lawyers
This isn't 10
Don't fuc
I can set them up
Lawyers that
Trump hired bad
I'm only for shooting Or democrats
Sabotaging him publicly
By the way
When that lawyer was saying
Get the s*** thrown out
How do you say another president
It seems like a process has worked problems like corrupt
Dictator historically you have an election
McKay's
Is
Maybe
A decent argument to try
If we didn't have any precedent for it if this was the first time if this was like
We were having one of these
And people were having that are going to be like
I don't know
Who ever tried this before
Baby gunshot this is about the
Does January
This is about the storm and
A capital is about that from time to time
Because I'm
Nefarious s*** heads
BMX stuff up and
Whatever
That was not
That happening
Because
Provocateurs
Did it to make
Alex look bad because people who are in the same communities outdoor Pier to be
Are being violent
Right now at the same time
Violence is cool too
We are well past the point of being able to use violence against these institutions organization
A few hundred to go in the capitol
Insurrectionist Terrace
Okay
Coherent messaging
No I think that one is actually really coherent
We should absolutely storm the capital this was bad planet
They tricked us
Into not storming the capital
On the 20th when we would have all been able to actually kill everybody Maybe
I think he's essentially saying that it
It wasn't the right time to fire the shot heard round the world
Yeah yeah I guess so but the reason it's incoherent is cuz I don't think he wants to take
Responsibility for that
Cut
Dry message
That's why I think
Is the what's behind
Violence is obviously Justified but this was this was a misstep
Yeah I know that's why I blame it on agitators him provocateurs tricked us into shooting before we were ready
So in that case
I'm pretty sure he
He said that will ya previously we wanted
Play the kill everybody and overthrow the country
We just wanted to do it at the right time so we would win
Spell course I mean Alex even gets into his blood loss
Halfway decent mood today
Physically
Nauseous
Because my
Nervous system was telling me
You need
To go
Visit violence upon the people that are doing this
And kill babies are newborn and they admit they're doing it
You are an accomplished my very cells are
They're mad at me because
Offensive
I understand your gut
And your blood and your soul
When your mind is burning
With the desire to kill
Pull up
Stop these people just as much as you do
We've got to be wise as serpents and peaceful of doves
I don't think you pulled it off
I'm going to end with two cliches because I realized that I just basically told everybody that it's fine to kill
And that I want to to
So you got to walk softly and carry a big
I feel like Alex might not be lying about reading Infowars,
That's cuz that sounds like in responding to a lot of feedback of people who are like
Alex your soft let's just go Kellen let's just go Kelly
I think that our
That's Alex trying to like have an olive branch to the
After murderous audience
And also do you know who else anthropomorphize has their murderous intentions
Serial killers
Lucky wants to kill
And you understand that the audience wants
Skill and they're connected on this
Feel like there's a problem
There you got to be
Why is it a serpent
Vista problems
It doesn't get better
The last
Twitter
Dorsey
You know what you're doing and you were just as guilty as Bill Gates
Mark Zuckerberg
He's the next.
Eonline
You guys are mass-murdering killers and I Know Who You Are by knows who you are and you will
What you've done murderers
I don't care what you do to me
You are you you are guilty
Military
The diversionary tactic to wipe them out for the Chinese
Have the Civil War
Civil War we want a removal of the globalist
Collaborators
The number of people that we want to do that remove these people that I
Read it out for you from murder and I am specifically
Violence and everything is okay because they're murderers and we're well past
What's the point of being able to write Teresa
But would be good planning
He's clearly implying what would be
Be good
What are you guys doing stormy the capital with only a few hundred people you can't win what you should be doing
Targeted assassinations
It's unfortunate because one of the people that's on Alex's list
Alex Cox
Italy calls him Jeff Zuckerberg
Zuckerberg
He's because I like
Can't remember dude now man he wields too much power it is too dumb to handle it
Responsible and I think you could make a pretty good argument that
You know using Shifty language Alex's
Is probably telling his audience that
Should maybe kill my
I think one of the things about the evidence in the Imp
Sprint trial that I've noticed was
How many times did they did a really good job of avoiding allowing that
Kind of
Claws
To like
Excuse any Behavior
So often they had
They played Trump's words
And you're you're literally like
Yeah
We all know he said
Peacefully protest peacefully and then they're like
Yeah but we've got 300 examples of him saying otherwise
So you can't pull that b******* this is a pattern behavior
Alex Jones is essentially on trial in the same way
Where are we are showing in some ways is a
Rigorous
Completely without legal backing
Specific
Crime yet
Right
It's just the behavior that would lead to that
God people
I have not carried out
His
Cleared man yeah
He's mad about this trial because these
These these lawyers
Arthro
Another at?
I don't know or are they just shitted everybody knows he's lawyers
Lawyers
They are sabotaging
You got a great job and you prove
Because it's a bunch of cowards
What was their making their move
All these so-called men are bunch of pinstripe wearing knuckle-dragging
Dirty stupid
Through this country over a vagina
Lawyers
Bio weapons
Globalist
They hate themselves and their going down Hollywood
Run by the same slave master Satan
Cool
How's it going to
Explain it when Trump
Gets acquitted
It really is going to be difficult to explain for a lot of people Beyond saying
These guys were just going to quit no matter what if Trump gets acquitted then why
How are you going to rationalize
His lawyers are in on it they're throwing it they wouldn't have it a trial if it wasn't rigged
That's rigged
Acquit
F*** are you talking about
Makes no sense in your rambling
You can tell the real dead giveaway
But he's probably just
F****** coked out of his mind and rambling about nothing
If you get to the Satan at the end
I'll tell you what
That's a real
4 in the morning Hardy I want to leave in the puppet
Anyway
Alex gets to talk about these vaccines
Thousands dead already from covid-19 vaccine feel like I would have heard it if there were
That's smart
Second is the
If Alex believes that then he has to believe that there's
About as many deaths from the vaccine is there is from covid
That's outrageous
Guesstimate
1 out of 10 conservatively
Smurf reactions gets reported
Moana.
Probably really
How many times do you take a reaction
Can you call the CDC
Thousands of dead people so far
HomeAdvisor mRNA vaccine
Europe us
I think viseart
Suing
I think so too yeah
Also either making up numbers or the beginning that are you don't call the CDC your doctor
CDC to report adverse
Yeah that's why you go to the doctor
Adverse reaction to something you will go see treatment
And then they will
Job really inefficient system
Divorce everyone to be like
Bring bring hello CDC
What frustrates me a lot about Alex's narratives regarding this type of stuff is that
Yeah man people have already thought of those
Problems
They happened
A long time ago and people were like oh let's not
Do that
Like the reason we have the reporting system
Is precisely because
You wouldn't call the CDC
Yeah you wouldn't do that
You're the doctor does it for you
Ubering to get to Alex maybe having a kernel of Truth although he still making
Stuff up
Is that like if you have a headache
That could be considered an adverse reaction and you might not report that
Be something so trivial that you don't seek help with it and you might not even know if it's related right so yeah
Maybe one in ten if you count like
Minor nonsense that maybe you maybe my back
Back hurts
Slight dizziness is often a
Britney saying is just a load of
I honestly think that some of the
All the stuff that he saying
Has a real potential
For Public Health
Problem
Holy
Micro
When you come across a covid virus the most common in the world Coronavirus
In the future
Most people will have a violent autoimmune reaction
And they're going to call
Everybody dying
Oh by the way
Both these old people that died they said an already tested positive for covid
Elsa said
Virus or Coronavirus
Or later it'll cause autoimmune response when you come in contact with
Never going to get away with this never there crazy
Kill everybody yeah that's
That's deeply deeply irresponsible
Yeah this is
This is
F***
Yeah like this is
The level of thinking that this is is
Which level like this is like a pure
We've never advance
It's beyond thinking that the
The person with
Two cats is actually behind illness
Yep that's where we're at
Vaccine for a brand new virus in less than a year
People are like nananana see if you're physically unattractive
Chances are you're the one killing everybody
Yeah I know I read I read a little bit about some of the folks who have died
After getting the vaccine
And some of them did test positive for covid
And with the belief that their peoples were writing about this had
Where they at
They had gotten the vaccine
When they'd already been infected in the incubation.
Vaccine wouldn't be effective right
At that point it's too late
Yeah
You're talking about high-risk communities
And
People who are prioritize
We're getting the vaccine
You know that doesn't
Number either
Like it's it's not in the thousands like Alex
Nothing but
But either way like this this kind of misinformation
Persuade people
To have
Either a belief or an inclination
To not disbelieve
This shot is a Datsun
And I can be really really Danger
Yeah it's hard even to imagine like
Okay it's not the best
Vaccine
And it does have some by adverse reaction
But
It's going to save
A Million Lives
You know like like that kind of level of thing
Where it's like yeah that's
Worth
Half a million people are dead
Strawman s*** all the time of life
Everybody pretends the vaccines are towed
Totally safe
There's never been a bad wreck
No no one says that
That's a fake argument that you're making an order to
22 strawman
Yep
Oh yeah yeah
It's just
It's childish and I wish these people
Would treat him
And he's arguing
With the
Distain but they deserve
Two talking about
Bitcoin
Of course
Yes of course
Because Elon Musk
It was just on Rogan apparently again
And maybe he is into Bitcoin now
He also has a guy named B boy on as a gaslighter
How about motherfuking bad boy
The Weeknd
You want to laugh
But you can't
That was that look over I can't laugh at this
What's wrong
Dan I'm well past
The point of righteous viola
That was going through my head
How do I just got his just a YouTuber whose into Bitcoin into currencies is interview
Not interesting
I'm surprised YouTubers are always fast
He actually has some interesting things
Get any sense of like
And I'm being a big at but I don't know
He just was talking about
Cryptocurrencies
Anyway
Alex is against
But then he interviews this guy
And it
Pretty positive
He's very good
Is a global government openly
Dollars
Obviously a giant inside job from the beginning just like
I told you that
10 years ago
So why are you having a long interview with a guy who's
Into Bitcoin who's giving really positive
It's very confusing
Also Alex
Hasn't been super negative
About Bitcoin
And it's much more
Complicated than
Been a promoter of it
But if he actually thought it was something that was meant to replace the dollar as part of the globalist
Plantain
Mad Max
Kaiser on
For the last 10 years on his show to
Constantly promoted
It cryptocurrency
His behavior will be totally different
And that's the same actually is with you if Alex actually thought that there wasn't some
Thing in it
For him to
Not fully denounce XYZ whether it's qanon or Bitcoin
His behavior will be totally different
He thought there was an angle that he could play some sort of hedge in the middle
Yeah man wants
That was clearly not the case
Oh I've known this was a setup all along
Bulshit yeah
Yeah it is
His pattern of like
Denouncing something
Softly and gently but that having
Pro
Guests on it
An eternity
Is
Clear evidence of some sort of
Issue he has with
I can't piss someone
There's always someone that
Be pissed off in
Or just like a there might be
Might be worthwhile to
Tonight pelean
This
Yeah maybe maybe down the road qanon become something that is profitable for me so let's
Keep that lane open until it's too late and then I can always have been against
With with
Bitcoin it could have collapsed left people with nothing could have been something that everyone hates
Will be great for him to be able to say I better get dressed hold out your right
Maybe it's a cool thing and then I feel like I said Max Keiser promoted on my show for 10 years I'm an old-school Bitcoin guy
If you play both sides and let me look like a prophet
But you're not you're just dumb dumb
Anyway
Is on trial
Because
He said something
People did something
What about Kamala Harris
She said some pigs
Who hasn't said things
.
Kamala Harris cackling like the witch she is
Will she be
Impeached
If you had to be stuck in an elevator with either President Trump
Jeff sessions who would it be
A possible interpretation of that joke is that she would kill herself
Before going in an elevator with one of them
So
I don't know I think this is a little bit then
You think
The laughter at crowd Applause
Indicates that this is a different setting
Baby
I would argue that there is a different
Contextual interpretation of someone saying a joke on the Ellen show and someone
I'm saying that you should kill one
Political enemies in a rally after having said that
Killing them is fine for a long time
Dealing with this situation
Entirely differently
If Ellen DeGeneres killed Jeff session
An elephant
I would say the cowboy Harris was very irresponsible
Kill Jeff sessions at elevator
We could be
I mean how could you.
Yeah I mean it's still hard not to add the context of
Couple killed in.
So in terms of the
Impeachment stuff from the the day before
Alex doesn't deal with much of the
Let's say previously unreleased
Videos that are real problem
Find me they certainly contradict his narrative quite a bit
Particular
People chanting hang Mike Pence
And like people wandering through the Halls yelling
For Nancy Pelosi
Though just the person the first person going through the window
Wearing fultz
Picogear Confederate flags
Following along
I think that everybody has different images it'll probably
Stick with them take was one that was really
Really tough for me
And particularly because you know I I I
Spend so much time with Alex's rhetoric in his narrative
Directly counter
This reality is to the game that he's spending totally
Yeah sure
But this Raskin guy right
Luigi
Council
He
I know that from watching
The impeachment not from earlier before that
Paul Joseph Watson Road an article about that
The slimiest like creature
Signal while Jamie Raskin
Said that tonight
On the 6th Trump supporters burn
Down the church
It's funny cuz that church is the one that
Fireball
Church
The gentleman
Is the
Visited with the Bible
Why would you tell
Such a gigantic
Interesting question
John's Church
Trump supporters
Well that would be an issue
Did Abraham Lincoln
Killed Abraham Lincoln
Bojangles biscuit
I know your background is green today
A what
Scott Israel in Texas
Because you don't lying
Couldn't get it
Play with it
By the master of similes I was just
Wild
Outrageous
Yeah so reskin didn't say the people were stabbed on January 6th
Blackpool's as a weapon
Turn against Capitol Police because
That's a super resonant image
That's the idea.
They're being attacked by something that has the flag on it sure it is hard to avoid
Strictly literally than yes no one was run through with a
The pole but that's the difficulty that Alex and his ilk have spinning this stuff
The previously unreleased video of like I said at the storming really disprove a lot of Alex's narratives
Do you really just don't want to deal with that
That stuff so
You Retreat to dumb semantics argument
The mean nothing
Pretend that that's the entire argument against Trump
And it's all a lie no one was impaled
Paled by javelin throw over 40 ft away we were slamming the cops head in a door
Come on right
I asked for the church burning Alex's playing.
Raskin said quote that's before the second million Maga March or rally that ended in
Serious violence and even the burning of a church
This sentence doesn't say who burned
The church but Alex and Paul Joseph Watson are pretending that it's making it
Satori claim
The essence of saying is that
Trump has a
Pattern of exciting events that lead to violence
Really debatable
Fake claim to respond to
They're also pretending that Raskin must be talking about the burning of the st. John's
Church which was the church that dropped it is photo op in back in May
The person or persons responsible
Possible for that fire are still unknown
Is Alex Camp actually prove that anyone from one of his villain group chat
He's just decided to report as if that is okay
Yeah as long as it's unknown
Fine for him
Raskin could have spoken more clearly but what he was talking about was the proud boys vandalizing the Asbury United Methodist Church
A burning banners they stolen from the church that said black lives matter
This is a secondary instance of Alex creating a fake thing to argue against and he knows exactly what Raskin is talking about
The guy who took credit for birding at Church's sign has been a guest on Alex's show
In the night of January 5th
Alex's employee Owen Shroyer recorded himself burning a black lives matter flag in d.c.
Come on grow up a******
Anyway what's really funny about this
Is with that lead up
Hibdon
Actually watched
Best time to tell at the end
Because
In the lead-up to this
He's saying
That Raskin claimed
There was all this on January 6th
Whoops
End
Before the 2nd
Million Mega mart
A rally that ended in serious violence
And even the burning of a church
And is the president forecast it was only the beginning
On December 19th
18 days before January 6th
About where the battle
Would be that they would
Fight next
January 6th
Would be wild he promised
Be there will be wild
Said the president of the United States of America
And that too
Turned out to be true
Still seeing the days
Continue to aggressively promote
January 6th
To his father
Okay so he said that the
March
What's the June 1st
PLM event burn the church
Did he say
6 months apart
Is that why he didn't
President
So you can hear him kind of Reese pinning in real-time because he realizes the clip dozen
Don't say what he had already
Processed it to say
You can hear it very clearly
Okay
Alright see you now
What he saying is something
Different from what I said he would say
And so he's
So whose fault do you think it is
That Trump has bad lawyer
Let's see what it'd be the entire legal profession thinking to his cases both nonsense
Physical and unwinnable or him
Try again Pacific person
Nancy Pelosi
Bruce kaster
So-called lawyer
Put
Oh yeah
Just three months ago
Lawyer
Son-in-law
Spell at Kushner
Okay alright
It's Kushner
Yeah yeah okay
Alright
Lot of buck stops their kind of secret leader of the
Deep state has been Kushner the entire time
Botanica said that maybe
I think this is a relatively Shakespearean Tale
Son-in-law
Betraying his father
I would love to just be able to be like Vibram job
If I could have it
Would be to be a person
Who
Hacks in to Alex's earpiece
And I can just respond live
What's 2 + 2
Alex hasn't earpiece in the producers talk to him
And just be able to hack it and respond in real-time would be so great
Cuz I just secure that is
You just say that the bad lawyers
He hired a lawyer who sued him at the path that he didn't know about that and this is kushner's Father absolutely
Convincing convincing anthropomorphize voice in his head
My mind that he would have that lilacs I got myself doubted that was bad
That was dumb
Is this guy supposed to be king
Hero-guy in
He hired a lawyer who sued him because his son-in-law trick tip
Yep
This is this is stuff that even like this the man I want leading the country
So Alex like I said there's not as much
About the impeachment
As Maybe
Would be
Interesting or seen
Should be merited by
Wake me up this
Show
But he spends quite a while talking
The B boy
Surely the motherfuking bad boy
Yeah we're two clips last
Tomcat cuz I'm not talking about that boy no I'm good
We have to clip
If you'd rather go culture-war or gossip
First
Who I feel like
Culture war is going to be more offensive in yet somehow I feel like gossip also might wind up with
Some really f***** up
Okay
Disney
Alrighty I knew it
Disney has fired
Gina Carano
So a man who is absolutely not a fan of Star Wars
Absolutely not appreciate a release of Star Wars very angry about one particular
The Mandalorian
I didn't know that
If I were Disney
I would blame her for grow goo
On our way out
Everyone else everyone
So in reality what happened was
That she had some social media posts
Including
Particularly offensive one where she
She compared being Republican
To being
A Jew in the Holocaust
Care much for that
No
Alex may not quite
Stand why
She got fired
Crazy about it is
Disney's virtue signaling
English former MMA lady office
Topman
Hero
Pedro is the Mandalorian
Amazon
Wobbled
Semitic
Wow
Wow, blade
The conversation
Cowboy Alex
Alex
You might be
Too used to people saying worse things than that
That's anti-semitic actually does make sense cuz I compared himself to a Jewish person during the hollow
For him
Obviously
What she's saying is like
Towards
Little fire for her for that
I have Steve beyond my show all the time
He's throwing anti-semitic s*** out like f******
Candy in a parade
Yeah it's
It's interesting
To me the part that I find the most
Interesting outside of
Alex's Bazaar
Need
Have a sexual psychodrama with his audience
Yeah I don't know why you need to do that
Have looked strong and powerful now it doesn't mean I don't want to have sex with
But now I've got me should deal with your therapist
I absolutely have to air out the
This problem that I can't sublimate which is that I both attracted to strong powerful women and what them destroy
Weird I wasn't quite sure where he was going
Nancy was talking
I'm about this like what side you was going to land on
Because he's being very weird
Then when he said she groveled and said the Holocaust was bad
Why did you say grovel
I mean when you say the Holocaust is bad obviously you're caving to the ATL and the cuckoo
Klux Klan why did I don't understand that
At all
What should she have said that Hitler was a
Badass stud Alex's said maybe
Navigate to Gossett
It is
It would be kind of ridiculous if
The guy who said that
Hitler was a complete started a badass was like at Gina should have been fired
I wish
That I had the soundboard
Play that cuz I'm afraid that we had a drop that we used
Play where Alex says that Hitler and Stalin are total badasses
Complete badasses.
That's how we used to think
People for
We move on the gossip
Close the show
I will say one of the more rewarding things
It's about listening
To Alex's show
Is getting 25 little thread
Is it you can pull that you would
You know you'd never had
Like there was the story of Buckley's birthday party
Oh sure yeah
Naughty hat
Little glimpses that you get into Alex's life the globalist in the hot
Hot tub is always a classic
Springs tails
All the times he would go down to Barton Springs
The hike-and-bike trail
Tales of the hike-and-bike a lot of interesting things that happened on that trailer another thing is a lot of
About Alex's wife
Tennis habit
A lot more than I would have expected hilarious
We know that her tennis partner
I believe
I was
The scoping out antifa at grocery stores
Intel
And now we learn
But maybe not all is good
In the world of Alex's wife's tennis maybe there's some haters
Crossword just say
Jamie
Raskin says Trump supporters burn down that shirt
That quick huh
File the turnaround is fast on that
I mean I understand that it's most likely just a device for him to do like a character or whatever but I love that there's a
An entire genre
Within Alex's world of light Story 3 complains about the people that plays tennis with
Yeah he's almost doing like
Nursery rhyme levels of explaining things
In in like
Entail
You know like
This is why we don't touch
Search fire because there's a rabbit that goes around and it touched
Fire one time and you were like this
Is bad
This isn't her tennis instructor was like
Hey we should listen to this guy
That's bad
Now children let's move on
I feel like more his
His wife's
Tennis
World is like
World is populated by
Fictional characters that he just gets to a Caston little plays
To have seen antifa setting up at the grocery store
Somebody involved in my life tennis games
We need somebody to play the role of
Nosy judgemental Democrat
It is strangely enough the only both combined tennis club and private investigator Lori
Agency
It's like whenever you first saw Baskin-Robbins in a KFC in the same place you're like what are we doing here
That's the time
Thank you thinking
Dunkin Donuts in kfci
Supposed to know never be a Baskin-Robbins
Safe Company
Taco Bell and Pizza Hut
He said this and then Dunkin and Baskin-Robbins I think a company
Taco Bell KFC
And Pizza Hut all together with
Good meal
But
Don't eat it before you go play
Tennis with Alex
You will you will probably wind up taking a nap and missing out on some
Crucial information either that or you'll become a story that Alex tells on the show
I let somebody who ate too much shittyfood for playing chess with his wife
The new way to f*** with Alex Jones you join his wife's tennis club and you just every now and again walk up to her with a ugly look on your
Listen to say something
If I had all the time in the world
I'd still not do that that sounds hot.
Jordan we come to the end of this and I expected a little bit more fireworks but I mean he is mad
Show me wrong he's mad
It almost makes
More sense to me you know like you're saying this is a coherent issue
Responsive
But he shouldn't be
Looks like upset about the impeachment thing he think he's supposed to think the Trump won the election
Will be disappointed in whatever
Defense there is because they're not saying the Trump won the election
Yeah it is
It's even better for him that they're terrible lawyers because then you can pretend it there
Sandbagging on purpose course
And then whenever they whenever Trump wins and is acquitted
He's very like ca even in spite of the lawyers that the globalist
Dave Embry
He's so innocent
His defense
Was literally two men going bye bye man
4 hours
We do have a website at salad 5.com
Jordan
We're also on Facebook we are Elizabeth
Dallas I-20
Please find a local charity or bail Fund in your
Dzx Clark
I have no other place to mention this and it
It seems perfect
Set me a message
And
Can crazy Norm pattis primitive goddamn beard it is inappropriate
Anyway
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color