Jordan
I have great respect for its knowledge B
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
A little bit about Alex Jones
Guardian
What's up
Panino's Pizza
I used to live
Fairly close to them anyways
Go there get a slice
Pretty regularly
Like it
Slice
Good
I even moved since then I don't I no longer live nearby
Panino's
That will go nameless because I don't actually remember what the name of the place was
But there was a pizza place
In the Terrible
Snow
I saw this and I said
Built up a hunger I said I would like a slice
Jesus as good as Benito right
Terrible
Remembering how much better than Adidas
I ordered
Yeah so I ordered it and it was as good as I remember shout-out Camino
Congratulations
Dino's for making good
I finally tried out Haiti's
Fantastic
Now
It's nice and it's got a great
I like the mechanic of the like
You're supposed to
And that's part of the story like it's that like
Trapped in the in the Senate
Mythology I enjoy
I don't know if I have made this
Complaints
But I have one complaint about the game I don't think how fast this isn't it
I have not been important
Hephaestus is the reason I should be making all of these busts that you're getting like here at the he's the armorer
Glaring omission
Huge what beer
Anyway that was a water guy just thought when I was playing
Seems like it's a bowl of game reviews or Meredith
Do you know what it do you know what makes
Expedia it reminds me of old old PlayStation 1 game called as your dream
Okay I did was that same kind of
Infinite Dungeon Crawler that would
Populate a new dungeon for you every time but you would capture monsters
Is it was like a mixture of Pokemon that head
And that same kind of Hades Dungeon Crawl some fun
Fantastic
It was it was that weird kind of PS1 game though where is like
Also there's a dating simulator
Relationship system in Hades compared to that as well
Really dating simulator got nothing
Your relations opens up different
A very weird without a Pokemon
Yeah that's true you don't really
Hayward
Is even ready for that
I was hoping I could distract the holiday
February 14th
Sunday special Valentine's Day episode
I just love it family show and you know I'm big
Completely facetious
Serious about it being fat
Sing fun things. Supposed to sign up
Sophie
I'm a policy wonk
Deez Nuts wren
B r n
Classic
Solace Manhattan
Thank you so much
I'm a policy book
Classic
Michaels
T-shirt
I'm a policy wonk very much single
T-shirts
It's interesting Jordan
Gazelle Austin
Right now is
I have been for a while
But right now in the state of Texas they're experiencing an incredible ice storm and I hope everybody
Oliver listeners in that part of the world there are staying safe
Ain't no joke
Yeah I understand we are meant for that
That's where we're at for a challenge
Cuz I'm coming into the store so he does come in for a Sunday show
When you go to very easily
Done it remotely
Knocked on the show no problem Harrison Smith ramble about white genocide
From Today Show
Here's the video of the granny being thrown off the cliff
Okay okay alright
That wasn't Walker Texas Ranger
Should hear
Anti starts off the show as anyone would
If they had just come into work
YouTube driving through chaos
And I was complaining about driving to Chicago
This is got to be an incredible show today
Because I'm
Grown up
Grown up in people.be nose Drive
But I've never seen anything like that
This was road-warrior level I probably saw
100 wrecked cars in the way here smash signs glass
Firefighter trying to block major roads I wouldn't even be here if I had to just go ahead and go on around them
Because I was driving my wife's all-wheel vehicle
My favorite thing about
I need more explanation for how he went around
If its next line is
With an all-wheel drive vehicle get to him about that
But I do love the idea that he's starting off as Road like this better be a f***
Looking great I just threw under Road Warrior
Yeah I see you you're asking about this this car situation
Talk more about wow
And it's basically turns into a car crash
The house in my truck
Drive-In
I got her car
That's the only good thing that German cars good for
She wanted an Audi
And I was just telling in Westlake
Cuppy's bagatelles or meiosis wreck
And I'm just like
Commercial here ladies and gentlemen
Lorde
At vehicles
Four wheel drive cars just wrecked everywhere Range Rovers are all wheel drive they were wrecked
Subaru's wrecked everywhere
That Audi was like I'll just a robot
Wales
Black ice
20 miles the office
Unbelievable but a lot of people died in Texas that's really sad
Right total shift wow that sounds sincere
Yeah
Lot of people died out he's great but a lot of people.
Commercial but if you don't buy it out of your going to die
About a minute of rambling about a great his wife's car is
Play It Again to break reminder give the Darrell have been fatalities
Yeah it's a little
Yeah it makes me feel bad for making
2 fun of something that's
It's awful
One degree removed
From being off
A move
Yeah that's fair
So
I wanted to cover this episode
The Broncos Valentine's Day number 2 because
This is the point at which Alex would know that Trump has been acquitted
Yes he did his special report on Saturday which I tried to watch
Two bit of but it was mostly I'm talking about vaccines
Then I got really bored she wanted to hear about his Take On Me
He said this was this whole trial was a sham
It was all just set up to get Trump so now what happens whenever it worked out the way that we all knew it was going to
Alex Ivy I mean it's bulshit but he has actually pretty decent spinner
We have the insane trial the president
I suddenly ended
You had three days Tuesday Wednesday Thursday
Hours a day of total lies against the president
30 hours of garbage
3 hours by lawyers doing half a decent job
Killer kill Trump vice president
And they had to put
Drop it
Because
It was another giant frog
So I mean that's that's not a terrible span of like these videos of sugar
Yeah conversation about like they weren't
They weren't going to vote in conviction
How many Republicans
Voted with the 7 I believe
More than one is a crazy number
Directly going to be murdered
So there's that
I would I would assume he would be a guaranteed job needs a lock
We're going to be murdered like I assumed if Mike Pence was in the Senate would be like
Yeah I'm going to have to know hanging for me
You don't like that kind of feel I prefer not to quit this
Constitutional
Gets to message
Stupid
I feel like you should
No
You should be embarrassed
If you even
Try and say they did a half good
You should be
Embarrassed that was
Really really shameful stuff
It was yeah
Do you know we learned a little bit about what happened
Philly looting Philadelphia
That you and I watched
He was talking about fil-A
And then a different point he said
Philadelphia
Good stuff Yelp
Good stuff
So when you're at
You know
Radio show host
Sten you come in
Amazon Valentine's Day Eve through a
A movie like storm sure
Yes I'll perfect
Storm
You got it you got to
Cover the importance
Stop right you got to take care of the really important business
We've got a lot
We've got
Saturday Night Live is on
More jokes about pedophilia not existing
And more attacks about children being abused
Ritualist
Strictly because
I can tell you a large farmer writing staff
Pedophiles
A devil worshiper
I'm going to I'm going to have to send a couple of texts
Heard some disturbing news
Alex Jones has informed me that
So what's going on is that the last two weeks there has been qanon jokes on Saturday Night Live
The first one was about the Superbowl commercials
And there was a
Commercial
Qanon recycle eat your Papa John's Pizza on Eureka
But no sex trafficking in the basement already democratic
Did the character where she was a witch
I got qanon which was really after
Twisted and eating children
You know I did an interview with the Weekend Update
And Alex is like pretending this is the news
She's very mad
A second what
SNL cast that we grew up with would have done it
If qanon was around then
Farley going to do about there just not prepared for that kind of stuff
He's not in the in their in their wheelhouse
I don't want Adam Sandler doing prank
Qanon f*** nevermind I want Adam Sandler doing prank qanon phone calls
Sure
So that's important
Very important. Cloud
Qanon misconstrue as them
Making jokes of pedophilia doesn't
Good job
Another
You know kind of distasteful to
I don't I don't know how to say this but I found this really repulsive
Alex plays
Alex plays video of the pile up
Outside Fort Worth
100 + car pileup
He plays video that someone captured from like the other lane
Yeah and so it's just plain VA
Tire
Like Collision 8
Terrifying
And there is
No real value to it
But I was trying to pretend that there is
But I want to give you some
Viewer discretion
Should we come back
I don't show
Horrible tragedy
To just show you a horrible tragedy
Because
I see this
I was shown this on Friday by the crew
I didn't know
After 24 hours of the stuff happening at the Fort Worth and Dallas
What really happened
I've seen the helicopter footage
The couple hundred cars all piled up
We come back I'm going to show you what really am
When someone on the ground when it happen
Close
I've never seen anything in the Hollywood movie
Like this one
Crashing and flipping exploding
Wait till you see
On-the-ground the app
Actual pilot
And the reason I'm going to play it
Explain when we come back
So if you were to scratch invited because people were dying
7 people died
On the furniture
Showing it to save some live
And illustrates
Stop right there
We're not going to be on air
New Year
And you back
Just last year I told you that last year at Black
Just don't do it
Fun some other secret project for working on
Gosh I could do a lot better have my money I'm not doing that talking about
I'm about to show you footage of seven people dying
This was
Group home
Is f*****
Shocked by the
Gross
Coldness
Yeah the cynical is the
I'm going to show you what really happened
I was like are you trying to say there's a conspiracy here
He wasn't
There is no real value to this unless
He wants to turn into a road safety show
It's still a little bit
First of all too soon
I don't think you could
Use this footage to illuminate any
Particular finer points of
Hazardous Drive
It was just like
There is no reason to play this other than shock value
Or something
It's B
It's offensive
It's nakedly exploitative
And McColl
In a way that like
Makes you
Like
It is hard not to think that he gets
Some sort of like
Weird f***** up like you know that the people who watch the Faces of Death
Where you're like
There's something that you get out of this that I'll never understand
I just won't be there for you
Deal breaker
He said there's a reason and he's going to become
Cumplir next cycle
This makes what kind of has him expressing what that reason is
But I
I would say want this reason stupid
2 SE 2nd
The connection that he's trying to make
You don't need to watch
The video Tik
I'm showing you footage of
Dallas Tech
Texas State live
Shop there on top of one of the world's tallest building
Icy Wasteland no one on the street
Herein
Chicago or you're in New York you laugh at that
You said he'll we drive all the time while we're not used to it only happens
Once or twice
A year at
Hundreds of people died
Statewide winter unfold
That's a teaching moment
Americans haven't been under
Batman under Stalin
Or a mile or Fidel Castro or a Hugo Chavez
What he's trying to illustrate with playing this video is these people in Texas aren't used ice dry
Rising
And so there's a giant pile up
Much like Americans aren't used to dealing with a Hitler or Stalin
The Tyranny and therefore where metaphorically going to have a pile up
Now you don't need to watch that video to make that metaphor at all absolutely no reason
Add to your understanding of the metaphor you could just say it
It doesn't matter
And also what about
Booking Obama
What about Bill Clinton nothing they were fine
They weren't that they were no big deal they were working for the devil yet
I think they were according to him about it remember that they were also present
He was trying to pretend he was serious backpack
Not like one of those people who says that everybody is a devil
I'm not like David I could become my best friend in 10 years
We've never even had to deal with anything new like I Joe Biden
Right
I think it was
The most
Tenuous connection to make in order to justify playing this video
And I don't respect
The decision that all I think
It's disgusting
Alex
Is on the ground
The other line
18-wheeler
Biggest worth 117 in a minute
Alex is saying you're lucky you're not seeing this for the radio audience wow
He's playing you could just not
Every everybody could be lucky we could all be lucky right now I would like to be lucky
You're lucky you're not watching my show you're just listen
Intuit
It doesn't add anything it's
Outrageous he wanted to watch
I think I think you might be might be on Summer
To be something with with
That's purse
I found I found it disgusting
And unacceptable
Much like Alex's thinking patterns
So
He has decided that thousands are dead
From the vaccine
Already
Why
Well for what
Thousand okay
Who decides it
You got to know that
It's actually probably 50 times higher than that 50 times
Confirm that okay
So
I have a stack of this year where there are
Thousands of dead admit it I think about 1 in 50
Adverse reactions
So if Sal's are dead
Text 50 times
No one knows
Can you identify
Just really quickly if it like
The artist surface-level the problem with that ticket
No
I don't see any problem
It's outrageous
Then there's probably 50
Tee times more
That means it's proven
Right
Yep
This is dumb I mean like
If you would live if if I were listening to a professor
School right to lecture
They said something like that I would not trust them
To teach the rest of the class I might withdraw I wouldn't
Real confident in math class where they were like okay what's 1 + 1 but remember one is probably 50 or
Or could be more or could be fewer no one knows
Who knows I might be making up the one
Now
Yikes
Not good so that kind of thinking that Alex brings to the table
What is making assumptions
And then multiplying things
By whatever numbers he chooses feels good about today
Is just make sure it up like it has about this usnewsandworldreport sarta
What kind of the good news
Because it's very very important
The McRib
Maxine
Administration
Straight I'm in concerns of widespread refusal
US News & World Report
It goes on to say that the vast majority of
Are refusing the vaccine because it's voluntary
Mystical manipulation I go obit
We did get a sir
80 +
So what do you do when the vast majority won't take it
Navigate percent
You take the group
We'll take it
Sao
80 + percent of them 82%
82%
That's the statistical game they play
It's absolutely has not read this article about the troops of vaccinations
He's claiming that the article says that there's a subsection of troops
82% of whom have received the vaccine
That's the statistical game Alex claims this article is playing
The start of 82% is actually a reference
What's the percentage of vaccines the Pentagon has received that have been
Administer
Probably article quote
Pentagon spokesman John Kirby told reporters that department has so far ordered more than 1 million doses
And as of Thursday morning had received roughly
Of those 800,000 or about 82% have been administered
Almost 600,000 were first doses
And more than 200,000
A second dose
Scene of the number and made up what it means so they took the small subset of people
Otherwise the people who possibly could have gotten
And they're manipulating those numbers to say that those people did get it
I don't end of the people outside of those numbers while they didn't get
No Alex's just skimmed the article see numbers and written the story in his head about what those numbers mean
This is what he does
Cuz he's really really bad at
I can't believe people actually take him seriously as he does seem to play Madlibs and then search articles for like
Numbers to Circle
Eighty-two percent under lock
Did it underlined 82%
What could that 82% be
I can't be bothered to do that kind of work
About this
You saw usnewsandworldreport I mean the military
Least evil people
Said
British military
Started before the US Military
A bunch of miscarriages
Oh
Oh but you don't say that US News & World Report
You just said the US Military
The rank-and-file pulled out of their ass
The pregnancy stuff is so be covered under past episodes so don't get too bogged down at here but this is just another instance
How's Alex making more s*** up about this article cuz he hasn't read to get mad about
If I were to actually read the article I found this quote
From Air Force Brigadier General Paul Fredrick
Quote are we seeing people who are declining to it
I've heard people say that for a variety of reasons
They're pregnant
Which is a very reasonable concern
They want to talk to her doctor first
Very reasonable concern
So there are people who said they don't want to get it
This whole article is actually a
Big problem for Alex's narratives because he's been insistent that the vaccine is mandatory or it's going to be mandatory
But the fact that the military is allowing enlisted person
Decide if they want to get it or not makes them have to change the subject
Because they think he was making his audience afraid about didn't happen
He now has to Pivot to make it look like the enlisted persons who don't get the vaccine or somehow being maligned
Which is article doesn't
Support
He didn't read it
No one listening is going to read it
So this technique works
Barclay
Liquid might as well not to do
Yeah
And with the military that thing is
Your
Most people aren't going to look into it
And for most people I would imagine that there makes a certain sort of like sense that well the military would be mandate
Is there's a military
Follow up on that especially not Alex's listeners they be like yeah the military Sportster
To do everything
Alex claims to have some information that he does not produce
Mean season
Take me to
I got so many adverse reaction death reports
I got over 200 upright beer
The last 3 days
15 minutes
Nicely worried about steps I want to win the fight I was worried about my family everything
Things are so crazy now this ain't going to go online
Whatever's going on
Whatever's happening a number of people they're killing
Whatever's going on baby we ain't never seen nothing like that
I thought they
Put some in there
Oh no don't kill your ass right now
See I mean if you have these these 200
Want to talk about any of
Yeah
I would argue that
If you just say something and you don't prove it or dammit
X-rated at all I could ride ignore it
Yeah
Especially something that when tied to your other rhetoric is
I guess lyson
Since to go murder whomever you wants right
Because
They're killing you in 50
15 minutes there killing your grandma right now in 50
3 minutes
Well you thought you were going to have a lovely 5 years to like
Hold your grandma's hand as she dies from the government murder vaccine
But now you don't even have that much
The only comfort I really take is hoping that people who listen to this would ask themselves at some point
Does Alex actually read the things he talks about
And look into it and then that might have rode public
Confident with his dumbass
I could
What are the times when Alex is just rambling about something on are it's something that our old friend
Paul Joseph Watson
And Paul has struck again
Oh
Lincoln BBC
UK government could Grant
Catholic minorities I heard this a few months ago an MPR
Where are black people are dumb you know where liberals we can say that
Did the UK say that
U.s. military they're dumb
You know they just stay just don't trust us
And so we're going to have vaccine waivers for them
Have a job you know how they are
White people you're going to take
Show the black people not to be scared you roll up your sleeve and take a shot
This is just a total
Criminal
The cover-up
Steve
All the corruption
And the derivatives of the scams of the dollar implosion
New World Order the rigging on the cloning
So you forget all the crimes they committed
And don't do anything about it
Dumb plan
Is a dumb dumb plan is hard not to think about what would have happened if
You and all of your right-wing lunatic dum-dum
Friends had decided to take
This whole f***
Nothing seriously way back in
In February of last year
I think they did
Take it too seriously for a minute I apologize
In March of last year
There is no link
To the BBC in Paul's article
There's a link to a story in The Spectator and wanted
Sky News
This guy news article says nothing about exemption
Paul Dudley Cherry picks a very minor side point in The Spectator article which he then turns into his head
Because it has the potential to help boost white victimhood feel
This is an editorial column and what are the concerns that raises with the idea of vaccine passports being required for
Travel is according to this column vaccine skepticism is higher in non-white communities in the UK
Sure
It's really interesting how Paul works here
Paul takes this quote from the Sky News article
Government insiders stress there's nervousness about
When such a system will even be announced publicly let alone rolled out for you
If you read the article it does seem to be implied that the nervousness in question is about the vaccine's efficacy and not moving
Too fast
However here's how Paul uses that line
Part of this nervousness is based around the perception that meditating mandating vaccines for travel could be seen as races
Because suspicion of vaccine that poor inoculation rates are commonplace
Within Bame community
He's taking the
Concerns raised by the editorial of The Spectator and apply them to the quote for the Sky News article without in any way
Demonstrating that the two are connected at all
Paul just kind of making things up in order to justify writing a blog post about white identity fears that Alex convened report on any Sue
Super racist play on air
Cuz that's what Their audience needs to stay interested
Appreciate the real lack of
That went into that
DePaul yeah like
It is
It is always we're going to heartwarming
To know that some people
Wake up at 9 go to work and they're done at
It's nice to know that there's a dream that somebody can accomplish you know
Transparent about it
So so far I think we seeing
Just a real tragedy of
Michelle Weekley crash
The makeup nonsense about a couple articles
Majlis
Jesus Christ
Boo
You know what we're out of time for out-of-town maybe this is a good teaching moment as well
All right now
Understand that we're not going to get anywhere with the Coronavirus
With him it's too or too far gone
But let me toss this out for you Dan
If there were fewer cars on the road during a nice store
Don't you think that would be better at preventing
Yes
Right so perhaps if Alex
Wanted to do his part to prevent Acts
You could have stayed home and done the show remote
Now do you understand how those things might be a
Nectar tires in the metaphor their Bakery but I also expect he did come at me the problem
Bored
So when I was coming back from break after
Good pathetic growl
Very long
Passionless growl
He starts complaining about how people think that he
Exported drunk because
It somehow was good for his business now
I know that I've heard him a hundred times say that is traffic went up
Ridiculously
A doll that is really good for his business
He was person
Secutity Alex was persecuted
I got
Persecuted
Fort Trump
You got
Persecuted first
We're not losers because we support a present
Trump really won
And I don't just say that
Any lost yesterday he lost
Chinese agent charge
Myself
Okay you're sold not since about then
I will know what's really going on
That's what
Give me
Missing my wife
Read that usnewsandworldreport article that that's a good starting point
I would I would argue he really wants to know what's not going on
Or he doesn't want to know what is going on
Yes yeah
He desperately needs not to know what's going on
Yeah in order to make this work
Which is why you
Yeah but there's bad news about Trump
But bad news mix
But it's all bad
Okay
Especially
He's not just lost
Deal 5000 lawsuit against them
He's actually stronger than ever
I understand that and if more men were like President Trump
It more memory like
Broadcast
But he understands leadership
Buy Colonel Travis at the Alamo
Drunkenly
They said that final otorrino was about to happen
I couldn't back down because he believed the causes
You want the suicidal
I can't get out of here.
Jesus Christ said
Just want to lay it
Down
For others
Countdown to
Colonel Travis at
Nowhere else to go
Dora
He had nowhere else to
Trump may have nowhere else to go
Put out a little statement
About the impeachment acquittal
Yeah and now it's Alex
What kind of pissed off is that no one's reading
The full state
Nowhere do you really see them
But you don't really
Maybe a line here lying there let's read the whole thing together
It's beautiful he said that's totally true
National follow the story itself infowars.com
Take me home
S and P 4
President-trump
To the office the former president
Worcester State
Celebrating
Damn right he's a man the arena
I've overlooked is under attack
Coming after you what you think I did you think I did this. To be attacked
Apartments in Cimarron with you some country club
That I do think
Yes I agree with that looks like me
Put a gun to my head I'm not back until you dumb sons of b******
Your background
Real shame that no one's reading the Trump statement
I do I do appreciate that
It does it does appear that for most of the world
We're finally passed like half and to deal with
The stuff he says on the daily
Everybody
Enjoyed
I have personally some trouble whenever I see too much of him
Yeah
I don't want
I don't want people that I would normally think of it saying
To talk about him and not because I want exclusive domain over Alex
I just don't think it's worth it now
I don't see this is a problem for us
What's 2
I don't value my own time but I value other people's house
Save yourself
We're too far gone
B kick us out of the mall we're not supposed
To be there
Will be on the roof
So Alex does get around to reading the statement I will say it in full but he does add some commentary
It is a little bit ridiculous
Spell president
Never gone through anything like it
And that's true
The key
And it continues because our phone
Not forget
Almost 75 million people
Way more than that
The greatest number
Everpress sitting president
Devoted
I was just a few months ago
They lie about it though
He won those others
6 days by half
Do you want to buy
Five points on a
Understand
Wait more than quadruple the number of
It's weather
Crapping their britches
That's more than quadruple the number of Victory number
Yeah
Kind of feels a lot like that
50 * 50
I feel like Alex doesn't know much about
Numbers
You know very little
So
Complaining
And of course this leads into him yelling a bit about
Abuse towards children and I don't show her
I don't respect his position on the issue
I got a lot of complaints about snla I think we can let that one go I don't think we need to worry
About that is really not
Any reason
To engage
That's one break
It comes back
I want to tell you
He's not killing
Doing time
Argue even mentioning snl.on you're apparently political talk show would
Be killing time
You know debatable if it's killing time
This next minute
Definitely not
It sounds like it's going to be
In the snowstorm and rebroadcast
Luther show
Infowars live
Sunday night
Is that coming up if everyone can get it reduced calling
Because it is
It's insane
Yes
Ask him to come to work
Oh my God
Emperor Palpatine
The song
He's like a hundred generation clone of Palpatine
You know that happened a long time ago in a galaxy far far away
Tom
Oh you don't know about Star Wars
Thousand Clowns
Is going to beat Houston Michelle
I have a lot of stuff
I got too much of a
Installing out
Does
Weather for May
Play five minutes
How to go
It's because
This is surreal mean it is it's just the real is too much
There's too much
Just got a refund
Tom Peppard name being similar to Palpatine
For a bit
Dick
What a dick people dying outside people dying outside let's see if Owen can get
To work
Yeah
Great
Good boss
Good boss love working for you buddy I will say what I would ask
Respect of Alex as a boss broadcast if you can't get in
Kind of a stand-up guy that is
Also Scrooge being like you get Chris
I guess that's
Maybe it's killing some time
Here's the video of the granny being thrown off cliff
Replace video that's
A guy or rolling a woman in a wheelchair
Through a park
And that ends with him dumping her
So it is like that Conan O'Brien
New Walker Texas Ranger schedule
It's
Well there's a little bit of lovin
There's some racial undertones for Alex
White Lightning
Liberal
Illiberal
This video is a campaign ad
That was targeting
Paul Ryan
Because you could cut
Take that take Medicare
This is at least a two-year-old ad
That was against the GOP that Alex's play against some kind of attack on
Liberals are subtitle man-to-man
I was like this is business real and Alex clearly hadn't watched it and advantages new was an old lady
If you look
Pretty surprised when the thing comes up
Call Paul Ryan
Hold on one second
Subway
So Alex
No he's he's he's he's a bit of a fatalistic mood
You know
We already said earlier that
You know we might not be here
Next year
F*** that we might not be here tomorrow
I got a final second
A bunch of news I want to hear
I bought a pair on that
Tell you all this license elmet it's been a great pleasure to be on air
What do you
I don't know how long I'm going to be here
Things are so bad things are going so fast
Now that I'm not even sure will be here tomorrow that's week
Next year
It's all up to God right now but
The bottom fell out
It's just their euthanizing the old people
We've got power
5% death rate
Text shot
Weather
Successfully covered up most areas
Okay
That's a ridiculous number
Okay hold on
Even then just make up numbers like that
No
But even then what
Current but nevermind
I don't even know
So stopped
Stop just stop
One of the things I think is interesting is Alex's talking pretty fatalistically stalking a lot of
We are gone
We're done it looks like that I won't say that I'm falling for it again
Or anything like that
Looking for real but I do need to tell you this but I do think it's important was that
He's playing a lot of doors
Who played are you learning songs by the doors as Bumper Music
And my friend
A lot of things
Erroneously
Bums me out mostly cuz I don't like the doors
Such a scent like the mood of the music that he's playing
On a very regular basis
Like multiple coming in from commercials per show
The Aria Dora Dora songs
Has the cone of a dirge
Okay
Let's see how this goes
I just I think
I will say that if it doesn't end soon and he keep playing the doors
You know what
One thing that I realized
After the impeachment trial
Was that
Don't think that's
What's the appropriate punishment
And I think the same thing for Alex I don't
Appropriate
Punishment is to liked
Take them off the air
I don't think the appropriate punishment for Trump
To take him away
From politics
They should have no money
0 money
Take their money if the impeachment trial was like
Yeah sure run for office again
With
Nothing
I got broke
I think it's people do
Things that have Civic
Are civil penalties
And what have you and I don't I don't want Mike what I'm about to say to be like Alex
By people who he has Ross
Then I'm not particularly concerned
With him having money or not having money
I'm concerned about
The impact that
He can have a greater punishment for him
Is the illumination
Explanation
Of how
Bulshit everything he does is
Sprite the how is basically defraud
People with
Posture
Like some guy who's again
A system when all he really is a f****** idiot
Right and I want to take
Take away the thing he cares about both
Memories of Colonel Travis
I'll take those two if I could sue him for those
This show has been largely devoid of
Meaning
No
Pop culture grieving because Alex has found a video of
AMC
Well
Medium fries
Current Stars review they did a little song
About the vaccine and Alex is not happy about
Run DMC
Members now put out
This
I guess the money must be good this type of garbage I got something even sick
I think there's
Plenty of valid criticisms
About this song
That it's too good for the rest of us this isn't this isn't really my territory to keep receipt
Too much
But I will say that Alex was
Far less critical of bike Adams rap career
Weird Ebola Reston
I mean I respect what they're doing it
Stay here and after
Preschool special
From DMC
It is
ESA
I just I don't really know
I don't know it just seems weird that Alex would care that much
Because he's filling f******
Time what I'm saying
Like this is what he spends his other time
The show
Bill Gates says he wants to
Populate you
You're going to take your shots.
What is Bill Gates
Disappeared
I will buy
My money
Gates and solve the problem
Alex plays a video from like a YouTube channel called omsom
I believe I'm some
And it's like
It's for kids it's an educational video for kids
They've a big series of videos of what would happen if blanket disappeared
Numbers disappeared
Okay
Good animations for kids
Sanders what about what would happen if Bill Gates disappeared and some of it is like well he's a big philanthropist
Sabata at money would be drawing
Warren Buffett would miss his best friend
It's like what are you commenting on this
First thing that he can engage with on a equal footing
Yeah
Embarrassing
It's for kids
I mean I'm not
I'm not going to say that that doesn't have
Kind of propaganda feel to it
I'm not going to say that making a video where you like
What if Bill Gates was gone at that didn't also include like
Well
It's possible that his money would be shuffled back into the economy and put into places where
Maybe he doesn't have a visitor he's a philanthropist but maybe he's still got 20 billion dollars
Might be complicated for children might be a little bit difficult except
To the point that is not the critique that I looked at
I get what you're saying I here I here
Maybe in a little bit weird but it's also a giant public figure
I didn't watch the whole thing
But the stuff that Alex plays
Is just like
All right this isn't like
Bill Gates is our God
You know what if he went more like a Starship Troopers wrote where is like
Doesn't it seem a little bit weird that we're making these kind of
Campaign videos
Public figures
What we should be doing is talking about the issues
Stuff like that but even then you talk about a kids video
I know how you can tell that argument Cuts both directions
Perceptive
Before
I don't know I I just
You know I was I was feeling like
There wasn't much
Happening here but there was a lot happening
You don't like it was really disgusting
The Athena playing of that the crash yeah
You going right into an Adesa
Talking about
Amanda
No really makes you think
This is how we ended the show
Going to an Incredible God for the frozen roads
Road Warrior level crashes
And hopefully back tomorrow 11 a.m. Central
What do I broadcast
AAA job
Bomb National file
There is no reason that he needed
To come in at all nope
Tom pappert is in
You know he's not he's not in Texas
Like he doesn't remotely Alex could have just set up a little like a man
No need no need this is all for nothing
Is all the way
The house on Valentine's Day
Alright
Okay so they debuted with his first time I saw that there was a new commercial for my Patriot Supply
And Alex is at their warehouse
Betty's in Salt Lake City Utah
Clip
My dick
Eastbay Alyssa warehouse must have been why he went or at least part of it.
Baby it's baby it's
Steno kill two birds with one stone we are already there at least part of it
I love you you talk bud
The number one vacation destination that's thoroughly
CIA
I don't have any clips of it
I'm talking about a great the food
If you were to say hey
All you beers are all you listeners
You're lucky not to be watching this video right now but it said you just didn't play it damn true
Restrain
Did you know that if
If you get my Patriot Supply stuff and you open up one of those buckets
What's up
Be careful
You might not be able to get it close cuz there's so much
Is that like three times
What is ologist
What it's all just a buffer
But like you pull it up and then it pops out and they're like
You can eat it forever I would
Be Charmed
By that
Yeah I don't know
I don't know how you found this
Episode 2B
A little frustrating
Children's videos
Run-DMC vaccine songs SNL complaining
It's like everything receipts of trivial
I feel like it's trivial stuff is happening
Yeah yeah
I think that I think that Alex
Start
Some level didn't have as much
Skin in the game with the impeachment as
You might have thought he might and then
The spin of they just played clips of Democrats saying stuff and how do you defend
Against that
As if that was
Legally relevant
No kidding
I think that works for him
So
I don't know
I want to see if he keeps playing the doors
Yeah and if that hat is a bad omen
I can only imagine if he comes in for break with like the sound of silence so we know it's over
It's just
He's just sing along with Elliot
It's method
It starts raining
I paid $50,000
Set the mood
How I feel
If you can afford to have your environment reflect your interview
Yeah but I'm just
Well
I guess we'll be back to find out what the next step in this adventure is
Dot-com
Skip world's on Twitter
Please find a local charity with bail Fund in your area to help out
Doing God's work
Until then I met you I'm Leo mdzs
Text Clark I'm Daryl rundus
I am
Miles Jones's wife Audi
Alex
Kirsten color with huge fan I love your work