Damn important swetik
I have great respect for Tenaya Lodge like I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Knowledge
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Nike.com
Everybody welcome back to knowledge play damn damn
I'm sure
Like to drink novelty beverages in their own homes then sit around and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
It does appear that that is our plan for the the time being right now Dan Jordan we are we recording
This separately probably the first
Actual episode that we recorded over
Distance it's a little bit weird
Removable remains to be seen. It's an actual episode
Jedi with the in
Intention of
Of a regular episode kind of kind of a mini episode
I don't want to again just don't want to stress to everybody that we not going to have episodes every Monday when
Wednesday and Friday
But
Circumstances kind of demanded
This weekend we had to
We had to jump on the horse and get something
Get something together
Yeah I don't
I think that's a terrible idea
But simultaneously
We can't get together
Does Chicago has waist-deep snow out
It's bad
Really bad
And I ran out of coffee I ran out of coffee last night
Yaz morning
I was about to take
Take the dogs out for a walk and I always start
Cup of coffee
Coffee
A pot of coffee
Before I take the dogs out and I realized in that moment I have none
So I had to walk through close to a mile
Waist-deep snow
Coffee
Is the most brutal morning I've ever had
I walk down to the grocery store
Cuz I had needed some some salad
Stuff for lunch
And it was a
The Dead Zone
There's nobody there it was
It was fantastic
Yeah
It was
I mean
Despite
Logistical problems that everyone's dealing with
There was no one at a grocery store was pretty nice
There are some advantages
So I guess my bright spot is that till you and I are both doing relatively alright
It was coming down
All day all night yesterday
Disaster
Last night was it was one of the first times I've seen that kind of snow storm and I was like
Man I think I'm actually scared for sure
Argo
Like we did look we get covered in snow.
That's fine one was like oh s*** this one might be too much
For us
Yeah yeah whatever people start talking and feet
It's like
You didn't say 16in you said multiple
That's trouble
That's the reason that we needed to jump on the old Zoom here and get an episode together was because
Alex is also dealing with inclement weather
Usually
You got some you know. Texas is seeing
Unprecedented
Winter storm
They're happening right now
And in Fort Worth Studio his
Spin instructor
Bye
By the the dice
The Winter Queen
What's the name of the character in The Lion the Witch and the Wardrobe
Cuz I think it's just
Well anyway Alex wants some Turkish delight
Okay
Alright okay
Running out of breath
Will stop playing all of the
Voyage of the Dawn Treader
Boy and his horse
Sorry
Yeah Silverchair Prince Caspian
Lion Witch and the Wardrobe
Right
Did they say why to the Dawn Treader I think I said that first
You're two of them
You're missing the final two
The Magician's Apprentice
Call close
Sorcerer's Apprentice
Not only real close the Magician's Nephew
Yes
There you go
I think I
I forgot
I think it's just the last battle
Oh that's probably a pet very boring
Everything really boring book
Can't believe I forgot them
The Magician's Nephew
A book
You know what I think that one's always been my favorite
I was like that one the little rings
Did they go into the little middle of the world to teleport thing
Always fun
I read the hell out of those
And I don't think I remember the
Plot of
Any of the at least the last
Four of them
Oh no that's fine
Totally fine
The prequel
No and that's why I've always liked it it's
The prequel to The Lion the Witch and the Wardrobe
Okay so it's like the Tokyo Drift
Before the main characters die
Picture
So Jordan
We got tell you know some Alex Jones stupidity to deal with it'll be a little bit of a briefer episode but
What's I wanted to check in with how he's doing in occupied by Ice OST
Before we do that I want to say thank you
Sporting show
The first Bill W thank you so much
Next Jordan has snot Jordan 8
Jordan
Nikolas B thank you so much and I'll probably want
Text Andrew Avon
Text Amelia or thank you so much
Text Mariah and finally
Brock's thank you so much you and I'll probably walk
Are you very much drox
Don't say hi to
Rocksmith I was I saw it
I saw that joke coming
Try to duck
And you still hit me in the face with it
That's out
Wild sorry I have
Cookies on the map
Yeah and I think we've got one more little piece of
I think we've got one more little Visa but we're getting into this place if we're just shouting people out for
No reason at this point
Unreason over this particular Shout
One particular reason and that is it is their anniversary today
Play I Believe
Bonnie and Eric
Happy
20th wedding anniversary
For Wednesday the 17th
20 years dance exciting
Anniversary right
The 20th of the piano
Yeah yeah first is paper second is like silver no way that's my
Much later
20th and Vienna Rose
I hope you guys exchange pianos and that would be the right way to do it
Yeah that's is traditionally back to my hosting stand-up comedy days I like I like to do
You know you start out ever showed Zanies with a
Anybody celebrating anything tonight
The difference here is that people have
Told us that they're celebrating something as opposed to us starting the show having to fish
4 something
To love are different
It's
It's more celebratory less sad
Jordan 16th
Or maybe was yes I didn't 50th actually Alex put out a series of
Vignette
Of himself
At the Emporia Studio
Lights are out in the studio there's also
A couple of them where he's outside yelling in the snow
What does this make sense though
It's all nonsense and we can talk about it
Today Show
Don't be scared yellow
Hello dogs Novi property rights
Wow that's
The plan that's
They are very interested in borders
They don't like immigration
From house to house that's the the situation that dogs are Libertarians
They are part of the Austrian School
I feel like this is just Alex like
Protecting other people
From his mist
You know he's hurt so many dogs because he was afraid of them right
And now he's sharing his wisdom with the rest of the world hey guys
Just throw a rock at a dog murderer
Just throw Rockets dog that's fine I forgot
Yeah yeah
Don't shoot too hard
Lil'jordan we're here recording on Tuesday and that's what time is episode being put together Infowars has essentially been off a
Are since Sunday evening
Cancel culture
Austin and most
Do Texas is dealing with a once-in-a-lifetime winter storm has left countless people without power
In severe
It appears that
Bn4 Studio has been left also
Without power
And that means no show for Alex
It makes sense and I don't think anyone would bat an eye if you just got on air and said there's a weather emergency and they had to take an unplanned breaking
Program it
He could be an effective way to push emergency food sales even so it might not end up being a total money loss if you did that
But Alex does not go that route
Instead of
Expressing solidarity with
The people of Texas is encouraging people to stay inside if possible and donating to a mutual Aid fun
Alex decided to record a video of himself at the Infowars studio with the lights off
Explaining how power outages are Act
Actually a globalist
Conspiracy really we
Had to get there hog scalar attack I would have scalar attack or what aliens if we're going to do
Globalist conspiracy
We'll get to the specifics of this but right off
The bad I wanted to explain why Alex feels the need to make this
Conspiracy
Instead of just being normal
Kind of thing you know you were human you accept it
Inclement weather happens
But sometimes it gets in the way
I have I have a reason I've got a he might want this to be a conspiracy
I'm just going to go with Mage mainly one of the large contributors to this
Disaster being so much worse
Is his state
Actually being interested in following the policies that he himself
Advocates
Number for off the list that was number four
The first reason is that Alex has a vested interest in infantilizing his audience
You need their critical thinking skills to be on a child's level so whenever he has the chance he
He creates childish narrative
When you're in bed and you hear a bump you can either think that it's the water heater or you could think it's a Viking
Who's invaded your house to come and get you
Adults are really capable you know they're ready able to reason it out
There's no reason of Viking would be in your home but for children
Reminds gravitate to the more exciting possibilities which is often nonsense
But it appeals to a particular emotional need in a drive
The children have
No ignition
Are are we is it around like
860 ad in which case
It is a terrifying time travel is possible
So I'm traveling water heater
Noises the water heater doesn't prompt an irrational response in
A person
They can ignore it or if it's a serious noise they can choose to call the technician
If you can convince people though that it's actually a viking who almost got them
You might be able to sell them all sorts of product
Vikings or even
Documentaries where you explain how Vikings operate and how to avoid their attacks lamp
Keeping the audience in a state where they don't deal with
The problems that the come up and
A boring but ultimately real way
And keeping them
Fixated on childish emotional interpretations of every step
Stimulus they receive
Is essential for Alex's business model
So even a giant storm can't just be a storm
Clearly an attack on
Conservatives
Absolute
The second reason that Alex has a strong interest in presenting this storm is some kind of an act of Foul Play is that
It's really
Something that just
Happens in nature and if so
He should have been prepared
For it
New brand has largely built around being a prepper type of guy so the first question that comes up in the case of his Network being taken offline
Find by a storm is naturally why weren't you
Prepared for that
Winter storm like this hitting Texas is obviously a very unlikely event
And something that the infrastructure was unprepared for
Play my heart goes out to everyone who's dealing
With the country
For Alex
The fact that he could be caught off-guard by a natural event
That's a contradiction of the way he wants the audience to see him
Then so obviously that's to be prepared for the literal end-of-the-world I would imagine that include some
Sort of the power grid going down
Your rights
You touched on the 4th one which is the state of Texas
To somehow they operate will talk about that a little bit down the line
The third issue is that a storm like this brings into
Some of the Elementals
The climate change conversation
But Alex doesn't want people to
Africa climate changes and weather events
Become more severe
They're going to TASC long-standing assumptions
Interest
Structure and how we built
Princeton
Houses are designed differently in different parts of the country
Like in California they prioritize Earth
Quake
Protection
Where I am
In Blake in Missouri where I grew up
Every single family home that you're going to find
Has a basement
Because of tornadoes
Right
Do you know basement or less prevalent in flood
Pro region
Florida is not known for having tons of basements that are literally underneath the
Yeah it as
So do you know
Different sorts of weather patterns and more severe storms hit different areas
You're going to see
Those things
Did the long-standing assumptions that we've had
Not be enough
To suffice
And Alex doesn't want the audience
About
Because it requires
Shipping ideas and paradigms and he's not it
Horse
I have plan
Here's my
Okay because as shifting weather patterns are going to test our assumptions and our architecture
What if
Now and hear me out
We got a lot of Real Estate
Now admittedly it is being held right now
But if you go underneath the
Get all right
No problems with weather issues problems with you know all that stuff
Dorm dare you knock out a few Nazis and then you got a home for life then there is essentially a city under
The Getty Museum if we are
To believe the people we've hurt
Problem
Face down there
Yeah
It's so
You know these are the kind of things that are essential for Alex to have his audience not
Wait this is a natural storm
This is this is bad but
You know you should
No middle
Was a possibility
You are prepared for this you got caught on
On your back foot
Weird
Maybe I shouldn't trust you about every
Instead of a conspiracy maybe go like milk
Conspiracy
Buy snow tires just in case
You know I kind of felt like that was the direction he was going to go on Sunday after obsessing about the like
The traffic
Yeah
But it turns out
Turns out
Did Alex
Is in the great reset
And that is why
The power is out Aiden for Studio
Our power has been turned off 40% of the state without power this morning
All the great reset
I told my wife
That this morning
History guy walks american-statesman admitting
Coal plants in Texas under Obama
The windmills in West Texas failed
Feel weaker longer
Rolling blackout
Because
Cole is evil
And we have to open the windows up to have light
They're going to give you a chair real quick
So Alex wants to pretend that the wind turbines freezing in Texas is what caused the blackout
But that is absolutely not
True
German article in Bloomberg
Quote well are uses for some turbines to shut down as the brutal cold wave drives record electricity demand
That's been the least significant factor in the blackouts according to Dan Woodfin
A senior director for the electric reliability Council of Texas
Which operates the states
Powergrid
The main factors
Frozen in
Instrument that natural gas coal and even nuclear facilities as well as limited supplies of natural gas
ESAT
The article goes out the hole is evil
The article goes on to quote Daniel Cohen
Associate professor of environmental engineering at Rice University you said that it quote
Is really a red herring
To blame renewable energy production
And for the blackout
If the wind turbines were operating at full capacity thing
Still be bad
Because the infrastructure of Texas power grid
And how was unprepared to deal with the weather event like
Alex doesn't want to address that
Point because it's real
And it requires calling in a technician
You would rather blame imaginary Viking
Yeah
Peoples of windmill
You have to pay for a technician you have to pay for maintaining your power grid
You have to pay for all of this stuff
But if it's the imaginary globalist somehow they're paying Alex
It makes perfect sense
Going to do it
So Alex doesn't
Quite understand the conversation that a lot of people are having surrounding
Climate issues
We've heard this kind of position be expressed
On when he was on Rogan
Gunshow
This idea is that like
Everybody wants like
There to be no carbon
Shore shore shore shore
It's very strange
Here we are
In the world
Carbon dioxide water vapor
Not even close
Texas
And they admit
The whole
This is green energy
But it's worth
This is the new Dark Age
Let's not
See that in the Austin american-statesman article
Just doesn't understand the issues of like
Excess carbon
Not like that there will be no carbon
Dockside in the world
I don't think that that to anyone
The Advocate
No it's a it's this is a this is a child going
Okay what
So I eat 35 apples a day you want nobody to have any apples
0 apples then huh
So you're saying I should have a moderate about
Q
Yeah take apples away from the honest working man
I don't know why that's a six-year-old kid but
It's creating a false argument
Yeah it's stupid
And that's because Alex is able to do that because he's a climate scientist
Just basically
It was a lot hotter in Alaska
Open tiny bit
Thank God that's us terraforming and a good wife
Wow
He knows a lot
He's he's very very insightful on these things
Yeah
Yeah that's not good
No
Also oxygen is
Specifically not
Gas
No it's
The chase guess there's only like what
Percent of oxygen in the atmosphere nothing
And saying that CO2 is a trace gases meaningless
What's in this contact
Goodbye because the message you seem to suggested that there's so little of it that we should just make more
That's dumb
Ammonia is also a Trace
But I think that Alex would realize you don't want a ton of it in the
The air
Because of obvious
Obvious reason
All right you're making a good point but have you ever walked near a volcano and just breathed in
Pure sulfur dioxide
Get your breathing real good you know that's what you want that
Gas we should limit the amount of sulfur dioxide
Don't you want to chew your air
So good that we raise the temp
So good
Terrible at this point if you're a climate denier it has to be like
I think I can wait out the clock
Rain
You don't like there's no way Alex isn't is it like at a certain point like
Oh s*** the climate really is f*****
I can't ignore this anymore
But I'll probably be off the air by the time people would have really hold me accountable for it
You know it could be I mean there has to be a certain amount of I'm not going to have to pay the Fiddler
NFL
There's another part
With Alex though I really do think that he is
Is just like
Dumb
He is just not interested in someone has explained it to him in such a way that like
Play the totally clean
And he's never seen fit to have to look into it
Cuz why
Yeah
I just don't know
How stupid do you have to delete be
To just believe that unlike a gullibility scale
I wouldn't trust a coal plant if I walked
Like the people who run cold
Demonstrable be evil and have been for 150 years
Insulting to politically aligned with the
The sort of things that Alex is into
You know generally higher
Yeezys he's inclined to
Even though
He does
F****** Darth Vader Impressions all the time
The dark side is the good people
So Alex is inside in the hallway at this point in the video and then he eating out Elder
We can go outside
I put go outside
Okay outside and show you
Bill Gates 12-quart block out the Sun and look where we're at
Freezing our asses off
21st century
He is not established
You did not demonstrate this in any way
No
When Matt Barnes
Real cool
Cool
Destroyed by Obama see it
The great reset
Or you could say those things but it doesn't mean it
No connection
Reality really Obama
The great resets fault Dan do you understand
Yeah
Sure
So Alex goes outside
And these just
The man yelling in the snow
He is hanging out
The snow backdrop
Being mad
I think this is really in
Interstate because
If you take him at his word he seems to be lamenting the Industrial Revolution
And how
How it made it so we don't have to make our own power or something that made us suck
Piety
Domesticated on the system
Are they pulling the gas station in a
Or they go to the grocery store today
Fresh food
Away from Atlanta
But at least I know that
I don't understand what he's
Complaining about
You're So Soft cuz we
Back there to be power when we
You know I've all agreed to collectively pay for a power come
Yeah yeah yeah
Hello Unabomber it's been awhile since we shared
No
I think it's far worse
Look if you if you and I want to say we're unaware that the technology has
Domesticated Us in weave
Moved away from the land
And then act like that that's fine but if we are aware of it and don't take steps to avoid it and instead only tell
Other people to do it
What are the critical pieces of s*** you recently listened to
Oh yeah absolutely his is pretending that like at least I know
Is yeah it does make it way worse
Yeah you should you should be
Putting out
Little tiny videos
Should be
Underground somewhere maybe
You want to join the land
Yeah if you want to broadcast
You should not ever
Have inclement weather getting away because you should have a ton of generators can you should be broadcasting from
Compound somewhere that no one knows where it is
You got a bunch of potatoes growing so you don't have to worry about anybody
Hello Unabomber it's been a long time since we've
It is strange
Hello there it is it's a really interesting thing
Alex is like Okay so
Are uplinks are in another state
So they still have powers and what we have
To do we have to shoot these little videos
And then send them over somewhere else
Men
You got an elaborate system to get like little tiny videos
Kind of
Yeah that's great
Yeah it's
It seems like you should just not do this
Take the day off
That's my feeling about it and the argument that he's making is so not come
Compelling that I don't even know why
Will you bother
Why try to make
Conspiracy
Stay-home
Yeah you don't need to risk
Yeah
Yeah but on the other hand he couldn't risk
Other people's lives and still probably make it to work
Which is maybe his favorite thing to do Dasher and I mean there's employees there to talk he's alone at the studio to so
Even better his wife is still playing tennis
Probably
Yeah
So Alex I think the reason he's doing this is cuz he wants to go out
Really saw this coming
He knew what was going to happen
Written about every
How do you think I can make a film
Blueprint for Global enslavement
And you watch the damn film almost all of his come true
Because almost
You deserve to have this done to you
They all have private jets we all got a bunch of kid they all have palatial Mansions they all live however they want
Yu-Gi-Oh
They're telling you
That's a lot of snow pulled out of his little brain
But like
This is nonsense
I'm starting to get feelings almost like Stolen Valor
On his bike his part of like being right about things yeah yeah
I resent that he's just pointing to endgame being like I was right about everything
You should go to re-watch your own work
This is not good
Here's the worst part
Okay
Endgame
Was it say a large amount about a road
Chat
Had it been built
Would probably of ameliorated a lot of problems they are currently experiencing
So Not only was he not right about that
It should have been built so he didn't have to deal with it today
I'm not positive that the road would have helped as much as you think
But it was a really big Road.
Pretty bag
And also Alex's does need to do this show not only to gloat about how he was right
So he wasn't
He also needs to make an announcement there are new numbers out
The new number
Do you want you know these numbers are
Quicken
Is working a new number
It's not.
It's not brand new numb
You misunderstood
Okay I'm not discovered a new number
I was just checking to see if maybe they discovered any number
I recognize that's a fair interpretation of what I said
To the globalist
Yeah long time they had claims of how many people they were going
Nikhil
Sure.
There's new number
Pretending like you're part of the establishment be going along with this
Over to get rid of half the world's population of 70
The good people she'll be around the Earth
What percent of world population
Call Teresa cell isolate
A culling program
They decided to
Dynamite
IQ ball
What's happening to you
What happened to you as it happened in real life
Scumbag
Chick-fil-A
Michelle
Lifestyle
Poster children commit suicide
Ruthless
Dominate control others and if you lay down to them
And that's why we need to primary week Republicans
I'm confused is this not okay
All right take back the house
This is so exciting
It's just nausea
Beautiful Soul Justin
Idiot standing in the snow yelling for no reason
It's kind of a preview of what his life is going to be like in 10 years the visual of it is really jarring
Because it is like I mean it's Alex Jones so like he's
You know this
It's notable Firebrand
Idiot
A complete imp
Videos showing
Because he's
Standing in the snow
Yelling about his animated
No he's leaving Nicholas preacher
Yeah but
How little
Importer meaning is there to him being like there's a new numbers
But ninety-nine percent of the population going to be killed
Okay now you can't
Make it smaller or they could be survivors number smaller
Like you have just backed yourself into a corner where it's like okay now
You're just making up numbers and now you've gotten to the end of the line
There's no more numbers
I like the idea that there are quarterly extermination reports
Every quarter there's new numbers like we were going to kill 99%
At the end of the first quarter but now rebooking things into the second quarter projecting a 97 Ford
Recent murder
Some weirdo like Daniel estulin
Call zalika Bilderberg they were saying it's 99 now
There was a faction
They were saying 98
But they lost to the end
Wealthfront
Call fell apart
Not to not to spend too much time
Talkin about why he's standing in the snow
Alex decides
BL about the vaccine
There is hope
That's why I said
Marquette
Get over it
Huge move that van they got scared
Australia vaccine that they put on a Chevy
Hy-Vee store
Yeah right
Most of that s*** we've covered in the past and episodes that's all nonsense
The India one that was a new narrative so I wanted to just
Clarify why India didn't approve the use of Pfizer
There's covid-19 back
Maxine
Is reported by CNBC back
February 5th
The Advisory withdrawn their application for emergency use of their vaccine in India after
Quote
The government in January approved
Too much cheaper shots
There were a couple of other hurdles namely that India requires local studies to be done to approve vaccine you
And studies advisors vaccine that had not been done
India
The second issue is that Maxine the one that they've created
Divisor one
It requires that words in very cold condition
Concern
About the ability for it to be rolled out all over India
Yeah there's there's
Concerned about the
Supply of deep freeze
Capabilities
Weather
I was just pretending they banded Peak
When in reality
Really just kind of a boring lives
6 issue
Again
This is a water heater noise Alex is trying to tell you is a Viking
Yeah that's it that's like crazy India they like listen guys we're going to have to ban the import of snowballs
Now I know they don't get far once they get across the border but we just can't let this happen anymore
Cheaper options that will do the same thing that a snowball doesn't
So Alex still
Being dumb
Starts talking about how
Texas Eustis
Supply everyone with power
In the summer in the winter
Credible job that we've been shut
That's a complete lie
Texas is it unique state in the country in terms of their power grid and it's actually one of the reasons
That the situation in the state now is so much
More complicated
Texas is the only state in the country that has its own
Completely autonomous power grid called
Which is run by the electric reliability Council of techs
Houston Public Media recently posted a very concise
Explanation of how the system works
And how it got the
Maybe the way it is which I will paraphrase
It doesn't and they f***** it up
When electricity started to become more prevalent the country saw utility companies begin to
Combine and link up
Regional
Things
In 1935f Dr sign the federal power Act
Quotes which charge the federal power commission with overseeing Interstate Ali
Electricity sale
The federal government could only really get involved with regulating interstate
Power exchanges
So in order to avoid that regulation
Texas has remained the only state in the country with its own power grid
This has been breached a few times notably a1976 when a Texas power company said power 20K
Oklahoma very briefly
And what's been called the quotient midnight
Connection
Alex is completely making up
But the state of Texas
Is formally provided energy 250
18 states
I suspect that he doesn't even know that his dates energy setup
I is the way it is and how some of the problems he's complaining about all these direct byproduct of his State following his own anti-federal
Government paranoia
It's kind of embarrassing
That he has no idea how it works
Because everybody else does
The differently it's
It's their fault
Together not knowing how he does
Yeah probably
You know
It's really it's really weird to me
Cuz like it should be a point of Pride to him
Babe the Texas dozen
Supply
Yeah to other states and other states
Why power to them
It should be like this
Rugged individual pre-industrial Revolution
Instead of mine our own call we burn our own call at that always f****** do
He's still he's instead choosing to be more attractive narrative to him
Which is that Obama made it so Texas doesn't Supply most
Of the country rap
Electricity
Somehow it still
The a Obama pro-coal
Kind of narratives
Take precedence over his
States rights
Jacking off
Like
I think that depends on the day 2
Probably
Yeah
I would I would also argue
In this circumstance
Alex is
I guess trap
You know like
Everything that he says is going to be wrong
Because the reality of it is like
This is all f***** up Beyond reason because
You know we made choices to
Get this place
I think that Alex might be literally trapped
As well
His wife might be driving the Audi
So he might be stuck
Studio
Like this well scream on the street I'm not going anywhere.
The five
Alex
Skip's to rambling
About some other stuff and I found this
Particular thought that he has a little bit
Upsetting this has to do with the storming of
The capital
Because the globalist
Fear what you saw at the Capitol
It was a few hundred that got the big Master do it
Globalist
Security standard
What they feared in
In the future
Could be discredited now
A million people
Okay so
What I'm hearing is
The globalist
Afraid of what
And on the 6th
And so they did.
The 6th in order to make sure that Alex
Couldn't do it better later
Yes
You are correct
What is exactly what happened
Gray
Alex's Alex's point I believe is that
A few million people
Over-running the capital
That's a
W guys that means we win this one a few hundred people with
Fox
So
Yeah I think he's really against
The principles of what happened at on the sick
I think I think it's at
I think it's become quite clear that now he realizes he's not going to get arrested or anything he can
Subtly
Just chill out
You know hey guys guys two weeks from now anybody not busy two weeks
That's where we got to get a couple million
So
We know that Alex is a scholar on the
Matter of
Carbon dioxide
July Matt James
WWII
Alex does he seems to think of this
Before and that's why I wanted to play this again
Because it's such a dumbass thought
That
I'm surprised he repeats the
Multiple times it's clearly something he actually believes
And that isn't that people are only afraid
Of carbon dioxide
Cuz it sounds like carbon monoxide
Oh boy
This is very bad
The sun is energy
Light
Carbon dioxide
Jenna Waters at Harborside
Very nice
No option
So what is it they attack
Carbon dioxide
Just sounds like Moana
Penn and Teller did it 20 years ago I did it 15 years ago we got to go out and do it again
You know I'll give you a people
The name of water scientific
Monoxide is everywhere is toxic
If you drink too much of addiction kill you
Even better
Table salt has a really scary name
Average
Person will come to you
Alex couldn't remember the name of
Table salt
Yeah I was going to say why didn't you
So proud of knowing what it is
Jordan I hate to say it demonic word here but
Sodium
Chloride get the f*** out
Crossed
The sign of a cross
Scandalized weather
I might be crazy I might be crazy but I'm going to toss this out for you Dan
Somebody who knows what dihydrogen monoxide is
Yet believes that
The president is secretly
Controlled by the devil
He's still dumber than somebody who thinks things are
What they are
But it's like
Just say what
Yeah that's my belief
And I think that you're leaving all that aside I know you may be right you may be wrong
My conjecture is
Anybody who thinks one of these kinds of
Studies of the public means anything
Is a dick
And they don't they don't have much going on
I mean you don't
You don't remember the greatest poster it before there was 538 then
Where was Jay Leno
All right or when you do jaywalking you get the right result
Yeah
I tricked you
Scientific tools
F*** you
Yeah
So we just got one last clip here and
I mean read the report ends with Alex sitting in a dark Studio
Internet
Actually ends with him yelling
About how the New World Order is going down
And just do visual of it of him
Sitting in a
Completely dark is like a review that is Andy Daly
Review it is exactly that
Guys where's everybody why is everybody leaving
What was going on
Yeah there's a guy didn't hate him so much there be a little bit of pesos in the moment
Of him sitting
Pacific you've got to destroy the public
I choose not to and re-up
Episode of that club because honestly it's angry
It's kind of funny
To think about but it
It's meaningless
Compared
To this
This clip
Fixes everything
That you need to know
I understand
300 books on
Correct
Doesn't read 100 books on Rome
Directions to fifty bucks on
British Naval History
U.s. history in the Revolutionary War
For five bucks
Civil War
Couple hundred bucks on globalism and
William zbigniew Brzezinski
Mouthwash
Nope.
Just because I have to
To get into it when I was like
9 years old
Shipperley
Call George
Crucifer
Potato chips
H off
Cuz the government shut the power off
Power plant
Yeah I think that's a good summation of Alex
Bragging about books he's read that he hasn't read
What what hundred books
Arabic class Schwab
I don't know just rambling about how well ready is it and he's not like normal people cuz he's
He's figured all this out
Because he's so smart and read all this s***
Atlantic
Completely derailed by a
Just a i a tattoo
Chipper lyrics
The greatest minds of my generation
Buy a little chip in the tooth
For want to do it
For want of a toothpick
The greatest minds of my generation
I've been torn asunder
Yeah
It's his
Bleak
Yeah that's not good
So I
Yeah I just wanted to check in with you and let you know how things go we're going for Alex and it turned out
This is how it's going
Last week last week I know of him at
At the time they were recording this he's just sitting alone
And I'd Ark
Studio
Santa
Notes no telling when he'll be back
I I do like the idea of somebody showed up at the office tomorrow turn the lights off in Alex's just
At the desk just like eyes haven't blunk
20 hours
He's actually wearing a tie is more put together than usual
By flooding the office for the first time in a long time
Feels really great
I didn't I don't know if you know this but you can read in the dark
Probably in better comprehension of stuff
Then he does
Guys I started reading book so with my hands even if they aren't in Braille
I'm figuring it out man
Did you know that
I didn't say all the stuff I said
No no
So you're really back
On Friday but until then
Highway website
We do have website its knowledge 5.com
We're also on Twitter
We are at her that knowledge unjustified. Go to bed Jordan
If you could please
Find a local charity or Bellefonte area to help out people
Doing God's work
Go back but until then I'm meiaum Leon dzx clerk I'm Daryl rundus
Hope the best for everybody
Going through tough times the weather all around the country
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work