Damn important
I have great respect for snowledge b b
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
A little bit about Alex
Everett
Jones
Jordan
West Jordan
Mochi
Do you have any other rice-based snacks that you appreciate
I do I do like cuz I haven't had any in awhile though
I did I was telling you about this like I've been trying to Branch out and try different types of rice
I'm kind of excited about that maybe that could be a bright spot right exploration
Capacitor gone down so far has been disappointing
I tried the Forbidden Rice yes it was not as forbidden as you might imagine.
From my kitchen
Exploration for the next
Stay Awhile
Why do people enjoy hearing about whatever like childish
Cooking Adventure but whatever Rabbit Hole Utah
Take forever for a few week whatever Elementary level cooking 101 s***
That would be more interesting if the word forbidden was
Just more apply to things
Suck
It's not forbidden cuz it's bad or evil is just bad
The black aboveboard and clear
It doesn't suck
I'm just not
It's not it doesn't live up to the neck
That's that the answer is
I don't actually know how to do it
The race itself is just
Whatever you expect a lot when something is forbidden Segal only the king should have this rice
Little bit
The forbidden
Tri-City is it just like f******
Detroit
Anyway right
I guess is my bright spot
My Brightside Dan is that approximately
4 hours ago by partner
Never got the second dose of the Pfizer vaccine
It is great news
So she'll be transport a transforming into a cyborg
Be dead within 15 minutes
What happened 3 hours ago and a half hours ago
Oh no that's not good
Congratulations
Everybody is healthy
Yep it's it's nice it's a it's a good little bright spot considering
You know
Shittily the teachers union
Is between you know like
Yep
We have an excellent episode to go over
Too early kid
You're like the guy with an AAS too early and Fast and Furious
Two cars racing and you just went
Too fast do I write to the barricades so I could slowly go around the
About you what you I'm always chasing you that's why you understand
Interesting
Which is a twin
Wednesday
And
I have some interesting thoughts about it I don't know exactly what was going on but he was able to Broad
The Studio's a bit dark
Sure there are lights and there's like focused on him. Like you sitting in a shadow
The giant million-dollar board behind him pays off
Okay
It's
It's bleak
It's interesting this said this episode is really f***** up
Sometimes when the
The vibe is this badge in the day off I would have advised
Basically by yourself I would have said you know call in
Don't do it to keep the flip side of the coin is it like necessity is the mother of an
Jen and Mike
Whenever your backs to the wall sometimes you f*** around and pull out
Something amazing
We've heard countless stories of that
How many times have you heard a stand-up talk about how like
It was the worst
Possible scenario
Sometimes
Cut out a few a whole thing then you comes out that you didn't know was there and
Derisory
That's not this I didn't think so
I was not expecting that
What could be wrong
To the occasion
I don't know
Anyway it's going to be a lot of fun
Overly white supremacist
Darkroom so you got to brighten it up
Somehow let's take a little moment to say thank you
Boca signed up and Reporting show
In Mike Tyson's voice
The in Mike Tyson's voice was not in parentheses so I'm not doing I'm not doing it
An impression
No certainly not you are not a policy wonk
Thank you to Dana for suggesting
To build to listen to this podcast very complicated name but Europe Asia Wok
I swear YouTube
Joke names and now we're just getting my driving balance it out
The demon deacon
Very much DD Wake Forest mascot
Yes I am fairly certain you know about Deacon Blues song by speedway
Steely Dan guy
No this is
Backyard name for the winners in the world
Call Alabama
Crimson Tide
Call me b
Okay alright
Do not missing the touch.
Scotch whiskey
Oh.
Steely Dan sounds like a little bit
I think Meghan has a better voice that I do like the Deacon Blues guitar
Hague
The Asia album is Aldi
What is pretty good
Boys but I'm insisting on
I'll calm them down with the boys thank you so much you're not technocrats
I am Jake
AKA Gibby
2 birthday
Happy birthday
You're not a technocrat alright
You are now a technocrat and I'd like to say hello
And good tidings to you and your family and your daughter
You're now also
Everybody's
Heroin
So good
Freakishly large
I didn't say I didn't like Steely Dan I'm just not a silly damn guy
Like I got into something same thing
I'm not in my I'm not yet 42 so I don't feel like it's the right time for me to get into Steely Dan
What's a Steely Dan
We have the same either with us
Cuz apparently I'm against you you were at the center
Check it out
I've never heard of Steely Dan song that I wasn't like
Black House guitar
Contact drops from today's show
I'll let you decide afterwards which you prefer option number one
And I'm just telling you what I really
Ultimate blackpill broadcast today
That is an
Accurate assessment of
He's very blackpill mood
Which is probably going to hurt sales of the real redpill she sells
What's good here is option number 2
Seattle Wash that Ass
What's it going to be
You do got to watch that you got to watch that ass over there's a part of you should try sell it
What kind of an untapped Market the black pill right it's real red pill gets you all that
Sold a pill that just gives you gives you like minor depression
Use a couple of days on the bed without
Liking yourself
I don't know if this is a good Market I think it would be best to avoid that that
That's great baby you'll be a prank
So that you get you know like it's a it's a white elephant gift you get the Jelly Beans
All right I don't know I don't know because
Okay.
So we start off the episode here and Alex is sitting in studio
Alone
Sad
No cool lights
Behind him
We watch that ass and I don't know
Kind of
I know he didn't
But this is responding to a question that we brought it
Hey man you're supposed to be the big pepper guy right it's going on here
You so much for joining us I have a skeleton crew
Unlimited
Our
Pain in the studio skier
I told people we should all take her vitamins being shaved
I'm pointing
Three fingers back at myself
Why the City of Austin was here two years ago in
Wouldn't give us the permits
For a full power generator system
That we wanted to put in here
And you can
To do that so we're just like the average function
Don't have power but my family doesn't have power
And so I've been going around dealing with frozen pipes and things like that
I'm not complaining
What's the red tape
I would very well may have been dealing with some issues
That's far from the only thing he's been doing well this winter storm is lingard in Texas
And apparently his family is without power
As it turns out in the middle of all this Alex decided to take a helicopter to Dallas
Sit down and get drunk
Can smoke cigars with Steven Crowder
While simultaneously complaining about cancel culture
And lying about what they do for a living
I wanted really badly to cover that interview for the show
Very stupid
It's behind a paywall
So kind of falls into that territory of things I don't feel right making content out of unfortunately the section they released for free
Free on YouTube
Kind of dumb it's not it's not worth it and
You and I were talking about this
How
Parable of a tease would it be
That is if we're promoting and then go listen to the last bit of their show I guess
We're not doing that s*** there was one interesting colonel in there though that I wanted to talk about
A lieutenant colonel there was a point where Steven Crowder was trying to help Alex sell his whole like I'm not left-wing
Or right-wing kind of Bona fides
And Alex said something that I thought was
Shocking and if
My mom's
Brother
He was involved
Contra
Text mother family
Humanity
Germany
8 years old
Stories
For me
I've got a group
The real world
Right and that other people are going
I grew up hearing about
So you're always more
You got lucky you didn't have a
Buffets reading
Right
Sitting
McGill ever decide call
You know they just all like
The Russians
America's going to win nuclear reactors and more weapons in them
People and I'm a grown up hearing all this
Go to college for America sucks
We're good I was
I'm going to join the Anaconda
You were going to
To fight against the
This is an interesting Insight does not complete idiot interviewing Alex would have heard that realize what can you do
This wasn't him saying but he's neither right-wing or left-wing he's just opposed
Communism
Alex is saying that a young age he decided to join the anti-communist movement
Any interview were worth a damn would have heard that understood what Alex is saying is that he's not a conservative he's about 1,000 miles to the
The right of conserve
Anytime you hear him criticize the right-wing like you did with George W bush
It's because
They're doing something that seems like something a Democrat would do so they must be a secret communist
Interviews of people at Crowder exist
Entirely to launder Alex Jones to a naive audio
Unaware of what actually being discussed
And getting them to think that he's
Cummaquid
Atomically Fringe right-wing politics that he has
Is actually somehow an expression of being above the two party system
Crowder's audience skews younger too so this is really an effort to mainstream like a zealot
Bigot like Alex to Children which
Steven should be deeply ashamed of
Being a part of
Yeah and also
F****** couldn't help it
So I decided I have a few clips
All right I needed to take a few clip cuz some of this is so embarrassing okay
All right really bad
This dumb s***
It starts at them sort of like Josh and around about Joe Rogan
You two guys
Talk about how's your friends cheat
Completely separate show
Steven Crowder as a baton
Broken show in like 3 years and I have never met back
Other close friends with the famous guy do I do find it fun when it's just like
No
Talk about the third person who's
Constantia Lemoore famous route
Did they start talking about butts
Describing
The Rogan Studio as being like the intestine of a whale or whatever
Talking about the digestive tract
I need to take a piss
Does a bush right there right now in a whale
Large intestine
Well I don't
Psychologist sounds
What what's the largest
Let's move on
You have the mouth
You have
Esophagus
The object
What is the small intestine
Oh yeah that's right
Then you have a small intestine
Largent
McCullen been erected
The anus
No the rectum
Smart the large intestine
I could do that
Call Lynn
Schoolhouse Rock
I think I missed that one
Connected to
Large intestine
Bills
Can you imagine
We cannot let jump
That's
Because you've been
Am I go through years
People here on YouTube
People were born
Put on YouTube
Defensive at all
But
What's that what kind of
Interesting to me is
Back in the day with
Mytalk radio
Anything's got a logic
Another word you can say that guys are
Or adopt
You can't say
My rectum
Anything is considered like
Potty
That's just such a great example of crowder and Alex pretending they're like this conversation they're having about that
The practice going to get them sensor
There's no reliable conservative media system they rely on this pre-emptive complaining
It's something that they haven't even released yet is going to get censored
Would be censored in a certain context nor give them the pretense of credibility
It's so edgy man it's kind of
Get banned before it exists
Tattoo
That's such a great observation that
Patton Oswalt made better 20 years ago and didn't make it about
Cancel culture
Wheelchair whatever interesting
Tonight is next clip here is a it's a one of the three of us needs to be hit with a meteor and I don't care which it is
After listening to that s***
One of the three of us
Got to go
Cooper from this that I was really funny where Steven Crowder was talking about how he got into what he's doing because conservative comedians weren't funny
I'd like to play back that Clubman
Look I see a lot of stupid s*** but I try.
Short you know I don't go in till like now let's get into the order of how stupid s*** is
And then trained
Effortlessly or effortfully weave it into cancel culture
F*** yourself by butts on the radio to show any time a kind of
Gross s*** you talking about a f*** if you're going to talk about being
Sensor jerk
Losers so was poorly timed and completely not true
Free-will Rush when he had the
Magic negro song member that he was facing the LA Times
Yo-yo
Censoring
Wouldn't do that
So hearing that
This is this is the laundering of Alex Jones is Persona on
Platform his racial humor may actually have been what finally did
Russian
There's actually no way to know for sure but 13 Lieutenant Colonels have actually told me that that is what happened
Like you said doesn't like that him right he's got to stop doing Fentanyl
This next clip is Alex carrying on his great tradition of outing his secret sources that he claims he never out
Because confidentiality is super important to him
Can't tell you who
And I was Don Jr who's at Saoirse
Please write lawyer
Great American
It was Trump and Rodger Stone
Nothing
Put out the story
CIA
And all that stuff
Crazy
Even though he made up
That my dad just decided
What they said
You can't Ted Cruz love Trump
And do all that
When they were the ones that gave me the store
To be fair you might have
Giving it more legit
That's not funny
That's not funny that's a tragedy you're just describing a
Tragedy
Hypocritical douchebag
Friend flash guest
But I'm kind of unclear if Alex is talking about just like
I will cover and pretend anything that's Trump and Rodger say is true
He said therefore I made it news
Or if it was
Like they had
Some kind of a plan and they were
They were discussing this
Conduit
To Alex
Here's a story for you
They gave me the story he's literally describing
Them saying we want you to
You spread this lie
That's campaign-finance
BECU
Might want to ask
So this last Clippers Larry's
Because it really demonstrates a little
Steven Crowder cares at all about accurately presenting the person he's talking
To to his audience
Your audience is loyal and even with this word
I know it's probably
Negative what you've talked
Clock to support
Because you have been people have to say to
It's about you
You know when don't do it
What do they disagree with you or
Goddamn
No matter what you think about Alex what do you like him or not the last thing you should say about him is that he's
You can say
That's the last word I would use
To describe this dude who makes up
She had all the time and flip-flops on anything whenever it becomes inconvenient for him work more convenient say something else
What happened to the globalist
Plan B
What happened to Alex's post DUI Crusade
Clear the names of all the people who've been wrongfully
Convicted of drunk driving
What happened to all of the friends we don't talk to anymore cuz they didn't like Trump enough
Maybe my favorite example of this in recent history was have toward the beginning of the covid-19 pandemic
Alex Miss read a headline about the then fairly unknown dr. fauci
Hames Alex decided to report this whole thing about you being a brave person inside the government
Blowing the whistle on how the virus was all a sham
How it's going pretty looked
Send the falchi teammates
Calls about him he was the real deal
Within days after you become the villain in the right-wing media and Alex pretended that whole thing about him looking into him and seen that he's a
The real deal
Does not consist
That is work is meaningless
Internally self
Contradictory at many points
What is branding is that of a guy who's consistent and he's right about the Bedrock stuff
That's why Steven Crowder is presenting him this way
Because he's trying to sell Alex's branding to his audience
As opposed to dealing with who Alex actually is a person
And what is show is actually like
Someone like Crowder is
Is actively doing car but this kind of s***
Like a way less talented Joe Rogan who by definition of his lesser Talent attract an audience that
Gullible or a mature enough to think it poo poo and pee pee jokes
And that all you're doing is creating a false image of who Alex is
I wouldn't even be all that surprised
If Steven Crowder is so God damn cynical that he didn't even know what Alex's show is like
He just hung out with him a couple times and assumes like
Oh he wouldn't be the kind of guy who yells about the hood devil all the f******
Time
And talks about
People eating poop on his show
No
Yeah it was it was a pencil
I just wanted to cover a couple of those little Clips kind of presentation of him is like
Some sort of elected official
Completely and utterly bungling
Health crisis
And then writing a ghost writing a book
About his leadership
I didn't cut out this clip but on this February 17th episode Alex reveals that Cuomo spends most of his time
Time chained up in a sex.
Bats
Better than what he does
I would prefer
Where is that it's come out give me a governor
Who spends more time in a Sex Dungeon then doing evil s*** like him my problem is
Sporting Heather 36 -
Slants to it that's
Recognizes the show a little bit.
You complain a little bit
Valerie just can't stop thinking of like
What is Lori Lightfoot had a big
Scandal wears like she spent 240 million dollars on a Sex Dungeon
Of course you do you don't give it to the
F****** cops
Alex
The broadcasters just doing a little bitching
Because
Z
Information is so heavy the information
I forgot it so insanely intense
I'm going to be covering here today
Broadcast you from a building with 9% except for the studio
We got three generators running just to keep this going 24 hours a day
Bring you this information this is the end
Publix
The end of the country the end of the world as you know it
This is the global extermination plan
Power there 24 hours a day or not at the studio
Save some of your money
Maybe
Use those generators to help out all those people you know you can use generators to help other
Rife
I don't know it's a little bit confusing
Becomes more and more confusing as the show goes along like
How much power do you have what is going on
Yeah okay
He's talking about you know Q or not
Right remember qanon
There is a thing in qanon where they were talking about like the power's going to go out and that's 12
And the hit teams are going to round up the backyard
No no no no
No right right the opposite is true
Now there is a black out there power out in Texas
And now
The right-wing is being rounded
I also noticed everything you said was the enemy bracket was the
House of Sauron
And when the
When the lights go out
SWAT team until around people out
Oh yeah
President
So there you go ladies and gentlemen this is a hellish situation
I would like it
Play hit teams
Yeah
Also howdy
What what
Happening
You just got into the office on a day with no one has any f****** power
300 text messages I'm being rounded up
Isn't this awesome and it's also a little bit
A problem
Through his whole life
Everybody is going to have no power here I am broadcasting live on my show
Whatever like
I don't know the apocalypse over the great reset is happening obviously I'm still broadcasting and nobody stopping
If I were him
I probably would
Think that it would be better to broadcast from home
Whatever is Lo-Fi as possible like we're in the bunker We're All in This Together would be a
Very nice sentiment seems a little strange too little too late but it would be nice
Through something really severe
To be like well you know my big problem is my warehouses close
Somebody made me cut my vacation short
America Has Fallen
October Baby
So America Has Fallen
America is gone America is dead and only admitted any chance of turning around
We are now completely overrun the FBI's completely paid off and he'll honor The Dumping really
I just feel like you'd hear that stuff and if you out if you believed any word of it why would you
Follow any laws why why would you feel behold into any form of
Social contract
And why wouldn't you possibly for one second
At least
Think to yourself
Okay
This is the result of me supporting every politician that I've ever supported
This is the
Literal
Inevitable result
Of everything I've ever believed
Sure
Yeah
A moment Not For a Moment do you think all this sucks
Done that
Oh no infrastructures crippled I probably shouldn't have supported the party that hates
Yeah so
Is Dennis McClure if we get to the the little bit of the beginning of Alex's
Little angry 20in to white supremacy or
He's talking about Mark Zuckerberg Zuckerberg
Theo talks about how we're fighting WWII with
This virus right
And it's true that is true
Okay
When he says virus
What he actually means is
White male
Christian
Explain something when you come back to the next track
If this
Everything with them is actually a truthful statement acceptance inverted
We're fighting equivalent of World War II
10:00 coming up
Find equivalent of World War II
The virus is
World War
Climate changes is like
What he says were fighting the virus you're the virus
They called human overpopulation and
Free Speech everything
And Christians
White male
The virus
I'm sorry you song by Bill Gates
Also
So that's the virus is straight
Males Christian males
Straight white males
Christian being something of a tox
6 presents
I don't know if I would describe them as a virus
No I think it's I think that even joking around there is
Is is a is a little bit iffy
When the evangelico block votes 90% for Trump
I think we're good
But that.
I don't know if you got it really parse out
Sure you're close to justifying Alex's narrators
I'm partying I didn't say they were a virus
You can solve toxic presences with things other than
You know
His plans
Okay
So remember Enron
Energy company remember address
Hanalei
Navigate dude yeah a real real example of late-stage capitalism
What happened
I don't know I
Not bad enough things I suppose
I don't really be able to go on trial I don't know anything about Kendall
Okay
Actually practiced
He fixes that
Cuz he came up with the garbage
You knew that right
Kim Lai
Then we already committed suicide
House arrest of them
What has he done in Paraguay
All this works lazy Jones got study
Aldi's boys operate
How they do it
The thing I think is really interesting about that is
The juxtaposition of Alex saying
Word is he's down in Paraguay
Cersei as if it
It's facts qanon people are
F****** crazy with this
Kennedy junior is going to find you and help you in any way
Out there
The word is
Does he have a lot of Paraguay and blisters
Yeah probably
Support
Info Warrior
So Alex
Is talking about China
Complaining about
I'm going to be honest this is a little bit my ear a little bit racist
Alex is going off on a little bit of a Jag about how
You know there's
More Chinese men in China than women so they
Sports
Man to other places to get
Brides in other countries
Interests of implying that it's like
Exporting people in order to make the world Chinese f***** up and weird
I'm in the middle of it
Text a situation you go find a wife out east and you bring her back to Oregon
The middle of this
Kind of disgusting weird Jag Alex
Get some bad news
A one-child policy to where there's probably
100 million more boys in China
Then there are girls so they export Chinese man to colonies and tell them get an African wife
They export American Wife
They
Forcibly rape
The weaker women
To forcibly make them Chinese instead of
Which basically is Chinese
The dark Daily's gentleman
Play the squip a moment but
This is all being done on purpose this is rubbing our faces in it
And we got another bad piece of nose
He wasn't
Wars
What wars but he wasn't American and he was loyal the country he meant well
Fought the Communists Rush Limbaugh
Dragon radio host dead at 7
But it's another disgusting sickening omen
Bbbb
Oh God
So Alex is not happy about this news
Disgusting Oma
It's strange
A little bit
Curious bedfellows
Considering
In the earlier times of his career Rush Limbaugh would have been an enemy
And somebody who was
Kind of like the
F****** shity globalist right never
Ellen Trump times you know Berlin bottle of trump so
The two of them
Well they reached a little bit of an understanding
Silly
Albert Alex is Rick consist
Yeah the
The Winds of hatred you are very
That's very much is dead
And
Alex pays him quite
Quite a tribute
This might be
Send.
Careers
Immediately after Alex reports
The news
That Russia's.
Radio host dead at 7
There's another disgusting sickening omen
I've learned 47 ago my guts never wrong
The United States is facing
Destruction
Are you saying he was murdered never been wrong
I keep having very intense nightmares last month
Going to be hit by nuclear weapons by China
Care about your dreams
Stop having sweet before bed
Oh your powers off
Approve that coming up
Just getting this ready for the disasters I'm going to hit the main city
Samantha military bases
That's why they want to keep
National Guard in d.c.
Shut off
And they say
To go through it
List of who
They're going to kill right away though they're not funny
If you don't want to stay and fight this I would have a q18 onstage right now
Very good chance that they're going to either blow the entire power grid with an MP's
Short definition for organism the first dry
Ocean's 11
Dover it's gone
Trump has removed of course he wanted a giant landslide
Press secretary in all by the people they are scared
I've decided I'm going to eulogize rush by making up scary bulshit
Yep that was a good must tell you
China is about to Nuke how do you say that is a fitting send-off for that's exactly what you should do
Call Diaz Rush
In your honor
Bulshit that are alert
Kind of defiance Alex's mood for a bit
Michelle it's over man Alex
I'm just going to throw this out there
They are shutting off power
On purpose
What if
They weren't allowed
To do that
What if there was some sort of like
Thing
That the law and I'm not saying that we have to give it a name cuz I think names might be a problem for Alex Alex isn't into
The label what if there was like a it like hey
This is a law that says you can't do that despite you being a private companies
Suggesting something that would regulate behaviors of company
I feel like I'm playing operation
Mode
It's over man America
Cuz f****** done
Rush was the last call I got together
Skip back to where I think this is overtly whites
Supremacist
Be honest with you okay
It's all are about to be hit with nuclear weapons of the military stood down everything's going
Sorry it's over
Queen
Death-stars warming the planet
Velocity we don't stop
Elections for a reason
Veterans are terrorists for no reason
Under the Chinese regime poster going to take all white men in Berea education
And then we every other group after that
Because they know that white men coming from a Scottish Irish English what are we doing their tradition
And the austro-hungarian empire
Notary services operations were own
Men
The mercenary
British Isles over tribalism
Who went
Really came from folks that you're ugly
Dalton's on Ireland
All the freedom come from
Oh boy
Okay so I'm going to be real with Alex I don't
Think he really read anything
That the founders Road
No I don't think so either
And Irish were fighting
For a while and they came over here and democracy happened I don't know what's wrong with you all Freedom flows from the
BB the Riverhead of white man that is everybody knows
Freedom originated in England
Whenever they travel to Africa in order to sell human beings America
Freedom
Sort of mainlining and supporting this Steven Crowder
I hope you're proud you promote somebody who has these kinds of ideas but they disseminate on their show
As we all know Freedom only comes from white men
Wow coming like
Such an interesting division that I find with his sure like a lot of the time is very much white identities very much like
Implicit bias and like
No clearly racist positions
That's why
Supremacy
Percent Beyond
It's saying that white men are supre
The only
People who have ever thought freedom is worth anything
Only white man ever had that thought
It's
It's a b it's pretty it's like shocking it shocking to see you
And how things are run
Only white men
I never considered that.
Deserve
I don't know I guess tributary kind of argument that woodspring off that that River
Is
That anytime
Anytime to raise actual movement towards freedom
It's got to be white people doing it for the only waiting on white people can really be involved
Follow whatever the white people that they call white men in order to run
Operation
Yeah you know how white men often promote Freedom throughout the world so many times
White man go all across the world and just promote the f*** out of freedom
I think that this might be a half thought through thing of Alex's
It might be something that's more emotionally felt
For him could be
Am I come from the place of white supremacy that is deep within
His white heart
I would say in his mind
The only freedom is the
The freedom of white men to do whatever it is they want and that freedom does only come from WakeMed
So I will give him that
You've made an interesting argument
Alex has problems with his staff
Not actually
He likes the staff
The look
This guy his longtime producer
Hey sister
She's weird and I just told you if you're a good listener you think I'm joking her
Oh yeah he loves you
I have a
Longtime producer hear the oldest employee here
17 years
You slowed Minnesota
Good detail
His sister
Pledges allegiance to Gigi
Does she
Mainline in Minnesota
Pledge allegiance
Gigi pip
It does sound right
Think I'm joking
The Washington Post
Roy Donald Trump to save America
Wow
This is what they do in Minnesota
It's just me
Obviously my producers sister
Pledges Allegiance is you paying because she's an academic and if you want proof read the washing
Which I assume must be about his sister had let I can't even really remember and I
You didn't read the article
The Washington Post
These listeners who are like in the middle of nowhere and Alex's
Yeah trust me
Academics in Minnesota all pledge allegiance
Find Jesus man
It's it's kind of like whenever you were in elementary school and you'd be like talking to somebody and maybe like
Yeah I have a cousin who's in France and they all eat bugs there
What are those things that other 12 to go to France
It's one of those things your dad tells you and then you tell everybody at school and everybody's like
No
I truly believe anything your dad says yeah
Speaking of things that I tell you that you shouldn't believe
Alex has a little bit of a Humdinger about his dad
Dangerous people
CIA definition
You know there's their types
Short
Nice friendly little.
Usually
Dark hair
Play my way
Two of the things they're looking for our physical characteristics
Stiff to be short and have dark hair
What the f*** are you
If you're looking for the Ubermensch they need to be short with dark hair I don't understand
That's what they're looking to do
Recruit
CIA dentists who are short and have
Dark hair
It is a pretty CIA Dentistry
Cuz he was just coming out of high school
The globalist really watermakers I was short
That's a little bit
That's a little bit like I yeah yeah
Stop short guy
Very stupid
Is a very dumb
So what are they
Through-line
Narrative kind of things that Alex is going on about on this episode
He's that Biden head of town hall the night prior
Apparently during this town hall he had endorsed
China's actions
And also about the weaker
Here's Alex playing necklace
Here ladies and gentlemen
Is Joe Biden endorsing
Communist China's death camps
And take over
Militarily
Unhhhh
Believable in your face
Treason
Over the top
You know about Chinese history
It has always been the other time when China has been victimized by the outer world
Is when they haven't been unified at home
Central Pro
The central principle
Is that there must be a United Italy control China
And he uses his rationale for the things he does based on that
Hi-Point no American president can be sustained as a president
If he doesn't respect
Values in the United States
And so the idea I'm not going to speak out again
What he's doing in
Hong Kong
What are you doing with the uyghurs in Western
Mountains of China
Find new Taiwan trying to end the one China policy
By making a forceful
I said but he said he
Culturally there are different Norms in each country
And ignore leaders are expected
Directions to follow
He said I'm not going to criticize it like he was saying you would criticize it
Chiquibil lawyer crap
Okay
There are plenty of reasons to critique Biden about his town hall from the other night but this
Is a complete
Misrepresentation that will drive Mustang
Anderson Cooper asked Biden about his conversation with G came up and
Quote we must speak up
For human rights
It's Who We Are
Alex plays
When you talk to him though about
Human rights abuses
Is that just
It is that as far as it goes in terms of the u.s.
Where is there any actual repercussions for China
Reply
Quote well there will be repercussions for China and he knows that
What I'm doing is making clear that we in fact are going to
Continue to reassert our role as spokespeople for human rights at the UN and other agencies that have an impact on their attitude
He's trying very hard to become the world leader and get that moniker
And to be able to do that they have to gain the confidence of other country
And as long as they're engaged in activity that is contrary to basic human rights
It's going to be hard for them to
To do that
Wasn't endorsing any of the actions of the Chinese government He was discussing the more nuanced approach to international relations
Then Trump was capable of
Alex is playing selectively edited clips
The treatment of the weaker people and all this is just not
True
Even in that clip is him saying
I have to respect them and their culture but at the same time
I'm not going to not
Speak out
I am literally saying I'm not going to avoid speaking out just because I have to respect their, and you can
You can take that clip
And get like
You would just enough
Turn off of there too
Spin it into
I don't know why he left that second part in there
Of course I'm going to speak out about human rights abuse he is a little bit strange
I don't know
Edit the clip better
Eviler
Yes powers out man that's fair
Do you know everyone loves that Biden is come out and he said the
The China can do whatever it wants and it's open season or whatever
He's not the only North American leader who is recently Ted's
Who else recently all the prime minister of Canada said
Women
That really excited so manly
He said
I like the Thomas Chinese system of total dictatorship
I like I like
And the women just like squirming and in their seats and just wiggling around
Where at
Immense
Woman's gentleman club when he was little bear
They were just jiggling and snickering and
Hopping up and down
It's so sexy have death camps
Small point
Alex is making up all that stuff about women squirming and being sexually excited by Trudeau's comments
That's just a product of his own
Curvy and very weird imagination
That clip just makes me want to be like
Wrong with you
F***.
It's an interesting question of whether he's just making that out because he wants the audience to think that
Or is that
Really his experience of
Watching a clip like that
Gross grocery Grocery
Yeah but how much of it is like
Actual and how much of it is right for me
It's for the audio
That part I have no idea
Either way it's f***** up that's f***** up anyway also not for nothing that video that he's referencing like
Recent
Content of it Shoreline weather
Context of it and wasn't it like 2 years ago through 2013
What do the prime minister in 2030
So with a guy like this who's this accurate
Straight shooter and consists
Yes
You might be surprised
To learn
I think Alex is having some money troubles okay
Around here goes all Alex don't worry
People going to give up
What is gray matter
Is it
Interfaces
I'm telling you
That that that
That you
Better get right with Jesus
Military Tycoon
The living snot out of their kill
Military
Veterans
Sure
The average American is a cowardly attack of demonic devil worshiping garbage
Your neighbors will watch the NFL while your ass is drugged out.
Raping you and you're going to find out now
They're going to rape you and enjoy it
Do you want to fund this we can stay on there if you knows how long
The propur
$50 off
Willow
Is
Holyshit
If you don't bite
Tide they will rape you
Your neighbors are watching your neighbors will watches your house is bombed
The other way to stop it is to keep my bulshit on air
Yeah alright whatever
Cloud
They're real real human beings who
Need to listen to that s***
No
If I would say
Every single human being on the planet
God that's so
Do you know if
Everybody did
Come to the show
Said no one would know that it's
Confirmed
It's official
Hundred percent 100
Satan is real
Now explain to you again
Squilliam
Athens to high
When we didn't start standing up for other people and our children are old people
Protection has been lifted and God is going to let Satan
Literally
Annihilate us
So I hope
Everybody enjoys
This kind of characterizes quite a bit of the show
Kind of fitting in another galaxy sitting in a dark Studio of course Satan has gotten
Control and God's going to let us
Destroyed
50 by the Khalifa It's but it's a little it's a little exhausting
I dare God to let Satan
Kill all of us
That is that is humorous that you are like cigarettes
I am fine with it I'll get up
Next to that
Comes before the fall I will not join you in this
Because it's really a scent Alex's real
I mean you don't make up numbers like a trillion
To do I think that's the exact type of number you makeup
Here's some more stuff it's getting made up
Jcu in advance
Because Alex uses that word you hate
Discernment yeah that's the one
He has that
If he uses badly I'm going to lose my s*** and he has this discerned
Right but the other side has something that
It's kind of like
Crystal balls it sort of works palantir if you will
Sickening
Deferment
Has a large understanding of the space time continuum
What long-term very accurate predictions that are
Almost
Future
Crystal ball
Real man
That's what you got for me
Crystal Ball but not foreseen
Basically
Most of what
Has already transpired
I can tell you things are not going good for Satan
So also now now we're not just
Applying Satan
As a malevolent Force
It's designed to torture us and sent by God
Phil is playing
Now we've got a Satan
Who also is like
God dammit guys
I need better help things are going well
Crystal ball
All the time
What is a good crystal ball
Got to put a part in Middle manager Satan I feel like
Is Alex would just write this as a comedy show like it would kick off
Overworked under supported devil there was a cartoon man your brother
I would almost guarantee that semi I was watching
It got super mad about
Programming
Tunes
Alex's in-studio is able to broadcast
Then like I was watching a bit of this as it was
Aaron Seuss live
Yeah
Cameras look good
The lights look good
The only difference really
Is that
Fresno
Cool
Backdrop sure
But you running it half
Alec is capabilities
Sounds like well you know
Bad storm
Make sense
It turns out that's not why though he's an idiot
Let me show you some of the history of this
Mostly
Because we have a generator but not wired internet
Probably failed
Like doing the Quan
Pride
So you have the generators you just know how to plug a Madman amazing
Microcosm of conservative
Leadership
Well
We have the stuff
Cuz we were told that it's a good idea to have the stuff
But we didn't prepare and we didn't hook it up correctly. No one here knows how to use
And instead of being able and capable
Creative
I quit
Yeah cool quite a bit about quitting
He's not giving anything about it
People say that he's giving up
He's not
You giving in
Security stole the election why didn't he have to campaign
Why do you tell
A group of people to Rally
I don't need you to win
Telling you
Because they're trying to demoralize us and destroy our morale facing
Humiliating us like this will make us give up
Really
I'm not giving up I'm giving out
Okay
Horses from carrying too much you want
You know how serious this is
You want to go off the air
You want to just shut it down
Because you people don't get serious and understand what that means I'll never sell off the bubble
But a certain point ladies and gentlemen
There's on the serious people around me
This Crew in here cuz they work with me they're great
Nobody else I know
Doesn't give a rat's ass and what you just sit there and watch people
Everyone needs vitamin D3
Wow
That's that I would I would have I would have preferred if that Springsteen commercial was like
Concentra Lamar
There's a town
And if you don't want everyone
Y'all better come to IHOP
Discord
Goddamn car
I wrote
Born in the u.s.a.
Afford a bomb
Text me I can afford this commercial and I can afford the bomb of threatening you
That also characterizes Alex's show this week
Yeah
We're all going to die unless you buy s***
Howard's
Who don't have the balls to step up
Do what needs to be done
You coward like the idea that there's not enough serious people around. The only way you could be serious as by Alex's
Yeah
That seems like a trap everyone he knows for Nabi
Big dumb enough to buy spills and so now the show turns
Takes a little bit of an interest
Alex gets hungry
And so they're sitting in this darkened Studio
Samantha breakout survival food
Oh boy
Studio
Texas gun as restaurant fettuccine alfredo
Pair with aleks.com
Good it's
Alfredo
Goddamn
Alright pretty great
Good-looking commercial for Thanksgiving dinner of survival food like that
Near the dark Studio
Fettuccine alfredo is a little too soon
Good
Yep so now
Compounded my issues with what is working there and what is not sure
Alex takes phone calls
Hard-working
Don't know what is I don't know it's very strange for that s*** you just connect it
They might have not
Been able to plug in the thing that blocks really scary collars is a prophet
Sequoia take
For the people of this country to wake up
Your nation is judged
You have been found wanting
Information for you Alex
That is imperative
I can't get into it over line
I'm going to tell you right now
There are
60 million
Live stats
Right now
All I'm asking for you is fit
15 minutes of your time
If I give you this information
And you hear it
You'll note the truth
And it's going to answer a lot of questions
But you have had
That you have not been able to get answers to
I'm a man of God
I'm a prophet of God
I'll get your info but I mean here's the deal everybody always used to talk to me privately
Make it on there but
I think this is judgement I'm not talking to you I'm not giving you 15 minutes
Excuse me sir I know
It's
Yellow bottom profit millions are going to die
You sound silly with the star of the show
You're just
The guy calling in
That's that's what kind of like
Can hit my ear really weird is like
How is that any different than the stuff Alex
I'm not really I'm always Blown Away by how local everyone is like
360 million lives are at stake
Globe is interconnected I get that you guys want there to be nationalism and ship but even in that way
World globe is interconnected if 360 million
He was saying that it's all
Just the United States
I could be all over the
Alright
GreatCall doesn't go well
Alex gets another call from a guy and I'm not going to play this cuz it's
Who cares the color is just he wants
How to plug the Philadelphia Church of God which I look into
Church of the sound about the teachings of Herbert Armstrong
Coach Isaiah guy was a noted preacher of British Israel is underwire
A church was started by a guy named Gerald flurry the prophet and the trap was a god-ordained ruler battle happen
So he calls in to promote that I was watching
Temperatures
Anyway
Alex gets to this is an interesting thing
They came up
Alex believes in weather weather
He believes that the globalist
Can control all this stuff
I'm so he has this
Too complicated position he's
Presenting that is
Did the Goblins do this
No
What could they have
Yes
Is it wrong
Song for me to ask questions
No
So
It's alright
It's strange
And then wouldn't you know it
He has all the evidence
Prove
Did they can do all day
Storms
Everything
Scarce
Can't find it
Bad luck bad luck for us it was 20 years ago or sub I got contact
Air Force director of heart civilian head would like to come on the show
Call because he heard General
Ignite the apparatus room fire
The
The Arctic blast south of they wanted to
Air Force I got real mad. Alana to the interviews over during the break and hung up on me
Interview it was a big interview
That was so big we lost sub
I couldn't find it and I've never been able to find
Damnedest thing
Well not everything
Something
Oh boy
I'll wait for him to produce this
Yeah anytime now
Not going to wait
So we know from listening to this episode that the Alfredo
If Zimmerman hadn't cooked it al dente
Amazing
Alex
PizzAmore survival
Call them this morning
Macaroni and cheese
Speak of the devil
Macaroni cheese
You are not going to eat that.
10% off they were under special for a long time
We'll get back to this here in a second but this either implies that Alex is just doing this to look Beyond
Camera eating
The food sounds like
They don't have feeling portion
I don't know survival.
Not like to make a big deal out of this company's different than the others cuz it's going to 1,000 calories
That's the other ones are like 1,000 calories
They had themselves in years in a bunch of cells last year
This is a huge deal
When it was coming
The price of food could not last
This low rate for much longer and now even Major Brands like Kraft Heinz
ConAgra are announcing plans to start
Food cost on
To you
America's Nationwide becoming
Where are the empire
Global pandemic
For Statewide outages
Powergrid
There has never been a better time to stock up a furball food while you still can
We are
Leaving
Food line
In Texas
I talked to
About 3 months ago
And I said please write this up
I guess this was written hastily so I can't really understand this but
Gentleman
You need to get
What's going on
How are they supposed to write that up in the dark while they're cooking you food
NASA
What if I could ask a better than O'Reilly's
This is a daily occurrence
Does not work
Crumple it up to
Open Oma's to rush
Paper crinkling noises Omaha
Another call from a guy
And unfortunately in the process reveals that he knows literally nothing
How about the power situation in Texas
Sure
First-time caller from Arkansas do you have power outages are
As well as the country
What does ercot stand stand for in the burkot
I think the the T stands for
Everybody everybody electric reliability Council
Everywhere
It is defined by not
There's the power Consortium on the left it on the West Coast
The East Coast
And then
Texas is ever
So I would say that whenever you hear somebody say something like that
Imply that they know nothing
About the issue they don't think about the structure the infrastructure the the way the power is
78 at around 1
You can strongly in further
Until whenever like Alex tries to sum up his feelings
About the storm that made the electricity issues like
Just go ahead and toss it out like he did that badly written
Copy
They did this on purpose I have family
What used to run power plant one on the dead now
Intuit
Calder
In Houston
Told others this is all fake to jack up prices
This means nothing
Literally just saying nothing in order to make more interesting stories for his audience to
I have then
Hey poorly-managed
What else is your family done
Everything on contra
Everybody's done I drag everyone on the right data recovery everyone that was like
Crowd of being part of like I was part of Iran Contra you know a good thing
Me and Ollie's
He's the f*** around it was a good time
Yeah I don't know it's all very stupid
I did I did find
This a little more interesting than some shows
Recently
There is at least one
Appears to be
A shift
Happening
And maybe I'm just tricked by the fact of the studio was pitching
I think there is a little bit of that just like
This is at least novel
Yeah
It's obviously he didn't do no reason
To do this
Description taking the day off
Come into the studio and
If you have power it's tickets
Revival food on air
I'm trying to get the money coming through
That was a great time to sell survival
Know what I want to do
So it's something he can still deliver where is all the stuff in the warehouse
Kidnap my power to the warehouse
He can't deliver anything for at least a week
What a f****** a****** using an emergency as a prop
Opticell shed is maybe one of the worst
You can do something he does regularly up
God f*** that
So also I think just two
Bring this back into really sharp Focus number one
Seattle wash that Astro number
Who
Alex Jones
Clearly was demonstrating some explicit whites
Supremacy
Two levels Vicky rarely touches
Like there's some things that are usually but kind of implied sometimes
But like that
Idea that he has
That freedom over human history has only sprung forth from white men
It's pretty clearly indicative of like
This is behind a lot of your other beliefs
You try to masquerade as not racist
The only conclusion you can
Can draw is that white men are better than other people
It's not that pretty clear that's the old
You can tell him his
So you take that
You really have it in
Sharp
Contrast with
People like Steven Crowder trying to whitewash his
His presentation is
Just everybody
What is
Like
Disgraceful
Disgrace
That's really the thing that I have is like
I I don't know how good the money is
B like
Just know that this is what you're doing
You're trying to mainstream and normalize this guy to your infantile audience
Who think PP joke
Behind it is a guy who thinks
The freedom only comes from White
Right so a white males
I don't think the money's that good thinking the money that good I'll tell you why
Because I was reading about this Ted Cruz thing
And in the text messages they point out
That the room fee per night is
It's $309 and they were like
That's a good room rate
If you are 10
Cruise
Spelling out literally the survival of the human race for Corporation
You not have to worry about what your hotel room costs
I'm telling you
It's cheaper just to buy be corrupt people than it should be I don't know I mean you don't stay comfort
Really selling out the human race if you don't keep up on room rate
I don't know it's
It's time for me to take all that stuff is so like
Shrouded in into the security that I really have no idea
No matter what the price
This is what you're doing
Stop trying to pretend you're doing something else
Yep hey Steven Crowder
You are spreading whiteness
Viet
I think it's I think it out I think it's bad and I think it's even like you can
To be even more direct with it like
What you're doing is actively trying to
Pretend that this white supremacy
That is celebrated at disseminated by Alex
Yeah that's not what this is
And by doing that you're trying to trick your young
Audience into believing
Did something that is hate isn't paid
I mean
Gross it's him
KKK member being like
See he's not wearing the robe so it's fine problem is really with the state
He doesn't like
The state in
Encroaching upon White
I don't understand why that's a
Oh I can't burn it on somebody's yard right
This is quite a bit
And I also resent that
I
Can't get myself to discover his episode
Goddamn ethics
Stan
It's like I believe in
Sarah principles more than 280
Is believing in reality
Jordan but until then we have website
We do have a website is knowledge, yes we're also on what it was called Twitter
I hate that knowledge underscore fighting I go to bed Jordan
Local charity or Bellefontaine area to help out
People who are still doing God's work
Seattle Wash that Ass
Words of wisdom
Holding
Alex
Kristen color my huge fan I love your work