Air Jordan
I have great respect for its knowledge B
I need money
Knowledge fight
What's fight.com
Tvrdi Jordan Jordan
What's up
Okay
One of my two favorite things that what's up
Shut up
And then the other one is the what's your favorite ice cream flavor
Turn off Sirius
The Rock
You're going to ask what my bright spot is Jordan
What is your vibrates
Except for
This month was a little late getting over to the Box
Because of snow and
Schedule and stuff but
This month we got these slow death hot sauce
And
This is
This is good
It's good this is quite
Good yes
Slow. I might die slowly
It's very hot
100 also is a Trinidad scorpion pepper
I like the flavor of that lot
Very hot very hot
I think you could handle
Before the show is over might might make things go down a strange path
Pretty good I like it a bit
Can use it to I could see myself using it for like
Dipping chicken maybe or
Adding to a sauce
Kick it up a little
Maybe I get a baby little meat sauce for the little
Hot sauce in there a little bit of
Marinara together
What's your favorite flavor
I don't know
It doesn't matter what you have to interrupt
Sochi Breitbart
Is a we were talking about this earlier today
My Brightside is the Chris gethard show washer
This show so much and you know I'm a huge fan obviously
Truly forced him to say nice things about me through the medium of money like some sort of indentured servant
I thought your book was in Barnes & Noble
And we've developed a great friendship
I've been starting so many projects I've been trying to find something new to like really sing
Sync my teeth into
And watching the Chris gethard show just that like
Unfettered creativity of it all he's very inspiring
Don't give up on doing weird s***
Yeah I know
Do that from time to time clock that sort of mentality
Republic
No no one's watching
That's why we're
Yeah
That's something beautiful about it that embracing of like
No we're not trying to get famous or anything it's really it's really interesting to to consider that both
Chris gethard and Alex Jones grew out of publication
Two people who
Check my life most today Merida vergence individuals
Yeah
Started used to be
The Browns won
Interesting thing to talk about Friday
The judges and the audience will determine whether or not you fully finished
The 21 I think you started
Before I finished that's why I stopped I think
It's Friday of last week
This episode is
Nuts okay
Powers back on
Pretty much in the Android Studio although maybe it's running on generators
It's unclear
Alex is really really mad
Maria Lema Hellyeah
He has a lot of breakdowns on this episode
And discuss what he's lying about in order to
Forget himself in the place where he
Yeah I'll freak out
Maria, this episode
Information
I'm worthy human beings thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much thing I have never said to the next
American podcast
I apologize
Happy birthday Elena next Alfred with 2 a.m.
Excel print bigger
I'm a policy wonk
Someone who I think it's two aliases this is just one
Shout out right
To name so it's old dirty
Ol Dirty Chinese massage
Is he
Knock knock you're busted
Swayback what is it go
Who's that
Oh
MN
How's your 401k
What's the business
Heroin
Barge
Yes thank you so much
So much
Jordans
Shut up
Call Sherry today
You know what the deal is either I've had very little sleep
Because the neighbors downstairs I have been partying
Oh I got you a little bit on fumes Rydal bit loose
Myconnect
The present is a tenuous
I think that there are some college students who live downstairs
And
Will text you in
Complain about this every now and again
I can
Hear them yell singing through the floor
Feel like sitting in a wet ass p****
This sucks
I'm waiting for you to go to Sawdust
Would get a whole circle in the topic I thought about harappa
Inches away from old manse topic
But I just can't do it
Feel-Rite knocking on the door cuz
Covid-19
New Pennywise
Tabroom that's why I'm a little silly but the good news is Alex isn't like totally
Center presents
Plainfield
From Today Show
Lawyer
Brother acts so much
If I were Alex in the position he's in right now I think I probably hate lawyers do
We should be which is everybody hating on lawyers
It's been awhile since everybody's really agreed to just hate lawyer
You know what I'm saying
6park
Lawyers were more of a villain in Jurassic
The dinosaurs
Exactly that's the whole thing
Yeah I don't know how is that in a weird state
So Alex starts the show by talking about how like
Maybe I shouldn't do this
Which is nice. Always a good sign
For the show that's about to happen
You know I learned something during the Trump Administration I've never tried to be in LA or being New York
To be in d.c.
Jimmy
Sycophantic
Pandan in the cyst
But I noticed very early on they would work around the clock
To try to make sure
That is not accessed
The president
Accept anybody
Because
Always just thought it
Form the public about things
And then that would
Percolate up in the government and in the governance and then we would
I'll be able to
Against tyranny tripleup lionomics
Take action against the law
But
It's about
It's a balance
You also need to Target
Obviously people that
Power structure
I'm almost empty
Now
With the news I have
To just not do the shuttle
Probably would be better if I just call Tucker Carlson costume
Steven Crowder
Call Rodger Stone
Can you
We cover so much hardcore stuff here
We just drop bomb after bomb after bomb after bomb after bomb a bomb
Familiarity breeds contempt
I get it I have contempt for myself too
Portland
This is this is an interesting hits
Startling number of words
For a very simple concept 2
Express
People other people have better reach than I do I think I need to probably
I could do better
But it is also like
Really shooting on the audience
Nyjah hub
You guys are so used to me being the best yet even give a s*** how great I am
Because I'm so good
I wish I was worse at my job so you guys would have to raise your level if only I killed time most of
The time exactly
Also why do you need to get the hold
The Trump has not spread
He's the president
That's very strange
You ever been at a comedy show
For whatever reason the host
It's just like
Their opening set was just something really weird
And everybody in the audience in all of the comics got the vibe of like
This going to be a weird show
It's not going to change
This just happened
It doesn't matter that there's an hour and 20 minutes left
Hour-and-a-half it's going to be weird
Exactly
Whatever B
I'm hearing right now
Yeah it's a lot
This town of like I don't want to do this anymore
Particularly severe on this episode
Distance makes the heart grow fonder
Broadcast
Eminem
Just because
This is too important to be smoking
John
Absolute
Total
Complete
Master plan of the enemy
We have them
By the short hairs completely
And no one is going to care
It's always the same
Always the same all you listeners I bring light
I give you all their plans but nothing happens I've got to call Tucker Carlson
Steven Crowder
I'm going to be on
Athea
I don't think
Familiarity always
Contempt
Continually starting the show with
My news is too big for me to do the show is something
Familiar for me not to
Contemptuous about
Yes yes
Equation
Is it screaming
I wants to quit
That's okay
Trudeau
And to prepare
Because I'm not just going to sit here
Put this information out of this
Today
Do it
Because we have
I don't know why people don't have an instinct to Victory
But it's incredible
Who was bleeped out season signal and gives a s***
He's very mad
I like these pretty mad
I do I mean there's something there's something weirdly Noble
About the tenacity has
Because
Every other human being I think on the planet what it is certain point go like
Well I've seen every other major news organization release huge information and then change the world
And I think I've done that literally every day for my entire career and not once have I changed the world
Perhaps it is me
Yeah
Maybe my
Radar is busted maybe I can't tell what big news
Look a little bit harder at the stories I cover
No no
It's everybody else's
The fault forever
I get so mad
Everyone else's fault
Always really loved about his broadcast-style when he gets in
These moods is like
He doesn't
Say what the news is
Why would it
I enjoy that I enjoy there because it's really the
Patel
The dishes perform
On some level
Definitely pissing him off
It's probably
Ufinancial and maybe
The staff sucks
Property lawyers
Call Susan Compton
Down. Not doing
The job that he needs them to do
But it is not that bad about what this big news is he's clearly still using this bike
This
Breakdown lashing out as a way of like
Anybody who's watching
Don't tell people that he's spanking quit on air
I'm going to use it in my speech today
What am I talking about
What's the big news
At least when I call other people that are influential daycare and I'll look into it but it out
I called Paul Watson Modesto he's busy on today or something
I'm at a party right like 5
It's just that I don't have the people
The keys to the
Lucifer
Nails done
Power Paul I would not appreciate Alex talks about him
Received
Unprofessional
Weird weird to have to work with that guy
It's almost like he lashes out at the people around him as well as the audience
On a constant basis
Yeah
Like he's a child
Almost
Get to the big news
Alex
Let it rip
What the story is
And it is
Bulshit
It's
You understand, we have
Smoking Gun
Of what did the power outage
100% was the department of energy
And their order
Keep the power off
Unbelievable
Kimberly so many Smoking Gun so much proof
Hong Kong
Running giant death camps
America
Then enjoy it
I want to watch to take somebody
Power
Tip of the spear
But it's a setback I'm still going to leave
All this emotional outbursts
In this childish
But he still able to say freaking he still able to recognize he's on the radio
Define
Little Falls
Alex is very mad about a document
From the Department of energy
He claims that its smoking-gun evidence that the power outages and Texas were intentional which is why he's putting on this shamefully child
Display a fake
Start the show
We'll get into the documents as Alex covers it
But at this point let me just some things up to say that Alex
What is entirely wrong about
That's not hard
It's not hard to believe
If no but it does it does the level to which he's wrong about it makes all this out verse really really funny
About all of this
Is
There is
And you can't deny that being your own boss is great
Right sir
Exactly like
That kind of a
You just get that if you work
For someone else
Wolf blitzer's not going on TV on Election night being like
I don't even know what the results are I quit
Let's let's imagine that Alex
Did have a boss but he had such a good contract that you couldn't get him out of it like firing him would require paying out 10
And years of his contract if he yelled I quit on air and I was about to be like you said it
Your letter of resignation
That the other good thing about. Having a boss
This is a Smoking Gun
Sure
Isn't The Smoking Gun and then there's another there's so many
Alex
Smoking Gun stuff
And then I've got a bunch of other
Big giant smoking
Guns
I am too damn angry to do this broadcast right now
Other stuff going on so
I do find my stack of those from yesterday I got to do a lot of stuff around here
I want somebody walking on my taxes
But I don't even bitching anymore I just can't do this 67
Public White Zombie
It's like walking into globalism
Because people are unconscious
Stop watching TV and playing on their phones
That's the problem
The public
Yeah
He's having a bad day
You know I can't help but feel like I've been there before I work comforts me
All the time
Is when I
Just go oh no I'm just an a******
Everybody else is asleep and I'm just being a dick my bad guys have an a******
Having a bad day
Be out somebody
I got to overcharged for something and maybe I'm taking it out on the people around me sometimes
Honestly I'm sorry you tell them and they're like
Eyeball berbere happens
Central piece of his Showmanship
Dwelling in that place
Having a bad day
And that means everyone's got to die
Unconscious
I'm watching TV and playing on their phones
Kill Everybody
Use Neutron bombs at least The Killing
He's right
Neutron bomb in the public
Neutron bomb
Mom
Do you know anything about Neutron
Start over
Yo Gotti
Bill Gates
Pledge allegiance
Do it
She wants to run something
The devil
Of course I'm serious.
Rappers
Department of energy
So anyways I'm going to go to rebroadcast for a while I'm trying to settle down
And then
I'm going to come back and lay all this out for you
Incredible
What was it a display
That was a show
That was a baby
It would really suck if his conspiracies were actually true
Movement about
Book The imagined like
Having to fall in line behind
Brutal brutal little a******
You know you know who goes down in history for being a hero people who is weathering
Adversity you know when you think of Nelson Mandela you think of being put
Prison for all those years
Not just surviving through it but then going on to help
Found f****** country for a real
Opportunity and equality you at you at his speech
Okay
25 years and I don't even know if I want to help any
Don't give a s*** about me
Bishop Desmond Tutu is an a******
Yeah yeah
That's who I want to
Following our noble noble leader
This document was available
Before I could have been covering the story
It this way before it's ready at the
Sort of childish it was the windmills narrative and what have you
Before I live on air
I got a bunch of extra news that I would already
Was told
Buy a very close
Perceptive
I dropped the ball on
Monday and just bought
Controlled by
Texas Powerball
That the feds order the map to increase power
I should have followed up on that
I should have gotten
I should have found out
Will let me see the director
Just went for another glass of wine
In the dark
And then son-of-a-b****
A whistleblower inside apartment of Energy contact
Someone that works here and said why is Jones not covering that no one else is
20 minutes from when on air
Website
And it was like being
Punched in the chest on the stomach over
And over again
For sure they raped us for sure there.
It's written
What is wrong with this man
I don't know
I'm not sure exactly what the definition of slimy documents are but I guess for Alex
The opposite of what you needed to say so you have to argue when they say yes they really mean no
Super slimey
Whistleblower to loosely
Publicly available document
Department of energy website
Hipster if anything
Maybe somebody's doing Alex's work for him
Been to that websites not a whistle
The document in question is titled order number 20 2-2 1-1
It's four pages long so there's no way I believe Alex Reddit
It's really easy to find if you go to do find what your reason order
That is the increase the electrical Pasadena Texas power grid in order to
To deal with the emerge
And see that the state is going
February 14th
Violetta
Reliability Council of Texas an independent system operator who service territory includes 90% of the electric customers in the state
Taxes filed a request for emergency order under Section
Can 202c
Of the federal power app
The beginning of the document lays out how I had foreseen the possible issue and this weather event is expect
Exit to result and record winter electricity demand
That will exceed even ercot
Most extreme seasonal load 4K
To try to adjust for this ercot attempted to maximize energy Generation by doing things like Avenue Railroad Commission
Texas put out an emergency order that quote specified
Increasing the priority of gas supplies to ercot generator
What are the main things of this order is about is that the electricity generation that they were needing to engaging
Would almost certainly not be possible quote
Without violating Federal air quality or other permit limitation
Caught appeal to the Department of energy to get an order allowing them to work
Outside those regulations
Due to the emergency situation
The order it says quote
Given the emergency nature of the expected loads
Stress the responsibility of our cots to ensure maximum reliability on its system in the ability of our got to
Identify and dispatch generation necessary to meet the additional load
I am determined that the additional dispatch of the specified resources is necessary
The best meet the emergency
And serve the public interest for purposes
Of f p a section
I'm 202c
Okay so the
Document Alex Jones the saying is them saying you can't have more power is them saying
Yes you can have more power
With some limitations destroy the Earth
Right
The order is the acting Secretary of Energy replying to ercot saying that they have permission to break regulations up to a point
Do you order literally says quote
Anticipate
The disorder may result in exceedance of admissions
As well as Wastewater release limit
To minimize adverse environmental impacts disorder limits operation of dispatched units to be
Three times and within the parameters determined by our cot for reliability purposes
It's pretty simple
This is just an order where I asked for permission to wiggle around some regulation in order to be able to meet the increased
Command of the energy emergency
The department of energy do so but that wiggle room only existed for the purposes of re-establishing reliability of the power
They couldn't just pull out all federal pollution regulations
Somebody less rigidly enforced given the human need that existed
Me too. So let's find a better place then let a way to make this work
There's nothing here
It doesn't sound like it just why I was doing this High School drama club club play about a serious and Smoking Gun
Dollars
It's actually a document that says the opposite of what he claims it doesn't because that is the case he has to claim that it's that ime
This is the level of work that he's doing and it really makes you wonder why he doesn't
Like it's B
This is nothing
I don't know
Cuz he's his own boss
Slimy
I don't think he's even read it so I don't I wouldn't
Expect him to understand some of these like dynamic
Texting all of this
Yeah
I think he realizes like I don't know if I can really even
So I can explain this to the audience in a way
It's going to make them
Motivated
Call Tucker
And tell them to look into this and let them break it I don't care
And then affected stay at the audience
Great but I say so much. People
Alex just said no it's not
Whatever happened to plan B ever saw
Robert Duvall in network
Canada
Okay
Bad
And then I sit there and I read
That works in these damn plants
To go
Power
Thunder
The freaking federal government
Because put them back under the son-of-a-b**** two weeks ago
That we all knew that
Man you know I here's my pic
Search for Alex
Anime this is going to sound crazy
But he's sick of being under the backs of sure Bill Gates
Warren Buffett
Ted Turner for some reason
Join the Socialist buddy we want to try and get rid of these rich people and remove their power come on man
How can you get rid of them let's go
Socialists are working for Ted Turner
They just don't know it
Ted Turner
Here's my cell back to you Alec
Ted Turner think
We're working
Looking for him
But we're actually working for our own goals
Using his money and power that he thinks he bought us
Another possibility would be moved to
Okay that's also a good one
Alex UK
Can also go to Antarctica
So
What are the features of Alex's coverage of this document from the Department of energy
What up what are the strategies uses alive I call it making things up
And guess what
Under federal law you'll be processed
Executed
Unless you exhaust
Outside power supplies first
There's no mention of process
Execution
The relevant part of the order that Alex is talking about is as follows
Consistent with good utility practice ercot shell exhaust all reasonably and practically available resources including
Mobile Imports
Demand response and identified
Behind-the-meter generation
Resources
Selected to minimize increasing Amisha
To the extent that such resources Provide support to maintain grid reliability
Prior to dispatching be specified resource
This makes total sense a story about it to make things seem more nefarious
When in reality
This is very much a document that is the Department of energy giving ercot a fair amount of leeway and trying to keep the system online
Frequently other document you see it made clear that if a determination
Of what is necessary is that they need to put on more
Hi live now
The determination of when it's necessary to put on Galvez other things
That's at the discretion of
That is not that's that's left up to them
Interlaken
Behind the meter generation resources for what it's worth is like
Solar
And batteries
And stuff like that
I got
I just don't say
I don't I don't see I don't see what he saying
Compelling
Texas always have their power supply before Obama came in
The states all around
How much is a country
The US under Trump got to where it was the biggest supplier of energy in the world for
Orthodontist
Again this is just something Alex is making up
The power grid in Texas specifically exist in such a way as to not supply power to other states
Avoid Interstate energy sales regulation
Kim from the federal government
Someone super 10 Persona that Alex has should really understand that Dynamic Weiland
Be proud of that
Also Alex is just reporting something Trump lied about
I'm pretending it's real
Trump basically lied in his State of the Union speech about how for the first time in 65 years with net exporters of energy
Prices
FirstEnergy
You're going up so well yeah I imagine so
Warriors
Texas Wholesale Electric price
Thousand percent of made out of
And what is this little sweet.
Bring up next
They had the first only buy from outside sources
Including available import
Demand response
Is it raining
Outside power when you don't have enough
Imports
Either a lawyer term
Once again that was just an economics term
Demand response according to Alex's lawyer speak
I mean you got to buy outside power
He knows this because he looked it up
Yeah this is made up out of thin air
Responses and energy-efficiency strategy that involves giving customers the ability to adjust their electricity usage
Play from peak hours by doing things like
Offering cut rates at other times when the burden on the electric rate is lower
For putting small Terrace on power during
Repeat.
Energy documentary saying that in addition
Using available Reserves
Demand response strategies should be employed where possible to maintain the functioning of the power grid
Oh so you mean incentivizing
People to spread out the usage of power
I'm fairly certain that you did just say by all your power
Sure
It would be easy for someone to hear me make
This correction of Alex and say that I'm just nitpicking and fact-checking him pointlessly but there's a really serious phenomenon that I'm trying to illustrate
Alex Jones
Constantly pretends
No thanks
He has a consistent pattern of just making up definitions of words and details about new stories
And then pretending at the thing he's making up his
Is the product of researcher
Navigation
He's important to recognize that he does this about the small details of his day-to-day conspiracies
In the same way he does with the larger worldview level
Conspiracies
He's workflows essentially like walking
Watching a shity improv show rooted and terrible racist politics
Uses headlines and words he skims and stories as the suggestions
From the audience
But it takes money rips a scene out of
I would implore anyone who takes him seriously to consider that dynamic
Critically engage with the things he say
You'll almost always find him fabricating details about
The stories that he's covering
In order to make them fit is predetermined narrative and worldview
Would you absolutely wouldn't need to do if he wasn't full of s***
As for the skyrocketing prices of energy some consumers are seeing that is being reported in reputable outlets and it does appear that
Get some of this is going on
The Public Utility Commission of Texas is opening in a dress
Navigation to the possible price gouging
And I would guess that if they find companies that were engaging in that
Then the customers will not be responsible for paying those outrageous rates
Was one thing to keep in mind however
Small number of people in Texas use a company called greedy
To provide their electricity which operates on wholesale prices
Most people use providers who have fixed rate
But going through company like gritty
Actually seems people money on their electric bill General
The downside is in a situation like this
Their rates are not
And making Skyrock
Even so I would guess that these people won't be stuck
With these exorbitant Bells
The solution will be read
I know I just I find it hard to believe
Better
I don't know
It's just at this point in time it's safer to assume that people are
Going to get
F***** over and some
Massive fat
Possibly possibly but I would I would guess that's there will be some
Forgiveness
Yeah
The examples that you see or these like really really high bills
And the ones that I've been able to see and someone could correct me if I'm wrong
But the ones that I've been able to find being reported
Are wholesale prices, which are not the majority of electric users
Most likely
Fixed rate
And there
Obviously their prices will go up to but
But not per like the right
But they won't
That's just a natural phenomenon
Uno
W
Do price gouging is illegal
Satellite
At the bottom
Alex
You know he's got this.
Document that he's lying about
Yes I feel really excited about this lies he's pretty pumped about it
And
You know what
F****** people in Congress
In Texas
And our governor
We need to lie about this document to Ono
And all
Ted Cruz
I'm self
All Jon Cornish to do is come out
Game over
By the way
Going out to get a cheeseburger
His daughters were going down there
Watching people down there with his daughter to get out of the cell
His power was off
Just came back today
Facebook
Now your grass cool Mexico
We go down there but I'm not even defending
How old is Bethany
He horrible
And the Democrats are all look he doesn't care about you
Ladies and gentlemen Alex Jones masterclass and intentionally missing the point
Yep yep yep
Remarkable
I could very easily be made that he doesn't
See that is something very difficult
To do because he too is
Could I could have something to do with that
Those things were rich people really understand why poor people get mad
Yeah
It's a really interesting way that Alex engages with Ted Cruz
Responsibilities as an elected official as opposed
To the responsibilities of other
Anime
You know it's weird
Need to be there.
Sure
So Alex is mad
Now I should say that he doesn't know that it's the elect
Reliability Council of Texas
Really know what it is he doesn't
He seems to think that her cot is like basically Enron
Oh okay
What company
I'm just reading it
Me so angry
Almost turn the desktop or seriously man that's a normal response
Learning
Just robbing our future they're blaming us
They're starving people
Killed over 50 people
They're going to rape us more and her telling is permanent
Blackouts because the feds
Put bots in control
Feds put her cotton
Control has no idea what that is supposed to be
Texas power grid
Which is run by a board of directors that's overseen by the Public Utility Commission of Texas
And the state's legislature
The public utility commissioner is responsible for overseeing ercot or
Berkeley appointed by Texas's governor
There could almost be no system imaginable where the state would have more direct control over the power system
Other than one worthy state
Itself runs all the
Power plant itself
Which I can't imagine Alex advocating for no no
Alex knows nothing about the sub
Dixie's covering a story to tell the audience
The shows larger themes and narrative
Jason reality at all
Outrageous
Also you don't get to
He doesn't get the care you already did the coronavirus thing where you denied all of that s*** do you don't get to be like
Oh how dare they do this now.
It's a remarkable how everything is
Conspiracy
Alex
Get back to this document and this is kind of
I just wanted the other reasons I'm in a nice mood
I'll be on Deezer to slap happiness and sleep
Deprived
Grounded
In the ercot region
Texas the generating units specified resources
Order pertains to are listed on the order
202 Dash 21-1
Resource list as described below
And it's all hydroelectric
It takes him a week to turn to call plant
Sandwiches reading this
Part of the doctor
Methodist giving
Her to come as no surprise but he's just making s*** up
The resource list that's referenced in that department of energy order is available
And it's easy to fall
It's just a list of power generation plants in Texas that are relevant to the order
Each plan is listed in the third column in the spreadsheet is the type of energy
Thank you okay
Literally zero are solar windmills or Hydro like
Because that's not what the order pertains to doesn't seem like those would be important
Killer one either all natural gas lignite bituminous coal or distillate
Fuel oil power generator
Wichita
Are being given special permission to operate in ways that would
The environmental rules
Specifically only when doing so would be needed to maintain the reliability of the grid
Alex hasn't read the actual document nor has he seen this resource
He's literally just making up what he thinks the story is then repeating that to his audience as a fact
That's what
Yeah it makes up stories
The story tell
Also
This should make it
More than abundance leak
Clear
We have an order saying that these evil power companies
These can destroy the Earth in order to save lives but
All the renewable energies are just like a you guys keep on
Like it seems it seems very obvious that
One of these is a serious polluter destroying the world and the other one there like okay well you guys
So Alex
Is really
Confused
About
And what have you and the
The federal government
Charge
Man lot of
Confused as to how this happen
It's a really really bad
Control
Wouldn't let him out the power
And unlimited what they can do
I'm not sure that's
What's happening
Fairly certain that I have heard many,
Comments on Biden's ability to
From what I've heard
Some people like it
Some people don't just about Borden totally clear I got kind of like texting bashing that
What's going on
I think is wrong
I think it's misguided and at least
Civic Center that is going on
I don't know
What extent
It is not really been exposed to much of it myself sure
I imagine if I spent more time on Twitter maybe I would have seen
Some dumb comments
But whatever
That's said Alex is doing is trying to take criticism
Memes about Texas
Their power grid is operated
How many turns that into people saying the Texans just walkie hall-dale
Opossum
He doesn't have a response to the argument about
The great because he doesn't actually even understand the conversation the people are having
Not a little bit
He can get his audience personally offended if he makes the whole thing about how the coastal Beats
Fake people in the middle of the country or stupid
That's pretty much the tax
Activate ucpn employed here
Infuriating
I do not appreciate
That he is talking about
Problem
That is almost entirely the result of a state
Desiring more than anything else
For the federal government
To get out of there f****** business
And then
To blame the
Beds for being in their business
Yeah I mean I think
Think I think
I think that there's a piece of it that you can probably blame
On the organizational structure
The disconnection from the interstate.
But also like I I think
You also have to be very careful with that because of how severe the storm is like
Even an ideal circumstances there would have been power outage
Like 100%
Perhaps not to the extent that it it going to we have seen
And maybe not as severe as we've seen
But
The storm like that in Texas is something that is just a recipe for
There's going to be a lot of trouble
I'm just saying that if the reports
Of them being that close to having no power for a month
Right
That is 100%
Look
They're going to be power outage
They happen here they happen everywhere and
Dealt with if you ever assist
That is like
Well we were a James Bond moment away from f******
Never having power for the next
Year
Yeah you're done f***** up in the planning somewhere along the line
It's really tough to say if that problem
Is
Essentially related to
The non-interstate
Energy sales
Just
Unrelated mismanagement or something
I don't know enough to say for sure but I think that those things are important
The peas out
Make too much of a judgement
But it does seem like
Whatever it is it something
I mean
At the very least it would be hard to imagine
If there was some sort of unified or
Greater
Area of
Power control where it would be able to be
Transported it effectively much much better
To the point where they we would have a better response time at the very least
You know it maybe now
But who knows
For now all we do know
Is that Alec
Over-prepared
For his shift
Massively prepare for the show
I have one two three four five six seven eight nine 10 11 12
15/16 stacks
That was impressive in red
Can't believe you counted all the way up to 16
Coming up
No
Department of energy override Trump's executive orders until Texas
I just wanted to see this all over the news I want to see them go to prison
Go bad news
Country travel
Good luck buddy
Personally offended because this is about Texas
Yeah
Do you want to know is
The Texas
What about you
I am looking straight on
Ritonavir
Texas
Those people take
And Alex might have the worst example
There's some mistake
This
Texas
Think of us take off down here
Peopleready
I'm just saying what
With a lot
Fire
Because they're stupid
No idea
People
Dedicated
Is there family
God
Who defended it
Why did you say
Look texting in the Texans will f****** kill the president will do it right
F****** mouth
That's weird I thought it was right
Now
GasBuddy
There's one thing I know about the South if that
They murdered president said
Conspiracy I guess
Had to been a Texan
This is interesting. The mob is not the Russians it was not a single load actor it was the Lone Star State
George h.w. Bush
I don't know you think it's a coincidence
I don't think it is
I don't think it's not
Cruz's dad
Alex Jones
Exactly the Magic Bullet was actually a exploding to situation
Calling card
So Alex Goes to College
And not a lot of these are
Worth even
Mentioning
Although I will say that this next call is probably the saddest
I've been listening to Alex
In a long time
Hellboy
With my free
Free kids I live close to the memorial
This whole thing and
Just want to say thank you to you guys.
Because there is not
I would have gotten
Brutus
With my Myself by Wi-Fi
Ree kid
How to think
Single
Incredible
Please get
Are you do not
Want to
A victim
Weed
Thanks
Infowars
Analysis
Tire crew because everyday
Hey you guys get on
Conversate
To be
Is your real
You stay when you make
Take the steak
When the Q thing
A real into war that is real that gets in America
And I can tell you
Listening to you guys
Mike generator-powered
You kept like
Connection to Human
My connection to God
I'm telling you
I have been freezing my butt off me and my family at 40 degree weather all we
Askew
Every morning when I wake up I was going to video
Waiting for your report
Cuz you guys keep
Connection
John the boom operator said
Doesn't matter geology blow up earlier that's real looking for red blood
Oh my God
Boy
Wow
Just bought me out so much
Check everything that dude was saying is so wrong
Just
Brutal
That is that's just uncomfortable conversation I don't know but that is just
Enumerated a crime
Like what he is just described is somebody soda
Destroying his mind
He is in thrall to the point of death
Buju bbid
TriNet disaster
This is one of the situations where
Some of Alex's
Product actually probably be quite useful like
I bought a water filter
The idea that in a disaster in this in this scenario that he's in he goes to the generator to
To try and find Alex's videos
Keep his connection with humanity and God
Is just dark
Yeah that is
The dark thought
That is a dark thought
Especially when like okay your connection to humanity
Just quit earlier this year
Humanity
This guy
Bill Gates your neutron bomb everybody
I mean it just it just makes you feel like you think about all the horrible ship
The tap into the past new like why would
People follow that guy anyway
People follow me over there
The expression they used to say in Missouri was it takes all kinds
So
Why would anyone listen to a thirteen-year-old pope
And then you get that guy and you're like wow yeah I guess
Believe whatever you want man
About this thirteen-year-old Pope
Is that the young Pope
Was that HBO show that was that was what
Is he the type who told his audience to prepare kill list
Yeah actually was I believe you
Ladies and gentlemen
Describe to you how serious times are know you are
I'm not saying these are cuz I will be misconstrued
People would go after just minions I don't
They don't
Out
The globalist
People Bill Gates control need to know
They need to know
What they're doing
God is going to hold them accountable where I pray for God
Are they coming
Address that we reserve the right to
He said threatening late
I'm out.
We are in the military
I just I can
Sit there
And lie to you and tell you that you're not
And so
Santa Claus
Researching
Naughty but nice
Polar sausage
Going to get little
Circular toys
So that's where we are
Ryback stay with us your call Zach redhead
Alex talks a lot about this idea of making kill list
And like I don't know I don't know anything but
I could see somebody
Trying to kill Bill Gates or
Something
And then being like
I was advised that he was trying to kill everyone with a vaccine and that we
We needed it was
Defensive really
WhatsApp told you that
Alex Jones everyday simply
Every
I don't know if it's like
The kind of thing that you could get in trouble for illegally booths
Spiritually or or just
Morally
He's doing everything
Zach Woods
Lead someone to
Do the thing
Just a thing hasn't happened
Yeah I would I would just
Say that it's time to write a sequel to Miracle on 34th Street
Where Alex claim
Santa is making
Kill list out of this naughty and nice list
We all know timilai papers
It's a no I'm sent
Unreal
All we know you're f***
Getting real. You're killing all of our children are going around
Elves know so blood red
People
Oklahoma
Power
Freezing
And dirt
National Basketball Association teams
And
Play their basketball
Game
Nicole
Technocracy is if they go oh
Downtown Austin stays open
For 6 days
Do some of the places they were taking power during the Texas storm seems a little bit
Strange but a lot of it's actually really easy to understand if you take the time to
Care
A lot of it has to do with sections of the grid where essential Services relocate
I'd like hospitals being a higher priority
The ones that say didn't
Kentucky hospital
This could easily create the impression that there was power in downtown Austin but not in outlying areas
But if you look at the proximity of downtown to not only the Capitol building but also
Dell Seton Medical Center
All kinds of warming centers
And st. David's Medical Center
You start to understand how it might be impossible
To retain power to those buildings that also keeping power on
For some 6th Street businesses
Then maybe you like why are they why do they have a light
Also
It appears that you do correctly understand why would people are mad at 10
Ted Cruz is the basketball being played but people learned
Oru flying to Mexico but people are depicted to be fair I would guess a similar
Things going on in Oklahoma city where the Thunder play at the Chesapeake Energy Arena
Which is within walking distance of the County Courthouse
The County Detention Center and Saint Anthony Hospital
As well as the entire University of Oklahoma Medical Center complex
Including the Children's Hospital in the VA
Said that everybody needs
Two separate Palladium
It's pretty simple explanation I just don't I don't understand why people
Mad or confused about things
Games that are like they're pretty easy to
Understand because it would be
Fine
So Alex has Mac
Text Kaiser on and they just talked about 2
Bitcoin
It's really mad about how
He could have bought Bitcoin when it was like
$5 and now it's over fifty Grand well the thing is or whatever it is
Max 10 years ago offered him 10,000 Bitcoin
And the Alex
Hey buddy how are you might have missed the boat around
Who gives a sheds to talk about how great
Stop giving out your web address makes it sound like you're a sponsor
How much
Bitcoin will be worth now
Kiser's Lake
So kind of joke about that's why you got to sell these bumper
It was really nice
Let's guys are his freedom
Alexa is
Kind of enjoyable but it also makes
His interviews not really all that worthwhile for our show
But after he leaves
Joel skousen
Symptoms
Amass
Yeah he is
Hey weirdo
And I just have forklift
Wisconsin's interview
That are four reasons why you should not take Joel skousen series
The first
Is that
He also along with Alex seems to think that ercot is at like a federal agency or a company
I want to set themselves up as a savior
I think it's important that you Groove me the other shows
Federal mismanagement control with
Removing the state from the process that took one of our backs Power Systems
No
Probably Federal
Didn't you correct him if you know
That air cot is a Texas
Pacific
If you understand the Dynamics
Play you shouldn't
Go along with Alex saying a literally the opposite I completely agree with your dinner
What it is that he saying is 100%
Go ahead and listen to anything the drill has to say about the the storm and the power grid
If he doesn't know this
Basic
Yeah that would be a problem I don't think I would want to learn
From somebody who doesn't know algebra
Now here's where it gets weird
Reason number two not to take Joel skousen.
Where do you think of fossil fuels and oil
No
Personally
I think it comes from God and you put them there about ten thousand years ago.
Petroleum geologist
Oil is not fun
Fossil-fuel what is it
Well
I'm afraid I have to get theological here this was part of the creation of the Earth
Oh my God
Fossil fuels exist if you create a boil
From deteriorating animals look at all of the trillions and trillions and trillions of tons of oil
Which would only represent
Tiny fraction of the decaying bodies of any designer stores
You would have had the dinosaurs 100 ft deep over the entire Earth plants
Marine life
Wow dude
This is not
Carbon only comes from old dinosaurs
Thank God
But he was making the Earth put oil down there
I swear to God I swear.
I don't know if this is really a narcissistic
And I'm going to go ahead and buy thing I don't actually believe it
It's kind of fun to think about
I felt a little bit of resistance
On Joel skousen part to say that I'm hoping
Is it be like God dammit
Make fun of it
Answer the question I have to go
Okay so do things that God put oil down there for us
22 you a reason not to take him
All too seriously suppose that look
Religion
Whatever
But you can't do that
You know like a demonstrable ridiculous
Thing you can't just
Like I said you can
You're more than free
To believe whatever you want to believe however it will implicate how I view your believes in
No I would like that to be true as well
Fortunately that is
Not true for most
Sure
If you want to believe
Jegs
Like
That God put oil in the middle of the world
I think it's harmless belief unless you're using that to argue against climate change
Belief that God put oil down there for us to use
How do you say to inform
My view of your arguments about anthropogenic
Sure I just I would just prefer if we had to if there if
Holy books now have to have footnote
That's my new rule
If something is demonstrable e true
It's a footnote in your book
I get it
Is that from
I swear to God if it is I kill myself
Any other segment called new rules
What's the joke
Turn into fossil fuel
Speed below-ground fossils come from
God no
I don't
You know what f***
Samson
Every whenever you pulled the temple down he made all the father
Was
Intelligently designed
Exactly
I'm you know I'm not even sure that
You know desire
Those actually lived on the Earth
Is very very possible this Earth was created by Mayors from other previous
Planet Smoothie sings our previously Groening
And put together
Oh boy
This is some this
Camelot
To be honest like I knew that Joel skousen was a bit of like
Yes I'm weird
Beliefs
Gelatos like
He comes from his his family anti-communist roiled
Everything is a f****** false-flag to him he is not
But this is
This is out of my
Itself was a false flag from other planet
That's it could be
Coupons
Other planets with themselves
Well okay
Spaceman
So I will admit that there are millions of people who've dedicated their entire lives to studying and understanding what
Fossils are
And I couldn't listen to anyone of them
However they look weird to me than those people do so guess what
Space
God
Understand about all those who will study fossils
It's all a scam
Do you study fossils
Cuz if you did
You would get into it and then someone will come
Put your put your arm around you'll be like listen
For scamming people with all this
That's why it's Indiana Jones was so cool he knew it was all a scam that was predicted program
Perfect grip steal it from the thuggee cult
Yeah
I guess fossils coming from space is going to be another reason I'm not going to take Joel skousen too seriously
Now I think you might also believe in Divine Alchemy of some sort
This is this is also kind of weird
You know when you look at the chance
This orbit of this Earth being so perfectly designed in the
The perfect season
And you're in the middle of an inventory
Things Can Happen by chance this
Northwest
A design Divine creation
And you know
Most Christians believe in and it should all believe in the fact that the Lord has power over the until
Over the elements meaning the elements are in Cheddar's
No
The most Shelter Rock and water poured out
Necessary
Small image of God
We'll be right back
Way that way to throw to break that
That is a thought process that I appreciate if God can command the element
Then the elements must be smart enough to know I didn't think of that
I didn't think that the Elementals could also
Obey
Or disobey
Commands
I guess Lee
The Staggering unlikelihood
Of life
Leeds 12
Beside arbitrarily that it must be
Fully designed and also the Bible is literal
Yeah how could how could we have such a perfect environment a perfect planet
Massive weather events are occurring almost regularly due to our faults where
People are being destroyed over and over and over again
Because
They get a perfect amount of water where the problem I'm guessing is it weren't burning enough
Oil well carvings good for the planet is what I was
That's what I'm hearing carbon dioxide
Starved
Damn where's my buddy Mark Moreno at when you beat
Dude is strange
Yeah
Euro much weirder dude then I think
I can kind of see why you normally stick to
Weird geopolitics
As opposed to some of these
Yeah more esoteric beliefs cuz they're
Very strange
They kind of make you look like a Project Camelot person
Get the theological
Oh well then I'm going to have to leave sir
Question is why is there oil and I have to get to be illogical to answer it by
You don't have an answer
I mostly bring this up
Show this to be like all right
Joel skousen is somebody who Alex thinks his
Super credible
Very
Important Source on like
Geopolitics
Looks like a suorin up to something
And he's also a person who thinks that got injected oil in the world for us to find and maybe fossils come from outer space
This is this
What is the level of
Expert
Babies hanging around here
The surface and you're going to find them saying things like this
It's that which is not to say that you can't have some out their beliefs
And not be you do like Jack Parsons
Everybody trusted him as an expert when it came to rockets and s***
Not when it came to Elementals
Not true sex Magik was not real
Yeah
Yeah it would be good if you stayed in your lane unfortunately his Lane
Bulshit that's the problem
Yeah
I don't know if this is really interesting experience for me because you know you start out with Alex fuehrer
And just like I quit f******
Navigate to this
Sucks
F*** this place I hate Infowars I want to quit
Yeah but
If you don't start quite that bad you know we're eventually going to go
Get to
I'm going to have to get theological to answer that question Alex you go along the path you find out what's making him so bad and
It's just lying about this department of energy document
Nelly Mellows out
Says some b*******
And then you get skousen
And I think that this this illustrates to really essential
What is metallic slime
Like this document making s*** up about it's just over and over again
Finding little things that you can use as like
Because if he's climbing up a mound little handhold yeti
Confined to lie about
The second thing I think this illustrates is they like
People like skousen
AR
Not reliable
The aura and the Bee
The attempted to facade
Robin like a serious-minded I look
Get the documents in
You know I go where you know
I read Carol quickly book and I am left to assume is it all Democrats are evil or whatever the f***
Like even if you put on that hat
Underneath that hat
The dude who's
Weird
But fossil never
Patient zero
For covid-19
Was indeed
Steve pieczenik
With
And
He rigged up this election as he is an operation against a Democrat
Nope nope
Nope a lot of his expertise a real I also arrested the
Forgot about that
Yourself
Regularly unmentioned
But we will we will get off this this year horse same time and I will
I'll be back
But
World's on Twitter
Find a local charity or bail Fund in your area especially
To help out with people
Struggling
Until then I'm Mio I'm Leo I'm dzx
Clerk I'm Daryl rundus I'm the juiciest
Holding
Alex
Christian coloring