Air Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Everybody around a little bit
Jones
Jordans
Question what's up
People who listen to the park
Podcast regularly eagle-eyed listeners will know
Emoji certainly
The Forbidden Rice paddies unforbidden
Not love
Bookminders of vinegar
Vinegar
I didn't know that you could maybe yours
Supposed to put vinegar in rice when you're cooking it
I did not know that either I don't know if you're supposed to put some people recommend that you do it
So I put some some vinegars
If not then with some rice I was cooking last night
Pretty good 22 great flavors that go great
Together D up
100% certain that was
That much better
But
Expelled
Like a garlic while it was cooking well that's fun
Yeah there's no problem there
It felt like I was doing
Something
And that really counts for a lot
Cooking Alchemy is a good feeling
Yeah definitely so I had a pretty nice time without making up some
Some rice and veggie
It was last night
How are you
Did my bright spot is that we're doing this episode at all
Tired
You turned around an episode that was amazing
We had a weird couple of days
Skyrim
Set out to play
Schedule a little bit of a
I need a little bit of a step back and to feel so I asked you to cover Friday
Dude
And we recorded it
Okay it was thoroughly okay was a very interesting exploration of some
Dies on YouTube
I realized it was like
You know a lot of
So the monotony going on with Alex
And it would be a good time to take a little bit of a break sure he's something else and I don't know if I'm really capable of finding
New
Fingers anymore
Like I brought alexson project
The dogs of war
And Bill Cooper Tucson
Text that but like
Somebody other efforts have not been great
And found something
No spoilers
It's already been
Spoiled thinking we should just release it the way it was with
Half hour the
Recorded it
2 hours
Dead Silence
Jordan craft the
The car
Get away from the wheel
We recorded it and somehow
Delta College
At something happened
There's audio of us talking for the first half-hour
Hitman after that point
It's just the drop
That's almost like one of those coloring books
You guys listen to the first half-hour of us talk again
Make your own doll
There's going to be 20 minutes dratch's where your there's nothing
There's no audio
Premeditated
Find you
So in a. Of
Mere hours you've put two
Together another episode for us to release their
Only share it for the rest of your one will ever know
Yeah it
Don't want you to feel too bad
It's not it's not your fault
I think the only problem really is that puts me at like
What
One out of every five episodes I do disappears
That wipe off 100 episodes
Yeah I am buy more used to the server troubleshooting knowing when something's wrong and I kind of
It's no big deal
I feel bad for the listeners in for you because
You know you did
About bring something into
Do that
To the table
Maybe there's something later but
Certainly not that episode can't redo it
Baffling enough as it is let alone trying to do it again
Lost episode well
So Jordan today we have a interesting thing to go over that I have
Scrounged up
Today we're going to be
Sing about
October
16th 2014
Typical price you have thought of you thought of that last night
Maybe this morning while I was laying in bed
Very bad blackjack
But
Yeah so I decided I wanted to go back
2 time
Before Alex was
Quite as
I don't know overly amphetamine.
Insert for a before the time of trump
I wanted to get a little bit more of a
Taste of that sure
Scrolled around randomly and
The name and the
In the description
Here we go actually I was
Listen to this
Hauntingly appropriate
We've done this
Too many times for you not to be a fee at Boost so my credibility as a
Either that or nothing ever ever change
And it is all the
Or everything is the reverse of always the same
So I am excited to get out of business on this episode before we do Jordan retake my birthday thank you
Revoke suicide up and are walking it up
This is at 2 name
Person this is a very exciting
A rare
Double alias
But they're both good someone allowed
First is North Korean ballad boat Hellyeah piloted by the skipper Rodger Stone
And the other eye is private chef of Alex's wife's tennis partner
I'm a policy
Captain details
Thank you so much
I'm a policy person I'm not good at emulator
Thank you so much and I'll probably walk
I'm a policy wonk
Skateland
Nutsack
Father of Theo Parker in Tucker
Adrenochrome
I'm a policy wonk
Adrenochrome adrenochrome
Chrome has a nice little bored
Dreadful feel too
You know what I'm saying
Sonam similarities similarities
Adrenochrome
That's icua we have a
Clearly illuminates the difference
Does between our personalities
Thank you so much and I apologize
I'm a policy wonk
Everybody likes a thank you to someone who is the Impaler
You are now at
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
Replicas trailer
Kwi
In an abbreviation
We can agree to disagree on that always
Nope
Articles never go
Okay so Game of Thrones is GT
Bye
Not got
What there's a reason o is lowercase in that always simply that everyone agrees with Game of Thrones.
And maybe they should
Okay
Spanked on your birthday
. birthday spankings have I ever been birthday today I think I was birthday
They spanked one time as
As like a 11 or 12 year old
And everyone immediately went
Now this was
A good idea to be really weird because like you
Do you know if you didn't
On your 10th birthday it's not like a towel pinned up till then
Somebody it was it was very much like somebody at my birthday party had
Just heard of birthday spankings and was real excited
Try it out like
This will be a new
Thing at everybody stopped and was just like no
What is
No I don't think
Ever
I don't think I've ever been a fun
Family shot
But there are some people who are celebrating a birthday
Spanking button
Light up light up for the birthday
I think I might have gone down the wrong road with this setup but
Earlier this week on Monday Pat
Happy birthday and wanted to say happy birthday to you Patty
On Monday but I'm not great
Also tomorrow
Haha
Terry MC
North Carolina
You having a good one out there and I hope you had a great one
Hindi
Happy birthday
Spanx all around spanking cuz I realized
Hello weird
I'm going to get into this house
That's a good transition
October 16th 2014 what do you know what was going on around that time what do you would you got together
Feeling
Let's see
2014 I would have
Just woken up from a 3-year sleep
Over here
Just welcoming awareness
It's once again tonight moved to Bloomingdale Illinois
Gorgeous
One-bedroom apartment
Nipple episode is shockingly mostly about residential pricing in Bloomingdale
All I'm saying is those are the only things I remember Brooks 2014 is a surprisingly right in your wheelhouse I may be a witch
No
October it was Ebola
Middle of the. We're
There were couple cases of Ebola here in the United States
The primary patient
The first
First patient to the Cape May to be knighted
Midstates had passed away
And we are right on the cusp of
The second nurse who had treated him
Has been diagnosed
Now with Ebola
So we're remembering when a possible pandemic was a verdict
We have done an episode
2 years ago
About
The first day when
There was a case of the United States
And it's really interesting
To take a little bit of a look at
Fancy
Growing on a couple weeks later
Abyssal I mean did he go
Did he go from
That if there will be lone survivors back
Back to there's no problem at all
It's interesting I would say is trajectory have a lot of similarities and a lot of
This particularly fascinating for me
So here we go go
Start off with him talking about some
Assertive Furious
Narratives
Pioneer host Alex Chao
They are telling 911 dispatchers
Fox television of DC's reporting
Not to say Ebola
Over the radio
Or when they're basically talking about a call that they're on
We have Obama saying there's nothing to fear is that it's a low probability than epidemical start in the US
Even as we learned that the second nurse to contract Ebola
Travel all over the place on aircraft
The plane was not even cleaned
That is wipe down
They pick up the trash on the floor but not a deep clean
45 more flights after she was on
Five more flights
So this story that I was opening the show is about the 911 dispatcher is not being allowed to say
DC
Fox BC did run a story about it with the headline that Alex's reading but that article is just a link to the original story with
Witches from the New York Post
The reasoning behind this trustworthy New York Post
This but the reasoning makes total sense
There's plenty of people who aren't First Responders who listen in on emergency radio channels and you can easily imagine
Alpana could break out if every called
The cavemen were someone with
Worried that they had Ebola was
Is misinterpreted by someone listening in
Has a definite or probable case
People would lose their mind
I know you could really
Do some damage
Did you know that
Words can have an effect in real life
If you actually read the New York Post article this is exactly what it's about
A source speaking to the post side quote
You can't say bomb on an airplane we can't say Ebola
Back in the 80s and 90s
Taking universal precautions met someone had AIDS
We weren't allowed to say AIDS then either
Dr. Jay Varma the Deputy Commissioner commissioner the City Department of Health give some idea of how many opportunities there
False
Text to Stark
Quote
We have now had about 130
3 calls
With possibly Bulbasaur
Symptoms and all 133 were false alarms
That's
Well
Alarming
Yeah and I'm people listening in could have taken any one of those 133 and like tried to
Presented as like look at all these other covering up all these
Use cases
To be really dangerous
You could definitely get into a fear-mongering panic when you're somebody like Alex Jones
You need to buy survive
Emergency response perspective I do see how it could be best practices
Is 2
To use language
That wooden
Necessarily
Be exploitable by
People who may have ill-will and are listening in on your communication right which is done for
Fortunate because
It would be
Be nice if we were just allowed to say words and even let me let me
Is that even necessarily people who ale will
Like some some people could just get
Confused
Just panicking already
Time for that nurse story that was
True sort of
It's true that you did
Fly
The day before she was diagnosed with Ebola
But experts don't believe that it was as big a deal as it's not
The first reason is that at the time of her flying she wasn't
Exhibiting symptoms that would put people at high risk
Like vomiting
Even so Thomas frieden then the director of the CDC was
Clear the quote
She should not have flown on a commercial airplane
Eddie immediately put in place guidelines that anyone who'd been exposed
Does somebody with ebola but only travel by way of
Controlled movement like private flights
Uncharted vehicle
Wowowo immediate
No prior to that this was just recommended by the CDC
But after quote
The agency would work with state and local authorities to in
Force this
I saw the Washington Post article about this and it seems to directly contradict Alex's claims about their being five more
Flights
Before the plane was clean
From that article quote
The plane Vinton that's the nurse traveled on arrived in Dallas at 8
16 p.m. on Monday
And remained overnight because it was done with flights for that day
And then what we found out she had a bowl that we blew that s*** to the Moon
Exploded all over the f****** place
After that the plane received a thorough cleaning per our normal procedures
Before Reserve resuming service Tuesday
Frontier said in a state
I was able to find the article that Alex
Misrepresenting
There was a piece of the Denver Post
For the headline quotes
Emails out to passengers on five Frontier flights after Ebola patient
Flu
As it turns out the airline did send notification to the people who are on the same plane that the nurse had flown on
But it wasn't because they had
You cleaned it was out of an abundance
Precaution
The plane had been clean
But later the nurse was diagnosed with ebola and by that point that anyone knew anything
The plane had already flown five additional flights
Informing the customers is definitely the right thing to do in terms of
Making sure everyone's informed
Even if you followed every preventative
Appropriate
Stop it still
Aboveboard
To tell people they can make their own choices from a healthcare perspective
Not telling people would be
Far greater Scandal for you later they be like
F*** you guys yeah it would be wrong
This article points out that after the nurse was diagnosed
The plane was going to undergo even
Further cleaning
Quote including replacement of seat covers and carpet in the vicinity of the passenger seat
But this still doesn't
Support Alex's
Pick up trash
Sure I think he's just trying to scare people
I think I should I think we should treat all diseases like The Velveteen Rabbit
And just immediately burn everything involved
Everywhere
I think I might be going a little bit
Play Pendulum the other direction
Everything
All stocks and bonds in the airline pandemic
We have not seen what it's like to burn everything to the ground in queso
I would love to live in a world where we still have
Who pandemic and then also everything is burning
That would be afraid that would probably be an issue
You're probably right
Silence is covering this news and I will say he has
Lassie take
He is dealing with things in a really
The newsman
We are
The Ebola
Vomit bag
The Obama
She's Mio Bola toilet
You know memes are very very powerful
And that's why we want this contest it's only running for another week
Infowars.com contest print off the Flyers hanging up shoot video of it
Send us a video will post it and then a week later on Halloween
I will announce the winner
#Ebola contest
Hellboy
Wow
Tagged
Bola contest contest
He has posters that are advertising for Infowars you record yourself
Putting them up
I think this is a weird contest could you be my street
Realized
Is that Alex is paid by big
Disease
Ignore
You spread disease
Man it's
It's really weird that you would think of
Somebody engaging response
Jubilee with topically recovering wouldn't be like
Hey let me try and use this as a cheap stunt meme promotional opportunity
Possible pandemic that could murder and incapacitate millions of people
We need a contest to advertise
My s***
A good dude
To Alex's credit or not I'm not sure
I'll let you decide
He doesn't spend the entire show
He also gets around to some nonsense narratives about how Christians are under attack
We have just
Absolutely over-the-top important news on the Ebola front
On the economic front on the Second Amendment
On the police state front
Houston literally trying to intimidate churches
And they're not giving sermons
The criticized transsexual
Behavior or homosexuality
Libertarian group semen coming out and even though they are
Open the other lifestyle
They are defending these preachers because
If you're going to have your right to live the way you want somebody else has to have their right
To live in
Nnn
Speak
Claiming authoritarianism
Pun intended
Out of the Houston mayor and the rest of
At best
That's word Play Churches
Europe
This is a model
Everything you see the political correctness out of Europe in Canada
Is coming
They are rest
Preachers that criticize homosexuality
So this isn't going to surprise you but Alex is lying about this story
Here's what he
In 2014 Houston passed an equal rights ordinance
And put included protections for members of the lgbtq community
Terms of housing
Employment and what-have-you
This is on the Vanguard of the right-wing Panic about trans people in bathroom so what are the hot-button issues was that
According to an article in the Washington Post
People Bard access to a restroom would be able to file a discrimination
Right
It's worth noting that the religious entities were also exempt
Did from this rule
So they weren't even
They weren't even involved
A group of citizens filed a lawsuit aimed at repealing the ordinance as part of the part of that lawsuit quote
City attorney's issued subpoenas to five local pastors during the case
Does Discovery phase
These pastors were alleged to have connections to the people who filed the lawsuit and we're active in the effort to repeal the ordinance
So the attorney's request
Beaches presentations or sermons related to Hero that's the Orton
Parker homosexuality
We prepared by delivered by revised by or approved by you
Or in your possession
The question that was being posed by these
Subpoenas were whether or not these pastors were using their churches at political organizing ground
Would you put their tax-exempt status on Jeopardy since Texas
Exempt churches quote are not allowed to engage in partisan
By October 16th the day that Alex is Huron
Controversy have been raging about this and The subpoena was revised to just ask
Score quote also
Speeches are presentations related
To hero or the petition prepared by delivered by revised by or approved by you or
In your possession
And as we know
Now that we live in the future the government really crack down on that and churches were no longer allowed to act
A political position
That would just be wrong dance
Didn't you see so many churches across this country
After Trump was elected did you see them lose their 501c
C3 status all over the place with political positions
Terrible
Complex topic
Gets into a lot of those
Is use more than anything else
You know you could make it an argument that there was over-reaching
Andover broadness in terms of the subpoenas that were put out by the city attorney's
I think that is a fair position you could take
Reporting this as like they're suing these dirges know
Know someone
Sued the city in Mississippi
Is doing discovery
Anyway
You just wants to take this
I am.
He wants a boiled down into a misrepresentation this easier for his audience to understand and more importantly be mad
Yeah
Walking out of control
PC culture
It would be nice if
Christ had lived in
Super cool cuz then maybe Christian
Things wouldn't constantly feel like
Playing the victim is the only way to deal with
I don't know
Cool do what Christ was just like the Buddha and he got old and everybody's like man you kicked ass
Invented
Person to say cowabunga
Jordan
I got to say what is it
Expect
On this episode
As I was getting a
What was a pretty big
Certainly has
Mirrors and
Echoes covid-19
Situation
What is expected
A large portion of this episode would end up becoming a movie review
I
Believe
I was a little bit surprised
Know the movie review is about
The movie Kill the Messenger
About Gary Webb
Okay
It's very personal for Alex okay because he apparently knew Gary Webb
Oh
This might be a little
Too personal Alex seems to be dealing with some stuff
After watching this movie
And you might make like a confession that I don't believe is truth but if
Cruise that Alex Jones is the worst
F******
Outlaw radio killer
Whistleblower guide
Call Kill the Messenger last night
I expected it to be a whitewash
I expected it to she don't imply that he killed himself
And it was absolute truth
Because I remember Gary Webb on the show more than 10 times
I had all these incredible conversations with Gary Webb off air
Do you want me to build a website
Light for him
He sent me all these documents that
The CIA has broken in his house a bunch of try to get
Making babies with my wife
Suicide
Thousands of pages of this stuff
Court records
I guess I'll put it out
Gary Webb
Now I hit movie out about him
And it was so surreal to be sitting there in the movie theater
I ignored that
And knowing Is All Storage so accurate
I am baffled by this movie review
I think there's a small part of Alex's pissed off that he's not in the movie
It's very weird that he's like
Yeah you know what
I had
That dude
Giving me all this
Secret documentation that the CIA was trying to
The kill him for Havoc
I was busy
I was making
Babies with my white out wasn't interested in those
Thousands of
CIA cover
Document
Blow the lid off of everything
But come on guys she's ovulating what am I going to do if I do think this isn't
I think it is story is not
True but
It's interesting the way he gets himself off the hook for having not broke
Open things
Can other stories I don't have time for this
So let me ask you a
In the beginning
I thought I heard him say I thought they were going to whitewash
And heavily implied that he did commit suicide
What you did
And then he said which suggests to me that he thinks he did
He didn't Alex thinks that he didn't like later on he said
A few days before he committed suicide
Alright so
That might have
Just been Alex's like
Sort of subconscious leaking through a big
You know what what are the reasons I think this is all bulshit is
This
Oh my gosh that shows important
I felt
Incredibly guilty
That I don't even know where that disc is
That CD-ROM
Open. But it was just
I don't know
Process
Copart
Talk about how I had that been working I like the killing people over the stuff
And then I went to
Last night when I got home
I went to bed I woke up middle the night went to search
Our
3 a.m.
4 a.m.
Couldn't even find one interview
I did was Gary Webb
Anna makes me think maybe you didn't interview
Hi Betty did I could see that absolutely haven't happened
That a certain point
It kind of God of Wonders like
Are you did you imagine all of this
It did you have a like quiet conversation with Gary Webb hammerhead
You know that you have the CIA to kill anybody who has all this information
And like Alex has the
Did CD-ROM that Gary Webb had given him
Wright was following him they would know who you made the handoff with Alex
Absolutely
Alex's is going to lose it
He's got a
AOL
We don't need to worry about that
Looking dude
It doesn't even have a file cabinet
I was surveilling in the other night just too busy f****** his wife
Trying to make babies
I'm sorry
It's not even like that disc
It's not even an AOL sleeve Ethan a Moody Blues
Cover that he is just
Lost he's never going to find that thing floppy that's what he's got
This is weird
I don't know why I put myself even in those
Shoes
Choo choos of a helicopter
I imagine there was only one set of foot shoes
That's what I was
Scary scary Mary Webb
I feel like
Is there
Phone of authenticity and Alex's body
The 2nd
That the guy who wrote dark Alliance
Is giving you a CD
Secret document
You drop everything
This is a priority
Do you remember when Snowden released
Chip
Every news organization was like okay we're going to put 15 people on this we're all going to read everything
Single one of these documents we're going to write stories about it immediately Wold wasn't like I'm making police state
2005 busy sorry
Supposed
Have you ever tried to adopt kids in America from Brazil
I don't want to s*** on the idea of like prioritizing trampoline what have you
That's all good but
If you're somebody who
Fancy yourself an investigative journalist Mission it is
Just to get to the bottom of
The nefarious doings of the club
This Behavior
Strikes me as very tip of the spear was busy
Swear
You know what I'm saying
There's a sense that I got
From listening to this that like
Alex seems to think
But that movie might be about
And then watching how they demonized him and how they tried to
Kill his name before they physically killed him
And experiencing a lot of this myself
It was a surreal
I've never gone to see a movie
Where
From what I know it was so incredibly accurate
And so incredibly sad
And then I resonated with it
Because
They always make it about the individual if they can't disprove your facts
Demonize and destroy the individual themselves
Feeling in my stomach
As I realized that the clocks just took until they come and shoot me in the head twice
Plant drugs on me or shoot me
Point or something
It made me sad to watch all the cowards his editors and
IQ
You literally said that you didn't have
Describe I so sad for
He gave all those documents to those that there's a baby
We're not going to put those out he gave us
Little bit of an a******
Is just out of
Just do it
Documentaries
Shadowgate
Think you might be faking a lot of it so he ran
This clip to me was actually one of the more interest
The glimpses into how Alex operates in these circumstances
The people that are supposed to be cleaning the aircraft
Are told that they can't wear masks and gloves
Aircraft coming in out of West Africa
In some cases with vomit in them
Because it'll quotes
According to those articles in the moment
Offer steps for avoiding public Asteria
A different contagious threat
About the hysteria being a bigger problem than Ebola itself
Well now the New York Times is reporting on it
Today
I just left the juxtaposition of those two stories is fast
In the first one Alex is claiming that vomit filled airplanes are arriving in the United States from West Africa and not being cleaned
Obviously trying to create the impression
Are so many more cases of Ebola in the United States that were being told
This is America that can really only lead to people freaking out and behaving irrationally
But the New York Times says that freaking out in hysteria is just as bad right
You both and Alex
Infowars has been saying all along the public is very is a bigger problem
What was everywhere but freak
How can you possibly not understand everything he does exist
The only to heighten Hysteria
Yelling about how the borders wide open and vomit planes are arriving is not only factually untrue but it's also does
Going to scare people
Alex understand
That and it's one of the things that he does
Is on his show that I think is incredibly abusive
Exact
Push and
Pull simultaneously the people's mine
It's. Good he's in a weird almost like
Experiment
If
His experiment to me of like listening to his show would be somebody sitting in a chair like strap
Down in every 5 minutes just a little jolt
Old is giving you the emotion
Center of their brain
To sit there
For 4 hours
And feel this constant emotional pressure
Yeah
Now
Experience I don't think
Not that far off
Disconnect
From it so it doesn't affect me as much listening to it but not
The brain would be very antagonized
If you believe anything he said
Since I don't
I'm a little bit of news
You're right you got rubber on your brain now
Alex is kind of right
Caesarea is a very serious
Concern when it comes to Public Health matters
It's just that in this
Case he's one of the most
Hysterical
It's not
Cruel cruel to be like a nobody is serious crazy
And you're going to die like okay
Maybe not
Killing you but maybe not now hold on
What's up
I thought
Listening to
The original episode
About this. Of time and Ebola
Situation
And listen
To the beginning of this episode
I thought do you know this is horrible this is
Response
It's got a tasteless
2 habits
Cbolo meme contest
But I didn't think it was that weird
It's not weird enough for Alex Jones
Here's where it gets weird okay
They first showed that
It was her fault that she shouldn't have done it
An NBC news that Ebola patient
Contacting the CDC before flight agency says
Was told she could
Comply even though
She was in a bowling nurse
And even though she told him she had a fever
Well she wasn't Peter Pan
And I'm sick
Can I fly
You can fly
My dog has rabies
The mouth should I put it in the schoolyard a kitsch
Yes but the dog with rabies
End of the schoolyard
Kissing on the ground
I pick it up and kiss it
Yes that's a good idea
There's a cliff by my house 1000 feet
The Ebola patient CDC
Hahaha
I'm going to fly horses that was on the news just been around Ebola patient
I was reading about a patient I'm a fly of a fever
That's a great idea
They're not just turning off the default they're sending me a bowl of kids to school they're not cleaning up the apartment
Weird is going on and why are nurses getting it
What the family
Isn't getting
Either they're covering up that they have it
It's what
CIA whistleblower
Back in the middle of last month here mr. Steele
It was your cue that clip up later
He said he believed they would release a biological simulant
It wasn't a Bola
People sick or even kill
False flag
Possibly mr. steal our buddy
That's Robert David Steele
Yep that one's got the multiple time Project Camelot gas
The global of dead children enslaved on Mars bases
Robert David Steele
That dude's credibility is in
Incredibly love
You can't disprove it
Pakistan you try and go after
And I can clearly see you just
Taking this to a personal place
You can't prove that it's not a
Bio weapon
Sure not my job
Still I have been on Alex's show in September
To speculate about the possibility of a
False flag Ebola attack
But the fact that he was creating narratives about a bowl at that point
Is it really all that weird
The first case in West Africa from this outbreak was reported in December 23rd
And by March 2014 there was spreading happening
By July it'll reach the capital cities of Guinea
Liberia and Sierra Leone
According to
CDC quote
This was the first time Ebola extended out from more isolated rural areas
And into densely populated Urban centers provide
An unprecedented opportunity for dreads
So Ebola is on the brain as far as any context
And yeah by August very bullet
Scares being reported to hospitals in the United States
According to the advisory boards timeline quote
Before the end of the month more than 60 hospitals reported some type of scare to
The CDC
But none of the tests sent to the Aging
Return positive
For the virus
So at this point it was
In people's minds
Right right now that's what you would be talking about if you are going to say there's a
Texas
He's coming to the United States you're going to say 100% it's the flu know everybody's thinking
About ebola is worried about it.
Robert David Steele had every reason to shoot the shot when he did
Hit that was growing in
Security around the outbreak and it was affecting the psyche of the American public
If a case
Did end up coming to the United States he would look like he was way ahead of the story and he had a narrative
In place
Have no case ever arrived here he could just ignore it
Or claim that the globalist
Decided to go a different way with their evil plans there's no downside to this kind of spitballing
Consequences
As for the story about the nurse on the
Playing Alex is making up that NBC News reported that she did in fact
Check in with the CDC before getting on
On the plane
The problem is that Alex is acting like a CDC has a staff of like
12 people and everyone knows everything
Things going on
This very article that Alex is referencing a
Explains how everything a
At the time it was believed that this nurse had worn all the appropriate protective
Gear and as such she was considered a lower risk category of person
Technically titled quote
Uncertain risk
Before she flew the nurse called the CDC and talked to a staffer Who quote
Looked on the agency's website
For guidance
The spokesman Todd spokesperson said
The category for uncertain risk has guidance saying
A person could fly commercially if they did not meet the threshold of a temperature
Of 100.4
She had a slight fever but it was below that reading so technically she wouldn't have been barred from flying
Director freedom
Know that you had contacted the CDC when he made his comment.
But you shouldn't have flown
From the NBC news article quote
The spokesperson says he believes frieden said that
Set that
Because it should have been common sense
Text to Vinson
That you should not fly with a slight temperature
Even though we have a CDC guideline that says you're fine
Yeah I mean look
I don't I'm not going to defend all that is gold but the CDC is wrong
Wrong not her
Probably got we need better guidelines guidelines
Clearly
Side oversight sometime I can't see anything
More response
Possible if you are this person then
Literally going to
Direct to the CD f***
Not going to the website
It also frustrates me a little bit so I went to the website
I don't like that
Seems like maybe in this case
You should have brought it up
Flagpole
No fault of hers at home
I see President just being like what
I see bases being covered in terms of like
Clearly no one was acting with
Like malicious and absolute
There wasn't even like
Covert negligee
Just this is
How an oversight can happen
It seems like like basically I'm saying is like if he
Decisions
Happened
Everything happened the way it did
They're certainly not enough here to justify speculating this is a false
Flag outbreak details
Anything but a false I don't know I don't know
Volkswagen
Honestly it's more his
Hysterical hysterical
For it to not
Be a false flag
Because they did something surprising as
Do we know
Everyday does this sound hysterical
Also does this sound
Familiar
Let's continue here
911 emergency dispatchers instructed
Not to say Ebola over the radio
That's out of Fox News d.c.
How to create
Code
To describe
Eyeball it probably is already spreading in the u.s. grade
Breed first and then they'll
Not where it all began or where it started and how it's all Obama's fault
And it's going to bring in a medical tyranny
Fortune aculation
Annabella Melinda Gates Foundation
Dedicated to population reduction in the Monsanto vaccine they produced
I'ma say that again Bill Gates Wiki boarding you about people
He wants to put a bolo shot in
You think that's going to be good for you. It's exactly the same
Cheese's
Shockingly.
I probably felt just as real to his audience
In 2014
As it does to people listening to him now
Hip AIDS
So
It's it's outrageous
It's just that circumstances were handled differently
And of course
Ebola and
Covid-19
They transmit differently
Require different
Responses
This is amazing
It's just it's almost
Script
It it almost felt like you
Could just take Ebola out and put covid
Or Coronavirus
Exactly the same
It is it is kind of
7 years ago
It is
I think a Lester do
The
Level of
Power
That Alex and his ilk
Patent
14 as opposed
Is 2 in
That level of influence was Far lesser and their effect
Far lesser not to look at this
As a
And it's not again there difference
Diseases
It's not a one-to-one
Compare insurance
But it's hard not to look at
Get the difference
Between 2014 and
No one
Should be held accountable for at the very least
You know
Truly a f***** up
I think
The people need to be held accountable
I think that one of the differences that you see is little people responded
What kind of more appropriately
At that time at least people who are actually making decisions and end
And being a dog
Right
Oh
I don't care
And the president wasn't repeating things Alex
Yeah
Think I think
Pickles better
One could make that argument
I've gotta
Yeah I think it would be a hard one to convince
If you're somebody who's
I don't know in the past and you're listening to Alexandra
Some of the stuff that you saying about ebola seriously
I would say like maybe you should hear this and be like
I'm going to turn this
Tonight to get groceries you heard about the phenomenon and government buildings suddenly
The people are peeing on the walls and going the bathroom and cubby holes and
In the hallways you know the bathrooms are working perfectly fine
And smearing all over the walls
This is what mental patients do this is what people
You are above the law start doing
Running around going to the bathroom
This is what happened
The government is so out of control and Drunk on Power that they were pooping and hold on hold on
I just literally Road
So I didn't know what I was talking about and it seemed really silly it so I decided to look into it and see if I can figure it out
I figured it out
So in late August 2014
There was some stories going around
About 8
Particular a EPA office in Denver which had quote
Been beset by roughly a dozen suspected incidents of a restroom shenanigans
Translate 2030
Being according to emails
Memorandums an incident reports
Restroom shenanigans
That's fun
Apparently someone who's f****** around
Unclogging toilets with paper and putting s*** in the hallway short
This is clearly the work of an unstable individual who works at that office
But here Alex is reported this as some kind of proof of the corrupt decadent to the government delete this so bored of me
Pirates there's a new phenomenon of everyone's shiting in the hallway weirdo getting his rocks off and
Really uncomfortable way
Alright
I love you like
I could be able to look
Back in the past and like seeing the wave at these stories get
Twisted by Alex into being so much larger than they actually are
He does in a way create more Fantastical in
Interesting stories
It's obviously a fairly interesting story that someone's
Putting s*** in the hallway at anyway
Sure
Kind of interesting more fun to imagine that
Government is run by Dean
Freeman tire and two are so bored
Did they have to ship
Is the hallway to get off it is kind of funny
It is flies a lot more interesting stuff is happening
In a world that was
Wasn't so much like Alex's
Weird dark circus versions of government
And then we lived in one
Is this bad
No good so at this point
In 2014 you really have psych
Gentleman speak
Creely kind of vibe
Oh that's not good they didn't really have the lawsuit
Why no protective gear for men with Dallas Ebola patient we have video This Will Roll some of it the background
Video from CBS News up on infowars.com
Prisonplanet.com
This lends Credence to Rob do running around the office
Analyzing video and he's work
Home Shopping Network
You know he's he's being Direct
Geno's Steaks.
And that he says that you know why are people not wearing protective
With the Ebola patient
As we have right there
And I usually people just don't care they're idiots
Or is there a third possibility would that be
So there was a video of people putting all that nurse
Into a play
They said I was making around
And all but one of the people are wearing Hazmat
Batsuit
It definitely looks like fodder for Alex to make it a
Conspiracy out of a Abdu to use
To justify crisis actor theories but it's not really that crazy when you get down to it or yes
The question-and-answer
From somebody
This person in the video is not in any direct contact with the patient
Who's wearing her own set of protective gear as well
The chances of transmission are incredibly low based on how Ebola goes from
From person to person
That being said
I wouldn't do this to his that's just because of me
But it might not be that
Really f***** up or dangerous
This very article that Alex is citing in order to talk about the headline includes this passage
When a member of the Dallas CDC team was shown in the video and asked if it was a safe moment or not
He said he didn't have a problem with what he saw
The situation
Apparently met CDC protocol because the people in the hazmat suits were the ones
Assisting Vinson
And the plain-clothes man was not
They CDC spokeswoman said that they man maintaining
Inappropriate
Since when the patient for the amount of time on the tarmac
And it must be taken into account that Vincent was also wearing protective
Gear
This is how little some idiot like Rob do needs to justify denying people's illnesses and deaths
You just need some video of it looks
Strange that he didn't care to look into it all
The thing that I
I still have a hard time wrapping my head around
That we found out from all those Depp
At this point
Point-in-time
Apparently only PJ dub
In the entire Infowars fair with listening that's going like
Hello
Stop blokes
Exactly
Of all people you know what that might not be true but it's the only one we know for sure
Might have been some lower-level funk
Oceanaire
I think
It's probably in those people's best interest that we not know
Because for them to be able to bury the part of their lives if they work there
Might
Good for good for them if they've sick
And if they
I've gone on to live a better life
Isotope
So
Stage man
The stuff's probably staged don't think it's stage but okay
I don't know exactly what's going on but I'll tell you this most of this is staged
It's scripted
And they clearly want to bowl with the spread now you can fill in the blank of Y
My head is spinning at this point and I'm trying to contain my aunt
Even during the breaks I'm trying to
Container
Because I think about how they're trying to bring down this
Kill our prosperity
Makes me angry
You don't want people to be sterile
I mean I'm furious because they're killing all of us into
Destroying property clearly return to intentionally spread Ebola probably by Steve
Call husband
Area is a big problem too well let's keep it
Grounded
Real
Bloomberg two days ago
Has the government facilities that are designed for this
Because they wanted to spread they want plausible deniability
They probably got sleeper cells walking around spreading it
I didn't think they'd use Muslim radicals to bring it in before I thought that was just some
Islamophobe
But now it's star
Eclectic
God only knows
I think the other shoe is about to drop
About to happen I've been saying that for much
And now you see this bracelet
Might be a diversion
4 nukes are about to shut off cool
Not only do I believe that the government is intentionally spreading Ebola
He's also
Listen
I don't know what's going to let me preface by saying I don't know what's going on
Now let me certainly describe a false flag attack that and honestly
I want to go with a 50/50 shot at the diversion and you're
All going to die immediately
Let me go over the top in a
Comically scary scenario that I've dated for you
As a very distinct possibility based on my gears of research about how these logos
Also this whole islamophobic thing I was like oh no I'm not going to
Engine islamophobia
Video where guy was walking on the tarmac so obviously it's the Islamic people
People's fault problem
It's interesting
So he's going down this road you know like
Hysteria about Ebola
The man also they're going to Nuke you
Hey man we're just in trouble
I mean it is just we have enemies in control that there is no doubt
We are in the most grave danger this country is faith
In 200
40 years
Hardcore
I got goosebumps on my
Face right now
The camera can probably pick up
Take down to the country
Infowars life.com
I'm getting my immune system ready
Cena is a
Good
That's a good little
Super Transit
That's a good little at switch
He does now
It kind of hurts the preceding
Passage
Absolutely
Play Emily out-of-control fear-mongering
That led up to that
Kind of
Weathers the relationship between the
You too. Suffer
Yes I guess making people really afraid of a nuke
And Ebola would lead them to
To take zinc
I would say that Infowars life plug really only solves one of the two problem
Describe
And in fact I would argue V second one kind of wipes out the games of the first
Perhaps we'll
So whatever games we've lost
Shall now be recouped
Because Alex
Have a ghast
Boy howdy
This guy
Mike down for that because with this guest
Says
Weather alerts
Okay but he says
No damn it if we had a complete repeat of the bro
I was hoping
They do mention how like he had recently reported from
The demilitarized zone
Correspondents deeper traffic for a while
Steve Zahn
The talk about ebola and keep directly contradicts
Something that he says in the present sure
Amazing
You're also a medical doctor on top of that so you can
Kabbalah
Yes correct
And more importantly
I was trained
Cornell University
Medical College
Very confident
Infectious disease
Anthony
Fauci
God dammit
Goddamnit Dan one-year witch
N2
Steve pieczenik is a month
Monster
I swear to you ever since I was at Cornell he's a loser worst
Give me
Stacy's so brutal
You know who's great Anthony fauci
Breaks my heart
It really breaks my heart
And I was this is this is this mirror this act always so
Funhouse mirror is on the way I
Describe is so bizarre
Yeah no I mean
Listen
It's not that I believe the entire world is a
Prank on me
But when Steve says stuff like that I'm just letting you know what
This is
Real
The Ebola situation
Pretty serious
And I would take that outside of it being hilarious that he likes
Fauci now and then
The president claims to have always hated him or whatever
That's funny
A lot of the stuff you saying I really don't take much issue with
Can you sing this is serious
Are we have to do what we can to make sure
That do responsible steps
Isn't bulshit
But he does have a
I would say possibly
Maybe not
Good plan of
And repeatedly recommended
Is that doctor
Reason of the CDs
Resigned
Volume down
Because they really have no
And inefficient
And they have no authoritative
Bandai does it
City-state
Mandatory
Executive
Privilege
Authority
Military power
Public Health Service
That's a falchi
If you give an executive control to use military resources to deal with you
Kids
I love it I can't believe this
Asus
This is one of those
You know what's funny it's almost like
It's almost like the Mandela
It's almost like we're looking back into a past
It didn't happen in the present
You know what I'm saying
Like this is an alternate universe where
Help me put
Some pieces together
Because I always did think it was a little bit weird
That is the beginning of the coronavirus situation
Alex was painting fauci at a good guy you made some calls and looked into him
Hearing Steve talk about him like this talk about fauci like this
At this point makes me think I go alexnld Stephen school was like this is a good guy and then they got the line
The right-wing media is the villain
Maybe they're the biggest
Things that happen
That we need
Need to go back
Analyze
Is the creation of the fee
Feedback loop
Between
The right-wing proper
Buganda creating
Trump and then Trump
Echoing right way
When propaganda back
I don't know how you would ever know where you would look
For that I don't know
Oh
Kill all the baby hit
I I blame Drudge
Just fall down
F*** that guy
Alex really wants
This to be fake
False flag
Part of the episode
Really felt like Alex was essentially begging
Steve
Come on help me out man
DACA me you believe Sandy Hook was staged more more experts have come out in a grade
Boston bombing
So many other events 911
The open funding of Isis
Change the name from Al-Qaeda
All this is coming out
But when you look at this Ebola situation I'm not saying it's not right
It isn't living in the body longer before the symptoms show up 21 days
Clearly
Getting stronger
But it
Just I can't believe that this type of an aptitude
Bring in
Ebola patient
Level 42
Let people fly in
From
West Africa from ravaged areas what other countries had already banned at months ago
I need a
Wouldn't be
This precise
At doing everything they could to grease the skids for Ebola
Are you getting any information
On them allowing this to spread
Bring in a medical charity to create a political distraction
Are there any motives for this to be a false flag
No not really
Cuz number one
Create an epidemic
Fun dip
A very dysfunctional
Functional governor and
And a bunch of
Connecticut state troopers
And it was easy
Create
Kaneria was Nan
Oh boy
Interesting answer
Nope
Although this is this should make me think here's what we
We should do we should
All the right-wing terrorist
All whiter
Stop
I thought I thought like the one that was going around before the al-Qaeda was that what it was
About it before I think I used to say
I think I remember that one
I'll let you do a meme contest
Look dude this thing that I think is really funny Beyond just
Stevie like fauci is a great guy he should have
Control over everything
Alex being
Over-the-top give me something
Give me
Andy Ruiz
That I mean
Blue sky pictures
Jok'air give me
Possible motive no
Just money just save money you could do
Play money
No
More Illuminating that is that it's really difficult to create a fake
Epidemic
People wouldn't do that a lot
Why is it would be a bad idea
Easy to get out of hand millions of people could die
Impossible to control
Donatos not a supervillain plan
That would really work outside of the movie
I think I think is really interesting is that Alex is talking
Think about all of these things
And almost identical way
The medical TRNA all this stuff
The other mention lockstep
It all
I know about that document everyone in the document all blockstack.
Then it's been in there pretends to have known about all this stuff
This wasn't part of your narratives then
Beer
No one had shown you this
Existed in 2010 I mean in the in the right-wing Spears
Misrepresented
What it was
In a way that was profitable
And
You just see it very clearly that he just didn't have the
The Manor
Do that attack
At this point
Kind of
Kind of telling
I just
I'm just so
It's so easy
His job the right-wing propaganda jobs
Soe
Easy
You do the same s*** every 5 years for 5 years and then restart
Every time
It's the same s***
Yes
And God forbid
Ebola would have
Nice pridemore in the
United States
At this point
But I could easily see Alex
Score on the very similar
Just don't have people cough on you or throw up
The more effort the
It puts into stopping at the or he'd argue that that's what they're not the reason that they released this on us
Civil liberties
You can you can
Almost
Easily see how the Playbook
Operate
Based on the
Incredible
Similar parallels
You have here
Yeah it is
It is really surprising
I mean that's what I'm saying
It's it's like
It's the it's just
You can see it going down the same exact train of thought
No matter what time. It is B
Because it's the thought process
Itself that leads you to believe action towards a version is
Actually close
Yeah
Yeah I'm so it's it's the
Thought process
Itself
Not like
The
Circumstance
Changes is the circumstances
Allow it to balloon out of
Birth control or it
Contain
Deeply cynical
Cruel
The the way that Alex operate
And in this respect
It really is a
Denial
And
Des Des
Regard
For the fact that there are people who are suffering
Dealing with this
Disregard for the people or listening or probably scared
I need information
They need to be have conveyed
Accurate information that allows them to make
Appropriate decision
Like the emails that were sent out to the people who were on the plane after
Even though they're probably wasn't a reason to be worried
That's appropriate
Giving the people the information that they need to be able to make
Appropriate decision
These listeners
Are tuning into Alex cuz they think that they're going to get some kind of insight
That they're not going to
To get elsewhere and he's lying to them in a way that's designed to scare them
And it just too
Get their immune system ready with the products that he sells over divorce.com
And
As the world economy melts down gold will go up even as other Commodities go down
Because it's an ultimate store of wealth and a head
Against employing economies
And it is
Bond markets in the stock market was down so much today
I thought man I bet gold goes down but I said her maybe it'll go up
Because oil was way down I thought I wondered but man when I saw gold going up
That's pretty serious right there
The other thing is that their economic impact
That are happening because of the above the situation
There's some like Airlines
Stocks are going down yeah impact that are happening at Alex's using that
Final gold sales
Gold started 2014 at 12:05 and 77 Sunset
Peking orange
30th at 1327 dollars and thirty-nine cents
On October the
16 today this show is recorded the price was
12:30 $9
Announce
From the day before
It would close the gear at 1184 dollars and Thirty-One
Nothing Alex says means
His syndicator at this point is still a guy who owned
Gold sales
Took golden super important to his world in 2014 and it's weird
How it's so much less so now
So in order to talk about the bond market
It's falling apart and how cold is
Is great
Alex brings in his financial body Max Keiser
Max Keiser
I will say
Does not give a s***
That sounds right
She is not taking this seriously at all
I was such a so close to Gary
Norris
Any other crazy stuff in my life
Another Rider
Oliver North in Gary North
And that ended I didn't break the big CIA drug-dealing stories weather
Cuz I was just like yeah I already know all that
Tell your book you're a hero
Why why put out new document without a website with you Gary Webb
Killed him
Attack me for saying they killed him
The movie basically says they killed instead
Tell him I'm just I just am speechless
How powerful Kill the Messenger the story about Gary Webb
Pulitzer Prize all the rest of it is I mean it's simply amazing
How all is so-called friends turned against him
When the mainstream media said he was a fraud with no proof
Have you seen Kill the Messenger yet Kaiser
Sounds good though
I just feel like I dropped the ball monumentally
Not working with him more and help him get his material out man
We're still alive
What you pretty
Tell people that they don't want to kill up such a beautiful beautiful
Examples of a human species
Come on beautiful
Text guys did not give a s***
Yep nope
I like kind of
The fresh air like a little bit of
Come on
We're too pretty
Two pretty their interview ends with
Alex comes in from break and he's singing along with balls to the wall
He's talking about how this is a
Okinawan error
Pilot term
Jamming the throttle about the Berlin Wall
A protest
Song
A little bit later
Like I was like I got to make a correction
That's about going balls deep
It's actually it's really kind of funny moment
You knows that it's funny
Play along with the guys are always at dirty but he's got dirty guy
Can't do it either mad scene part
Guys are just kind of like he operates outside of
That are going on coz
GameStop
So rich
He doesn't care
That's fair
That's the type of rich
Nobody really do only insane people want to be billionaires I think everybody wants that point of just like
F*** these guys
That's what you really want
Go onto Alex's show and
Perpetuate
Max coin
Or whatever I can try and sell whatever
But I'm doing it
Is that can be fun
But I don't need it I can also
F*** with Alex
Billionaire show on RT I don't need it by 4 either
That's weird
But
Someone who does needles at 5
Alright 10 Anderson Johnny Anderson California
A loaner the gcn radio network he also is one of the biggest private gold dealers
AAA rating for the Better Business Bureau
19 years
Sponsor 419 I worked
In this time slot
At 4
18 years
I never want to go up against Rush Limbaugh
He's got a monopoly in cities and what station is going to want to have a show to go up against it you're on here
Not at night
If you want to work at those Network
Here I am in funny enough I'm now beating Rush Limbaugh
In ratings
Are you
Is it some stations can't afford Russia
And Alex's is free
Makes anti-magic
Yeah
Just offered to sell gold
Alex is out here like 10
A ball is causing problems we need you on quick to sell gold I've been panicking people all day
What is not on.
Magical
Now is the time
Iman to pitch gold
If you wait until the fall we're desperately go shop
If you wait until there is a big rush it's already up with a 20-something bucks today
Pull that up for me CNBC
Now is the time I believe
Silver or at least get some of the book
Or financial perspective documents that modest resources hat
Men like a year later Ted would lose his license
Cuz he's scamming seats kamegai
Yeah like this is kind of the payoff
Prestige of the the panic and
And they fear
That Alex has been
Been building throughout the episode with his hysterical nonsense
His
Talking about the bond markets falling apart then
With Max
Kaiser is a nice Bridge
Do the interview with Ted Anderson
In order to funnel people
To give them the solution to the problem
We've created this problem
That is
False flag Ebola
You got it
Change your money somehow and the only way your assets
Forgot to be safe
With this guy doll
My buddy who I've been working with for 19 years
Buy some buljan you've never seen and have them put it in a lockbox you don't know who is real
Yeah so I mean I look back on this
The Scientist by gold
But looking back on this episode it was shocking
To me I mean the reason that I chose it honestly
What nothing to do with it
Yeah I didn't know that this episode was about a bowl I just saw Steve pieczenik
You're a witch
Arigato f****** 2014 FIFA
Sonic boom let's do this let's see what he's bringing to the table
And I started love dr. fauci is what he's bringing to the table
It's so bizarre
Dark Twisted
Distorted version of the narratives that are being sold
In the present about coronavirus
Being
Reply to Ebola
7 years prior
I just with
Completely
Different
Clothes
Like back then
They could f*** around with crisis actor stuff
Cuz they hadn't been checked on that front yeah I know Rob do thinks that maybe these before
Anthony fauci wasn't somebody if it to Trump got into a fight with
Hero
Steve studied under at Cornell and they
They're tight
I you should have control of the military apparatus to deal with Ebola
Think it's fascinating
Wrongly
Reinforce my theory
But Alice is full of s***
If not.
Definitive proof
I would I would argue that the totality of our work
Definitive
Is might be good argument not to take
Seriously
Although
If you need further proof
Go to dr. fauci
Poop band
Poop
My Wizardry I love when you
You bring witchcraft of the table damn
I'm uncomfortable with her
Kind of regular in
He's really kind of frustrated
Again
Everything is a prank on me
Beginning to believe that
Thoroughly
Well
Coronavirus didn't happen
Gaston
That'll be an elaborate plan if I was the only one who actually quarantine
Yeah that would be in
I don't think
Feasible
Although doubtful did read a white paper
Are there were there
Seen a lot of false flag
Also the other thing before we get out of here that was thinking about
That was without Alex
Like
Just a joke that he says I have the
The document
I mean like
He's claiming that he has these documents from Gary Webb
It's like
Do you
Or did they ever exist
Anytime buddy says he has the documents it might be just
Some
CD
ROM that may or may not exist in a warehouse somewhere that has no f****** idea
Be protected like a Holy Grail he would think that that would be
Mysteriously organized
Sirius Howard
Proof of all the conspiracies that have ever been at least the building block
That would get you to wear something
Is solidly proven
I think I may be billed from
And I think that would be really important for him cuz
As far as I can tell from the
The Bedrock of like
So many of these conspiracies
Primary sources that you go back to that just don't hold up
So he did have
These Secret
Classified documents
You would never let you
Can handcuff it to your wrist
Yeah
Absolutely
So that we did not record
I played this clip for you though the two guys that we were talking about
Watch the 20-minute conspiracy theory video and I only played you one clip from it and it was the guy narrating it say
About a month ago I lost all of them
F*** off
Yeah
There is a certain irony to us complaining about this
When were only recording this episode because of a Tek Rex
We didn't prove anything in that episode of Lila to observation
Who's just asked
Some laughs with ads
Never be had
Publicly
Jordan
Visible phone
Episode got lost
Here in the near future
Find something that we can go over
Anyway but I bet
Let's let's
Let's Travel back to the present day alright
Alright
Thanks to Mr Peabody for bringing us back to the president.com
Runs over Twitter
We are 20 minutes away. Go to bed Jordan
That was raining again if you could please find a local charity or bail fund interior to help out
People doing.
I was back but until that time.
Dzx Clark
I'm Daryl rundus
I am the leader of the poop Bandits
Alexandra Thurston color