Airjordan.com
I have great respect for its knowledge B
Need money
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Hey everybody
We're couple dudes
It's around technology Beverages and talk a little bit about Allie
Alex Jones
Jordan
What's up
My bright spot today
Is
Okay I think we might wind up having a very similar bright spot was last night we celebrated
Friends birthday.
Health Ranger our friend who is not a health Ranger
John fantastic
Time we
Master lights the light full time
I was at
Around the bartender asked me to leave
I guess I can't have that be my my bright spots
Got a message from one of our listeners a policy wonk out there
Who had the music
That they had made that they wanted to wanted a review of a little bit of a
Alright this is
Every
And I checked out you have Spotify
It's great it's so pop-punk kind of vibe
Listen to the album here's to better misery
And I enjoyed it quite a bit
And I can say that sincerely and I think that's probably why it's a bright spot it's because I don't have to be
I don't have to
YouTube
I love it with a fan.
Yeah I enjoyed it thanks for sharing that
Made Eric appreciate it and
People want some pop punk
Check that out
Jordan
Yes sir we are back into
The President's Day
I've gotta February 28th 2021 blackjack
I waited until you had your mouth so you couldn't respond
That was kind of cheating on my part
Today's episode of a recording us
One of the reasons why I wanted to do this episode for the Sundays I wanted to see you
C-pack is running
Of course you are
I just I remember last year
Such Heights
It was a big deal last year
So much
So much going on it was a celebrity field affair
Exactly
He missed his own speech at the end is supposed to be the headliner Nick Fuentes behind took over the show
Fireworks
It was a Enrique tarrio made a joke about how there's probably enough be a conformist
Which is funny
They was
Outrageous
It was such a good time
That Z-Pak event
There was so much going on
So much nonsense
And it's just
Such a sign
How sad
It's now like he's not even going
BC
Z-pack is Anya
He's just sitting in the studio
Having a show last year it was like it was
Is full-on the Gathering of
The Juggalos
Level but forget a white mask
Grateful to not have to have payday
A single Iota return
Attention to seapac
As some have
Because I just do
Don't care
The value of this
Episode
Is that
Going on during Trump speech it's a program
Which means that Alex
Who plays the speech most
Play 21st hours
And a little bit of commentary but there's still a couple of things that I find
Circularly important and one thing
They drove me a little bit
Crazy
What's a
Uno
Spoil yourself
Before we do any of that
Miscellaneous
But miss
Yell at you
I'm a policy wonk Mademoiselle Aeneas
I love your work thank you so much
Thank you very much. We subpoena the juiciest ice cream
Can we subpoena or
Giuseppe
Giuseppe's Giuseppe
No I'm not good with names
Okay next
MSRP thank you so much right now about what
Next Sully the Canadian youth
From what I hear
This
Refers to Alex Jones to the
Jody man with demon voices
Yeah
I'm about to jump into here first
Thank you so much urine out
Technocrat
And is this is this is tough
Lauren be thinking about your technocrat
And also happy birthday
2 weeks ago
Retroactive
We're not doing this current anymore
We will do a 6-month late
Sliding birthday shoutouts
Highway Lord I Hope two weeks ago you had a great birthday
And you're not attacking
Heroin
Freakishly large
Thanks so much
So Jordan
This is going to be a little bit of a briefer episodes going to be a little bit shorter and one of the reasons
Like I said
Right
Yeah
Out to you know get this keep a crap I thought they would be like a lot of
Condense things to
Reflections
I know it's a big old
A little bit of running commentary of trump speech sure with a couple of
Completely absurd thing
Thrown in
And I'm so
You know it starts pretty much
How you would expect it to
February 28th Sunday live transmission just started speaking
Florida
Control corporate press in big Tech are trying to censor and block
Everywhere where we hear from the real
President
Let's hear from the Imposter let's hear from the puppet
Who just did a Victory lap
Friday
Houston Texas
Yeah so Alex is setting the table with Trump is Lee real president
Sure
Good grapes healthy
Smile
Music clip of Biden
Saying some words that
It sounds like he is confused
That his
Brain is deteriorating right
This makes quite this kind of
Like indicative of how
Good Lord
Chunk of this
The show ghost
It's really just Alex getting excited
Well Trump gives a speech
We will be victorious
Herbalist
Alright
Alert
Portion of the speech
That errors on Alex's
Is it version of trump speech
Is a lot of fear-mongering about
Sure why not what are we what are we doing
It's pretty heavily hitting that that tone
Yeah and I found it to be alarming
Upsetting
I was surprised by one
And that is
There's a little bit of time to
F*** around
Best beef stew
Respect
Absolutely
Happy trails
America
11 player Buddies
Video really
I find that funny
Play Rush
Looking down at us
He's loving it you loving her was easier
Did he crossed himself
Did he pour one out
Sebring Crossing his finger
He strangle of parole in front of everyone
To celebrate the little hamburgers
A while back
50 years ago right after the election
Okay
After Trump had lost
There he was going to
Start his own party
People pretty excited about this because
There
Intercourse rightfully people on the left are like please do that
Yeah yeah yeah absolutely
Google go white nationalist and equator
Unblock
It turns out this is fake news
Never going to do that
Cancel the Republic
Yeah basically announcer
We're not starting new party
We have to Republic
Craigslist
The fuk up
Mr McLoughlin just gave me numbers that nobody's ever heard of me
Just like you saw with green and Jordan other people
5.71 point
5.70 points
All the super hardcore Trump candidates
50/50 before
20 point
Marjorie Taylor Greene want her race
Essentially unopposed
The Democratic candidate had withdrawn from the race due to personal matters
Why she won
Also a simple scan of the history of that District Georgia
Is 14th it disproves Metallica saying
In the 2018 election Republican Tom Braves won with 76.5% of the vote
Pro-slavery platform in 2016 2014 and 2010 Graves ran unopposed
In 2012 he won with 73% of the vote
According to the Cook partisan voter Index this is a republican Plus
27th District heavily Republican
That in addition to her opponent withdrawing his wife Marjorie Taylor Greene one
Not because pro-trump candidates are so exciting and then
Super-mega popular
How
Dario
You don't care about voting
You think that the election was stolen
Election
Well
Yeah because the election was stolen
B b like
If it happened
But still like they would want to like
80% of 90%
Popular people are
Well I guess I stand correct
You should know better
At this point I'm so Jordan
I
You know
Super Bowl
I
I definitely got into Alex's
Commercial styling
It's a very weird a breed
It was
Super Bazaar
Now
This episode of listening to through the gcn
Genesis Communications network speed
Which is the company that does Alex
Syndication
So all of the radio station
Forget this feed
Play Alex
The show
These are the commercials
That are put on
Along with the back
These people who sponsor Genesis
Communications Network
And
I listen to one of these commercials
And it really really upset
Oh no
Here is the thing that blew my mind and almost drove me crazy
The Final Phase of extermination
Is population
They cover for mass die-off is evolution and global warming
Used
From the lines that were disinherited 2,000 years ago
Go to nfl.com
That's unv
Whoa
Wow
Do you have any idea
Did you make sense
His his at his voice
And the way he's delivering it and the kind of
Choppy nature of the end of the
Since in the beginning
Give a new one makes it sound a little bit like
He's a synthetic robot voice or somebody
Speaking like
Somebody wearing a mask speaker
Vocalizer
My time of trying to get into voice-overs for commercials they like a lot of the time
If you're not a
Pretty good editor
It'll sound rough
Because you're trying to jam it into a very
Specific
Span of time
Got to be 30 sec
It cannot be 28
Whenever you're not that good you'll end up sounding like that
And that's that's kind of important
You stood in the content
And how is that like
Did you take away from
What ice
Thought I heard was that some people are claiming to be
Christ
Are related to Christ may be alright because it is unveiling them
Them so there's a group of people
Haha
Who are doing that
Now what I don't
Understand is
How the
Population die off
And the fake climate change and such
Ties into the people they're selling
That's a good question for it's nothing
Alright
Commercial hit me a little weird
And honestly it's
Speak to the level of sponsors that Genesis
Communications network is able to attract
That's terrifying
I checked out this website and apparently the person behind it believes that the MMR vaccine is created Iron
Poisoning in the population
Which is the cause of all disease
Now I should be
Be clear there's actually the iron poisoning goes much
Deeper than this
It goes back
Quite a long ways and the MMR vaccine is really creating it as much as exacerbating it
It causing problems for people who are already iron poisoning
All right so even if you didn't get the MMR vaccine is what
You don't worry
Worried you're still f***** you're still iron poison apparently the Euphrates river is actually the Mississippi
In the real population of the United States
Just about 200 million
As it turns out only people with
A b blood type are safe from this iron poisoning
I have to admit this site's argument is a little bit difficult to follow
Kind of
Inevitably drifts into a little bit of British Israel ism
America's you're reading through
Through this
There's one page on the site titled round them up
Which argues that everyone in any position of influence in the world is in on this plan to poison everyone with iron
I need they would have to
This includes
All of mainstream and alternative media which I think would include Infowars includes damn near everybody up
About these media entities there's a note
In bold letters
Quote commandeer these immediately there's a note
Wheatland on the website
Yes
Like it's something that's a
Like it's on the refrigerator if I commandeer those first
Like literally everyone is in on the plan
Including quote all nursing and assisted living homes all corporations
Water treat
Facilities
And food and beverage industry farms and ranches
What would I think
Is that kind of thing
I have to work but ignore that have
Is
Iron poisoning the other half
Well
Apparently
This breaks down
30 people who are a b blood type
They're not
Iron poison
Okay their blood type is not susceptible
To the iron poison
Yes
Something to do with a question
Quite able to figure this out but it's something to do with like a b blood
Being
Found on the Shroud of Turin okay
Alright Jesus
I don't know
Not so they're not going to be hurt by things like the covid-19 vaccine
It'll take out all of the people who have iron poisoning
They are the vaccine will like
Exacerbate the parasites or whatever the inside
You do to iron poisoning
Can we do a follow-up on
Like can they
Because we will know in the future whether or not her correct
So I would imagine that
Next year
Let's meet let's make a gentleman's wager
Me
Into the British Israelites
I don't know if this is mainstream British as realist thought
As much as visit
A very weird geocities ass page
Starting a very convoluted
I think that's basically what's going on
There's these people who are a b blood type
And there
Poison they want to get the
Vaccine in people who have a or b
Cuz it'll kill all of them off chair
And in order to avoid this horrifying conclusion
The page literally says quote
Round up everyone of them
Account for all 40
13.3 million in the United
States place them in holding areas
For out-processing
Now I'm against a b blood type
They are those
I hate found this
Very
Confused that's a little that's a little
I don't think they're going to win in the end
I'll put it that way
On the one hand is a deeply pathetic state of affairs that Alex's radio syndication Woods
Website like this that doesn't actually appear to be selling everything
On the other hand it
It's deeply disturbing something for them
To be intentionally or a
Accidentally promoting to Their audience
This website is explicitly accusing people at everyone who has a b blood type of being part of the
Conspiracy to kill off the publican
Rounded up
Big people little irresponsible
Yeah I was curious about this a joke around a little bit more
Apparently this page
Has been up since 2003
And there are some snapshots of what
Used to promote on the Wayback machine
It turns out my feelings about this seeming a bit anti-semitic or act
From the page
As it existed in 2004
Quotes they are murderers and
Thieves and destroy the truth and destroy the Earth and Mankind
Now is the time to destroy these two
Destroyers
They are the ones who claim to be Jews who are not
All right there we go
Alright
The board
This point does not appear to have any connection to the iron poisoning
Conspiracy but
Instead
It's just classic anti-Semitic screeds
Basically the protocols of the Elders of Zion
Great white 2008 decided a turd added the iron poisoning
Clear the argument being laid out by this website
Is that
Jewish people who aren't really Jewish are running around
And they're going to poison the world that iron in order
Vertical iwanoff down the road
All right so this a b blood type I think it is a way of talking
When Alex complains about how everyone thinks he's a Nazi it's important to remember that his radio buddy you know run
All of his
I'd like radio syndication affiliates
You know
He's he's responsible
Paralysis radio career
That guy is willing to accept advertising money
To promote a website but essentially Advocates rounding up
Jewish people I would really prefer and I'm going to go out on a limb here
And I think this
Look there's going to be an unpopular play
But I don't
Care what side of
The political aisle you're on
I think rounding people up is usually a bad
Yeah it just going to go out there I'm going to say that I know it's an unpopular thought then yeah it's
It's not a sign of a healthy
Body politic
Let's think of all the historical examples of people being rounded up
All of them worked out well
Nevermind
I found this
Bizarre
Confusing
I would never have imagined
Isn't that something like this would be
Able to
Secure and advertising slot on Alec
I was going to say it must be really fun
F****** cheap
Dirt cheap for just a random ass website to be like Al by
Consider what is maybe this person is independently wealthy
So maybe
It's not that cheap and there's like f*** it
I can't get the word out about iron
Possible
Second possibility
Is it is that you
Just think about it like
There's no big businesses knocking down pad 200ml
On this s*** no one wants
Yes bottom-of-the-barrel stuff absolutely also see this as just us
Favor
Almost all advertising on TC and just being dead being my man
Batman if that's a favor then
Opens up another can of worms and that is like
They know what's being
And they are willingly disseminating
Supporting this
I would have to I mean there's no way that somebody does
Doesn't know what's B
You know what I would
I would believe a world exists
Where no one knows what
Wait the check cleared
I don't give a
Exterminate that works for us
What's this iron poisoning
Okay
I'm not going to look into this for
Just a little while to find out that you are a deeply anti-Semitic
K clique
Close enough
Getting ready to get on the network come on. Going to check in on what your
Pausing to the point where I run
Alternative media
Becoming beer demita
Where is that
I could do like the idea that
There is a 30-second spot
With the website
In it
And no one bothered
To look at the web
I'm not positive what I think is more upsetting
The idea that they didn't check
Is it someone checking it
Spine
Neither either is pretty a pretty scary
Give me a VIP event like
Some of Alex's audience might go to that website be like oh my
My God
If Alex would promote this
You'd allow this on his show then there's got to be something
Time to it I think the only thing we can
Can do is
Get our own ad spot on gcn
Wow
I think we
I think we should try it maybe we know
We could
Yeah we got to get another website
Oh yeah I know we can't be
That is good that we're planning is on there
Alright I'm going to I'm going to work on this I'm going to see if we can
The point is Bill never know when it's coming
We can announce it's going to happen and you maybe that's the real torture there they'll always
Be wondering
When is it going to rain
Alright so we get back to Alex now
That is deeply upsetting
Little row. I went down
Also deeply upsetting Alex is really thrilled that no one is wearing masks
And she was almost done with wearing masks in the seat back event
These are good people
Elizabeth Smart
Slacking to look great
Good night sight wow I would assume
Wow
Alex started the show talking about how Trump
Why is the rightful president
Upsetting
It's more upsetting when Trump himself
Says that on stage at sea bass
You're watching coverage of President Trump's ongoing live speech
About 20 minutes behind
We are going to the live show
I may even decide
To beat them for a third time
Okay
Hitches
Yeah
That's what you need
That's alarming
Rainbow
Just can't we you can't keep doing this
No no no no
No
Refutes
Yeah you know what like
When 2000
The election in two
The Supreme Court awarded the presidency to Bush using all of the president that was available to
But the time which is not and then they were just like
I think little lot of people rightfully or inaccurately felt like that was a
Stolen election
I don't work all people insisting that Al Gore was the rightful president
And I don't recall Al Gore giving speeches
Where he said I'm actually the president instead he went
Focused on
Climate change
Yeah I don't focus on climate
Old Monroe.
Bungled go back inside of a very small hole and stay there
I just
Find this to be untenable
I can't I can't
Imagine
These kinds of rhetoric
These these kinds of things
But leading anywhere positive it's it's
It's going to get another storm another cannibal what does rape it happened on the 6th
And in response to that they changed none of their rhetoric so it will happen again
That's how
It does seem that way
So Alex
Steve's one of those influential voices
In the world
The true most influential voices in the world
And there might be surprised
Hula hula
The famous Alex Jones saying my son always says it was a joke
Podcast
Target
Snow
Authoritative
Influential
General Public
Thought leaders
Across the planet
You can probably imagine who listen to the show
One of them died just a week and a half ago
He listened everyday
Real
So this is not about brackets but understanding
This broadcast is a Brain Trust
Catfish Hunter
And lied about
Demonize because we go to the source document
And you're over the Target store get the most
We got great products you already need
Straight
Yeah there's no way Rush Limbaugh listen to Alex everyday
I can't think
Give anything Rush Limbaugh did less
Then listen to Alec
Text jokes you do you know what's
I mean like he's on air
4 hours
Himself
And then you imagine like oh yeah he's going to spend his off time listening to
Someone do a
Exactly
I find this to be so fascinating idea that Alex thinks that his audience
But he thinks that his audience will believe that
Like really
Serious people take him seriously
I can't imagine
Anybody who is like
Critical thinking they're engaged
Listening to showing up being like this is stupid
Insanely stupid
It is
Stupid on a level
Mobile vet like
Can truly comprehend understand being tricked by like a little
Clips or Snippets Ooltewah something into thinking that I want to show you something that it's not
It is dumb it is
Incredibly dumb
It's Meandering is often pointless
Eight so full of emotional outbursts
It's a Psycho Drama that he's having
He's engaging
The audience
Just bizarre
Well I mean we
Saw I mean literally
Playing a
Clip
Somebody doing just
That too
Republicans attic
You know like
He's playing a clip
Trump saying nonce
No reasonable person would
Seriously at all
Everybody
50% of the goddamn world is like imagination
It's wild
Yeah
Creature of Comedy
We know that mean machine he is
Indeed
Sometimes he has to be dragged
Screaming
Into doing
Horribly racist
Disgusting comedy
Teeth with this guy
Regatta
Is there a lot of requests for Fentanyl
The Communist Chinese dragon
To make a return
Bummed out with the news but I've decided to be my get pumped out with a dragon
For fun
Because the global want to get our first down something to do it
He's a little racy a little a little gross my wife thought it was a little much
I told mcbreen who made it
Repulsive
Kids love adults love it
What did you just described to me
What did you just described to me in a way that makes
Public demand is so high that I would bring back his racist Chinese
Game character
Which by the way is not be
Been gone for 6 months
Seen recently
There was one making fun of that
What was that that guy who had his cat on Zoom
Like instead of the cat
Wow he's made those videos as recently as
6 months
Regularly anal probe confused
So why you told me about the anal probe part I feel like that's
It look
That's a no spoiler situation
I also love the kids love it
Adult
Kids love it adults love it
Some s*** coming out of a dragon's a******
Kid tested mother approved
Choosy moms
Choose anal probes covered in blood
This is
Wild I mean like I would have listened to his wife
Does sound like it's a little bit much I would have listened to her tennis partner
Text Beth
So
Alex plays this video of
Australian journalist
I feel like journalists might be a little bit
Generous
Editorial commentator type
He plays video of an Oscar
Yeah and this guy is giving a speech about globalism
TiVo
Fine whatever
I also thought maybe this was a little bit racist
He's talking about like how you got to be
Skeptical of any organization that has the word world in it
Like a world
World Health org
Organization world food
Sure and then he throws this in
Part of the United Nations
Until you remember that Barack Obama won in 2019
Having the right skin color
Wow
I think it's a problem that Alex can't seem to find any of anybody who breaks down
Complaints about globalism
Beer into that directions to Bentley boils down to somebody's going to say skin
Yeah
Yep
He understands
How
He got tossed Aurelia right
Mikey understands the routes that'll Colony think it was a was perhaps a word
Journey if you will
He understands.
Right
Concept that he gets I would assume so yeah
Because it seems like
He is absolutely
If he's making this argue
White
People should leave
Australia
You should go away
Well
Interesting
I just I I find it really interesting the way that
Like UK and I obviously I think it's
Partially because
These kinds of things are attractive Allison
But you can't like find somebody to talk about these issues
Always liked are the challenges of
Globalized connection
Living in a modern world
You can't find somebody to
Play the
It doesn't say
Obama wanted
Peace Prize cuz he has blacks
Skin like that
Bucked up
You can't find somebody that isn't
Like
Subtly racist
Subtly
And it's the same thing with like
Genesis Communications Network
Big advocate of cracked anyway to give ads except for
Sweetly nonsense
Nicole website I mean what
Wild about that is
Not since you know
Like there
Plenty of great reasons to say that Obama shouldn't have that Nobel f******
Peace Prize
There's a lot of critique
No sounds Yuki shouldn't have her Nobel Peace Prize either but here we are
Oh yeah and and the fact that
Like you have to distill it down to throw that kind of like
Do you know what the audience
Want poking at
Got it and they didn't know that he was going to drone bomb the f****** world
But the audience wouldn't find that funny you're satisfied
And they just don't like that you have the wrong skin color according to them
So what are the more delightful things that came out of
Of the sea pack
I think was the video
Of the people getting booed for trying to tell people to wear my hat
Did you see that no I didn't see I I want
No I wanted nothing to do with this year CB
A guy comes on stage
We're going to listen
He's going to give you like a little bit of a breakdown
Masks I know you don't want to wear them but
We believe in property rights
And
We are in someone else's Hotel they get to make the rules
Good angle
Good angle way to do it what is the f****** pull that one through
That's a good Landing understand you don't want to wear a mask
Conservative principles demand that we respect the property rights of the owners of this hotel
Twitter allowing us to hold this second dungeon here and I assume all the people with there were like
We don't have principles go
To a young woman
She says
You know I know you don't want to wear masks
But
Can you work on that
That's also Fair
It's like
The children
Somebody
It's outrageously funny because it is
It is so
I'm just so so much of a clear illustration
Vista Fire
Yas Oppositional defiant
Manslick characterizes
These crowds
Yeah
That's it
It's childish tears my pet
Alright z-pack but we get all the conservatives in there when we just play Schoolhouse Rock
And maybe we would be at least a better off
You know
Hippie wouldn't fix everything
But maybe when they understand how bills
Tumblr
Might be globalist
Soros brainwashing after the kids right
Anyway Alex plays this clip of the people booing
He loves
It's very weird
Oh my God
All-weather mask and they didn't and they booed
Almost no one was wearing the stupid mask
That was all a giant fraud saying I'm not wearing your little
Scumbag
Post Bude
Muzzle
We conservatives
Believe in the rule of law
Because we know that when
The laws enforced
Horizon 4
They got practice
Back to talk about the
Brownsville dementia month
And I know this might sound like
Little bit of a downer
Property rights
When does the private home
And we believe in the rule of law
We need to comply with
The laws of this
County that were in
There's a long private Hotel just
Like your house gets to set its own rule
I am the law
TPAC director
Well as
Dan mentioned we are in a private facility and we do want to be
Tactful of
The
Ordinances that they have
As there
Private property so please when you're
Seated do suck
So if everybody can go ahead
Work on that
I know I know it's it's not
You have to ride William Wallace ladies and gentlemen
You have to let us in your own house
And where
Barley
Just
I can't imagine
Having a response to that other than like
Wow
That's
Bummer
Like it if
Even if I were somebody who is like opposed to wearing masks are being required to
We're here
If the rules of it
The place
Okay I understand
All of these people should be embarrassed
Yeah they should really be embarrassed because they're f****** chilled
And it's kind of sad
Credibly said
It bums me out and the fact that I'm going to go home and say
Think about how stupid they are is an even bigger
Bummer to me
The club just so fully like
Demonstrate that behavior
Someone gently trying to
Come up with
An excuse for why
You need to do this
How to put kids into eating vegetables
Deal that you would have to somebody
A group of people got together more like
We've got to try and get these people to wear masks
They're not going to listen to Medical ideas that are going to listen to they'll give a s*** about other people
Person could die right now and if they didn't like them they would all Chi
Yeah so what do we do
These people really loved property rights
Borderline like you have to be hey
If we want to carry guns
In this place
We got to wear a mask in this place
That would that would my work
I mean that's about all you can do
To deal with
He's f***************
Yeah
But like I said
There's a little bit of a shorter episode because it's
So much are just trumps
You know whatever
I feel like
Like it is
The greatest privilege in the world
Speak ever again
Yeah and it's
There's one there's one part where Alex
Refreshing
Gloucester weeks of Biden
Call just so B.
Disgrace
Nemo
What was the Paula
Policy platform
From the came out of CPAP
Is your dad
Avoid canceling
No bother with like we want lower.
Texas none of that just straight-up Non-Stop
Bayou animal
I was looking at the speakers list
That is pretty surprising
Ike
Trump
You got Trump jr.
Yeah then that's like
Don't know why computer needs to be there anymore
I kind of understand trap you got a excuse the diluted
Text Blake
James O'Keefe
Who's giving the speed drill
Rollie
Lauren boebert
Oh my God
Wow this is
Wooboi
So we have one last clip here and it's
Alex
Someone has found a clip of him
Talking
About his Rockefeller
But he calls me lockstep document
Which is not that's not what it is
Watch that was one of the four scenarios that are painted
About
Possible ways the technology
And governor
Can.
The future
And
It's interesting
Someone tried to clip him talking about it back in 2010
No really hit Alex plays this clip
As if like this proves I've always been right every
I will make an argument on the other side of this clip
This makes things worse for Ally
I would make sense
And that's with my prediction 11 years ago the lockdown
And then I'll show your coming
With
Sunday live please spread the word
God bless you all
The Alex Jones Show there is a war on for your mind I mean I'm not even worthy to be bringing you in
Information is powerful hope that
Because I've had chills
Since last night
This just confirms everything else we've already research
Envisions future dictatorship control by Elite
Millions being killed mandatory quarantine
Checkpoints the end of the family
Everything that's in the other documents but this DuckTales Vol the other Rockefeller Foundation documents about the GMO food
Sterilize you enforced vaccines and the hell we're already living in this just going to continue to intensify until we take our government
Back flip
It's just another headline
At this point
He doesn't call it operation lockstep because that wasn't the branding on it at this
Here is why I think this
The worst
I wouldn't have played
You didn't
Keep talkin
It's not like
It's shocking that someone was able to find a cliff
Complete I'm covering this sack of that
Yeah
I guess it probably someone picked it up and ran with it didn't have much legs
Some people just forgot about it
It's not like
2011 2012
He's still talking about this document
He completely forgets about it and tell Jim Fetzer
Start yelling about it on his blog
In 2020
Like he doesn't
This is this is worse
Because if you actually believe like Alex
Pretending to that this document lays out the globalists plan share
You had it in you with
Yeah
Again
Yeah for the millionth time
It's astounding to me the way the way in which you eat
I like
He he thinks that this is a win and it's actually like
Kind of raises more questions
About a prophet
I mean I make it look more full of s*** I would probably argue that the
It is really bad for him because it's
Basically saying that this is
Cuz it's not
The same document
That he's talking about
Yeah either way
It just means that he said the same thing about God damn near every
Document
Yeah it's been 10 years and not only has
Talking about it
None of it is happy
So
What is a prophet
Sure
He's a psychic
Everybody
That's why I found a little weird and what are the things that I decided that I think I want to do is
I want to go try and find that epi
I think I'm going to go try and do that
Maybe we'll do that for when
Wednesday or something
I hear his coverage of it and compare it to the present day
Coverage
Do this document
I wonder if he knows what the document is back in 2010 really good
Oh yeah
You got to do that now
Yeah you literally have no choice I'm getting to work on it
Now so
You know I think this is
This is a shorter episode but I think it's worth it if only for the weird commercial
Is the kind of thing not only
Should you not accept
Commercial
Advertising
Money from that
You should denounce it
This is the kind of thing that person should be forced to apologize for accepting advertising money to are that
Is something that like
There would be a scandal
Any other media Outlet
Bed with something like this
It's like hugging
Somebody running a
Advertisement
Hitler in 1937 in the New York
Times just like straight up
Rose Goku
So it's
It said it said I would I would humbly request
Anderson
I'll pull that commercial and also
Apologize
Sell the network and go away
Play Forevers point of this episode really
Episode hopefully we'll be able to put that together for Wednesday
We are on Twitter that knowledge has revived that go to bed Jordan
Please find a local charity or Bell found in your area to help out people doing God's work
Until then
I'm Leo hum dzx Clark I'm Daryl rundus
I am but William Wallace of mass
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work