Air Jordan
I have great respect for its knowledge B
MoneyGram
Dot-com
Everybody
What's up
Which price for today
My bright spot today Jordan is weird to the month of March
That it is time
Munch Madden
The doughboys
Alright
Very much enjoy
Turn my time off
From listening to Alex
2:30
Define other audio entertainment that I
I can just order like
No one hates Jews here guys arguing with each other
I enjoy it and that it's always always fun over here whenever they have their March Madness food tournament
The March Madness
My bright spot day I was going through my I was going through my iTunes listening to his music the other day
And Natalie Alfred popped up
Oh and thought about her in thought about her but we haven't spoke
Damn filled cupcake
Whatever you were allowed to go outside
And I was just thinking man she's so good and I want I was I felt very good about the
Natalie Grace
Kind of like
My first started doing stand-up all admit.
Big deal
One night I was like
Ticketmaster such a great person
I don't know her super well.
She was always very nice
Episode to go over
We be time-traveling mine in the past we are finally going to the Future
No we're back in the past
Because our last episode on Monday
He's at the end that I was going to try and find
Where Alex made that they prediction
You talked about the Rockefeller document
Stop short shorts compulsively go back
What is coverage was like
Amanda's going to be a whirlwind ride
Love Rockefeller the greatest guy in those are the world locks
The way to go I will admit that I had no idea what
Expect and I think that
Sometimes you fish
Well is dry
Sure like
Monday you know what the reasons were doing the Wednesday episode of cuz I felt very unsatisfied
So that well I thought I felt like hey we were
Looking for the CPAC
Scrap up and we got
Snake Eyes I always one sad
Three-eyed fish with
Humanize no good
This time
Alright nothing but fishing okay alright
I'm so excited too I get down
Business on that before
Tupac suicide
So First Harrison but not that Harrison he's really trashing hook brand
I don't disagree
Harrison
But not.
Next
Horatio cornholr thank you so much right now apology walk
I'm a policy wonk cornhole
Game of bags goodnight College
Horatio Hornblower play lot of bags
I don't know
Next to the greatest super villain of all time the hinge Master thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Very much
Alex
I'm a policy wonk
For the ultimate bastard Robert Evans
Someone doesn't like kid stays in the picture
That doesn't sound true I think everybody loves
Once you know more about fisting you know you're in a good time
Yeah
I remember hearing I see
Patton Oswalt
About
About the kids in the picture audiobook
I remember
I don't know probably soup I got audiobook of it on cassette
Ocean
Mixtape yeah
It was as good as advertised
What was it what did Patton call it
It's like the
Devil reading
His memoirs
I think I think there is a similar data listen to it in a long time
Technocrat here
Give little shout-out to thank you so much
God cowboy
Could be
Joakim
Okay Boardwalk
Could be
Jordan
Kim
Is that literally Joakim Noah know it's not better for the Bulls team in the early aughts whenever
Derrick Rose Road
Because this is Joakim from Denmark
Heroin
Freakishly large
Very much
Canjo came specifically
If you can I assume all joachim's do each other hook me up with Joakim Noah
Great fantastic
Center for the Bulls in the early aughts when Derrick Rose
I feel like a friend of mine had a story about run
Into him the long room
Oh yeah that bar on Irving Park
Seem to recall the story about that
Who never wanted to know if it's true
Number two
Don't remember the story
I don't know
Again story might not be true and I
I don't remember the story
Betty White Jordans
February 24th
This year
Infowars released a video titled quote
Video sharks in the world
!
Alex Jones predict
Covid lockdown
In 2010
This is a three-minute clip taken from Alex's July 6th
16th 2010 show
And this is a little bit rare little bit unconventional
But I want to play the
Entire thing for you
BB launching off
Point for this
Entire episode
So it's important
But we give a fair hearing the original Source material
How long is this
3 minutes and 20
Brutal sorry alright
Let's do it there is a war on for your mind
Information is powerful
And I hope that you pay attention
Because I've had chills
Since last night
This just confirms everything else we've already researched
She envisions future dictatorship control by Elite
Millions being killed mandatory quarantine check
Appoints the end of the family
Everything that's in the other documents but
The hell already living in this is going to continue to intensify until we take our government back
From these Eugenics Madmen with that story is up on Prison Planet
Dot-com the question is will you have the courage to really do the research yourself because I don't want you to just sit here and here
Near me make these claims
These people are so arrogant
But they write policy papers so many of them that they're producing these policy papers and reports and white paper
It is an open conspiracy against you and your family I pray to God
I pray to my father Jesus Christ every night to give me strength and the will build
Give me the strength to carry on because I know why a lot of you don't want to look at this information and
Comment on the YouTube videos are on message boards and I'm a liar
I know because it's scary
You're not going to be able to go to the ball games anymore
You're not going to be able to just go out and get drunk with your friends not to be able to just
Go out and enjoy yourself all the time
Dictatorship
The time to incrementally enslave you
Mentally psychologically physically spiritually
The defeated is for the rank-and-file of this planet
Realize that
You have a choice to make what your destiny is going to be
Once you face this about that works
What else what else could it be
We got to get past the artificial stigma that the control corporate media has been putting out for decades
Dictatorship
Step display the seriousness of our commitment
Tesco Home and abroad
Infowars tomorrow's news today
Wintersun
Plus
Highest grade
With vitamin K
For your amusement
The reason at the end
I heard that video the first thing
Stuck out to me was
That seemed strange to me and it made me suspect that Alex in 2010
Not have been talking about exactly what
Do you want people in 20 21 22
I think he was talking to
Believe some things
Details here and there.
The second thing that caught my ear was helvegen almost formulaic this coverage of the Rockefeller document was back in 20
Was this really as deep as Alex got into the document that
Supposedly demonstrates an outline
The globalist evil plans
Is in
Anyway believable that if he consider this document to be anything even
Close to that but he wasn't able to
Find the clip of him that has more
That was soft yeah that was a big load of nothing
Is Alden sit right with me
This is apparently a video that shocked the world
This is supposed to be Alex dropping the mic
Proven that he was always on the lock
Operation walk
And that's you totally wasn't doing about everything you're saying now cuz dog
Don't come true in the future
That's the underlying argument
It's being made by this video
And it felt dishonest to me
Surprise
I wanted to understand the larger context so I went back
To this and let me spoil this
A little bit
My suspicions
We're not unfounded
Give some background about what was going on around this time if you're listening to Alex's show the only real world
Actual Edline is that the Deepwater Horizon
Oil spill was ongoing
And BP had announced the day prior to this episode that they had successfully
The spell
Which represents
Progress store
Resolving
Alex also mentioned the car bombing in Mexico that was carried out by cartels
But he doesn't really dwell on the story much
Outside of that
I'm not sure we get much else in the way of news
You know who else predicted a pandemic
That would be the CDC when they made up
Plan for how to
Deal with a pandemic that was
Really important Ilse a certain time. Whenever it was ignored and
Mistaken the CDC cuts
Basically their job to plan for things that are going to
Here we get to we're starting here on July 16th 2010
The David all that is taken
Confirm
For Alex is very
Moodily
Discord
Here is the beginning of the show Alex driving is
Story
And I have all the vital stacks of information here in front of me that we're going to be covering
BP claims for the first time in 80 plus days
Have stopped
The leak
At least three times
In the last 87
Plus
That alone is weird to me
First of all
Weed story is the BP oil spill on the day that he supposedly breaking these.
Yeah well I mean destruction of
The family in quarantine
Teens inhaling of all the p
People that's
Race
The other thing that I think is super weird about that
The clip is the way that Alex seems to be willing to give BP the benefit of the doubt
About whether or not they'd sealed the leak
Well I mean
BP's
Leak happening makes oil prices
Is go down right
Prefers oil
Alex has sources he has documents he knows everything he's kind of psychic
Will see it
Well that's weird
I certainly hope I certainly hope the Pennzoil company
You got to give BP the better than I thought that was weird
Is Hell British Petroleum is one word away from British is realism
Some dad and that's
Basically what
So
Alex does get to the Rockefeller document pretty
It is the second headline
Buddy's got although I'm not sure he's ready
I'm not sure he knows much about it
I was here in the office last night when Aaron Dykes and I were doing research for the
Full-spectrum dominance Eugenics film
We are working on that deals with other issues
And we've come across so much more information that are
Earnest
The globalist master plan is
Growing exponentially
Don't think you ever know everything
The more we learn
Add more horrified we get to discover that things are far worse than originally thought
Rockefeller Foundation document over to Paul Watson wrote a story about it this morning
And just everything we talked about here
The magnet
I mean I'm not even information
And I hope that
Because I've had chills
Since last night
This just confirms everything else we've already researched
Rockefeller study
Millions being killed mandatory quarantine checkpoints
Everything that's in the other documents
The hell we're already living in this just going to continue to intensify until we take our government back
I promise Eugenics Mad Men
But that story is up on Prison Planet
Dot-com
This is about as deep as it gets
It's not much
Fixed it Alex's just reading off a headlight
From an article to Paul Joseph Watson Road
And everything that in the present-day Alex is trying to pass off as his prediction
Actually just him reading from
Paul's outrageously bad opinion piece the one who told Paul
Who found it
Global pandemics that killed Millions mandatory quarantine checkpoints biometric ID cards and a world of top-down
May control
The Regal in the present
That's just the first line
So if anything Alex
To be saying the poll predicted all the stuff that's happening now and Alex read it and then took credit for it
Think Alex will be doing
And that being said both article is not a dick
KeyBank
It's just the same kind of trash coverage of this rockfeller doctor
Give me the Racine 11 years later
Just happening in 2010 and being quickly forgotten even by the people who push
Another conspiracy
The article lays out
Did this is a scenario
In the document titled
Scenarios for the future
Technology and International
Development
And Paul even notes that it's one of four scenarios that are included
The document
Event described the scenario title block
Doxepin
Exhaustive detail
Ignoring other scenarios or the point
Of the document at all
Conclusion of this article is absolutely unearned
And completely unsupported by the underlying asset
The Rockefeller study is not a warning against
Preventing the kind of tyranny contained in the scenario from unfolding
It's a blueprint
Global crises like bioterror attack and pandemics
In order to completely destroy society and rebuild it under a new world order and their image
Crystal clear from reading the lockstep scenario that the oppressive Society portrayed in the study is not presented
As an admonishment of how governments would
Khaleesi's upon a pandemic
To set up a police statement Empower themselves as dictators
It's a ringing endorsement that this approach would be the correct
To do 10 I've been holding
Hand up your ass
Please call on me
I have a quick
Why
Just pull think so
Oh okay
Now that I've got that
He said
It is not a document
Predicting or or like
Because
Because it's not
Yeah because
No course not
These conclusions are not sensible to arrive at from reading the documents
Unless you went into it with those conclusions already in mind and you were just
For anything you
Define to justify your nerd
That entire blurb that I read you there from Paul's article
It's completely dismissive bull by just reminding you yourself that everything he saying is his
Opinion
It's not fair
Coherent onala
The real tell
Here is
It's a completely
Ignoring the other three scenarios in the doctor
How come the conspiracy isn't that the globalist are secretly trying to reveal that they're trying to usher in a world
Depicted by the clever together scenario
Where quote
Pharmaceutical Giants release thousands of drug compounds shown to be effective against diseases like malaria
Public domain
As part of an open Innovation agenda
They also opened their Archives of research and development on neglect
The disease is deep not commercially viable offering seed funding scientist to wanted to carry the
Forward
Why isn't that the conspiracy that's in the document
I will argue
Because in that world
Zinc sales are
Mario is
That used or even mentioned because it doesn't pick the
The kind of vibe that Alex in Spanish
His career making his audience
Scared about
The four scenarios in this documentary
Equally likely
Sweetly different future
That wasn't
Captured by the two variable exercise of this study
But the only one that matters to Infowars is the one that paint for the dystopian hellscape they make money by convincing
Listeners is
Is right around the corner
Alex and Paul wanted
The fear Monger about the stock
Responsibly
They've an obligation to answer one very basic question with today
Refuse to
In the past
Or in the prison
Which is
What is different about the lock
Except scenario that makes it the global of secret plan
Whereas the other three aren't
Well it's in the
Other
GMOs
Sure
They're going to
House
It seems
Kind of like an arbitrary choice
That's the one that
It appeals to you you think it's profitable probably that would make sense profit motive
Most of all the thing
Things we talked about
What's up big
Achilles
Truck bed basically
It's always been
DNA has been altered to also across sterilization I mean they're getting us on so many fronts
And I've got all the government report admitting that the births
Never-before-seen we are being mutated
And many of us that are able to even think it operate today
Are children their children in the children after them are going to be
Deformed monsters
German course that will never even get to that point they plan to exterminate all of us long before then
Why do we have to sit here and fight with each other government bureaucrats police military
I mean we're all in this together it's a tiny Elite lessons
Round analysis that ruled the planet and how it look I'm going to get it all
All news coming up in your phone calls today it's just
Achilles
You know this is like this reminds me of the
The Heaven's Gate
Colt now
Just on account of like
I'm worried
That we'd like
Sure
We don't want
Time to kill all of
But on the other
If we all killed ourselves that would
Take away their satisfaction
This 6000y dozen
The devil just get more peeps
You can only really devil it up with
Thousand at a time the devil behind this or not at this point because it doesn't feel like it
Administrative plan
I will say that we do know that the global is plans are 10 years behind and here we are sure
Translator
It just has the vibe of like
Definitely
Being
A mortal plan
A little different vibe
Devil get out of it
I don't know
Dykes was the one who found the document
Across the pond
Which is why Alex is a psychic
Predicted every
Yes
Now here's a little bit about Aaron dykes
Stampede found his way to Infowars
There are so many of these reports that Aaron dykes
Only aided by coffee
What
Mini
Dave's
Will not sleep and I have to make him go home after two days of being up here
University
Didn't really believe
In what I was doing didn't really buy what I was saying and kind of laughed when I hired him
That's exactly who I wanted to hire
I want
And he's gone to you
Public Relation School
Very good grades when he graduated he was very intelligent
I said
You are going to
Hire me you coward wow
If you really want to believe you I've got a candidate for the position
Alex Goforth
I do like that idea.
Google person icon
I want somebody who thinks they can
Can see through all of my b******* and I'm going to give him the truth
Pictures that we make a lot of money here you can make some too
Integrity is for losers
I heard about a public relations school because
Is journalism school with
Not where I find people that work at Infowars nope usually contest
Alex
Sounds like there's so much proof managing so much proof
Things
These people are so arrogant
But they write policy papers so many of them
That they're producing the policy papers and reports and white papers
So fast
So Furious
We could never
Read them all it is Warehouses full of it
It is an open conspiracy against you and your family
If there are in fact warehouses full of the proof of Alex's
Conspiracy theories
Then I would suggest you start by producing one
Piece of that proof
Everything he's pointed to so far in my experience has been
Bulshit
Jumpy Holdren's Eco science book doesn't Advocate sterilizing people the riding
The water is Rockefeller document doesn't lay out a master plan to bring in a dictatorship through a pandemic
The club of Rome Publications don't prove that they made up
Climate change
Everything
Specific I've ever heard Alex mentioned doesn't say what he claimed
There is a warehouse
It's just a warehouse
It's full of books and Publications that Alex
Never read or can't understand
And he's just using them
Props to
Justify in supported
Is flimsy facade
Abdominal theories
I'm going to argue
Do that rather than a warehouse
Baby
No cuz you know cuz you used to print everything out its fizz
Got to be a filing cabinet or two
I hope they have a
Shredder
That's how important the stuff they print out as
We got to get rid of this the moment Alex printout at
Sweet
Be caught with this
Snob
20 stacks
Are there was listening to this episode one of the parts of Alex's 2021
Predict
Action Montage clip
The Chocolate World
I noticed something really suspicious about how his words
Represented
Here's how this appears in the overly dramatic current date
I pray to God I pray to my heavenly father Jesus Christ every night to give me the strength and the will build
Give me the strength to carry on because I know while I don't want to look
Information and just want to comment on the YouTube videos are on message boards and I'm a liar
I know because it's scary
You're not going to be able to go to the ball games anymore
You're not going to be able to just go out and get drunk with your friend you're not going to be able to just
Go out and enjoy yourself all the time
That sounds
Kind of
Prophetic
I want to sing I want be able to go to ball games or get drunk with our friends at the bar
And that's exactly
Actually like what happened because of coronavirus safety measure
Be intentional this Clippers to give the audience that impress
But Alex's predict
LivingSocial lockdown which if you haven't forgotten
Is a kind of the title
Of this video
Problem
Is there's a slight
Edit that whoever made this clip did that changes the entire meaning of Alex's word you mean when he said
That they were going to Nuke us
Said that's why we couldn't go to ball games and no that was a that's from another show
I pray to God I pray to my heavenly father Jesus Christ every night to give me the strength
And the will be able to face this har
And to give me the strength to carry on because I know why a lot of you
Don't want to look at this information I just want to comment on the YouTube videos are on message boards and I'm a liar
I know why
Because it's scary
And if you admit this to yourself
You're not going to be able to go to the ball games anymore
You're not going to be able to just go out and get drunk with your friends you're not going to be able to just
He'll go out and enjoy yourself all the time and not spend some of your energy
On resisting there
Shady you lying piece of s*** f****** liar
Saying that if you are available to learn this information that information was so dominant
Be able to go to ball game
Five-paragraph rich but I think you expressed it
Yeah that was that was really shocking
Wow what a difference a couple words
Make a big difference
The cutting out of those words
Completely Alters the point of what Alex is saying
It makes those images of not being able to go to the ball game or bars anymore
It makes when you cut it out it seems like they're in
Independent thought
Yeah everything else that he's saying as opposed to be
Part of 1/8 of then state
You got it
This is intensely dishonest and whoever edited
This clip together took those words that because they knew
Did in their original form
They Don't Really Work
To make Alex sound like he made an amazing
But
If you chop them off
It looks like you might have been onto something
Using the cheesy score and making selective at it's like this the person who put this together is able to transform something
Pretty meaningless
In standard form looks like a fairly specific
About stuff that would happen
Send a text later
They do this because they know they can get away with it
Anyone was acceptable for falling for Alex's s*** is
Probably not going to be the sort of person who goes back to look at his 20
10 episode
Actually making a prediction back then
So this is a safe game of exploitation and manipulation Metallica's free-to-play
And man it's just
Parents
Frankly
At this point I would argue
You're literally the only person who would go back and
Find the episode that Alex said that
Kick-Ass
Of course you are
You can't go to the ball games anymore cyclone-hit like
If you really did say I still don't think it means anything anything about it it's
Hey buddy would be
Yeah I don't know
You're right it would be interested
I would like to do it for your react
That's why you play the game
How to throw baseball right in his head
Happy Spring training of baseball to the brain
Cheese's
Christ yeah
Battery that is unacceptable. I was sitting alone in my room when I heard that nice of you who asked
Out of context in the clip
Infowars
It's not fair
Alex
Obamacare and what-have-you until you can't
Eat foods and stuffing Ono it's no good
Tracking how much you want her to do that to the school
What you can
Put in a child's Happy Meal
So it's okay for McDonald's to put
@cnn
Extremely poisonous
Illegal in England
Another country
But you can't put a toy in there
It's not so much that McDonald's puts
Silicone in their food which is the impression that Alex
Just trying to give the audience
McDonald's
Use a silicone in the preparation of
You can find this information on McDonald's own website
That they use dimethyl Polly
Siloxane in the oil
Use to fry french fries
What a great place
To hide
That information
Right on their website never look there
The reason for this is because
The food grade
Empty foaming agent
Which prevents the oil for bubbling up and burning employee
Anyone who's worked in fast-food knows that getting that oil on you is no joke
And with the high incidence of younger employees at places like McDonald's
It's really important as a safety measure to do what you can to limit the possibility of evil
Getting oil all over
It sucks I got a little
Awful
Alex can't prove that this chemical is dangerous.
People I'm actually interest
In 2018 MLive reported the quotes
Scientist that Yokohama National University in
Japan say that a chemical added to the oil to cook
McDonald's french fries could help you were bald
Listen to humans
That's right
Some early-stage testing this young that dimethylpolysiloxane
Who's used
To quote the growth of black hair on the back and scalp of mice
Okay alright
So Alex
His it's his own fault he's losing his hair
Of course
People are kind of dumb after this news broke these Japanese scientist had to come out and clarify the eating McDonald's fries would not help you grow back
Of course not it's not
Their lead researcher judge
Bukata told Reuters
Quotes
No matter how many fried potatoes you eat you'll never grow more hair
That's a total misunderstanding that's gone viral
So sad
Besides just have to take time out of their day to say stuff like that
Alex do stuff like this all the time he'll say something like McDonald's
Put silicone in their food
And then do nothing more to examine the Claymore help his audience understand what even means
If you just listen to Alex you beat you know
Equally easy to
Conclude that McDonald's is using
Does chemical of the oil
As it would be to believe that their Big Macs are half breast
Austin Bryant
Yeah he leaves you
Treading water
I'm in the worst part of that is we are a little bit
So much
That type of process
Food that there's
It's almost borderline Ruiz
Isabel to be like
I can see Madonna
Putting silicone in their food
I mean
We getting so much gas
You know all that's right but it is
And I'm not I'm not blanket defending
Use of all kinds of chemicals also different conversation
From Lake
But you're
Just sort of out of nowhere brainwood
Pull up
As opposed to something that is a
Food grade antifreeze
No he's
Is he's taking a
Advantage of the fact
Pettyville Shady Corporation
Attend attend to be evil in
Does not demand any kind of specificity out of them
Yeah
So now we're back to beep
Sure why not
This is so weird
Gulf of Mexico
But we've got screenshots of their
Looks like there may be some hanky-panky going on but we are looking into it right now and working on that but
Is true
Praise God this is certainly
Wonderful news why are you still taking a wait-and-see approach you
You claim to have evidence that indicates there's hanky-panky
Money you got money in oil
I don't know I don't try to have something I don't know if it's
That
I don't I don't know but it's weird
That's very weird
Well I mean we've seen some screenshots that show something weird is happening but you know
I think in this one
Situation I'm going to last
Corporation
I'm pretty sure that escape pod is
Filled with nobody's there's nobody in there we don't need to fire a laser to blow up that escape
Isn't this company that
Spell millions of
Thomasville
They tell us that it's all good but I saw some evidence there might be some goofing around
Might be some
Chicanery down there
To say that this
This massive oil spill this
Ecological disaster
Trust that they are there out there above board
We all make mistakes
This time frame is
He's going to go to Carl's a lot of time he does
Like it's babe
It seems more
Consistent that he'll get
It's a call
And
He'll take some calls then jump back
To just doing the show and then
You take some more call chair
The fetal of like an actual radio show
He goes to some calls
As opposed to maybe somebody
Who's abused amphetamine
Yeah yeah
Scholar brings up that like
Hey
You know
Finding out about all this stuff about the evil
The folks around the world and all that
Kind of makes it tough for me to be happy
Alex has not seen
You hear that you're a talking point that dead
Not a lot of times people will bring up and then what you had mentioned this morning earlier before
I got through to talk to you
Once you obtain this information
And the truth
Basically
How much
Change your outlook on
How you value your life
And then
Ashley said
My life hasn't been the same and then sometimes
You don't like I might even be asking for something right here buddy but
Sometimes
It's really hard
To find some balance
And it's right here
Even maintain a reasonable amount of
What
My god-given right by the Constitution
Yo my right to be happy
We got out of balance
Thomas Jefferson biscuits
George Washington Thomas Paine Patrick Henry all said you must guard the jewel of Liberty
You must do everything you can on its defense
Not yet is you going to the prime importance even if you struggle to keep freedom
You're probably going to lose it
And and and you will go into bondage
And the worst elements of society will take over
Now losing
And so
What did Barry Goldwater
There is
No such thing
And by my underwear my a
Yeah
Listcrawlers
Expressing this stuff is really
But like you scare me a lot
And it's not
Pleasant
State of fear and my adrenaline is always pumping which makes
Smithfield
But it's like a while
He wants to give this dude a little bit more
Kind of advice in a little bit of like
When I'm with my family will I be okay
When I'm out there fishing with the kids
Kidzoona like
I'm thinking about fighting the gallbladder
Doing this because that's why I'm fighting
He won't be able to go to ball games
I mean you can take your kids
Ball games cuz that's why you're fighting
You got to integrate
Enjoyment of family time with
Your passion to fight
Not yet with the Devil the devil
And then this caller
Flip the script
And changes the
What's interesting is 10 years ago you know I've been married for almost nine but video 10 years ago
All she beautiful
I would still be I have a lot of Flash and now
Almost all of that is burned away
My wife but it is still
Mydrive states are fully survival warn people
Deal with this
Anything else
Yeah
Fixing gears out here
You were talking about you.
What people look at as important These Days Inn
When I
Crack open my Yahoo page which is my homepage
They have this thing called trending now
And you'll see stuff like
Lindsay Lohan American Idol
Aurora wrestling dancing
Stars
Saying at the end of the very last
Article
Guess what it was
Oil spill
That's what kind of priorities
Our country has these days
My Yahoo account
Couple years away from
Divorce at this point
Going to say
So
Yeah you know the internet like the way that he described that that reminds me so much of the way that Douglas at
Describe the Babelfish where is like finally everyone in the universe
Was able to communicate
That caused more and
Bloodier Wars
Whatever in the back
Get out
Oh no
Maybe it was a bad idea
It just like at Universal communication
Internet is
F******
It's probably bad
But it does
Definitely at very least
Expose some parts
Cursive r
Behaviors in our patterns
Maybe we wouldn't have been aware of otherwise
Certainly trolling
Becomes more
Noticeable
And then also like the phenomenon that this dude stalking
In about Westlake
Things like
American Idol look WWE wrestling
The people's attention that other one
The opiate of the masses I don't know what don't want to
I don't know
We're trying to feel Comfort Inn
We have Obama in the White House everybody still like maybe we won't have an evil presence
Is good time
So
I had something
Trigger in his brain
Because of what that guy said about his Yahoo
And he is come up with a plan
And you'll see how it's a news item normally
They kind of feedback loop in feet
The Scandal
The media hype so don't look
The number one trend
Facebook
Or Mel Gibson
Or Kelly Osbourne
And the BP oil spill
Is way down the line
Unemployment extension 2010
Is number 15
On Yahoo trends
Are you for or against
That should be number one
LED and Mercury in our children's
Juice drinks
And chips and food and soft drinks that's all admitted your children are drinking this in mask
That should be
The top trend
Now what if we
Actually
Gained their corrupt system what is every listener of the show
Today
Sunday and Monday typed The Obama Deception Yahoo
Google search engine
What have you did it
Over and over and over and over and over and over and over again
That would put The Obama Deception
Links to the video
For free
That would put links
At the top of Google
At the top
I'm Yahoo
Millions more would
This guy's a goddamn genius
If
Everyone
Would buy wooden Sheriff's
Yeah that's Bill Cooper all over the place
Completely nonsensical
The solving non-existent problem
He's a genius with marketing
Supposed
Problem here is that the news about the
The BP oil spill is not higher
Then the internet
20 top trends are about trivial matters
Like celebrities
Cryptids
You can easily see how this is an easy argument to get people to agree with
The oil spill is probably more important than pop
Top stories
This isn't the problem
It's just kind of a statement about what attracts people
Attention
The oil spill began
3 months prior so headlines about it
Might not have been all that exciting to people
And just a few days
Before this Lindsay Lohan
Since the 90 days in jail for violating her probation
And I believe Mel Gibson was in the news for
Racist I remember I remember that this was not the time he got pulled
Dover
It's fine to save the BP oil spill is maybe a larger story for more people but it's ridiculous
To complain about the public paying
Attention to those stories and they were pretty serious stories
You think the BP oil spill should be higher
Well here's what we do tomorrow
Make something else to do
Supposed problem
Just caused by some
Vague idea about hubby
The algorithm search
Just working then the solution is that everybody needs to search for The Obama Deception that movie to the top of all sorts
The results this makes no sense
Feels like it does to Alex's audience because
Cuz they've been trained to equate
Promoting Infowars
With engaging and
Activism they've been conditioned to believe that it
Possible that if the Obama Deception
Get seen by millions more people
Maybe I'll have an impact on getting people to pay
Spell celebrity gossip
Why do Hindu Siemens Clippers
Phenomenal it really represents
Be Bleak underbelly of what Alex's world is always about
The only solutions that are ever really offered are those that directly profit out
The solution to the collapsing economy is to buy gold from Alex's father Ted Andrew
The solution to the
Becoming societal collapse is to buy survival food from our to sponsor my Patriots
What
Solution to covid-19
Every other health condition is just to use Alex's
Dissolution
Do people not paying enough attention
Deepwater Horizon oil spill
Apparently
Trick search engines
The thinking Alex's movie is more popular than it actually is
Recommending it
Two more people
It's evil
I'm looking back on this is painfully transparent to see what our she's doing
Great marketing
Strategy
I also enjoyed that as Alex was talking
Like as soon as he said The Obama Deception the first time
You rolled your eyes
Sugar
So that's that's his big plan
This is serious plan
He spent a half-hour.
Really yeah
I'm like hey
Look
Sure
What do the Obama Deception
And then later we can do it without
What if you all right now
I-Ready a-listers could just go to Google
Go to Yahoo go to the biggest search engine and type in
The Obama Deception
This will probably work it'll probably push it to the top and then next week
I can put on a viral video Stay on genetic engineering causing DNA damage
And then millions of new people
Because of that information Warfare tool
Will see it
I like this Tech
Technique
For the Studio's one for me, okay
This first one is just going to be promoting my s*** and the second time I'll do it about some topic if you want to drop it
What what I want to do is kind of a ladder attack okay just get my name
First and then I'll put out
Content to go viral Alex has done this kind of thing
Earlier in his
Career as well
Google search
It's not a new strategy for him
But it is
Tremendously desperate and weird the way he's acting
Right there wasn't even playing field
His stuff is most popular everybody knows it shut up everyone knows it
So the globalist
Cheated
Okay so now Alex has to cheat
So they can't cheat
Complicated but I just had to
The clip because Alex is really accepting and admitting they what he's doing
We won on the Level Playing Field so they cheat
Before they start cheating the system
We need to gain their system right now
Now we got a game we got to cheat that system in order to make sure they can't read again cuz
No cuz they cheated before a Level Playing Field
Popular radio show on the
So
I want to
You stressed you and I hope that still Mariah stammering
He talked about this for a long time
Because he does
Jump off to another topic
And that is
Pearl Harbor was a false flag
Okay
From Japan into
Iguana cross the Pacific
Here's Japan
Here's Hawaii
Here's the West Coast United States they had to come all the way
And the aircraft in the US submarines and
All the islands we control they were coming
And they are ordered to stand down and die
Can't prove any of that big one
We've talked a bit about his Pearl Harbor conspiracy in the past
Just to represent that he spends a while on that topic
Because he is made
Is blank that everyone needs to get to
Typing in their search engine
How do you get the call from
A guy named Angel Eyes
Okay
Scares me I'm listening
I was talked to
Angel Eyes in Texas here on the air
You got me how you doing bulldog
Pretty good
Okay
You know Angel Eyes just
Because I think my shave what you know other people don't
You're freaking me out a little
No do you do a bow dog
IRA
Alright maybe if it's
3 a.m. at a bar and I
Don't want to go home and if somebody starts with
I'm Angel Eyes cuz I think I
Hey baby I'm listening the last one
On the follow-up anytime
Before that I can always leave man
I think I'm going to start episodes now
Yeah
A little bit of a
Amateur Maguey degree tweeter
Some interesting memories
He said he wants to try and run by Alex
I called you about a month
Citgo in regards
What's to the interview with Chandra Levy's aunt
With Barbara Walters
About Chandra called her week before she disappeared
Headsets
Bigfoot
It's not happening American I can't tell you about it
You put out the
You know the flag that if anybody had
Recording event that they send it to you
I doubt anybody would have it that way
Looks like 10 years ago that happened
I wonder could you find out who concert Levy's aunt is an interview her if
Disappeared
You know died mysteriously
You're saying that she said something big is about to happen but I can't tell you
And
You're saying you saw her say that on what show
On a Whopper
I believe it was Barbara Walters and it may have been
Leslie small or one of those
Global
Reporters but
Does not spare the details
Chandra Levy's aunt is named Linda zamsky and the interview
She gave back in 2001 and her statement about her niece's disappearance were widely reported
The time in every Outlet
You can imagine
Who be the easiest thing in the world for this call or do I have to
Just Googled
Chandra Levy
And found articles
Explain this
Which kind of illustrates
Illustrate where his memory is
Failed
The aunt didn't say that
The Chandra it said there was a
Bake it was going to happen in America is Angel Eyes as reporting to Alex
According to the washing
Newton post quote
On April 29th
The day before Levy was last seen leaving left a message on Sam
Lansky's voicemail
Never hear from her knees again
Quote hi Linda it's Shandra my internship is over Levy said in the message
I'm planning on packing my bags in the next week or 10 days
Heading home for a while
Don't know what I'm going to do this summer
And I really have some big news or something important to tell
Call me
The article goes on to say quote zamsky said yesterday
She did not know what Levy was referring to but
How did the twenty-four-year-old
Did not seem
Upset
According to samsky
She was chandra's confidant
Better relationship
Representative Gerry Connolly
So taking in its proper context as delivered by zanski
You could use this
Comment to speculate that
Maybe Jean read some news about it
Change in her relationship
Wakanda
But that's not
Contacts that angel eyes
Bring this information
Alex
He's saying that the news
The Chandra had for her
Something big was going to happen
In America
Which seems to be him implying that you had foreknowledge about 9/11
Hey Auntie just want to let you know coming home soon I'm not sure I don't know what I'm going to do for the summer
9/11 about to happen it's going to be a wild couple of my
I've seen this
Conspiracy floated online before so it's not like a completely new idea to me but it's
Generalize on connecting Randa
Damn. I'm misinterpreting and misrepresent exams
He's come at
Kind of shocked
Sing to me honestly that
Alex would hear this
Some kind of not know what the guys talking about
It seems like this
It would be something that he would have covered
It didn't really have leg
Probably
So this internet spam
It works
WIC
Start working while Alex is still on there
I'm noticing that on Twitter and Facebook it is alive with the Obama Deception thousands and thousands
Twitter
Facebook
My posting The Obama Deception from YouTube
Or just return The Obama Deception
People are also going to Google and Yahoo and typing in The Obama Deception
Where to try to trim that to the top to show people the power of
But we can't make future films
If you don't purchase them from
This is been a lot
Yeah it is a few more than I was hoping for that this is all working out great
But also you need to buy the fit
I got you
I got you in the door
Now you got to buy for also or else I can't make another one for us to artificially promote
This
War
Is it over until we defeat the global
We can't defeat the global is so this war isn't over
Until you have made me
Obscenely wealthy
Beyond obscenely wealthy
Alex goes back to Carl's and
This one dude
Eat wrong
Matan d.c. your on the year
First
I just wanted to say thank you for doing what than anybody else in the world to fight
New World Order
Okay well.
Actually have to disagree with you when you say that you're not smarter than average
You're probably
Way above average when it comes to intelligence just based on your discernment
Yeah that way
It's the duty of Great Men to leave
Alex
Most people go cross-eyed when they try to process
Not an input that you do on a daily basis
That's 343
We need to know
When you going to step up
Run for political office I mean
Run for mayor of Oz
Governor attacks
Millions of people migrating
Just to go vote in that election
Oh man
Just a population of
Texas would explode in order for vehicles
Cedarland correctly
If Alex announces that
He is going to run
Vermeer of Austin
Whatever length of time you must be a resident in order to vote either some requirements
So millions of people are going to go to us
Just to put Alex and Ani
I guess I'll just stay in Austin is
Keep Austin Weird
But not that weird run away from how weird off today's now
Yeah
I'm also is a cross-eyed American I resent
I'm saying people go
Go cross-eyed taking in all the information that you do
What time Alex was gonna run
Do you know that he was going to run for office
Oh yeah but there was a problem
He was too busy filming
Guardians of the
2 popular
Legal campaign rules
That way they can selectively enforce against
At this point
True
I just here covering the news in the information
Millions of people
Millions
It's growing exponentially
Why should we stop with working and broke don't fix it
Well I don't think you have to stop you could just
Do what you're doing and then have people coming in for you
I mean
It's not understand wrong I completely agree with everything you say
Wells Fargo
Because we do have a hundred percent election fraud
Iproven Infinity on the paper
And again in 2010
It's also the most wealthy per-capita that's why the bloodsuckers are here
What
What are you talkin about
Business income
Sleep 100
Percent
Election
Got stolen this for ten years at least
Father
Much
No
I'm confused as to why
Oh cuz he's
Full of s***
Oh that would makes you just talkin
I was going to say I feel like I would probably be like I don't want to
Live here any longer
Scared
What a little time with Lori Lightfoot did he like
I don't want to live here anymore
If you really believe this revolutionary s*** that Alex
To talk about
It really seems
Like he would be
Not a radio host
Stevia Terror
He would be here running a cell
Indicating that
People do something crazy
If you like
Storm the Capitol Building living in a city where there's
Broadland elections for 10 years there's nothing real in all the leadership
You can't vote him out because
Feel like
What recourse do you have
I will say
I haven't been to Austin
The barbecue is
Sure is that worth
Ed endlessly corrupt election
No certainly not.
Alex
What's really most important those
You guys got a
And we are having lister's today
Try to
How many BP is not even the top 10
Google
And
Yahoo Prince
So we're trying
They look
The top
If you put the term The Obama Deception
The Obama Deception
Is go into
Google
Bring up the results back out again
Put your cursor on it
A couple minutes
Search
Then you put your cursor in there click it
Or change one letter
Back on it
Guys guys just show about a Google
How to Google things
Repeatedly
Because
Again
The BP the oil spill should be number one surprises what we do about
Hundreds of times
Now listen many times
I have had
My videos already number one
And
Being the top
Search
We're just artificially doing this
And Mel Gibson
You mean you really just
Got you something it up
But you were yelling over his last clip which is
BP should be the number one Trend why are you doing this
Yeah Alex is doing this
Because he wants more
Traffic and more money to come into his business
He also knows that admitting that would look really bad
He wants the outcome but he doesn't want to
Ask for it so he pretends that his motives are noble
Please actually incense that Lindsay Lohan is getting more attention than the oil
In reality
Alex is pissed off at Lindsay Lohan is getting more attention than him
But being too obvious about it
Who's pretending
Concerned about how many people are paying attention
Royal Spa
I will say that
It's so
Transparent if you go back and listen to to our coverage
The Obamas
What is Upton I will say that I can
Completely lost my mind around the
Eight or nine hour bark
So we're the last
Few minutes of the Obama
Caption about a BP oil spill that was
Going to happen for a couple years I don't know
Certainly
So
Alex's
Get on there
Type it in
Hit enter
Caller has
For those people who sit down
R5
Time today
Check their stuff
Then they get up and leave they're probably not going to think about
Doing a search
For you
There are however really really simple to use add-ons
For just about
Any browser
Out there that can automatically
He searches for them or refresh
Current searched at they have
Google
Yeah that and like
Extensions Lake
Just for example Google has one and I use it for this exact purpose
Call
Siri load every nuts Firefox
Firefox has one called reload every
And it can set up a refresh
For you
Randomly or everyone
10-second or
10 seconds
10 minutes
However often you want to search
Search for you
Lindsay Lohan
The media is already doing this themselves
Direct
It's cool that info Warriors and
Patriots you just leave their computers on
Did they
Install on are there browsers that will help
Matt Ryan do it so I'm going to do is I'm going to get a list together
Bots we can artificially inflate
First first
Are you telling me that you want
Non computer-savvy people to start downloading add-ons to their browser
Box generally speaking that does not work well
No
Seems irresponsible
And yeah just seems like
They know what
Traffic look
Looks like
Not hard to figure out
Also like
Euron are planning a scam
All right so if we are going to go rob this back and I know we are we've already
Confirm that we will be robbing this Bank
Call her
Cars to get away
Do you want to drive for it to use
Specifically
Right now that you have
Very strange
Bob Chapman
Chose up
Great the the
Snow forecast for Bob Chapman
Yeah
Guy sucks but it's really all that in
Borgesen Alec
Give this time
Don't buy gold
It's all about buying gold
Getting gas a copy of hard copy or an email copy
Or
You can get a free one year
Subscription
By getting
Small gold coin
So here's the point I want to make very clear lake
If
You're like sort of
Expert on the economy
And the radio show host
And the guy who syndicate's the radio show who also runs the gold company
Are all intertwined in a bizarre business relationship
Don't get involved might be untrustworthy
It might be that shady
Fiesta forecaster recommends buying
The exact amount of gold that I sell
Perhaps this is not a good
If the forecaster like his
Business
He's doing a newsletter
You can get a free year of it if you buy gold
It does seem like he hasn't affected by the forecast
Cast of Rosie maybe people might bore
But buy more gold or not Rosie
He does work at school
Usually
It's it's
You might have forgotten
By now but this was supposed to be about the Rockefeller you remember that
So this is the last
Clip from
I'm on Sunday 4 to 6 p.m. I'm going to cover this in more detail remember disrespectful video this weekend
Future dictatorship
To the environment
Total control martial law
Quarantine checkpoints biometric ID to travel to live
Read what these monsters are planning for you
It's the same thing in hundreds
It's about food now
I don't know what's going on
I heard that
Atmos like well
You're going to get into it on
So we better
Better check in on Sunday while we're here
Alright
So we're going to be covering also the July 18th
2010 episode
I have
To tell you this.
This is a bit I got to warn you in advance
Alex comes in a little
To the show
On Sunday okay he's got a head of
Alright let me Adam Lenny Adam I am fired up
Control myself throughout the next 2 hours it is Sunday the 18th
We're here six days a week Monday through Friday 11 a.m. to 2 p.m. central vac Sundays 4 to 6 p.m.
We have a lot of news in Mexico
Part of the drug war down there
How they climb now therefore days into a successful cap I pray this is the truth
In the past but let's cross our fingers
And say a prayer
These are the same headlines
Are you still just wait and seeing with PP
What happened
I don't know
Okay
It's very strange
These are the reasons our
Sure the reason is Maddie
Is because
Cover all the news today
Security
The web
Friday
A listener
Pointed out the top searches were Lindsay Lohan Mel Gibson and
Just do.
Top search should be depression because we're going into
And Friday and Saturday was number one
More than 20 newspapers and blogs
Email sent out for year-and-a-half
There are hundreds of versions of it up on YouTube
We don't have
6 years ago people that have them still have them
And so
Had gotten 6.5 million views at 6000 change Friday
Saturday
Well above 6.5 million about to be 6.6 million
Well that sucks
6.4
Barack Obama or Obama or President Obama
Not the number 3 like it's been like that for a year
The number one ranked on the world wide web
Mega viral video
What's 6.5 million in growing no f****** way
No
Who is the first
If you search for Obama Alex
Absolutely
McKay's
It's only on Alex's browser
Yeah
Yeah I don't know I don't believe any of this
But it worked
Apparently
I was just playing work
You got more traffic I would like to know more about the people who pose
Reviews
Oh
Could only find one or two
That doesn't surprise
And they were complementary
I would like to have
Examination from a film student
Yeah
So
Melo news is Rosie
I mean we got definitely
More traffic
Make the plan
Shake It Off
Sure we got the money and ran
But unfortunately
The FED might be on
College professors politicians news people whatever
You type
Obama
President Obama Barack Obama
It was hacked
And it it shows you're done by user that's what the heck is that go in and once it's deleted
It's gone the 6.5 million views is gone
All the tens of thousands of websites that are linked to that video
It's dead link now
And of course
It's the Obama girl at the White House it's not our video
It's an inside job from YouTube or Google
Or as soon as I heard that my first thought was
This Fiasco somehow involves the audience doing more free advertising
Yeah probably
Apparently according to Alex
This guy
Website that's B users Channel on YouTube.
Must be an inside job
Partially inspired by how jealous Obama is
Of
Alex
Yeah
Yep yep Obama
Obama
President President Barack Obama
The most
Well known Pat man on the planet
Yep
Jealous
Widely widely respected
Alex's
Starpower
Is reach
Yeah man it's like it's like people get petty over download numbers you know or like YouTube views
Alex and Obama were beefing
They have the White House YouTube channel and they weren't in the same kind of traffic that Alex was getting
I mean I would say they thoroughly fun
F*****-up Healthcare at this
Point so maybe Obama was like look
I just got to focus on everything else
So we'll get along but I want to get out in front of this in advance
I don't believe that this even happen
The most that I believe is that there was a
Temporary Tech glitch or something with being blown out of proportion or conversely I could believe that this is all made up
Hear my reasons for having that position
The video Alex is referring to on the chain
The channel YouTube channel
He's still up
Active in the year of Our Lord 2021
It still has the original publisher
Date it didn't lose a 30-count nor did any of the
The comments dis
There's over
200000 comments on it so I couldn't go through all of that but I was able to find some from the time. Of around 10 years ago
And not her saying hey so glad to see this got put back up
Thing to also is because
There have been a couple people who have been having a running argument
And for the last cup
Couple months all right all right I like that
Individual competition
Possible to navigate still like if they both sound stupid
Took two I was able to find some blow
Who's covering the alleged
Take down to this video and none of them can actually confirm that the video is too
Taken down
All of them rely on
Entirely on claims the trace back to Alec
What's himself
Which seems sketchy
It just so happens
Is that the evidence that Alex had a lost and they were already dead I'm sorry
Redan a true breed
Are we able to find a forum thread on Gamespot about
The claims of the video was taken
Can down as an attempt to silence Alex and some of the poster little interesting
Angry Pelican comment
Quote I'm watching that video right now on YouTube
It's not deleted
Another user chimed in quote I have it on the background
ARS one guy has a good analogy
There seems to be a lot of people who work
Confused at the link that was post
The Twist supposedly
Delivering them to a page that began playing a documentary about Obama
So I believe that this is a
Continuation of
The traffic
Began when it's Friday show with cheese now heightening
On Sunday
I can't say for certain that the video didn't have an error loading or something like that at some point but
There's literally no part of my being
That believes
Hackers got into a YouTuber
Accounted took down the Obama
It almost
The most unbelievable thing I can imagine
It look now
Alex
Improve-it see when he went to YouTube
Page opened up and it said you have internet connectivity
Issues which
Clearly mean
That the YouTube page was
Taking down
Obviously if you get if you get that kind of message there's only one explanation
So this is a federal crime
The name, or President Obama Barack Obama in
It was the number one link on Google and Yahoo
That was before we had lister's promote the term The Obama Deception to make it the number one Trend search Friday and Saturday
A whole bunch of newspapers reported on the film
That film The Obama Deception of my newest film
The rise of FEMA
Luckily we were Twitter / by listeners and were able to call the director who runs the director Channel
To get him inside their change the passcode before they took off
The point is this is a serious federal crime
This is an attack against everyone's free speech
The other thing that I want
This is that if you
Had deleted the video which I don't believe they did
I think they would have been within their rights
Alex is clean the engaging in manipulative rack
Necklaces to artificially game there
He's openly discussing that is his plan and there's even been conversation on a radio show
Groups of people using
Box to boost Alex's view couch
I could easily see an argument being made that this is an abuse of the platform and against the
The terms of service
That said you didn't delete this video and there was no hack
I just wanted to point out that even if this was realize
Still wouldn't care
It is a federal crime for YouTube to enforce
Terms-of-service policies Dan at stroke
So Alex Shadows video the night before
On Saturday night
He's pissing
So serious
But he had to shoot a video talking
Sing about how this video got taken down
Google bomb in the video about how people make Google
Beach
My friends there has been an assault on the First Amendment and Free Speech
The Obama Deception has been erased obliterated
Don't know why is this important
Well it deals with the First Amendment and Free Speech
This hack was illegal
And somehow got our passcode
This film and other documentaries I've made so that you don't have a right to watch it
And make up your own mind
You don't have the right
Alright so it still hasn't been taken
No it's still up
Yeah that's
Definition of logic
This
Was so funny
Alex describes
What it was like
Experience
This hack this is still from the video from the night
Before
And I got not his YouTube channel though right
No it's another guy
If they work together apparel a
Jeffrey Wright
And I got to say I don't like this
This is where things
Reached a level of like
Bad movies
Farce
Luckily one of my webmasters
I have to be writing a story about the fact that the Obama Deception was getting hundreds of thousands of use a day
Number one
Trend being searched
On major search engines
We were getting Twitter pink telling us it was down
And I said hey
He drove in from a barbecue
William of the hour of the starting
And was watching someone live in the interface
Release date for the rise of FEMA and The Obama Deception and thank God we can change the passcode
Saw a little guy creeping around inside the YouTube account
That's up to
It's good day sir that's good days
That's another that's actually reason for
I don't believe
But I didn't want to spoil the fun
It said that he has a way to fight back
And so in this report that he's playing
He has the solution
Here's the good news we can fight back
And the destiny of this documentary is now in your hands you can do several things
Number one
Go find the links on YouTube Google and other sites
And send that link out to everyone and tell them
This is a censored film
This is a film that the establishment
Doesn't want you to see
This is a number one that was deleted
Century book-burners
An expression
The American
And the people the world are going to strike back
To The Obama Deception
Out to everyone you know
The Google and Yahoo and other major search engines The Obama Deception
And let's keep it at the top of the trench art let's make it the number one searched term in the world
That it was
Let's have The Obama Deception Rise From the Ashes
Like a Phoenix carrying the light of Liberty
And freedom
It is up to all of you to carry this torch
Wow
Can I throw a base
Baseball Beckett
I don't know you can't do I have the arm strength
I don't
Think so I can reach 88 miles an hour I know that for a fact
You can
See how Alex is doing the exact same thing gear as he did on Friday
Super height
He's creating fake problem and he's made it emotionally resonant to the audience and then he's made sure that they know the only way for them
Don't really fight back is to do more
Free promotional work for Alexandra's website
Instead of appealing to the audience is understandable feeling that the oil spill was more important
Celebrity news
Then co-opting for his own benefit
This time houses made this
Supposed deleting of his videos
Attack on the audience themselves
And freedom
This is psychopath levels
Yeah yeah so so what you're saying
Is that you've manufactured this lie about the
The video being
In downtown
Convince your list
Nurse 21
Share other versions of the same video
If the video where censored dad
Well it censored on that one that had all the
Reviews
Haha
Yeah so we need
Me to pump up the other views
On the other ones
Which
If that is the point
Those will be taken down in the same way
Right
And then we'll do it again
So I remember
Hearing
Pretty regularly
That the reason that Alex was embarking on this was
Cuz he was a fender
Did the BP was not higher
Up on the trend
Important story where is Lindsay Lohan and Mel Gibson
Not important
I think we may have lost sight of
That
Particular
Okay no but Alex is about to
Turn heel on TV
The establishment
Could not put up
Friday and Saturday with the number one search Trend in the world
Not being Lindsay Lohan or Mel Gibson
BP oil spill
It was The Obama Deception because
And the video
That was the top
Going on for at least a month
When you type in the name Obama
Any variation thereof was this filmed
Chanel BP oil spill is an example of something that the gold was too wanted to
Trend over Alex as opposed to the reason he's doing
Hahaha
This is silly
It is
Slippery
You literally went over Lindsay Lohan in the
They're trying to make it number one over
Everything's like Lindsay Lohan in me
Terrible
Is it outrageous it's censorship of the highest order that they're trying to make BP the number one tutorial
Was advocated for yesterday at Alder
Justifying things
Bigger than that it's about me
Dealer show
Not the video you chop tonight
For this is where I
I think I would say this reaches its natural can
These sensors are going to have their way but let's not stop there let's make the second surgeon case they blacklisted
Blacked out
Obama Deception
McCarthy
I want you to search the term infowars.com
No ww.w in front of it
Just infowars.com
Over and over again
We'll see how they like it
This is you naked
Manipulative
Piece of s***
What
Can you listen to that and not go
F*** you
It's
The kind of thing that I see like I'm offended by how manipulative
How is you are someone who took him seriously this would be a really tough
Thing to experience
But
Looking at it now from the 10 years later
Perspective
Hard not to laugh
Ed Howard
Embarrassingly and cleared
Charade he's putting on in order to try and gain more traffic
Yeah it would probably not work if you just said hey
Hey guys I would like you to artificially inflate by traffic
So I can become more well-known
Open if you put on a patch
The government
Suburban all of this stuff
Celebrities are trending what it should be serious stories like BP and so what we need to do is we need to get
Get my
Documentary about Obama
So we do that
Can we pretend that it gets inserted
Then
I didn't work the first to buy a new house
Parkside
So Alex now gets do what I would describe as a v
Yelling face
To eat up all of
Dallas and I made the film
I'm a Level Playing Field of ideas I won the Superbowl
Shut up here didn't work 7 days a week
To make this documentary and fly all over the country it's been hundreds of thousands of dollars to make it and I gave it to you for free
Google girls boots
I can't sell this video and I put up with it we wrote an article about it 6 months ago but left it at that
And now they won't even let me give it out for free when they put their stinkin ads on it and I know they're the ones that
I think
The problem with the teacher was like
Copyright
Because he steals G
Just about every
He doesn't seem to understand for someone who's really a property rights
Property seems to be a complicated
Not interested pickle
Intellectualism the name
Sober
He spent a little bit of time freaking out and yelling
And
Blown Away
Listening to this like
Like how clear it is that it's
Just like
Everything is driving
Towards just like
Self-promotion
I need all of you to be my street team
I need you to do this
Yep
Web but I
American even make up some hanky-panky is every time they file false complaints against me
I just filed in federal court
Behind the scenes I've had to file in federal court no fewer than eight times in the last year-and-a-half to keep that stinking video
I had to go in there and file
Against false copyright claims and tell people put up or shut up let's go to court
Barack Obama really is I am busting my butt here to bring this information I'm not complaining
I know you understand that you're upset out there with lifter so I'm going to beg you
On my knees for all of our few darts
We caught him inside the interface deleting videos where they weren't able to
No you lying
I want you because that's basically part to The Obama Deception and quite frankly even more power
Viral
I want you to get that video
The homework if you choose to take this mission
Over and over again Obama Deception censored
Infowars.com
The Republic
All of the Republic
Yeah so now he's promoting
Sequel
Oh man
Oh boy
Is this
Is this how movie should advertise from here on out should we should we have more movies just being like
This movie is coming out on
January 21st
And you are going to love it
What they don't want you to see it on January
21st so what you all need to do to see this movie is Google
The name of this movie on January 21st
Because they're censoring it
Hankinson in Africa
Campaign
I don't know if it would be effective outside the context of a very
Cracked audiobook Alex has
What happened
With the Snyder cut
Or whatever
I choose not
Not to know anything about that smart
I just know that a couple times
I'm going to go the other way
So they took
Is downright
This documentary
I don't believe it either
But they did it
In order to keep
Are you okay
Cuz they they were afraid
I understand these Trends it would have gotten a million in the next week
Probably next week they know we hit the zeitgeist
Quintin
And they shot this video down so you don't have access to it and so you don't have a right to see it
They're going to decide what you get to see
This is 21st century book burning and then I've got stacks of news
Right here in front of me
I mean here's one that's ignored due process First Amendment shut down thousands of blogs
That should be the number-one 73000 blogs were shut down last week no judge
No jury no nothing
Vice President Biden and intellectual property enforcement coordinator Victoria espinel
Gave an order
And they've got quotes here
The DMC takedown actions were direct violation of the First Amendment under prior restraint
However explains law professor Wendy seltzer
They have not received constitutional scrutiny despite the high risk of error seltzer'ade
White House
Now issuing 70
Thousand
Take down orders
This week
Mainly of blobs critical of Barack Hussein Obama
So Alex is talking about the blog platform
Blog entry
Hiiraan
It was there was some initial theories that people were kicking around
The platform was taken down due to
Dcri dmca
Complaints
That was just pure released
Speculation
It came out a couple days later the reason the server that
House blog entry kicked it off and just removed 73000 torso blog
Was it someone was using the server to host an Al-Qaeda recruit
Provement website
Complete with a hit list and instructions on bomb make
Marquetry was hosted on servers on by burst. Net
Who got contacted by the FBI regarding
Terrorism stop
Emily decided to stop working with baggage
Apparently there had been some past terms-of-service violations that are unspecified
Must have just decided
If they were allowing an al-qaida site to stay up at they may represent too much of a risk
To stay on the
I'm not sure in the end what happened with all this but as of July 21st 2010
There was an article on scene at about burst. Nets effort
To try to get
The data from people's blocks back
So they can have their blog shortly would not rehost blogatog
You shouldn't lose all of your car
That to the extent that was possible they were saying they were
Find a way to make
That happened
There's no indication that any of these affected blogs
You're critical of Obama or if anyone had anything to do with these acts
I was just making that up
Because it's a
Concurrent headline that can be used to strengthen his Obama Deception censorship patch
They are taking down 73000
Block the no one's talk
Talking about it which is why you need to Google The Obama Deception
Right now
Also to be clear that stuff about Biden and Victoria espinel
Unrelated story from
Dune where there was
Discussion about it
The massive economic cost of copyright
The Infowars story about the
Roblox being removed
Just kind of assumed that the reason that they got taken down with copyright violation
So the whole angle is that
But it's not true
And also
You just tell Alex's like
He doesn't even know how the story on Infowars
Kidstogether
Just finding bits and pieces of it and I needing it madly
Using it in a way to adjust
Supply whatever the
The story already is
So luck
What the internet
Do you know will be hard to censor
The internet
The real world
All the free links
With the expanded actress
And make copies of this
We making a hundred copies of this might cost you fifty bucks
Thank you
Give it out to everybody you know
Your local church
The system doesn't want you to see The Obama Deception
Fall Republic
We are part to here
Absolutely one-hundred-percent
That is
Yeah
She was little
But you need to know that this is
Sprint
Need to get this
That you are converting people to the word
This this next trip is a little jar
I found his
Switching to a little bit weird
They can arrest all of us it's over
It's over we're done
Rolling over
Dungiven in
I got a deal right now
Infowars.com you click on both of shopping carts
For films for 1995
I don't even make money on that because I put a free Pocket Constitution and every order
Okay with the cost of the filter thing else that comes out to less than $5 for film
If you get 10 films
That's very weird
Wow that's
Sales right now
Ideal baby
Oh man
So Alex throws to break
Really really patch
He's freaking me out a little bit
The underlying message here is that the only thing you need to do
To break the will of the NWO
Is support Alex's stuff and give him
Free Press
You print up an image of Obama is a joker and you say Google Obama Deception and you never stopped and
You left these Nazi blood-sucking anti-American parasites that want to make you and your family slaves
I'm not downtown everyday
Better to be who I am
Yeah
There's a little boy it sounds like on Thursday of her dues it was Alex we
DVD sales
And then you can hear this is like
This is like after a comic
He's been on the road for a year
And they bought
200 t-shirts
And they got 190 in the Box I took a bath on this printer
Give these away
Better turn families
Continued existence
If you something it's conditional I'll buy it yesterday I'll get this s*** out
So
Just more of this
They know what we're doing is effective
They have all these statistics
And taking down my film The Obama Deception
White House live
Barack Obama or President Obama Obama
What's the number one link
Are the number one searched term last two days
What's not let them stop us
What search the term father Republic my newest film
What search
The term police state for the rise of FEMA
Infowars.com
We can't be stopped
It doesn't
Keeps going doesn't
Tires
Just doubling down on this side this
We need to remain organization
Obama's
Policies
And I I don't know what any of them are and you're were about to take control of the Senate because
Is the Democratic party is s***
I'm going to have to say the only way to stop him is to make him
Feel bad when he Google's his own name
In my imagination
I'm a guy and he's trying to
Pump It Up about doing free Street teamwork for him
Are hitting everybody right now is a test because
The bottom fell out of Obama
He is their front man
He was supposed to bring us
We oughta be happy
And just lets me know the effect we're having so what are we going to do about it
Antonio
Are you coming by tonight
Are you going to send everybody the links to The Obama Deception that are still online are you going to make copies
Going, Drive-In and at the top of the France
Yeah they're only making us mad to do it more
No sir
His collar is so close to recognizing the dynamic that's happened
When Alex asked if he's going to burn the DVDs and send out links
All sorts of free Street
Teamwork for Infowars the caller says
They're only making us mad to do it more yep
That's totally correct
Except the imaginary globalist aren't the ones making him mad in order to get him to post more
Infowars
Alex's doing math
Yeah you didn't stop
Open thing
Will the globalist be mad about this more will Alex just
SP morfema
Yeah I might
Be wrong
Yeah this one could
Beyond me you know what I'm going to stick around
And I'm going to stay listen
And for the rest of my life bet
Everybody who took the races them
I could either engage and self-reflection or
Can send out links yet and did you know I'm definitely going to keep sending these links to people who have
Long ago
Put my
It filtered into the
Forward forward forward no
So I asked if another caller
And this guy is weird
He seems to be a fan of some
Financial broadcast
And that lead people on this
Does broadcast
I've been wanting to have added
With Alex about something
Sure and Alex has been
Or something along those lines
This past Saturday on the webcast from Financial sense online Jim puplava who's the proprietor said that
Your office hasn't gotten back to him yet another issue
We have sponsors and very white shirt
I'm sorry what. You guys coming here on Sunday as well
Probably 10-15 interviews a day I can't do them all physically
And Beyond
I tried to recruit other people I'm trying to find other host I can promote
Problems
Are they can't handle the power
I can't do it all as my problem
Do they turn it on go maniac
I just can't afford to at
Advertise
You guys do it
I don't understand what this is that this isn't complicated
No I mean like you responded to exactly the point
Of that clip that made me angry
He's like I have a plug but like 30 seconds on the show heard everything
You have Plugged In The End
Hires everything mad
BB laugh
Two episodes of the show the Friday and Sunday show
Have been
Protracted nonstops
You're a mental long-form advertising
Impressive advertising
I do think
Did this possibility that Alex
Doesn't
Experience
Is plugging
Or whatever but
Take and take
Confirm lichen
External viewpoint
Like that's all he
He's doing
Everything
It yeah yeah I know this is
Complaining
About
Not getting enough
Views
All this is
I'm being mad.
Mel Gibbs
Is racism is more interest
Sing the news Angelo hands more famous than him
Unless and until the show ends on Sunday okay
Boy it's familiar
Shortwave
Doing let's count
Obama Deception out to everyone and infowars.com out to everyone God bless you all
Is this
Episode
Hold and also kind of tickled
Confused
Because I went
Back trying to find the
The coverage of the
The Rockefeller
The most important document of all time was all over like
Plan he reveal Roblox
They got the information out to everybody now I might be
Cynical
I might be a little Jaded by my time covering Alex but I will say that my
Experience of listening to these episode
Football's altogether you barely cared at all of us
Feels like he even told people not to worry about
About it so much
Yeah
Let's get better reception out there
Okay so what we re contextualize that
Dumb f*** video as yeah
First off
He's a lying piece of s***
Enterprise
If he isn't
Align peace
Piece of s*** if he is
Claiming that he predict
This entire thing
He failed on a level
So incomprehensible
I had to listen to
For f****** hours of him tell people to Google The Obama Deception
I'm warning the Free World we're all about to die
If he had come into the possession of this plan
Document that was a good laid it all out there
Yeah you do
More time on it
Then he did
Probably more time talking about the
The BP situation and how
Lettuce
Which is not hard-hitting news
Oh yeah
I think there's very little by way of the
That's why
The present day 2021
Video about
Coverage of the Rockefeller document is so thin
So where we even touched nothing
Another headline
That was
It was able to roll with
Paul wrote an article about it
Alex
Skim it and say some scary words
And it could be used to help
Scare the audience
Browbeat them into a place where they
Google things for
Here's a here's what I'll say
F*** him
+ 2
If you are listening
To that and you do not immediately
Demand
What step do man the knowledge of
What are this
The globalists are going to
To take in order to implement
How can we stop
Each of these individuals in order
Lockstep
From happening and instead he just says
Going to happen in the only way to stop it
Google the Obama devil word out
Promote my s*** this situation
Not only is
Not at all Hero for predict
Sickness or anything along those lines
He is
Insane dating and abetting accomplice in this regard
Is aiding and abetting the imaginary villains in his head
Exactly
Cheese's
Yeah
It was not what I expected
I mean in terms of
In a in a way
Yes it was what you expect
Expected
Something
I don't know what I expected
Do you expect the unexpected
No
I did not expect
Two episodes
Google Talk
On Friday Jordan
Annoy the s*** out of you
Gyros on Twitter
We are on Facebook
Could please find a local charity or bail Fund in your area to help out
People that do and got the
Until then I'm Neo I'm Leo and bcx
Clerk of Daryl run this Sunday
About to go Google
Strategic relocation
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color