Jordan
I have great respect for its knowledge B
Knowledge fight
Everybody would make knowledge write them down just a little bit about Alex Joe
Jordan Jordan
Oh wait no
That's not always work
I guess it's kind of related to that but I was a joke
I guess
What do I break so I think is kind of like I'm starting to forgive myself for enjoying video games
Like we talked about some games were playing every now and again in these bright spots that
I'm started to recognize some of these like unexamined
Biases I have towards myself for liking video games okay
I would like growing up there was like my parents were very against
Video Get Lucky play half an hour
It's always been like something that you could be doing something better than that
And I think I have a little bit of self
Appointed
Stigma about it I'm starting to feel a little bit less
That way
Part of that is just like I'm recognizing there a lot of really good that are a lot of fun and
I don't know it's it take more a little bit of that shame is good because I've always had that same experience that even if
If you classify it as like a complete Leisure activity you should be doing
Better Leisure Activia
You're playing a video game as a Leisure activity
What you should be doing
Is going out to a park and throwing the ball around its like I get that I'd sometimes I do
The museum
I think it's good to retain a little bit of it last I defended you only
I'm finding a balance
There's a new Mogwai album about Dan and that is important
Don't be that out my permit
No it's not it's really interesting to me that there's a new album all the way in 2021
Because I think the first time I saw them live was in 2001
And they've been putting out music
Sick since the late eighties
But it's Mogwai so it's not like
It's not like the Rolling Stones at those old bands of like 70 year olds who are still touring
Weird post-rock so
Everybody who goes is like
I want to hear your new s***
Post-rock all sounds basically the same have an interesting confession tag I know nothing about
You don't know anything about Mogwai Mogwai is one of the most important first
Scottish band's there's ever been
Mogwai help
Create the entire genre of post-rock as we know it
This is a big blind spot for me clearly cuz you could have told me they were metal or Folk
God dammit
Wonder of influencing other
It's only fair that I do not because I got a lot to
Through insurance
Jordan 3 episode to go over I think there's a lot of twists
Cool boy but
The first
Hendersonville Nike walk
Kiwibank is about you and I'll probably walk
I'm a policy wonk
Enemies
Could you very much however you are also my enemy for Iams Bungalow to Orono
Next thank you to eviscerated by a Reptoid over Cadbury eggs
Very much
Vision of all of our faith
I'm a policy out there actually it's two people
The technocrats so maybe they're both
Technocrat or technocrats
You decide
I'm a policy wonk
What's the business
Money off that heroin
Why you poop so good
Freakishly large
Thanks so much Madden been
Special occasion to celebrate today
Yep
If mogwai's birthday
Birthday shout-out going out to Easter
Happy birthday a holiday by the name of Easter
The Sumerian god of
Nobody know but I am excited that Easter candy start show up
The Walgreens and what have you do appreciate everything out there
February 15th baby I like those
The eggs the that the hard-shelled eggs but many eggs
Easter I hope you enjoy Smith everybody's doing well
It's terrible but my partner is allergic to
Peanuts
And so
Hoard
Reese's peanut butter eggs and eat them like a squirrel before I get home
Mouthwash and brush my teeth but dance
They're worth it I'm going to get you some Reese's almonds
The butter age
My flights
We didn't have an episode on Friday and then the interest
Full transparency
Discuss what
Essentially that video of Alex saying that he wished he'd never met Trump
Threw me into a
Fleet tailspin but not for the reason that people who listen to our show or who don't listen to our show by thing
I was flooded my messages and comments
For people wanting our take on it so naturally
I sat down to digest this footage
In the name of being able to have a conversation that the audience can understand
Let's listen to that clip now all together
Part of me
Salvage
Never met
Unlock
Previous
Those workout
Time space
The 3rd
Is this is you guys actually
Mercedes
Truth
Oceanaire
I'm so sick
Donald Trump
But I'm not doing this
People unfamiliar with Alex Jones or the right-wing media speaker this Probably sounds like a huge huge deal
Here's Alex on film saying he's sick of trump and wishes he'd never met Trump Rodger Stone
Listen to our show regularly this probably would less shocking
Though Alex is created
Personality cult around Trump that he's inexorably typed
To he also frequently lashes out at Trump in people interrupt orbit
When things don't go his way
There was a classic
Piece of his breakdown after Trump bombed
Syria in April
Yeah then
Of course the old part where Alex yelled f*** Trump a bunch of
That day before he realized he was screaming a lot
No one will ever know about it
Betrayed his family and talk about how ashamed you was of trump in a supporting
So out of hand
Shroyer had to try to stop the
The show because Alex was swearing so much and they were out of delay
So they couldn't believe things
I see that
It's so f****** clear right now showing
That was a tough drunk Nitro rally
We did a whole episode about that night so if you want to hear about that detail with episode 1
But the thing is that might is not at all an isolated incident
Alex very regularly blows up
Trump and the reason is pretty album
Trump doesn't actually care about what Alex thinks but Alex's business model has relied on him claiming the Trump does
What trumps public actions contradict the version of reality that Alex is painted on his show the only response Alex can have
What is portrayed as butt
Betrayal
The alternative is to admit that you're either conned or that you were aware of the Trump associate you were helping
I'm calling your audience
Neither
Are acceptable for Alex
Does bran
Yeah they don't they don't come off in a
Positive light no matter how you
The same thing happened during Alex's March 2019 ask me anything stream that he did which happened after face
Could Purge more count
Did Alex and Infowars ran
And just after Rogan didn't episode with Jack Dorsey where Alex's Twitter ban was
I was really wrong about how Trump wasn't helping him get it back on social media
And he expressed that inaction on Trump's part as made him turn against
Trump has all the power in his hands
And he's a good thing
But the fact that he
Doesn't
Jose Sanchez.
The end of the day just have
Person
So he should be abandoned
I'm unhappy about that cuz I've been persecuted
A Boy drum
I got is my ratable away
Cast
And it was a r i don't want updated probably cuz of them
They just run me off Trump's they just make me
Cut against Trump
Trump
Maybe turn against Trump
So it doesn't matter
If Trump is right
If he's going against that way of turning us
Some of these clips
Might be a little obscure
No they haven't been
Seen by multitudes of people there can be argued that Alex said these things that unseen areas of the internet Worley weirdos like me looking
Unfortunately Alex's literally also said that he hates
Trump more than Hillary
When he was a guest on Joe Rogan show
I don't dislike Donald Trump
I hate Donald Trump
Because I got behind Hillary was bad
Because
Donald Trump
Your trunk
In a fight like this it's so dumb down
That then no matter what I do they take my radicalness
But it's like
My legs everyday
This is John from your own personal perspective and I appreciate
But he's not your daughter know how many people actually think you'd be said he's your identity
You might notice that in these lips
Is clearly intoxicated on air
That's something of a theme and it's something that seems also to be related to the clip that was released by hatewatch
The clip of Alex
Yeah and you can argue in vino veritas if you would like them not going to
Alex definitely seems Drunk In that clip and but the thing is this is not a behavior that
Exclusive 20
He's clearly f***** up
In late January 2019 Alex was getting deeply frustrated at being associated with Trump
Partially because
Does fundraising for Rodger Stones legal defense
Was cutting into his profit
Rodger
For his his his his his issues
When I get a job here which is great
This is just a split where we may not get the funds to find Infowars
Because the 24/7 Rodger Stone
We can win the battle
Because of that
Infowars as a bill
At least 10 times Rodger Stones yes okay
Have 100
I have all the bills and all they
Equipment
Rodger
Cost money
Playoffs
Alex is definitely more demonstrative and more
Gregarious I got f***** up you'll still Venture into Minneapolis
Like he did here
In this segment he was doing on his a big Marathon
EBay 2017
He said this
Trump
Is the
Johnson holster
Andre neocon Democrat
Trump is
The Johnson holster
Special complex
I neither just clips about like
Trump they're not even about the people associated with Trump that Alex has gone back
In 4th on
Heroes 2 villain
Wings Over and Over
The point of seeking to make ears that if you follow Alex
You know that him saying that he wishes he'd never met drunk while drunk
Controlled setting where editing is possible
It's not a bomb
It's a good headline and it seems to have driven some traffic if my mentions or any gauge of that but I'm not sure it's helpful
And the reason for this is 3-prong
The first is the fact that this is not a comment that
It's necessarily groundbreaking Alex's said a lot of s*** about Trump on his own show
The second pieces that literally nobody who listen to Alex Jones we care about a 90-second clip being reported on by the Southern Poverty Law
Law Center's hate watch they always check the splc
To trust people I can personally respect the work that the sblc doesn't acknowledge that they are an important entity while at the same time
Absolute certainty that no one who believes right-wing propaganda will respect or accept a report
From the splc
A very beat up basic piece of right-wing ideology
She is that the splc is a
Communist globalist front organization
Meant to launder money and demonize Patriots who threatened the globalist established
Any report coming from that source is go
Going to be basically hot like I'm normal
People see a headline that comes from Glenn Beck
Yeah I was going to say it's like you being like Russia's not doing anything evil today
Presumably the people that this clip in things like it would be helpful for people who suspected Alex may be a valid source of
Information
And it turns out those
People they will not be reached by this reporting at all
That's not to say that the sblc shooting to reporting like this
But the fact that they only they have access to the underlying material which will get into in a minute make
Little bit difficult to believe will help anybody that it could help
The people that this hatewatch article appeals to our people who already think or know that Alex is full of s***
The third prong is it this base
Basically just plays the same game that we've done so many times with Alex
The past
The response is predictable and honestly
It's one that Alex comes out winning
On the evening of March 2nd
When this article on hatewatch
Was released
Appeared on the War Room
Too disgusting
It was honestly so formulaic that I probably could have written his responsible
Before listening to this episode
So here at the beginning of this is Owen
Introducing this headline
And asking out
Alex
This is just I just might as well bring this up to his
Kind of funny
No no that's at that's a different one this one just came out from the Southern Poverty hate Center chisme Southern Poverty Law Center
Ridiculous
Especially when I work here and I know the true story and then to just read their lies
Howard Jones on leaked video I wish I never met Trump
You can see they're calling at the Southern Poverty hate Center preemptively minimizing into writing the headline in the source
This isn't a big deal to Alex Rowan
The thing about there was that apparently Daily Mail article attributed words that an Alex
Impersonator said
Do being from Alex himself
It's difficult to tell though because what's apparently parody is
Indistinguishable from things Alex would say himself
From the article
This is normalize Mass extermination to biotech on Humanity
Before the day of our Lord's birth in the name of the satanic pedophile globalist New World Order
They want Force to knock ulation of the gates vaccine which has the HIV delivery system Gene coding it has HIV
That's what happens when you defeat
Parody
Yeah when you
Finally won over at like SNL can't f***
Touch
Have been said by a person doing an impression Metallica said all the time
Any episode transfer
First it gives him a chance to try and wage of publicity campaign where he's able to see if he can get some cheap attention by yelling about a more pop
Popular broadcaster
In this case Howard Stern
We're mere days away from staring getting the Sneaky Snake
Second it did distract from the main point of that Daily Mail article which
Ex-wife house in a helicopter
Which a terrorized their daughter
Show me article
In the video exclusively obtained by dailymail.com the couple's twelve-year-old daughter is briefly seen waving before rushing over 2A
Screaming
It's scary Mommy
.
We tried to stay out of Alex's personal life but this incident seems like Alex being a real
Piece of s***
Sing on this detail about the stern character seems like a way to make this up the audio
It's not even care to look
This article
Kind of makes him look like a real piece
Yeah and that's also another thing that's beyond parody
No good or reasonable human
Being would f***
Fly By Their Own
Child with a helicopter
You've defeated me
That's ridiculous
Yeah
So we now get to the formulaic
Exactly what you would have
Alex
So they're saying that it's a leak
Footage
From a documentary filmmaker that you paid
On his film even though that's not even actor I don't we didn't pay him to make that he did it on his own
Turns out those guys work for help. Hey
Volume up that whole group
They they came to me and they said we're making this documentary of Paul watch hollifield over here one day
They did the interview and they said what's your feelings on Trump and I said most Devil's Advocate it's in the film
The part of me hates my life
You know it's terrible I wish I would have met him but I'm still glad I did it
His overall endorsement able always do that you know they always get me on that
Here you see the reason why this minute or so clip is not really threatened
Name to Alex at least in the eyes of his Alyssa
It was taken out of context
Which is the standard excuse that everyone in the right-wing media knows damn well they can use to get out of almost
Any situation
It happens all the time because it's something that the audience has been trained to accept
Particularly when the clip
It's sad to be out of sorts.
Sinfully maligned like the splc
The audience requires an answer for that clip
Because people are posting it around
Just delivered by Alex saying it's out of context
That's enough
The audience does not then become curious about the larger context is matter is just dead
Yep and you know what
Alex is standing on
Slightly sturdier ground here than he normally is when he makes that claim
I went my re-watch the full documentary called you can't watch this
And the part that that clip is in
Part of it is in the movie
Here is that
Part of me
Salvage Farm
Wish I never
Fantastic business out of
But it's doing great business I hope your audience
I just want to finish by saying your reputations amazing
I will not let you down
Into that
Vortex
Yourself
Everything I did everything I was
I was trying to do
That point didn't matter how diverse it
Better
Did that
It made from
They understand
Donald Trump
We've been merged together
End of this
Obsessed weather
Target on my back
Promote
America's resurgence
To promote
Bootcamp
This was a real bad
Crazy
I left it at the beginning and end of the show that that
That's where
If you listen to the clip that's included in the final product of the documentary
It's not really saying anything too different from what Alex is saying in the newly-released clip
Yeah I didn't know that that was in there and not happy about that
Particularly around how the identity that Alex enjoyed
Prior to being associated with Trump
I swallowed up by this new images
Make no mistake though he did create that image any profits offer
Because that does seem something like a very clear-eyed evaluation of how things have gone which makes me think he's been listening
I show too much
That fits in the documentary is somatically the same as
The only difference is that Alex seems to be
A little more mad
And he's having a little bit of an outburst someone shoved Isis up there
Dirty a****** I of course I don't care if you've already said enough
Tough to top that if I told you you should
F****** up the bass up your dirty ass
I don't think we would be
If you're on the lights
It's what's been said
So the thing that I find fascinating here is that the Clipper to the documentary is actually a clear articulation of Alex
The clip released by hate watches
Is interesting only because it appears to show a secret revelation
An emotional out
You can see emotional outbursts on Alex's show everyday
Secret Revolution ultimately here's one of the things that I'm really struggling with
As far as I can tell
It's someone who watched the documentary is watched Alex's show around the time that this
Documentary was being filmed
I do think that the clip is taking Alex out of context
Alex was struggling with his identity at the time
According to hate watch this documentary was filming in January 2019
Which is exactly when Alex was spending a lot of time on are discussing his desire to
Get back to his roots
And not be so singularly associated with Trump
Here's a clip from the January 28th 2019 episode of the show
Where Alex discusses how he doesn't just want to talk about Trump and Rodger anymore
Audience
Wanted to go back
Back to his roots
I don't want to just cover Trump
Rodger Stone like Rodger
It's taking all the oxygen out of the room
Stuff going on around the world
Iran on the edge of Israel
What's happening in Venezuela
What's get ready for China collapse which I agree with
Elsa jumping on the bandwagon
Usher's Love the show
Secret society some and the globalist and
Weather modification because the last 3 years
It's an Ultra Ball the time
He'll still be alive
It's just I don't want to cover every facet of everything from Josh
Alex was feeling like hit his identity and Ben
Subsumed by the Trump
You clearly was greatly
Feeling some kind of backlash from the audience over there
They were expressing that they weren't
There was some
Whatever it was
Cuz maybe it's somebody who works it in for the maybe it was
An outpouring of feedback from the audience right we miss back when you were fun
This is Vegas boring in OneNote feel like this is such a
Nothing
Simply because it's
Seems impossible to believe
Impossible for me to believe
Then any right-thinking person
Would look at the
Grifters
Not think they all actually hate Donald Trump
Like in the primary
Hey Tim
Bill Hader
But it's just part of the
Game he won the game and now they have to lick his boots
Any reasonable person would be like
Donald Trump
Yeah I think I think anybody except the most ambitious grifter would have
Receive it like okay
The money is falling fast
Most ambitious grifter would have probably the best might have paid off
I'll probably not be alone don't know if anybody who boosting Rand Paul is
Making a lot of money
This was part of a larger. In time where Alex's
Really f****** tired of Rogers legal fun siphoning donation
Definitely this phase but he was in unilag
That that legal fees and
This disillusionment with trumpet wanting to be who used
Going on
In January 2019
And if you pay attention to Alex and you were listening to it you would know that this stem from Alex being mad at Trump
For not declaring a national emergency
Close our Southern border
This was deep in the
Caravan propaganda cycle of 20/19 Owen Infowars world
Trump not
Declaring an emergency and season complete power was essentially him allowing all Americans to be murdered by MS-13
Just hard to rationalize
So Alec
Turned on Trump for a little while
That was a really rough situation for Alex
Because he had all the
But guaranteed the Trump was about to declare an emergency
Has he heard we can be heard here
Watertown to be alive my friend
Privately
I remember that one I like private declaration
On their faces
It's as if they're being let up before 8
Firing squad
Or how about this clip
Mike Adams incredible job net.com
7:00 Central
Recovery
Declaration of emergency
Emergency
East County Clare
Or this one
My dad is God bless you great job is going tonight 7 Central
Emergency
How old is going to end
The globalist want to fight
Here in January 2019 the migrant Caravan fears were the biggest story in the right-wing media and Alex it essentially gone all
Clinton Trump declaring a national emergency
Read it a special evening stream to celebrate the Declaration that
Didn't end up happening
That's f****** embarrassing
Understandably a little bit raw bout it after the fact
Constitutional lawyer really smart cookie founder vote
Skippers
Those cookies to be joining us
Yale for his writings
Smart guy
He concurs with what I've said
Essentially is no longer
He is advocated his responsibilities he shies away
Pettigrew people around him
Are the helicopters
What you can do in a cloud
So this is one of the things that makes a clip like this really it's incredibly difficult to understand without a nuanced understanding about
What is propaganda
In the context of the things are set in
Alex angry sick of trump is attention-grabbing
What is completely in line with what he was saying on are around this time
And we were talking about back.
Alex was
Sick of his identity being associated solely with Trump
Which expresses more coherently
In the tape that they actually use in the documentary
I went to said way worse things about Trump on his show
Like before decided to support him for president back in 2015
How to regularly talk about how Trump was a front man for the mob
You going you show it
University
Palisades houses 40 million 13
Is this Donald Trump
Just a front man
For some
And
They go in there
This is mind-blowing I don't know what to say anymore
And like he did this a lot
Donald Trump owns a bunch of casinos
Donald Trump's bunch of stuff he's basically the frontman
More
The last 30 years so
You can bet this is all this phone I have sources
Shop
John Trump
Haha
This is the reality of a clip like the one released by hatewatch
Schroeder's clip
It's simultaneously in and out of
Contacts
I do believe it captures a moment of frustration where Alex is pissed off about how pigeon-holed he's become as a trumpet cheerleader
But I don't
I think that the moment means anything outside of the
Exciting people who already don't like Trump or out
Yeah
For me this falls into about the same heading as that Bon Iver parody song that was made about Alex
It feels like an attack but in reality you just blaze directly into his hands
Consider this
I hate Alex Jones
I don't know podcast about how full of
Shiki is 4 / 4
4 years
And when I heard him respond to this clip by saying that it's out of context
I don't think he's totally wrong
The heat watch article doesn't discuss the other version of this clip that appears in the documentary
Nor does it address what was going on in the world around
What time is the documentary was filmed
Could have contributed to what their readers were seeing
Perspective these are important aspects the understanding that clip because
Without knowing what was going on it
Really easy to see that clip and make up your own story in your mind about what Alex
Still when he says I'm so f****** sick of
Trump
You never met him you can
Can come up with your own explanation of what that means
And it's
Not
It's pretty clear you know what was going on
He means by that tweeted out immediately cuz I got all those
I got all those
Suggest an ad for Alex and the film
That's what it is
I know it's not
It's just because God dammit Dan
How many times are we going to do
Snap-on
That's why this episode is going to be a little bit
Dunno different
Is because
The frustration of
Everybody wants us to cover these things that go viral
3 years ago
Is that like this is a little bit different than those other instances or because
Caseware
I do believe that it's
In context
Inasmuch as it is a video that doesn't have like a bunch
Quick Cuts
No it is Alex saying I'm f******
I'm sick and tired
Trump gaffe
You know it is that
It is also divide of the surrounding context that could be accessed
I mean just by listening to his show
I mean there's a certain part of me that night that is not ansible
Yeah just because
Look
You shouldn't I mean it's not you shouldn't be paying attention to that world
I'm not going to I'm not going to say that it's
It's hard to pay as much attention to it as we do
And that's something that you know we constantly has
To check ourselves on in terms of being like
How can you possibly not be aware of
Sweetly sensible thing to not be aware of what there's absolutely value intake
Something that otherwise people would
No
And bringing it out to them
I get tons of people who don't pay attention to Alex and just know of him I'm sure it's a very Valley
Valuable thing for them
You know also
He's full of s***
You know and if they didn't know that and now they do that's a
Positive this is where we get to why we didn't have an episode on Friday
When I was exploring some of these ideas and listening to this clapping
And what-have-you I realize the cover and Alex's response to it would be unsatisfied
I didn't want to do an episode where we look at this and then just say that Alex said that the clip was it that was released without a context in the
The best I can say
Kind of
I felt like
Too close to defending Alex
I felt like the best thing I could do is try something
I've never tried before and that was make some inquiries
I said emails made
Bunch of phone calls
I'm tried everything I could think of other than starting a social media pressure campaign
Because I'm opposed to those
But I was trying to get access to the raw footage of this clip that hatewatch it released
It came from sea with the surrounding
Discussion was around that
What happened after Alex walked off camera as he does at the end of that clip
Did he immediately clarify himself or did he sit down and say stuff that made it clear that what he meant is that he f****
Can personally hates Donald Trump as a human and that he's connected to the Mob
I felt unable to wrestle with this clip fully without the surrounding context
Tumi
This was a headline being presented without a body of text
Yeah then we don't
World
Headlines
Being their own
Story is not good
What's with Alex.
No one at the splc your hate watch return my calls or emails and my press request went unanswered
But they wouldn't suddenly drop everything for a podcast
Smoke dude I am thinking I understand people are not everyone's aware of us personally or anything
I completely understand and I'm not sure about anybody
I just them saying this to say I tried
To get access to this
I don't know I take it a little personally
Can I junk a roll I do I'm taking a little bit personally I find it I just find it a little bit
That if you're reporting on Alex Jones you can't find
The only podcast about it that I put on all the effort
And then you get to be mad that it didn't work out
Okay
Okay are you going to play the victim for being a better person than me.
I did see however that the producer of the documentary that the clippings from who gave the footage
Hatewatch
Replying to a tweet from one of our listeners that indicated that he would be willing to
To come on our show
Typically when things like this happen
Ignore them
I don't have a lot of interest in doing an interview with someone who comes from the worlds that we cover since I've added
Default position
Distrust and skepticism towards them
And I'm not particularly drawn toward making a show like we're b and a propagandist gallate each other until errantly
Don't think I can interview and because I'm famous for saying cut his dick off to Rochester
So true I would make things a little bit at
Cereal
Convinced that I should interview him and you were
Strongly opposed
Yeah so I figured a middle ground would be to reach out to him and see if he was open to letting us review the larger context of the clip that was
Released
I made guarantees to everyone that I
I spoke to that I would respect the right of hate watches reporting
I wouldn't scoop them by releasing Clips they may or may not be working on for future story
The documentarian
Caitlin Robin Roberts
Said that he gave the footage hate watch
Discuss what it was like to work with Alex
I responded by asking if there wasn't
Exclusivity situation hate watch
At which point he stopped responding
It's entirely possible that he saw me at someone just out to get the
The footage to create clickbait and undermine whatever plans there may or may not be for release
Sure he doesn't know me at all and I can't begrudge someone being careful about who they would trust online
So this didn't seem too strange to
I think I moderated my tone but honestly I might have come off as a little thirsty for the footage maybe it's really hot
Hard to tell how your tone works you are a little thirsty for the foot
As Wednesday became Thursday I realize that we needed to record an episode
Set alarm the audience expected that we would be covering that clip
I hate watch released in there without the larger footage
I didn't have much to bring to the table
There's a larger context Alex is still an ass-whole he lies about everything but there's nuanced here that might have been
I didn't know what to do but
At that point
I still thought there was a chance
Did someone get back to me
Covid is a total pain in the ass so I can understand the bureaucracy the splc and hate watch being slow down a little bit
So maybe I hear back on Thursday or Friday
MSI decided to punch
To Monday to make the best episode we could
But that was the point
But here we are on Sunday and no one's
And there's not much
To say other than that
The splc is bad now.
If I didn't have the raw footage I felt like I was at a dead end
That said I'd already thought a lot about this clip and I had some things I wanted to say about it so we have to do this
Jeppesen
I decided to re-watch you can't watch
How
I could watch it
I wanted a job down some questions that I would like to ask Caitlin Robin
Robertson
To see where I would take a theoretical future interview
OverWatch
What's through that lens
A ton of question
Jim came to mine
Particularly about the state of mind one is in while creating
Clearly full of s*** propaganda documentaries that feature
Opinions of extreme
It's like Alex Jones Tommy Robinson Laura Loomer and Gavin McInnes
As well as I believe Wiley
Coyote
I got into this idea
So early on Friday I said Kalin another message
Explaining the reasoning to my wanting raw footage
Listen to better understand the context
I also said that if that wasn't possible I still might want to chat and then if he was interested
I could email over
Questions you could decide whether or not he wanted to
Participate
I'd absolutely no interest in blindsiding anybody and I felt like he could
See the question
The tone of what I was looking
Sing for
And decide whether or not he wanted to participate
I did not know about to be fair I'm just saying that might sound a little bit
Do you know if you're on if you're on a date and you don't get a response for a day and then you come back with
I might answer questions yeah it was definitely reason I didn't send another message after this one
I'm also not interested in harassing somebody and I felt like another unanswered message in this change would look good look
The guy who keeps sending messages
Yeah that could be dropped
It dawned on me that I knew very little about this guy Kaelyn Robertson
The right-wing media but he's a behind-the-scenes guy
And is only direct association with Alex
So I was in this film you can't watch this
Switch didn't impress me much
I didn't cause a big splash when it came out
The hay watch P says that Robertson has disavowed the far-right in
Controlled hatewatch
He's working to undo the damage he did while producing propaganda for extremists such as Jones
That's good
But words like quote
Producing
Propaganda for extremists like Jones
All the kind of words that make me curious
What other sorts of extremist
Are we talkin about you you know I read that line in my immediate thought was
Tell me again
Exactly how he is disavowing and improving from there
Give me line by line
Do not tell me that
He told you
He was disavowing the far-right
And you took him at face value
I started poking around at this dude's fingerprints are on so many of the side characters we've discussed on the show
He used to work at Rebel media
He did extensive work with Tommy Robinson
He directed to flagrantly racist and intentionally manipulative documentaries with Lauren Southern
And perhaps most interesting
Langley he was the uncredited
But at very least a man and probably editor or director of Stefan molyneux film The Hundred Year March
Philosopher in Poland famous for his
Declaration of I am a white nationalist empirically
We covered that
Entire documentary divided its episode 285
Lore podcast
But not only does Robertson bows
This impressive list of right-wing should had credentials
He also went along on that trip that Lauren Southern and Stefan molyneux took to New Zealand in 20
Spoke prior to their talk
After screaming screaming his very racist film farmland
Which argues that black South Africans are trying
Kill all the white Farmers there
Here's a little clip of him giving us
My name is Kailyn
With my colleague George Lounge on
Incredibly challenging Craigslist
But together
Highly emotive subject
Very very
In the right way
Are so powerful
Every child properly now
Case you're interested here's widths
Stephon was talkin about that evening
Giordano's, Gaston
Appreciate being hairstyle
Pedicure
Now the beginning
So I thought
I've heard about the noble savage
Pull up
Data analyst find out so
We started researching into
Average
My plane is going down sir
But it's important
It's important because classical
About
European
West Katella to the White Sox
And then does the Aborigines
Collision
Who invented a good way of Altar and civilization
Whitewashing
And another
And then like
Engine
Call Twisted lose that you
Cutting tool
Manipulator
Giant red Vending
Wow cool stuff. I want him to get Collision
The New Zealand and also that
Christchurch shooter donated money to
Stephane molyneux and was a big fan of Lauren Southern
Images Manifesto the great replacement which is he
Conspiracy about white genocide that Lauren Southern's movies are based on which were directed by Kaylin Roberts
So real quick if I played Caitlin speed
Good thing you told people that he disavowed that
He said that in that speech in New Zealand
That he was covering this very sensitive topic
Think about the South African farmers
It was crucial to tell their stories properly
What about that
In a very interesting review of Lauren Southern other film borderless
The YouTube commentator Jose
Interesting problem about how Farmland told the stories of these farmers
Here's a little clip
From Jose's video titled the many lies of border
Towards the end of the video I highlighted one of Lauren's major
Works and that's the movie
Farmland
A movie that advanced
Erases conspiracy theory that blocks
Africans were out
How to kill wife
Farmers
Fueled by
Some sort of
Racial animosity that's
Chin. Bye-bye
South African
Petitions
In that movie a woman named Janine ihunt Phelps
Had the gruesome details of her father's murderer used to it that said racist conspiracy theory
I mentioned that I didn't believe Janine was a willing
Participant in this evidence by the selecter
Evangeline ever entered
Interview of May 2019
I can tell told
Ariel Levy
Writing for the New Yorker that she had been interviewed under a false
I felt exploited
Another farmer phone me to say he's got this Canadian chicky doing a documentary about the drought
Can you bring her to me
Hence I was in my farm boots
My shorts
To go and show them the effect
Of the trout
On the farm
I mourn sat down and said
Tell me about your dad
Completely caught
This is a shocking revelation
Because it's not something that can possibly happen by ax
It's the result of a conscious decision to mislead interview subject
An exploit what they tell you by taking it out of context
The further the conclusion you want you're probably
Ganda to arrive at
The behavior precludes good-faith
There's just no way around. That's not possible
As it turns out this is not the only way in which farm lands the documentary directed by Caitlin Robertson
Fail to tailed woman story properly
In reality her father was killed
And that is a tragic
But the film fails to explain the details of the
The crime because they want to use it as a prop
To make the argument that white farmers are being targeted for genocide by black South
Her father was killed by a guy who'd been working on his farm
5 days prior this man hit
Stabbed his girlfriend who was a person of color to death
And was chased by police
But not apprehended
He went to the woman's Father's Farm killed him and robbed his house and was subsequently arrested
He's now serving a 30-year set
Denton jail
This is a case of a double-murder and it's sad and an awful crime
But it's not
Lack of racial hate towards White Farmers which is what kaylyn's filmed
Portrays it at
This isn't telling the story properly it's creating a fake version of a South African woman
Paying to exploit
The further a racist Mario
And then
What's further gaslighting an audience of New Zealand well-doing audience warm-up for a guy who decided to be a white supremacist because less of the
Food is dumbass
He's look I get it but
He told the splc that he disavowed that and he gave them some
Footage of Alex that everybody's already seen before
So he's repented
I'm struggling I'm just whatever really struggling
Over the course of the weekend I watched and read everything that was available to be found
Created about or created by Kaylin robber
Because this picture was just giving me trouble I'm
I was confused it was
Accidental going down this road but I'm not
I was interested
And I was confused
Wow
You know what and I look
This is by no means retaliation
I know because we've talked about this every step of the way
Should have given us that f***
No I understand I understand
I think it's funny you think that but we talked about this
Extensively
Believe me
That is not your motivation whatsoever
The more I watched his work the more I didn't like him at all
But the more I watched his interviews
Borat kind of
I like them
You going to mentally Charming person and that Charisma probably played no small part in his ability to rise to such a position of prominence
On these right-wing
Appearance
Is so critical
As well as getting them to
Perhaps
I mean you know like
Louis Theroux isn't
Incredibly Charming person that's part of why is documentaries
End up with people saying stuff
I don't know I I feel like
EZPawn
Interesting and New Yorker would have written
In a glowing profile.
I would say so
Yeah I mean I'm not immune to it
Like watching TV Guide
It's so intriguing is that going on here yeah
So
Here we are in the present-day and Robertson has disavowed the errors of his ways from a few years ago
He's trying to undo the damage he's done commands that I do I want to be very clear about that
I was curious about the stories of his path to Redemption so I decided to dig a little bit deeper and watch some of the more recent interviews
That were available out there to try and get a sense of
One of the things that I
Love the most about our podcast and unfortunately
Maybe tainted now is that episode about Jessica shop
The crystal child school not be as much of a
Wonderful success stories
God dammit always looking for something like that.
For something uplifting it cuz
Is it it's so much better than Alex's dumbass
I know and I think we is that
That's a great example because I
Thought about that one a lot
My exuberance towards Escape was
Undeniable
But
The more I've thought about that
The more Act
Cannot take
People
At their word
When they just say that they are
Disavowal
And the reason that we
Do
The reason that we always
It's because we want
You believe that
Yellow heart
I want to believe this guy but
The reason that I'm
Against
Believing
That this guy is
But that's about it
Is because I know I want to
Cuz I know that part that provides hope for me for my f******
Family that provides hope for me for so many other
Books you can come back and so I am not going to trust anybody and that also is what
Makes like
I'm struggling
With the idea that
It feels like we might be attacking him or something
Because I don't want
Attack the idea that it's possible for your family or for people around you
I'm just
Curious and I want to deal with reality on realities term
That I talked of course
Everything I say is
Sounds like
Is that
He is learned
Where are you
He's earned where we got
And if you want to go somewhere else you have to earn it
And those
Maybe they don't have to equal but I'll tell you that given a few Clips to the splc is not for earning your way
Way out of being a
Shitbag
That you were right
A couple of important points
It's one that's not frosted
And
But you can have your feeling and you're entitled to your feelings
You're not the judges of
This person absolutely not
We cannot possibly know
What he's done
Privately
He doesn't owe anybody like us
An apology
He has made amends with folks
Behind-the-scenes privately and I think that maybe even more appropriate
Then anybody. No one's actually what he should be
Yeah absolutely can't judge
Whether or not that's the
McKay's
And I'm not sitting here saying he has a
I'm saying I'm struggling with this
Because I believe wholeheartedly in
I believe wholeheartedly
People can make it out
And
Often times their stories on the other end
Can be very
Uplifting and helpful for people
Yeah I also don't
Don't think it's appropriate
Pretend
But this history isn't what it is
Exactly like
Did Redemption needs to take stock of the
The professional career that
Baguette the Redemption
100% And I was not convinced of that until I was watching this
As I was looking
The story of
You know the uplifting this
This doesn't make sense
There's something that doesn't match up
The first thing that stuck out to me was an interview that Robertson did with a Muslim activists in the UK named Ali dawah
Ali and Tommy's crew had a really high profile running
Mean in the past back in May of 2018
Surrounding a rally the Tommy with the wrong called Freedom Day
The event was supposed to be a free-speech rally so Allie requested to speak
At the rally
Why wouldn't a free-speech rally you I want to have everybody have speed
Initially he was told he couldn't
But ultimately he wasn't allowed to when he was rapping
Threatened and attacked by Tommy's fans at the event
This interaction between
Miley and Kaitlynn
When in September 2019
It's actually really fascinating for a number of reasons
The first is just a simple fact that these two people who are on opposite
What size of things a little over a year prior
We're now able to
Polite conversation
The other reason is that halfway through their interview gets interrupted by an
An old British islamophobia spouts a bunch of anti-muslim talking points at Ally
For no other reason than because he looks like a Muslim
Do you know
Get sidetracked and derailed by the
The consequences of kailyn's
Prior action
It's almost as if this interview was metaphorically Express into the damage that Caitlin didn't is past lives on no matter what he does
And beyond that
ATM gets in the way of and will be a
Constant problem even when he's trying to do good
I see presumably is by having this chat with Ally
It's remarkable how this turn of events
Captures a reality
And a metal real
And both
Involve the person in Body by Ali
Patiently trying to deal with the aftermath of what this white nationalist propaganda has done to
The reason I find this interview the most interesting however is
Because of one detail that Kailyn gives
While discussing that Freedom Day March
I was all about fries
I remember when you were invited when you made the offer we were in a room with domain
Hotel room
Lucy was like he might be
And it wasn't
You arrive
. the head of the DFA lay with a Leo B B far-right group football
Text if you let him onstage will throw this age-old
I'm here
Pokemon
And you said just a minute and he said yes
And that's only realize
That moment
But he didn't give up
No but we were quite convinced like I
You
We are like a cool penticostale - there's a lot of far-right idiot that we don't want
But we genuinely believe that f*** you
F*** you was the moment that was the moment
I have no idea what was said when Kaelyn's might cut out their butt
The gist of that story is that when Tommy was okay with the idea
Free speech of
Because he was Muslim
He made Kaelyn wake up and realize the Tommy didn't care about free speech at all
The conversation goes on to be about Hitomi uses Free Speech rhetoric as a mask to hide his real agenda
Which is racism generally an anti-islam vegetation
Specifically there's no way for him to have known
Before that point that the far-right did that
It's not possible
The claim that he's making I actually kind of believe in the reason I do
Is it in July 2020
Easter video to the byline time
Which captures Tommy Robinson essentially saying exactly this
Back in 28
Repeat song
Is it awesome
Imperfect
It's interesting cuz that clip is from 2018 and it seems to be Tommy discussing the idea of doing the Free Speech rally
Which would be really just to trick large numbers of people to come out who wouldn't show up
If you're honest by granting Muslim intense
That Freedom Day event
Allegedly Free Speech event that year
And he did spend some of 2018 in jail so it's pretty likely that this clip of Tommy
Free speech is a mask
Might have come from
Before the Freedom Day I got probably say
I have a hunch
Could
Be there
Either way I find it super hard to believe that anyone working with these people wouldn't understand that Dynamic and I think it's super embarrassing
Tommy got caught on tape explaining
The most obvious game his friends play
Very sad
Yeah
The point here
Whether or not this tape was from before or after the Freedom Day event
That Day in 2018 is supposed to be the day that Caitlin
Realize
The Tommy Robinson use the
The facade of free speech is a way to cover his racism
And trick people into getting involved with
I was just so loved
Tarsus moment
That rally took place on May 6th
So it's safe to assume that anything that took place after that point
Was done with the full awareness
The whole Free Speech argument from the right-wing media figures is not
Well then I assume he quit at that point right
Has a problem
This what you can watch
Kaelyn interviews Alex Jones about how he was
Kicked off all those social media entities were
What happened in early August
2018 after the Freedom Day rally
This interview is being recorded in January 2019 even later than
To reflect on how baby Tommy Robinson isn't the
The only person who uses Free Speech complaints to Mastiff
To make matters worse Tommy Robinson himself as one of the subjects of this documentary and the entire point of it
If you couldn't tell from the title is it these people who
Just alternative
Only being called racist
The entire concept of this documentary is something that
Based on Cleveland own timeline you should have completely understood was just a way of masking racism
Appealing
To free speech
Bulshit
In January 2019
At the same time he was making this documentary
Dude was interviewed by Sky News
It is interview he tells
Story about a short film
We made about Muslims
Extremist College
The film premiered didn't end up making
The client is screening
To carefully to this interview
You might notice Kaelyn using
Free Speech argument to justify people's racism you think so
Well I made a like I think was a 9-minute film just about a
It wasn't an entirely but there was like a bunch of Mustangs
Extremist Rebel looking up
I'm down white Tahoe
Ivanovich of interviewing a another day we want to talk very much
Cameras
And then I should have one of my lectures and they're like oh this is
In the screen ink
I'll be official
Like I'll be official screening of older short film to the end of the year and I was like oh that's pretty strange to do anything much of it
But then when I started Googling about universe
Teapot for me things on living. Showing all the old
Different ideas
Contrasting what
Qdoba
They said
I'm using word inflammatory that eight
Could be perceived
I think they
Wasn't for like a super Insidious way I think they would
Just trying to be polite
Translate anyone outside a lot of dick
People and bring that
Kind of argument into the
Do you know I wasn't
Until I started researching University
But yeah that was
That was sort of
The first time I reckon
But I was going on
Is it fair for me
Enjoying
Adults between
And that film
And then
Get your lace up
With Tommy Robinson
Informative video
Yeah well this is why I said at the last race
Relation as well
If you would only show something maybe we have some
Difficult conversations and actually not
Silence freedom
Silence
Content then people might not start Quest
Start dedicating the light switch or or getting involved in activism
Invited like that
That wouldn't be the case because it wouldn't be there wouldn't be silenced around it wouldn't be these issues
Sounds like you just about it to me
This isn't a
Appeal to the idea that the left being censorious and limiting free speech of people like Tommy Robinson read racist
Is what causes people to become races
These people aren't actually even because normal society won't let them at the
Conversations that they want to have
You know those difficult conversations like the ones is Buddy Stefan molyneux wants to have about phrenology nothing
Love more than a
Pressing people for hundreds of years and then blaming them for making me feel bad
That was in 20 miles are in January 2019
Anime 2019
Human appeared as a guest on RT to promote his documentary
If you can't run
And he discussed with the film covers
Once again
After Yorkie should have realized this was no good
Sure he relies on white washing his subjects behaviors
By appealing to free speech
The project looks into how social media is being used as a
Tool to exclude certain voices
Focuses on the online war with
Comic conservative
And the implications this removal of content house for the freedom of
Speech
The director says he hopes
The film would uncover how serious and widespread
It's become
And the danger it poses to our culture
The film follows
5 controversial figures who have been victims of social media
Curtis
One is British activist
Tommy Robinson
Who founded the far-right English
Defense League
Facebook accused Robinson
Promoting hate against the Muslim Community
Also featured is Alex
Jones director of
Infowars website
Permanently banned from Twitter Jones is said to have promoted
Discriminatory Behavior
And spread
Information
No he did
Not to discuss the documentary and the issue it touches upon we're joined Now by Kaylin Robertson and executive producer
Picture of the documentary you can't watch this
Surgery
Chair of the Islamic Human Rights Commission
You're both very welcome to the program Caitlin if we could start with you social media platforms
Are public forums do not think it's a fair argument to respect the diversity of users
And not to actively provoke or offend them
We have all this documentary explores his increasing powers of social media have in
Changing the Overton window and influencing what people cannot watch online with consumers
In in changing elections and this is why it's so important to people argue all well you know their private companies I can do what they want
Directions to my Publishers and they actually have a duty to actually
Whole free speech
As one of their core values especially given how important social media is an Honor Society
Looks like someone's using Free Speech arguments in order to elevate the
Complaints of Laura Loomer
Gavin McInnes Alex Jones
And Tommy Robinson those people all have something else in common besides
Century
This is like a year after the Freedom Day rally what do you
Yeah but you can possibly you can hear in his voice
That he recognizes that what
He's doing is wrong old man
Killing them on the inside
This is a man
Crying out for help then please someone
Stop me from doing this
It seems like
Even though you'd known for at least a year that this was a specifically a tactic that one of his
Text Amie Roberts
Used to subtly promote racist ideas
Caitlin was still willing to employ the same tactic to subtly promote his film full of bigots to an unsuspecting population
Strange
I was sitting with this I was really like this
What's going on I was wondering why I was even doing
Yeah yeah
And I want to jump back here real quick cuz I
Looking for something interesting that I noticed
In that interview that he did in January 2019 with Sky News
Illuminating to me cuz
Here he is discussing
I know this is going to
I think this is going to be worse than it is
But here
Here's Caitlin saying some things that he thought about the Civil Rights
Sarah goodnight love with Alexa
70s and 80s
With that with the Civil Rights Movement with the rights for women with the right spaghetti
If it's groundbreaking
That's what made us
Vice news
Great
Of course everyone told me that night seems they were the ones who
Progressive pairing
But it wasn't until I actually saw what was going on until I actually started
Sing the homophobia from
The people that they were already friends with
But I thought
If losing it
Stop that I don't know if everybody could be a little bit better
I do better but I think that if you wanted to compare
Let's not pretend that there aren't
Really critical point
To distinguish Caitlin from the rest of the extreme right-wing that he was hanging around
His right-wing existence is not philosophical
It's not rooted in the same Traditions as extreme right-wing Pierce
Sport deeply auntie,
View The Last of Us
60s and 70s
Is one of the greatest existential threats that the West has ever seen
If Kailyn was rooted in the morning
French School of the right-wing
He would do things like integration voting rights and lgbtq protections as things or push bike
Communist
In order to divide and conquer Society
He doesn't seem to me from looking through the available information that I can
Can find that there's a lot of depth
To kailyn's right-wing views
In many ways
It seems
Aesthetic
Almost
Yeah it's performed
Where could he did back in use on the rebel is often about dumb pointless culture War
Compliance
Like this clip from July 2017 Oso mad
But there was a new emoji that got relieved
Someone wearing a hijab
The original ID according to the website was I have an emoji with a dog
Purple headscarf
But fearing that was a little bit
To crazy they decided to honor more neutral
Phone color one which I think is a lot more
In the change.org
The group asked her they were going to make progress
If they don't include everyone in their path for
Payson acceptance boy are they right
How on Earth are we supposed to achieve world peace
Without the right emoji
And I don't know about you
But I'm so proud
To see the tech industry
Making such
Giant leap
For Humanity
And I tell you I can't wait
Pontiac GM emojis
Oh
Wow
Oh wow wow it's like a he's like a
Paul Watson out there
I'm convincingly argues with
The britisher at war with Islam after the suicide bombing in Manchester in 2017
Just again this this doesn't feel convincing
And once again it proved so we
Currently
Right now at this
Very place in time of the 23rd of May 2017
War
On the left
Seems to think that they still dominate them then now except for this entire purse
Perspective
Katy Perry only hours ago saying that we need to
Ignore what's going on
Keep the borders open and stop
Hate we've had
Hundreds of political figures on
Pretty much every side of the political Spectrum up
And down the country explain
All of us
Elektra
About how we must
Come together
How we must Unite
And how we must
Not
Hate anybody
Choose
But we are coming together
We're coming together
As British
Just people
An islamist
I'll coming together as themselves and we are
Becoming even more of a Target and it's a total
Waste of time we are lying to ourselves if we think that having some sort of
Vigil
Posting
Notes all over City Center saying that we will not
Kecoughtan lighting candles
We'll make any
Difference
The only differences between WWII the last time this country looks
At War as we
Arno
What's that at least then we could name
The anime at least then we actually
Buck
I know we don't do it
Even slightly
Something like that
Just seems like an act
Videos and complaining about people cutting loose at Pride
Is a video game complaining about Starbucks
Exchanging our logo in Saudi Arabia
Feel like it has anything
10 going on like it feels like a pea
PR person doing the right wing
Piece of propaganda
Because that's what it is
He went discuss the beginnings of his career in that Sky news interview for
No like my career was always in Mach
Cotillion on politics
Lots of the pr and things like that at University and
After I graduated you my partner
Baby saying I was broke
MPR Farms
And that's where everything was ready focused
Obviously how I transition
From
Traditional established
I'm sexist
Into what we doing now
So taking all of the
But stop at a party
More assertive friends alternative
Subject
This isn't a person is motivated by the same ideologies that many of the people we talk
About our
The Infowars universe
Particularly in the pre trapera but still to this day
Is based on the Bedrock of ideas disseminated by the John Birch Society and their Associated figure
It's almost entirely emerging of Cold War anti-communism
Run amok
And extreme white identity change religious beliefs
That's what you find behind many of Alex's guests
And in his own intellectual tradition
This is the same and intellectual tradition that popularize conspiracies about the globalist
Switzer morphed into the deep state
Conspiracies in the past few years
The cool that Caitlin is swimming in with
Build by anti-communist conspiracy theories
But I don't get the sense that he knows how the plumbing work
He knows marketing
That was his job
And he's good at it
I would say like that alternative
So covering the
Stories
Allura traditional media established
Immediately
Want to talk about or
Sun covering the other side of the conversation
Play Life
I'm bringing production value that as well and legitimizing is argument
So they're not like
Fringe Salon
Things on there on the corners of the internet I'm bringing bringing up
In 2019 while on Sky News prior to being on art
Tea to promote his free-speech documentary full of racist
Caitlin fully expresses an awareness that is roll
Is to take Fringe things make it look presentable
So the people might get tricked into thinking that their names
What this one
This raises is
The question
Of like
It doesn't mean it was
Does it mean to disavow a right-wing ideology
See if you never f****** believed it in
In the first place if your ideology was simplistic and not really based in the same things that are motivating
This
Wide swath of right-wing
Ideology
30 speed back to the militia movement back
What is disobey a z disavowing f****** opportunistic bulshit
Is he disavowing the f****** deceptive editing
If you disavow
Surprise interviews like I want to know what that is
I think that's one of the things
That I'm kind of
Confused by
And I'm interested in
And these are the sorts of questions that were coming up as I as I was
Taking in a lot of this content
I don't guess it's racism I guess
Okay fine
You're a Merc
For Nazi
You're not a Nazi yourself
Yeah I don't think I care about the distinction between those two all too much
Do you know what I'm saying it's not it's not necessarily A
It's not a disavowing of right-wing
Ideas although there are certainly a lot of racist problems
I don't get the Sun
There was anything other than
Like
Yeah I I found a guy answered an ad
Like make these PR puppies and I was like I'm good at that and then six years later it turned out being a Nazi
Is wrong it turns out there is a wall
Yeah I don't think I'm going to be able to work at CNN is a line producer I've got this on my bag
The thing the thing that I run into that I think is really difficult is that like I do believe
He probably ended up in a position that was different than where he wanted to be
I do believe that there is entirely a possibility that like
Some of that radicalization did happen
Total eclipse from everything
I can tell
It's not the story of somebody who got sucked into YouTube algorithm
Yeah I got into right-wing ideology or something like that
It's a somebody who sought out
Working with Tommy Robinson and rebel media in order to produce
Racist
Content that looked better than what was being created at the time
Yeah Market in efficient
Yeah yeah
Yeah and
Which is also incredibly fun
Locked up
That's not Beyond Redemption 2
Different
It feels different than the
Story
We're being told that you like them the story
That you get from reading that hatewatch article
But it's not it's not
To be a person who's Beyond
Care it's not or not
It's not Beyond respect
Like I'm going to look a little bit this person for an oil
Sure can redeem
You know
Loyal company
He's destroying the world your work
Essentially evil organization
But that's different
It's different
It really is different from being part on parcel of
People who are there to inspire vial
That's what
Cuz that's ultimately the reality of it
I get that maybe he wasn't a believer in the.
Deepest deep end
He is still producing content
That is only design
To drum up
Violets
Did I mean anything new that
Hey here's what else you knew
He knew
Vitale
Would get murdered good yeah
Right so he knows that violence is absolutely on the table
Andy's
Probably
He probably knows
Dory should
Or you would have to be incredibly stupid
Not to know
That that is the f****** the result of what they do is that group
People texting Tommy Robinson saying will
Who killed that guy
Yeah that's the result
Apart
It's the face of it it's the idea
Production of this documentary about Free Speech being infringed to these
For people who are
Sweet bigots sure like that would
Going on
After
He had
The Freedom Day
Experience
Top It's just tough for me to swallow
I'm not I'm not trying to be an empathic and I'm not trying to sit on the guy
And I hope
Just don't know man
I just don't know
No I mean
We talked about this in part of why I was so vehemently against
Interviewing of Zen
I don't know if I'll bore you with this
One more time but
Whenever
My family left
The Cult
Before they could be accepted I think this is an important
Perspective before they could be accepted back into their family and it took awhile
It took a while
They had to send
Actual letters of apology
Single spaced that actually enumerated we understand where we went wrong and here is what
We are going to do
About the
To improve
This is a genuine apology
Did you because it's about
Knowing how to correct
The mistake instead of just saying
I'm sorry for the bad things
Things that happened
And that's what I don't
I think that needs to be made because that's about personal life and I don't
Entirely in terms of professional life
Because I'm not interested in Caitlin's personal life I'm not interested in anything about that
I'm very willing
Going to believe it is a good person
And that he's had a change of heart
I'm concerned about
Product
Concern about the
The effects
Do work
Like
To making things right
Somebody who
Had his hands in
And produce
Slash directed documentaries for Lauren Southern Avenue
Few years
It's a path
It's not that
The public
Has been hurt
Buy them a lot
I do think that the
Things that you can see online things that he said
They do give me any
Vacation Inn
Suggestion
I don't have any reason to
Necessarily distrust it that he wants
To make that thing I hope he does I would say that
The questions that I've
I've been raised
With through this
Is
Okay
So he's
Part of his Redemption
To campaign is
Gotcha
Eclipse
Half of which were already in the f****** documentary
That show Alex Jones
Represents himself
Differently in public than he does in private
Right and what you have just played for me
Is it clip
Abyss guy
Representing himself
Differently in public
In the interview where he says
Here's what I believe in this is the moment it happened to me
And then a clip from a year later talking
Sing about his f****** documentary
More so to me
Well those are different
They are the same
They also don't Point me towards
Believing that a
Guy who's very good at marketing
Is not rebranding
Edison said
Contrite
And changing
It's it's hard
It's tough
Because I don't want to live in that place of Suspicion
It doesn't make me
Feel good I'm not like hey
You know what is great
Thinking of worst of people
That's not true but at the same time we can't live in this space
Otherwise
It's going to happen
Again and again and again
Always does
Are we get to why I I told you this
Call Ciara and I
Again I think this is one of the most difficult and complicated episodes
I've had to prepare
For two main reasons
The first is that I had a
Constantly check in on myself and make sure that I was not doing this motivated out of spite
I don't feel bitter about people not replying to my messages but you never know how much
Might be below the surface
There was this
Emotionally interesting ride that I was on ideal
No trying to Branch out and do something like requesting raw video
Blew up in my face there's a lot of processing going on
It's kind of funny
To be around you with that emotional rollercoaster
Because we don't talk like
The entire way through so I'm getting little chunks in Black
Oh you're on the down way if I could definitely kiss
This text is definitely not to go
Interpretation of the snapshot
The second reason why this was so difficult
Caitlin is sincere and that he's trained
He co-founded a new organization that's quotes designed to show people radicalized
The far-right movement
Is that there is a path out
That is an important goal and people knowing that there's life after whatever thing they've fallen into his critic
I'm personally
Absolutely this is for real that I don't want to be a part of impeding Kaelyn from being able to live
Good healthy life
They can be an example to others that they
They can do that too
I'm not interested in being a dick about someone who's trying to make their way out of being in the right wing
That does not benefit me at all
And it's not interesting
I don't like the idea of people
Shooting on somebody by default
Sure I don't like that
The point that
Hi Isaac
Think about
Is
Regardless of whether or not
He specifically is on the right
And I
Just like you I hope
I hope he is
This story is still instruct
Yeah because
Sure
He's on the path
There are still plenty of people who have taken advantage of this
Exact type of situation
Just saying
Ultimately also I think it's important to remember that in the big picture it doesn't matter whether or not we believe
Doesn't owe me or you anything
Any apologies that he needs to make or probably to other people and they could have already happened and we don't know
That's totally cool that's their business
I'm not interested in it
This show is largely created by me taking an Alex Jones
The content finding things
Stick out is interesting in
And see where curiosity takes me
In this case there was a high-profile viral video of Alex in the exploration of the context of it and where it came from
Let me to learn a bunch of stuff about a guy was apparently turned over a new Leaf
The way I went through this was largely
What I would do if this was
That Leo zagami clipped or something
Except I will admit I pulled a few punches because
Some of it is like well this is
Probably should
Yeah and also he didn't claim to be Jesus
No and I'm not I'm not here to I'm here
911 if you want to get back in my good graces buddy there's a very simple way
Redemption
Wholeheartedly
Someone very important to me got sucked down a right-wing media hole and managed to find their way out and I know that I
I would have hated them
Back when they were in that place for sure
I respect an elder
Define people's right to change
I think there needs to be really serious examination
Professional careers
But people who are claiming to have change
Because to not do so
Is dangerous
Professional
Recent history is full of people who tried to make dishonest Rebrand
I'm sure Samantha Bee isn't happy she played along with Glenn Beck b******* about how he was sorry about all that
Back on it
What is the price
In May 2019 the daily. Published an article about how denoted white nationalist creepa Baked Alaska quote
Is a recovery
Troll
This article quotes him as saying quote I was brainwashed I felt like I was part of a cult
Flash forward to the present in the last we heard of him was when he was arrested
For being part of the January 6th storming of the US Capitol
Yeah but that was it
Side of a cult
People like Mike cernovich of me more pivots than I can count and there's many more people like this
My my kind of just on how I
Because I've thought about it a lot
Since we've been talking
Think about this whole thing
And part I think
Part of the simple things that I kind of want
Dislike
Okay
You don't get to be in Pub
One thing that I've noticed so off
Is that
It's just
I'm just going to
Change job
It's not like
I'm going to do anything to
I'm just going to get a
Yeah and I don't I don't approve
It is it is just a shifting over of
Like
I'm going to now do stuff that isn't hateful
I'll make slick content to make sure people
Not like stuff that like I used to do
They don't need to go to a judge to say give me 100 hours of community service
News organizations that should say we're not going to put you on TV until you do 100 hours that you do like
Along those lines of like
Get your
F****** hands dirty
Really I struggle with
Again to it like
When you have stories of people who have been sucked
Down rabbit holes
Of information like
YouTube
Radicalization in and what have you
I feel like their stories are value
And I don't think Caitlin stories on value
I think their stories are really useful because
People in their position
Can hear them and relate to things
That they're talk
Usher Yeah
Humans experience is pretty f****** unique
And I'm not sure his testimony is going to be persuasive to other right-wing propaganda
Take that lucky
Think you can get out
You can follow my lead and get out
They're going to look at him the same way Alex is audience looks at the Southern Poverty Law
It's not going to be persuasive
To other folks who are creating and disseminating this propaganda
It is going to benefit
Rehabbing His image
Will
And again I hate coming off
The way that I sound
Cuz I do sound like I'm beating the s*** out of a dead horse right now
I'm just
You know
We're just not
Far away
From the
Storming of the f****** Capital it's supposed to be like oh he's disavowed the right and Eyecare
Great
You know yeah
Yeah it's all I'm so that the alarms
No I know it's tough
It's complicated
I mean I don't think the rehab in your image is wrong if your you know if your rehab is apps
I think that people deserve chances and
I just
Like
He's doing this
Organization
That supposed to help people get out of right-wing stuff
If the idea
Is 2
Pele
2 people who are
Sucked into these these web
These right-wing
Information spaces
I don't think
Vicky is going
To be a very easy or upside I don't think he's going to be a very hard target
For the right-wing propaganda not into second Galaxy
You can again you can play clips of
Him doing the things that he's
You know it if it blaming Aries exploiting Alex for doing
Cuz that's what he's doing he's explaining Alexander splc
At the same time
And they're obviously exploiting his b*******
And the only people who benefit from this
Are the three parties involved
Well the issue that I have is
I guess you could
Describe it is exploiting
But I don't
Know if its intention
I could see I could
Scenario wherein
He thinks that this is going
Going to make a difference this video of Alex of course
Hey this'll show Alex is full of s***
Impossible I see it is being fairly unlikely
Super unlike
Would demonstrate a uncharacteristic Neva tape on both of their parts
So
Did the rest of the reporting in that hatewatch article that this clip was released in this initial clip
It's not stuff from the video
That's just things like Kaelyn telling them
Now like that Alex brags about selling dick pills
Audience was gullible
Paul George W
$16,000 a month
All these things are
Interesting
But you know how much Jerome corsi got paper money
What $15,000
Problem is I can't
Accept the
Substantiated word of someone like this just because they're telling me something I want
Totally that's not fair
Also something that
You should deduce
It is far more likely that he is
Making fun of people for buying
Dick pills
Behind their back
Then otherwise
Yeah
But I mean
Sure like the entire
The entire supplement intra-industry is laughing at us behind their back
I feel like a lot of them are
I think that
There's a problem with stuff like that it's definitely something that I've realized
Over the course of doing this show
Is that
That is something that everybody who
Isn't on the inside a suit
Yeah and everybody who's inside
Won't be convinced
But that's the case
Particularly based on the hearsay of somebody being quoted by the Southern Poverty Law
Totally
It's just
Well I mean you'd have to change your in
Entire worldview because some guy who you
No it's
Headed to the splc
Told you that Alex thought
Buying dick pills made you a joke
You know and it's like one
These are dick pills
I'm not even going to admit that I buy these
I am not going to believe that I've been conned out of having good boners
Never
At the end of this will become too
Is
Yeah we have
A situation where it's essentially another
Instant
Of
Don't media
Bungling
How you report on Alex yeah I think that maybe
You could look at this and think it was a slam dunk by
You know if you just had a little bit of context to what was going on in Alex's life at that time
Entirely differently
Then how it's
Supposed to be presented
Hello after that I just don't know man I don't know how I feel
I don't
You finished recording over at the end of this and I don't know how I feel
I don't know if I feel shity
About like looking at these things I don't know if it is worth anyone's time
Would be like
Hey here is somebody who's
Embarking on a Redemption Arc
And
I think that's
Cool
I think it's possible but I also think we need to wrestle the fact
That this isn't somebody
Who
I just
Came off the YouTube
Somebody who went to New Zealand
F****** Stefan molyneux
Winter Poland with Stefan molyneux
It's a serious like this is
This is somebody captured the shot
Of Stefan molyneux
Proudly declaring himself a white Nasheed
And when he clicked
Cut he was like
That was great
Now let me editor
Yeah exactly
I'm going to watch
Hours of him saying that he's a white
Let me edit this together in a way that makes
Kids
How are you this
Who click on this video will see it and think like all you know what he does make a great case for why Poland is a great country
Maybe it's because everyone exact
Tumi
The reason that I
Like play any of the clips that I played
Are any of the stuff
Is not to beat up on this
Because I really don't want to
I play it to illustrate
As far as I can
Until
Everything that I look at and I can see
It's the mark of a willing
And excited participants in this.
It's
I think that there's a victimhood that inherently comes along with right-wing
Spears I think that the lot of the time they abused each other
In ways that are sometimes subtle and sometimes pretty over
And I do think
There's probably
Fair amount of that
And I feel bad that he had to be involved in any of that stuff I don't think that anybody is not a victim to some
In these
Machines in the same way that we talked about like
No Alex
Fire is Millie Weaver for shadowgate
You're dependable and Kuna
Is inherited a fight with Stevie peas so your by David Knight
Decade in your f****** gone I don't care
That is
Like an inherent piece of this information
In the world and it is an intrinsically abusive place to be
I'm not minimizing that I'm not sounding like
He doesn't have a fair point that like
I was probably some mistreatment along the way and that sucker chair
That's sad
From the second
He is involved
In right-wing media
A treble
Then
With Tommy Robinson
It's not
Somebody
Who is not
Like
Driving his own trip message board
He's filming their f****** documentary
You know
I don't
I don't have any place to judge
By no means
But one thing I did
I think when I read that article was like
Oh man
I thought the splc would be better than this
I really did
If I saw that in like
The times or something like that
Of course you guys are all s*******
But it's the splc hate watch
They're good at this
I was
Man I was like God damn you guys are
You know what
I thought the left
Lost
A little bit
I don't know
Anyway
Let's end this
Apologies if
Hey buddy thought this
Episode is pointless
I doubt they'd
But really bad
We are going to bed Jordan Wilson
Wait we're on Facebook
Did I say
No you said we're on Twitter
Nowhere on Facebook
Absent minded
Alexandra first in color with huge fan I love your work