Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Nick.com
Everybody was a little bit about Alex Jones
Jordan Jordan
Is coming to my life
I'm pretty excited about
And that is
Hot honey
I had
Reviews I was at the store
I don't understand
I was at the door
And I saw it on the shelf and I thought what the
The f*** is that I never heard of it before
It is honey that's
Confused with chili
And so it's spicy
It's so good
It is so good Delta like honey goes on
It goes on that honey next to it
But then also the Heat
It's great
You can add honey two things must
You can add honey to
Mustard honey
Honey
Honey my friend
I'll make some muscle honey I'll be right back
You might come around if you try a little bit of that in my room
It's so good
You know I've only had it on a bagel or two so far but there's so many things I want
Explorer putting it on
Delete
Bronson Koenig
Come here
Bonnie on you
What's your bike shop
Food-related
Okay
This is
He's going to seem simple but
Have you ever had a really good pair Dan
I love Paris
Pears are the best butt
The shortest
. the shortest window of her
Perfect roux
They turned pretty quick
He's either eating a heart
A or an
You must shoe long and it's mushy
I would too yesterday
I need a pair at like
Precise
Five minute window
Where was
What kind of parody look like an ant.
Not like a real green I don't like the brown pairs I realized as I started
To talk I don't know other kinds of
I don't even take
Boss is one of them
No Basquiat was
That's
I don't I don't know Paris
I do love them
Incredible a little bit of shade
When I was younger with him a little bit
I'm still actually little bitter a little raw
And I got air my grievances
Paris
My dad
It is a huge fan of Jelly Belly
Answer the Jelly Bellies were often in the house jelly beans of all kinds of flavors and of course is your a kid
People like the toasted marshmallow
That's the kind of thing people like they liked all these candy kind of flavors
My favorite was the juicy pear
The juicy pear it was the best I thought it was really good
And I took a lot of s*** for it
Damaged hair
Left some deep wounds
So Jordan
Episodes of Alfred little bit different than normal get into why
Here in a second before we do the tick little boat
The first one
I put it on scalia's pillow thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Barry much American Hero
Thank you
Can I buy zyn
Next Wingo Bingo think it's about your nail polish
Find Slingo Bingo next to BB star stuff
Thank you so much and I'll probably walk
I'm a policy wonk
I knew BB star's South
Just to be just not the Better Business
Iberostar
Text Zilla
I was wrong
I'm a policy wonk
Ruvilla next tomorrow thank you so much right now.
Are you home
This very special chair.
Laura's baby needs to arrive now so she can take
Maternity leave already
Hold on I'm getting an update on email
Heroin
Freakishly large
Congratulations Lauren baby policy
Both of you for no reason at all
Thank you very much
Make a little bit of a correction
What about our last episode
I want to talk about Stefan molyneux giving that speech
I thought that was a New Zealand and I kind of f*** that up
I completed two things in my head that was actually in Melbourne
But he gave that speech
And the reason that I got it mixed up with
Because when they went on the
Mister related
The speaker New Zealand
Play music
Bright Ray Rice mixed up if I had my I apologize I got that
Yeah it would be yeah that's a nice little bit of
To add to that yeah
Australia
New Zealand tell Stefan molyneux to go f*** you like
Jordan today
I felt like it's been awhile since we checked in with present-day Alex Jones and honestly I was getting
Pretty happy
To have had that break from his uninspired ass broadcasting
I was actually kind of excited though to get back into the mud and see what his dumb ass was up to but
Wouldn't you know it
I checked back in
Owen Shroyer has been hosting Alex's show all this week
There's no new episodes of Alex's stuff to go over
As it turns out Alex is taken off for another work keishin
This this time heading up to Florida
To cover what he calls a mask Rebellion
That's taking place at a grocery store in the city of Naples
The store is called Oakes Farms seed to table and Alex may or may not be
Bee broadcasting mini Special Report
From live inside the store
Here is a little clip
Because the state is so freaking awesome
Florida is awesome
Florida
Everybody shopping
You nearby like
Talk to people
Southern Illinois at the American Legion where they're holding a math Drive
Play my cards right I might be able to
To go to a car dealership opening
Record live
Alright wow
BoBoiBoy
Situation with this grocery store is actually kind of funny
It's actually not in the city of Naples
Technically and if it were
It would not have a mask mandate
Because the Naples City Council decided against
Supposing one
Preferring instead to just make it a thing I strongly recommend
However this store is in North Naples
Which is about five miles north of city limits
Any subject of the jurist
Diction of the county
In this case Collier County
Who do have a mask mandate
In place
That sucks the store's owner Alfie Oakes
This has been waging a protracted campaign against masks
Something feels like this covid-19 stuff
Is a hoax
I poked around the story a bit and honestly it's kind of cool
Cookie cutter
Republican business owner making a mini celebrity of himself in the antemasque game and there's not much more to it
Everything is about what you
Should expect all the way down to him calling
George Floyd a quote
Graceville career criminal after he was killed
Black lives matter is a hoax
Alright that led to the least County School District severing their contract
Which prompted Oak
Looks to sue the school district
450 million dollars
Claiming is all bigots do that their free speech have been filed
Oh yeah
Of course I don't know what his contract with the school
When they're about being able to terminate the contract
Because I don't
The Free Speech issue
In fact I would assume that
Conservative
You should be in favor of the school district
Being able to practice free association
Guys with some of their opposed to being connected to
I don't particularly care about Alfie Oakes
Nor do I care too much about Alex's very transparent
Do vampiric leave
Feast on the attention Oaks is getting at the moment
If Alex is done like a whole show from the grocery store
Then you might be dealing with
An excited damn
As it stands this is just too little to get worked up about
It's really funny to imagine though going into a Whole Foods or a jewel and trying to get some produce and you hear a guy yelling about the UN
Trying to kill the children while you're shopping
Image of my head of Alex and Owen on supermarket
Sweet together
And that be great
Cry-Baby
Fill it up with emerge
Get the beans
Do you like that wood
Elevate my customer experience
Not so I set out to find an episode
To make for the good people out there to enjoy and as luck would have it
Wow it's been in Florida
He paid a visit to podcast in Miami called
Flagrant 2
I watch this thinking maybe it would be good to cover and it's just
Embarrassing basketball
No that's a flagrant ones
That is a real Park
Castle
The guys from Hollywood handbook called Art
I'm talking about this being like flagrantly
Free Speech offensive
Talking
Out of here
22in that
I watched it thinking maybe you'll be good like I said but I got nothing
Alex is so f***** up
But it's not even fun
The guy who's throwing hatchets on Christmas Eve at his own cameras
His own Studio
It's fun
The guy who's
Trying he's just trashed
Annoying robbed about the ways to learn a Cristo
Skull cover
Conceiving is fun
This is not fun it's sad
There was a moment in the interview that Alex did a while back with Logan
Paul where one of Logan
When's friends commented to Alex that he had a quote heavy poor
What are you getting another glass of booze
The tone wasn't like hey cool poor man
Concern in it like telling Alex to slow down
This interview has the opposite dry
Where the hoes are laughing their asses off
So just celebrating
How basically incoherent Alex's becoming
Alex Liza the host face about things like
Sandy Hook
Position on reparation
It was trading with these host to do absolutely no show prep
Before interviewing propaganda
At the end of the thing what are those does a list of quest
For Alex like
Was 9-11 a part-time job
Which if
Did you give you some
Consent to the value and comedic Merit of this show
The interview was so bad that I don't even think that it rises to the level of
Deserving criticism
I'm like the only thing that I heard in it that I thought was interesting was
Alex really drunk
Trying to explain why we need to cut off all for it
Ron Paul still is a drunken soul
There's also a very very
Just depressing
Stretch where Alex is really drunk and he tries to
Call Rogan a few times as a rogue
And Joe doesn't
Answer it's such a mess
Not worthwhile as an episode
Bro. Trying to figure out like what are we going to do and then I remember though that's right
There's another motherfuker I've been meaning to talk about very often
Hey motherfuker is named Harrison
Oh no we're doing white nationalist happy hour with Harrison Smith in the morning
Of the American Journal
Cowboy Harrison Smith he had caught my eye or a while back
Because of first of all his
Gleeful
The Patriots
Taking over the capitol at January 6th
I meant also just listening to some of his shows
Hoover chip man
Perdido Biggity
And so I decided I'm going to get back in see what he's been up to
I didn't think that this was a possibility for a while
Cuz he's been gone
He just had the paternity leave
Oh you just had a baby congratulations Harrison
And he's been gone to Rob do have been hosting and Tom pappert have been hosting
And boy
No good
But now Harris
Do white nationalists have
Have to scream like
Placement every time they have a kid
Probably like in the birthing room whenever the kid comes out there like it's breaching they have to be like take that great
Replacement there a very least they make little fun jokes
Alright here we go as you don't love me
Anymore okay
There's one particular reason that I decided actually look at this particular Epps
What is March 10th
I turned
F***** up so we're actually going to have to listen to another thing
But here is the beginning of March 10th
Still got some good
Bucking music
Good morning ladies gentlemen you're watching American Journal infowars.com banned. Video
What a
News I have for you today and at the end of this program and around
10:30
Central
Standard Time Alex Jones will be
Taking over the broadcast from his
Outpost in the state of Florida
Very excited to bring a lot of information to take your calls as well
And we do new sale at enforcer Taekwondo give you that information very shortly but her hair lighter
Let us begin as we always do with our Daily Dispatch roll the Stinger please
What
You got sound effect
Wow we're doing
Machine okay
All right so this is directed by Quentin Tarantino and there's a fax in the
That's all I know
Still love it I don't care
Is that intro music for like
The beginning of the shouts mellow as hell I think I pointed this out after our last time we talked about him
No no it's great but I was mad at the song that build and Kill Bill volume 2 or 60 as in Kill Bill
And that's why he knows what's up
Course
The thing I think is really interesting is like that like
Bbbbbbbb
Okay
Showing
The Berrics
Bones
Attempt
The Craft
And that's interesting cuz no one else really try to like read off headline
I don't really care it's a very boring second
The beginning of this episode he has a quite out pronounce
Today's program
Belaying out
What I think is a rather convincing argument for the fact that we are rapidly
Racing towards
A conflict
That I would call
World War 3
The lines are being drawn
Embarrassing
A lot of posturing
That
Portend
Great Devastation in our future
Has to do with China
Ron
And the
Western powers
Aligning themselves
Against
Those
Those bad countries where the good at
Also Harrison clearly hasn't gotten the memo
According to his buddies like Alex
The Cold War was World War 3 World War 4
So there's another one coming Harrison
Should be calling at World War 5
Nazi still seem to be the bad
In this case I think that him music
World War 3 sounds a lot more exciting
Really understand why Harrison would
Just go ahead and stick with that branding
Joanna not only does Alfie
The Oaks
Think that
Floyd
No was that
Criminal and blah blah blah
Meanwhile d
Election of
Trial rather of Georgia
Boyd
Continue
To move forward and not more Revelations are being made releasing
Of the
Autopsy report has revealed
Massive
Amounts of
Drugs in his system
And as they say no injuries
That would lead to death and other words
Jeffrey Epstein
May not have killed himself
Looks like George Floyd did
This is nonsense
There aren't Revelations coming out about the case of this point because the trial is
Still in the jury selection
Enphase
The coroner's report in autopsy information that the public has access to the exact same information we've had for likes
6 months
It doesn't show what Harrison
Sun is climbing
He's pretending there's a new piece of information
Verifies is pre-existing talk
It's because he knows that no one in the audience demands better
And they already believe the Gorge
Floyd's
There's no big deal
The Washington Post article about the upcoming trial on March 10th and here's what they had to say
When chauvin's trial for his alleged role in Floyd's tragic death
Up against much of the argument will Center instead on the autopsy
Details
Most specifically weather Fentanyl and underlying health condition
Not the police officers action
Stop Floyd heart
Dreadlocks
7 experts and toxicology Cardiology and illegal drug use
Consulted by The Washington Post largely disagreed with that idea
Most of them strenuously
All but one said the autopsy findings
Another court documents coupled with a well-known chain of events that evening
Made death by fentanyl overdose unlikely to mm
Impossible
And the other one was just
Is Rudy Giuliani wearing a
Experts on the matter are pretty
Pretty clear that what happened to Floyd doesn't resemble what happens in cases of opiate overdose
Which is why no one on the scene administered in a lock
Song with they did have it
They had the drug that would be
Be used in the case of an opiate
Say half the overwhelming consensus is that
Although there were drugs in his system drugs were not the cause of
George Floyd's
As the wapo article points out this defense
Police
Abused all the time
When they kill p
Abused
The time
The King was on PCP
And that made him such a threat that it Justified
The police's actions
Is there something that they do in business
Harrison Smith essentially just
You know taking two
Defense arguments
Uncritically
And then also
Toeing the line
For just sort of like exactly what cop
Say all the time
This is
It's weird how pee
People are trying to litigate this like the NFL tries to litigate what
Patches
Football movies
Forget all the way and you have to take one step
You have to make a football move whatever the f***
No no no no George Floyd is dead because of Derek Chauvin and
His buddies
Vnd
There's no there's no
You can talk about how much
You know it's like
Diddy murder him a premeditated again or you can do all that stuff but now he was dead
Because of those guys
And it 88 appears that even if there were
Some sort of a like
If they're like this argument that is being made by Harrison or even
True
Then you still have negligent homicide
On the part of these cops who
Have that would have had a responsibility to address the medical condition
There was
Supposed to keep people alive now what's their job.
Protecting and serving I don't understand those words at all when applied
The cops
So
This show starts out a little bit slow I know Harrison has declared that World War 3 is upon us
And
I got to be honest I didn't make it to him
Explaining that if he did
Cuz I got I got sidetracked
The slow news day
Yeah
This is this is just like there's like
Scattershot headlines until he goes
The calls
Here's another one of these these little
Petty complaints
She has this one's about Biden
Not giving a press conference
You can only imagine if
President Trump had dared
To go 50 days without
Taking questions from the Press
Cancellation to be having a bean impeaching him all ready for this
In February 2020 it was reported that it has been over 300 days until Trump at a formal press briefing so here's something go ahead and
Shut that stupid tone of his up his own ass
To make matters worse ABC News reported in September 2019 that not only had drop not done these Prescott
Conferences quotes
Months that the White House Press Secretary last game 2
The podium in a briefing room to
Field questions
From report
Yeah and if Biden have done that
Wait what
I do think if I should face criticism
For not having press
Is enough or yet since I think it would
No it's a helpful piece
Severe moving forward
The same criticism of trump when
And he was doing the same thing
Because I think
Transparency in availability
To the public
Is it good thing to encourage in our leadership
Harrison Infowars don't really have any underlying belief
They just attack their predetermined enemies and glorify whoever they like at the moment regardless if they're doing
The same thing
Don't pretend that their hero didn't
Can actually do what the villain is now doing
But worse
Not long ago because if they did acknowledge that
They have to explain why it wasn't a big deal for that went drop did the same thing with her so upset Biden
And that would unravel the game
It would really make thing
Things difficult if you had to
Sort of like a
Position
But your whole that would really fuk up
Petoskey
You know what
Maybe
There's something to this not having press conference okay
Perhaps again we can take another lesson from this witches
So maybe what Trump should have done
Maybe that just
Cut off the press and you just do whatever the hell you want without taking questions without
Accepting criticism
Harrison you're in lock
I've got great news
You can get rid of the Maybe
Get rid of the water
This is so dumb you are talkin about a thing a man has done recently
If I
Recall
Huger Network celebrated extensively yeah
I'm sorry way Trump is out of office but there's someone else who's in office
Infowars
Is warming up to quite a bit
And I person
Is Marjorie Taylor Greene
And without it like to go to another video here
It's
Marjorie Taylor Greene
Talkin
On the floor of the Congress
Yesterday
Turned out house resolution 8 and house resolution 1446
Gun control red
Legislation
So it's really cool to see them warming up to Marjorie Taylor Greene
I definitely wouldn't have suspected that was the inevitable destination of the passive
Begins with hero worshipping Ron Paul
Anyway
Hr8 is about expanding background checks
Checks are people first
Saint-gaudens the other Builder talking about is meant to close what's known as the
Charleston Loop
Named after the 2015 shooting because it was how dylann roof
Was able to purchase the guns that are used
Skill 9 people
At the Emanuel African Methodist
Episcopal Church
He shouldn't have been able to pass over our gun
Soundcheck what he did because of this Loop
See when you go by to go to buy a gun
Name is run through the national instant criminal background check
Which should provide a yes or no result within minutes
However in some cases the automated system runs into complications
Can't make a determination
He needs case
The FBI who runs
System have 3 days
Provide a yes or no to the gun seller
And if they fail to give a determination in that time
The seller gets
To decide if they sell the guns or not
You better believe they almost always do cuz they're selling gun
Yeah I do appreciate that
Guns operate under the same laws as
Pumpkins
Turn into carriages
This bill that Harrison
Complaining about wood
Change that window from
3 days 2
The 10 days to provide more oversight
Top things like future Dylan roofs having easy access
Consider this stat from a report put out by the center for America
In progress
Quote
It 2018 4240 background checks were denied Nationwide after the three-day investigation
. elapsed
In at least
See those cases
A gun was sold to the prohibited buyer at the
The discretion of the dealer requiring offers officer
From the Bureau of Alcohol Tobacco and Firearms
Supposed to attempt to retrieve these guns
From individuals
With a potentially dangerous criminal
This loophole result in tons of people who shouldn't be allowed to have guns getting done
Poses
Threat and also creates a ton of work and expense or the ATF
To try and correct
The mistakes
Call
Clearly Too Short window of time being given for these background check system
To provide an answer
I'm really confused as to what
Situations
Require a
Guns
That we cannot wait
For the FBI to give a determinate
I mean make him someone to 10 days or if year
It's someone's barging into your house you need a gun immediately perhaps
The background-check delay isn't going to help you one way or another whether they like it or not
No
Yeah even if you've missed out on hunting season this year
Feel like that's your fault
You should have
Gone two weeks earlier earlier not a problem
Yeah I I don't know
I think both of these bills are completely sensible
Wait to see Harrison try to attack them by not discussing the bills in detail at all and relying on a video of a qanon weirdo
To make his ark
It's just pathetic all you need to do
Outrageously dumb
I got a recording I made of Marjorie Taylor
Green's remarks on the house
House floor
So
Harrison
But there's not enough
And I would suspect that this is because Rob do f***** up
I need this phone line full with got empty spaces here I'm not used to seeing this
I was hosting American journal for
Little over a month
Wolf online 2 whole time I go away for 2 weeks take care of a new baby boy
Come back nobody's calling in this is unacceptable folks
I need your help I can't do this show by myself I need the info Warriors calling in
I suspect
What we're going to learn about some of these callers
I have a very strong theory about why calls might have dropped out whenever Harrison laugh
It was on vacation
Cuz Rob do was like no Nazi
Please please yeah yeah that was that was that sound
That sound
Excuse me could you please get rid of everybody who says
Code words for Jew
I just think he's weird I think this is a weird dude
And that we will go to our first call we have Andy in California
About the upcoming Passover thing calling in and eat your on the air
This year
I knows that that Easter is Passover on
No it's not
Yeah
We look at the
Deuteronomy
Play Chapter 38
I talked about the
And the second after chapter is
Call Dad
That'll happen
Like a real shity God to me
Sedation
Jody got it
My face like well maybe this
Look at everything you guys talk about
Cursive
It's not
Satanic organizations but not better doing it
Definitely allows
So I guess you want to learn something
Easter and Passover are both religious
Observances that don't involve specific dates on our
Christmas Princeton like that's always observed on December twenty
That's because it's tied to our Khalid
Easter and Passover however are both observe base
Which results in the holidays lining up with different dates
Every year
According to our Gregorian
Easter is always the first Sunday after the first
Full moon
Unless you're following the Eastern Orthodox tradition
Because this issue that's too complicated to get into because Harrison in
Touching on that aspect
The thing I want to get into it now we'll do it later I've had a lot to I've been quarreling with the Eastern Orthodox
Facts about this for a long time to leave you to that
Passover is based on the Hebrew calendar which
Tintern is lunar base
Send begins in the middle of the Hebrew month
Nissan in last
Typically because of how these days are
End up being very close to each other and very often
Easter does fall within the week of Paso
This year Easter is on the last day of Passover April 4th
Which I guess the
This color thinks mean something nefarious I don't know
It's very interesting according to Harris
Is blood moons all over 100% blood moon
The more important aspect of this collar I think is how much he's internalized the underlying message of a lot of Alex's rhetoric
There are demons up
Sure but the curse
That are plaguing everyone are the results of God letting the stuff happen
Because you aren't
Good enough for him to
Protect
This is the messaging of cult
And it's very present in Alex's contact with his regular Outburst about how the world deserve to
Bird
For things like allowing abortion
Yeah
Ridiculous
Yep if you're if all of us don't act in
50 cordwell all of us will be
Who killed his protection and then you go here come
Cups and it's your fault operates under the same laws as like a teacher and if your stew
Student who didn't bring enough gum for the class well everybody
Emmanuel
Sent the hell everybody knows
Conceivably it's your fault
As an individual because you didn't
What is bringing gum
Glass metaphor for in this case
Basically
Setting up a religiously ordered Society
Overthrown the teacher brutally deposed her and murdered her
And then God would have showered you with all the gum in the world and it's a little bit worrying when you start to think about
The ramifications of it
Internalizing
The blame for God's Wrath
So Harrison starts talking about how the Pope
You know that Global spoke
You going to jail for well over a year
Yeah
According to experts
What about that that I've seen going around
Respectful
Steve pieczenik arrested the pope like a year ago
Augusta fake Pope
Somebody pretending to be the pope recently
I guess an interview had said that your climate change
He's possibly going to
To cause another flood
Comments are what they are and whatever
Took that very simply and calmly as him saying that there would be a regular flood
The pope is calling God a liar
That because of climate change
We Face threats
Avenue
Flood
From God
Now
I don't know what maybe I was just a child maybe I
Misunderstood
But wasn't one of the key aspects of the flood
That God promised never
To do it again
Wasn't that a promise God made
And is the pope calling God a liar
Got a liar
Now we'll get into this here in a second but
I think is really interesting as the Harrison starts
Speaking about the flood
Start thinking about the
The flood story
Are you getting mad about no no no
The original reason that God flooded the Earth was
Sexual immorality
What does the pope have to say about that I'm pretty sure he has to say about that is don't worry about it
It's fine
Come on free Love Boat
This is interesting to me because
The flood in the Bible happen
It's pretty early
Pretty fast in Genesis chapter
So I decided I would go back and refresh my memory about the lead-up to
The flood
And see if it happened because
People weren't f****** the way that God wants us to
So Genesis one is the creation of the world and then Chapter 20 The Making of Adam and Eve
Genesis 30 the fall of Adam and Eve had eaten from the Tree of knowledge
Retaliation got made
Snakes all slithery
That one was guest written by
C.s. Lewis created
Painful childbirth male-dominated relations
Egypt structures
And I also turned gotten to Adam into a farmer
Really important
Get the male-dominated social Starboy
Right away
Rick from the first chapter been rule everything I'm moving on
It's going to hurt when you whisper
Very weird
Prices for deals of Cain killing Abel and then there's a bunch of
The names of the family tree
Genesis 5 is a bunch more names and how long they
They lived Bridging the Gap from Adam
In Genesis 6
It's God gets a little bit tired of people who decides they should be living so long
In addition to that he sees that quote sons of God where Marianne Koch Daughters of human
Which I guess is supposed to mean that Angels were breeding with human
Strange that there aren't any lady angels
But I'll get off my sjw story about Dan come on now
Kirin here's Genesis 6
It's verses 5 through 7
Quote
The Lord saw how great the wickedness of the human race would be
Become on Earth
And that every inclination of the thoughts
Of the human heart was only Evil all the
The Lord regretted that he had made human beings on the Earth
His heart was deeply troubled
So the Lord said I will wipe from the face of the Earth the human race I've created
And with them the animals and the birds
The creatures that move along the ground for I regret
That I have made them
Wait hold on God real
Bisquick question God
Adjust we're in the planning stages I can see that you're reacting emotionally
And frankly I think it's a little bit offensive of you to say that they're acting evil all of the time
I mean come on
Also what did the birds do
Burger King now
Well I mean look
If you wanted to turn the birds that's your business standing beef
I'm not going to go to bed for that but I am going to say that I was reading over this and it struck me how weird this is that like
You know it's a big decision
And to create a race
Human system
It's very weird that God wouldn't see it coming that he would regret doing that
Open strings to fit into the
Conception of a God is over gret over the creation of humor
Wolfman
Those guys were s***
Whoops to Doodle very weird
And by the way even if like
God was justified in being disappointed by humans
Is extermination a rational solution to that problem
After all it was God
That created human
And so wiping them out is really just him trying to cover up his own mistakes
No no
That brings us to Noah
Godlike Noah because he was on like the rest of the people
From Genesis 6
Now the Earth was corrupt in God's item was full of violence
Gotsoccer up the Earth head
Become for all the people on Earth that corrupted their ways
So God said to Noah I'm going to put an end to all people for the Earth is filled with
Violence because of them
Why isn't 3 versus the
The complaint of violence has raised in relation to gods
Kill everyone off with a
Weirdly
Sexual impropriety isn't brought up at all it is odd that God would care more about
Violence than sexual impropriety Betsy
I'm so weird
After Noah built the ark and saves all the animals
Before I do, they have to live on that boat
That's comically oversized for about a year
No is 600 years old
When the flood end
Noah gets off the boat makes
An altar to God which pleases God
Appreciation God says quote never again will I curse
The ground because
Humans even though every inclination of the human heart
Is evil from childhood
I never again will I do
Destroy all living creatures as I have done
This story is f***** up
But the promise that God makes at the end of it doesn't preclude God from cause
Avocado flooding
That we would see arise
Climate change
People aren't suggest
We're going to end up in Waterworld or something
I'm s*** just that there a lot of places that will become uninhabitable
This will lead to master
Displacement likely a lot of death
That's completely compatible with God's promise
To never again.
Play all living creatures
Harrison Smith is a dumb f*** religious zealot he's trying to repurpose religious stories to suit his extremist agenda
In this case is opposition
The lgbtq rights
And access to reproductive health
It's a pathetic display it honestly it's important to recognize that this
Is not a new show
They aren't even really Conspiracy Theory shows at this point nope
Their extremist religious programming gets masquerading as something
Open political Orbach
Conspiracy in order to make it more interesting and attractive to an audience
That would reject them instantly
If they were aware that the mess
Message they were being delivered
And was being pushed
To that was religious
It's a nature
Please get these guys on this like this
Podcast for they're all drunk
If they realize what was behind Alex's
Rhetoric and like with messaging
And how it was really large leaf
I don't think they would think this was as funny
I know we had a lot of fun but
Just to remind you the Earth is only 10,000 years old into
Your sinfulness is going to get you sent to Hell forever
Anyways
Aborted baby
I know I'm
I'm three-quarters of the way through this bottle of Jameson
But I should tell you
Kamiakin
Conception of Angels and Demons
How serious it is I can see the
You know when you read the the biblical flood myth
You really start to think
Was this written by a dude
Cuz I think
Pillsbury dude written
Weird to go back and
And read it after a long time and it's been it's been quite a while
Like the story directly from the source
I don't know baby
I don't know what it is
About my brain but I
I can pick out little things that I missed
But I was younger like that's a weird detail
Isn't it isn't it really kind of strange when you when you sit down in like grapple with
Reality and end like where we are is a society now
And you look back in your like
So are you telling me that I was
When I was a child
That God just a rash
Definitely murdered everything and I'm like
And that's the guy I need to worship until I die
Is that part of the story is really underplayer really not important
I do think
They're still like some metaphorical value in terms of
You know I don't know
Steadfastness
Faithfulness
Or just an educational Value Inn
Learning about how people explain disasters
Throughout illogical
I agree I agree
I think it'll be interesting
Back in my Bible study groups or Sunday School
Disgusting
Ramifications of
Extermination
And there are so many better flood myth
To the only
Is there actual flood everybody's got a flood myth around
The time the explanation I remember is like they're all bad
100 100
The jump in the Bible it's like well listen
Killing everything that evil is on the
Yeah
Harrison believes
On some level that the motivation
Behind
The flood
Read on God's part
It was something
The effect
Of
Something related to lgbtq
Thank you
Are you might be
Inflating the story of Sodom and Gomorrah
Of course and I think the reason that he's doing that is
Cuz he doesn't actually remember the flood myth
Maybe not but he does remember that the rainbow is a sign of God's covenant everybody
Course you look at that
That you know the Indian Christian mythology I guess you could call it the rainbow
Was the sign from God
As a promise that he would never
Flood the Earth again so just think about this that you have
God flooding the Earth because of sexual
Immorality
And then you have
The symbol of this
The symbol of his promise to never do it again has been co-opted by
Alternative sexual lifestyles
Satanic
To its very core
I have to say
What that is as interesting as
Is Easter and Passover happening on the same day
Is he trying to say if it's people turned over the rainbow
But that's what he said
But beyond that I think what he's saying is that
People who have quote-unquote
Alternative lifestyles are immoral
You saying that he's not immoral to be
Lesbian okay
Yeah
That's cool I mean I guess
On that position then there isn't because
You are saying yeah
That's f***** up just come out and say that you think everybody was not straight should be put to the sword like you're God.
I think Harrison might be only a little ways away from that
So we get another color here and this color blue like
I'm still reeling
From that okay
This is a minute-long
Listen to the mic down for this
Easy
Use okay I'm with and without we go now to Carlos
In Texas thanks so much for calling in Carlos you are on the air sir
Yeah what's up Harrison I want to congratulate you and your newborn child
Thank you
Yeah no problem and you're going to raise the great info Warrior I've been listening since David night
And ever since you came out in the show
You've been a great addition but it should have been had you on
Thank you I appreciate that
I want to give a huge shout-out you shut up
Extra Strength formula
Here I am saying
Anna Drive parking lot University with a 5G
Tower being right at me
And I'm ready to go for the day dude
Last night and had
Agrate
A great Glee
And I'm ready to go for the day
And I don't need that system or this morning and we're chilling
And where are you going to start the day
And that's it that's all I had
Oh that's awesome man
Identify
Thank you very much that the doctor Jones is natural extra strength
Kava chill
And a beautiful plug from Carlos from Texas
The whole call
The only reason he called in at all
What the f*** is product
Subway
So you're the one guy is just like man
My friends and I
It took this
And we were like
I got a good sleep last night could call guy got a good sleep last night and then I took some more and I'm chilling
Campus is a 5G Tower
It's not getting in my way
Not a problem
Call Harrison I am chill
I'm so chill I'm going to give Harrison a
Call let him know I love David night but listen
The white nationalist happy hours so better Harrison castanou
Chill I got to call Infowars
That's
Nuts
That is not
That is not that it doesn't sound like a plan
Did something like that guy was just a little bit High
It is a little bit High
I think I could have guessed
Felt like he was bagela
Yeah but he ended
The call felt like maybe there's something else he's like after
Could you call in to the show and just because
I guess I guess to let everybody know that it gets you high
What a waste of time
Anyway
Read this next caller and actually just call her
Starts
By talking about
Man this stuff
Did it
The next caller Jordan
I had got into this episode and I started listen
Because I thought
That this was the episode
Where Harrison interview Stewart Road
OSHA
To hear that
Listcawler started up
He says I want to talk about
Stewart roses interview
So is Akashi I got the wrong day
However
This caller is then proceeded to really freak me out
Let's go now to Scott in Florida who has a common
About our guest from yesterday super Rhodes leader of the oathkeeper he was on
For an hour or so breaking his
Media silence
To talk about some of the Fallout from January 6th
And a color Scott from Florida has some comments about this
Thanks for calling and Scott did you enjoy the
Interview or do you have some concerns about it what's your what's your
Congratulations on your child
Awesome response
Fidelity
Leader of the old key
Keepers I pray for him and his family
Evil government incarcerated
You do you shut up you shut up
Catalyst you can do a show I don't know
Will you catch up
Three percenters
My favorite group
The John Birch Society
Take over communism
Society Sovereign citizens
Westboro Baptist Church
Whoa
Okay so this list
Spiral yeah yeah yeah we're on the edge of being like an also letsgetlexi
Is Lutheran the guys from Captain Planet
Sinister Six
All evil everywhere I did the ideas like what have around people powwow with
Stewart Rhodes maybe someone from the Cowboys seems like okay this is
Your show is at now
Yeah that makes sense
Why Sovereign citizen
What are we doing
This is very rich when he said Westboro Baptist Church
Like my like
What's going on here is this caller
The beginning of the trouble with that
Oh boy
Put forth
The theory
Who is deposition
The January
6 was
The beginning of the second American Revolution
And I hate to Mike down you twice since you're going to scream
January 6th 2021 is going to go in American history
It's a second amount
As American Revolution
It's going to be the chemical up at the beginning of it
American people are being pursued
When you come
Bi
Targets are threatened
Because they don't like them
Canyons
They don't like your thought process
Sprouts of a dinosaur
Specifically
About our government
It's controlled by a pack of
Is the Rothschild Bank
Just sent you the moment
With the Rothschild
Surprised we talk
Capitals Wild Water
International jewelry is a
Is involved
What would stop get stopped
I'm not talking about
Albuquerque
International
Oh boy
Is off the rail
Wow
I feel like
Okay I feel like
When Rob Deuce I was thinking
He knows to hang up on people who says Zionist occupied government
Let me be clear on what that means
I believe the moment you talk about is our blood what that means
Brandon is supposed to be that we're against that kind of stuff
In order to support that kind of stuff we have to be pretend to be a Deadpool
Subway
International jewelry my friend
I have never heard that in a
Positive way
Whoever has ever heard you celebrate the international
Ford
To put out
This is not say nothing
And I would argue buddy
Just I mean and look
I'm going to go out on a limb here
And I'm going to say that he's very mad at the FBI for choosing
Take me to Prost
Go after people
Who don't share his opinion
Now
Feeling that he was a big fan of jid
Edgar Hoover's that's
You know
Maybe he's probably a fan of the FBI murdering people who would say things like black lives matter
The tide was so
Count minutes
I need the
We're trying to root out communist sympathizers everywhere
Willing to bet there'll be a slightly different tone
Bitdefender
Is that this dude
Is
F****** over
He doesn't give a s***
He is
He's putting it all out there
Regular everyday everyday
Because he's so comfortable
Floating all this
Stuff
He kind of
Makes clear something that we already know
I know
I know exactly what he
Globalist
I think of the Rothschilds
I always think of the product
Pushing forward
New World Order
Call the Jew World Order
He laughed at that
Harrah's Harrison laughed at this guy saying the Jew World Order
Is straight-up
This is a region that's a real nothing how is this happening on air that is
Nazi broadcast
The game a little bit whenever I hear Alex a globalist I know what he's talking about
I have a weird reaction to that because
Chris Martin that made me feel like
Well good for you buddy
You understand what
He saying
That's it's nice that he at least can read
Between the lines I don't know if many people can
Can do that I think it's bad but he can
And does and believe
Is that it okay
Experience that I had was
Like taking no duh
But like I'm so
I'm so dull or numb
Go to the fact that like that is
The code that
The characterization that Alex uses the globalist relies so much on these archaic forms
Hades meditrope
I get that I know that
Intuit
Surprise me
Shocking to hear somebody just be like come on let's talk honestly no it is weird yeah it's really weird
It's strange because it does indicate that I mean this guy isn't the only person in the audio
Who has a
Cognizant
Sort of
Self-awareness
But that's what he thinks Alex is talking about
Everything
Why do you think we use the code word
So we don't sound like this don't sound like this
Damn it dude
This guy
Materials that he might want to promote
Talk to the audience
If you pass dispensary
And want some
What's going on
Please call
Protocol
Cherry Tree Inn in any venue before Scott 90 you've also mentioned it
If you times
Identity politics
Text2meme
Sure I don't care I really don't care I'll make any of the things you know better
Don't care
Yeah I was also taken
Know each other kind of
Real
Call Juice
Duh
Promote the protocols home
TV show
You made this point before hang up on this guy
She's Jesus
Christ anyway I Harrison
Not
One to shy away
How is it that people are bitching about banning books at
The protocols still isn't man
Yeah.
Sparbar
Like
Push back
Too much
On this guy
Okay but yeah let me just say you know it's ensuring that you
You bring it up with
Exactly 10 things
I was going to mention yesterday that I didn't get to us to a roads is the fact that
The organization's who are actually advising
The FBI on what to do I mean you don't Central you have the FBI and you would think that they would be answerable only
To politicians that would be taking
Directives from civilian oversight
But in reality what you see and there's stories going back all the way to 2017
Is that organizations like the ADL in the splc that are actually directing
The FBI
Call Maryellen
Jewish organizations
They're calling themselves that right so you have an organization that is
You know of a certain ideology is not
Claiming to know before everybody's Anti-Defamation League it's a Jewish organization
And yet they're the ones who are directing
The FBI now
Is it there is a weird sort of disconnecting the American psyche
Where it's like
How do we not see the dad weird and wrong that is a private organization
That I consider a hate group that has articles about me calling me an anti-semite calling me a homophobe
Calling me racist let me all sorts of horrible things
They're completely untrue and totally baseless
Yeah that's that's a little top Bachelorette on
Previous
How would they have known any of these things they claim if they had not list
Listen to me speak for the previous 10 minutes
Wowzers
Wow
Insinuating
International jewelry is a cabal that
It's trying to push the Jew World Order
The protocols of the Elders of Zion
And then
If you then respond with
Hey you know the splc
Cnat our Jewish organizations and they were on our FBI
And there is a hate group
It runs our
Hey buddy you are signing off on with this
Disagreeing with him this isn't a debate this isn't
An airing of
Alternative ideas that you have you guys are just
Both
Yeah
Out there
It is it is interesting the difference in react
Between cuz I feel like now that they're all just letting it out
Just like Hey we're Nazis
How you guys doing well let's have a conversation about Nazi
I like
I can feel my
I guard being lowered a little bit
Because I'm not like
I'm not like
What is this supposed to mean
You know what in what way are they trying to hide and what were they trying to lie
Yeah however I have
Let my guard down there and put it up to fight
Cuz I would like to fight
I want
Like a moment you're just like a wheel of be enough
Then you're fair game
You know like it
Brutal
SMS
Henderson does have one robot
That I would say
He gives and it's just to protect the business
It's just
Protect the game
He has to disagree
Globalist
Means
International Jewish person in the FBI's
Bring that to the conversation
Until I do disagree with you there where it's like
It's not
It's a certain thing it's an
Very particular thing
That
You can subscribe to whatever religion you are and you doesn't mean you subscribe to it if you're Jewish
I do disagree with you
Certain points
That's not even what that guy was saying responding to a false point in order to try and protect the
The Infowars
Usevs
Globalization
Dog whistle
Listen to the rest of us
I don't listen to this show much
And then I dip in and there's
This
Like I
I think you are going to be a lot of my diet in the future
Just
Straight up not
So
I got through that call and listen to a little bit more and I just started to get bored I was like
I am so overwhelmed
By that call
How over an offense if it was
Nothing
Is going to be worse than
I can't imagine it'll be worth
The interview that I was looking for was on the other day
Yeah so I turned this episode off and run over
You didn't wait to see if somebody called in and said the Holocaust didn't happen that Jews are also responsible for all the problem
Homes in the world
I don't think it was a call that might been a guest I could've been Harris
So I went to be the interview with Stewart Roads cuz there's some news about him
Recently
Related to the six
Right right right
Super cool dude
Very cool
I never wanted any violence at all wanted to check
On his response to it
And I thought it was interesting that it's on
The American Journal
But that's good
The grocery
Yeah store
So here we find the introduction to Stewart's interview and
Bad ideas this is also
Again you have to regret jingly admire the ability of mainstream media
In the corrupt establishment
Their ability to
Manipulate the minds of the American people
Especially when it comes to an event like January 6th
It was a force as more information coming out
We know
Inside Job
Same way that 9/11 was an inside job 16
Was an inside job
Flashback to the Capitol
Don't even want to listen to our coverage of January 6th
Was very different
Do Patriots have taken the capital
This is him doing the I don't know why the splc thinks were race
It's a little bit it's
Take with a straight face
Like I don't really believe
Any sincerity here
Not all f*** Harris
So he gets
Talking about they said the marked are the generous
Six protest Amy Says something that is categorically not true
What was occurring there was the largest
A protest
I believe in American history
The most number of people
Ever together in a single place for a
Political
Nuvent probably upwards of
A million if I had to guess
That's not true
I believe is doing a
Heavy lifting job Annabelle
Quite a few believe that that was the big
Store comes in
Has to say
About
But all these people were talking about your noise
But how was it interact
They're going for your head man I mean what is it been like for you
Well it is
It's been like
Orwell's 1984
Thoughtcrime
Space crime
And all the things that we've seen in the past
Not being done
Not just me but anybody else who
As you were saying earlier there were no weapons
No one brought
John's
Insurrection is that
Frankly it's an insult
Football
Planned insurrection
Doster road is coming on the show to try to get out in front of some pretty damning information that
Just been released
Related
To the US's case against Thomas Caldwell
I know keeper who was arrested related to the storm
Capital
Caldwell it made a motion to reconsider his detention and this document that was filed in the evening of March 8th was a
Response to that motion
There's nothing that's in here
The first thing that's important to remember is that the charge this guy is facing his conspiracy to quotes stop delay and Hinder
Congress is certification of the Electoral College vote
That's Keith
Because the conspiracy wasn't to storm the building
The storming of the building was quote
An overt act in furtherance of the
Conspiracy
Regardless of when they formed the intent
The prosecution isn't claimed anyone can
Inspired to storm the capitol Jeff
Conspire to make it so Congress couldn't
Carry out its work
This should scare the s*** out of someone like Stewart Road
Yeah cuz
He did that
The reason I could scare him is that this filing also reveals
That the government is in possession of logs
From a signal chat
Entitled
DC Auto
January 6th
Which was previously undisclosed
Caldwell himself is not
Been proven to have internet
Snapchat but Jessica Watkins as well as another
I understand person who were both Keepers were arrested
West Caldwell
Worried
Password multiple quote Regional
Keeper L from multiple States across the country
And Stewart Road
Who would have
The people who believe that the government
What is surveilling them at all times
I'm trying to constantly and plant them with
To track them
Would have
Absolutely no idea that the government
Actually read these f****** conversation
These chat logs
Clearly show that Stewart Road was in
Contact with multiple people associated with you
Goalkeeper who stormed the capitol
It also establishes fairly well that they were all involved in a plan to mess with the certification of Electoral College votes
Based on the publicly available evidence
Looks like Stuart could get rolled up in this
Conspiracy charge should the government want to pursue that
The full extent of the cats aren't disclosed
Elizabeth Stewart did tell the group quote
We have several well-equipped
Quick reaction
Enforces out
Outside DC
There are many many others for
From other groups will be watching and waiting on the outside in case of worst-case scenarios
Famous people that have weapons
Because they had a plan
Involved heavily armed backup
Yeah they didn't have
He's in the Capitol because we were keeping them outside of the Cavalier use on people who try to escape the capital dummies
January 3rd Thomas Caldwell send a message to three percenter group asking quote
How many people either in the militia or not who are still supportive of our efforts
To save the Republic
Have a boat on a trailer that could handle the Potomac
Bookcrossing
If we had someone standing by at a dock ramp we could have our quick
Response team with a heavy weapon
I'm standing by
Quickly load them and Ferry them across the river to our waiting arms
Event set maps to people alleged to have been part of his
Wow that does
I wonder and we clear
I'm just spitballing here I'm not being sarcastic or facetious at all
I'm just curious I wonder if this dude got the idea to use the Potomac from list
Sling to Alex's show
December 3rd
First episode of Alex's show just
Days before Caldwell tried to get this boat plan
Together
Alex
The color on the show suggest
Did this
Just wanted to touch bases with you with the
March on DC or the occupation of
DC
I think that you
I'm going to talk to all
The Cajun Navy and all these people that did boat parade
For the past
324 mud
We need to have every single one of those people
Plug up
The Potomac
Because you know that
Like and I can sit out
Facebook post
Yeah well I'm sure they can especially like
The Cajun Navy when the hurricanes come in they have to go in there
And I'll get people out
I agree we need to see the Cajun Navy come in and then get on the grounds that I totally agree
I'm looking at it if they tie up those boating that they try to shut down those bridges and that's a free
You can get in
At the public area
Cayucos ghost they tried to shut down those bridges just imagine the info or Army
Let me tell you what this is about it's about global governments about lockdowns about control that's what the whole
Covid hoax about
Exchange of the subs
They're a little bit
It's not quite the
The same thing
This caller is talking about clogging the river with a boat
The fairy wepa
But there are some similarities
What's being suggest
Clearly this caller doesn't mean that the entire River should be clogged up but that these boats
To tie together in Block the area off
To Infowars types
Cross the river in the event that the bridges were
L p Mattox
Similarities to what Caldwell was trying to achieve
Probably not connected in any way I just thought it was really interesting really good and went to staff
Before
Maybe this is just kind of how
These folks mind
To work your parallel thinking in terms of like
Well alright we could use the river
Yeah if you don't seem like these are plans that they like
Cobbled together from half-remembered war movies from
The song something like I remember from Bridge on the River Kwai
Anyway the point here is that store road is going to have a really
Interesting year
And it also makes a whole lot more sense why he's trying to promote Jessica Watkins legal defense fund after the 6th
Yeah that doesn't
Scentsy app
So
He has a bit of a lie
Right here about
The signal messages
The only thing I've got is a message
Army person on our operational chat
Arm signal saying
Anybody
Donna
PSG
Come to the north
East corner of a capitalist route standing
Rendezvous there
What's the make sure
Guys stayed out of trouble
This is a lie
On 1138 on January 6th
Stewart posted in that chat
Quote all I see Trump doing is
Complaining
I see no intent by him to do anything
So the Patriots are taking it into their own hands they've had enough
Later Stewart send a message to the to regroup on the south side of the capital not the Northeast side is he saying you're on the show
Stewart posted a photo of the southeast side of the capitol
Caption quotes
Southside if u.s. Capital Patriots pounding on Doors
By that point multiple people in the chat
Had entered the US Capitol
See how this shakes out and everything but stewardess
Is totally full of s***
That's outrageous
Stats bot
Yep
It's interesting because Stuart has a little bit of a new kind of Defense
Here
Listen to this
Alright
Give you some
Think about why you listen
Okay
Assume he's telling the
I will do my best
Ask yourself
If he's telling the truth
This okay okay
We had a situation
Pembroke North Carolina
Sadly
North Carolina
Acquired
Clear Choice
In d.c.
Call January
Not going to have any national
Or take part
I'm a post Valentine
Remember
Screenshot
So there's that
Right so Carolina
Okay
So
Look guys
What so I built this organization ride to entirely around right-wing violence
Sand and and
A super-strong distrust
Centralization and then strangely enough one chapter went rogue and decided
I had no control over that essentially declared State that's cool
Cool I've created these heavily armed
Mini Army and cooperate with me
Accidentally created Warlords by bad guys my bad I created roving bands of Warlord
Really a huge mistake on my part
Exactly wondering why people don't like what you do
Oh okay so you guys were talked about the warlord problem now I see what you were talking about
Create these
Loosely connected
Proof of RVs what effect might go Rogue
Crazy lionizing a leaderless resistance
It seems that they don't want to follow my
My leadership for summer
Is true and like let's say that the North Carolina crew was responsible
I still think Stewart you get sued
Yeah I think you still create the whole shebang
Say like whoops by group went rogue it happen
Sam
Rugs
Accountability there
In this next clip Stewart misrepresents
With the government's
Keep in mind that the charge that this will keep replacing is
Related to
Conspiracy to obstruct
Interfere with
The electoral vote
They're trying to say that
We
The election was stolen
Anyone election was stolen
Encourage people to go to d.c.
And then like
We did courage Trump
The Insurrection Act
We said itchy does we're going to serve
As the militia
Which is a
An illegal act
Fresno
Beautiful dancer
He calls us up
Federal law as the militia
Call Cindy service
Is every right
Before you do so
No they're not
No
That's not at all what they're they're doing already
Yeah yeah yeah yeah
No it's
Everybody
Could say come to DC
Anybody can say come be a part of this protest
Can't
Conspire to interfere with Congress as business
What you actually can
Yeah as long as you don't do any
Right you can
8 /
Sports
Furtherance of the conspiracy
See here's what my defense would be my defense would be
It was a non violent
Island protest now the problem with that.
Is that it
Wasn't right
So that kind of changes your
Yeah you know like it if nothing had happened and they were loving this charge to stop the
Nothing happened
We didn't do anything we didn't go anywhere
The capital has had a protest outside
Nobody said you know why you know why because Congress is ability to carry out the wouldn't
No no it wouldn't be the cry
Taken to further the conspiracy that
Conspiracy wooden
Be
Mistaking criminalizing the first
Where you're like a
We don't like this thing
Let's all get together and be like
Whenever our problem
Was the second part when they were like
Let's go kill people
That was that was my problem
I don't like the combination of it
But it's the second part that
The legal problems
Come back to bite
Turns out
Did because of what's happening and
Prosecution of these people for
Storming the capitol
We are now living in
Prostitution America
Right
Play take this mix.
We're
Clear American
You are
Not one
Justice bands
Of this so-called
Just called in.
Department
Ghetto
I don't know if this is one of those things
F****** dramatic
Yeah this is again
The drama nonsense of these people
Constitution America
Spell
So we can take those real quick I got bad news
I got the quarter some soldiers were living it up
Even more silly playing coward
The thing that makes even more silly is that Harrison agrees with him
I bet they were living
Going to post Constitution America
And then he plays a clip
Of Marjorie Taylor Greene
Talking about defending the Second Amendment
Today representative Marjorie Taylor Greene congresswoman
Rose to speak against
Hr8 which is a natch National gun registration and HR 1446 which is a
Permanent firearm waiting list
So
The Democrats are
Coming after our
Constitutionally-guaranteed rights
1 after
The other and there's no
Sense of them slowing down only increasing their speed
There's not constitutionally protected anymore according to you there's no Constitution
You guys got to adjust your f****** rhetoric it is you're going to say we're living in a post
Constitutional America
Which one f*** your second amendment if it's most comforting
The name that's all good
Okay
It's Underdog
Yeah yeah
Man f****** let's do this
If you really sincerely believe Mad Max me let's go
Sincerely believe
That
The Constitution no longer applies wearing a postcard
Constitution America
You're not just saying that to be
A dramatic weirdo
Then it should implicate a whole bunch of other boy
You should no longer be talking about protecting
In the Second Amendment because
If there is no cost
There's no
The Constitution
I guess you probably should
Stop complaining about free speech
Wow don't worry about that that's not guaranteed know anymore
No and if you're going to stay post
Constitutional America then essentially what you're saying is
If we want
The Constitution
We're going to have
To overthrow the government
Write a new one or whatever
Re-establish the old one but either way Altima
You are saying we need to overthrow the United States government
And the way we're going to do that
According to Stuart
It's disgusting to watch all the
Bro everyone at the Capitol under the bus
Condemn them all
And the Democrats
We have.
Looking party
Start the bottom up
You got a job
Rhinos
Call the coward
Or Traders
Inspection report both
Traitors and cowards
You got a purge amount
Real Patriots
We got to get more of that
Gallium or Marjorie Taylor Greene there
Do not Stewart Roads for one second
Can save it someone else's
The coward
For once
You're going on this show
Lying about the ship
That you did on the SEC
If you were not a coward Stewart
Can coward as Road you're into cover-your-ass mode self in
You would have claimed that this whole thing is b******* and you would have said I'm going to stand and fight
These f****** charges
Because I'm not a coward you went on a radio show
Maddie Goodwin
City radio show
I didn't do it
They're going to blame me for stuff that I had
Nothing to do with
Trainers because the North Carolina goes with North Carolina guys went rogue and did all the things that we
Constantly talk about doing is a bigger
Then Stuart Road
No no no no
F******
Marco Rubio
Amanda Lang Republican
They devote about get more Marjorie Taylor Greene
Cowards now at what will the federal government did I didn't do anything but I will never take responsibility for any of my ex
Also insinuate
But even if that
Goes through
Are mites
Going to really work with might help
What a f*** is going to happen
So we get towards the end of this interview and Harrison gives us
You know basically like what the
Mostly prelate
Actually about
I want you to tell us
Stewart what
Like somebody was listening right now they see what's going on and they're thinking what do I do as soon as this program's over
What do I do in Fort Worth store.com
Dot-org
But what can they do who do they call Ghostbuster
How many more less of 40 minute infomercial for
Stewart Rhodes
Feigning
Ignorance and innocence
And then also trying to get my
Just tell Stewart to take
Take some of that f******
And chill man
Going to be dramatic about the post constitutional America
We got some product to you the fuk down I will say
City High
I don't know I mean I have trouble sleeping sometimes maybe I should I mean
No I will not
I want to make this clear I have gotten this question a couple times
Recently
We would have asked have I ever
Tri Delta
And we haven't
Dressers in a while
Nor would I ever
Other people do those videos
You can watch him they're Gravedigger better than us we're just going to be sad
Realizing that we were doing that and then stab
So we come to the end of this and what are the things that I really am
Pretty insistent on
In my own head
Is going to be paying more attention to Harrison
This dude is a real f******
Bravo
Nazi Nazi
I mean the
The kind of thing that is
Apparently acceptable conversation on his show
Is
Further than most of the time that you see on Alex's show
Let's eat outrage
The kind of thing
Video viewer on here
I did not think I would I would get to this point
Harrison brought me here a lot faster than I was expecting
I miss David Knight yeah
Boring as hell boring but he wasn't knew how to walk that line and honestly I
You know not to not to be too
Explicit about my feelings about this
I honestly think that this is revealing
Doing too much
I think that this is actually incredibly bad
Strategy
I think that this is bad for Infowars
It appears to be a head poking up
And I'm going to play whack-a-mole with
Yep I'm going
To pay more attention to him
Because I think it's a
Soft exposed underbelly
And a f******
Who doesn't know how to play the game Alex
And Owen Shroyer clearly
Play better where they can shut this stuff down
They can give the appearance
A signaling to these white nationalists 296
Yes absolutely are
Clearly either doesn't have the desire
Or the ability
Or the the smoothness
To be able to
Have all that in the
The package of presentation
That will probably see a lot of really
Really f***** up stuff
Yeah we we
To joke about it though.
One of the reasons that it was
Edifying to watch Alex Jones
Cuz Alex was the weakest link in the proper
Harrison is the weakest link of the floors
Sunflower they did Dandy lion
So we'll check back in on him from time
Timer
You trying to pay it
Attention keep up with him
As well as Alex
Monday hopefully Alex
Will be back
From his grocery store Adventure
I think it's really funny just
We were going to do an Alex episode but he was at the grocery store
The cleanser palettes after this we have Stewart Road lying his ass off
Harrison Fielding calls from
Outright
Anti-semite Nazi types
And all the meanwhile Alex
Because the state is so freaking awesome
Florida is awesome
Alex flew to Florida for school
Hey this seems like a great way to take a vacation while still pretending to work
Hey Rodger
Back on Monday but a website
Yes we are also on Twitter
People doing God's work
It will be back but until then I'm Neo I'm Leo and bcx
Clerk I'm Daryl run this I am
The prince of the
Pamphlet
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work