Alexandra Thurston color
A couple dudes
But I know a lot
This is Calypso Blue Ocean ocean blue lemonade with real lemon bits
Which is
Is not enticing
To mine
You go ahead and take the
The first drink
20 oz it is
It is blue
It's nightmarishly blue
30 that's not good but
I'm worried about the pole penis
But I'm going to reach the bottom
I'm just
I'm just still mad that I forgot the coconut juice which is just water with
Never bring that over the refrigerator
Driving to throw into your window one day I can say anything but you know
Coconut juice
Today Jordan
It is a major day
In the world of Alex Jones theology
Which is the
Is Alex Jones
Interview with Megyn Kelly is come out
Coordinates on Sunday
Right presstime we don't know exactly how fawning and pathetic
Megyn Kelly really is probably
Pretty strong
So we're recording this this part one of the two episodes were going to be released
This is an exploration into
Before the interview
Suspect
That he knows
He f***** up
Write and post
Yes
This pregame is going to be comprised entirely of any
On Friday night
Hour-long I've cut out almost done of it
It's scary
It is absolutely scary and documents a man
Who is lost it
And is trying
I love I love hit the criticism that people are giving him on Twitter which is perfect
Because it's so obvious
They have listened to
0% of Alex Jones
This kind of like
They're they're always looking Alex Jones isn't
He's coming from a position of
Feels the need to get out in front of the story
Because nobody's paying attention who's criticizing
Aren't going to change their mind is Megyn Kelly is like
Your
Call the globalist
Workout
Absolutely self-reinforcing systems
The thing that really bothers me the most is when I see these
These critiques that we're seeing on
Twitter as you mention
People don't really understand Alex Jones is worth
So I understand it to empathize with it
But if you're going
Critique him you have to understand
The globalism portion of it fundamentally misunderstood Twitter and it's
Purpose summer. Don't misunderstand is how much I appreciate our new donor ladies and gentlemen I'd like to give a shout out to
What's up
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you for donating
Absolute
We haven't had a new policy wonk and I like a couple episodes.
Before
Out of context
Fing
Do you want to tell you
I love you
I'm sorry I'm doing this to you this is your proof
Free apologizing to me
It's that crazy stuff is really f***** up and be about we've had to do this
Weekend or the amount we had to engage with this weekend
Is a lot to put on your diaper
Everyone out there that I do a lot of work if you don't know whatever
F*** off Jordan have to put up with this and that's a lot
Unbelievable
Thing is not Alex Jones
But it's something that I I discovered thanks to a couple of Twitter interaction
But I had with listeners
Durant
Who's the guy who broke in
Bohemian Grove
You did not run it through the bushes
He has a slightly different take
On the whole situation
From Alex
He was being interviewed on C-Span
I'm going to play this clip from the interview
Because I think it's important
To understand
Summer
Alex's brain and how it works
As we engage with
This video he put out on Friday
So we're going to put together like a baseline of
Ostensible journalist Jon Ronson
EBay
Creative nonfiction
Alex
Reinterpreting
Steven Jon Ronson perspective on Alex himself
Now the C-SPAN interview recent
It's a couple years back
But
What happened with me and Alex is that
We both witnessed about open instead of me and I realized it was that
Play grown up
Tracks
Gangnam Style
Anything that stops made with distance
You have two presidents of the United States was dependent on the vacations with the finger
Torchlight procession which kind of balance
Alex
Spin on its which ways that human sacrifice
Wood nightstand
Which was
It's not that crazy
Alex went back to his people with his own incredibly crazy
I noticed a couple of weeks ago and Alex Jones
Try to break into Bohemian Grove heavily-armed and
Alex Jones
The outside Mystic evidence of human sacrifice
What you saying about Bohemian Grove
Play playing with fire
Alex said
Liechtenstein
Number two
Build up his own miso soup
End
It's
It is a struggle for us
To figure out exactly what is self-delusion and what is like
Because the lines pretty thin with Alex
When he is lying versus when he believes
It it's pretty tough
To tell and I think there might be a point where is you just
Like he was lying back then
Completely bought his own hype
He believed his b*******
It's possible
Too much super male Vitality a chiropractor chiropractor
Don't they
Grouper the fish
Yeah that's for the next episode
So this video
What I wanted to do the reason we're covering the
Is I wanted
To give
The audience
And everyone out there who doesn't listen to Alex Jones
A little bit of a glimpse
Into what he was saying in the lead-up
And how
Anything he wants on YouTube
I'm so
He gets to shape the narrative for his list
And what you would think you would want to do is like
F***
This is getting a lot of publicity
There's a lot of people who are maybe new people who are coming
Need to find me
I should put out a video where I think everything
I should put out a video
That notary in your head underwater reasonable go to reasonable
Gets very defensive
I've ever heard in my life
Unfortunately after that this was Friday
On Saturday
He put out another video
It indicates to me that he doesn't have the power hands anything
He's been playing this game for the last week that he is tape everything that Megyn Kelly did
The whole time she was there he was
Which of course
Is that true
He has an audio accounts of course it's not true her crew be like
Stop taping
But NBC
That's not
Ifucking YouTube channel but I believe that he has audio of everything that happened
In his Studio
I believe that I don't believe he has audio of them at that restaurant that they went to
It was a secure location
I do believe the house that he was interviewed and they had he has audio of all that
Unless he had just some sort of a little recorder is pregnant
Panera Palladio
Consent would be illegal
And that's why we're not going
He released an audio of
Are recording of Macon
Kelly's closet
Okay before the actual interview
When they were discussing like what it was going to be and what have you
He says that she lied to him about stuff but
The audio of that call doesn't
Is that at all
It doesn't indicate any of the things he says
But we're not going to be playing any of it because I do not really know
The legality of it
And I
Certainly don't respect Alex Jones a choice
The idea that he's putting out private phone calls with
People
I mean we called
Larry Nichols and we took it off the show
Do the Point Clear Coat Factory
Realize we messed up and I can't believe I have to sign some sort of
Maybe
I don't know
That's better mattress
Put out after the one we're going to be going over
He was saying
Hey
You guys go ahead and post your put out your 11 minute interview
To put out the raw footage
Which means to me
You don't have
This is a Blog
This is just like
What are you guys do the right thing
I could do it myself
Maybe maybe it's illegal for me to do it but you guys if you want such
Howard
Afraid of what the
Footage says
Then you should
Really
The audio of the interview is edited
Play malicious way Alex Jones
Like there
Fall under the
Slander
Certainly is
Legal department
Sort of b******* about please
Gotten
Alex
Please just don't say that
Now
Yeah
So I don't believe his strong
Hand but he thinks he has
But I do believe this
This video that you put on Friday I believe
Is sincere
It is a desperate man
It is a sad man
It is a crushed man
I texted you earlier it was heading a guillotine
Just waiting for it to drop
That is basically what's going on
We're going to start with this first
Where I talked about how you know all I'm trying to do is save the world that's all
Watsonville
Mountain 5
Pacific oh my God. Explain how sometimes go over here
Global media
Remove like a cancer
From the Republic
This country a lot of people fought and died for that is
Amazing Nation
Vision
Our dreams our forebears have been amazing
Is it is under the knife right now we're in an emergency surgery right now
Globalist face sucker off of
Another movie rap
Prince and parasites
Even though Trump
Olive Branch
For themselves but also us
Very classy movie made
Absentia
Doesn't know what that word
Imma go over that with Goldman Sachs
Open up America riding with China's infrastructures better in the Goldman Sachs has moved Industries are
Americold ever come back on these people
Assholes
They're assholes
I hate I hate ask
Presentation
Keep a running tally of
By the way
The reference to Empire Strikes Back
Because they're necessarily there's just sort of the setup of the premise
Surgery against them
Or something
Yeah sure
You should learn about the real Renaissance like
It was free market at the time which led to patronage and a lot of
Poor people
Absolutely stopped
Renaissance
Luckily it's
Not a real thing
It's never explained what it is
Just a catchphrase for Alex over again
And also by the way we are on Facebook now
Made a Facebook page
Done anything with it you and I both have been off Facebook for a good long while.
The people wanna find us on there it's knowledge fight on Facebook
And just as a goof
I put our founding date in 1775
Anyway
A date you cannot add
I got a little charge can't believe they let you go back as far
So I am about Donald Trump
And they think you're so stupid
But the good news is only a fraction of people really fully awake
You get a fraction 12 3% that's the Detonator
The big one
We've already got 30 40% they're partially awake
We've got 60 70% for supporting Trump and real polls
50mm Gallup
He's at 65% despite everything that's running it
And so they cooked up this Russia narrative and now
Dolly obstruction Meredith
So
President does it it's not
They're going on TV
Do they not know that Nikolai car they just
Are they just like a
You know what the problem was
Nixon didn't say it often
Yeah I'm also the most recent Gallup poll is 40% disapprove 54%
4% disapprove 39% of proof
Strong like
Plus 10 points conservative bent to it
All other polls are like Trump Rasmussen is like
Interesting things to do
Wisconsin terms
The methodology of statistical Gathering really doesn't understand that the
Terms of like
Adding on
Fit representation
It went he went to Junior College
I'm guessing he never took us
Statistics course
That's what I'm guessing
It's not some sort of nefarious
We're going to add more Democrat
It's the trying to get a representative sample
Group of demographics
Certain point
You can
You can kind of estimate what is in the larger
Absolutely
Mid-thirties approval rating
Mid-to-late thirties
These guys are in the 50s disapproving
Exactly where Trump should have
Gone to hell in his mid-to-late
Some of the more extreme polls are showing likes
B+ percentage
Those are those are ones that are there
So
Nonsense
Anime idea that they're cooking up Russian stuff
Open Cooking up collusion Subs
You doing it to himself
Yeah all this stuff is not made out of
Yeah his lawyer went on TV on Fox news with Wallace today and was like
He's not
He's never said he's obstructing justice and he's not being invest
And then the next question
Was like
Yeah he knows he's being investigated for obstruction of justice
And they're going like
No you can't say both of those
Contradiction
Yeah
Is it going to be really sucked up
But trust me it picks up real fast
Flip is Alex
Accidentally revealing that he might be a liar
He discusses how we
Vicinity
Which
As a former comedian and
I consider myself
Game records
I think I think he might be indicating in this club that he's aware that
He's doing it in a manipulative
The globalists are so evil so corrupt so pathetic
I'm a shame
That were not more effect
I know hero
I'm here promoting Freedom versus a bunch of pedophiles and devil worshippers in and islamists
Usually 20 years it seems like it's pretty tough
We have a nation we have a world we have the West
White,
The world if you have the
And so a lot of it
We've got to make this epic battle as possible because it's showing
You got it in strive
With our verbal acumen
Oracle palette
Just how amazing this fight is if we speak to them like they're sleeping
And ask him to awaken so the vampires
Cultural
We want consciousness
You want to be alive
Just like in they live
1960s
Short story turned into a grape
Rowdy Roddy Piper John Carpenter film
We agree on that
I want you to live
We should all live
Glasses on
You know
The way he's setting it up is
This battle is a globalist
We've got to make it more entertaining cuz otherwise people are going to wake up
Bratz
We need to use our rhetorical pallets
Right
In order to take care of
What are your thoughts on that
I mean
What do you say we have
Use our rhetorical palette
The first thing that
Words an argument
And we have
Constantly in
Vent
And exploit new kind of worth an argument
To get
People to wake up
Wake up shore
I don't think that's what he saying
No
Is that true
Is barbed wire and I got to be over me
He's a hero
He's allowing
Hero
But again this comes to that like
This I am giving of myself
This interview with Megyn Kelly will be destruction
And I'm aware of it and I am hitting you might come over
He's setting him
Hopefully you'll come on
Lamprey
If you are sitting down to listen to this with your family
You are a big
He's setting himself up as a Christ
Absolutely
Little weird, rotary I have a kinship I have an alliance
Humanity
An alliance of my ancestors Ivan alliance with you
All this energy
Mission with no gravity
Was no spiritual and cultural muscle because our forebears were so good they created this
Actually brought us down below
So that are mine
Our forebears were so good
Well I think he's going even further back
The mat I think he's talking about creating
Agrarian civilization
Like I think he's talking about the Agricultural Revolution
Well that is basically built around alcohol so
Entirely
In that case
I don't disagree
I like a good I like a good pinot noir
So he and I are on the same page
That like unfortunate accidental result of us creating civilization
Is it
So
He's talking about praising hunter-gatherer
Maybe which is which is not a terrible or not terrible I mean
Not an out-of-character
Taking for him because if you're
If you're saying is I'm
All the time I am
A predator I am here to provide
For my family
Of course of course
Of course you would want
Go back to that
What happened is to get that bone juice
He and Mark Dice robbed robbed together
Globalist
Global Academy
Society
Everything wrong with hunter-gatherer Society is
You can't really get auto-ship
Super male Vitality furano though
He responds to accusations that no one is
The term information War
Channel I see the news
Jones coined the term information
Us
Department of Defense
What was the department defense department War
The German
Psychological War we call it knowledge fight
And we've got the real truth
Those are the big hundred Megaton hydrogen bomb
You do
We don't we don't need we need
The courage to not care about
The propaganda by people like Hillary and the horror media
I mean if I can't beat
Pedophile Robin witch
Oh boy
Nobody
Well I guess
Aesthetic
Yep they're weak and pathetic
Because
You think truth
Are you think lies are true
Right that's why
Destruction
The fact that he goes into Bohemian Grove
And spells it out like it's a Satanic ritual might be killing kids
I all this all this nonsense
That is why there's a problem
If he was telling
20-ton Megaton
Bombtrack
I don't care
It's not going to care if people would really respect him
I would respect
Oh absolutely
If he was out
And acted like he does
But he was telling the truth would be awesome
That is
Very very true
Why isn't there a why isn't there an Alex Jones on the left
Keith Olbermann
Alex
I think if you take some of the politics out of it he's Overman has Jokers 0 time
You do need an element of crazy
And maybe give me some
Absolutely
Play who knows
I think the truth to a lot of people or the way it's presented
Is boring
Dreams about stop this is free-form ramp
He doesn't understand about the truth like that's That's essential
Every way too hard
By Jose I just yell about reality for 4 hours a day
No I want to say yes and then I was like no I can't lie
If I was allowed to do Coke on TV dexedrine for 4 hours
Medicinal
If I just went on freeform rant about how our government has
Extension slavery and they're still doing it with the prison population and they're going through
Creating private prisons
Make sure that we put more people in prison
And all that they're doing is
Utilizing that is
Free f***
In labor
Go to those people like all of this stuff is still f****** going on
And that's why we need to stop the non global
There's like 45 sec
I was really going for it
My cartilage pills
Otto shark skin
Next clip we have reached the point where
Go off the rails
Yeah
Almost nothing from
Hour-long episode
And here is where Alex
Just goes
Goes for it
Things are never going to be the same
Cuz man it gets f*****
I'm not a pedophile
Border
A client's pedophile child rapist her husband Jerry Epstein
Information
Do what you want supposed to pedophiles
Helicopters and police
So this is become a new narrative
Police in there
This has become a new narrative because scalise
In the past has
Supported legislation
Human trafficking
Mike cernovich
Is
Who started pitching this idea that the pedophile globalist
Had a Bernie Sanders brainwashed supporter
At Payback
For trying to take down their pedophile Network
Which is irresponsible
Absolute
Very very responsible
So why did you say
Disagree
I get where you're coming from but I don't like that
Right to live
I agree with you there
Here's here's my perspective on
I know your type
I wish we lived
In a society
Where guns were not available to shoot
Since he is already been shot
The world is a better place without him
What did not without
He's going to recover
Unfortunately
I don't
I agree with you that it would be great to eradicate certain mindsets from the world
Certain
What's a brain
Hurting or
Killing white supremacist
But because he's are alike
And I wish
Buddy Hackett
I truly do since he is already been shot and there's nothing I can do about it
And he's the one
To make sure that he was
I don't care
I don't
I could give a f***
I'm I'm I'm on the fence
I'm on the fence about your position
I don't think that I hope you have
But I
I get where you're coming from
I'm not sure I'm ready to be that extreme.
It is a rejection of the fact
His position
In the same way that if let's say someone shoots Alex Jones
I don't want him
Todai
Necessarily even though he's already been shot and we can't take that back
I'm not going to wish for him to not
Recover
Alex Jones
Even though he is an awful bigot and water
Perhaps one of the worst people
Hubbell in the public sphere
He is still a parent
He's still someone kid
Exist within an ecosystem
Where parts of his politic
Parts of him Beyond his politics
Make a big effect on
I'm Steve scalise I'm sure
You wouldn't leave a massive Gap in a lot of people's lives if he dies
A white supremacist
Understand that
Is very cookie-cutter for subways
Accusing him
Of being a wife
Supremacist
His own words
He made a specific
Points
To say that he is a lot like what
Two-faced the governor of South Carolina
He's the one who fought so hard against
Integration
That guy he's the one
No I don't know
The point is he himself has said I'm going to be a white supremacist
Who doesn't say I'm away
That is that what
You said well again that's
Basic wheel
Like a ton of the new right
Beaver
I don't want to have this debate
We're not going to get to any kind of agreement
That's Beth probably
Let's get back to
Okay girls online trolling a New York mateso
Some of those girls 13 14 15 to get truck going the mall
Obliterates they never come out of those dungeons again
Imagine people like those globulus leaning over your daughter
Kidnapping subdivision right for a month straight
Portrait of teeth pulled out
Skin pulled off
And they're crying out to God
Send me defend me defend me
Spirit world
Men
After then admit how bad it is
Field against it
When you're attacked by these devils
It's almost embarrassing for people praise what we do
I could see that but at the same time
Do that voice
You know really does it
Little girl
Exactly
Incredibly creepy
It's
How he
I don't think it's the idea of
That turns him on
I think it's the
Telling of it
Not that like
Look at what I get to
Just a look at how awesome it is
That I get to
To say all of the
I disagree
Yeah I think
It's what gives a boner is the idea that
That you've actually a hero
Okay
Spells
Fantasies of
In his head
He gets really into
Yeah this isn't the only time in this episode
To put on that voice
He doesn't quite a bit but not so crows not always about such horrifying topic
Website
I mean there is definitely a problem with white slavery in the world
Only problem
With traffic
Yeah that happened
If
And I think this is the most likely so
Scenario
About
Aldi's globulus
But he talks about all the time
And how they trade in children
And what have you
Is incredibly
What he's doing is incredibly irresponsible
And he's just trying to trigger people
The thinking
His political opponents
Cheez-Its
It continually goes back to that
Pedophile
Because
Cloud your mind
It keeps you from thinking clearly
If you if you genuinely believe
That your enemies
AR
Pedophiles
How could you not
Get that visceral
Hatred
Turn off
I'm taking out people's teeth
Which is just a weird fantasy
I mean you shouldn't be saying these sorts of things on his show without some sort of a warning
Quite frankly you're right if you are someone who maybe suffered abuse
As a child or something like that
You could be traumatized
Alex talkin like
Absolutely
Not as bad as
Dammit Dan
You hate me
Show good that is a pedophiles and islamist
18 ocean
Oscar's every 5 minutes I mean this is like
Sure Victor
They don't have the power they got Hollywood
All these anti-christian anti-america anti
Civilization assholes
To think they're going to break our will
I know
I've already seen
Is systematically releasing men
And went right now
Just a few years are going to be so articulate so powerful so psychic
So f****** show ready
In business and media at
Military everywhere
Level of human development is here
Has been given birth to right now but are women
White
And that's why sex is s***
Hillary Clinton
Are are crapping all over their depends right now
Because
Dana
Analogy of Terminator
Phone number three
Another already beat Skynet and I since my back try to stop it
That's why they're freaking out so bad they already lost phone
Turn off
What are any number of movies I could have gone with
Out from there
I would prefer movie reference
Uber
So there's there's something more important that I want it I want to pull out of
This cliff
That
In a couple years these info Warriors
Are going to be
And then in the same clip you saying
I know I've already seen it
Yeah
Or that he knows
I want to be clear
Or that it's children
I don't have
Too much
To go on just from this clip
But this thought that I've just brought up I want you to track
Get through the rest of
Whenever these sort of weird things come up
Cuz they do
There's a trend
I think
Super
I think he might think he does right further the other thing is I think
That we have been far too
Too generous
How about the idea of Alex Jones being brain dead
Because there are a couple instant
Amazon this episode where
He spells out some things but
He's alluded to before
And if the way he describes them are like
This is
So
I'll just spoil it a little bit
He might think he's talking
He might think he has communication with
I'm not entirely sure
Are we going to make
Making pottery
Whoopi Goldberg is right in front of me
It's a
I wish I wish
They we can put a fourth checkmark there but
His
Like his constant
Illusions to reverse engineering is kind of his cover for saying
I can't eat
Into the past
And I can communicate with people
From ghosts
I don't know I don't know maybe
We got a lot to do
That that thing
He always does
Is
Start with pedophiles
And then
Add an islamist
It's in Hollywood
So it is
Even though he's not playing islamists
And Hollywood people are pedophiles
He's lumping them into
Together
You're right
To Doom
It's a little bit.
I'm a selfish person muscles my family
Analogical
British people
Where to break up soon
Everything they're doing right now because they're broken already
How are you cure King off onto the deck
Feel the fires of hell
Just push him over the edge
I don't know how you don't hear that as a call to violin
If you're someone who believes his anti globalist
Nonsense
I don't I don't I don't think that you could do that and not think let's go
Absolutely well we are and we have so much evidence
People who are info Warriors
Going to places with guns
With the intent of doing harm
Yeah I mean Alex is really really careful that even if he's going through bad people
Being soulless
Still really smart in the sense that he's using this metaphorical language
Talk about the gates of hell look push him over these can get away with it literally
Calling for violence
Man
He's getting so close now
Frappuccinos that
Inevitably if people keep paying attention to him he's destroyed
There's a part of his brain that knows he's been lying
For twenty years
Yeah absolutely guilty conscience
It is it is the twin he absorbed
Movie
Arnold Schwarzenegger
Certainly started out as Arnold
I'm not wrong is life is Twin
Here's where he gets into some islamophobia
And
Is using really meaningful statistic
6 to talk about it but
Do you think they're all over the news and kill me and kill everybody else they're not
People
How to get up
Out of bed the morning
Because those are the dead see the living at the curb
Like they were
Somehow they still be alive or not
Take the Muslims that they're so sad
And so pathetic
After 1400 years of their religion that teaches inbreeding
Covid in Europe and England up to half the deformed babies
Even on the populations only like 9%
That's a low number of the babies are deformed
Helen England 34%
30 +
Of the baby to form the UCare Muslims
Text Danny
That can't be
Can you imagine what that's like
Statistically impossible
Like the British royalty
Transylvania
That's why they want to end Humanity that's why they want time of Euros that's why they want clones that's why they want us all diseases like them
That's what they wanted DNA poison
Because they want us to be like
They are
Is this all Muslims are inbred disaster areas
Is a very popular narrative
The push by
People like Gavin McInnes
He talked about it a bunch on the Rogan program when he was on
Alex talked about it a bit this is one of the first times I've heard him be visix
Explicit about you
Statistics aren't really accurate
But
There's a lot to unpack when we want to talk about
Historically
There has been a lot more marrying of cousins
In Islamic
Oh yeah and that is allowed in the Quran
Said that you should do it
It's allowed
Important
There are a lot of benefits
Come from
Keeping families married
Enter married together
One of them is
That you keep property within your family
Sarah bunch of reasons
In less developed countries
That you would want to keep
Keep your tribe together
Well
The same way with
He did put
He did put a
Sure
You pull it down for yourself okay
Marrying your cousin
Having a kid with them
Does not necessarily
Create birthday
If one parent is a carrier of it
You can be more likely
But you will have genetic
Defect
Both parents will likely
We have that
Their carriers are
So the actual Act of f****** your cousin
Is it really that bad
We endorse f****** your cousin
In countries that have
Far better
Medical tree
Their tests you can undergo beforehand
People who have kids
Just do that anyway
America only 300,000 have those
Hey
Are you dating somebody related to
And it's like all the time before you have kids
It's very
Smart to go in and make sure that you're not carriers for recessive gene
They could end up creating
Lullaby
Another thing that's important to point out is the
Statistics that are kept about birth defects
Include
Superficial or minor things like cleft palate and those are far more common in Lesterville
Countries
So when you want
To talk about
Do you know any anomalies in statistics about Muslim countries having high
Birth defect
One of these
It's really important to talk about is bad prenatal care
It's not necessarily the
The f****** of your cousin
Right now I want to take one step further 10% of
Women who contracted
Did the zika virus
Babies with
What microcephaly
Yeah like it's not
Inbreeding
There are plenty of viruses
They don't have good medical
Technology
Yeah if so I want to ask how many
States do you think in America is it legal to f*** your cousin
It's illegal in every single state
With the exception of Mississippi
Nevada
Dakota South Dakota Texas
Utah Wisconsin
Kentucky do you mean the states that historically have a problem
Places where they like to make a law
We've been doing this for way too long at the Mormon Mississippi
The South hillbilly States you got Nevada
A lot of people who want to have sex
Moved into North Dakota South Dakota native
American tribe populations in those
Two states are so low
Sure Wisconsin in the same way with Iceland like if there's only
Fifty thousand people there
It's a good idea to Wisconsin
I've no idea what's by they made a lot
I want to
How many states do you think you can marry your cousin
In the United
Well outside of those States
I would say again all of
I'll give you a list
Maine
Alabama Alaska
I'll give you a list
Main Alabama Alaska California Colorado Connecticut
Florida Georgia
New Mexico New York North Carolina South Carolina Rhode Island Virginia
Those are the states where you can straight-up marry your cousin no-questions-asked
Your first cousin
Arizona
You can marry your cousin as long as one of you is sterile
In Wisconsin in Wisconsin
You can marry your cousin as long as the woman in the equation is at least 55
Or one-party Estero
In Utah you can marry your cousin only if both parties are sick
65 or older
Over 55 and one of them is farro
And Illinois you can marry cousin if both are over 50
Or one of you is Daryl
So there's apparently going on in the United States it's completely legal
I mean I guess you just
Like basically like
Hey you can marry your cousin as long as you don't have a
Well in those States
You put that into a
States is it legal to marry your cousin
I just assumed it was because they didn't have any laws
If it's not a problem
Make a lullaby
Stipulation
If weird if you look into it
Inbreeding
Is a really bad way to phrase because
Who creates this idea of
Horrifying
Deliverance style hillbilly type
But the reality is marrying your cousin is really that bad
It is only bad if one or both
The view is already a carrier
4 something
Like
Give me diabetes in the good example
Just because you have a shared what I understand
Humanity was down to like a mediately after the Ice Age I believe Humanity was down to
Between 14 and 30000
The statistics that they have for at least
I think the genetic
That they have say that in order to maintain enough genetic diversity
You only need like
10 to 15000
Which means their eyes
Plenty of cousins
Exactly
It is really unfortunate a lot of the birth
Defect that exists within not just Muslim countries
And if Alex
You want to really
Be
Sort of
You should raise awareness
Things you should donate
Two causes
You should support Doctors Without Borders and stuff like that
Charity that fixes cleft palate
Jimmy Pardo does give them a real help that you can do this
Demonizing those people
Right
I think it's worse than this next clip
More about
Now it's 6
General skyscrapers other buildings have been torched
England and Muslims are celebrating it
And the media can't even come out and say it's Muslims in fact
The new socialist
You f****** pile of garbage
Shares
They should take middle-class people's homes
Not middle-class people
Rich people do happy dogs
Save a small amount
Thousand Muslims running around
U02 houses your farmer you want out there another house was your grandma's or whatever
In Germany
Christian ethos
And I'd only little Coastal hotels and things were assembling a little Mason crying to go
You either control all your Gaston Street
Put in
200 Africans who just landed your house
He said that's over-the-top no no no
Testing
Poking and prodding
To see what you'll put up with
Economy
Look for deer screaming
And what he hates the idea of forced charity
Hate the idea whenever we talked about the clip of him being mad about
18 Muslim women
Starbucks
What makes a man is integration
Yeah he's not mad about the idea that these people can't integrated drawers
Living evidence of integration right that proves his whole premise wrong
Basically
What he's really afraid of here is worried about people helping
Other people and then proving I got we can all get along
Takes away from
Isaac it again
If 1 people are so Supreme
Explain to me why it is that we're all better off whenever everybody's in
Yeah
Has better outcomes
Not just
Are the people who are going there
It is for everyone
Yeah every school that's been integrated like in Alabama and the like
Those
Good like people worst like the picture of that
Young white lady
Screaming in the face of that black girl
In that
Time immediately following that
Everybody
Was better off
Yeah everybody was better up
And that is
F******
F*** them
If those if those conservative Tory bowls
F****** lit on fire themselves
It's b*******
So Alex is theory is it is Muslim
It smells sticks
Spiders that have happened
He's misinterpreting
That's crazy
A rich person
Wanted to save
What
Or whatever it is a hundred thousand pounds
Or something exterior cladding
Facade of the building
By the waterproof
And apparently according to regulations
Veteran place
That fireproof not fireproof only supposed to be used on like one story building
Sprite and when you have a 24
Story highrise
You're legally supposed to use the fire retardant
And they didn't
Are is a small fire
Cuz
Spread
And because they didn't
Install sprinkler system
Into this
In terms of
Conflicting things about
Sprinkler system
I've heard both sides that some people did not want
To have sprinkler systems
Some of the Reds
Themselves and that's possible
But because they weren't there the fire spread got to the exterior of the building and the whole thing went up the Christmas tree
Yep went up like crazy
And to make matters worse
There is a group
Call Dee grenfell Action Group 2012
Have been complaining about this building
A talking about how it's a disaster
And they working
Consistently ignored
Course
The thing is that
Really sad and
Is that it was in 2013
They made a statement that was
It is going to take a mass tragedy
In order for you to do anything about this
Yep this building is unsafe for people to be living in
I am
I mean it didn't happen
And don't you know what I would guarantee
Even though there was a mass tragedy
They're not going to
And the building was
Just inhabited by Muslims
Diverse population of poor people
How much
How many
Like
Death
It's not worth a lot
No
It's genuinely
Soylent
Middle-class people's homes
Which is complete b*******
Corbin Assange
Rich people's homes
That are just empty
Better just always empty because they own the property
And they're waiting for the values to go
So f******
Get
Do a good thing
Put these people in there until they can move someone realistically there's no way to
Like
Tell people they have to do that
So it's not a Galaxy's even misrepresenting the situation there's no way to force people into other people's homes
And that's not really what
Discuss this more
This is a proposal
This is something that we should do
Yeah it's
Should I dilute
People need to be taken care of it
Absurd
This is
The people
The people write public are being victimized
And have been victimized
And you have an opportunity to really help
Pre-market
Also I've seen
Prosperity
Really bad judge of things cuz I thought
Like 9/11
Was going to be
In the tenth 20,000
Yeah but if I saw that I saw the grenfell tower
I can't imagine that's not hungry
Well
More people are still called messy
Read some really sad thing about a guy got out with his old old wife
And he knows that she
She got out of the building
But you can't find her
Jesus
That sort of stuff is just like
When Alex makes these bucking
Declaration
Things about stuff
It's so hard to look at the real life stories of the people who are
The victims of these things and not think
How did you
Look into this at all
Do you know what you're talkin about
Are you
Willfully ignoring
Right
It is
Like when we started doing this
We started doing this podcast
There was far less
Just abject
Let's Patrol
Yeah
It's turned into
These people
Ark
Rule
Like they're immoral
They don't give a fuk
Like the
I mean
There should be
Seriously
And they're almost always want
Now I want it I want to say this
Alex Jones has a big
The media likes to say it's 6 million that they're talking
Pinpoint now I don't believe that
Is GoFundMe for the info
Or he was going to be like $400
But be that as it may he still does have a ton of listeners
Legitimately if he wanted to
He could try and mobilize them to help the people who were
Victims of the tragedy
If he cares about the idea of rich people having to put these people in their houses
He be like everyone I'm starting a fun
We're going to get hotels for all the people who've been affected
Via 6 million people
Everyone donate
Two boxes of 12 million dollars
Hotel
Campaign
For all
Call Samira
For all the people displaced by the fire
But you can't because he thinks Muslim started it's called Raya
Well Emma the GoFundMe numbers that they put out was last year
Half of GoFundMe was
Medical expense
The numbers going up
Yeah
So anyway
We got to go whenever people have to
Crowdsource
Being alive
Two strong bigotry out of
John dumelo voice coming in there even
Podcast
He hasn't really talked about
I want to go over some of these men pieces because
Unattended to business
But I know Megyn Kelly's planning I want to let her know
And our controllers and those stupid Ford Foundation Spooks they've got running Refrigeration
I just want to know that I'm coming down fast but I'm miles above you
And
I want them to know that I either angles because they're pathetic
Because I'm good but because you
Heart attack
I know your mind better than you do I want you to understand that
Groceries delivered your father
Important
48 l
Blown out the garbage
You're gone
University want to keep you
You can go to my phone
Heaven destroyed
Bloody
But you're so weak lobotomize toad
New every move you're going to make before you ever made it
Are you saying you're lobotomize toad
Yeah I think it is beyond Alliance
He knows all their moves ahead of time
I do like the fact that he doesn't believe in hell
I just don't understand why people would want over not exist
Yeah I don't know I don't know where I land on it I think reincarnation
People live new experiences
Give it give me a give me a goodbye
Funeral home still alive farewell
Is responsible
Inevitability
Going to stop at
Megyn Kelly you're going to hell
Yeah
It's like you are going
To be destroyed by the universe
Right Hunters Miss does not want you anymore
Desperate that's really pathetic
He can't own up to public scrutiny of the things he says
EXO
Is going to hell they're demons
They're pedophiles
It's
It's nonsense
It's it's to me
A great indication that he is so scared
About this
Another thing I wanted to bring up
Is I go back and forth on whether he's drunk
I can't tell
Episode
It's hard to say cuz he has the wrong f****** posit
He gets worked over there
Bridget those are sort of indication that he's drunk
But he's not
Liquido drunk
Be tipsy drums
Cocktail Jones
Something like that
This
Oh no
I don't like the tone you just started
Jordan it's not so much
An adventure
That
There're certain Revelations
About Alex Jones
And one of them is
He's way more into certain things than we realize this is
Sort of more proof of that getting back to 12 dimensions
It's not quite that
Okay
Let's begin
With the greatest abuse of a life
This planet
Has ever seen climate change
It's the Industrial Revolution causing climate change and nobody doing anything about it right
Doordash
Just miles from where I sit
Research laboratory
That is in
All the major medical and
Genetic engineering literature
And complete
Joke
To the people
But are so self-centered
They don't realize that the fall
Species their fault
Shell shellfish they don't know
They're interconnect
So foolish
Show on God-fearing
Weird ramble but you're wrong on all of your death
Chimeras
Oh yeah oh yeah maybe this is the maybe this is the one time of year that he smoke pot
I can definitely see that no cuz that was on Rogan show that was the only few months ago
Obviously like his course
The way his thoughts were disjointed the way he's like
Nibbling on an edible or something like that
The word about to get deep into chimera
I'm totally on board
Not his version of chimera
What I want
Tanuki
Move on its own
Your f****** lazy lazy finger
So let's get on with it let's get it
It's been Declassified because the information was not released the seventies that the Nazis
By 1938 were able to clone rabbit
Researchers
They were able to splice
Humans
And other mammals
Hold on
By the seventies it's not been
Declassified in
Peer-reviewed studies
They were able to create
Human insect
Oh f*** yeah
Fish porcine
Canopy bed
Alright I'm in
Pause
Mammals
I remember like 22 years ago
Read BBC articles about Halford Britain
But how
It remained classified and then I parked
The sum of the genetic engineer is well-known people to help patents animators going to dollars
These are serious scientist and they told me they said
They said the stuff going on underground labs is is beyond any alien movie you've ever seen
This is crazy
I like how you described it basically
Basically like a suicide drink that you would do when you're a kid and like a McDonald's and you would just put a little bit of
Everything in there
Spiders
Porcine
Turn off pad
Mammals
But you talk about each of us individually being sliced
We have time to get into all that Nibiru
Just completely repetitive cuz the episode
We recorded an episode tomorrow that's going to come out later in the week where we break down all of the
Current episode yesterday episode
Middle of the week and we get into the
Specifics about is dumb ideas about
Things you saying a real
Hey get this
If there were documents
That were classified
They would be everywhere everywhere
Dude
Where is are real
There are fish people
Now we have fish
Humanize if they're legitimately peer-reviewed
It would be one of the biggest deals
No way that you could get even classify it enough for somebody would be
It would be possible to keep it under wraps
Somebody would be
Chimera
Any evidence
Ever seen these on classified
You better believe your
F******
But
Loss tracker app
You better believe your ass
Jurassic Park
Hang onto your butts
Well you better believe it
That document
Profound
Let's get on with it let's move along
It's just like the Isle of dr. Moreau
Years ago
H.g. Wells envisioned
Genetic engineering in atomic weapons
99 and then coming back here later wrote equations bigger
Symbol of medicine Institute snakes the double-helix
Zappa done before the first rodeo
That's from Greek mythology
They already know erase memory
From other planets
Creatures
Laws and rights for humans
You should
Their new
I just means not of this world. Originally this planet
They were artificially created
Oh he's hot
And this is the true Revolution
Positronic rollectra
Surveillance Creator your appliances spy on you that's like 34 years old
1776 3.0
The Chimera computers in 1961
The internet in the 50
They should call it at that email
Coin email
Are you talking about
Do you have the Breakaway civilization
Do do you got to Breakaway civilization
He's made his point
I don't know
I mean there were there were like Elementary computers
What is wrong
Like
These global
The break
Elevation is he called
They have erase memory
Possibly from another provider
There aliens
And or extra-dimensional demons
That are coming in and they're trying to make animal hybrids
Do you realize
Like this is not a political show
This is a lunatic I don't think it's his audience
Even like
Someone
Who wasn't nuts
Spelled out exactly what he was actually saying to them
Hold on
Libertarian
If you were a libertarian
You would have to be on board with the free market creating if there's
Is a market for camara's Libertarians are super into you owning your own body
Body and what-have-you
The right
Of the chimera
I think I think they wouldn't be into it
Is it still be texting is being done on living things
That's true
But I also know I don't know
What is the official
Call Rand Paul right now
The official libertarian stance
Alzheimer is it
I am just I'm just wondering
What is your official position on chimeras
Did you know it's illegal to f*** your cousin in my stay
Got to go
I love I love the idea that we got to go
So it was like well if I was just takes a little bit of a break from talking about don't worry it'll come back
But he wants to say something
Specific words
Megyn Kelly about
That's just one aspect of this
I said statistically is cancer rates continue to grow
Your three children by the time you're 67 years old
Are going to die and she said how dare you say you want my children died of cancer
If I taped it to Megan I just said to you
If there's any human left in you I said
This is the end of us were being set up for extinction
Level 7 test plan
Don't want to escape this evening machines
David told humans
4shared
Whatever it is I don't know but I can see it's work it's not of this world it's not him
Kraynak said that she sent me text messages
Show the text messages
NBC4
Horses that shows she still had Humanity
Sheepishly collapse
Totally panicky totally scared about her career
She's done three episodes
Also I would posit that it's possible that if you're talking about her kids getting cancer and what have you
Even if it is in the context
That you think it's in
Kind of bullying
That's a little abusive I don't think he would you don't do what I say your kids will die
Someone else
I think that's kind of abusive
Idea to save his kids
Same keep him away from
I don't I don't which is also the official position of Liberty
Even if he thinks he can rationalize
She's having an emotional response to
I just
Just come here to do an interview talk about my f****** kid
Yeah you're affected by me
Cuz you're weak
So
Abuse
Yeah it doesn't even come down to gender lines or anything like that
Well it does
But it.
It's just
Like Alex Jones
Is being a s*** person
Trying to
Response to him being a shity person
Into a way for him to be even more
Right
Don't worry about your career you're upset because I told you
That I have four children and our Destinies are tied together
I still have to make the decision to have those children even though I knew this knowledge
14 years ago my first child
We do know that he did have to make a choice cuz he's for multiple abortions in the past
Also we found out that he didn't pay for those abortions
His dad did but me knows about that personal responsibility
Philosophy
Statistically Megan
Already one of your three children will die before you have cancer
If the numbers keep growing all three will die by the time you're 60
That's f***** up looking
That's not what I swear
The child had to make the decision to put them in a toxic environment
Because I'm decidedly I had to make the bed with you and try to fix this
Battlefield
I know they're really doing it out of the plans we have moles inside your organization
That we saying your kids are documents
But we have the type of what I actually said make
Cannabis are going to make it out alive
In 10 years in 20 years in 30 years
You're going to sit over your daughters and your son
He Sho glad to hear
That you're panicking and depressed and crying and freaked out Jesus is that shows you do happy man
What I saw in your eyes
We were going back and forth
Possessed by the force that controls you at you still
You still like one of the thieves and murderers lacrosse
You still at love God and you can ask
Christ to cleanse you and you can say that you want live anytime
Megan
I love your children
Oh this is f***** up
That's so f***** up the audio drops out of
Yeah there's probably some sort of technical glitch I don't I don't think
I don't think they necessarily like cut anything
Text that doesn't really show anything
Black
Text messages
Hey dude
What the f*** is wrong with you
That would be good text your behavior is incredibly inappropriate
Cuz I don't think we are to do a hatchet job
Like we talked about
Before the
Show started
She would love and softball that's right Amir Putin
I don't think
Fitness apparently she's there to be like
I think more likely
She's trying to get an interesting story out of it bring up
Sandy Hook
You do have to bring up 9/11
If you're talking to f****** Alex
With what the f*** kind of interviews take anyone wants to do without you
Well the one that I go to church on that's
Love that someday
Cuz I'm a Christian but not these glitterbug churches
Okay
Betty White
You can make jokes
Plus you're old
Truth
They don't want to debate
They kept the Quasi secret until now
Nope
They've done some weird stuff they've got whole research Labs they've got
Cast
They got people that are like
1% wolf
3% chimpanzee
A really nice park near me
Papers
I'm bad you guys are going to pack in the lawsuit
You are
You should be pushing I'm worse than whatever you know Adam Lanza or whatever happened to Sandy Hook
That's not the narrative it's being pushed is your guilt
Guilt coming out because you know what you're responsible for you know
That many of your listeners harass
Sandy Hook
Families
Have you know that they probably wouldn't be doing that if it weren't for your info
Now you're trying to pretend
It's very cowardly
Does not what a man would do
So
Yeah that is not that is not going on
That would be more fun as we discussed basically reference in Gremlins
That doesn't count for the references though okay
We will discuss all the specifics of his Chimera is wack
I just don't want to go over it all again
As he brings
Some other stuff up
But
The next episode is not quite as Chimera heavy
Yeah
Well
Rhonda chimeras quite a bit
To talk about and we go where his wind blows
This the slip-up
Guess what
Cameras
Well kind of
But also about we're testing
15 years ago by a engineer
Biologist
You think you know what's going on he said I'm going to show you something
Took me in
The DARPA labs
Nope just restricted
Just a Republican
They said this is the monkey Farm in the Egg farm in Bastrop
You see a little bit of this
Punch up the strange I was like
Jumping out of the Matrix Man
It was just
AirHead Extreme
We're just testing
The flicker rate for humans
Heather Lavallee said yeah they get these women are they Pam
They masturbate they watch p***
Winchester Salt looked up to him
What they're doing watching p***
He said
Work work work work setting the flicker rate
So that we can just manipulate actually make women have psychological orgasm
While they're watching television he said no
This whole place is about women
Everything we did was about 1
Because women
But it's like dark matter they can't measure it
They can measure the response but they know there's a signal
Women that is controlling men
Women
Then it got them like like like cyborg broadcasting kill the kill yourself death.
Murder in rollover
Is that not sophisticated
I don't understand what my wife
That's what he thinks feminism
Yeah legitimately
We can only measure the effects of it went dark matter
What God
Jesus Christ that bananas
Some of the
Seriously I couldn't but I can
Listen to this and be like
If he gave any goddamn specific
To anything
The only thing he says really specifically
Edwin
University lost thousands five they gave a
4.3 million-dollar Grant
The University of Austin
University of Texas in Austin
And here is a description of what they were doing there cuz it's all it's all very publicly available
I've been single.
The goal was to develop a new class
Technology scalable power-efficient high-performance microprocessor
Women to women
To make them hate my exact
Oops is designed to produce an architecture
Scale down to
The future semiconductor process
Accelerating industrial consumer embedded
And scientific workload
Calculator
A second with
Today's weather
Scale-down microchips and speed up position
Absolutely getting of different universities and University
Steve Texas at Austin
Was Kepler and Doug
Does not appear from any indications also this article gives out both of their phone numbers
You're really suspicious about them you could go ahead and
That's what what's up with DARPA
Also there's a robotics lab that may have something to do with some DARPA funding at the University of
Exhausting but again this is not
It's not at all buddy
Talking about
Who's providing funding
For the
Let's make women masturbate in see if they can send out a signal to control men I think that what he's saying is
Cuz I don't understand the bachelor
I don't understand drag race
Why do women like these shows and it must be because their kids are coming
Specifically designed
To give women psychologic
Magical orgasm
Literally
I know about vaginal orgasm
Was unaware of psychological orgasm
You don't have to come just by a certain
Anthem
Is it is true
Not quite
But I would say turn off the radio
And this is bigger than hip-hop
They schools can't teach us
Crackers and City Hall
I want to do more
Going to come up
Black Labrador Retrievers
Walking to the slap we got microscopic cameras
Scanning people
News
NSA whistleblowers
Structured person
This woman because she's going over the bad guy that said Sandy Hook
We are at the question just like babies
I mean he has real only defense that he has is the babies in incubators
Which was
Palacios testimony
In the lead-up
To the first
Iraq war Desert Storm
There was the daughter of the
Kuwaiti
President
Remember exactly I apologize
But she gave testimony that people were coming and taking the incubators and leaving babies to die
Visceral sort of gave people a real show this is horrifying
But it was not the only impetus
Four people going into Desert Storm
No but it was bound to be
She wasn't telling the truth
Right but that's his only real defense
People have lied about that kids before
But he's also lying
He said that it didn't happen we played the clip 100 times
Very specifically over and over again
Said that Sandy Hook was fake
He was excited that robbed FBI agent uncle was going to go Rogue and investigated
Great so I mean it's all bulshit
It's all bulshit
What NSA whistleblower
What kind of
Also isn't he against whistleblowers as long as they are not agree with there's a there's a thin line about
You believe them
Meaning
Coming to me
Usher
Yeah but the other thing is
Sure
He says this woman is sitting in front of me with her millions of dollars
Megyn Kelly
Accidental driving it is
Is first of all there's the misogyny
There is the idea that like
I've been to these DARPA labs
Seeing all this s***
You think
You know stuff
But you can't convince anybody that you're not lying
Jon Ronson
Going on record very clear that he was with you
Every listen to at the beginning of episode you said
Bet you he's not going to tell his
You're aware of the fact
Do women masturbate
Horse knots
Being like Megan you don't know shitt I've got all this information I'm the real truth
He proved that you have realtor
Yeah
Something otherwise all the
Is
Chimeras
Massage
I even show you the thousands
Research articles
About
Just in the US
Sodalite
First of all
He doesn't even show us those articles if you wants to prove anything
He just said all this stuff only in America and now he's going to talk about something in China
Your wife has a baby
First of milk
Do you know what she does in China
Wish.com
What
What's a she orders online
He has a pen he's putting it in Life Insurance Corporation arm
Chilling milk
But do you know that milk is not from you
The milk is produced
On farms with cows
2R
99% in general
Beulah studies
Mammary glands
Almost complete
Giant
Human breast
Account on YouTube
Then we'll show you the Giant
Optional
I want to see the cow with giant
So the implication is that they're so much worse that they're not showing up
Bulshit
Look that show me a cow with tips
I'm going to guess it's the rest of the show
I'm going to guess it's a Photoshop
Google me
I'm not given
Write on the check tonight
These are not real pictures
There's one here
There's one here but that's that's not real
That's that's a cow with
Tiffany said of utters
Yeah but that's not real it's not a real real art piece
Let's see
How does a disorders
Those are all just
Shutters
Route 222
That looks like a daughter that
You could
Maybe say looks like a titty
This is disappointing
Yeah you probably saw that are peas
I don't believe that Alex would be able to or interested in knowing
Other picture was fake or not but he looked at the Army
In China
A good thing article here from 2011
Professor ning Li was the scientist who led the research
Eye of the state key Laboratories for Agro biotechnology to China agricultural University
He insists the GM genetically modified milk
Is milk from ordinary dairy cows
She said quote
The milk taste stronger than normal
I don't know what that means
Quote we aim to commercialize Azaria incoming in the coming three years
For the human like milk
10 years or more time will be required to finally for this enhance
Milk into the customers cup
Absolutely
I mean you can't you can't say that
This article that I'm reading that from is what he flashes on the screen
Direct opposition
I think he's sighting or the thing you claiming as like
Proof because the headline of the article
The headline of the article
Is genetically-modified cows produce human milk
And because the headline says that he doesn't have to deal with what's right under the fold
Which actually is exactly the opposite of his bizarre fantasy
Is it do you think I icing
There is a certain amount of
Does have to go to
Go to the
Go to the editors of all of these things because they are oftentimes
Just like Sensational journalism I don't deserve it has
Even then most a lot of those wind up being like
This is possible
Cuz we talked to a scientist
And even when we talked to that scientist he was like
This probably won't
But maybe you could I don't disagree but I understand the business are genetically modified
Cows produce human milk
Yeah bear
That's pretty fair
Definitely
Dangerous
Jerome corsi
When I was in the van
And he told me about the stuff he saw these Laboratories in Maryland
Now we tip it to a different story
Explain something to you
Whoosh
Maryland serious I went to George Noory once in Austin Texas
Completely overjoyed
And he told me about the CIA and Killing Kennedy
Now they came to his office
Later life
To Arms the country back into the family I want to Dallas
Fort Worth
Arresto now they robbed
Lee Harvey Oswald body out of the crypt
The Sun
Billiards basically
They tried to kill him when he left
And then threatened his family
I talk to family
Humanoids
They're begging for help
A boy
It's the worst thing the children
And then
Like to suicide
Very not suppose
Which guy
People ask me
I don't care that I'm nobody
I just been chosen
To be a messenger at this point down the road
I'm not worried this is so exhausting
I want to die.
Waze on you
It's like I'm in a science fiction movie and I'm walking around I got total proof cuz they're just teasing and out like snow
You are kind of living tell you what I know exactly
Lying
It's very hard to do
For twenty years to lie
Is very stressful
It's tough
If you were just telling the truth
You would not feel the immense pressure that your aunt
I would have been chosen by God to be a messenger
I am a prophet of the lord we heard in 2015
He had a prophetic dream
No no
We're going to the next clip where I told you to hold on to this idea
This clip is where he spells out I think
A biopic
Schizophrenia
You talkin about
Race memory being something that is just
Encoded in our genes
I think he thinks and pictures
Straight talk to him
We'll see what you think
Can I get made fun of by subpart
F*** you stupid lawyer cross-examination
Let me respond
I hope Megyn Kelly's kids, years old
By then I can live forever
Literal
But I won't be silicon
Let me forever to your children and grandchildren
Do the ideas picture stand for
Stupid
My ancestors are alive right now they're sitting here
I want to fight
Stop
So I don't know how much that is metaphor
I don't know how that could be a tall metaphor
I could see a way of like thinking the pride of your lineage
Like maybe if maybe if he was
Maybe if he was pointing to himself
Like
In here
Yeah he's like my ancestors are right here next to me
How do you say
I am
Yeah I think he talks to ghosts
Yeah I think there's a possibility that he legitimately talks
Well there's another part later in the episode where he appears to be responding to something
Isn't there
F*** yeah we'll get to a little bit later
They just created really fun.
Fairies like
Is wacky bulshit that he's on
The liftoff
Misrepresenting
I think I'm going to just go ahead and cut the
Getting repetitive
But
How to set up the clip
It's creepy
Oh boy that's weird
Subway let me just get a few other subjects now that I've covered Megyn Kelly and I open children of 1,000 years
Their children with a trillion years
Affinity
Because we are the Sheldon
Very selfish person
I want the big Birthright
I want the next level
I want it all
The big Master architect and I'm ready
Selfish person
I want the next level
Other stories
It right there that no
Was not in response to any
And maybe there's somebody off camera or something like that
But he appears to be wrestling with a thought in his head
Yeah I want the next level
I want the master builder to know that I'm ready
He thinks the next
I mean
Turn on if you wanted pretend he's actually Cristiano Could Be Heaven
If you want
He believes in an eternal reward
But if you like in the same way
That cloud again
I don't I don't see him
More like
Where is the forest ghost possible I think it could be a
Sort of futurism thing where we become a type 1 civilization
Realizing the keys the one working again
Would be like a fully-realized
United Humanity
But
Keep saying believing in anything other than
I can become like
You saying I'm very selfish
See him thinking that there is some sort of
Next level of his own conch
Right
Looking more into like a guy situation
We're all part of the Earth
Energy you referring to God is like the master builder is very Masonic
Realtor
I don't know I mean it's a mystery but I want play it back I want to play the end of that back
Because I want you to I want it like really wrestle with this no
Master architect and I'm ready
Incredibly selfish person
I want the next level
Other stories
It's unlike anything I've ever heard on the show before
And I know we might be making a mountain out of a molehill
But the idea that my ancestors are right here eternal life is already around us
You live on through your
Ancestors and progeny
I want the next level
That's not how we would respond to someone like one of his employees off camera
They're just a hairy f***** up
That's weird this is a man breaking
Cuz I do
If maybe he's high amp breaker
Cuz he knows
It's all because of
Megyn Kelly
And
He's not ready for primetime
He's not ready for people to scrutinize at Mannino's it
F****** Nosa
I just don't understand what this 11-minute interview
Possibly have
Five times longer than that and yeah
Way worse
Like there's no way like I ever met Kelly I would air this
With no interview at all but just 11 minutes of this ago
Like the way he's
Portrayed as a kid
Conspiracy
Because he is so much more insane
The future episode we're going to talk like
Passing reference to Mars
Right he's a guy who has much more of just a conspiracy
Or someone like Richard Belzer
Like those people are they wanted the distrust the government and they want to dig into things
Alex Jones is not that
That's why I speculated on our most recently released episode
Uses the glittery Allure
Conspiracy theory to bring people
Into his psyche
Weird religiously bent white nationalist world
More really about
Yeah it may be in the maybe in the past it was more about conspiracy theories but that f****** boat is sale
We are in
Territory
This is crazy and I can't imagine like any of his
I have to
What does I think a lot of it
Employees are going to leave
You think so it goes down
I think I've taken down from outside is
Everybody just kind of band
The level of self-indulgence
The level of
Insanity
I'm going on in the last week and a half feet up
To this interview I mean you're never going to lose David Knight
Probably never going to lose Rob do a f******
Years
But
Emilia Macado's already on an extended hiatus
Might not be back
Millie Weaver I don't know maybe she'll leave who the f***
Make a lot of these other characters of already gone
Already has the life-extension technology very well may
But then
Beyonce
If he does release
Facebook
If he has
Audio of everything
It does inject
A lot of really into
Everything legal issues
But whether he has the right
To that interview
I could see him getting sued
For doing that if he has that audio and releases it
I mean I could I could see a lot of possible outcomes
And none of them are good for
Nope
It's and he knows it
Yeah
This has been such a strange six months
I have such a hard time believing
Where we started
Verses where we are now
Banana
It is interesting
256 episodes original
Like just
Even our
Pretense that we started with is gone
No abs
Salute
Laugh at this Airport
Still kind of
And now it's like holyshit Batman on the loose
And we're getting these glimpses from his path
But really explain it like rental abuse
Ivy
Nipping
Fumes under a building
The wacky
Head trauma
Traumatic head trauma
Did it might be expressing itself through
Messianic beliefs
It probably is expressing itself through
The belief that he's
Communicating with dead relatives
Right
I don't know anyway
We're not done
Alex wants to talk about liberal violence
Finally
Finally there's an article of the Daily Caller that is something everyone should read
I spent probably 30 minutes this morning that I didn't have reading this
Forgot
I mean
People that murdered Scout
Burn shot one Overkill leftist slaughtering
Police
Conservatives shooting
Only a fraction
All these crimes are being reported
The exponential level of what we're facing
Interesting that you want to use that logic when conservatives don't seem to be all that interested in going to really give
Bring some validity to Rachel
Differences in police reporting
Throw away any kind of hip-hop
Chrissy arguments
There's no there's no getting Beyond
Well
They don't
Hair
Like
If I am being hypocritical
I know I want to have some sort of
Bluelight I want to have some sort of idea logic
Belief system
That is
Consistent
Play the world
Like the whole point of that
Is to be able to apply
Quiet
Across-the-board
Yeah no
So if your ideology only accepts when you think
Things are bad versus when you think things are good
And they have nothing to do with each other
If they don't
Hair
About being hypocrites
Like there's no such thing as a conservative ideology
It's nothing
Cuz it's not even gun
It's driving guns right now
That guy is committing violence
It's not like
We need to support him for having
Anna Gunn it's nothing
They don't believe in anything other than
Everybody is attacking them because their world is
How does all the conservative ideology is right now
It
World used to be this
And now it's not and I will fight
Tooth & Nail
To try and make it
Not back to what I thought
Was supposed to be
Yeah I'm looking at this as an hour this is
That's sad
This is
All top 20 I mean there are
Some liberals that are
Attacking people absolutely that's.
That's not something that we necessarily condone across-the-board
That's not really the most important conversation to be having right now though
Cuz we got to flip it around
Do you want to talk about conservative attack
You're not going to like the outfit
It's going to be much
Worst conversation
But there's a bat
That the false flag
Every attack
Every attack is organized by leftist
Soros
That that's what they always believe
Yeah so good also he thinks like a really legitimately thinks the staging of Julius Caesar
Is called
To kill Trump not recognizing that every president has been debated
I'm not trying to make an argument
So he believes that and he believes that everyone is calling for Trump's dad
You think that everyone's calling for him to be killed Brett
Respond to what he wants to happen to people who are calling for the death of trump
And the nothing that shows
Did the courts are broken
Mostly up y'all this is open sedition
George Washington would have military team
Erratic 10,000 people tonight
No he wouldn't
Grimes
Men women and children but if you shed
If you like Patriots if you want to kill people
Kill members of our military kill members of our citizens kill our people kill them
They sounded up warrants
Drive to Walnut Avenue
He raped a woman
Lack of atrocity George Washington
He was a rapist who owned
You f****** in Fort Washington
Maybe he has some Vision understanding of what we're dealing with the president
We are being hot War George Washington president right now
I don't have any blood loss after these dumb liberals I just know that they are organizing
Murder and death publicly and it is a crime to let them do it
So you better stop them
How do you spell
Probably kill him
Which means we're justified in killing
Also George Washington there are multiple incident
Pictures of him killing prisoners of War
Which is I don't know if
The Geneva
Around back then
Applying our modern standards
Atrocious abuses of Humana
Prisoners of War supposed to
Tubi
Healing sleep sellers that to f*** you
Argument is well it was everybody doing it go f*** your
Go suck your
No
I can't
I can't fathom
How
Stupid
If you are protesting
Julius Caesar
You're a f******
You're done
You're stupid
Not not recognizing at all murderers either is not a good thing
Right
And the rest of it shows
The negative Fallout of democracy existed
Killing us either it didn't
Until 1770
There were just kingdoms so like
It is a Stark
Misunderstanding and
Just reactionary
Think of what you're looking like you're killing my guy
Again
We're emphasizing with Alex
Jones
From time to time
I like
Reasons for why he's the way he is but I
I stopped well short of saying
He should be pitied
I think I
Underoath
I'm saying pretty much a human like you see the difference
Like none of these people f****** read the play
Nope
Also check the Soviets response was that he was going to put on it
Play version
The Salem witch trials
And they're going to burn Hillary at the stake
Do it someone very astutely pointed out it's called The Crucible and again
The good guys were not the people burning Hillary
You just don't know what you're talkin about they're very dumb
Very dumb angry people
But you shouldn't kill him
No of course not
That's not that's not where we're at
So Alex we're coming to survive
Build a society
Where
People are
Constantly under threat of mass shooting
And you get mad shot
It is ironic
NORAD
Couple more clips
Maybe like
6 or 7
Jesus
Sorry I thought those were going to be shorter yet another episode might be as long as
Why does reproductive
Be
Again
Ostensibly what I would have done if I were him
If you like okay it's going to sound crazy
When I
Talk about
Chimeras on
Megyn Kelly show no
Specific research
Just lay it out
Pacific thing
Hearsay from a random unnam professor
Clearly fictionalized story of
Women watching p*** at a DARPA lab
Don't do that
Like this is your chance
To really specifically bring it home
What you actually believe in
If you want to be given a fair day in court that's what you should do that's what it sane person would do
Instead he's been a lot of time
Bullshiting
Talking about Megyn Kelly how she should come to Jesus
Right by your people
And now for the rest of the episode
It's kind of out-and-out
Islamophobia
And good sprinkling of anti-semitism
So we're going to get to this is how you want
To f****** deflect
From your interview
And so much of this is just hatred
Depends public shareholders meeting
It's all of it together
A bunch of wimps
Grenfell Tower fire so much other fires
And now I guess I'm into the Socialist leader
Just give
People's homes to Muslims
So I can borrow got more Tower
I feel sorry
For the Muslim
But like
It's like a rabid dog do they want to write children murder people
Situation
Chopper
So notice that he's not talking about
Extremist
This is how he feels this is what they all do
And I mean I'd like to point out that there are examples of Muslims
Is when they
Blow themselves up
Or
Style women
Yep and you know there was that fritzl guy kept women in his house
And raped them in the
There was Ariel Castro here in America
Not something that's
Specific to some culture
Really f***** up people
Dudes
FairPoint
But I can't say anything
Unresponsive
Cuz it's undignified
It's such a
Twisting of reality
To suit your bigoted
And I would love to say that
30 years ago it was
That
I had the same exact
It said about them
Unfortunately it is
Now current black people
Still have that
Bye summer popular
Hopefully
Fortunately
I want to go to the next level
Universal
People
Yeah sure the next year is about how Alex doesn't afraid of
Afraid of being sued
Yeah I probably should
Mme misrepresents
He basically shows that
Doesn't have any idea what new shows do
Right so that's
No
I'm not going to just person you're the people I got on tape line to me
He's not he's not proving those that Final Touch specialist
She always had a tough interview she would just act like she was fair and I wanted to use our
Gravitas your gravitas shutting attention to her failing career
A pleasure Feldman Megyn Kelly yes you do
That's exactly what you want whatever you called her a tart with millions of dollars
You wanted her to fail
Dumb dumb
Guess what
Of course she interviewed
Yeah also he said reported
Family members
That's him stating that they're not real you say that why would you
I can't believe he doesn't think like oh yeah they would want to see both sides
Corsa going to f****** talk
New York
What does what
They're all my God what Ambush journalism
That's insane
There's no way she said she wasn't
Do that there's no way they said he was going to final plus he was going to get Final Cut that person
Was f******
Or it was robbed
If they did that's wrong but I can't imagine any
Legitimate news organization
Lying someone like that
Alex has a tape
Of her saying like you can see it or something like that
That's like if
That's like if one of these To Catch a Predator guys like
Hey will give that pedophiles
Hoarseness
Revealed that he definitely believes in
You people need to cause a national debate about this but the elite have a breakaway civil
Station with a technology
Football game
I don't care
What's it like being a one-story is a demon criminal am I
Means nothing it's all a projection
We're losing our very species
And then they roll out Tom Brokaw
It's all just a big joke
I'm not even Maximus
Let's just not kill each other
WIC program
At some Scientology s*** right there
Yep and every culture said there's evil
Without maybe that's some operating system of humanity
Wants to make us be great I don't know what it is but it's real
What's going on
Propose this as an alternative Theory artistic expression
The reality that every decision you have to make in life you can do it
Lead to negative consequences good thing lead to
Good consequences
Artistic
Legendary
It's probably
Probably not true but archetypical something that cultures trying teach artistically
There are expressions that come out of
Would like the fear of the devil
To get you to do negative
The pleasures you could derive from
So I mean maybe it's that I was operating
System of demonic
Well and if you want to go with
If you want to go with operating
Just go with evolution
Like we are 8
True we are just
3% 2
Jesus
Christ you fuc
He's an idiot
Irreverence
Next clip more islamophobia
Oh wait no dump
In this next clip
We already heard him say that he wants
Go to the next level
He wants to know about you
What about you
How about you and this is just boot camp training
Don't you want to see the next level in the next to all my gosh imagine
Precious
You actually have Wonder
You should have Mystery of Life with creativity and ended the shared wonderment
That's experience on a power trip
You imagine
Did you talk about Super Mario World
Rainbow Road
There is a framing of like kind of like a video game
Video games are at DARPA program to brainwash people
Wildly
Positions
Requisition
Evergreen felt our residency atomos burned-out ability enough
Communal
Come together
He's terrible when people come together
He's trying so hard to come up with a nefarious way to describe
Community
Really really f***** up
Cuz of the community that he's really scared about
And
Uber if at the end of the end of the Grinch story
Instead of the Grinch's heart growing 3 sizes
It shrinks down and he's like those are f****** evil
I just wonder when they wear off
Are you know what hey I knew I was going walking into a trap I recorded the whole dinner
Gila monster
Used against them
They're sharing their goodness
Outside alien cancer
Play turnaround instance against
Oh I Brothers
Heather building burnout move into your house
Tower tragedy Rises
Deformity
Stare
Always the Arrogant demon stare of someone that could take life and creative form
Women of the scumbag
The power to be a piece of Phil's you will bow as you see the ugly face
You're guilty that he's ugly and you're not until out of your guild
Given to you by creation the only meant to be given to those that deserve did you send the key
Guilty
Well I mean that's also
Didn't you say that
Confederates about Uno
You know his royalty but then like
I really really want people to juxtapose that
How we talked about Timothy McVeigh
How we talked about the guy Ruby Ridge
The guy
How he talks about dylann roof
Well that's cuz that was a time
The shooter at the Batman in Aurora
Everyone
Every single one of those
He doesn't talk
Talk about like this
Another reason
There's a f****** reason
Offends them
Even if you think they're guilty
Like even in case of like James Holmes
Deniability
Because of his wife
What it's someone who's a Muslim is like
They're also bad arrogant stare
Cuz they know they can take away
Deformity
Bruh Bruh Bruh Bruh
Do f****** racist
So f****** big
Look at that
Yeah
Like
Again
All of his words
Describe
Him
Like he's giving birth
He said he has the power to do
And you see that and him being so open about it
That is
Just a more aggressive version of
Everything you hear
From
Talking
White Congress
I think one of the failings of people who are like
I think one of the feelings that I fall into has a sort of cocktail liberal tard
Or whatever
How is that
Stuff like this is a cry for help
In many ways
And that's the wrong way to work
Right because there is a part of me that I don't know what it comes from
Wishing someone saved me as a child you know
Did I feel the
I feel I emphasize with people like Alex
In the sense that I can
Can feel a lot of pain
Coming from
And what he screams about things that are clearly
Projection
Inside him coming out right there's a lot of
Me that has to fight against be like
He just really need someone to help him
Because that's not the case she is just
Out now.
No you're not going to help a psychopath
Nothing we could do to help him is
What we're doing now
People stop buying his dumbass
It's like 5 minutes long for the anti-Semitic
It's crazy
So here's what
Goldman Sachs
Lloyd blankfein
He
Got on Twitter
He had been on Twitter before
And he tweeted out a couple of things
So you tweeted about the Paris agreement
On June 1st
Today's decision
Ever the US's leadership position in the world hashtag Paris
Then the next leadership
Helps America are languages.
Money global
Talent come
Bad if lost
Consider with making policy on environment trade defense etcetera
Now on June 16th
Arrived in China
As always impressed by condition of Airport Road cell service a tetra
Us needs to
Infrastructure to keep
Three days later on June 9th
Now this one's a little troll
Just landed from China trying to
The catch-up how did infrastructure weeks
F****** balls on this pile of f****** s***
Like you didn't help destroy our f****** country
Like you f******
Motherfuker
Turn people against
The f****** government to help us
Bright
But you are the one who sang like well we can invest
We can invest in people we have to bail out the f****** bank wheatena giant stimulus package
It doesn't help any f***
Person in your lobby
Against
As we speak
Turn down here Mike a little bit
Fight against the very
Fair enough
And that has no
To do with him being
Reasonable response
Alex's response
Do these tweets
Is a little
I want to close with this
Goldman Sachs CEO appears to troll Trump
I'm quitter / infrastructure
How's ABC nose and and he comes back and says all China their building so much that have ghost cities they don't host
Dallas 434 daughter
Vision coverage
Bring the Muslims
Open your friends
I love you we love you we love you
Open
Open the gate
He's good he's such a rotten demon
I just little
Running around catching on everything
Borders funding a matter of genetic engineering everything you can
Sonic blizzard
Beavering away
Blow up the Earth basically
As soon as he killed everybody
And I are just like they they think they have everything they're just like
They just operate in the state of ecstasy
Dementia
But you can't get through
China Wok
Joshua
Anti-Semitic
Turn
Takes on a very sort of
Aspects to Anoka
But then also the the idea of globalism is anti-Semitic
And the idea of
Weaving and Satanism with Judaism is classical classical
Will do
That is
Not appropriate
We bet on a big weekend
I just want attention
So that's bad
But he's still trying to find the pocket
Cuz he was doing like the straight to my neck and it has gotten too little
Hamzy nerd
Alex Jones is a master in prayer
Everyone knows that
He's just really struggling cuz he is teleprompter free
Define exactly like
I want
To really do this voice up
I promise you
Full effect
Lloyd blankfein With Us
Minimum mm long dick
I'll show you out
I'ma die
LaunchPad
Music
Tell everybody that is it
Goldman Sachs Providence
Wonder why that is
Thelma's 30% hundreds of billions of dollars in bonuses to these assholes
And they're mad at Trump because of hundreds of billions also went to the general investor in the public
That's where it is
He bet 42:1
Course
With other people's private brokerage account
Challenge
Did you like begging someone to stop them just like
They just can't believe that God keeps the planet control
Keep stopping
Spiritual infection I've seen my own family
I don't know what that means at all
Very exciting
What are you saying assault all I can say is
I'm not saying I'm your huckleberry all I'm saying is
I know I'm on the winning team
This body means nothing
I am committed 100
What percent and nnn is Riverdale
There will be a remnant of humanity to survive the fire
And I'm just your other for Southland but we want something
Without us doing anything
How much do genetic engineering no matter what he's got he and his whole family are in a diet cancer
Oh almost felt when they brought in to devour them
Oh boy
I just don't think he does but you can look at it he is
He is like Gollum
Oops
Cantera Golem
He's not going to be good
Neither are going to go with the ring from where he came into the fire
Look how does a separate reference
I mean unless you want to
Distinguish between fellowship with Rangefinder it's been returned over
Lloyd blankfein is not among the living
Easy The Walking Dead
The real problem is
The classical archetypes of anti-semitism
Explanation of court
That's not right
And if you wanted to have a nuanced discussion of the legitimate
Has been responsible for
Specific
You listen some specifics
Behind
Platonic specific examples
What is it
Vampire squid
Blaze out
The years upon years in which
Goldman Sachs
The government is stacked
With former and current Goldman Sachs executive
Have orchestrated a
F*** the poor policy
It's mysterious.
Strange coincidence
Publix they have also been behind
Of those f******
Goldman Sachs
Evil so the important point though is is like a
Alex really wanted to get into stuff he could get into those things
Like even the topic that he's covering
He could say okay
He's f****** trolling Trump I get it that's fun
Bababababa
Deers with Goldman Sachs
Instead of being like he still mad they get all this money but they want all
Goldman Sachs does want all of the money
Well but it
BitLocker
Here's the thing
Billions of dollars are going
Normal people
That's not happening
Blankfein
So all that
Observe we're almost done
George Soros
I've always been a boogeyman
He mysteriously doesn't really come up
But at the end of this episode
Alex Jones decides to go after his son
Oh what
Son of George Soros
Jesus and
Decides to throw him into the Mack
Soros
All of them
Whittle's Farm
God will crush them in God's time
Hours for satanism
They only ship of this wicked Force
There's no evidence that any of these people who you claim or Satanist are Satanist
The only thing that's in common
A lot of them is that they're Jews
Well enter
F******
Why do you fix
What he said to Megyn Kelly
Probably
It's not like a
Your kids are going to die of cancer
If You Don't See the Light it was probably
Your kids are going to die in God
Yeah or something along those lines
How I say things are not always healthy
Consideration we want to live in a society
Any thought to that
Thoughtful
It's such a simple thing
Just just
Think about other people
Damn
For the episode
This is how is there a dismount
This is been a high-wire Act
And there is no activity
Keeps falling off underneath keep
He lives underneath it
If it's
I'll say this
Doesn't give a good summation
I'm really angry
Megyn Kelly's interview is going to be at
Destruction
Of my career because
And oh s*** around realize I hadn't read the thing
Should I claim that I right or am I lying about them
My entire globalist mythologies going to
The collapse from underneath
People are going to buy my product
I know it's an inevitability so I'm going to present myself
As a savior who his
Graciously throwing himself against the barbed wires of people
Can climb over me
I stood on my own petard
And the house of cards that I built
Bulshit
Yeah around me oh my God
Please
It's all the Muslims fault
That's kind of
Everything
Everybody else's fault
View of the Jews
The globalist
Or the people who enabled the Muslim
The lobster
Yep
I want to thank Jesus Christ and I am not
Alex
Soros
Thank God Almighty
Father of all creation all is good
I won't blame God for anything that happens to me never just don't let me be with them for eternity
Let me be with you because I have seen the power and the glory
I've seen the light and that's where I want to be
God
Transmission 45 minutes going to be
That's it
Alright I'm out
Thank God I'm not like George soros's son
I don't want to go to an afterlife that involves them
Long Pond
Good God
Another
Broadcast
We are going to
Rap-up
I believe that Alex is in a panic mode
As I described right before they clip their position
And whether or not the interview is actually as explosive as
I almost guarantee
Of course it was the interview yet
Animated
But you can check out knowledge
Oh there's a button
The show called
Alright
Call it
If you don't
Left a positive review algorithms things
I don't know
Climbing up the ranks
Anyway
It's so cannot call him Lord blank fine
Easy walking
Who can you name who isn't
That was the guy with life-extension technology
Ability to hang pictures
Jon rappoport
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work