I have great respect for knowledge B
Knowledge fight
Nike.com
Everybody looks around technology Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Jordan Jordan
I have a quick question
What up
That my bright spot back to
The act like real Chucky came back and came back from the grocery store and back from the grocery store
Yeah it is and that's why I actually feel like I'm
Doing the thing that I set out to do instead of like looking at Owen
Troyer feeling in and blow like
What are we where is he
Yeah what is going on and his stories of his time away
Not to be believed. Very excited too much
Is that okay
Okay at the new genres it feels good to be back in studio to be full of s***
And I enjoyed
Bright spot is it is
Part of me
Alex would give up the whole radio thing and I have become kind of a troll that lives in the grocery store
In like the Mexican food section
Just pop it out and be like
Yeah I like about the big enchilada
We're going to get to the big enchilada as Africa's next break
Apparently this grocery stores racist at me
I feel like Alex
Fit in in the deli I don't know
Here's the interesting thing about that grocery store shows that it's also like a big restaurant
Large Market
Slash
Alex Azar
If you will
What's good like cleanup
Maybe I don't know I wouldn't I wouldn't hire a nuisance like a bad employee
They do me like eventually we're going to see the
A remake of the wrestler but it's just
Lot of lot of that movie will be about coordination
On the part of Alex as an employee I don't think you take the rec
Action well
My bright spot then is Benjamin
He's great I was I was watching some Bob's Burger
Fantastic
Whether or not it was him with the capital
But then I started thinking about it I really
I've been listening to H John Benjamin since I was like
Hand doctor
Call movies yeah.
From the jump I was watching dr. Katz
I'd like a little kid and
And now I'm a full-grown prayer that H-Town regiment is still in my life yeah it is interesting
Think about I don't know if I have gone a year
Archer
Daughter
Yeah probably not he's even had his own shows on Comedy Central Network
Incredibly short-lived
I think he's been everywhere 20 years at least
Until I wanted to celebrate
That I've always enjoy each other Benjamin in my life I ever had a moment where I was like
Too much
Yeah for sure
Stand-ups that was really funny
Me too like from that invite them up CD totally forget a Buddies
Photo of him like a genuine
One of it one of our generation
Great comedic talents
And I
So jealous of his career in terms of like how famous he is
Probably Gomez
Perfect family as long as he does like a slightly different voice
Fly by
People bothering him probably
And also it's not like he's
A guy who got famous for doing so many different voices
His voice
Mostly just a little little bit different
Edit
Perfect every
So anyway Jordan let's get down to business
Today we're going to be doing is talking about how March 15th and 16th 2021
Closest dump
Did not
Well alright
I was thinking about
This is kind of an indication of how like
My brain went to some Flights of Fancy
Like a regular like
The 14
The pie day
3.14
Right
50s is the Ides of March
16th is 36
Steve Austin 3:16
Naturally this is a big
I don't know I don't know if there are like
Obviously there's like a Christmas Eve Christmas boxing day kind of thing
Kind of related
Birthday this year
I think Saint Patrick's Day weekend with this last weekend
We already have it I know they turn the river Green in Chicago
Patrick's Day throwing up on walls
Terrible
I don't miss when I used to live over by Clark's
Wrigley Field
That was a menace
Friend talked me into going
Link to that Sluggers
That bar that has a batting cage on the second floor.
Humanity that you were so proud that you're still here
Yeah it was touch-and-go for a little bit
Three stretch days of holidays that are really holidays
We're back to Alex Jones
Who all walks
Oh that's great
Today we got a couple of technocrats alright
Nothing birthday anybody get married
No no no marriages but I remember
But then we got to do we have to have a symposium
About the whole birthday
I want I want
I want a picture new plan
Your mama
Eric me a charger cuz what you and I'll probably walk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
The 21
I'll let you have that
A couple of technocrats raptors he can chocolate in your area thank you so much you and I would
Gmk AKA
Thank you so much
Business
Money off that heroin
Usually large
Chocolate in your area and corn dog
View I'm a little bit
Sometimes
Behind on some messages I lose track of somebody inbox
That's all
I sometimes don't see some of these birthday shout-outs and I feel bad
With a couple of these shout-outs today
Belated birthday would be like for $5 in a cup
3 weeks light this is from
March 22nd
It's not that far
You know what I want to do I want
Institute a new thing because this is getting to be too much and I love
Making
Can people's birthday special
I love
Being able to do that
We going to do this once a month
Birthday Roundup
Brooklyn
So from now on
By the end of the month
If you want to send me a birthday shout-out
Do you want us to do
For the next month
Will do it
I'll probably lose track of some
This isn't going to work
Do you like any solution that doesn't have anything to do with the problem which is that we're terrible with correspondence
Terrible.
Certain things in order
In my head
It's unfortunate that we live in a world where we read every male and responded are headed then forget to actually do it
Is a big problem that I have
I'm just a little bit too old I was born
Maybe a couple
Who years earlier I would have
Really integrated a lot of
New technologies in Troy
Sure organization in like
I don't know
What is what is what does QuickBooks for a to-do list
Yeah but it goes
It goes a little too far sometimes you know like my partnership she'll respond to emails from students at like 10 or 10
P.m. because it shows up on her phone you know and that's not a good work like that might be better though
In terms of like
And things
Moving you
Is that
Mitch W yet birthday earlier
This month
Happy birthday
That'll be a great one
Also Adrian
Trey wants to send that little happy birthday message out to you
Earlier this month
Sorry we missed it
And I Dylan
What's up Dylan
Got done with wants to wish you a happy birthday
Alright
Episode to go over whole lot of bulshit
Of
Another context drop I wanted to do something
Sing a little bit special
And so Mika
My baby Micah I'm not entirely sure Mike
Their partner had
Of the working-from-home
Oh no they may have some hydration problem
Jason pohlman go drink some water
Now when you say airplane
Not drink
The water
No
Is putting putting sugar water and people
Absolutely 2nd Hysteria
I have water samples
Unscientific
Water
Drink some goddamn water alright
He's been gone for for a week and I was
I was interested to see how he was going to return he came in and described him as dramatic and
A little
Lowrider
Sister comes back from his weird vacations usually what he's got a day wears a little bit.
He's a little sleepy
Ladies and gentlemen we could not be doing more important work right now
A house right now
Almost live March 15th
Monday Global transmission
The Ides of March
I am going to
Arrow special
And then when I return
Get into the
Months that are unfolding
Here today
Weird vibe
I'm going to start the show
And then leave
It's a weird vibe but it's also not that weird
From listening to show a lot
It's fairly like
Dura Dura
Expense
It is weird
It's a strange vibe
There's something going on
And then I realized what it was later Alex reviews
So the mystery will be solved why is Alex so weird
Probably break down some of the big headlines
Like a
Great Marvin Hagler
Dog pregnancy
You don't just have
Marvelous Marvin Hagler
A day after the vaccine
You know just have Hank Aaron dying
Applying and battling to keep that information coming out from the families
Because they can cover up
People dying it's hard to cover up Sports icon
Took the idea that boxing great Marvin Hagler died after getting a covid-19 vaccine didn't come from any solid
Reporting that Alex is working off of
Do you think that information from a random Facebook post buy another box
Hagar's wife Kay has come out been clear that this
This is not the case somebody passed away from natural causes
I can't determine whether or not Hagler had been vaccinated and if he had I have no idea when
You would have gotten the vaccine
My point here is that I really wanted demonstrate the flimsy level of information Alex works
He has absolutely zero evidence past that Facebook post that hagler's death is related to a vaccination
That's sufficient for him to report it to
Definitively
No one interested in getting the story right
Possibly use that as a word
Workflow
Also there's been no evidence found that the guest
At the Hank Aaron's death was related to getting vaccinated two weeks prior
He was 86 years old
And who knows what else is there
Also Alex
Those two names specific
Out the fuk of
His mouth you'll be nice
Marvelous Marvin dealt with
So much
Goddamn racism from geizig
Exactly like f****** Alex
Hank Aaron
Dealt with so much f****** raises if you guys like f****** Alex keep their names out of there
Out of your mouth
I saw so as we know Alex was hanging out in a grocery
Restore for a little bit
It's early on in the show
He give us a little bit of an indication of what he might actually been
Might be doing something a little bit in the fairy okay
I'm honored to be back in studio with all of you
I had an amazingly powerful trip
In Florida that I'm not at Liberty to get into any of on
Basically but I will give you just some of the
Basics
Assistance for me
And also a sense of what this broadcast
Has.
I want this broadcast
Text husband table
Are you are you trying to imply that you raised an Army in Florida
Operations
I'm not entirely sure if he doesn't
He doesn't elaborate more until later but as this goes like
The f*** you talk
Talking about I talked to Rodger Stone 45 minutes
So I know that we're going to
Destroy the government Rodger and I were smoking
Cigars and
Wasted to that weird podcast
I know it's good weekend
Special Report that's why he doesn't elaborate more and
Man this is important stuff man
Like I understand Alice has been gone for a week
He comes in he's like we got these special reports we got to get to it like
Thank God you did
Because
Hard-hitting journalist
Inspiring
Who won plenty of awards
Perform
Supported them
Lil Baby
The performance you do not want to miss
Probably too much.
The narcissistic
Hacks
Who has hijacked the soul of American music
The real warship
Grammy-winning Legends Bobby Rush
John Prine Chikorita
And many others had been given a moment to receive their Awards
American Music they right
Man johnbowne is mad at the Grammy's who could have predicted
Yeah Infowars employee mad at Grammys
Yeah I was going to say oh my god oh no conservative men are unhappy with women and
When people pop culture music app
We lead I was also listening to this and there was a really
But there's a part in his report that made me look really fast
I think he's trolling
Yeah I don't think John bowne serious
I think he's f****** with people
Trying to get a rise out of them
So then he can talk about how everyone's mad at his stupid report
And here was that
All overseen by the self
Queen of Crowley in magic
Beyonce and Jay-Z
Because the
Real American music represent
Must never be allowed out of its paw
Which is buried
Beneath the Grammys
Craving it JonBenet
Reporting
Infowars
Tomorrow's news today I think he's f****** around like I was being serious
Yeah
Is being serious
Right like how much it is just
Goofing off and being a dumbass do you actually think that Beyonce does
Crowley and Magic course
Cuz I know that Alex would probably say that Aunt Leo Crowley
Adjectives
That's in line with the Infowars
Editorial position
They are witches and warlocks
I do appreciate here's how much Beyonce is the queen
Her enemies have
To describe her as a queen and some patch
Richie is a Powerhouse
Okay
So you might as well recontextualizing
Is it to her being a Powerhouse at Magic
Australian whiskey
Lady
Actually do
I think I think he's just
Do you know
Just trying to piss people off so just trying to be a dick about stuff
Said maybe people will pay attention to
Is this phone where I can make you like
Clickbait headline maybe we'll get a thousand more views on it
Absolutely
Do you say that Beyonce is a
The master of Crowley in magic
So we get back to Alex
After jump-outs very dumb report and you want to talk more about
Oh you're not going to see the
Produced establishment program
Talking about why are all of these old people and young people and
People and white people and others dying
MRNA vaccine
All of these baseball players in famous boxers
Shot
Totally healthy took
5 hours later
Is Libertyville
Oz reporting hagler's family is that the death is related to the officially challenge
Tubac reclaim up
The only statement I can find from his family's from his wife who said quote
Herscher wasn't the vaccine that caused his death
My baby left in peace with his usual smile
And now is not the time to talk nonsense
Alex needs to back up his claim or else he needs to retract this slanderous
Better Business
Apologize to the Hagler family
Their pain is not a prop for him to use the
To put anti-vax married
Is just horseshit
No
And
You know
He was a fighter
Took a lot of hits
And Marvelous Marvin was somewhat
Known for being willing to take a hit
Just keep coming and beat the s*** out of you
So I
I was
Like I said in a in a strange state where are they
Alex got a weird f****** energy at the beginning of this what's going on he's going to mediately to reports after being gone for a week
He be hungry
And then I realized what was going on
Ringo break
I'm going to come back with all the news but I wanted to get to that first
Broadcast
Barber shop
Earpiece problem
So we had to write
Do it
Because storage
I just realize though that it is Americans themselves
Resistance we don't have a
Future we don't have any
I should quit
Because my earpiece is f****** up and quite frankly none of you were fighting hard enough
So that puts me in a bad mood so I assume the lash out of you everything right and it's all your fault
Because I'm a whiny baby absolutely because
You people whiny baby who pays John bowne.
The most relevant thing to music
The dork
Anyway Alex gets back to his Florida
And here is where I started to get a sense of what
Might have been
Been going on
And I went to Florida
And I wouldn't even call mostly Secret
Exciting
The same message
By everyone that I spoke with
I'll just leave it at that
The top names
.
Florida
And the revolution
We need you
We're counting on you
We're counting on your listeners and
Sickly
That
We are the engine
That is driving
Most of the Rebellion
You see here today
Alex
Has been bestowed the title of the leader of the Rebellion
Talk to
We would know
It would have been reported on not I not only that
Alex would have shot a video there yeah yeah yeah but how I met with
Trump yeah but even even then even if it was like Trump wanted to let you know Trump and his team or like we're not actually
Because
You know
You know they don't even have to stay there
But even then it would have been reported like Alex Jones seen walking into marahlago
For like Stephen Miller spotted at grocery store
Axis of Evil revive at grocery store
I think that the world
Bucked up that I
To believe that maybe he did talk
And I could also believe that he wants people to think that he just hung out with Rodger and a grocery store
And now he's annointed him bleeder
Yeah and I can also believe him
I'm telling Rodger Stone to tell Trump something is him be like
We have we have seen many instances of that over the course of the show
Bigwig
In the auntie globalist
Fight that Alex's is engaged at the leader of
Sure
Big Nate
Want to know like how do you know what
Oh man
You're so smart
Dreams
3 most prominent names
Ian
The countryside of the globalist all after the same question how did you know all that
I said whoa
Yeah there's a lot of
I know the key groups
They built so far
Predictive programming
So I know what they're going to do
And I said Well you certainly do know that
I met with the former head of to us intelligence agencies
I'll leave it at that
Experience
I cured covid-19
It was like 1,000 lb weight
Lot of weight on my shoulders but I've had this
And I've known it was my job but this time
Win
To do what we've done I told you that
Get out up front
So the others can interior the ball
I just literally
It was more like
This will happen this unfold
And the Mist
Stop
That I am inspired
With my discernment at my own research
To know what to look at to understand
And that my understanding of human nature
Was that on but that was all given to me by God
Smartest thing Rush Limbaugh
Said was
Talent on loan
From God
And so I just am very humbled to be here
Humble respectful to be with all of you
Time to get
40 minutes into the show Now isn't covered anything
I have I have written down the moment he said we do important work here I was gone
Let's just tally up some important work and we got we've got Marvelous Marvin and Hank Aaron we've got his mysterious
Strip x 20 we've got the Grammys on we've got my earpiece
Priest doesn't work
Important that special report
It's cuz he needed to fix his ear piece that was I was going on
All the many rambled a bunch about how he was anointed the king of the Patriots when he was hanging out in Florida so
Engraving
For Alex
Complain at this point that he doesn't have time to get to the real meat
Recover a properly
He has all the time in the world he just knows full well that
If you ever tried to go anywhere deeper than surface-level on any of these
Restore easy covers
You become clear immediately but he has no idea what he's talking about and its arguments
Make no sense
Put up with him just rambling about God giving him a download or whatever happened career is going to be when everything is at
Direct contradiction
It's not like 20 years ago God told him
One day you will be
Foot soldier in Donald Trump's wall
Before he supported him out to start the truck was in the mob
I'm so disgusting
This way then sometimes that includes making you tell everybody that you're goddamn
Alex
Had like some kind of a download of what he was going to do and some kind of an idea of his
Future then like you
Couldn't have possibly known anything pass
Supporting Trump because
Fizz mid so
Avast departure from
God didn't tell him that part
Sure
Also I have I'm struggling to believe that you want to follow
Top names in anti globalism who are willing to take you at face value when they say
How do you know everything you know
Well I had a vision 20 years ago
I'm sorry I'm so sorry
You tell that to them you don't tell that to
Sorry but I don't imagine I conversation with anything like that
Yeah
What kind of stuff that happens
Is it like
I don't know
Aleister Crowley circles
I will tell you that the king of Crowley and Magic does also get visions
Yeah that's a place for that conversation. This dumb dumb s***
Anyway Alex headset like you said to me last clip you like you felt like a big weight was lifted from her
That's cuz he's kind of
Completed his mission
Don't feel like my missions over
Completed
What I was sent here to do
You've been sent to this planet as well
You're here
Why God created you
About
God literally had his hand
Do tell me all the same message
The same message take care of yourself
You help watch this whole thing you're even alone
Apologize
Now people are asking me what to do
Level
Specifically but
That
I completed the mission so far now
Now
And don't even need me
Space shuttle
The main boosters just fall off
Imagine being
You were the most yourself
The main fight this is all
Pre-positioning for what coming
Dog people versus Satan's people
This was setting up the chess pieces
Now ladies and gentlemen it is.
This is very stupid
I mean like honestly as somebody who listens to a ton of Alex
I mean like one of our episodes
The people like a lot was the episode
The drunk Hotel interview tomorrow
Patrick bet-david
It was
He completed his mission and things that are like
There it's
It just it's a it's a refrain that comes back this time to time whenever Alex Fields a certain way
But he talked
Just somebody
Maybe not Trump
But it's somebody who gave him like
A real sense of affirmation
Yeah somebody validated him in a way that he doesn't feel generally validated by like
And I would almost say
Maybe it was a financier
Maybe he was down in Florida trying to get the money to stay afloat
That could be
Someone agreed to go through a couple bucks at Infowars
Mike went out
He might not have any money in a little bit
Could be the guy who runs a grocery store
I don't know it's very weird all I hear is like whenever you whenever Alex talks about these like this idea look at weight is lifted from him
It's just like someone patted you on the head
You feel really good about it
I am glad you had a great trip but you
You still alive mean everything
Still sucks is down right now is because he
You coming off the highwomen like I'm so great and now he's in a bad mood so we're helping you out gradient
I'm not your fault
Finally stopped talking about his own dumbass and starts
Talking about some
Some issues
About climate change
And I found this
Fascinating
Freeman
Of of
Two different idea okay
And I'm sure you've all heard me the regular Lister probably
5000 * 2
When they collapse of third world of the lock
You're going to say that that
Weis
Because of climate change
Sure as hell Nancy Pelosi cannot set it
Mike said they're also going to say that
The new viruses are rising
Because of climate change and that's why they're
It was criticized Robertson
Say hello humans are bad
There's a snowstorm
Gerbil
So a couple quick
Long before covid was known to anyone they were many people discussing the dynamic that went climates change
It makes some regions uninhabitable released
Weather by the risk of rising
Sea levels
Supplier some other variable shifting
This weed
Inevitably to some degree of displacement of people
The extent of witches
Is going to live to be
Second when people discuss climate change cause new diseases they're talkin about her changing climate displaces animals as well
And as that happens
Animals who previously would not have been in contact with humans
End up contacting human
Adding those cases
There's a possibility for transmission of Novel diseases
There's also the matter of rising
See temperatures making water more hospitable for
Things like flesh eating bacteria
But all the discussions around
Cause-and-effect
Not every new interaction between an animal and human is going to result in a new disease but
Does happen the more possibilities there are four new disease
Papa Doc
This is something that I guess Alex is complaining with Pat Robertson saying that natural disasters are God's punishment for the USA
Accepting LGB
EQ Focus humans
In 2015
Pat Robertson said that a drop in the Dow Jones Industrial Average was God punishing the Obama Administration for supporting
Access to reproductive health
Oh yeah but that one
Actually was true
There's an important difference
Prince between these two things
The Alex's embarrassingly not understanding
And that is what is moralistic
And the other is descript
The conversation about climate change
Can be something that you can discuss
With moral implication
But it can also be a conversation that you have strictly as a matter of X will cause why
And it still makes a
Robertson claims are things that only work as a moral argument
Add almond flimsy one
I can't possibly be taken seriously in any other
There's no way to coherently explain how Planned Parenthood existing
Causes hurricane
Except if you embrace the worldview that we're living at the whim of a venture
For God who decided that reproductive Healthcare is immoral
Morality is a hurricane
That's the only way that Robertson
You would make sense for my grammar standpoint
The same is not true for the conversations that people have about the side effects
Climate change
It's really amazing to see this kind of equivalents being made
And realize that there's actually
I would probably how I Oz brain works
These two things probably do feel about the same to him
He just thinks that Robertson
Claims are closer to reality
I get it
It's staggering
Yeah it's weird to exist
We talked about this before but we exist in multiple different
Time.
Simultaneous
Play like it's weird to understand
The main factors of climate change and how they swirl around in a global sense
Which is
Incredible
In such a short. Of time to like relative
Simply speaking
We've gone from believing that
Which has caused all of our problems
The understanding what those problems come from on a scientific Andrea level at the same time
People still believe that which has caused our problems
Crowley in witches how can you do that
Yeah it's it's it's interesting to me and sort of hinge point of it is
Alex seems to think that the conversations about the
Potential new diseases that we will come in contact with
Animals
Get this place is climate
Let's change that it's something
It is intrinsically about humans being bad
And that's not at all
A beautiful conversation
It's a straw man in order for him to make this somehow when equivalent
Call Pat Roberts
Something gay people cause
Great
So dumb yeah
Yeah
It's real difficult to to swing with
Bulshit man
We got is I think it's a good indication
Example of
They have a lot of
The stuff that Alex does
It's kind of a trap
By the way Fentanyl
In the last two months just as Biden got in
DEA says he's up 360
Sprinter 62% I saw the article
This weekend
360 plus percent
Is killing hundreds of thousands of people Autumn black but I know you're not going to see
The Emmys are the Grammys really shows pushing this
Central importation in the US
Lowe's
Infowars quotes acting Customs and Border Protection commissioner Troy Miller is saying the following during a media call on March
Quote we're seeing a dramatic
Increase in fentanyl seizures this fiscal year
More than 300
60% higher than this time last year
Now here's a fun game
And this is why this information is almost impossible to get rid of ever
Alex could use that to argue that there's so much more fentanyl coming into the country then when Trump was President because biting this thing
Signal to the cartels
Then it's open season
Of course this doesn't really explain why the police are season all of the bouquet
Now imagine that Miller the acting Customs and Border Protection
Commissioner
What if you'd reported the
Seizures were weighed down
From last year
What do you imagine Alex's narrative would be at the
I believe it would be that
There you are hiding the number of seizures that are occurring
Were there just letting it all through yeah
Message has gone out just let him on through with the Fentanyl
Yeah yeah
It's a trap
It doesn't matter
And also
I do
Care
Anyone from customs
Border
If you can't trust
That's a side issue
It's somewhat reliant on
Stasher
The actual facts or information
In the come out
Matter
In cases like that
The argument is that trumps approach
To the board was good and biting
This bad so no matter what
Details get provided they get filtered through that lens
The predetermined argument is made
That's all that's going on
A b advisor admitting the trumps policies work
Alex is reading an Infowars headline that fails to capture
Show the real story
This was about the southern border and coordinator Roberta Jake
Discussing how there may be a relationship between the ending
The prompts inhumane policies
And a spike in people heading towards
The Border
There was a hope for a more Humane policy after 4 years of pent-up demand so I don't know if I would call that a coincidence
But the idea that a more Humane policy would be in place may have driven people to make that
Decision the perhaps more importantly it definitely drove Smugglers to express disinformation
Spread disinformation
How about what was now pause
This isn't. What Alex's reporting because
Little bit deeper than the surface appearance level
We can't really handle that
Kind of material so it's entirely possible that people were like oh the president does
An actively want to murder us soon maybe now would be a better time that it was
People who are taking advantage of that perhaps
Selling selling people a bill of goods about getting them over the Border
Talking about trying to balance mess
Messaging responsibly with policy
Yeah it's
It's
It's just a little bit more complicated than Alex want
So
How is disease
You know
Euless guy who's like above The Fray
Sure
Left-right paradigm
But
As long as we don't give up they're going to run out of time they're going to fall apart
You're run from Democrats you run from socialist
You run from leftist you run from liberal
Monsters
Criminal syndicate
And most people to start the left
Being used
And destroyed themselves
That's all coming up
May I could have sworn he was above the left-right Divide I thought that was just a way that they the man got me with a fight with
Each other out of the groups that Alex is talking about you need to run from cuz they're monsters are right-wing at all
We're
This is really important to understand
Alex is branding in his earlier career really relied on him pretending to not be extremely right wing
He was making arguments over straight out of the John Birch Society of putting forward ideas that were
Far to the right of the
The GOP in the 90s
So in order to mask that in
Expand his potential
Beyond the weirdo militia people
You have a lot
The essential live his career that he's above the party system and ready to post Democrats and Republicans equally
He's not and he's never been
He likes extremists
And only the Republicans or
When liberal-leaning people got tricked into thinking that he was just an iconoclast truth-telling kind of guy
What they were actually being tricked into his supporting his right-wing extremist ideology they thought they were being sold
Is just an alliance against
The man
This was done because on its face Alex's it is weak and dumb
And people would see right through it and rejected if it was delivered in any way other than in a trojan horse
That's what I think about the Pentagon at the end there
Alex's just covering something
Tucker Carlson is whining about
On his show last week on Tuesday
The military's too feminine
Panda
Considering the needs of soldiers who may not be mail his quote a mockery of the US Military
I don't know whatever that guy is should just be like
Just that guy let's not even worry about free speech
Implications or anything let's just be like no no those guys whatever that is if you do exactly that
What is illegal
What just doesn't seem like a sincere position
It's not even a position
Rockwell that's fair enough
So naturally a lot of folks in the services were offended by these comments and spoke out about it
Speaking to reporters Pentagon spokesman John Kirby Express revulsion
Tucker's comments
And as reported by CNN quote
Said the military still had a lot of work to do to become more inclusive more respectful of everyone
Especially women
We pledge to do better and we will what we absolutely won't do
It's a Personnel advice from a talk show host or the Chinese military
Maybe those folks feel like they have something
Approve that's on them
Tucker went on his show and whined about how the Pentagon was attacking him and
It's an outrage
Now Alex is reporting on toddlers whining
This is a game for people like Alex and Tucker
They see something that they know is offensive into meetings and people responded what they said was offensive into meaning
MMA pretend that their victims of being a
Depressed by people expressing their what they said suck
Yeah everybody
Get the good news nucycle out of it and then we all move on the next step because
Cuz we're all stupid
It's outrageously Domina waste of everyone's time and energy
And that is the best argument I think for making
Tucker Carlson not street legal
I'd like in the literal sense
It should just be
Like you can it's against the law
Tubi
Carlson on air
And if somebody
Does that then you just play clips of Tucker Carlson
Something that
Atkore
And then you can pay
It's not hard
So are you a linguist
I like to ask random question sometimes
I want to know what you think about this Alex Alex
Oh I don't
He has the right to make up words
I hope he does he's not Mickey
He's an innovator
We just found something very very interesting
I have remembered a few months ago
I'm so I'm so glad that they didn't want it falls
Cracks in one of the crew members
Saw this a notice of themselves
Reprogramming
I'm wearing masks in Hollywood movies
Set up a future as a dish
Topia
I called him just topics or dystopia
That's awesome talk show
I can find me a few weeks ago out of town
That's another word
You can
So you can put on them
Disco
With people that want
Dystopia
The form of governance on
Communist
I called them
And just as I started using the
I think it's been picked up
Okay that's fine
It's not worth it Alex Invented
No I was going to say that's a adjectives
Your version of the exact same word as dystopian
Both are adjectives
Take a note something being similar to
Dystopia
You can find some really interesting debate among amateur linguist on message boards about whether or not you should ever use this Toby
Pickett said of dystopian
And the general consensus is that there is no really good reason
M2
Alex Tanaka
Password
The earliest appearance of the word in Google's Archive of printed work appears
To be a 1905
But interesting lead the frequency of those jumps
After the night
1860s
I found an interesting article on the website daily rating
Apps that offer is April
Control theory for why Alex
Has this is like his preferred word or words it's in his head
The author of this site was discussing how they use the word dystopic
I wondered if it was actually a word
I think my use of it in an article may stem from frequent reading of film criticism
They then go on
Want to give some examples of instances where the word is used generally
In the discussion of
Pop culture science fiction
I suspect Alex is so entrenched in and so influenced by pop culture science
I'm thinking that it's a real
He's probably encounter the word
Just hoping that context
Wait a bit
And now I guess who just thinks
Going to term
Whether my theory is right or not this is Justin
Embarrassing time-wasting that Alex engaging in here
You know I actually didn't
The right
Have you ever heard the word
It is a real way to remove blood from
I created the word
Explanatory
Which is when you're watching like
Samurai movie
They get excited when they did but it goes all over the splatter it version
That's a good word
It could
Really thinking about
Like did we make fun of Alex
For saying that like we misusing to toe.
I was trying to say
Who cares
I think so are you else other than us would be paying attention and I've used dystopic
Yeah I would imagine
It's come out of our mouths
Prefer to dystopian I think people proper like more accepted version but
It's not that just hoping
Isn't
A word that you can use dystopian very elitist
I don't like it
That's the way I roll buddy you and Alex
Going to hang out
And a hot tub and talk about it sounds good
So grouchy
Avatar
Disturbed
The Trump voters don't want the vaccine
Fauci says it's so disturbing the Trump voters
Skeptical
An experimental mRNA vaccine
Why would you be skeptical let me just reading somebody's headlines again
Let me just read you some of the things I lie about
Suspense AstraZeneca mRNA vaccine
And people being paralyzed and having Strokes
I think it's okay to be skeptical about a vaccine that was developed as
Quickly as these ones were
That's fine
When you find yourself feeling skeptical the appropriate things
To do is to look into the source of your skepticism and see if you can resolve that
Skepticism
Chronixx
Really healthy
And whenever possible you should transfer your skepticism in the direction
A finding a concrete position
If you can
This is kind of what I killed
Socrates are just sick of that guy being annoying
The kind of sleight-of-hand that Alex likes
To use a lot
When he's actually advancing a pointlessly and aggressively anti-vax position he hides behind the illusion
Just being scrapped
Bad to be skeptical
What are you pushing narratives to his audience by various
Victims of gun violence are actors in the hole
Events were staged as an excuse to take his gun
He's actually telling his audio
Cold on it
He hides behind the illusion
Questions that examining things from Alside
What's wrong with asking questions
Alex does this because on some level
He knows that is bulshit doesn't stand up to adults
Scrutiny so the only way for it to fly at all is for him to preemptively give up on his own narrative
As opposed to be forced
Defend them
It's easy to criticize him
But it's
Very hard to criticize being skeptical or asking Quest
Topic
Dwight plays the game that you.
Alex is lying about Marvin Hagler and he doesn't even have a
Conspiracy timeline of Hank Aaron's death rate
Now I see that other issue in Germany
They are just a temporarily halting the rollout of the AstraZeneca vaccine quote
Over a small number of blood clot
Concerns
There were people in Germany who ended up with blood clots but there were a couple cases reported in Denmark and Norway
To Germany decided to halt
Precaution
There has been
37 reported cases of blood clotting
The population of over 17 million people in the world who received the AstraZeneca vaccine
According to the company quote there is no evidence the vaccine
Gary's an increase risk
Klotz
It's entirely possible that number of people out of 17 million would have gotten them anyway
Yeah
Italy halted to use the vaccine as well quote
As a precaution and temporarily after there was concerns that one man in the country died after getting
The shot but
Clear that the death is related
The vaccine
This is a dishonest countries being hyper
Precautious about the vaccine rollout in it isn't it
Any evidence that it's killing anyone or everyone or the back
Dangerous
When I brought up Alex's fake
Titanfall skepticism
It's
To realize that these are the first three stories
He said he comes up with two.
Justify that skepticism about the vaccine
This is bad work
Answer level of s*** that he's bringing to the table
He'll be wise for everyone to recognize that Alex has not
Succeeded in justifying his skeptical position
His opposition to the vaccine doesn't rest on facts and reality
It exists
In spite
Yeah I was
Thinking about it is you know like
This vaccine was
Develop so fast
Part of the reason that we are
Article about it
Is because
Almost
Utopia
You know it's almost like
How how
Remarkable
That far but how quickly we didn't suggest like
How quickly
Can we do it
Is there a situation has a lot of potential is there a situation in a few years where we can manufacture vac
Seems almost
Instantly you know like
That's the type of s*** that is almost
Too-good-to-be-true
I told the skepticism there is comes from a place of
Yeah Wonder
I don't
Think I don't
Think that beating
Taking a bath
Bye
Circumstance
Pictures of the world
Particularly you know the life series been so
Insane and adjustments are so complicated and difficult they do to people that had to make
But I think that
You can't have reaction
Is that is in some ways skeptical whether it's
Worry anxiety Bass
He's all based whatever but you do have resources that you can go
To explore that skepticism in resolve
And if you behave like Alex does Synthroid stupid headlines that mean nothing
I do take into context the actual circumstances
Then what you're going to do is
You're going to end up staying in that skeptical place
Or retreating into a dumb position
That was where Alex wanted you to begin with
It's not it's not healthy
It's also a little hard to believe that
We can manufacture vaccine soak
Quickly
At the same time as
Half of Republican men believe in witches causing our problem right so that's a little bit weird
It's hard to believe but that's because we have human breast
And we can't believe it also
Because we have
So Alex referenced earlier
The program Ensure
You talk about Oblivion again
No talk about that one where Will Smith fights Orcs or something
You're the one the one where it like it's the last guy on earth I Am Legend
Works in a different one now
That's technically vampire
Is it
Are they actually coming from the original the bad guy
What's the review
The evil about
After Earth was at the other one reason space I don't know I think I'm only going to watch movies that either Vince
Price was in or a remix of Wild Wild West
Will Smith movies
That's true here come
The Men in Black
Galaxy Defender absolutely
No it's not
First one
Play a clip
Addictive
Is it from Pocahontas
James Cameron film
How much are Oso it is
Chose
The planet Earth in a hundred years or so
And where the atmosphere is so toxic we've all got to wear these face mask
You go back
Can you see the film Blade Runner
Same motif
Dark-sky
Always raining
Flooded city dystopia
But that was what was going to happen
Alia Bhatt oceanfront property
20 years ago
Bill Clinton
Obama by the oceanfront property
10 years ago
And of course the fees aren't going up
It's all lies
They show you a polar bear
What does cob on Ice Flow
Darling they can't swim
They can swim 300 miles at Hunt
Whale and seal on those
Anybody can go read the Wikipedia entry on them
Wow it is pathetic and on brand
The Wikipedia page on polar bears
Through some kind of dumb point about climate change
The illustration that they classic picture of a polar bear and Cub on a nice
Flow is
I can't swim
Mixtapes
When the ice receives the polar bear loses its ability to hunt
Polar bears don't just hunt swimming around in the water they had from the edge of ice protruding into water
Where are they
Can catch fish
As ice disappears or becomes less stable they have
Cross longer distances or be left
To try and Fish on the shore
Do they last
Plentiful area
The result of this is that we are likely to
To see collapsing polar bear populations of enough to distance
Future if ice continues
Alex has one image that he thinks we can mock
Better Counterpoint all climate change arguments but in reality it's a strawman he's built so he can win a fake argument
As for people buying oceanfront property I don't know if they did or did not do that but if they did who cares
Not all property near the ocean is in
Intrinsically
High risk due to Rising
Nothing means
Also one big
Problem with Alex's idea but Avatar being pre-programming
To wear masks
Cubans don't
Have to wear masks on Earth in that movie they wear masks on Pandora because I can't breathe the air on that planet
Happen I don't remember Earth being very important in that movie
Beginning a little bit on Earth
Some people do wear masks and appears to be like
Because of pollution but not everybody is wearing masks
The only only some people and
In the scenes where they're inside a place everyone doesn't a mastodon has nothing to do really
Fokuslah PS work
Asian cultures have had a mask wearing as more except
People more acceptable as I totally normal thing
Prolong
Sometime
Probably for Avatar
So f*** off
I don't need this
Yeah but like
You remember of people wearing masks
Then Avatar is on Pandora
Because I can't breathe
Also
Are we going to like
Remote into genetically modified created my other question is like it what is not
Predictive programming about that movie in what
How does that work
Get to join the noble Navi
Uplifting message
Life entirely
Think
I think this might be convenient Sprouts we found a scene in the movie where some people had faced
God decided this is predictive programming and decided to ignore the rest
Talk about blade
So Alex gets to take
Some calls here at the end of this this episode here on the 15th
And this is one color that he takes you talk so for a very long time
And there's some
Very serious problem
Forms of what he's bringing
To the table
Patriot doctor in Missouri
Works at nursing home and
Mister, don't covid vaccine
Colin Dexter holding
Pieology
Emoji
Evanescence
Attorney Kirsch I work in nursing homes
21 patients live identify
I don't have
Died with a
In 48 hours
Getting either the first
As vaccine
AstraZeneca
I'm a geriatrician
They are not calling it
Vaccine-related incident because
CVS is the ones that are out
CVS at the contract
There's one
Giant
Hole in the Sky story
There's that there's no way that is Paige
Could be dying after getting the AstraZeneca vaccine
Because that vaccine is not approved for use in the United
It's still in Phase 3 clinical trials and do the US has purchased a lot of doses of the vaccine
It's not looking like we're going to be able to get approval to begin using them until spring
It's pretty embarrassing for Alex to not even know what vaccines are approved for use in the United States
But with his alleged doctor to get that
Very critical.
Detail Ron
F****** disqualify
I don't even think I don't think the key is actually a doctor
He starts talking and like
He just gets into like Infowars talking
Complaints about
The dangers of vaccines
Music
I'm not going to take you seriously
I mean I don't know I guess I'll see
Take you as seriously as you're taking
Claim that your patients are on the AstraZeneca vaccine
Because not seriously at all go fuc
Sometimes
I halfway think
Some of these guys are
Roleplay
This is this is what I should say because people need to get
Disinformation
But I'm not actually a geriatrician but it's
The radio on Infowars so f*** it
I'll just say that I'm weigh in on
Medicine in 48 of my patients
You can't take
United States
Exactly so f*** yourself doctor
Anyway so we get to the 16th
And Alex
Interesting Lee doesn't talk anymore about how he is now the leader of the anointed leader of the Patriots
Don't need to worry about that too much
Storyline drops off
Yeah
But look man booster going to kill everyone
Ina year 6 years 10 years
Every person is different
And then they'll just playmat it's something else causing it
It's called a soft
Kill weapon
Silent weapons
For quiet Wars
Pentagon papers on that if you'd like to go
Look that up but here's the Wall Street Journal
Last year looking forward
To the end of humanity
Humanity will be exterminated
Good loving thing
Silent weapons for quiet Wars is completely fraudulent document those pushed by Bill Cooper and
Book Behold a Pale Horse
We covered it in great detail on episode 381 of our show so if you'd like to hear more about why that's bulshit
And why it's embarrassing for Alex be referencing it as a real
Pentagon document
Hey go ahead give that episode of spin
The article that Alex is referring to the looking forward to the end of humanity that doesn't discuss how great it'll be when Humanity isn't around
It's an easy misrepresent
Patient to make of the headline but the text of the editorial article doesn't say with Alex
To telling his audience that does
The essential game that Alex plays as to make a really scary claims that attempt
Defendant by pointed to evidence of that
Pure does support the argument
What is actually misrepresented Oregon
Completely fake
Thing
You can sum up most of his career just with that one
Staff
Yeah you know
Is it possible for things to be
Great
After
The only people to invent the word great
Argon
I'm not sure what I have I'm not trying to follow you but you if you Manatee has
Gone extinct
There's no consciousness
To reflect upon the quality of
Thanks
What about that thing
Counterpoint
Octopus predict soccer
Oh yeah but I bet the octopus feels in different you know it's not great
Octopuses just like it's really okta
Two p**** right now
All right right
I don't know what that octopus would think about this but I do think that Alex
Might be trying to Launch
A chain email
I got really can't
Used listening to Mescalero
In my chair like
What are you talkin about
What is there
Let me read you this first
Yesterday
And since I didn't cover that submitted you sent it to a bunch of national talk show host
And so
One great talk-show Salma steal this from
Because it's the truth
Irishman 1776
In the video I did Sunday
Okay I got to stop right there.
Because like I'm listening to this and I'm like
Irishman 1776 wrote this and you're sending it to
Your contact in the media so commenter on your website wrote something
Okay that's the state of play where at
Marvelous Marvin Hagler dying
Is Oregon's liquefying
Sadly one day after he took
MRNA
So we can put up the live show feed name of the broadcast today
It's on infowars.com live
Show Caesar.
Politico celebrates end of humanity
Total sterilization
I-20 45
Wow that's why the headline
Top scientist women
Courtney Chad
Holdahl covid vaccines immediately
Uncontrollable monster
Quote will be Unleashed
Let's go ahead
The Irishman
1776 set
Call public information
Prime aphasia
I'm going to post what he said
In the live show feed of the broadcast today we're Politico is celebrating the end of humanity so you
Ensure this
One of the crew saw this this morning and said you know
I'm going to give this to my family
What would happen if you want the infowars.com and copied it
I actually
Globalist
Extermination
If you just take what the Irish
Monroe
Iris
Refuse
To listen
To first-hand information
Tim from Irishman 7
And we'll get to that
The first just a long and short of this isn't celebrating infertility in the end of people being able to reproduce
Exacerbated interview with Doctor Who
Is theorizing
That we are running into
Fertility problem
In the next couple decades
Add some chemicals
Send the answer to that I guess
Probably be regulation of
Business industry by-product
Regulate
Murder
So the problem with the signing these kinds of things like Alex is doing to Anonymous screen names as I have no idea you Irishman
17 seven
26 is
I don't know if he's the same person who uses that screen name on Reddit
If you guys that he posted this message two years ago in an oklahoma-based Reddit board
I'm 22 and I'm trying to lose my virginity ladies hit me up
Obviously you need to be 18 or older
Aside from that I don't care about age
I don't care about race or looks
I don't care about your marital status
No idea if that's the same guy or he ended up losing their virginity but you can see the problem here
Silly debaser reporting on Anonymous internet,
Also if this is really funny to see Alex trying to get this comment on his website sent out to people like Tucker Carlson and make it into a jvm
Email your grandparents consent to you
Because the user
The 1776 Irishman
Didn't write it
If you Google the tech
Text with this post
You will find that Irishman 7
1976 is just reposting a meme
But I can find being posted on Facebook as early as at least January 30th
I look around a little more and I found
Exact text
The Irishman
On January 15th
There's a number of responses to her tweet indicating that this was a message that have been circulating previously on WhatsApp
And Pooja had just copied and pasted it from there
This is an old anti-vax meme that Alex didn't bother to look into and it's pretending is the work of some sagely analysis 21
One of those Anonymous viewers
Conducted
Is outrageously sad whether or not this is the same guy trying to get laid on Reddit
Also the claims in the meme
It better not be David R
I'm disappointed that's that
Level on showing up at the
The capital dad
So if you're listening might be Patrick McMahon
The meme and it's basically just like if I get back to Republic
Government
Alex is like yeah you got a
You got a phuc
Can get this out there cuz we're going to win
Take this live segment later
The page
And the Washoe feed
You can share this video
Breakdown
I suggest you just share the text of it
Infowars.com
Dot-com in the live feed
Everyone you know
Okay
On Thursday morning
Free shipping storewide will end
Or perhaps synergistic
Oh God
Separately Irishman 1776
Posted a dumb Meme and my comment section we're going to start a chain email about it send it along
I remember seeing
Wyndham chain email seem to reduce or call if I don't send this to 10 people I will die
You just sleep
How to resolve an email now
Yes it has become a chain meme
Pokemon evolution
Do something
He said on the previous episode
Which is that
Many people on the left are just useful idiot
You two are destroying their lives haha
And I feel like
I'm more looking
To apply that
To Alex himself
Yeah I think about something you said on the previous episode and that is that all the bigwigs
Exam the higher-ups in the Auntie globalist world
I can't believe that you
Yuiri communication with Irishman 7070r how do you know so much
Can you imagine how are you right about everything
Read about Irishman 1770
Leaders listen to Alex's show near Dumbo
That's because it what did Putin doesn't have the time to go through Infowars comments
Alex filter that fit a lot of people
It's tough to listen to Infowars without our filter shorter and I totally understand that
I I get it
And I think Alex could extra filter for his own, I don't think I could handle his comments
That's that would be too toxic
How to do a show where he takes all the Nazi comments
But it wouldn't be much that would be one comment from Irish band 17
Give me a bunch of people that are just being like reposting of memes
Anyway Alex has found a new operation
That proves
Joe Biden does what he's told it's
Rockefellers it's the Rothschild
If the globalist
Bill Gates
Works directly under the Rockefeller Brothers Foundation
I thought he was on the couch
What's event 201
Was
Operation
Crimson contagion which I will cover
Tomorrow
It's just so complex so important
Give me the folder on Crimson contagion or make sure
Forget that tomorrow because that's so critical
One of my favorite things in the world is things that are so important
Prince them but have to resist to getting into them until tomorrow
Seems like he's really thick
Seriously
Crimson contagion was a real thing
Here's a series of exercises undertaken by the Trump Department of Health and Human Services
Took place between January and August
New York Times reported on the exercises last March
In a conversation
For Trump and his administration dropped
The ball in terms of dealing with the novel Coronavirus
There was a report that was completed in
In October 2019 and reading it is really depressing
Thing today
This report based on an exercise testing response
Let's do a novel influenza outbreak
He's full of lessons we learned after the coronavirus outbreak
Things like a quote
Currently there are Inns
Sufficient funding sources designated for the federal government to use in response to severe influenza pandemic
Geico quote
State and federal entities identified challenges in implementing remote work
Telework policies
As a Workforce protection measure quote
The current medical countermeasures supply chain in production capacity cannot meet the demands imposed
Buy Nations during global
Influenza pandemic
This is
This is the result of living in both a week and develop a vaccine in six months and a
We Believe witches are causing our problem Circle
All of our scientists in professional people were like
Here are the problems will face in a pandemic guess and they were like what if instead he was nothing
What if we get rid of all the witch
Yeah what if you take zinc
So this report also highlighted that exercise participants were confused about which organization
Find local or federal took the lead in the case of an outbreak which is
Boy I sure f****** was everybody whenever the federal government decided to kill us
This document is a really huge problem for someone like Alex because it basically demonstrate to the Trump Health and Human Services Department
Was asleep at the wheel when it came to implementing the changes
Recommended by the sex
Precise
They did this study that revealed things that were clearly a problem then
Trump did nothing
Public paid for it
Basically at this exercise is a strong indicator that
Efficient
Effective incompetent government
We could have avoided so much of the pain and misery that's comfort covid-19
This is something that was reported on over a year ago in the mainstream media but I guess Alex
Just heard about it
He's got to come out and do some spin
Because it's so clearly shows the Trump's government had every reason to be aware
Aware some of the difficulties would be in the case of a pandemic
I'll test it make this exercise itself part of the globalist
Conspiracy in the plot totally
Alex claims to be tomorrow's news today but in reality he's last year's spin being half-assed
Tomorrow
I'm really proud of that line
Yeah I know you you delivered it with
Aplomb then
I could hit a little bit harder but
We can say we can do to text
Yeah it's just it's a it's a bummer
I remember when that report was first out
Last year
I remember reading about it
I don't remember that name
Although quite catchy
Yeah sure we'll be hearing
Crimson contagion quite a bit
From Alex
Yeah I'd kind of forgotten about some of the findings
Of it and how
However like a year ago I think a lot of it would have felt
Different
Then it does now tell her
Because I don't think that we would have realized how weary learned all this
I just March 2020
One thing that is
Is a little bit f****** me up about
How we we deal with this as we do talk a lot about
Rightfully all of the
The people that
The Trump Administration has
To death
All the people that have been
Crippled by the response
And at the same time
We don't talk about
It's also their fault that we were trapped inside for a fuk
Second-year
Hear of everyone's life was taken
Yeah
Around the f****** world
Because nobody could f****** respond to this like
Goddamn adult
And it's very fresh
Yeah it's very frustrating
It is
Yeah I'm with you
Anyway because it's such a damning piece of evidence
The effectiveness of the
Proper response
Scott King
It's part of the
Revealing their plans
So Alec
Talking about those big new Brzezinski
I didn't know this
Carolee
Zbigniew Brzezinski of the speech one-time-use like kill everyone
That would be an interesting thing for Brazil
Surprising new one I was surprised to hear that was a new one
Until there's a rock in the sixties going
We need to sterilize people
That's actually just talking about like a person
Control
So strong
Once you remove the sexual organs it's Bass
Just The Kilt
That's why
Thirsty afar instead
There's
Easier instead of
Propagandizing a million people
We have passed the point
Now this time
Who killed them
Work
Inoculation
Know your enemy
You know I just quoted
Joyce it would be good
You will not win this fight
Only killing
Then we're just going to go okay to go okay
So if I'm to understand
Amman famous
Really
Good writing
Speaking and
Diplomatic
Language
Just went to
To Canada one time was like
Look we got to kill everybody
Second yeah it is a silly
Although it is fun
And one of the things I think is most revealing about a clip like that is like know your enemy like no no your fake anime
This is not real
I'm not going to go to Bedford zbigniew Brzezinski or any of like
Any specifics about his foreign policy but I'm looking at this claim
Alex is making
The quote is real I'm a part of the quote Israel
There's a short clip of him again
Passed around a lot where you guys quote
In earlier times it was
Easier to control a million people literally was easier to control a million people
Even physically To Kill A Milli
People
Today it's infinitely easier to kill a million people than to control a million people you mean he's describing perhaps
Humanity's ability to drop a giant bomb on 180
It was hard to find a full transcript of the speech or any concrete citations of what else was said
And I'm certain
From the jump
Is making all this s*** up
What percentage of saying here's kind of just
True like weapons development have been such ever the past hundred years that it's
Technically easier
How to kill a million people than it is to control them
That's descriptively accurate
I can see no indication from that clip
Bucket passed around
But he's saying that it's good to go
Controller kill people
It's where the disagreement with Alex comes in the drink seem like this has any moral
Indication Tri-Rail
So this quote comes from a November 17th 2008 speech at the Chatham House
The rest of the clip that goes around the
Can find has to do with the fact that there was a political Awakening happening around the world so
I found it interesting that when I was looking around the next thing I found was a December 16th 2008 op-ed
Represents get published in the New York Times titled quote
Global political Awakening Shore
The article is basically making the argument that the US
Leadership role in the world
Severely tarnished by things like the Iraq War
And Obama was coming into office
Very serious need to recover International legitimacy
Seems to happen after a lot of brezza
Certain
Turn might snap the compounded things
Was that two countries like China Japan and India were taking a more prominent role in the global stage
Bruzdzinski had this to say
In this dynamically changing world
The crisis of American leadership could be
Become the crisis of global stability
Yeah in the foreseeable future no state or combination of states
Can replace the linchpin Rural America plays
In the International System
Without us
Recovery there will be no Global recovery
The only alternative to a
Constructive American role
Is global chaos
The New York Times op-ed was in
Complete text of the speech but
The full version was published in the January 2009 Edition
Of the journal International affairs
If you read the quote and its full context
The actual article
What percent ski is talking about is
The ending of American colonialism
Which is the need for which
Is demonstrated by the Iraq War
Again another one of those lessons that we knew
Before we did the thing
These major world powers new and old also face a novel reality
Wobbly Sawadee of their military might is greater than ever their capacity to impose control over the politically awaken Bass
Answers of the world
Is that a historic low
To put it bluntly in earlier times it was easier to
Control 1 million people than to physically kill 1 million people
Today it's infinitely easier to kill 1 million people then
Control 1 million people
Bears directly on the use of
Woodforest particularly by societies that are culturally alien
Even if technical
Technologically Superior
As a result in the current post-colonial ERA
It is too costly to undertake colonial wars
That is a reality some recent American policymakers failed to assimilate to America's debt
It's very clear that the context of what he saying has to do
With the
The gaps
Bush bush War policy
To 2% Seidel Tendencies of far-right in all countries
Pierzynski in that article or in that speech
The transcript of the article
I'm sorry
To pretend that
You saying is
It used to be easier to
Control a million people than it was to kill them now it's easier to kill them to eat
Yeah that's outrageous I mean I was just making s*** up
The end know your enemy yeah the fake one that I'm going to sell it
Cuz if you knew the real one you would be like oh
No I think I'll
What's my Pete my aunt
And also the big new Brzezinski had some ideas that you should take your shoe with it but
Difficult for you to wrestle with
Some of the interconnected realities that the big new Brzezinski was dealing with Alex's pretending
Someone might say that if you were above
The two party system
Famously opposed to the Iraq War if I remember correctly right
Alex was opposed to the Iraq War
Yeah yeah
So
Seems like
You would be like yeah I'm glad that even people on the left
Paradigm
Are like the Iraq war is bad
If you were above the two
Party system is not it's all an act
Yeah and I don't think he's ever actually even read that full
Why would he
The memes of the context
And the rest of the context for Alex is a dumb impression
Also we must kill them it's time to move and Kayla Bieber
Yep so it's so stupid like and then claiming that the direct quote
F*** off
Yeah
Recite abusive to the audience
It doesn't give them the ability to
Actually choose
Who they liked and disliked in the world when you create completely false portraits
Love your enemies
Because you want to scare them and keep them
Keep them in your in your side
I don't want these people to have a choice
Llavero
So Jordans
We got a guest
This guy that I haven't heard of before I haven't seen him stew Peters stupid and so I looked him up
I thought his name was spelled St Peters
Can't I look that guy up
Apparently there's like a broadcaster in the UK who got in trouble for
Beck's making some offensive comments about black lives matter
I understand correctly now I know it requires
3 to have a pattern but I am beginning to suspect
Suspect that all stupid eaters are bad
I mean
I know of two
Peter's in Oradea
But these two are not
They're not helping your team if there are I need to know now you need to
To break the pattern of 3
Cuz once we get 2/3 I'm going to then assume all Stu Peters from now on
Haha people
So stupid as not stupendous
Shut up
I like like how I told you to shut up when you said nothing
Stu Peters is on Anza
This guy's a s******* put like I found this clip really interesting
Because he is like
If he's auditioning for a job with Infowars
He nailed
Okay so many buzzwords
If I ran out of time and I Was preparing this episode
But I was legit going to make
Go-karts
I got bingo
He's hitting them all legitimate Lee said in the middle of this clip when I was listen to episode I got to go
Did you need to use the
The free space or did you get home now okay
Due process here is not something
The new Wok
America
Condemnation
Demasculinization
Immunization the neutering the castration of law enforcement officers
All over the place
Is no longer a
Policing is a
Leftists
Communist
Terry and Faye
Basically ignores you come from
Is the new nazi-style brownshirts
Oh God I got to cross the road
Written all over him
And then it turns out that he didn't got to do a little bit of white victimhood I'm like Alice's writing
The contract right now
During his other interviews Alex is eating a cheeseburger
Saying buzzwords
Okay we are legalizing crime in the United
Baxter's
Anybody
Go to work
If you are a y
You are deaf
.
Because there is not
Anybody
The higher ranks of law enforcement or the government
All these institutions that we were raised Alex
These are the people that we can try
The ones that are coming after you
I don't like whites
Anymore and everything but now we just
Yeah I think
Quickly when I hear someone who's got this
Verbal pattern guy who throws around buzzwords like he does
This guy a guy who's
I need the whole reason he's on is to talk about the Floyd trial
Derek Chauvin
And trial
Do you know what this is
Is that that's what is the neutering of the police shouldn't have your Shake Shack
Benno bring up something like
Straight God-fearing
Conservatives are heading for a gulag of my calf
I got to go man
I can't stand
These people
Because
This is the type of s*** where you're like
1 in a certain sense this is a benchmark of the progress of the conservative right
Because you could grab that again
Exact dude
Put them in the SEC
I need say the exact same s***
But it be
More Explorer
Take them put them in the 30
He be saying the exact same s***
But even more explicit than the 60
And then he's a Democrat
You know that's what this guy is
I know this guy every. Of American History go away
Yeah we're leaving you behind I'm not up to speed
The table
Actually had a really complicated sort of experience
Trying to figure out like
This guy's deal
Used to be a bounty hunter
And so I was like man you should just ate a bounty hunter like I don't want you to be a bounty hunter
I don't want you to be a pundit
Nor Bounty Hunter
Two weeks ago he was about to Hunter
Great data entry as a medium ground
Turns out if you listen to this clip careful he doesn't know much about data
The level of gaslighting has reached
Mad Hatter levels here
Well some of those numbers
I don't have
Exact
Debate numbers
Chasing fugitives
Weeks ago
After 18 years of doing
You know in writing and
Sufficient numbers to understand
What's really going on
Every single community
We're doing a
People taking people to jail
People of color with blacks
You know I don't know why that is
Last year
Look at the cops and black people
9 unarmed black people
Cops last year
White unarmed
People
Every single year
Question is what is the blue eyes matter
So I can sort this out for us to really fast if he's actually interested
The reason more cops are shot each year than unarmed black people is
Because they're cops
And the job comes with the heightened likelihood of
Encountering criminals with gun
It's not good the cops are shot but it's also an understandable aspect of that line of work
An element that they don't share with
People who happen to be black and unarmed
Ask for the discrepancy between 9 unarmed black people and 19 unarmed white people being killed by cops last year
This is another one
Really super easy to sort out
I have no idea if his numbers are even accurate but let's assume for the sake of argument that they are cuz that's what he's bringing to the table
According to the US Census Data
In 2019 the most recent numbers that he could find the u.s. population
60.1% White
+ 12
5% black
Assuming Stu's numbers are correct
Even though there were more total white people who are shot by cops
Still wildly
It wouldn't be in terms of
The population sizes
If a country where 50% light in
In 50% black then his numbers might mean something
But the demographics don't look like that it is numbers are nothing more than props
He's using to mask the underlying racism of his actual argument
The thrust of this and the main point is that we shouldn't
Be concerned about police killing unarmed black people
Can I find that offensive
We should care about police killing people regardless of other variables involved
Even stuzo numbers
Illustrate there's a much higher likelihood
Of an unarmed black person being killed by police
Basically this clip
The perfect encapsulation but how I feel about Stu Peters
He's either too stupid to know that the statues using are meaningless
Understands exactly what he's doing and he's trying to minimize
Issues related to racing
Policing
If he's been sloppy with something like that
Fury has something to do with his primary field of expertise
Donkey with a bounty hunter
Floppy there
I'm not going to listen to him on any topic that he's not
Conceivably an expert at like
I want to know what the
This guy takes about covid-19
Yeah you know I was
I've never wondered why it is bounty hunters aren't in charge of things
But I think there's a good reason
You don't support the reign of King dog
Just don't
Bounty hunters should really be in charge of
That look I love Cowboy Bebop
I think bounty-hunting on mccreight
That's great fantastic
They do run things though I'm aware of
Since I listen to this interview this guy
Bounty Hunter
Spike Spiegel
Jet-black I do a valentine I don't know any of these people radical Edward and
I'm talking about real life
Oh okay
Took this dog and this guy both of them have stories
About
Crossing the border and trying
To kidnap somebody dog did that and then this guy was telling story
Show about how you got in trouble for going to Mexico to FedEx
Easter dates
Bounty Hunter why do I have
To pay attention to international law
I am Batman
Wherever I want
Want to solve crime
Most of his interview
This annoying of a voice
You disqualify yourself that hard
On stats
I don't even really care
And
And literally everything you say is just a giant racist dog whistle
Yes yeah
And we have
A return
On podcast
Beaver return
But somebody we haven't seen a little bit while cat little bit while
We got the health Ranger
Mike Adams
He has a story
About
A guy who
Interesting perspective I don't fully understand it myself
And it would be kind of
Silly for me to try to
Pontificate about it
But it's easy
A guy who's trying to make an argument that
A vaccine works on individual levels
But there may be some negative consequences
From applying them broadly across the population
When there's already an outbreak
Brett Sher
As I understand that they are
Putting forth
Mike Adams takes that and now is a new tip
OKC Thunder new tip
Is it under for Humanity
No it's really really over vanity
Can we do
Of course it's which is
Boost your immune function make sure you have
Good nutrition
Get plenty of rest
Void
Vaccinated people
Because they are the virus
They are the mutant
Factory
Educate the people around you so that they
Before they run over and tried
How to get vaccinated
Yourself
Person
You are soccer
Vaccine
Suicide
Wow
That's that's something
I mean you could have called it back
Vaccine
You could
Yeah I think that's a
The tongue a lot better
Fixies are rapper
Even Alex can invent words that already existed
This is this is kind of interesting to me because it's like okay this is evolve
GolfNow and that might avoid anyone who's been
How do you get away with it you said it's over for Humanity now you're gone
The idea that he's trying to put forth
What is that
People who get vaccinated will
End up causing mutations your virus and then they will give you
They're the incubators for a whole new generation of murder
You got to avoid turn into like
I don't know
I don't know how
Many people take any of this seriously
But
Assuming that there are like
You've got to think that this is
This would lead to communist
Yeah you have to isolate yourself
People
Like I don't know they're really mad about
The idea that international travel Comfort countries might require
Proof of vaccination
Have to create communities were proof of non vaccination is the only way you can get it seems so and if they have it
Outbreak in those communities
Yeah
I don't this is
Just dumb
I don't know anyway these guys have
Bad solutions to imaginary problem
Wednesday May.
But I think that the function of this narrative
In terms of the the larger sphere of Infowars talking
Is I think that they recognize
Is that historically
Will you see an outbreak
Vaccine-preventable conditions
And non-vaccinated community
A lot of times anti-vax
Clusters chair
End up having
A resurgence
Things that are prevented
Measles became a problem
I think that they recognize that there is a
Decent chance
That
Should
Covid
Stop being a
No problem due to widespread vaccination that they'll end up
Being blamed
Because they don't want to get vaccinated until they have to create a new explanation for it and it's vaccinated people
Have created
Mutant
Things within their body
Guess what happened
10 people are going to come to your house
Vaccinate
Gunpoint and not only that I want Daleks
Today
Race war also
I got bingo I was still closed. From this
Could be much could be a year
Medical doctors and scientists
They're going to blame us there already are you going to live with us
It doesn't matter
The mask
Second the second one
And then say that this
Surprise
Vaccinations
Point they will be able to have the
The political power
To unleash now the
Military
Insta will Kateri
Confiscating your guns
Go ahead 90
I got 92nd
To stop rewarding restore Medical
Sound bites only know complicated plans
Definitely not anything with nuance
Josh it's over for you
Why the race war got thrown in their accessories a preoccupation of these pigs out there race war in there
Yammy
Just feels like a preemptive
Narrative building fourth possibility
Gated communities
So if I understand correctly so far what we're dealing with
Is Alex Jones as the only person you can trust
You need to avoid all vaccinated people would probably means you guys need to get together in a communist
And a race war is obviously coming haha
So explain to me how different Alex is from Charles
Speak
Well Charles Manson never inspired people do storms
The capital
No that's true there's that
Yeah
I don't I don't know
They are both friends with musicians
Billy corgan's been on Infowars
Totally
Alex hasn't carb
Swastika
That's true
True
Now we haven't seen him with his I wouldn't look I haven't seen him naked I'm not saying he hasn't carved just wants to cuss
It's interesting
Everett proof
Evidence
Something like that
Mike Adams
Now is predicting
Hundreds of Millions
Will be dead
Because of the vaccine do not because of covid
And you got to lose you don't get to
You just got to say goodbye to you and your family right
All the things you just mentioned
Take care of your health
Avoid at all costs
And avoid other people who are vaccinated
We've got to continue to build out our independent
Continue to expand our
Mainstream media
Is collapsing in terms of its viewership
Viewing independent truth media even though the censorship is
It has never been worse
We are winning
To those people who are willing to live
Those who want to commit suicide and die
Any longer
Within the bass
Wave goodbye to those
People cuz many of those people millions or even hundreds of millions make.
The survivors
Educate inform internet
That's how we can rebuild Society after
Vaccine
Is Unleashed
It's a vaccine
Holocaust absolutely
Maybe after
More people
We don't know
Thousands of times the people that died in the Holocaust
Is in a billion
Well I mean unless you believe the Holocaust
Didn't happen
Yeah I guess I got to take Mike's temperature on that talk about that
The number from the home.
This is this
Dramatic it is what though it's almost to the one-year anniversary of it's over for Humanity so it's a
So every year we Humanity around March
Beware the Ides of March
Yeah and then in a couple months Alex and Michael have a fight about something and I'll disappear for a few months back up
At to Adams as dramatic as ever
God it's just
He seems like
Teenager
It really seems like
Somebody going through puberty
Like
Feels like he's out of
Control with his own feelings
Yeah or something
Just feel childish the way
Communicate
Ya know it
It's insane
It's insane and it's insane the people allow this
A lot like people listen to this
And don't go like
You said it was going to be over for Humanity last year this is Rerun
But also the narrative has shifted so many times since then maybe almost even impossible to keep
Keep track of what it is
It's going to kill you exactly
How it's going to play out but
Don't forget that they've been
Consistent
It's important that we build our immune system
Separately the Infowars store as well as Mike Adams the health Ranger sell things that can boost your immune
Quote unquote
He's selling like horse dewormer with me trying to push horse
Dewormer
Something you do back
Bleach dude
Right
Can you shoot
Alcohol ademola
Have yourself a fun time
Guest
Before we get out of here
And it's
Stroud's
Stew's are becoming universally bad
Yeah it's a bad day for students
I'm going to have to get rid of that dish on my from my diet so bad
Yeah I would say that Stuart's interviewees largely
The same as the stuff that we talked about when he was on his Harrison
Smith choa so there's not really all that much
Have to go over but I do think it's really interesting
First thing this way that Alex is trying to engage
With him where
He simultaneously wants to like really talk about how we should have a Revolutionary War
Really want the response
Stability of having said those things
Look I don't want to get into a gate of gate a circumstance all over here like
Degree away from the people who were in the capital
I kind of am too but maybe I wasn't in a group chat
RICO case was brought against you girls who
They're bunch of the Bill of Rights and Constitution
I decide you're going to confiscate the guns
Inoculation the borders are wide open
Yes by any historical yardstick
We have every right to declare
7076 part 2
I just instinctively look at
Realize how they set this up politically
Now they want a civil war so China can take over
Governors of the political system
Stop this you may be right
There's no way to fix it or is there a way to fix
Claiming you on violence they're claiming you on offense
That's not the man I know
But at the same time if we're attacked
Pass the Declaration of Independence
I don't want that
I do the same thing they did
How do you even respond
To that
Question
Gramble
Hey so it's cool that we kill everybody I'm not saying we should kill everybody but it's cool that we kill everybody right
Clip of Alex was just multiple times saying we have every Justice
Application for starting a Revolutionary War
Talking to government what the f*** Governors you talk
Dr. DeSantis
He would be a top
Anti-global
He would be someone
Who is any Governor will talk to Alex
I would suspect
It might be he's on he's on the shortlist
It's just justifications for why a revolutionary war inoffensive violence could be set off which is actually offensive
Respond to that
If you think there's no like
Yes yeah bro no
Super Broly
Yeah he's just like a a dudas walk-in take selfie
Yeah the capital of 26
I'm not going to let him hang out to dry
I just
It's so weird to
Broadcast
Your
Extemporaneous fantasies about murdering
That's a strange I would hope
You would keep that one quiet if you were like
I fantasize about murdering people all the time
So much so that I can
Cannot go several hours without talking about
You can
You keep those are ours off air
We'll see this is where we get back to what I was saying at the
Beginning
Like that tone that Alex has where either coming back from
Like a week being gone
Any sleepy
I got to like I'm going to go to a special report
That's weird
Yeah but it's not weird for Ally
No
Being so obsessed with wanting to talk about your murder fantasies radio show is weird
Yeah
His show is so stupid
And
But that's just what this is
Yeah it's really it's really f***** up
That
There
Murder fantasies
Have gone so far from the original ones that we used to listen to where they're like
If somebody tried to kill my family I'd
Get to shoot them bunch of time
Which I don't want to do
I talked about doing it all the time if I don't want a gun
Is will rise up or whatever people and that's what we have to do
The point of justification for all of this they're attacking us with bio-weapon
Yeah
It's irresponsible
T i means I guess
I feel good
Did Alex is back where he belongs in that chair
He doesn't belong in a grocery
Tree store unless it
Was locked from the outside
Yeah he's waiting out a zombie apocalypse
Exactly
Here you would be the guy who would lie about being bit
Totally
Absolutely
And he did enjoy eating you while he was
Still not a zombie
Just practicing
Eat your ass
How we come to the end of this and I don't think a whole lot happened
Alex is
Back but he's
I guess
Is upset
Yeah
Marvin Hagler
Stories that he's making up about him
He's mad about a bunch of other stuff he's making up
Yeah you know what let's go through the important work topic
Text real quick. Let's just keep counted would you want to get a percentage
Sure
We got Marvelous Marvin nope NADA Borden
Mysterious trip dadweynaha Borden Grammys nope
Earpiece nope I'm great nope
I suppose climate change would be important but it is punishment
From God so that's an opiate drugs
Is it the Border that's important
He's covering his cut that one out to left
Does evil we're probably
Avatar Bladerunner definitely not silent weapons for quiet Wars
Supernaut 76 get the f*** out of the circle
Operation Crimson contagion real but he's lying about it right for Stan occupations not going to happen
Why don't we have Bounty Hunters Run things very obvious not important
Right gunpoint vaccinations
Same thing as forced inoculation and
The one-year anniversary of it's over
For Humanity
There will only be Lone Survivor
Best week 5 purse
1 out of 28 back
Jordan movie back on Friday check back in see if Alex
Can start cooking with some gas I have
This is kind of fun though
I mean
Scooby back
In the saddle
Yeah you know what I do mean that but then as soon as I have to say why I can't tell you
Absolutely not
If I try to rationalize adjuster
The Pirates playing why it's like
There's still fun to go over this even though it's all incredibly stupid
I think it's cuz you like
The work
I think it was just because I got you know I got to read that as a big new Brzezinski article
I found a primary source with
Yeah about probably
We are on Twitter that knowledge of right and I go to bed Jordan
We are on Facebook Dallas Jackson's and if you could please find a local charity or Belvidere area to help out
Got to work
I am the Goblin
Monthly birthday shout-outs
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
I love you