Jordan
I have great respect for its knowledge B. I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
I would like to know
Jordan Jordan
Quick question what's up
Yes
Tangiers parallon alright alright
Is a Jew
Because it's
It's me expressing some of my drives towards novelty what have you
The CVS
And I went
Inside and
4 CVS
Remember this is
I saw a new beverage products
Coca-Cola
With coffee
No
That was my first instinct
Here's my second instinct
Double nail
DoubleDown and I got it
Is very excited
Rise by things in the past
Sure coffee Seltzer's really good really good
Is a
Disgusting
That's the worst thing I've ever heard anyone do to coffee
Yep
Bad
Grz2 try putting some cream and I was thinking about it
And actually I should be perfectly honest varieties of
The regular
Okay
The other two are all three coffee though
God these I got all three
Problems already I got all three of those like what if they're amazing and now I've tried one
Cuz I'm going to stare at the other two for a while
Not excited to drink those
Yeah maybe we could do that miserable drinking Coke
Batman
Is that
On Saturday
I will be
Finishing
My Final Fantasy 7
Project it will be done I couldn't do it last night
Wednesday night
So I'm going to do a marathon on Saturday I'm almost at the end of the game I don't know how long
It's going to take sure but it's going to start at 11 and she's going to go until I finish the game and the walks conjoining over on your
JB home summer other 209
You got it
I'm not going to stop by
Please let's not get any better like maybe their special guest
No time you going to start okay
If you hear a rapping on your window at about 11:30 that's me it's me and I'm Play Drunk
Crashing it through your window
You talking about
Wednesday and Thursday of this week that he's March 17th and 18th 20
This is a terrible idea that is I think it's over I think it's over because
You probably will
Yeah that whole thing was you I would never wish that busted by you winning
Hold on what's that is somebody at the door
Oh no
It is now that we don't know how that it works
So it's a little bit of time I have a couple of very important things
No, but actually I'm kind of shocked by what
Doesn't,
And then we have one of Alex Jones is most
Tacular flare-ups
Okay I'll blow up Saint are in recent memory
Hello
So first
A high in Seattle
I'm a policy wonk high in Seattle thank you very much i g h
Or
Could be like Frasier Hello Seattle
Grub Ibiza Camacho nail polish
Big Rob next Paul Joseph Watson thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
Ejf
I'm a policy wonk
Shout out
Email somebody
Asking to be a March 1st
By saying at the end of March we do a problem like God we're not going to be able to do this now
Keep track of this right
Let's try and give everybody birthday shout outs but never actually get to the name
This isn't their fault
I've got no problem with this person and I hope they have a happy birthday
But clearly
For your birthday we get Annex
Just a joke right
Clearly I'm not meant to have an email address
Anyway happy birthday and congratulations on becoming a technocrats tattoo our beloved
Transdimensional chocolate male Vitality Raptor
Alton Michigan thank you so much Dell
What's the business
Money off that heroin
And the Funky Homosapien how could you not enjoy both of those
So Jordan Wednesday and Thursday this week
Was dreading this
What's Braden doing the show because I had a sense
That possibly Alex
Would talk about the Atlanta shooting
Yes at the spa in Atlanta have left 8 dad
No interest in doing
Got no really complicated because there's a lot of issues to unpack
You know both
About the ante
Sex-worker ideas that are possibly motivating of the of the shooter and
Also certainly the violence towards asian-americans anyone who created
Fentanyl the Magic Dragon or whatever
Can shut the fuk up
Difficult with the information that we have available
But both of those
Things are things that intersect with Alex's World Mana
Kind of scary way and so far as he is misogynist and anti-aging
Yes and I didn't want to deal with it
I was worried
Get into it and
He doesn't bring it up at all
Not on Wednesday
Not as he makes a passing reference to being an incel on Thursday but he doesn't really talk about
Incident at all
And so if he does
In the future will talk about it but for now I mean that my
Ceiling is
Looking to get more information as it is becomes available and nothing is a horrible
Started it show on Wednesday
Aurora
Get the f*** out
We will talk about this in a moment
So
I think that might be a little tasteless somebody help me that there is
Asians is not high
Go ahead and tell me that whenever this is
Just f****** available
You know even if
Like
You even if
Anti-asian sentiment wasn't what
Predominantly motivated this shooters
But even if that were the case if you're Alex Jones doing Infowars
I would think
Hey what are we
Put this off
The next day you're starting your show with a fentanyl the Chinese dragon
How do you spell characters
The shooter was both motivated by misogyny so it's totally fine for me to disrespect to the victims
By being racist
Yeah it's
It's weird
Tell Alex starts the show in Earnest it comes in
And he's got
I do not say this on are for dramatic effect I say it because it's the truth
We've absolutely gone into the side guys we are in for lack of a better
Revelation
Out for a hike at the blood pumping in my brain
Complete and total clarity
Is it going to be about what aspect
Recorded about 20 minutes
Breakdown
What about the layout again
I was very calm how I did it and very cogent
I am so I am going to have that
Video file
With a few documents in a few video clips but I'm going to air it
Are the bottom of the next hour
Tower
And 25 minutes it'll take two segments
Tear
Talk about it ahead of time
But
Everything I'm about to say is document
If you
Don't
We catch what he's saying here's what's going on
Okay he took he took a hike that morning yeah they got some clarity up in his head
Right
Driving to the snow
Studio on his phone
He recorded a 20-minute breakdown of whatever Vision he got while he was like
Yeah that sounded like what I was hearing and that baby deeply uncomfortable
Now he's going to talk about this stuff and then play the report that he's the recording of him on his phone right
30-minute comp
Prank call that it needs to get to recorded a nice little break for people
Most reasonable explanation
Yeah or you didn't never guess
To eat well that person's on air
Anyway
The long and short of it I don't I don't want to spoil anything for you but it turns out the globalist
Complaining
False
Extinction in 2030
I think did you need to go on a hike
Like to get there
I don't know I honestly was looking at
It's kind of cute implies to me that Alex wants to live
You putting it off pretty far for it's like
Alex
Yeah this is
It's not next month
It's not
2030 man
Probably tired by that almost ate well somebody will hopefully have forced him to retire
This is that's kind of aspirational it's really frustrating to me because
Using a sweet position as far as doomsday cult leaders
Doomsday cult leaders go you don't like other
Doomsday cult leaders
You can only predict the end of the world a few times and be wrong before people of time
How to get the
The gist here
We're on
That world is going to end on this date
Happens all the time
What could be fake
Swag Extinction also comforting
I guess okay
Sweat bee
That's what Alex was calling on his
Successful
You really don't even need a false flag for it right right
Anyway we'll get to that when we get to it
Yeah that was definitely the alright guys we got him
When you get to it and we'll get to it when he gets to it
Before that he has to talk about he's got high-level sources sure give him really in-depth
Mountain oh my God that yes and that's why
They have access to such
Like
Current
Important information
Because they're radiating at that high high level frequency
Wings of time
Wherever
Everything's you can be out in the open now
That a national talk show host sent me minutes
Tucker
Phone up and call Trump
I can pick the phone up and call Terry Carlson
I can pick the phone up and call
General Flynn
I can pick the phone up
And call Joe Rogan
Pick the phone up and call
Basically anybody
If I'm a good guy side it's just incredible
Responsibility
Real quick just a point of fact
Podcast
Flagrant 2 or whatever the question one in Miami where there is actually video evidence that he can
Let's just call Joe Rogan tries multiple times a Joe does not pick up feels a little bit like how I can say
Hey you know I can pick up my phone and tweeted anybody I wasn't right now
You have their number but
Nobody's respond
I remember back when I used to produce a comedy show like we have people like
Hannibal Buress or Nickelodeon would come through town
And I would have their phone numbers because I was booked up on the show in the coordinating when they were going to arrive
Sometimes be drunk about eyes and a nose
I got I have Dave Attell in my phone when we work together forever
That I can do
Just call Dave Attell that's how it feels
Exactly
Yes
I was just at the throwing line
Gender activist makes argument
All children to be put on puberty blockers until they can determine the identity
Puberty blockers are toxic
Put you into the system
That's what these monsters are they
Scientific Deckover
Leaving aside a lot of the finer points there was a story from December
So whoever Alex's cool media sources contacting him right before he got on air
Maybe a little bit behind the times
Or maybe they don't exist and Alex just recently heard about
This morning maybe one of his staffers
Found it
Now it says reading his word for word the headline from an article in the Washington examiner from December 14th 2020
It has to do with something that was created by a YouTuber named Xenia Jones
Xenia was making what essentially amounts to a reducto out of
Absurdity of argument against the notion the trans U14 capable of giving informed consent
To take puberty blockers
Dupree red quote
If children cannot consent to puberty blockers which caused any permanent changes even with the relevant
Professional evaluation
How can make him sent to the permanent and irreversible changes that come with their own puberty
With no professional evaluation whatsoever
This was followed up with another tweet quote
An inability to offer informed
Can sand or understand the long-term consequences
Is actually an argument for putting every single sis
Damn transfers
On puberty blockers until they acquire that ability
Sure what does person was suggesting these pretty clear aims any explained as when they were reached
For comment by the washing
Examiner
I was not making an argument that do youth should be given puberty blockers
This was not an actual proposal and it's not something I advocate or endorse
This was an argument that that claims of transients on readiness
To give consent to puberty blockers if followed consistently
Lead to the conclusion that all youth are likewise not ready for the experience of puberty itself
Because that conclusion is absurd again that was not something that I advocated or endorsed
The argument that
Trans Youth Camp consent to puberty blockers asphalt
That makes total sense
Explain the arguments being made here is structurally fine
But the argument isn't advancing
It's good to put all use on Peabody blockers I have clearly stated in the article that Alex's
Hidden arguments
Specifically designed to illustrate a counterexample that shows the flaw in an already existing argue
Videos tweets
Where in response to the United Kingdom
Supreme Court decision that quote
There will be enormous difficulties in a child under 16 understanding and weighing up this information and deciding whether to
Consent to use
Of puberty blocking medication
Only make sense
In light of that contact
Yeah these please put I believe in good faith contends isn't absurd implications a logic
Being used by the UK Court
Unfortunately from a purely logical standpoint the argument put forth isn't super effect
Active in this case
Fresenius argument to hold water
We would need to somehow illustrate
Howdy proceeding of a naturally occurring process and the intervention in that naturally turn process
Require the same level of consent which is going to be
Yeah
They did
Though I do recall
Xenia saying that she wanted to eat the Irish
And that she did they did standby that I know Alex has an expert in
Swifty and Sapphire
F****** Irish self-soothe having access to puberty blockers
The logic of zinnias argument just has a hole that could be easily exploited by people arguing against Steph
But otherwise
Alright anyway Alex is mad about this 33 months later and he's opening his show bragging about how one of the super
Local media friends brought it to his attention
Tomorrow's news today
Yeah I do like
Hearing about tweet
Tweets from 3 months
To go see house you're my favorite news stories
Also the whole thing there were Alex's hanging puberty blockers were linked to lot C
2 deaths
Understanding of it at all
I looked into it and it turns out Alex's passing along
Fake news no in September 2019 a bunch of right-wing Christian sites
Posting articles about how a drug used as puberty blocker for transients called Lupron
I've been linked to oversee
This headline was flashing and it led to articles all over right-wing media and places like lifesitenews and daily wire
Ben Shapiro retreated in the claim went viral all over social media
The drug had been linked
2 / 6000 that's what the problem is that Lupron is not just a drug that's given to transfuse
According to NBC News quote
3000 people who died while taking these drugs are likely determine Ali ill cancer patient
To receive hormone blockers
The fight hormone-sensitive cancers like prostate cancer
According to
A wolf that's hardly fair
Right
The underlying FDA data that was used by these blogs to show the therapist
6370 deaths over the past 40 years there were patients who are on Lupron
That's all they they were using
From there they just assumed that all these patients were transfused as opposed to
Do terminally ill cancer patient
And decided to create a
Duplicitous fraudulent Auntie trans narrative out of
I'll bet anything that I was just saw this headline back when it's being posted on social media
You never thought to look into it or understand the matter further
Cuz he's dumb and lazy
You know 50 years from now I bet
The Japanese will improve upon it
And call it Lupron the Third
Come on
Oh you don't even get that reference at Aldi
I don't know if I should pretend I get it or just
Okay loop loop on the 3rd so it's based off of our sin loop on French
Cat burglar the famous French cat
Oh yeah
50 years later and in Japan called loop on the 3rd
Forgive me for not knowing my anime and famous French
Cat burglar history did Lupin the Third
It was incredible
I'm sure it is it's okay it's a hole in my cultural awareness
Few people get it and they will f******
Can shih tzus intensity of that book you gave me was really scared
Anyway Alex's is
Is full of
Bad information in already
XO you know it did this clip like this kind of his
A little funny
The average Westerner has less attention span than a goldfish
But their subconscious brain and their conscious brain
That basically been murdered where there
Why jellyfish
I'm a sleeper
Must awake
EMDR
What's the politician they chocolate very
Very
Slowly
And they talk
Very
Softly
I don't want anyone in PR
Talk to him excited voice
I would say that it excited voice like that actually distract from the glaring holes in the information being yell
Okay there might be that I will a meteor
Italy become the greatest left-wing commentator there is in Alex's eyes I guess
I mean I think that there is a a lot of
People who make up
If we riding over performing
That would be me say I'm literally word for word
Performance and is Showmanship or whatever is designed
In order to make up for distract people
From the fact that he doesn't know anything it wasn't making all this s***
One could argue most people who scream are often
To doing that
Yeah
Broad loop on the 3rd
Anyway
This next week
This is great man
This is this is where I live
I like I like people who are happy
I like it when people are happy
Even people I dislike
Like Alex
I'd rather I'd rather everyone be happy cuz I'm positive vibes emanating out to the universe
A real good mood because magic happened in his loving
You want on that hike
I need an idea
Right and then listen to what happened
The crew they're amazing
We've all had dreams that come true
This morning
I cut an audio recording dealing with the globalist plan to have a stage in the world event
Have you forgotten
I thought I'll just
Graphic
Over that episode I'm going to have them do that as a background today
And I swear
On
Everything I am I on my heart on my soul
I walked into this building this morning
Looked up and they were punching up
This background of a satellite of the Earth
We probably do this twice a year
Printer
The headline
Globalist
Plan
The control my wife
As I walked out of the house I said I have just received
The biggest download I've ever gotten on the hike I just done
What do you mean what I said
They're going to stay
And she didn't think I was crazy cuz she seen
Okay that's why that's why
Download into my brain that they're going to fake the end of the world of 2030
Okay
Alright
Could you pick up something to eat on the way home would you like a little road soccer team
Cereal
Yeah it's a little bit silly
But want to hear him read The Pale Blue Dot
Over that
Glad y'all that pale blue body
Extinction in 2030
Okay so I was got a weird idea while he was hiking and now he's decided this is the greatest thing in the world he figured out how he want
Wanted to visualize it comes into the studio
Staff is already f****** with that image man
Is this is synchronicity blows your mind
Holyshit
I don't care
Mile
You're cold hearted Mac I'm cold-hearted
I am cold-hearted X coincidences
You know they say that
You can never really know the people around you and I feel that now cuz I can't I cannot believe this is not penetrated you.
Dark
I don't think ghosts are real
What else you got what else you got Alex I'm not doing dreams
All right well for a little bit later
Do a dream
Sex clip
We get to Alex responding to some big news
And that is
The Trump has come out in favor
Vaccines for covid-19
Breaking Point
Reweld
But he's Limited
Stop this big giant 40 chest got everybody says he is
Optimistic
And by too much into science when it's Global of science
All the stuff they gave him a severe and the rest of them
Esau I'm bored
He is coming out
Donald Fox News endorse
Vaccines
25 countries in Europe
Around the world problem
We chop Trump
I'm going to
That sounds like you have a lot of eggs
Yeah
I hope you got all these drugs for people that made him feel good he's like vaccines
Hard time believing that the
This conversation
Didn't happen where somebody's like
Trump we need you to endorse the back
Seen it can save lives you have a lot of influence over people
A lot of Republican men
Almost half of them refuse to get vaccinated
And him saying
I can't do that it would piss off my followers who want to kill
Emma and the other person coming back here is 100g
Feel
Course
I Am for sale on Fox and Friends
Eastside.
Yeah whatever too little too late
Amore is that I think Alex might realize that like Trump
This would be a really good time to just be like
Alright
Don't care anymore
Dover
And I'm going to call his son up
If you continue to say this is wonderful this is good
No problem you're a bad guy
And I'm going to be against you
That's that
Wonder Wheel the economy. Okay it was just a vaccine
I might well that's still bad but I understand what he's doing I don't agree with it but I see it's respect
I always like everybody needs to get it
Oh
I think he sees an off-ramp
There's no hope of trump really ever becoming president
How were there really
The movement or whatever it's
Splinter
Sheridan hate each other yeah
Yeah yeah
There is a possibility of coalescing again but it's not going to be around Trump
Trump Juniors a
Trucking
Think they're running into the problem that a lot of would be monarch
I've run into witches
Is that their children are
Stupid
Incredibly
So right and that's why
That's okay if you're already Amano
Exactly you can't stop it going down
Straight Caesar on this guy
Yeah and so you know I think I think the chopper are Alex realizes that
There's value in maintaining like I did
Make a huge mistake with last few years but this is a line too far right now
I think we may see that unfortunately I wouldn't be surprised if he could
Could carve out a better
Space for moving forward by being the
It's the crazy guy who's also anti-trump now like
I mean he could have
This whole time probably but also like one of things I think is interesting is he take
Eventually
I miss show and the next show in like no one
Cares
No one is like a what what's a
How you're talkin bad about Trump
They've all moved on to that he was just an avatar for their hatred and desire to kill them
Apparently can
Exist without him so they realize they don't need him
Hypno create another
Anyway Alex
Patted him on the head
Alex Jones Show
Talk about Trump
It doesn't mean that I won't say he's good on topics we should take over the Republican Party
Dropping congratulated my wife we got married all that great stuff
Broadcaster and I'm going to take over for Rush Limbaugh
I only kept the eclipse
Because Alex is definitely not mad the Dan bongino took over
Very insulting thing to him
Specifically
Not even a little bit mad at all about Dan bongino taking the spot that he considers
Is rectally
Isaac most radio station
Yeah definitely not mad
Yeah
He's media contact reach out to him and told them about this three-month-old tweet
Alex also has some information he's been trying
To get out
To his media contacts it where you know it's over a year old
Tell you something here
We cover so much huge nose continually
This is critical for me and you and all of it to continually
Constantly realize how huge this is
Huge
Because it's easier to get live on Aaron cover while stuff cuz it's live
Slick Rick
10 * the views online
I didn't know about this
I finally have read
A month off and on spending 30 minutes 10 minutes
Read this entire folder
And
Greek researchers
New report on this everybody else that's time
Whatever every want you to different ports on this because
Every time I read this
3 *
Doubt it
Time I look at this
New stuff
Mentally exhausted
Very scientific.
And this is a small portion this
Pages or more
Crimson Contagion
If you get
Mentally exhausted reading
Scientific papers. Maybe you should
Birria
Signs of a paper
Yeah I don't I don't know
Crimson contagion we talked about on the last episode York Times article report
Dirigo some stuff
And now he's ready to eat actually really good town into Egypt
Complaints
About how his media friends don't want to cover
Crimson Contagion
The 10 minutes after day
Action Amanda video
To say bombshell will call the show bombshell
You're not
Ashley sent this
Leaving talk show host in the country all of them
Might want to do that
The other two guys
Believable
I think if they're saying I'm busy you covered cuz they know it came out a year ago so far
Right I mean that has to be the explanation
This is this is nothing new.
Would have enough sense to realize
You shouldn't be talking
About this
This looks bad for Trump
This looks real bad
Spin it you kind of need to exist within like a fully-realized
Conspiracy world you can't have a foot in reality you have to create a
Complete
Isolated
Kidspace
Where you can pull off a
Actually it was
Was the globalist
Display
Tucker is trying to pretend he still lives in the shared reality we all live in
He gave up on that elude a long time ago
We got to Agenda 21
You remember that
Agenda 2030 Maybe
Now there's a genda 20:35 I like that
Planet
I gave us life
And then there's the rest of the levels going to be operation
If you were among the first we supposed to 20
Oops
An hour exposing agenda
What comes after agenda 2030
Deltron 3030 first time ever going to hear next hour
Peter Denny autumn
It will be no humans
As we were down today
Left on Earth
That seems like a bad play
It's it's
Complete nonsense
Makes up a new agenda
Mansa Musa
30 is actually real
I didn't choose the name of like
Summer
But at Jeddah 2035 I think
Entirely Alex is on creation. I like that you can create where it's at
We can create agenda
So what time is agendas is
You know
I've never watched any of the
Freddy Krueger movies
Sure
Do you watch those movies I watch The Nightmare on Elm Street or two I know that they take place in the realm of Dreams
They do and you shouldn't f***
If you f****** a nightmare Freddy going to get you at Freddy's going to get you
Alex lives in that space to a lot you know these Visions when he's on hikes
Ed apparently I would think that a lot of
The stuff that he
He does weather for good or bad
May be driven by some
Conscious things
That he might not understand
Oh I would argue that also conscious things he does not understand
Context in mind this is about how if you getting
An abortion
Then you'll be fine with killing old people in
Slippery slope
And then I would start talking about his own history of pain
For abortions
And he says
Some stuff that makes me really uncomfortable
Truck coming out and doing this
Crossing the Rubicon
A major push
They say it's not a baby
Monroe bway 97
Tens of millions of women getting abortion
Uterine cancer cervical cancer
Ovarian cancer
What's good
Crime against God
You don't get God to forgive your servant of evil
Once you're on that track
Would you admit you pay for abortions
That's horrible
Swear to God
When I was like
17 years old
Now.
I would not
Do that again
Years without even dating
And an In-N-Out
Great to know
And I
Painted himself
For the positive light
That'll show him the children as they grow up and how beautiful they were
Hold this little baby in my hands
Incredible sign
Your son was an inch
Got your ass
Has delivered me and cleanse me of what I did
So he was holding as his
Tadpole
Not even
Not even that
Still borderline Andover
Meaning of itself and then the devil ate it
And the devil laid in front of
Bugatti
Alex said he has nightmares that God shows him these kids
Apparently gotten sending these nightmares where the devil
D2 trials in front of him
I've somehow Alex is like a god
Forgiven me I protected everything's fine
Because torture is being my drink
That's how you keep Alex in line
Okay if you're God you've chosen Alex defeat the Devil and you can't let the
Strafe
From the bath
So you got to send them cons
Terrifying threatening nightmares to make
Make sure he knows you love him
I look at this from a more
I don't know materialistic
Perspective
Sure
Spell icup
See your stoneheart right now
I kind of
See this as a thing
Alex
Mayfield tremendous amounts of guilt
Wow about things that he opposition to abortion
Demonic Miss of it
Maybe a lot of it might be a byproduct
Of how terrible he feels about himself
Sure sure
More importantly
This is what I want to say
No
This is not cool
This isn't cool is bad
This isn't good for a new show this isn't good for an editorial show isn't good
As analysis of anything real bad
It's maybe has a place as like
Mid-range
Televangelist
I could see that
Local television
He doesn't have a private jet but he can afford a tour bus somewhere under the
The Jack Van Impe level
Yeah I just has to be really bizarre that anybody would listen to this and just be like
Mayonnaise guy gets
He's talking about are rambling about how he has Visions at night of his
Babies that he paid for abortions the bed the devil eat them
And Alex gets mad and
God it just like
It's hard to take a man seriously who says we've got big news
To get into and then later on goes to be like I had a dream and let me tell it to you and exhausting.
Details on board child to punish me or talk to me and God welcome that dream into my head
Alright
Subway
So I meant like I really got this f****** weird sense about him
That is
Nuts
And this is not
Coming up in the next two segments that key report on the globalist plan
Rolled into the world in or around the year 2030 learn what agenda
20/35 is exclusively
Seriously
It was 25 years ago it's all come true
A lot of contacts a lot of sources but
Above basically any of those sources
Except for the fuel the top level
The only people outside the top globalist
Leadership
Actually have all the contacts all the info
Two-seater complete master plan
And I'd literally
Okay
The only only Alex
And like King globulus
Yeah actually know what's going on
Nobody else in the world could even see through
I'm listening to him like this is
Rank narcissism somebody having a breakdown of some kind
Like that this is not a well person
Existing in
In space no no generally speaking as as a bipolar bipolar 1
Delusions of grandeur usually a
Big size
That stuff is going on
He has he has delusions of grandeur on it
Semi-regular basis
I don't even know if I would categorize it as like feeling because like there's also this
Dislike
No it be malignant narcissism
It's bad
Truly if I'm the globalists and I know this
You got a killer
I mean you do there's no big deal
Whatever backlash you might get from killing them is going to be worse than having
Him know your entire plan
I mean like everybody
Conspiracy world still believes that like
The man killed Bill Cooper
Total and it didn't unravel any globalist plot
You know that cuz they killed him
That was just what would happen if the global killed Alex to accuse the only person who can
Can see through everything and understand everything how to do it
It's not like anybody else
Arapaima globalist
Even even if I'm a pacifist globalist do you know like I don't want to solve my problems
Buy a murder
This is a special circumstance you're just got to do it yeah I think what you've done is provide
A pretty decent argument for why there are no Global us
If they were as demonic at his Cutthroat after working on a thousand year plan
Galaxy
Yeah they would have literally no reason to hold back
And even if you have the protection of God but God you've got protection
Is the one sending you weird Demonite Mary how are you
No big deal
Yeah
Get down to business doing what he does best
Best witches reading headlines
And just saying about them
No analysis at all
Where should I
Start the segment have this big
Let's go ahead and just read headlines in the vaccine stack
From today overhead shot please
Another article of the New York Times watching the coven attack
A year and 3 months ago
It's the end of humanity and maybe it's for the best
Time says get rid of
That's a religion
This headline Metallica's reading on Aries real but it's in the New York Times book review section
It's the title of a review of a novel novel by Guido Marcelli titled
Ahg which is published in 1977
The plot has to do with a suicidal man realizing that all the rest of the humanity has disappeared and he's the last human around
Hey newberry's absentee waxes philosophical and also notices that nature is taking over what was previously City
From the review quote
Beneath the philosophical Welter a new world Glitters with prelapsarian strange
Gangs of Plum cats rate administrative lobbies
ShamWow guy
Prince along train tracks
Felix's Gray's Hotel lawn
I sort of one-man Utopias
Possible
The phone isn't Strivers Argon
The city's churches Banks and military installations lie abandoned
An index of Empires ruin
Is the work of fiction that was reviewed in the New York Times book section and Alex is trying to pass it off as some kind of news article open
10 piece
This is beyond the kind of sloppiness they would get anyone fired anywhere else than
Infowars
What the f*** is wrong with this s*** man and I've got a breaking news story for him
This comes from the 90s
And
There was a piece published
Where a guy specifically said
That it was the end of the world
As he knew it
I remember the kids f***** up you know when you think about it it's the end of the world and this guy feels by
Do you know what that means
Pop
Globalist
I think he also predicted Like a Hurricane
And then he'll listen to himself Church
I get rubber later tonight so
A long time
You've been teasing this
This a report
That you recorded in
The car on the way to the studio with you were so
Shallow about his
Is Vision but he was like
So
Infant teething
After reading a slew of headlines
How far into the episode are we
I'm not sure
Maybe 2 hours couple hours at lunch time
Forget about her
Hugo's
Okay good
Pecos and they play a special report
Sound sound like
What he was describing about agenda 2035
Or any of that stuff
Intelligent
No special report
Commercial and then it comes back
Bike down for this
Amazing freak out
That I will actually tell you is out of the version of it
Our lights are going on around here at the office and I do use lizards our Focus that's fine
Appreciate that you heard me say brand Airlines 2035 report we come back
I just went off and had lunch
Oh hell was that about
20:35
It's coming up it's coming up
Computer that put
Maybe I should just quit
Thinking about
I just walk out of here
And they do a better job at never see me again
Because I can either
Coming on
To talk about how this is a massive crime against humanity
Biological weapons attack on Humanity
And the master plan
Also said I'm going to have the support
Promoted promoted
Trying to understand
I'm the worst
Discovery broadcast for a while
Just bugs
What's your Governor Newsom
Man
I just like
This is
Add a certain point
This isn't the show anymore this is a guy breaking down
I feel bad laughing about it but I hated him
And it's kind of funny
Also
Did it just occurred to you
To write out a f****** script
Or something an outline right
That is all that's what the military
That's what all good shows do
It's called like producing
Yeah and so he asked to give a little bit of an apology obvious
Play any explains
Fds that was a real freak out on there earlier
Because it's normal when world government is coming in and setting up Global passports
Inoculation to doing it to newborn baby
I wasn't clear about hearing that report I guess to them
And
Report coming on
Really meme
Myself in the face
But I am mad at myself I wish I did a better job
Yeah me too
Man I just love this as a bookend
Cuz the episode begins with him talking about how great it was that the crew psychically knew the video that he wanted to play
Yep
Beautiful
You know what I'm going to tell you this right now
I'm going to tell you this right now my Stone Cold Heart
Not wrong I said I said it on the show that we're premiering this report at a certain time right
I guess the producers are listening to the show to get that report ready
Maybe we should have talked about this
Before the show started
I love it though
And
I don't care anymore about that guy
Because you do you have this whole thing where it's like okay for months were talking about how
The coronavirus itself is a bioweapon the fauci made in this lab and now we're going to be doing the
Vaccine is a bioweapon the fauci
I'm tired boring
Francis Boyle
Royal
Boil
Apologies
Frustrates me
Because if you are named Francis Boyle
I assume you have been knighted
I don't know why
But if your name is Francis Boyle it better be Sir Francis Boyle because Arthur Conan Doyle
Ugly but it didn't sound right
Right yeah
To hear what I'm going to call the Larry Nichols mistake
Permission to give out his phone number on the website to help with legal advice
4 to assist
Their lawyers cuz you are is not license
Practice in one state
But he'll advise their lawyers on how to help them not get vaccinated
I don't care
Francis Boyle
We jump to the 18th now cuz I didn't review goes and I thought it would be funny not to cover his
Report
Cuz it's it's a 0
Brother honestly more pressing issues like this
That Alex
Gets into the beginning of his March
Show
All of the place the leaders of the lgbtq movement
Arrested
There's the truth is
It wasn't about gay marriage was always about sex
With your children
Ritual
To drain author energy
Android off there
Future
The only like better is chopping your children up with a meat cleaver while they rape
What the big boys do
So this is the kind of moment that you might describe as a mask off
Scituate
I'll pretend he's a Libertarian and then he doesn't
Care what people do in their bedroom underneath all that belief is this
Switches
The classical propan
Homophobic
Put this in context Alex's found a story about a judge in Wisconsin named Brett blomme
Who was arrested on suspicion of uploading child pronography to web
He apparently was a family court judge and it's normally been the president of an organization called Cream City Foundation
Which of the philanthropic Organization advocating for members of the LG
G b t q + community
And in the past that Foundation is sponsored some drag queen Story Hour events so naturally this is being presented in right-wing media
Is this guy being the head of dragon
Queen Story Hour
What Alex is doing is engaging in select
2 coverage
He makes a big deal out of every time that someone in a group of people he wants to attack gets arrested for a horrible crime
Read more the other instances where the perpetrator is someone who's a member of a group that he doesn't want to portray as evil
When there's a school shooting
It's just an individual doing a terrible thing it in those cases
I don't fully understand how bad it could be to engage in Collective blame for individual a
Most of his career is based on gallon about how gun owners will be blamed for things like Sandy Hook or the Las Vegas shooting
We have to resist that also
Get guns taken
But when you get right down to it Alex does the far worse version of ascribing collective blame for the actions of individuals
Because he's doing it to Moline and attack historically marginalized groups
Two people
Any immigrant committing a crime becomes proof that immigrants are all criminals and killers
The crimes of any gay person becomes proof
That the lgbtq rights movement is secretly about
Potranco sex
With kids
I'm certain most listeners don't need this bailed out but this is profoundly dangerous
Because what is coupling the perception of criminality
With an entire group of people based on the actions of individual who's a member of that group
And this
Is just unacceptable
Now that's
That's just so f*****
It just doesn't it
It just never ends no matter how much f******
Violence we see
On a daily basis
It is still a man
Out there trying to get
People
Attacked
And it's just so f***
So
We're not going to dwell too much on that because like a lot of that does surround like a lot of the turtle
Gross stuff
Did Alex say I do
I don't expect him to Tampa replay on our show but that Rose to a level of like
Okay Alex's saying that the children of lgbtq
Seacube rights movement in the push
For gay marriage
Was actually secretly about trying to have sex
For kids
A Moment Like That
Does deserve a place of honor show because
It reveals
Something that's under the surface of his is
Is
Worldview his is belief
That's f***** up
It's alright he's
That's that's where he's at
Yeah
And it's it's
Even more explicit than whenever he was like
Lgbtq
Tqp or whatever it was
I swear he's trying to add that in there
And it's just
It's just
So Alex is that
Biden
I said some tough word
About Putin
And I get the sense
From list
Make this episode March 18th
Did there's a there's a sentiment Alex
Love's
Real probe the Monarch that he wishes would take over the United
I think he wishes
Just drop was more like bolsonaro or
Quite frankly I think he would rather one of them invade the United States
He wanted a god-king strongman instead he got a
Grifter
Got a front man for the mob exactly and so now he
He's like oh look at what could have been we could have had a
30-year monstrosity of a Russian Roulette
He's going back to that
Wendy's on
Amazon Channel TV
Buses going to pay soon
And that they're going to be coming after
And that
Look in the mirror
Let's talk about what
Alaska
Ears over and over again
He pulled troops out of all he's ever places
Elijah National
Organic Drive Sonoma Supply roller
The cleaner fossil fuels
Marriage and Christianity
And they are decrying the
Foundation Ford Foundation Rockefeller Foundation
Foundation
They're saying they want to post human world and that Russia is not for
It's so funny to me because like last weekend I was watching
Alex's documentaries
Prepon
Some stuff
Storm I believe of Sentara start together cuz they're
He was talking about how he
He had proven
Bomb does apartment build
I mean it's not hard
DIY 2K episode that he was talking about
Putin looks like a demon he's going to seize power at all
I just I don't know it's weird
Weird
It doesn't it doesn't mean anything it's just wherever the wind blows with my prejudices today
That's a long as you stick within the relative
Boundaries of those prejudices Elsa
Support you forever but if
You Breakaway like say you support vaccines then your f****** done
Yeah and I think he recognizes that Putin is a leader that would
Protect the thing
Better important to him which is
Absurd of heteronormative white
Consider the matter
Of course
Alex
I like it when it gets a little heady
But I like this even more
Directions from 2000 plus years ago from sings 4000-5000 years old
Tells the same story
India
Thousand-year-old hieroglyph China
6000 year old stone carving
The tell the same story
A story we'll talk about
Here
In just one moment
The story of
Let's talk about keeping the broadcast on the air
I want to see if you off your support
Make a lot of money
Promise operation whenever on a structure on cruise
I love it
I feel like you slept
Me and my face three times over the course of all history about the same story
And I will explain it to you after
That's the real story that's
Been told beautiful over and over again
Sounds does a really really long plug
A fairly long talk
I don't know what's longer
Anymore
My radar
But he hasn't he has a bit of a plug
And
Gets into what I think maybe is what the message
Batavians we're all about
Okay
What do you do this
Cuz I can't in 5 minutes for 6 minutes do it justice in this segment
Humanoid
What that mean
How much how many times I've told you about
Dick this
They admitted to producing humanoids
50 years ago
50 years
What about 50 years ago humanoids were already created
About humanoids
DC movies
I mean we are we already know about the fish people with that human eyes
Naturally and then now we have
Returns of replicas
It's walking around
Oh yeah
I don't know
Iowa
Was going to take this seriously this house
To do with you no more stories about like
Advance
Ventura being made in
Replacement Oregon
Technology
I was going to take it seriously but then he said there's anyway come out
Nnn
Promise
But Joe Biden and
Bye-bye
Little nasty dudes technology
Bible calls a demon
Promise live extension but they
First got to kill us
And test
You better hurry up for Tristan
Thanks to us because
We grow into them what we do
Pure
And it come together as a species
A bird that is a knock
This is actually a giant
Genetic war on the planet
Set up for this song
Just like you should get ready
For that
If there's a story about some scientific
Breakthrough
Some kind of scientific it's going on
I find that interesting
But I don't care to talk about it realistically when it's being presented to me
Is part of
Plot
Where Joe Biden is going to get life-extension technology
Who is Promised by a demon right
They're nasty dudes
Notre Dame
Call demons in the Bible but there are other worlds
Are you a nasty enough dude
To extend the president's life is a question that
Yeah I just don't like one once this
Is the realm or in any real conversation doesn't matter
Aliens or demons
Nobody I'm out
Also I just
Anytime he says pure
I don't want him to
Expand upon that we all know it's better if he leaves it alone
Stay away from the even said he shouldn't be allowed to say the word pure
Comes off his lips correlate
Pure o.j.
What does that mean is it white inside what do you want
Impurity that he's dog not I think he means fully
I think he does although I do
People in his community have it
Healthy relationship
But I think he's talking about all humans not humanoid right
So at this point in the show Alice
Alex Goes to call
And
This is one of the more uncomfortable
Tribble and unpleasant
Set of calls
Studies taking
It's all Harris
Austin Smith call again
No
At least
At least I wouldn't be this like this is the price I think this could get people
Oh that's
Yeah Google talking about the vaccine stuff
And I would say some bad medical advice
Also just is acting weird with these people
I just one caller
He calls in and what he's talking about how his dad got the vaccine
And then died
Announces response
Is a little weird
In-N-Out
And and
In adults
God Almighty Ralph who do you blame
You know all these famous
Stars that died today
They said I want to protect
People were tough guy
They did it because they were lied to they were actually Heroes your dad
I believe meant well and was a hero at the end of the day
What about the
Brother
Bill Gates and the globalist
I would love to meet Bill Gates
So weird
The weird response to have when someone's telling you this story about their dad passing away fairly recently
You to ask
Who do you blame we have a
Come
Literally
Very very old term for is this thing that he is
Asking the man to do and we see it in a bad
Contacts what's up
It's called a scapegoat dad who do you blame it's not a good question ever
No it's
It's definitely not it's a
It's rude to
I don't think that color took it is rude but
It's it is who do you want me to kill is this that is another answer for
Your dad was murdered who do you blame the thing is like
Bizarre
Real conversation that you want to have them public value
Exactly what Alex
Because this is an intensely painful story if it's true I'm not sure if
It's just calling it.
That's f****** super hard
Dude lost his dad
Recently
Really hard
The function of Alex's show is to take
Feelings like the one this caller is experiencing
Translate them into feelings of anger and Hate
Direct me to the people Alex has decided are his enemy
Now
He's talking specifically about Bill Gates
And what have you put
Make no mistake
This exact sort of
Transmutation of
Hanging into hate and anger that is exactly what happens towards the marginalized communities
That Alex
Attacks demonizes
It's exactly the same but that's
A switch
It is which s***
Blame the witch's Golf Course
It's the witches it stop raining do blame the way I know that's God the demons Make It Rain and God makes
Duh
Gay people
Alex gets another call
And this guy was saying that his dad got a shot
And then
Maybe have
Some indication
He might have
Prostate
Here is how this goes
So my dad is a
He had the second
Vaccine
And now he just
Receiver that his
PSA levels
Greater Highway
Original August
Station House
Do cancers
Actually said that Surly said when you said he took the Pfizer or moderna
Pfizer but I'm not 100% sure on that
Pre-cancerous
Oligo cancerous
Oh wow so
Now they want to biopsy of the prostate
Can you show them the literature saying
But it makes a hormone-based tissues swell up and that they should not
Autobiographies for 6 months
I guess I was not aware of that
Videos
Be alarmed
After mRNA vaccine
If your glands
Uterus prostate
A swell up
Okay
Whether or not covid-19 vaccine causes a side effect of gland swelling this is so irresponsible
Possible of Alex
If it's callers dad who was a doctor has reason to suspect he may have prostate cancer
He needs to take appropriate steps
To make sure
One way or another because
Akita treatment is early detection
Oz advice for him to avoid getting a biopsy and just assume it's probably a side effect of the vaccine
Even though the caller can't even remember which vaccine is Dad got
Making people hurt
Alex is misrepresenting a recent article from the Cleveland Clinic
Titled
Don't be alarmed by this covid-19 vaccine side effect that could be confused with breast cancer
This deals with possible swelling of the lymph nodes under your arm
As a side effect
To the covid-19 vaccine
Which is relevant
Because that's also assigned a breast
Does nothing to do with prostate swelling
Immediately taken off air for offering this Reckless medical advice to
Do his audio
Please call her
Do we clear this caller is probably going to be fine
Is that teams not believe this b*******
Diesel doctor so I would imagine he's taking appropriate actions
To protect his own health
My son sent me YouTube videos and I'm a doctor to get a biopsy
The problem is with listeners who
Hear this and pick out two nozani
What if one of them has a possible cancer symptom that they decide to overlook
Because Alex told them
It's just a vaccine side of
Legitimately that has the potential to get people hurt
Or to give
If you have
God forbid
Some kind of
Swelling or some kind of a symptom of cancer outside of
I mean even if it is Belen
Nodes in your armies probably
Make sure and go talk to a doctor
You shouldn't get a biopsy for 6 months
Critical
Yeah I'm dumb
This is one of the instances with me being like very much
There should be a
If there's a consequence for telling people to drink bleach
There should be a consequence for telling people not
Got to get
Medical tree
Or not to
Do what ya
That's
It's outrageous that is it is just as bad to say like
Hey here's a
Cure for your problem as it is to say
Don't
Seek out medical attention because what you
You should listen to me
Yeah you're fine exactly
F***** them
So this next caller
If this person actually kind of tickled me
With her with her voice
Enjoy this guy's voice
Hey Alex
Man I'm just watching the hot the new Holocaust brother
Iron Man
Not that depressed me
Oh boy I like him calling a man over and over
Yeah yeah
Listening something with sex now that's
Not good you can't understand
Damn
Things that sick
Kind of topics that Alex is covering you have
No ability
Totally to tugade r222 measure
Holyshit
At a time whenever everyone is telling you that your dreams are not real
You are listening to a man tell you about how his dreams are real
And that's how you get political awareness at
Definitely not good
Subway
Yeah I mean what is
6 like
Second grade
What is that
I think
Yeah that's not
I remember
Finish my work early so I can play with Dinosaurs
And I remember nobody telling me that
Dinosaurs were actually put there by wait no I disagree
I was told that dinosaurs were put there
By God
To test our faith
When I was 60
Well that didn't have any negative effects on me dad
First year that I lived in Hawaii like
I was
First grade
Holy child look
I think back on like
I didn't know anything
Listening to Alex from fat
I am going to
I'm going to listen to Alex while I work on my multiplication
Tables real quick
So
Okay so three times
4 + 12 +
12 is the number of the Illuminati trying to kill me this is meaning
The teacher might be the devil
Yeah I think it'll be tough
Live that way
I mean like I would come home from
From school and I would do homework
Sometimes watching
Tarl
Also it seems positively cheerful cheerful for someone who is absorbed
Bulshit
I want to hear about what happened in his life recently you'll be even more surprised that he's that chipper
I don't know man
I lost my wife last year
I couldn't really get her
For medical attention
And she had real baddie
COPD
Cheap she would you would not go to the hop
They wouldn't let me stay
She wouldn't she would not stay
That's right and I know you and I wasn't going to let her stay without me because I knew
If I got her in there
With her condition she was
Be done for
PCR test an innovator for the money
Yeah I know it
And I saw any anyway
Said it home till she
Died
Jesus
I mean that's
So sad
Set the person who
Alex killed his wife
I mean not individually but like that information sphere
How's like insisting that they're going to
Kill you for the covid money
Made it so she didn't get a
Appropriate care in
Sat at home and died
If true
Again this is just calling about the shop
Calling and complimenting the guy
Who is
Been listening to
Since he was six
Yeah
Got it deep into his head that
You can't
Let your wife go with that
While this episode as a body count this is a this is a body
It really is
Hypothetical future and which self
Locked up
Does he like
That's how
F***** up your brain gets
I would rather
Blame I would rather lose my wife
I would rather lose my wife
And still believe that I am
Following the correct path
Then I would
Confront reality and save my wife's life
Roar
Whatever
You know improve her life
Serially I mainly alternative
Was
Think you had this paranoid delusion
And about this conspiracy that she's gone
Dive to go to the hospital
Yeah well she did die
Like not going
To the hospital
I don't understand how this is a win
It's not
It's no f******
Ringside
That is just so funny
And it's so awful when these like humans
Stories if true
Penetrate through Alex's show and they are taken as seriously as they really are like that
Family messed up
And you have this and it's like okay these are glimpses into
Some of these people's lives who have been
Affected by Alex
The contact presumably since they were sick
Yeah huh
Yeah
At the same time the show the day prior
Was a complete freak out of him just being emotionally unhinged
Yelling about 2 how you needs to quit cuz the staff won't get his video out on time
And how he has Nightmares of the devil eating his Unborn
Like its
That's the same person
Who is being looked at as an expert 5
This guy who
What does wife died at home
Empathetically
A quieter
And then
Continuing to yell as if as if you weren't listening to somebody tell you
Hey you're responsible for my wife's well and what you're going to get is that sort of pay sorry about that
You're also going to get a doubling down and a reinforcing Anna validating
Of the exact
Mercy nonsense that led you
And your wife
Tenada getting appropriate care it's
Verify this is straight up
Real
Cult leadership
This is 100%
Hey your wife died
And
Because of everybody but
The cult leader
That's just so f*** she would have lived if they wouldn't have killed her at the hospital
Okay you know what happened in my cult
The cult leader was responsible for the death of a child
Yeah
As was his parents
And everything that they believed in
And whenever that child died
I do to their lack of
Care
Their denial of care
And their belief that
Caring for the child at a hospital or even can
Considering
Medicine
Would be
Arrests in
That guy went to
Jail
Everybody has the right
Accept or refuse Medical Care
Answer like I'm not
That's going to do that and I can play that game
When you are responding
2 misinformation or called leadership
And that is what is motivating you
It's a completely different
Now that is
Is that is a
Yep
Question in my mind
I feel like
When I
This is the complicated like difficult Pusha
Tympole evolve list
Coming to the show
It's like
I kind of feel bad about myself
Is all last
That what's clearly a guy freaking out I'm having an emotionally unbalanced day on the 7th
Don't feel bad
And then I'll get to this and I'll be like
I don't feel bad
How can how can he
How can you deserve any consideration
None
It's just a
Difficult
How to preserve your Humanity when face
With
Such inhuman
Like just
True
Psychopathy
I just I'm such a narcissist
That I can
Hear this story
That I bear responsibility
At least partially
For the death of this man's wife
And I'm just going to tell him that he was so great
I know I have a strong scent
The Alex
Would not have
Kept his wife at home in a hospital
Very expensive
Yeah no it's
It's so it's
Just such what you see and I know
You want to provide empathy
For this because you are a hue
Human being
And you can't allow yourself to let empathy
The diet challenges me
It's tough but when you get pass
After certain point
It's just like
F*** you
It's Harbor good
Forever
Let's get that good
Let's put that behind us
Listen to Alex
This is not tell you belong to the city
Is Alex
Bumper Music
And rambling about nonsense
Just a sort of
Cleanse our pilot on the way out of this episode
This is a little
Track night
From me
Tron Legacy soundtrack
Big Red
A digital Frontier I tried to picture of information
What do they look like
Motorcycles windshield Apartment B
Home Alone
I got in
WorldMark interspatial attack
Are those all Solaris in the song God's plan
One day I got it
Coming from that perspective it all makes sense
Fold-up finally respect you
We chose the winter
You're going to lose
We both laugh
I left
Significantly I would argue that I did not just laugh
For it buddy
Yeah I guess they're the enemy respect to 12
I really don't think they do those three imaginary King globalist that have the same understanding of
The plan is Alexandra got a lot of
Now that's
That's probably true
That sounds right like that like you know like Achilles and Hector eventually
How to respect
For each other although I believe that was after Hector was dead
You know
It's just like
Ezra Levant comes on
The show at towards the end of this episode
And these are complaining that the u.s. Navy hired researchers at the University of Arkansas to spy on him and his website
And then somehow somebody sold that report to just
Trudeau
I can't find sorry what I don't know okay I can't find any evidence of this other than an article on rebel mean
Weather report is referred to as
Canada election cyber-forensics analysis the date
October 10th
The X-ray report isn't linked there and I have no idea if it's real so I was trying to
And I googled it
I guess what the first thing
Comes up if you Google those words is
Bulshit
Is a page where Rebel media is doing a donor Drive
I've called cyber intelligence operation donation
Using his alleged reported
The bait on the hook of a pledge Drive
I'd like to CBC we don't get a billion dollars a year so if you can chip in to help cover our costs and fight back against the law
Live
Appreciate it
I don't know if this is real or not
Ezra Levant is a bigot
The career liar somebody
I'm seriously until he produces the report
Yeah I don't
WellCare
But he does say something kind of funny
What you know what
Where is the ACLU
If it was The Young Turks or Jim Acosta
MSNBC
Or even Eleanor B of the leftist on
The View who were spied on
It would be
Lose your Canadian way if it were Ellen
It's vatche ACLU
Dan
Where is the ACLU
I mean that
Seriously
Is there a physical location for the ACLU
He was asking an honest question
I don't I don't know how I don't know if the ACLU does work with people who aren't protected by American civil liberties
The First Amendment right
Where are you
The ACLU isn't in Canada
That's funny
If Ellen was
Spider Bond
Her get elected committed as bright candidates prime minister
HEB
Probably a coincidence that right now as relevant as in the middle of a defamation trial
For saying that somebody was involved in a terrorist
Attack they weren't involved in
I'm at Alex's interview yeah it doesn't come up
Seems like that would be the first thing I would want to talk
Front of that thing
Nope
Does not huh
Yeah I think it's worth $200,000
I think that's the way
A couple new donors
He's going to need a lot of new donors
Let's cease being sued
According to chocks
Statement in the client
That's Bieber's new song Hampshire during is February 25th 2014
Broadcast that Chuck was involved in a shooting
Edmonton nightclub in 1993 when chocolate 19
Talk was acquitted of the 1993 charges and what he called a case of mistaken identity
If you mentally denied any involvement in the shooting saying he was at his parents house with friends and had absolutely no knowledge of what train
Inspired
That legitimate
News outlets
Don't just print the first name they can fight I don't know I don't know how that's going to play out but I do think it's a little bit of
Maybe an Alex Jones money bomb types
Situation
That's Abby
I don't know be funny if he was like where's the ACLU in there representing the other guys that would be quite funny I would enjoy that
An immense amount
Anyway
This is this episode when a little bit of a bummer for me top t2b top-to-bottom hat
It is over now
Is that the new way we signed up yet
Bee episode
Is over
Well I mean
The freak out that got edited out of A League of Their Own show
Try an outline one time
Quite an amazing thing to see
Because there's a point when Alex says s***
And I was like I got to go find the
I do find this on the court
It's gone
They cut that whole thing out
And put the
The Right video in
Where the
Didn't post
I'm furious
So depressing and the other thing is
The guest
I just don't care
Like you had Francis Boyle on the
The first ones are Francis Boyle
Excuse me
And then you had
Avril Lavigne
On the other one is neither of them are people I care about much
Shut off
I mean if they're going to bring something to the table that was interesting
Maybe but they did
Damped
Now that we've had two episodes back in the present I grow weary of it
Play Time time travel for Monday there is a little bit of that
Get browser on Twitter
Could please find a local charity or Bellefontaine area to help out people
Will be back but until then I'm here oh I'm Leo I'm dzx
Clerk I'm Daryl rundus
I'm the juiciest
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color