Damn important
I have great respect for knowledge like I'm sick of them posing
MoneyGram
Dot-com
Acknowledge
Just a little bit about Alex Jones
Doordash
What's up
And Auntie Brightspot
I could not resist the urge while I was sitting around the house
I saw those Coca-Cola with coffee gathering at me
They tried the vanilla one earn better than anyone else in certain areas in another's years simply impossible
Glutton for punishment
2 weird packaged Goods
I've never had it before it's like you're Guiding Light whenever you're at a store
Yeah but it also it's a pretty specific
Let's try that it was like
Coca-Cola now with octopus
Georgia
I'm kind of a really like
13 year old that kid might get excited by this cutaway
Grocers ropes came out like
5020 years old
We sold those of the movie theater I used to work out another 7
I'm sorry I'm not a snack
Vanilla one
And
I got to say
Who's better
Okay
Do really dry
Okay but it was kind of like you know the vanilla mask
Some of the problems of the coffee
What flavor is vanilla
Coffee shop
Not atrocious
I'd like when somebody describes wine to in there like it's got an Okie
You finishing this handsome
Fruit and there's somebody's like what what if we just added all those flavors in the coke maybe like a regular drink
Sommelier
Somali
You're already
Committed here this is nuts in the fridge
Just a matter of
How long
And how many times will I stare at it
Before I try
Yeah
What celebrity is it happens to be a very beautiful day
Chicago and my partner and I went and played tennis and
Wow
Outside is nice remember the outside I've heard of I've heard Tale
Doing it you were what are you do on the show again
Yeah
Do not part of it
Enjoying the outdoors life
We also have conversations about how much I love nature and how you think it sucks
To go away
There is that yes
Contradict
Well I'm glad you had fun playing big-time ping pong
Who is the original name
Originally ping-pong was called with
But before that
Tennis balls
What's pickleball
Pickleball is that related
Tennis
Is it to the one where it's got the Wiffle ball and there's holes in it need to do the thing with the
I don't know
Pickles are actually involved
Save-A-Lot and I don't know what to do
Just about it I'm going to look at me as soon as we stop recording
We're going to do in a little bit of a time travel Adventure
You ask that every time every can't go forward I've tried
We are going back
Back in 2010
Okay.
Magical eleven-year-old time of 2010
Yeah it's like
Turn of the millennium
Instead of the Iraq War we had more of
The Iraq War
The midterms coming up
Remind apocalypse on the horizon to wear that still the Cubs certainly
Lot interesting stuff happen
I'm excited to to Belen on this
But before we get into that looks like little moments
Joined up and are now policy want
The first doctor yummy feet
I'm a policy wonk
Brendan the policy
Brandon the policy one policy walk
The 12th
The Conqueror of five Empires lord of the blood pits of
Excuse me thinking about you and I'll probably walk
Thank you very much. Really pissed if you don't pronounce their name properly
Yeah there's a brutal brutal
Before my mispronunciations of rotation will hashtag on brand
Fleming's
I'm a policy wonk
Are you paranoid Lebanon
Thanks for the brain worms John much love from
Is my Wii connector
What's that I do believe that these are both about the same person
Dialogue
John I blame you for getting jokerfied love Rex Vegas much you're not bazzi
John is maybe getting Speedway
Text John
Chuck Jordan
Like I said we're going back
Kantime and
I've made this call on the show before I think I did it at a time when we had a smaller audience
Then we do now
And maybe just have a little bit more reach
I am so is anybody out there listening has access to really old Alex
What's Jones episodes
Late 90 really really
Try and find a way to get my hands on
Stuff from like 95 96 97
And if anybody has a line on those I've tried a number of avenues
And they all kind of reach that at
A lot of people have
Some tips
Did you text him
No
I have not
Last option
That assumes that you already have his number
There are a number of has that I've gone down that
Seems like I was
Bissell Bissell workout
I think there's
Summit there
The episodes exist somewhere
That for sure
But it's very very
Define the run any any meaning for what
Library Congress
Yeah
Absolutely
So today Jordan I was trying to find a fun time travel things
To do
And
You know it's tough
Challenge
And you're a witch so you have high standards
Yeah it might my standards for witchcraft.
I got a message from Nate by the name of Kirby Fergus
Videos on YouTube
Derby just finished up
Duo videos
About Joe Rogan and Alex's last interview and so
Techniques on the styles that are used in the conversation
As I started thinking like
That's fine some Rogan
Oh no no I went back to September 15th 2010
Transmission
Hi I got a call last night
Fighting
Is in town and he was inviting me tonight
You come into school yet
And get his view on politics and quote conspiracies
So that is good
Enough
No no
Not enough this is before The Joe Rogan Experience
Or like at the very beginning of it maybe I would have a hard time knowing exactly when it start
I know that
Promotes joerogan.net
Which is his website
Experience
Menasha Lake
See it maybe being in like its earliest
Stages
At the very least we know he does not have 100 million dollars yet he certainly doesn't
But he does have a friend okay
Eddie Bravo know he's also going to
Alright okay
Today we got an episode
With Alex Atienza Rogan
Is Alex's Studio a glimpse back on cell
Take a little bit of a load off from present-day nonsense
Maybe a little bit lighter
This was back when Eddie Bravo is still a
Practicing doctor
Right doctor jiu-jitsu
He is
Pizza
He's not made for SEC controlled thing
We'll get to it when we get today
So Alex is going to talk to them at the end of the
Let's start our baby
I wonder what's going on beforehand
What sort of show they're going to buy
If buy a
Appearing on it being advertised as credits on the show what are they basically wearing elephant
So are we get to
Talking about how
Back when his grandma's was around you know Grandma's time it was offensive to see a belly button
Then I Dream of Jeannie okay
But now Society is collapsing
I was talking to my mom and she was discussing her grandmother
Back in the sixties
Was over at their house
And she saw I Dream of Jeannie
And she was just shocked
Halifax
Was visible
And now
You can make fun of people
Shocked by things
Like that but civilizations have been wild and crazy before
People singing
Millions and millions
Simulated murders
Austin torture
And every time I go to a movie.
A fan really violent films
What
What is a serious contact
I would like to be there when the road came out
A few years ago I saw it on DVD and was
Profoundly affect
Goodbye because I'm
I don't know
Cannibalism in deprivation
I never
Are you
I never put the pieces together until that clip
Entire idea of like everyone becomes a cannibal within 15 days is just from the road
Straight up
Yeah I wouldn't I wouldn't rely on Cormac McCarthy for the betterment of mankind
In terms of thematic elements
Alex pretend
Studies
Just kind of like a bunch of
Bad people who were cannibals in the road
If they made a movie of it I could see Alex
Is devil being based on the
Judge from Blood Meridian bud
That was a book
And it's hard to read even if you're good at
Readings out
Post-apocalyptic
Fiction novel
Viggo Mortensen
Yeah yeah yeah
Most historical examples of cannibalism have been in ritual contact
Text which makes sense because
Does the amount of energy
Exert to kill and eat an uncooperative human would not be worth
Whatever nutritional value game
He'll be smarter from a Clark
Perspective to eat
Just about anything
It's just another example of some supposedly research position that Alex is a
He's coming from a movie
Experience is real
I would argue that man
He's the most dangerous game
Because
It fights back and it's harder and crap is easier game
Yeah
And that includes leaves and s*** man it's not hard
And
The other thing to his icuee will find a number of examples over his
History of course of people who are in desperate
Cannibalism
It would make those
Sort of unique
Isolation
Crucial for those
Yeah it's
The lack of
Other legitimate option
Eat somebody
If they were on
Perhaps
A road
It would be far easier the problem for many of these people is that they are
In the middle of nowhere with no hope of Escape or is wildlife
Substantially easier and better.
Forever 12
Not eat
So much better than a teepee
You don't need to wait 15 days to fix
So dumb
Hello what a dumb dumb
I'm not going to eat any of these goddamn fruits
So Alex has this idea that like
Any easier to touch. It in that last clip
This notion that fake violence
On TV and seeing it
Makes you
Experience at the same way you'd experience real violence
And I have some thoughts
Oh yeah
Or somebody who shocked
Buy images of violence and death
Someone
Mackinvia
Shocked by the image of children have been Napalm with their skin burned off
People were shocked by the image of
Vietnamese police
Blowing a man's head off in the street
That's what now
Not the
B they don't have a
Common sense
And see they have an experienced trauma
Wild
And this is all been done by
Your kids
You're even your own family isn't going to be shocked by to just accept it bad things
Because the mind
As
Ezreal
Cut off
The clip is really key to me
It's one of the only times I
Remember we're really disappointed he got cut off by the brake
Kind of interested in where he was going
A Galaxy's lamenting how fake violence on TV is experienced by people as real violin
Sensitize them to see against
Centers of real-life vile
I don't know how common that is necessarily as a phenomenon I bet there is some
A fact that it has but
I know that I've seen plenty of horror movies in my life and I still pretty much
Experience
The violence
What's that I do
Actual
Pro wrestling is a really good example of
I can watch people hit each other with chairs and send each other through tables
Real I would not enjoy it
Anytime it appears that someone is actually hurt themselves in a wrestling reality Creeps in and
Become worried for the performer
Because it's possible to enjoy the narrative.
Depiction of combat
And still remember that it's
The performer performing
Then there's stuff like the UFC where people are fighting for real and people are
Trying to hurry
This is still kind of ritualize violin
Everyone watches
Understand that these are two trained competitors
Agreed to fight each other under
Specific rules
To see who's better at the sport
It's closer to real-world violence
Formalize professional
Both parties have consented
Do what's going on
And then there's movies right
Right which are just totally fictional fictional yes
Most people can tell the
Prince between these forms of
Display the violence and experienced them differ
Currently weather that different experiences conscious or subconscious
It seems to me that Alex cannot
And he assumes that because that is his
Experience
Everyone else must also not be able to differentiate
Now here's where this point gets
Important
Because Alex can't tell the difference between
Fiction and reality
You can't also tell the
Prince between reality and
In the same way that he thinks that a fictional movie like the road
Depict illegitimate realist
The cannibal future
You have the tendency to think very real thing
Like a Sandy Hook shooting
We're completely stage
Alex pretends that exposure
Two petitions violence
Has made everyone desensitized to real-world Island
And yet in my experience what are the major themes of the show is denying the experiences of
People who
Experience the effects of real-world violence
Because he thinks
I think that's an important dynamic 22rec
Yeah that mean there's that extra level of not just
Because you know
She can't tell the difference
Between reality and fix
And so he assumes everybody else can
I do think there is a
Dynamite
But that like second level of of
Course he
Pant also not
Assume that of everyone
Because if he were to realize that
People can
Easily
Where's between reality
Infection
An attack upon Him person
Or it would tell him that it's possible to tell the
Between reality and
You know so
The only way that
He can maintain his psyche
Through this is by assuming
That not only
Can nobody else tell the difference
Between reality and
He's the only person
Who can tell you
You can't tell that
Difference between reality and
Yeah
Perhaps that is
That is true
Yeah he's a mess
That's a real bummer
Another story that's going around
This is this is interesting to me because
You know about the political divide
Left-right Paradigm is an illusion and it's all meant
Democrat
Right
Republican
Meaningless words just inviting
For no reason
This seems weird
This is a big story and Infowars
Dot-com by Kurt demo Pennsylvania Homeland Security put the and attack protesters
Unlisted
And we got
Same reports out of Texas
6 years ago
Western Gun Owners veterans
As the number one threat
But because it was Bush's Administration doing it
Conservative media wouldn't pick up on it
Now that it's Obama
Meet the new boss same as the old boss
Like the song says
It's like oh my gosh
Conservative
You've always been the enemy
Watch conservative pundits
On Fox and it wasn't on the radio
Read
I knew they were reading Federal demonization scrubs
Floating the teleprompter is a globalist
They're getting a direct
Government propaganda feed
We know they're bad
Open and shut
If you under
Understand what are you saying
He's saying when he's trying to make this argument that he's Above This sort of left right
He's saying
That
Obama
Is targeting
Conservative
In the same way that
The conservative
Targeted
Still left isn't
The target of any of this stuff in
If they are always
The victim of no matter what
The enemy of the global
He's vs conservative
Like Alex's
Interesting
It's only the only the far-right
Only the flower
But it is interesting that he can articulate this
This idea doesn't matter who's in charge after all the same but
The thing that he's
They're all the same
What is that
They're all globalist
To hate
Super fall right people
Yeah I mean essentially it's like a we don't have any white nationalist candidates and then
Do they got a white
Nationals candidate they were like holyshit this is what we've been
You starting to see a little bit of the beginning of that materializes
Going into
A possibility
Beat with the Tea Party being on the ride because of
It was a major driver
Not cokehead brother
So there is something that's going on
At this point
In September
And that is that Christine O'Donnell
I was running for the seat
In Delaware
And there's been some
A little bit of a problem
Karl Rove had come out and you had an interview
That was a little bit
Play critical
Of of O'Donnell
And Alex's
Is not happy
Here is the New York Times today GOP leaders say Delaware upset
Hertz
Hopeful
Now they basically said the same thing about Rand Paul
Today
The campaign against team
They put all their money
Behind the Republican establishment bailout candidate
They demonized him just like the Democrats are now doing
And he's widened his lead
Against the Democrat
In the last few months since he won the Primary
Against the Republic
They said the same thing
People extreme like him
And they lied about what he really stood for
He can't win
Until they create the Shelf
Because they can't win the Republican
Creating the hoax
With the Democrats
Realty
Actually
You are against
The out-of-control spending the banker bailouts and rust out of it
That that
They can't win I need to go for establishment
The same Republicans that are for
More Banker bailout
The same Republicans
Under Bush.
The same Republicans like
Global carbon Tax Center
And
The hoax intensifies I have the transcript
But it's up on
Infowars.com and prisonplanet.com
In an article that Paul Watson
Anti-establishment
A hammer blow to the Washington Elite
Here's a transcript
From Fox News
From last night Karl Road questions
Christine O'Donnell serious
Character problems
And then I have the quotes here
Because it took years for her to pay off her student loans
Bet that is deceptive again these serious questions about
How does she make her living
Why did she
Mislead voters about her college education
How come it took nearly two decades to Collegeville
I see numbers of upwards of half of
Many college students now not paying their loans
Cancel it
Yeah that would make sense you're on top of it you should absolutely cancel student
Disposition
That means
Bro was just
Protecting his Brands hair and everybody's bran
It's not really anything more inch
Sting and seeing conventional Democrats be resistant to embrace AOC
Enterprising
There's just that
Pension
Someone like O'Donnell in particular and the Aesthetics of
The Tea Party in general where this departure from the type of politics
The Grove
Excel that for decades
So I obviously would represent a threat to his position in the market either the strategist or commentator on Fox
Yeah let's keep the depths of our evil quieter guys
Is Karl rove's
Philosophy I believe
In the end was probably right
I know Donna was unlocked
She finished third in the GOP Primary 2000
Text after making
Pretty offensive comments about the lgbtq community and in Lost b2008 general elections
Joe Biden
Who's simultaneously running for vice president
Dude followed this up by losing
The 2010 general election after it came out that she had quote
Dappled in witchcraft
In high school
More to the problem released of this ad
I'm not aware
I'm nothing
You've heard
I'm you
None of us are perfect
But none of us
Can be happy
With what we see all around
Politicians who
Bending
Trading favors
Backroom deals are the ways to
The standoff
I'll go to wash
And do what you do
I'm Christine O'Donnell
I approve this message
I'm you
I was really hoping she say I'm not a witch
Cynthia just like just to reiterate
I'm not awake
I'm not a witch
Obviously I don't care if someone mess around with sandwich
The coolest people I know it's been some time in that water
I don't care but man Republic
Looking boaters sure do
It's one thing to dabbles in witchcraft in your past when you're trying to run for office
But it's another thing to kuttanad that's
I'm not a witch
That's so goofy and embarrassing from a political strategy perspective
Anyone who would do that is someone you shouldn't trust to make good decisions
If you don't indication of them having bad dreams
Surrounded by people Arvada
10 states and neither is a good option
This 2010 midterm and the Tea Party candidates
Who came into office with a world warning
Of the future we were heading toward
It's not surprising to look back in 2010
Nancy Alex supporting someone like Christine O'Donnell
Flash Forward to today to see him backing Marjorie Taylor Greene
Is what he does
The issues about O'Donnell's College history and Loans probably sound like Petty issues
WinCo Road was making was more that the way that O'Donnell was addressing these questions about her history didn't come off as convinced
For instance as early as 2006
She claimed to be a graduate of Fairleigh Dickinson University but
Actually didn't
L degree until September 20th
Attempt
The reason for the delay at first
Couldn't claim to be student loan related issue
I look at the lake
But then the story became that she had to finish an outstanding elect
Of course before
Get her degree
Road was expressing on Fox News
But if she was going to win she would have to be more forthright
He said exactly that
She can't get away with simply saying my answers on my website or it's puzzling to me why the IRS would file a lien for me
When I didn't pay my taxes
I mean she's got to be more honest than
If she does she's got a shot to win
But it's got to be passionate and factual on hard head
Yeah you know and I
The very
You should have somebody like me if you're going to cut a political ad
Because if you open with I'm not a witch
The reasonable person's responses that's just what
Which would say
Right
She's like
Woodstock Inn right there
Anybody with
Like just a little bit of political instinct
Thanks for any awareness of how
The media Cycle Works
You're going to get
Piled on for that leave it alone I'm not a witch
So easy to ignore dad about how compassionate you are and how you care about the needs of the people of Delaware
Don't jump
Get ahead of the whip
I got to go. I got to get out in front of this witch thing
What's really funny about that is
Christine O'Donnell.
Immediately popped up there was a space in my brain for it
But I wasn't 100% sure and then you said which and I was like
Oh yeah I remember that I remember that
All that much about hair appointment
Because he likes who does
Seem to like her
I don't know this lady from them
Side of a barn
But the fact that that's how I take my pills
The fact that the system is demonizing
The fact that they have the Republicans and Democrats coming out against her
Cialix is just
Like the fire
Tyrese
Why isn't Alex talking about how she's a witch
It's because
Backflip doesn't come out until two days after
Boy
Replace back two days later
Jesus
Snooze cycle
Playing the clip
Rose
Talking on Fox
Snooze and I think this is really interesting
Because Alex
Sex it up
Pretty poorly
Play Short clip
I'm Coral Road
Really demonizing
This poor lady
And just repeating
That talking point over and over again that she has serious
Character problem
Find out what they are
Oportun loans
$11,000 lien on her
From the IRS
No due process I just slapped it on
You know what if you poop
For cap and tax
And you have an opponent that says they wouldn't
Then they have a choice they have an option
It was it was very sensitive very based on issues
It does conservatives support candidates who at the end of the day
While they may be conservative in their public statements
Do not Avenge the characteristics of rectitude and truthfulness
And insincerity and character that they voters are looking I think
She doesn't
This little guy up there high-and-mighty
I tell you
Yahoo
Vote for who you can time the grand poobah
I'm going to tell you Republicans what
You can and can't do
You're need to stay on the Karl Road reservation
Because I am morally a Pyrex
This is the guy lying about wmd
So what you have is Alex introduces this clamp in a way that the clip doesn't actually reflect what he say
Is actually making a
FairPoint
In terms of the context
To this conversation
That is theirs
Some kind of
Non forthrightness
What's going on
Yeah that is not great
Yeah yeah Dan so in order for Alex to deal with lipids
Play the attacks
I'm sure he's just
I don't care but
Sing f*** him and then you lied about weapons master
Destruction doesn't deal with the issue that he brings up
Oh my God you're all liars
Snarky
Debate kid
Online and I would say that is a
Who does the personal attack
And I have scored a point
Yeah whatever
You can do it whenever I mean
The audience enjoys it
I think you even
I'm kind of enjoy it
Enjoy what
Just piling on Karl Road
Alright
I don't have any
Skin in that game I just I just like to see a
Baby s*** piled on car rollover
Is a good day for
So it is next week we see Alex doing something we saw her recently on another I believe time travel episode
We saw him
Pretending to discover the strategy of
Google bombing
Google search the term
Gates death
Panels
Gates
Gates death
Panels
Just search those three words in Google
In every major search engine do it over and over again
And send the story out to everyone and click on the story
It's already the number one link and you type in Bill Gates death panel
On
Google news in its article regarding number one
And then hundreds of papers and blogs if you've seen
You'll cause another chain
Reaction
Bill
Gates is who we're going after today and for the next 11 sheet
Hellboy
It's interesting to think about like the 11 years
Intermediate
I like
Free careers Allison Bill Gates
There is there's a moment where they could have come together you know
It's one of those I took the path less trod.
Stylistics calls
A lot of it ends up being about vaccine
Sure
A caller
Today is because you're a witch
This caller is is
Is a
Scheduled to be vaccinated
Short as Alex has a
But as waiter
Is it you
Here's a bad metaphor
Stars going to to thank you for what you do
You're my hero
A bondsman to say that
Really nervous. Apologize
I have a 2 month old son
Our first child
And he's about to get
Richard
Schedule
Vaccines and stuff like that
Schedule to get on trains and get the f***
What's your schedule
Your time to ride the carousel in Logan's Run
Just cuz they say it's scheduled
I think so I'm not real sure I let me do it more in the hospital
Roof
So that's
Atone
He was coming at the
This caller with the colors you're saying that the schedule 2/2
Keynesian
They were scheduled you know I really like not having measles
And I I think I might childhood was better for not having measles
Great
To not have polio
And of course
You died of the whooping cough
Yeah well that was
That was a struggle
I think that's great but
17 of your siblings died of tetanus
Doesn't it seem like
That should be an easier sell
What hey
You know how we don't have polio
That's because of the vaccine
So just because of hand-washing
Or something
That really bother
Really bothers me the f****** witches in people being good for a while or when I left
So
To see the way this town were
Restart the call and the guy just says it is getting scheduled
Immediately
He Compares it to trains in the haluk
Call Rye Rye
Penny he tries to sort of play reasonable
A little bit
A decision you have to make
Now the Japanese it's got to be more than what are we doing
Because they
Found completely that
This stuff cause the neurological problems autoimmune problem
But it's much worse when I was a little bitty baby
Has all the shots
It won't stunt them
Tonight Alex is trying to play that hey everybody's got to make their own decision
And then immediately jumps to the story about Japan which is a complete lie
In 1994 Japan amended the law that they had they have a law that made vaccines mandatory
Demanded this making instead
It was more of a civic duty than a strict legal obligation
According to the aafp
The World Health Organization stats
2018 reflective vaccination rate of 99%
For tetanus diphtheria
Pertussis in 1 year old Japanese children in 97% for the same age group
With the polio vaccine
Making s*** up to demonize vaccination put it's important to pay attention to that
That way that he's trying to frame thing
You know what you did
The color brings this up
Comparison to the Holocaust everybody's got to make the wrong decision but also here's a lie about Japanese
People okay so if
99% 97 percentage Avenue
These babies
We can look back and
And see if
His numbers makes
25 years
Later whatever
They don't sell
Can't we be done then
But we can't because Alex is now because Alex has said
Everybody needs to make up their online
We have the proof
Concert from Japan
Look a got to make up their own mind I'll call her this caller is still on the line
This is f***** up this is not what you do when you want someone to make up their own mind
Answer your question
Yeah I really really appreciate that and I appreciate your time
I guess I'm just not going to do what I mean I mean
The winner he comes over enough to go to school and then with that will that be a problem
It out in the open
Now they say Okay Mercury there is good for you
And you say I know you got the waiver
It's not even law but it's a waiver to a non law
So they make a list of
Not even do that
I'm from the feds
The Federal
97%
And then you can already have Google.
Tennessee
Vaccine
Waiver
Conscientious objector religious objector
And you can go really principal
Or assistant principal
Here's to waiver for Tennessee
You lied to me
And so you'll know you're there with a hardcore liar
Entire government corporate system train
Any teachers take their kids and injected with a
And they love the fact that many stools a third of the school down special ad
How's the children
Football helmet literally
Kaiser belt
And they loved it they just love all that and soon the whole school beats in the corner drooling
Savagely
Make a cement and then just come in and had two helicopters fly over and spray gas and kill everybody
Everybody ready for that
Those are criminals
Nnnn
Appreciate your call
Anybody's in gentleman
Everybody's got a backup
F****** bad you
They're trying to kill you and I love
Book everybody's got their own choice between getting murdered in their own bed and being a heroic patriot who gives me money
Episode of Big Show
That would have made
Oh well we get another caller
This is just for good clean
There's a little bit of parsley
JFK documentary
And then we find that Alex doesn't know a variable
Bit of trivia about JFK
Now he he fancies himself kind of like a guy Knows Alot About That
Conspiracy
The conspiracy guy
Kind of rough that he doesn't know the
Kind of a big one
Incredible deep deep you should watch
It's revealing even some of the attorneys that were defending
Date the guy who took over JFK's
Nakia members name
When heat when they assassinated him
Who is the who's an expert
Vice president who took over
Well it was it was Robert Kennedy
What
Of course
Who is JFK's Vice
President
I'm having a moment your I should know that
Yeah you should f****** know
Is a big part of the
The reason is my God is probably one of the bigger
List reasons that Alex
Hateful left anyways hope it's because of LBJ that we got the
Civil Rights Act
Because of him he fought to
To The Nail for a long time
The part of the actual
Eventually remember LBJ couldn't come up with
Who was lbj's vice
President
Wow buddy how did that
Take like a little bit of a second
But like that's too long
Yeah and especially for LBJ
Who is kind of a big figure in America
Figure 8 JFK assassination
Totally
In fact
One of the many people sis
Murder
Definitely
Weird
So now we get to the point of the episode where
We get the introduction
Of Joseph Road
And Edward Bravo
Call boy
It's interesting they were different back then
Well maybe not
Joe's definitely High
This is really awkward
Awkward
Well it's good having you here it was good seeing you last night either so much to talk about obviously Joe Rogan of Newsradio
Fear Factor The Man Show
Obelisk goes on and on UFC Ultimate Fighting Championship
Pretty much since the start haven't you I started working for the UFC in 1997
The post-fight interview
13 years
Yeah it's been a long time
I remember like an I-9
Madness UFC's going to be
You're crazy
What's now
Giant
Austin Texas
Frontier
You know when I was with Ventura last week one of the guys from the
Company that do stuff for UFC was there he was going every Brock Lesnar
Right after that one
I told rocks back bigger than ever huh
Yeah
That's great it's not as Electric
As some of this present day stuff and I think it's cuz I would
Texas sober
A Berkeley different chemistry Grease the wheels on this
Remind me to be some grease on these wheels that's awesome
Holy Ship
S*** this is not what I expected
Alex is sitting here with
Eddie and Joe
All of the human
Elements
Are there for the
Record-setting most listened to podcast ever
Edmonton the sequel
Eddie it is just
Trashy I got to be drunk
You got to be in Rogan's house
Cindy got to be a half of a fifth through
I think there's some funny
Stuff to get into energy
Really gigantic live at Alex Telles
But this is a case of me getting it on my own
Petard
I legitimately thought it would be fun
Kind of
It's not it's a
Define interview for the most part
Like broken
Hi
Pencil like Alex is talking about like all we're talking
Last night you told me something really interesting
And it's clearly that Rogan was like trying to spit
Football maybe who's working on a joke
Or something as like a real point
That I thought were
Right on
The red button
You're talking about how that I believe that
All human behavior is not
Just like I believe that all animal behaviors natural
Humans are far more complex but
We don't think of ourselves as being natural that we're moving a natural Direct
And I think that June things in a human society especially with
Technology I think we create
We create technology and
That's what we're here for
And it's very possible that we human beings are here for
Is to make some new reality make some new
Technological innovation that's going to change the world and egg
Could could be
A big bang machine it could be a time machine it could be
Just some
In in in
Incredible
Discovery something they're going to invent eventually maybe keep going with things like the Large Hadron Collider then I going to stop there
Use whatever findings that they get for the Large Hadron Collider
If it doesn't blow up the world
And they're going to try the next thing
The joke is that we're here to make the big bang
Every fifteen billion years these intelligent monkeys get to a point where they break down matter and try to figure out what
What is at the center of the universe
Restart all over again
Just speculation
Wow
Heavy man
MattyB
I think I think Douglas Adams put it better that if the question and the answer we're ever known than the
Will be destroyed and replaced by something weirder
Is a lot
Simpler insurance
That kind of a thing is like yeah I could imagine getting high with
Someone
Like a lot of the people I knew in college and have an almost identical conversation 100
There's something wrong with the
Simulation Theory
Buying place for Jodha exist
Older brother who's into weed
Only stolen a few beers
Sure at this point
Goodbye in Spanish
Can be useful in people's lives like
I can open up the you're at your brain to nuvista
It's just not
That deep a minute also
Clearly
You can tell the Joe was talking about this as some kind of like a knife
Idea
Has the structure of a Rogan
Yeah it has the structure of something you could
See him doing on stage
Alex Isley
Yeah bad
0 it is at 8
Big idea that humans are
Not being able to parse out do you like reality and
You can't have jokes if you don't realize the
The transgression over reality
Start wise humor is Soto
Alex now gets the train
Plug some Eddie Bravo
Jiu jitsu
Got both of you found out your website
Joe Rogan. Net
Ajj
Change to jitsu
Dot-com
Stuff everywhere
10th Planet stubborn
25 I think
Jiu jitsu teachers
So I'll say yes
He's one of the most Innovative and
Importance of Justice charge
Probably be asked is my best friend but it really is true
He's
Important
Weed and comes up with crazy to get to Moses
Turns out they work
And I'm also known as
There's freaking me
Eddie sounds like
Kind of fun
I'm here
Proceeding as
Energy is off
It seems like
Eddie or Alex should have just been like
Let's do some
Conspiracy theory
What we're here for
To push in that direction but Alex can't because no one
If you got to talk to
Pidgeotto
The big star whatever
It's more of that like
He's not f*****-up
And he doesn't want it
I just think it's that he left it too weird
Yes
I just looked it up it turns out that
Podcast
Started in December
So he's almost
Herein
The Rogan
Inexperienced
Yeah
So Alex is talking about
Eddie wants to know
About the
Troops
And they like
Drug trade
Opium in Afghanistan
Okay okay
One of his one of his like
Money I'll text Emily make money selling drugs
How was the actual process for
We never do get an answer on
Well.
I think it's fascinating because
Is it is the behavior that
That you see on the Joe Rogan
. whenever Alex is a guest
Being carried out by Joe
11 years prior
It's flowing out and the US troops protect the opium
At and no no no I'm serious I play a clip of Fox News Geraldo sing out patriotic
You think I'm joking
So he calls them on
Recalls
Alex on this
Show me this video
So they start playing the clip
But Joe and Eddie don't have headphones
How did the Americans get paid
For the opium
That's what I'm saying
It gets
Rivera
Coherent
Headphones on
North or
Position
I don't know if he was the one who had the
Zapruder film first on television
The word is he knows all about this stuff
What are arabica helping them grow the opium
Eliezer
What
Here's the actual clip but Alex is talking about
Innocent victim
And we are tolerating it
Abby opium speakers
The population would turn against them
Security risk
Lieutenant Colonel Bryan Christmas
The commanding officer of the Third
6 Marines
Contradiction
What are you doing about your culture
So well my grind in my gut and it's what they do we provide them security
About giving them seed and fertilizer something about alternative crops
Can grow instead of poppy but
Taking all of their
They're popular destroying the field
Wouldn't be productive
Go to the mission then
He's trying to undertake
What's goes to Commercial and he shows
Presumably Jose seen it
Zebra too dumb
Completely edited version of it
A fascinating piece of video footage with Geraldo Rivera
In-N-Out in the poppy store
The poppy fields and
Acting up and providing them fertilizer and helping them grow it
I mean
Rideable
I'm it's
Outrageous if you go and actually watch
Today's like the context of it is really
The Opium sap
The plant and I watched everyone that was for sale
Cotton watermelon cucumber it's all great stuff they grow out here. We just want to see that that come to
Completely outer to the contacts that Alex
Is describing it in and it's also counter
Contacts
But Joe is been convinced.
We want to see the puppy go away is a very hard sentence to avoid when you're art
They're helping them grow it
Specifically in the fertilizer and when you look at the eclipse
Specifically seed and fertilizer in the contacts exactly
Other crops that can grow in
This behavior is so consistent throughout Joe Rogan career with Alex
I just don't
I can't believe that it
It's not
I don't know what to think about
Is it okay
Stop himself with being
Yeah
He's too credulous towards a guy who has been lying to him since they met
Doesn't
Video like
It's believable
No it's not it's not believable it's hard to it
I can't Square the idea that he is not in on it and some fat
At least a little bit
This level of being duped
Yeah
It's
Pathologic
Like it would
Have to show up in all of his other relationships
Advantage of him
Subway
Honestly I don't
I think that's
Unbelievable
You had Steven Crowder
Wasn't the molyneux on there all the time
I think there is a decent chance
It's that maybe he is pathologically gullible gullible
Open his relationships with the people like
The closer Folk
Looks like an Ari shaffir
Tom Segura
Bert Kreischer Comics hang around with other,
Next we don't know what you normal people are doing
We don't know what's going on with you guys you could say anything We're just trying to write B man I guess you got
Take comedians out of the
Out of the entire conversation
Is that the whole other world has seen a lawyer
Yeah I find it I find it difficult to believe that that
That's true though cuz
It would be
It would be something that I think
Think he would need to
Get therapy with electric made it to the point he's at he falls for this kind of s***
On a regular basis
I also do
1st and what
So special about Alex
Yeah that requires him to make excuses for decades
I know it does seem like he has like a weird
Appeal to Authority like hack
NM
We're if you just say something so
Confidently and you have like a
A group
People who
Tell Joe that
That you're at you're actually a very smart person
And then you just say something confidently Jose like wow
A lot of people
Please cool it does seem like there's that just
Oh okay well I heard this was cool
And this guy is
I told this guy super smart so I have to at least engage with it and then
It's too easy.
It's just
It's just remarkable to me to see the exact same
Dynamic
That happened
In these present-day podcast appearances
Being done to Rogan
In 2010
This lying about the context or something
Joe calls him on it
And then there's evidence proffered
Weather
The evidence
B given is
Selectively edited to the point where it only shows without
Usher
DC Zatanna
Except Alex's framing of it despite the
Right context that that's to the contrary
Whatever it is he's not equipped to deal with
The sort of people leaves
Clearly
And then I met you do and now of course it's got to be ten million times as hard
Because if you confront that
Reality now
Then you have to
To be like
Well for the past
30 years
This guy I have thought with my friend
Has been taken
Sweet piece of s*** liar to me that's almost like
You know you get that Nigerian prince email
Give $1,000
It's almost like Jose pot committed on not calling out Alex at this point
Pennywise sorry Joe
Dog did you grown up
Did you ever
I don't know if this is like sort of it.
That I had
It's more Universal
Bunch of National Geographic
Effects on the house
Tons of magazines National Geographic
Educational philosophy
Berkshire
Things about Florida
Preston
Animals dinosaurs
Is it National Geographic was too believed in Evolution for my household at the
The time itself
What did you know that Nat Geo is putting out a lot of
Cover-ups
Cover okay
Okay
Entrails
You know what it is Nat Geo put Southeast
Connect with the government
You've all heard about
How record numbers of missionary turn out to be CIA
National Geographic
Is a Eugenics organization and they are the highest level CIA front
Malarkey
A very good friend of mine his father is in the CIA
Cool
Okay my buddies dad is in the CIA so obviously met Geo is
The f****** higher-level
It's meaningless
But it's never substantiated in a high-level CIA operation
Highest level
Throw that out there and then 12
You guys are going to say this is malarkey
But my buddies dad is in the CIA
Sad Joe Biden stole Malarkey from Rogan
That's what he gave him a hundred million dollars for
Extra
So
Conspiracies that
You know
Doesn't seem to be on the Earth is flat
At least not yet
Right right
Actually that actually comes
2 point I want to make
I'm at is the Earth is flat
We were trying to get to this for a while okay I've been waiting for you
Sooner or later we discovered Asians off every year
Interested to see if like
You go back and you'd see the same conspiracies
But he's into in the present being floated in 20
If the Earth is flat now it was no less flat then
It's not like
These ideas weren't spiraling around in places on the entry
A recent phenomenon
I was going back
It's incredible there is not anything like Flat Earth stuff and part of the reason
That wasn't that popular
In 2010
It wasn't
And this is something that's important to understand about conspiracy
Theorists
They think that they are independent thinkers
And they think they're like
Really
Really digging into thread
Pill man they are the biggest f******
Can followers in the world
Things Are
Popular
And then they get into them
And then they like
Like nothing ever happened
And something else
To become popular
He said probably a Sandy Hook truther whenever that was popular
No it's a fashionable it's a fashion
Theories are fashion
And some things are aesthetically important to retain along the way
Much like
I may not listen to the Bosstones anymore but I'll still be a Bosstones fan until I die sure he's going to be a 9/11
Truther until he dyed his hair
But it's maybe not the most primary things
Need to talk about all the time
But if you can't
Your life always talking about 911 to be a piece of
Each of Our Guest
And I
I found that fascinating that is a kraut yeah
Of course you're into what you're into at the time that he's into it the time
Is it to Hurricane Katrina
What do you think about
The conspiracy theories about
Katrina being a controlled
Hurricane house the way it
Multiple top meteorologists said it had two eyes for a while and just sat there and didn't act like a normal hurricane
The father of weather weapons on
Was flying into Cyclones
Add a long story short
1967 Stanford Research Institute
Can create and control hurricane
So
Was
Weather weapon Horizon
We don't get back to this
It was or it wasn't
Cool yeah
Well let's see if
Katrina was Aiken
Controlled hurricane
Sent by whom would be the first question that isn't
An important first question we would assume the American government
Warrior or a foreign power
Follow y
Specifically where it was
Was attacked so then you got to say that it's a weapon I would assume
Another conspiracy to get
It's loaded with a comeback
Break is that the movie
Is meant to start a race war
Okay
So you believe that the movie Machete with Danny Trejo
Is by the government designed to fuel race war hero Mexican
Home Depot guy
Peter answers
Just just
Okay
Stop guys
Come on
Sorry guys
Alex is not drunk
Did we just racial slur iFixit
So you and Alex
Eddie Bravo.
Explained that he is
Right
Certainly not to images on the radio I wouldn't put that one out there
I would put your business out like that better situation
Seems like whoever was on the button on the red button there
Yeah yeah big bang machine
Actual adults working for him instead of hiring teens
We have Alex
Sober trying to deal with doing a
Michelle that has X
CC rules
With two guys who are high
One of them
Clearly eluded
And unable to
What's the deal with AF
So he's been shamed
Teddy's been shamed a little bit
Received
The background
Wow joke
Complains about the governor of Arizona
Hilarious is that dumb lady that's running Arizona Jan whatever the hell her name is
Who's it the who's the governor of Arizona
That lady is so dumb
Dumb have you ever seen her on TV
Oh my God
Pause
Coupons like
Ten solid seconds
Said nothing
To make some stuff about people getting their heads cut off over in the Arizona
The Mexicans are coming over here and cutting people's heads off
Sounds like Alex
I don't think
Joe should be allowed to call
No
It's tough to hear
Yeah it's
It's interesting cuz Alex Len has to sort of
Rebuttal little bit
Because he is also
Quite xenophobia
He's trying to be at your cutting in on my racism here. There's a Republican
Is Benita have sort of at least a little bit of
The pushback
Sure
Element of Chaos
Let me know
I'm not a big fan of Joe knows if I hate
Superman
The movie
Bravo come on man we're on the radio
Professional
I'm a Mexican
Thelma said I wasn't the greatest whatever
Please try to get back to machete
Is that what we were doing
Superhero movies
Haha
Okay
Has Eddie goes on I think he's making actually a fairly decent point
And that is
You know what I as somebody of Mexican descent
Heritage
I
See Spider-Man
Gotta fly with Spider-Man with Batman
I don't I don't see myself in these these Heroes and For Me Maybe machete
Is it somebody that I can see as
Not on eyes not nice enough to white people
Mexican you can't relate to Spider-Man
You know and then
And then
We're going to have dinner
We can have Mexican people we have nothing now we have something
Is Superman a white guy from another galaxy
Now we have, cheddar
You know premier
Felt like a Mexican scientist
Who you know who becomes something superhero hacks up Durango
People up with a
The axe that ridiculous long-haired cat
Let me tell you something the Mexicans I know that warned me about this film that run the production
What stereotype of Mexican
Working at Home Depot in wanting to kill Gringos
Hahaha
TextNow app
Yeah
I think he makes a fine point
Look for the most part of me I think
Acceptable point and I think Alex is playing at these essential he's just
I don't know why we can't be having superheroes who are nice
Hellboy
So
We get a really big revele
On this episode
What's up
Cliff Superman
Did I don't know KK's expansion efforts in His Radio serials
I don't know how the mainstream media
The MSM
Failed to pick up on
What could be
The largest story of our times
Okay and that is the Alex Jones knows how to mind
Control Birds
I've even tried this with birds around my house and things if I come out in
Put my mind the antenna
I'm going to kill that bird
But if you're just being out nice and friendly
LaBarge to sit there almost land on you
Your hand
Telepathic
Pick up on me to take this clip and use it and say Alex Jones
Uses mind control on birds
Probably will I have fulfilled the prophecy
Drawn Birds
I just have to play it to the bank you could not do it
It had to be a little bored
At this point like pigs
I'm starting to fall apart a little bit
Patience
And their their high is like kind of like
Having fun
Whenever Eddie starts trying to talk and his
Like just a normal way he's so
Socially communicate
He ends up saying things but he can't say on the radio or friend at work you're not allowed
This hardware store let me drop some
Racial slurs
Is this the last
Lips here
Is it possible to create a bomb that make everybody gay
Probably not
Okay
Bleed nut
So this is where like sort of questions are coming a little faster
Can you make a gay bar
Probably not
Are you disappointed Charlie Sheen doing lightning round
When Charlie Sheen choke his wife will you like
Damn
You're messing up the car so I can add you on the program you were looking good
Charlie Sheen
Calling for
Full disclosure on 9/11 names going to go inside
Is that what it is
I'm not going to get into that whole story
On you I mean you're constantly dealing with negative
But also took his wife
Joe I'm going to go with
It says a lot about
You and
And Alex that
Your first thought of Ali
Alexis reaction was
How is Alex going to take this as personally hurting
Bring him
As opposed to
Giving a s*** about the fact that
Clarify that even more
He's saying
How is this going to affect
The car
Alex's
Pretending to be so passion
Nutley fighting for
How is Charlie Sheen personal transgressions going
Alex
Crusade
Against imaginary windmills
Now here's where things turn
For me
I feel like that super dark
That's what that's a real.
IPad Mini
Yeah
Really dark that's like
Sooner violence trigger warning
Maniac
Charlie's a good guy
Charlie Sheen
How about that
Someone get a little mouthy
You want to get off of Asia know who's paying
Especially
Yeesh
That's dark
Yeah significantly darker than I was expecting
I guess what you call it is the sort of
Playful misogyny of 2010
Is this
Yeah
How was you cook
Wow it is
It is like
It's really
You know when you go back and you watch a 90's movie like a weave when you re-watch trading place
I re-watch that and your leg
You could get away with a lot of s*** there
But then you think it's 2010 and you couldn't get away with that
No you can get away with that s*** in 2010 for sure
Yeah
Yeah it's wild
Jesus
It's not a joke
No it's not
It's a joke
Even if it you know
Even if it
Is a joke
It's not like it said welcome
Construct a joke it's not a really good playing on the edge of
Sometimes domestic violence is warranted Honeymooners level s***
In the 1950s
Is Jackie Gleason can be like I'm going to hit you later yeah but no
No no
I think is even more strange is that Alex
Sent like
Responsibility he has a hose
Real cheetah completely abdicated
He has so he feels some responsibility to be like
Come on man
Come on
That would be interesting to hear today would he just be like
I know right
Yes are you would have to write if you had Steve does not give a s***
Goddamn
Some semblance
Some effect
That was precluding him and stopping him
From going into
Maybe it's a possibility of like
If the audience was more family audiences
Maybe there was more of a puritanical streak to the people who would listen to him on the radio and shortwave
George was the most of his audience
As the internet
And the supplement lines
Came in
Maybe he didn't
You have to
For keep such a
Pretend arrows
Hey
Conversation doesn't fly here gentleman
I imagine getting
Kicked off of social media and stuff probably
I think you'd given up some of that
Even back in like
I bet he would let Joe Rogan
A little bit more even if it was
Getting into territories that was
Seemingly advocating for even if it's
Facetiously advocating for
Sometimes women
Paw Patrol
Yes this is a real misogynist episode
A Joe I wouldn't always our Joe I wouldn't look back on this episode calling
Jan Brewer Arizona
Governor
It is in a vacuum
Could be seen as like
Things that this politician did were dumb
Sure you could view them outside of like an essay
Sara Lee misogyny
It's tough to when
I just wish that conversation we cleared
Not a good cover
Yeah I wish that that
Conversation
Do you think so
Katrina was fake
Porter's Auto
Yeah
This gets a little bit uncomfortable and they date you know they have to come
Towards the end here
And
Galaxy phone
You're fun to hang out with me
I'll show you the cool guy
We have a good time
Last night we went to Fogo de Chao
Delicious meat it was awesome we had a great time
A lot of laughs
The world vaccines
Defensive about hanging out with Alex for over a man
Ask yourself
Why would that be
Dip
Why is it that people think
Hey that guy you keep out
14 News
Over the course of a decade
Constantly having people be like
Don't do that
Yeah I mean
Comedy that is such
Like the way that it
Search for so long in comedy of
Just like yeah there's a little bit of
Permissiveness
It's totally like
Oh yeah I know I know I've heard he's a f****** monster by how it's been cool to me I haven't seen
So that means he can't be a violent misogynist race
I wouldn't listen to his show to see what
Happened right before I came on
No
That's office Behavior
Also there's another funny thing
They're talking about Brock Lesnar
Maybe I'd like to I-40
Tickle itis
And they were talking about how like
It was because he just ate
Before and that's not good
And that's really funny to me because
Joe would later have Jordan
Peterson
On his podcast
Advocating his all-meat diet
Christ
Hey these people these people so much
Yeah I mean it has to be it could also be I could
See it being this where it's like
Joe discount anything that happens on this
He's just like
Yeah Alex doesn't show and it's all bulshit at the entertainment for nothing he says matters on the
The show
It only matters what he says whenever he's off-air when he's
The person that doesn't matter what he says on your show.
Exact
Because it's the same
You would think there's overlap
Yeah and then just
Like
Maybe it is
Look I get it if Joe in the Alex are super good friends and Joe Knows for a fact that Alex
Bulshit
And is baba Baba B all made up
He's still a friend
Is directly responsible for so much evil happening
Even if you think he's Faking It
It's almost worse
It's always sunny
Did you grab a debate on that
More malicious
Weather
Real or you know it's fake
Is ethically both bad no it's not good
For Joe it's no Redemption for that whatsoever over a decade of negligee
Jents on his part not wreck
Recognizing
The cancerous
Toxic
Influencer
This guy that he just
Has funded
Steakhouse
It's it's
It's
Apathetic
Lack of responsibility on his part
Seen it on it
Joe show
Whenever we talk about these
I didn't think it went like
Exact same behavior
It's the same thing
And you know it
It's annoying
Sing to me
The way that you'll hear in these interviews
Present
This like we put on those Bush masks yeah you know that they have that same story that they tell that
Solidifies their friendship in there
Connection
And
That's annoying
But it's even more annoying
To go back to the
The past
In 2010 and see
The inability to fact-check claims Alex's made that you have sinks relief
Think are correct
And then at the same time
Fun making
Excuses for misinformation
Fraud
Based on like
We have fun
I I think
Are you find it
Viscerally
F***** up
To go back
Nearly is like a
A decade
Encino
No growth
And if anything
Regression
I would say regression
That really sucks with my head
You know cuz I like arriving in my
Time. I think week
You can go back to our show and
Just pretty consistent like
There's growth
There's change there's some
What we can but
To just be
That
Yeah and then get
Worse
Casey Jones
Sijo kind of worse because I think he's got
More entrenched
Yeah
Positions of like Alex's a fun guy why does everyone not want me to hang out with elderly
And if you
So consistently being lied to by
Alex
Alex showing him
Either fraudulent or misrepresented proof of his claims
He's just gotten deeper and deeper in those holes
Yeah
At this point
There's something about him that just
Is
Delightful Eddie
Goodnight I guess there's a nature about him
Kind of
I enjoy it when he chimes
Recycle
I appreciate self-awareness to of of himself
Back then
Napa, conspiracy
The freak is a recognition that some of the
But he saying a probably dumb
Articulating important things about representation in Media
I don't know if
It's just it's weird all of these people are doing worse now
Yeah
Yeah it seems he's
He's just a guy who's like
I know
He's laughing at me
And I've accepted that
And I'm cool with it cuz I still got me I've still got my stuff and I'm respected in the field where I meant to be respect
Whenever I say some stupid
Conspiracy theories
Yeah man
Conspiracy theories are stupid you should laugh then a couple years later my best friend is 100 million
Billion dollars maybe I start taking this a little bit more seriously
Hellboy
Play One Life
Eddie wants
Sterno about Y2K
Which is an interesting analysis question
His answer is
O'Donnell Ian
And it's not worth right now
I got a question
About other Y2K
You were saying
I was listening to old tapes and you were saying
You noticed it before a question was even asked Alex Goes to do defense mode
And she says there on ABC News saying a missile was launched
Now it's his wife
Asphalt
And ABC
NORAD
And it's going to drill or something
And then I went on I got a Michael 4-0 that day and make jokes about it
Edited 9 hours part of the me joking around like Joe sent earlier
Don't know what they did is they just took
Pieces
To create fear
What
Okay
What did you
I don't know I feel like even those excuses are contradictory
Nonsense
My wife told me but I didn't believe it then so it's her fault but also when the Pentagon Saturday I was like well obviously
It's true I was a millionaire
None of this is my fault that all I was on here for 99 hours
Taking everything out of context
Misrepresented I've been smeared
Now weird sir simultaneously I was reporting on things that were a hundred percent accurate
It was trying to create fear about Y2K
Did those store
Wait
Both
Neither
And everything
Search Porsche
What an a******
This is an interesting glimpse
Just one time be like oh yeah
F***** up on that one
Just not even a wouldn't even have to put no
Explanation no just like yeah that was on me
My bad
I think it's
To embarrass
It has to be
Episode
Looking at the Y2K episode of his show
And I think
Some of the stuff that he was doing was
My kits
Really too far that like bases were being set up at an Austin airport for people to be
Everyone's out of gas
Hard I remember decoding that is too hard
To do so you have to
To create a defensive strawman about like
What actually
Send then
Yeah Boy karaoke just give you a pass commercial anyway
Run out the clock
I miss answer I've been Eddie will drop it
Yeah or what
Commercial and that's not a fair question to ask me on air
I know we're playing a game here sounded stupid now you're making me feel bad
Eddie
You're high and have
So when you get to the end of this and I think this is an interesting glimpse
Back if only for
This Dynamic is so different and so similar
It's similar in the ways
But you hate and it's different in the ways that you miss
It's not fun
Fitness in the way that these present-day interviews are cuz Alex
Is f***** up
Yeah
Alex is more willing to
Keep the keep the ramble going
King the Riff going long enough to where he hangs himself
Put too much rope like that guy
Where is on the show he's trying to
Cut stuff off before he looks too soon
Trying to protect
Yep yep yep
Will be back to the present
I'm sure our next episode or
You know
Probably
But until then
We're also on Twitter
Could please find a local charity or Bellefontaine area to help out people
I doing God's work right now
But until then
Emilio I'm Leo I'm dzx
It's Clark I'm going to run this I am not a witch
Holding
Alexandra first in color with huge fan I love your work