Damn important swetik
I have great respect for knowledge B
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Nike.com
Looks around
Jordan
What's up
My bright spot today is I like to thank a walk out there named Pat
Who got in touch
Episode 1 the first time
Actually paid off and I've got to
Some interesting stuff
Got so I really appreciate that is kind of like
Spoiler alert
Basically I'm really underselling the episode were about to do
And I don't enjoy listening to it nearly as much as I I probably would some kind of
We ain't even the past
Intellectual EX
Exercise kind of things
But you're saying we're going to be at 12
Now I would
Baseball that is all about Auntie communist
Torero's
B b w Deanna is I found a TV show called what
Burlington paranormal
Okay that's made by the same guys that did what we do in the shadows Jemaine Clement
Send taika waititi
Ttn.
Fantastic is really good
It's like an X-Files that's super understated in that New Zealand way where it's like
They're trying to give a
Ticket to a werewolf like that kind of
Situation where they're just
Oblivious to be absolute Insanity going on around them is just like we're just trying to do our job
I can dig that
It's really really funny it's in that great
Bane of the
Battery kind of stuff
I hate I hate these kinds of almond
Because I like
I hear that if I got sounds good I probably enjoy that it's not exactly
Oh well maybe one day maybe
Get to New Zealand
Watch it
Yeah
Do you know Jordan
I got to say I don't
I feel like it's been too long
I don't
This it feels like too long in between episodes
Between Mondays and Fridays
It really does
Okay
It just feels
Like too long
You are I'm I'm itching to be back in the seat out early incapable of doing anything but 12 episodes per week
I don't like it
I feel like we're getting back together
In Forever
Surprising
Especially considering considering I think we watched a movie together on Tuesday
Whatever anyway
Homicidal
And this is
Right hand man
Beginning of this week
Alex was gone
Again again doing something
On the east
Coast
Mysterious
He's trying to get out of Texas
Slowly and then
Mulligan back in like the
The Twilight Zone got a situation he apparently recorded a video of himself
The Skull and Bones
I applaud going back to his roots kind of thing you should be moving back towards
Certainly better than
Literal devil stuff
DL or whatever it is fine at the same time as I expressed to you
I'm going to be furious if I have to do more episodes about where geronimo's bones are
That's true don't want to hear it
Anyway he's back
On the 23rd
And
I would say but not better than ever
And we'll get down
Talking about
Some folks who are you
Globalism
Kirby
Jmendez Journal policy
I'm a policy wonk
RJ gury Winola sepan thank you so much you and I'll probably walk
Very much
Cake wagon
Muffin pan
Bankers about Jeremiah pilot
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much buffing pads
Also
Baby goblin what's going on and I'll probably walk
Did you know that baby goblin was made a lord
Between now and when they sent that in total
Alex our Lord did not realize it was this honorific
And then also that reminded me that when we were doing our zipping up the mailbag
Cameron Cameron
You are now.
What do
You are now a technic
I'm a policy wonk
Business
Money off that heroin
Yes thank you very much
Would say that this
Stretch of time is bad
Actually a b v
That I felt
It was
Offensively bad
Felt more like
I don't want to do this
Which type we have many different types
Is it bad on time
What kind what type of batter we talked about we can't even use the word bad at all that's true
Gyro exactly pigeonhole it but it just feels like
Generalized insight
And it's kind of a generalized boring incitement that's
She has to do around
White Spears
Immigrants there's a lot of that
Question
On a certain level while I was listening to these
Is this even worth
It does this rise to the level of paying attention to it
Because it's
Pretty much just
Parking Brooks
Most of the time
No
It's not even superb
It's gross
Here's a air contact dropper
Today Show
If people
The ugliest that they're not real
Can you see a mannequin
You know it's plastic fruit matter how good it is
How big it is
You look at it you know that's fake
You just know
Normal
That's not normal
God bless
Ice cream
Took God him sometimes you make me kill my son
Black
I am
And I was like
All I want to do now for the rest of my life
Plastic fruit around Alex
I just want to get him on camera eating plastic
Yeah
It's like somebody goes out of the way at all of a sudden be like you know I've never trip going upstairs and
People do it before but not
So Alex is late to work
On the 23rd because his plane was delayed
Answer he recorded himself
Prior to this
So you have something to play
I'm Alex Jones or Houston as we speak I'm about to arrive
Video
But I'm coming to you
From earlier today
Time continuum
Information
You're seriously on The Cutting Edge
Goddamn maybe communist Smokey the Bear alright
Homemade ukay-ukay
I want
Video surveillance footage
Give him recording that in a weird bathroom
Nevermind
Some of the stuff he's covering his pre-recorded s***
Bulldozers project veritas
Crawdad
Did not win that lawsuit
The headline that Alex was lying about here have to do at the New York
Supreme Court Judge determining the Veritas is defamation
Ensued
The time can move forward
A couple articles in the times are referred to as a Veritas videos as deceptive but the judge felt this way
Who's more opinion
Then it was straight up recording
Live news
This kind of ruling honestly just seems like a parody where a liar is getting the court
Journalist
Strictly adhere to rules that they themselves think our jokes
How do I get the game here for project Veritas isn't actually to win the case or anything like that
It's about the media circus that can drown up along the way while simultaneously trying to make other outlets
Hypocritically cover their work
That's what's going on
Yeah we should there should be there should be a
Consultancy for dumb old judge
Who are like well I guess we have to take these people as good-faith actors because of the legal system
And we could just be like
Hey know you guys probably should have charged them with a federal crime
A few years ago so no
So Alex still hasn't shown up at this point
And
It's getting to be like
Ways into the show hand-sewing
I've got a break in
Snooze
Gentlemen we are live inside the Infowars World Headquarters are Owen Shroyer sitting in studio
I want to go back to Alex Jones here shortly he's going to be joining us alive here shortly as well
The break-in and
Support some of the latest that we know of the Boulder Colorado shooter
Obviously his name Ahmad
Issa
It's now coming out he was and Islamic
States
Besides her show and Islam assist he was a
Immigrant from Syria
I don't know if I can find any evidence that he was in Islamic
Mcstate sympathizer
Outside of wild conjecture being made by the guy who runs
Jihad watch
Yeah I was going to say all we've got there is
Is Owen read the name and he was like well obviously this
This is a terrorist that I find really interesting is even like within the last week you can see how
News is dealt with differently
When there was the those shootings at the spas in Atlanta Alex didn't even talk about it no MMA next day was like
Weird out or whatever
Batman just moved on
Maybe touch
The story for a second
On the second day
When is this
Break into coverage
Yeah
Trying to see what's going on
Phil people with
Great shame
And the only way they can survive this long
Having that part of their brain removed
Did Tom Boyden
Because Daddy
Just on a
Really deep
Human level
Just discussed
Because if
Cruise
Beyond Reasonable Doubt
That they are choosing which
Stories
Malicious
Not
Because of any kind of newsworthiness
Purely by me
Yeah
Straight throughout the Moses career
That's pretty tough
Sewing
These cases
I'm shooting
Of course but also psych meds got to talk about that got a
Portray him as
The other side bro
He was it seems maybe a paranoid schizo
The phrenic
So who knows what kind of pharmaceutical drugs he had been prescribed potentially
For those mental
Problems
And then we also have a lot of his social media activity before it was
Deleted
Before it was deleted
Showing that he was an anti
A he was a
Leftist
Liberal
Progressive
He was a
One of those
The leftist narrative
To a T
They do have some screenshots of what appear to be his social media and I don't
Slightly Fair
That post that they
Show that were critical of
Trump but like
Like cool I don't know how much
It doesn't seem like it has anything to do with
At least I would demonstrate it at all it is anything to do with what happened
Please audio
The shooting
Incredibly exploitative but I'm not going to play I know he has afterwards
This is his
A pre-recorded also
Is the name
Was Eric Chou
1 year old father
Who was the patriot
Amazing
He died heroically
Helping stop
Boulder Colorado
This is tragic
You know not going to diminish anything but that the way Alex is behaving around this
Is really
Exploit
Yeah it's really the only way I can put it
And then when towing starts talkin about what the solution to these problem
Bizarre
It kind of runs
Counter to
Way Alex
Is pre-recorded stuff is
To build this up
Here's the deal
Mass shootings in this country are really a rare occurrence
And they would be even more rare if we had citizens with
Gunstop
But they know the police take at least two minutes to get to the scene so they know they can fire off at least
Around
An innocent people
Killing people and get away with it
Because they never get stop
Until the cops show up
Person one citizen
One good citizen with a gun could have saved lives
In that Colorado
Grocery store
Until there's a toll notion like
Oh you just want to be like Allah bless everybody with a pistol on their hip
That's not how I want it
Then I wanted at all
I want white people to have guns
Crazy guy one bad guy with a gun to kill
10 people
All it would have taken with one good guy with a gun in that store to stop
Problem is that one of the people who is
Who was responding who had a gun
Oh they weren't they didn't give
From the gun that day
I mean it's not it's not like this
Disproves any possibility of someone disrupt
Take an active shooting or anything like
The notion that they have it this is a magic
Bullet 222 stop situation
It's just Luke
Yeah in order to stop mass shooting
We need to get one good guy with a
The gun to either
Assume people are going to be a mass shooter and just start killing a before anyone is a mass shooter
Get to the point where they're killing your fight
Michaela
Into the center of an active shooting
And deputized yourself to
Do shootout
Somebody who
I don't I don't think this is a good
Good solution reporting is is a little bit convoluted on this front
Belief that most people won't ever be released
Anti
I mean
There's a little
Little offense
But
Will be affected by
Liberal policies
Most people listen to this broadcast
I will probably never be directly impact
Pray to God that continues
But almost everybody listening to this pot
Podcast almost everybody listening to this radio show almost everybody watching this right now
Is going to be negatively impact
Happy by Democrat liberal policies
Just like everyone in that grocery store was
Wow
And now the liberal-left these are going so out of control their minds are so warped their minds are so
Bent
Propagandized
They've become
Danger to society
This individual was a danger to society
He came in with a gun
Ethiopia
Almost these liberals may not have a gun
But they're dangerous just decide
Their policies will kill you
Their policies will kill
Freedom in the West
The only policies really that he could be really talking about how every gun control
Ability disarming people who could be the good person with a gun who can carry out murder Sheriff against the murderer
Or it's
Immigration-related
Because this guy came
From Serie A number of years back
And so that would be the left
This policy that he's attacking the Earth
They're letting people who do these mass shootings
Either way
Dumb
So
Disappointed
Yeah I mean it's hard
To just
It's not far
Apart
It's hard to be like oh it's
Liberals letting people in
A week after 8
It's not liberals
You know it's
It's like
Maybe there's a larger prop
Maybe there's one that should be dealt with
Maybe we should deal with it in a way that make
And unfortunately
Do you want to come down
No-oooooo are you sure
No I'm alright Fred house
Would you like an appetizer
Are you doing looking at this through he's very milquetoast
But also like
Clearly
Pretty extreme
Yeah.
You've got a psychopathic energy of
The banality of
Evil about him Alex
Is boar
Laxative
Interesting and Harrison Smith
Is more of a straight-up bigot
Yeah Harrison Smith just says
Don't let brown people in and if they are in shoot them with guns but
Being boring about
Which is terrified
Owen is done
At this point Alex's backup
You know he was doing
Secret
Well I was on a secret mission in Connecticut that will find out what it is
Austin just landed about 30 minutes ago rushed here to Studio
Flight was delayed or I would have been there to start the broadcast
So we don't know we don't get the we don't get tune-up find out what this Secret
Mission was
Etiquette
We don't get to find out what it is
What about the music
That wasn't it meme
His main trip was I would guess if I had to bet anything of your employer related
Connecticut
Does he have any possible reason there's no secret mission I could think of to go to kinetic
You know if there's a lot of reasons to go to Connecticut if you're Alex Jones
He has more reason to go to Connecticut that just about anybody else alive
He is one very specific reason
ETA is locked into kinetic
Discovery or something
To do with
Sandy Hook case I mean like I can't imagine it being unrelated hard
Said he was going to the East Coasters like
Smells like Sandy Hook something
No I don't I don't I don't know this
Well you either
Good either Sandy Hook case related or went to Stanford and he's trying to get
Get a job Within
I'm not going to say no to that
It's the only other possibility
Hidan I went there for a semester maybe he's following your footsteps he's always wanted to be me
So
You know
This narrative gets really interesting with Alex
Bad camps for immigrants
Coming over
Trump cleaned it all up good and good
Good out bad again
What bad really fast seems like it's too fast
Well it's because
Biden had a clip
It's playing where you saying
People to surgeon whenever you
Becomes president sure
He's talking about his people applying for refugees disallowed from being able to apply for refugee
That is during the Trump
Administration
Because he would
Refugees during the entire trumpet
Ministration
Sounds like can we have
More than four
That's not accurate but also
The ceiling was dropped
Quite a bit and the only way to
Apply for asylum in the United States as a refugee
You have to be in the United
Administration would stop people from making it
Into
Consulates or On the Border
Yeah that was what you talkin about
Pretending
That was like everybody
Anyway it's bad
The camps are back bad sure and sure
Water fountains in each area
AOC went and cried
She's not crying now
Because she's a monster
And explore the most powerful rich
Tax-exempt billionaires
Planet
Ladies and gentlemen
AOC literally came out immediately against Biden having migrant facilities open
For children
She tweeted quote this is not okay never has been okay never will be okay no matter the administration
Dinner party
I was just making up that AOC doesn't oppose
The things the bidens administration is doing at the border because that's
That's too complicated of a story for him to tell his audience
The listeners are used to vary some
Simplistic Good vs Evil characterizations of people so
Introduce the idea that AOC was against
The treatment of migrants under Trump
Still opposed
Do the same types of treatment under Biden
Represents a threat to the
Pictures that Alex's paint
Yeah really
F*** things up whenever your enemy I suppose
Alex
Has ideologic
Consistency
And ideological differences between the people Alex wants are all working for the
The f****** devil
That's what I'm saying plenty of Democrats who are like
Democrats in the white house now it don't need to worry about her
Yeah that's
Veterinary assistant
So
I like the most
This episode has been emigrar
Bashing at this point
I am not
You know cut out
Just because
Cuz it's kind of
Standard boring Emigrant bashing
Just don't I don't know he said
A lot of this stuff before
It's non-white people going into
We got it
In hard
People
Most of the Court Middle Eastern immigrants
It's over 75% better man
In Europe
5%
Military age
Yeah there's a sweet I'm mad
Isa
Why refugees and immigrants are
Good
Search
Connect that to the
The boulder shooting in a can of makes a little clear without Owens line of thought probably was
Episodes almost impossible to listen to there's no real Subs
Going on it's mostly Alex's rambling nonsense to make his listeners afraid of
According to the
Pew research numbers put out in August 2020 Alex is completely full of s***
One thing he probably doesn't even know is that
Among all refugees admitted in fiscal year 2019
4900 are Muslim
N20 3800r Chris
16% Muslim and 79%
That's super different than the picture Alex tends to paint
Which is a queer
Got a weird
Also
The statistics from the Department of Homeland Security regarding Refugee arrivals in
There's just no way to pretend that everyone coming in our military age men
4149 percent of arrivals in 2019 were women
Secondly 12% of all arrivals were age 45
Older but then again I have no idea what Alex
Who considered military age
Finally
The thing that Alex is mostly banking on here is it 43.2% of arrivals were between the ages of 0 and 7
That's a pretty wide age Gap so using the same number Alex
I could try to make you scared of refugee.
And someone else could explain to you that a lot of these
People are
Issues related to immigration and Refugee resettlement are super important in the real world
But they aren't important when dealing with Alec
He isn't living in reality and making an argument for policy
He's decided that he hates immigration and the us becoming less white and he's making up s*** to justify
None of this stuff is real and it's just
Manipulative fear
It's boring
Really really
F***** up on the back of a racist
Misogynist mass shooting
Like
Okay
Well we got a hold off on being racist towards Asian for a little bit
So not be raised
So we're going to switch Target
To just
Blanket image
How many bucking years are we going to do this
It's not like this is a new thing for some white
Mother f****** a******
To start screaming that all immigrants are evil
We do it all the goddamn time you mean Alex not the shooter
No I don't mean I get I mean Alia Bhatt I mean like
You can read
Newspaper articles from 1790 words like now we got to close our f***
Borders
You know it's like
Animal groups can change
But the mentality stays the same and
Up in
Violin
It does
Stop
If we could deal with it but we just refused
Still under some b******* Banner of
Just like project Veritas being allowed to go with their f****** lawsuit
These guys are not good faith to act
Probably not
But you know who
You should go to for information
And ideas about immigration
Someone in Europe where the great track record
Someone who might be the head of Hungary
Forbidden
Touche
So in Europe but this year's
Organized invasion
Are military age men
Yeah that's some of the boatload coming or not
95%
It's on
Morning settings
Holyshit
That seems extra
I don't know
Viktor Orban
Is your guy I don't know if that's great citation
Dancing is he's made
Assisting refugees criminal act
Boy it's it seems like he's like you know what
That child rescue had some good policy
He's a good guy
You want the towel and you get the chest
Okay
Stream
Anyway if I bike
Shootings that have happened
If you want to take a gun
Turns out Alex and his friends
Are going to be more deadly than the Vietcong
Let me tell you where this is going to end
Joe Biden tries to take
It's going to
Wipeout law enforcement in Lawton military
Civil War
The Vietnamese resistance in Vietnam looked
And then they were even successful to break the back of the country and in in
Get most people to do it
Police involved will all be corrupt
That you will be worse than Mexico we will be a completely
Spell state with
Hundreds of thousands dead
Every few years
Just like we basically are becoming
Pic of the Tower of Babel can everybody take over
Killing everybody
What about human world
Okay
Yeah I know
I don't know
I'm not sure exactly what he's trying to intimate like is it that if
Bible Hub
Put in better background check
Regulations
Four guns that everybody will be murdered on the street or is it that he and his friend
Will start guerrilla warfare
That's what he
He's talking about he's
Talking about joining the Wolverines are going up in the mountains and running
The swamp
Fox 2.0
1776 2.0 no
That's over with
Seems like a little
I don't know
It doesn't make me feel all that come
Ball
Going back to a lot of the ideas that
You know we're more popular Within
Some of these militia right-wing communities
Earlier on books like on intent
And the consequent
Kinds of ideas
Migrate to
Can popping up again a lot more volatile right now
That give up at the first hint of actual resistor
You know it is it is a little bit heartening for me to look back on the 6th
And remember
That win
Push comes
To shove
Alex will say that it was never his idea and it was all the Liberals
Asphalt Indiana
Guerrilla warfare from these assholes you know all those people
That's just
Because of the double rat.
Proposition
Okay
So
Boy this isn't good
I'll just tell you that
There's a good setup for this clip this is good
Explain how this works
Florida's would Africans religion
Strange man Europe
It doesn't sound right
Yeah I mean you're going to tell
They put 2,000
Military-age man
Jobs
They start robbing you some of them
Now you hate black people
Do you want to
Annihilate
Join them
Extermination
That's coming
I don't know if I would be susceptible to that sort of
The planned at the club
Cuz I see other solutions to problem
Confused entirely sure if there are these towns
The 500 people in 2002 emigrants come into it all man
With no jobs or whatever but
I feel like there could be some other
Sort of
Structural ways that we could we could
Good deal with the issue
Let's go to buy a government works projects together
Get these people employed let's get me where Outlook get to her
Consumer maintenance
I know this from the United States
Chicago in specific
Every bridge needs a little bit of work
That's true
That is true
Deteriorating quick
Get the government involved in
Inject a little bit of money everybody has a job
Said is that determine at this house
Trick you into want
Take me to Annihilator population
Yeah I really feel like maybe
You don't need or maybe I feel like maybe your manufacturing reasons to
To do what you already want to
To do maybe
That's what I would that would be my history if you want to feel blameless about having those feelings already
If you're creating excuse to say that
That would probably become a national news story baby in the
Global news story Legacy Germany's government Merkel is just like
2000 only military rage
Small tiny town to 500 people
I know they're going to murder everyone
And they be like at the very least
This would call for a special session of Congress
At least one
What are the things that I think is really into
Everything is the Alex plays luck games with his
What he believes is going on pure you know like he'll say that the globalist believe that they're talking to a next
Dimensional being
I'm not saying I believe
What they believe I'm just here warning you what they believe
He does follow that up usually with now it's up
True well yeah but
Just to be totally clear here Alex is expressing that he literally believes he's fighting biblical devil
Some of the elite white people think you're going to be
No
Posthuman world
The Bible's the devil does not want any humans
Bible tells us the Devil comes to destroy God's creation
So Alex believe he's fighting the Christian
Biblical literal devil
Question
Alex's fiala
So the devil
What's the astrology
Okay what happened
To their soul
Do they still
Heaven and hellafied
Or is he going for all the souls in Heaven and Hell 2
That's a great question
And if so
How is it going to pull that one off
Finally
Should he sick
Being and killing all the human
And then what
Or let's go another Direction
Let's say Alex's
Successful in vanquishing
Okay
What is it you do who takes over
All those people are just hanging out
Pre-K oz cup the infrastructure of Hell currently
Right and then how does that reshape
Theology
Play the future is like
You have
Yeah the Old Testament or the New Testament and the Jones test
Almost all of the prophecy
Would like the revelations is
You don't even talk about God defeating the devil thousand years of Jesus's rain
It's just more like Alex did it
That's the end of Revelations is
Hey man it was a good thing God gave us Alex f****** joke
Last verse of the Bible is I'm not bragging but we did it guy
Just one Mission Hill Bible at all just a mission accomplished
That's it
Guess you're really quite understand
What
I don't know I just know
I just think it's really important to recognize that whatever he says stuff like
I'm not saying that I believe the stuff they believe that's him trying to hold on to some thread
Respectability and credibility with people who would call him
Nuts
Needs to recognize that really tough
You need to recognize he thinks it's
I know it is it is a little bit like how they
The older of articles about Rodger
Sonar always
Conspicuously like
He was a lobbyist
Close to Trump's Inner Circle and they never mentioned that
He hosted a show on Infowars for 2 years that is 8
News Outlet whose editorial position is staunchly anti devil
Anti-communism
Absolutely I guarantee said
Bet the
Basic problem is the
I probably ever believed it
Hideout
I don't know
I think that it would be interesting to like
Like what the public conversation is
I'd like totally free speech Crusader ezotic Trump
Fans fighting
The devil
Hooey
He's also super AC
Sarah interesting things that he tries to get too easy steak
Some calls here on the show
It has astillas B conversation that has a color I'm not taking these
These racist feeling
Things you have and then redirecting them at the global
That's nice
No
2024 medium mass
Political Express
I got red blood don't you think I see all this
Groups that I go
That's my animal side
Old times
The enemy is using that against us
Whatever we have to be aware of
That's the only way to defeat
This is an alien attack
UFOs real
I don't care they were just killing me
Birthdays are killing everybody
Boutonniere
Not totally
He's trying to make is essentially the he has this old timey racist program and get inside him
Here take that
And directed toward
Globalist
Psyquel
No you should Rise Above It Maybe
Wrestle with those feelings as opposed to
I hate someone else has to be Evolution itself
That makes him racist
Can't possibly be cold
I actually don't think that he was talkin
About like
Caveman days
I think he was talking about like when he was in high school because he constantly talks about how black people beat him up in high school
Talk about that all the time
I think you talkin about you
I think it's so ironic now with all the reports that we have from very credible sources and the government real
It's like
We see UFOs all the time
I got to be honest with you we see UFOs
All the goddamn type here
Types of Navy Pilots here's
Here's video here's everything
And Alex is like whoa whoa I don't believe in UFOs
If the devils are fighting a demon
The devil
Set the same time still
The functioning lettering ESO is you
Of course
Get some more let's make those ifo's
Can I see what you say
So Alex this guy seems to be worried that the FBI is following his social media
Announces response to does a little bit weird
Hey Alex
I just want to prep
Message with
What Paul said in first Colossians
Because it's kind of scary
He said that
The powers of Darkness
We defeated on the cross
And that is
That is only hope right now
Look
The FBI show up in my house
Iiii
Have a Tik-Tok
Accountant
Snapchat and I basically preach the gospel in there
And I went into the vaccine
Nervous on the phone call to Beyonce lyrics
It's okay for the FBI's Realm of the Chinese now
Did you come out the gym at 8 she was hit salt
That does relax made that's okay that's a wildly man I'm so relaxed
Was worried about the FBI Vanessa American government's fbii now that I do there
Controlled by the Chinese and the Chinese just tell him to go rough
People up a little bit I don't know it what to believe about this
Listcawler
He sounds a little skittish
Emily
Little bit
I don't believe that the FBI
I don't know if I believe the FBI showed up at
As if they did I believe it is posting more on that account then the keys let him off
Maybe the FBI wouldn't just walk around at the
Cast of the Chinese government yet
Scare him a little bit
Whatever the reality or non reality of this one visit is I'm guessing there's not going to be a follow-up visit they're not listening to him
Call idalia show
There's some delusional paranoia that's going on here and Alex is doing a great disservice
Who's listener by being like
Don't worry about it
What is the weather like
Deal with delusional paranoia he's like
We're not going to deal with the delusion whatsoever we're going to deal with the paranoia I'm going to try
You called Dowd
Of course the delusion is
I'm going to make you calm down but also make it
Way worse
Whatever you're worried about
How much worse nuclear bombs coming
You worried about
The government your Bail Enforcement
Also and the New World Order
They're working with the spider leadership
Play run by the literal.
Does the devil want to destroy alien
Alex
Makes an interesting point
And that is Victor China isn't
Communist
There is that which
Is a itching problem for Alex
Because
Because of the calls them
Jack talks about a communist
Chocolate
Country
Totalitarian dictatorship
Globalist
Muse The Leverage out the whole planet want to make an omelette with Warfarin
11 minutes timer
Which we absolutely have nothing resembling I'm going to rephrase this
In a way that works
For me which is at the test
Open ground for the globalist yeah and then we'll move on and I won't have to deal with
Pollution might as well just like neener neener neener I'm going to call him communist
What's tomorrow
Like that might as well have been his respond
So you get another call and this guy is a story from a year ago
That blows Alex is mine
Because it helps him
Demonize Muslim
Locally in Knoxville
A year ago April 8th we had a stabbing
You can find it on the internet 3
Pilot
That's a gas station
3 pilot employees killed
Stabbing attack
Knoxville
I-40 truck stop
Corsa got no coverage cuz it was a nice
Article on the front page of the local newspaper a rag
The Knoxville News Sentinel under the leadership
The editor
I wouldn't wipe my rear end with it
Did read it though
Coverage to the mother
Of the stabbing
Stabber
And she said that it he he was in
It was not possible
He could have done
Dunwoody did so why are we not hearing about it what is the racial makeup
He was a middle eastern
Bingo Muslim who else wants
I mean
I'm not against all Muslims but give me a break
They got a thing about killing women
Wow
That's
That's wild
Wow
That's really wild
In Alta Dena California last week two people were fatally stabbed on a zoom call and if it all
There's a new story out of Michigan fourteen-year-old girls spent months planning to stab her friend in the woods
Guess you quote wanted to see
See someone die
Yet to hear this reported on Infowars we could do this all day but the point doesn't matter
Stories are props for Alex and this is a prop for him to demonize intimate hatred towards Muslim
I believe the colors also complaining things
The claims
In those articles
That the guy
Couldn't have been
The person at the stabbing
They were that he
Wouldn't have been
Involved in
Previous stabbing
In a town called Billington initially people thought might have
Open Connected
He definitely wasn't in that other time
Things about the reporting being
He couldn't have been happy
Yeah but you've got a group of
Put people to smear and Hate
For the rest of your life cool
Alex is like this
Is exciting
Year old story about a stabbing at a gas station
Hooray let's talk about this forever media covered it up by putting it in the
Front page of the local newspaper
You can find about it
If you want
Anyway they decide to talk about it for quite a while
Alex they went on to have follow-up articles on the front page of the local newspaper rag
And they said
The people who stopped him
Who killed him and stopped him from killing people
Investigated
Cleared of any
Wrongdoing
Gail said should I be arrested for being at Yale
Wow I'm glad you call that know about this we're pulling the Articles up now
Islamic stabbed and killed three women
Free
Call Tim a victim holy
I'm glad you called what's up
That wow you can see here I'll expect little pieces of inaccurate information that a caller is passed along to him and then he writes his own
Headlines about
He's decided based on literally nothing
This person who stabbed people at a Pilot station was motivated by his religious beliefs
And because
So mad about what
Women being free because he's a Muslim
This is all completely made up in based on nothing other than Alex's intense hatred towards people he sees as different from himself
Also
This color is once again f****** up detail
The articles in the paper after the stabbing incident were about whether or not the police
For justified in using deadly force
The stabber
Ordered him to drop his weapon
8 * and the police killed him when he failed to drop his weapon and he began to walk
Towards the police car
The news articles of this guy's referring to wear about the DA's determination that it was a Justified shooting
Which isn't the same as being all was it right to
Whatever
I'm looking assholes
I'm noticing the length
Pics of time we're spending on this
Call verse
This is the one that was like
The Chinese are crony capitalist country
Like move on
It does seem like he moved on from that awful
Oh wait you had a story about someone who you think is a Muslims to having somebody I get right now this is exciting
Considering discovering that information about China is seeing is that China is
Maine book
Man really
That could shake his entire world
You should really spend more time
Thinking on that
Confirms is bias
C-SPAN
Symposium that Alex did about about 9/11 haha
And one of his
Did he make
Is that
It somehow
The globalist are working against China
They were like they were against each other
I've gotcha
To be like really intensely anti-immigrant
Announce its
Disgustingly anti-muslim
And boring.
Paint by numbers nonsense about
Is b*******
And then
Is just disgusting on the 24th
Some like weird
Pedophile stuff
All about
Holding your children
And as soon as you figure that out these are demonic
Monsters
Most of them are pedophiles
Silence is above the political divide an illusion
To this guy
But all mid-levels Evergreen.
Yep
What is a mid-level Democrat state senator for mid-level
Got to be any elected official
I mean I don't know I would
Could you call a State Rep mid-level an alderman
Chicago mid-layer
Mayor that's
Call Town
Sheriff
Share contact Sarah democratic
Constitutional
Yeah I just find this unacceptable and stupid
I don't have time for it
We get to
Texting story
This is a story about
Allegedly
Black lives matter
Kidnap
100 people
Black lives matter as a whole
Broadcast
Groupon Rochester
Black lives matter
Watch people inside a grocery
Store 100
Soros's
Apparently paying them to do that sounds
True about keeping us shutdown
Did somebody do something this over-the-top in this crazy
Because they've been told by Soros to go do what they're paid to do it
Newport.com
Gateway.com BLM mob
100 customers inside grocery store
We're shutting stuff
Sh
And they kept him in there for a long time
Going to reporter for wroc
See who's on the CM theater Framingham the story is completely fake and a racist live being perpetuated by right-wing media to attack backlight
Is matter
More likely
Kayla green
Wegmans closed doors and customers were capped
Since I temporarily but we're let out soon after
Protesters never entered the store protesters are currently listening to music and eating pizza in the parking lot
Nobody is quotes
Trapped inside every one of these
Text protest I've been to have been
Sometimes
Overly
Incredibly
Protesters were having a memorial demonstration on the anniversary of the day Rochester police arrested
Ultimately led to his dad
But instead of discussing any of that reality Alex just says that soros's pain
The good lie white people of the country to make them feel bad and stay inside a grocery store or something
Nonsense
It is it is kind of really a good
Example of
That kind of
Going
You know that
Propaganda method of going at your enemy strength
Instead of their week
Natsu no like
When he goes after like
Why would somebody do something so over-the-top and ridiculous
Because they wouldn't
This is too over-the-top of Earth
Haha
I will just cut past all of that by thing Soros
Done now I will say that this next clip of worry
Because even more over-the-top also made me think
Mount Everest and blow it up
He starts
Acting like they committed like criminal kidnapped you were
Under federal state law against
Kidnapping unlawful restraint
Smuggling a person
O.j. Simpson went to jail
4 / 24
These are folks you found out where counterfeiting to stuff and he was pissed at him
Mustang
Are you worried he's going to o.j. me
Protest in Rochester
Kidnapped
Wrongly arrested
Did Vitor
If Alex was there
He probably would started swinging
Occupied government aren't Claus
Meaningless now
That was
A week ago
Completely different conversation and I forgot really good at the time
Yeah
Started swinging on people man
Knocking people out left and right
And then
Then
The media
The media would have called it a race war
So they go to a grocery store
Wegmans grocery store
Call the police
What was that
I got an hour
But you have a couple hundred people can't walk me inside a grocery store
I have to go somewhere
No but I'm going to get Mama
Grocery store
This is out of control
Ha
This is what I'm saying I'm not worried about them
I'm starting a guerrilla warfare campaign
Because we're at the level of
Like
I'm not worried about Mark Wahlberg
Actually stopping 911 do you understand like
You blustery as well I would punch them in like
The fuk up
Yeah
This this formulation to of like
Because we keep
Putting up with it like
So the solution
Stop putting up with
Protest
Right right I mean like obviously that's the message
We stamp out any and all protest particularly related
We are ones that are
Central to Nan
Straight white
Christian males related issues
Because they're Soros instigated
Of course
I don't know it doesn't seem to 17 Gray
See
Did you understand
These people do understand
Actually never
I should I should end everything
Actually
Eyebrows
I think I can
I think the only explanation I can come up with for like
Maintain the Dignity of Alex's listeners is like
They have to just think he's
Telling the truth
Like yeah I can't imagine listening to this habit
A kernel of skepticism
Maintaining any illusion
That he knows what he's talking about
You covered this story
Found the like pictures of it you found the explanation for
What was going on at this Wegmans
And how Alex is
For some reason imagining people would call it a race war if you started fighting
His way out of the store right
You have to spec
Okay this is about you man this isn't about reality
This isn't about the story of those paper articles are written
Directly by
I saw Rose haha did you know that 98% of all newspaper articles in the Main Street group
We're written directly by George
I read that in one of the 2%
True
This Is Us on Facebook and Twitter as a good thing randomly do grocery store
A black people white people United inside
How did the whole building and the emergency exit and wouldn't let people out
Yo still
This is
Disgusting
Wow.
Globalstar I need to start arresting them racketeering
What
Anyway I'm not sure there's enough protesters there to surround a building a Wegmans
They're not usually small stores are usually fairly big
Pictures of the Gathering it was not a giant
Mobdro
I also in reality Wegmans
Close the door to their store out of fear of the protesters there any decisions
Complain about to be directed to Wegmans customer corporate office or whatever the f***
The reason the protesters chose this location for their protest
What is that Wegmans uses
Uniform Rochester Police Officers for
Security and their protest
For the firing of the officers
Who were involved in the Daniel Peru case
It all makes total sense
It's not random
The reason they showed up there was not random
And I would
Pretend that it's random
And very racist
What's the equivalent
This is a bunch of black people and white people
I guess looks like there's some brown people there
That are literally
Randomly at random people at a grocery store
The old lady in a walker looks like he's about to have a heart attack
And then she tries to get out the back and then yell at her
Again
And this is just the beginning of it hundreds of people
Grocery store
Welfare Queens
You were like 400 lb
You wouldn't last ten minutes in Africa
Whoa whoa whoa
Weird
Wild
That little to clear Alex
That's tough to back away from
Yeah
Tough tobacco it's outrageous
Yeah yeah yeah
Well wow
Well there's one of them
Yeah
One of many just on this episode
Review
Flagrant races
What's that's pretty
It's pretty much
That's two weeks
It's jazz
That's pretty pretty embarrassing
Yeah
I don't know
The stories dumb
Our time on this Earth is Wegmans grocery
Restore story
A lot of time talking about how I am
Infowars may be gone soon
I didn't say there was no protest about racial Justice that ever random
No and there's not even that
Daily occurrence
And there's nothing that Alex will ever deem acceptable
Of course not there's no version of it that Alex would ever see has like
Something that's
Bringing attention to Anna Borden
Mobile Bud like you wouldn't
It doesn't exist
Yeah
It would always be some kind of a Soros education in order to create division in
Society of make white people feel bad
And that's what I was kind of talking about that
Beginning this episode where everything is just kind of boring
Yeah but he's just
These are just Alex Jones tricks
Just racism on
Autopilot
F****** Boggle
Disappointed
Expect
Yeah
While we have it
Yeah this is just like
These people cannot be at all
In perspective whatsoever if you can have racism on autopilot
Explicit right
Like at no point
Time does he ever like sit down and go
What I say come off as super racist
It's interesting to me to imagine like a listener who's hearing
Like particular that last clip
He's talking about these Welfare Queen the 400lb
That's weird but maybe you're somebody who's
Inundated with shity right-wing media that's where that's where we live
Why did you say you wouldn't last a day in Africa
Weird
Yeah why why why was that where you adding adding all of that
I can't imagine being not being like
I mean if you were Reagan voter UK
Can't be mad about Welfare Queen at this
I'm not sure Alex loves
Hey you loves using Reagan's racist talking voice
Be gone soon we've been hearing this
For quite a while and I grow weary of it I'm running out of gas now I can play this
Bikes
Stuff about it being gone all the time
Except
He makes a squid metaphor
That goes too long and I find it interesting like a good school
Any idea of work
Let me just tell you this
Do not sit there and
Infowars
Be here forever
About a lot of classy family
That had cancer and was dying
Are you just here
They were one week got their Affairs in order
So manly stovetop so feminine so dumb
They just died make no big deal about it
The body to science and stuff like
What is stoic
Estimate my ancestor
I'd like to point out that I'm really glad that Alex did make that caveat
But that's not me
Yeah I'm not that person I'm going to go to I'm going to go down
Whining
God
I will do any
But America has cancer in this operation
Globalist
Squid attached to us
Knowing on our face
I just let it sit there
Can dogs get their order
I'm laying eggs real fast Escape
We'll just see how they do getting caught in the hole
Are you asleep
Analogy
So I need that
Ensuring the future
Continue
Possible future
And
We've eaten by a monster so off-the-charts so crazy now
But there's a good chance
Musketeers a pressure light
Carry out this Mission will be gone
Didn't he just say like when he got back from his last weird vacation
Florida bed like
All the weight
Had been lifted from him and eat
Completed his mission
I had a good week where the burden wasn't there and that was back and I really wish the globalist would just f******
Nothing in Connecticut made me feel like I want to die and that Infowars will be around forever
Connecticut whatever give me the impression that Infowars maybe going out of business
To think that
The metaphor gear the squid
The squid is beat that the detached Infowars is
Sandy Hook lawsuit
Paxinos how far they can nibble before it hits the Carotid right would be once his finances become public or they get discovered
People realize what he's really into
Laying eggs
Is that can either be like I'm trying to give money to
Other organizations are on
Hiding money in my dad's business
He's got tomorrow
Love life suicide
It wasn't suicide
I literally have no more fear
I've been through this so long I've done so much that I don't fear death
Out there anything I may lose
Call family I may lose my children
Bill Gates
But you got from me
Total commitment
I will fight just because
Like this at 11 like this this long
You don't just not care about them killing you don't just not care about
You start getting the point where
No give you my word that I will be as focused and hardcore as I can until the very end
But I need financial support
Yeah it's
It's weird I would I would pray that
Iowa
Would have all of my support dry up
If I ever get to the point where I speak that model
Firebird
You know just doing this at the level that I've done it I'm not afraid to die
I won't let you go out like that
About but I will
Very much need you to check me if I ever getting close to that level of blowhard already
Put on a boat I'll take care of you Godfather style it'll be
Be great
This is embarrassing
Yeah that's not good
The squids out
I believe he's a
Fish in the metaphor I think that's how far I've gotten with the metaphor I think he's a
The fish feed
I think he did say that
Say that he was putting out eggs he realized he had to be something
Laid eggs
Yeah it's for a second
Yeah
This is the problem with Alex and protracted Medical
So Alex
Some bad news here on the 24th
The made a ruler
Who's the big deal
Breaking overturning
Concealed carry.
Stream media that they fear the standing of the Court
Cuz nobody calls the bluff and left
Is Buffalo in US
Stampeding us
Crazy
Imperious
Get on the offense
Across the border
Do you like Ted Cruz
Everybody else it there
Don't
Do like Ted
That's enough
Don't forget
Is clunky want
Yeah it's a go after them for that'll do it
You got them
Man it's interesting how he pretends they didn't have hearing
Nobody ever calls
What's the elapsed
Bluff you know like nobody's ever like we refused to sit a Supreme Court Justice until
Never been like all we got to put pressure on the Supreme Court by
Removing and replacing all of the
Cool
Cool guys
Also
This is 9th Court ruling
Has said
If I recall correctly let me pull up the exact wording of it
There is no right to carry arms openly in public nor is any such right within the scope of the second
Yeah that's what the US court judge J
Barbie
I said
I would be hard-pressed to find the wording within the Second Amendment that's like yeah and carry them in the leg
Something that I would think that Alex would be like
It's over
Yeah that's the slippery slope right and he's already said the Supreme Court isn't going to ride specialist
Shouldn't this be at
The point where now like his
You know Vietcong thing from earlier there weren't any laws anymore anyways.
Government
Institutional
Alright
What are we going to do
Really talk about this story as much as you would think it should be
The most important stories in Urdu
Should lose it
The miac report came out any makes such a stink about it
So long
Some weirdos garlic a YouTube show
For an hour
About like trying to make people afraid of
Stop at the border and I didn't care
Because I got a little bit deeper into
Do this next
The interview
I thought it was it was different and a little bit more interesting and
Is that
Is brother whose name I refuse to learn is on
That's right
To me it is he's on cuz he's got some news about Kobe
Information it's a breaking exclusively Gateway pundit. Com
Location
Origin of covid-19 pandemic identified
Between two of China's biological warfare facility
Apparently situation where there was a
The cluster of cases
Israelite of covid-19 in an area that
Geographically between
The Wuhan Institute of virology and another lab in Wuhan
Put those pieces together man
Wait it was in between the two
Geographically in between the two like on the
On the street
The neighborhood oh okay
See what happened was
Obviously
People going back and forth between those I am sure
And they were coughing on people
Right
You proved it
So the place they stop for gas
What is where the covid outbreak
Started he's solved this case I got to say I got to give it up to Jim half-brother
Really I really
Agatha Christie
This one
I read the article on gay way but it's going to dismiss this and be like oh f*** yourself your mom's brother
But there's actually a really interesting
Peace for that
Just demonstrates how these people do their dirty work
That area that's really really dark or this is Sting signifies the most cases
Is between a couple biological warfare facilities
Editorialize in there a little bit better
EZ's Diddy's describing a map where there is shaded clusters where
There were early instances of
What is the
We started reporting Institute of virology
Last year
And look like yeah this is what's going on
Stockton was released from there
And then
Near that is another entity
Preparation
Destitute
BP is a yellow Square on that map
These two facilities
Is where
They're saying
A number of initial cases
So
How far away
You know
I guess more evidence.
This thing wasn't just us something that was natural
Food market
Between the Black Star there in the yellow box
So I've got some issues with this map
Eventually I found a very packed a black box that yellow square and a red.
No I mean like whatever is markers on a map
My first issue is that there are four additional clusters of early cases that are nowhere near either lab and at least 10 other report
Forged inspectors also outside the area
The gym hops brother is focusing
In theory it would be just as easy to argue that someone got infected in one of those other clusters and brought
The condition back to the neighborhood that hop
Focusing on
From the information that he's providing there's literally no way
That he could prove otherwise you know you bringing multiple points of fact that would undermine his
His argument but on the other hand have you considered don't worry about
No
The second major issue from a study in the international Journal of geo-information
Geographic data from a medical help-seeking app called weibo
The data isn't meant to be used in the way that Jim's brother is using
It is not it's it's misused
Only on 10
Yeah it's
Tracking the people who reached out for help through this app
Is datapoints maybe not for this
This is
The third problem is at the map that publishing on Gateway pundit isn't the map from that journal article
Call orbit leasing the only
The map
Closest of theirs is the one that depict
Weibo helps
Secret prior to January 18th 2020
Gateway pundit doesn't include the subsequent Maps
Depicting weibo Seekers from January 19th
20th
Which shows the distribution going
Way towards
The area's nowhere near the lab
Apps that they're focusing on
Nor do they even bring up the map
From January 21st
22nd which shows more of the same
Shifting away from that hot spot that he was
Decided to cherry-pick data
And just make it darken
Okay so then in this case
Here's my
Here's what I've got four
So some dudes
Shuffling
Dangerous covid
Back from Lab to lab
They stopped at a stop at a gas station
Accidentally drop a vial
Right it explodes that caused
But that's a small out right it's just one vial so then they go to the other places and that's where they
The big vial
Tossed out of the car
Interesting plot for a book
Or something but I don't have tickets
I've written it down
My final problem is that according to Google Maps
Jim Hopper brother his mislabeled the map he
It appears that that yellow square that he's talking about to signify the biological preparations Institute Shore
That's actually the biological preparations Institute marketing
Center
Advertise
Biological preparation
Attitude is about 25km South
Of where they have it marked on the map
If you actually use the correct location
There are no clusters
I wanted I want to throw baseballs at these people really hard
A little while looking at the map and asking myself questions about like
Is this entity exact
Actually like is this
Took a little while to unravel but this is like
Pretty basic stuff that they didn't even consider or they did consider and decided to lie about having service of making Gerard
This is that one situation of what was what's the name of those places where there's the
Institute and the
University or whatever and the heat they keep mixing them out of stock
It's the same thing where they just keep mixing up the dumb stuff in their life
Nobody's ever going to follow up on this except
That is a very good chance
It's the day just didn't even
They just saw like
Why would that no one's going to follow up on this except dance
So sloppy and embarrassingly
But this is business like gatewaypundits editorial
That's what they was good enough
To be put out
Exclusive
And then come on Alex's show at the end and ramble about it
Wake me up even
Problems that I was able to find with the way they were using that map from the journal itself
To what they were doing
Even if you did have the right location there were problems
But that is a different
Location then they're pretending
They just comical that fart
That's stupid
You're like the sigma five of propaganda let you know how
Scientists are like there's a one-in-a-million chance that we're not one hundred percent correct
3 is like 1000 or whatever
Your life
If there's a point in propaganda where it's like
Only dams going to care about that
So he might not if he doesn't accidentally curious about it
Just make this boring enough Jim hosta brother
Talk about it
Astride
6 / 3 is dead in like the New York
I don't know man it's going to spend a little bit of time looking at that
Burned me out at
Tiny bit between Lee like sort of
Just very
Constant boring
Racism
Immigrant
Bashing
You know that
I was like
I'm out
I'm out that late that made me miss Rodger Stone he showed up in the fourth hours should I don't usually watch
Before that
Maybe we'll get it next week
Boring
He sucks
He's boring now he doesn't do anything I think ever since he got that part
He's just not the
Just not the same man I mean you know I get it
Write like
You got all the adrenaline of life
Am I going to go to jail am I going to go to jail and then you get a pardon and you're like well now what do I do
Do it feels like
The definition of one
Once Bitten Twice Shy
I will try and get attention to myself as best I can maybe do some
Publicity stunt things from time to time
Oh yeah Larry klayman if I get a chance to do
I don't know
Stretch
Beginning
Michelle
Is there even value in Taka
I'm about it the reason is because I don't think a lot of it brings much new to the table
I think with Jim hoft brother and talkin about
Some of these Pacific
Instances of things he brings up
Maybe there's a little bit
Coverage of
Princeton's the shooting
He's all in service of anti-muslim rhetoric
It's all inside of
Yeah there's nothing there that you don't see in the aftermath of so many other tragic events
If you look at Alex's coverage
Kind of
I don't know it might it makes me sad that you
Still get away with this
Yeah it is it is one of those things where sometimes
We doing up
Episode that I want
In court as like a this isn't a First Amendment issue
This is Mal
We can prove Mal
Listen to this s***
Now you're going to have to listen to about
I think about 1,000 hours of knowledge fight at this point
So
But you'll get there
We'll get the conviction on this one
Anyway Jordan will be back
Indeed we will.
Until then we have website
We have a website its knowledge fight.com
Yes we're also want
But we are on Twitter that knows Irvine not go to bed Jordan we are also on Facebook
We are officially in Dallas if you could please find a local charity or Bellefonte in your area to help out people doing
How's work still Pledge on the altar
God
To try to force Alex Jones
To eat fake fruit
Alex