Air Jordan 5 sweat it
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge bright I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Knowledge
MoneyGram
Dot-com
Don't talk a little bit about Alex
JoJo doll
What's up
Matt was
Drawer
And
True backup on that I'd like to make my rice pot today that I had my first real job
Drawer moment
Where you were like what the
What should I put in here I was batteries
Batteries velvet
Neverwinter you never win the batteries moment so I was looking
Through the junk drawer
No no Double A's it turns out you are issued aaa's whenever you move in somewhere and nothing
Fitz AAA
Spectre Blazers coming to packets to Big you don't have this money is
If you think you do boys for one remote
Control
Echocardiogram
It says it was nice
I don't know if I feel
That's fair. How about you today is my support structure
My partner and you and the many people who helped me
It is been
A very difficult few days
Between me and my brain
Week or so
Not a good place to be
Sometimes my brain is
Downright abusive towards make sure so it is nice to have
These amazing people in my face
For the audience I did talk to you at all yesterday
Employee boss relationship I feel as strong
Pahrump
Yeah it so it is nice to have that is a huge bright spot for me because they're bent
Is my life
That support structure was not around and I was teetering on a knife's edge
Well I saw it is
A huge
And I'm glad that you're feeling better now a little bit better I assume
Do the show should have reverse
Just cuz I'm uncomfortable by View
Zhang's at positive things
Really helped me alot to as a
Sports
Vacu
It's great
Nice to be able to BMF
It's cute
Today we are going to this is sort of like today is also even kind of like my support
Okay I'll stop
Eyes open mic
Eaglewood say
What the f***
F****** self care
This is this maybe so care for me
Oh man we're through here a moment before we do got to take
The first
Also had a birthday recently thank you so much
Country
I also
Thank you so much
Who remember being
I literally don't
The Jarrettsville Jarod
I'm a policy wonk unclear unclear when his birthday if you if you are available
Please
Put in there just so we can give you a happy birthday whether you like it or
Next greetings from the city formerly known as Portland jurisdiction
Are you very much
All of you
This isn't over
Cillian
As well as
Genie
Who is also now polish
Anyway you got in touch with us and wanted us to wish you a happy birthday Cillian
Policy Wonka real rap
I'm a policy wonk
Play very much to all of you and Murphy to either he had a birthday
X
Jordan
What you doing today
Is
Emporia
Do you like apples
Okay alright
Today Jordan we got on our plate is
I found these old Alex Jones episode
I found episode
Woods dating back
2 2004 all right
So how do you like them apples was relevant at the time is
Okay I found episodes
Most insufferable and very boring
In the present day
Ignore him in the
But I also don't want to
Constantly
Just looking at him in the present day
To be dumb
It's worthwhile as a sort of social thing
Total electoral exercise I don't really care all that much
How about listening to a guy concert
Bentley say he's fighting the devil and then I'm
Supposed to take it seriously
And be like
I imagine that the audience does get a little bit bored with
I didn't listen to the third hour
Was too boring
Oh yeah and a lot of times I did listen to it and I'm just a guy who cares nothing in there
We will obviously still be talking about the Press
For today I needed to go back
Far back as I could
Today
2003 that won Christopher Lloyd Gaston
No
This episode is
Amazing
Number of reason
The bloom
Okay I am convinced now
I just
It's
It's a new day
Twenty years ago myself like getting these reinvigoration
Through like whenever it can find
These old-time
Frames to look back on it really is recharging of my batteries and
It's ma'am
I like it
Jordan restart
May 1st
Do you remember 2003 much humor was gone insane
Don't remember
Just ended a boy did we just mission accomplished
That was that day May 1st May 1st
2003 was the day that George Bush landed on the
The aircraft carrier with the bishop
An accomplished Banner
VI day as we all know it now
Victory was upon us
We're going to find out a number things
Things are really in
Listing to me
Five most excited to learn about
Are things like
How is Alex Jones's opposition
Into bush
And the Iraq War
How does it exist
Bush is in office
Prism of history in the context of knowing
How he behaves
Amore generally as a
Is a pattern
How can we apply that to this
Source material
Anyway
I believe you did you know
The New World Order
Has a plan
How many years was 18 years ago
We are now
Border
Control
That is all
Your health
Martial law
Bill Clinton want to know about Clyde
Don't care
Immediately I'm list
Something to this and I'm like
This dude
Is doing a voice
I wanted it I wanted to
Youth performance
This is so weird because I was I was literally writing down like I don't know how to describe it but
Sounds fatter
Has something to do with the way
He's filling up his mom's with air I think he's doing a bit of a Rush Limbaugh impression
It has a sound.
It's just
It's remarkable it sounds like a guy who thinks he knows he's doing
Got it just
You're constantly rebuilding the ship as you sail
That's how it's always work
Is it
Say it was really hard so I can't find the original article that I was talking about from the Pensacola News Journal nor can I
Find articles about archives
However I did find a geocities level website that's copied and pasted what supposedly that's articles I'm going to go
Read me article you can tell if it was going on there was a situation
Where the school called Hobbs Middle School
Who's part of a partnership with Whiting
Field Naval Air Station
A list of people coming to the
The school he was part of them volunteering to help
Search for a day
He did his very basic presentation as if the military was in charge of the school to help the students better understand the issues
They were facing the civilians in Kosovo at the time
As is clearly laid out as being effective
In the article
What are Whitfield
Students Julie McCool said the Press
The military personnel in her school
Made the news she been watching from Yugoslavia seemed a little more real
Georgia great it to use is an impactful lesson
For the students
Personally I don't think any military should go anywhere near a middle school
That's just me I mean I assume that they weren't like hey let's become fashion
Rested but I mean
The idea of making the newsreel are helping the
Students understand totally totally
If you were going as far as like
Hitting the kids with
I'm out
And also to sort of what you're saying
Be in favor of things that are basically like
PR
For the Armed Forces directed at school
That would kind of be a huge thing for me like that
I've been a Miyazaki fan for a long time and the military teaching children it's okay to be in the military is
Big deal
From the article
What I was getting from it is not so much
But they were teaching
It still has the effective rubbing off in like maybe turning these people into icon
Can you look up home
I can also see though like how this kind of an activity could be
Really positive educational tool for the
Some kind of
Position on it
On the one hand it could have the effect of making
These youths think that the Army is super cool but on the other hand
It also has the potential to open up the students
Two things they wouldn't
The chance to experience otherwise
Princeton's from this article
Quote last year students from Hobbs
SS Dixon Primary School email with a coast guard lieutenant
Bound for the South Pole
And had a video teleconference
What's their friend
She got there
That could be a really neat opportunity for students
To learn directly about all sorts of things
Much more real than reading about the South Pole in a book
Could be a positive thing
Yeah sure
What's it like on the boat
Have you ever seen a man die
We have to keep rebuilding
Before I've seen
Cool man
That you my arms
Also it's a where that voice cat was a weird voice
Keep in mind that these are middle schools to
Opposed to this being done with an elementary school since I could process any of this
You get Alex
Goodbye Middle School the kids should be exactly at the point where this could be a great experience for them
They're not too young to process it and not too old
To think that it's really dumb
Chiltern High School
Also this is an article for March
1999 so it's nice to see the 2003 Alex doesn't deal with
The thinking it's 2000
3 in word listening about Clinton and Kosovo and
I do think that that is a very important
Historical
Yeah yeah
If you're talkin about militarization of police post 911 obviously certainly a
Topic worth
Conversing about
You're leaving the show with his like
The military coming into a school
In Pensacola like that was pretty 911
You just need to
Better
To be able to just
Wok on a play
Whatever whatever the military was at school you can walk on to a place yet
Story from
The past is being woven in with a new headline Alex's read about
Program
If not it's over
So this doesn't really relate at all
Old story was about a day with military
A bakery in educational experience
This is more or less
The press release about a youth program run by former
The Young Marines is basically I'm bored
Discipline Focus version of the scouts
Corley go to the social organization performer
They basically put kids in boot camp like conditions and have them
Eat MREs in order to build strength in dis
Everything I can tell
It's definitely an anti-drug program but
Did not get the sense that it's anti-gun
Heated being in this group and I think it's
F***** up but the only way anyone's going to go to it
Is if they and their parents agree to take part in it so I'm not going to sweat too much
Time completely weather choices
I don't have to
The Iraq war is just
Speak going on
The Iraq war is just beginning what he said that mission accomplished sign up
What's the beginning of the Iraq War
No it did not
No it did not that was
That was way back when
Yeah man we really thought we were going to get out of there Dan
I don't know if I thought that back that absolutely did not I thought these guys were going to f*** everything up and we were all going to die
So Alex is above the political divide
The left-right paradigm
All this stuff
Think about Clinton's
He's above the left right there
Here's where things
You get a little muddy
Edward
No freedom
Evercore
America
That's pretty Illuminating
Tumi
It's really the Corvallis fake presentation to being above
Two-party Sher
He's presenting a position where the conservatives that they're actually secret liberals
Which is why the two parties don't matter
Cuz they're both not far enough to the right
Therefore they're actually
Play the same thing
What is above a two-party system at party system because I want to destroy them
Institute a theocracy what don't you understand
It would be just openly Advocate that he feels alienated by politics
Cuz he's way far to the right
Anything that exists
In 2003 he knows that's not going to appeal to a wide audience
Who plays the game
Being like
Call the left and the right is a lie
I not ended you know why
If you actually are conservative
You've got to be an extremist
Yes to the right because
These are really hardcore right-wing people are actually towed grit liberal
Yeah yeah that makes sense
At this point there was talk of
Do you need for the provisional government
Interact
Do you figure out how to set up
A system
There once
We were to withdraw
Well it turns out that crony capitalism is
Combined with colonialism does not work out well for anyone
Crazy
Appointment
I don't know how to read Alex's Stone there I really don't know what
Is he's he's being facetious or I was going to say
Smugness to it more than a facetious
I mean they had really
Hdbaset vacation at that test
Major things
Contributing to the mass of the stabilization in Iraq so it's keeping
Facetious in such ways that like
These get these idiots are trying to get rid of the best party
Or is he actually thinking that
The party is what's going to
Continue going on I think
That's based on the context that I have green
From listening to the rest of
This episode
I believe it Alex thinks
The cia's running fast party people
What's the Dow
Saddam was allowed to get away sure I set my alarm somewhere
Okay I'm okay
Workout
Susan hole
But
I think Ethan
Thinks that the best party loyalist
Some folks who the CIA
Trained up and all this will pretend that they weren't part of the bath party or whatever
And then they will become
People who are
The puppets
For the u.s.
Within Iraq
Moving forward
Betray them like they always do
I think that that that's
That's that's where he's going to lie is one of the things that I
Do you want to track
I'm interested to see how Alex's tone goes
During the
Pacification
For or against
I don't know really good question requires a nuanced to Alex's absolutely incapable of now
2003 Alex I think
At this point it seems like he's opposed based on this
Party members being allowed at the government
Right then based on political ideology
WWE super against house
Baby blanket
From all sorts of position
It just seems like
Zoopla he can't possibly be for
What would
What could
Possum
The only thing that Alex could before
A slide
We forced all of them to believe in Jesus
Jesus as their lord
Savior now
You're coming at this with too much of a 2021 allergies but I'm bitter and
What am I supposed to do
Like obviously can't have perfectly
Naive eyes
Different
Different different person
It's a Devour the same person
And you'll see a lot of similarities
What are the things I noticed I was listening to this
Is that he is
Definitely way more doing
And he goes to calls
And then I'll get back to a story and then later get back
Custom Calls
Like he jumps around
A lot of normal talk radio show
The f****** Russia
Compression look this is outrageous
What do you have more
Louis
Because
Sarge's I heard that impression
Guns is less crime can we covered exhaustively cuz
He talks about it all the
True
But I was listening to this
I felt like
I can see how someone would hear that
And believe
Yeah
Because it intuitively makes sense
If I were a criminal why would I
Risk going somewhere where someone has a gun
As opposed to somewhere where someone doesn't have a gun
Authoritatively
Almost certain the mocking the alternative
Right
Why wouldn't you just assume I knows what he's talking about you make sense
You know sometimes
Things are incorrect
It's the same way that people think about the death penalty of like well it's
The consequence is so high
Then that should act as a DE
Deterrent in the same
It makes sense of the macro or it's like
Well I'll be
Seriously we're not getting into a nuclear war because of
Mutually assured
Destruction
What's a deterrent against doing that but that is except
You're f****** hungry man you know like that's
That's a bigger deal then
Whether or not you're researching the possibility that they sold
You need to do it and you don't like that kind
Doesn't make sense in the micro-level
George Bush
Describe his politics
It's like on the
Spectrum
Right-to-left
Put him in the the the like
Not far right
Not center-right
It's part of like
I want to kill everybody but I want them to think I'm nice while I do it
Would you call him
Conservative
Compared to now
You're wrong on all counts
Conservative
Because
So he's a super socialist
Yeah
He's a super social
Socialistic
Creature
English
Just Cabinets
Alright
That cabinet
See now that's
That's a cabinet
Filled with pure psychopath
That's the thing about George W bush
I don't think he gave us
Push it I think you just filled the Psychopaths
Murder let's see if we can surround esteem
Just get it full of weirdos
Out of it Lisa Fred least four of the people in George Bush's cabinet
Had personally strangle the person you don't like that kind of level up so excited to see the tooth
M4 election happen
Anyway
At this next clip I think is is is why
How much does talking about how he doesn't feel bad
For Saddam which obviously
I guess that's
You haven't feel bad that
Missing
Target Field
Versa.
Alex
Play something she says later
I think he thinks he's on an island somewhere
Obviously don't feel bad for it
It's not like Saddam was Napoleon where they're like okay we got to Exile you that's our solution to this problem
And then Alex gives voice to some stuff that I can actually
You know
Appreciate
Feels bad for the citizens
The people
Look on the ground being affected by
But if you pay attention to this
Is one of these indications that you can get
Even this empathetic
Kind of
Vibe that seems really grounded in
Decent actually rooted
Sentiment
Her in the giant armored
Bored
It's all in service of just
Strong
Anti-government
Position
Yeah I don't
I don't see him
I'm carrying as much
Now about the
Hundreds of millions that were slaughtered by the
You know what
No
Continue caring about these
These people it's over after
Today but yeah and that's that's part of the reason
It's really interesting
Set an alarm
He comes from a place
Of any like
Solid
Center
Yeah it's not
It doesn't feel like it's based on intrinsic
Make believe
Stop position to cover
Yeah yeah yeah
A little bit taken aback because it seems like I want to say that this is a Slicker show
Already
Little bit
VR controllers exactly but
It's hard to like
Oh well see
Just because he
He's
I would say it's almost more disingenuous
By being a Slicker show
Oh yeah I agree with that video
And I think that's part of the reason why I feel
Cuz I can see how someone
Believe it
See how someone like listening to clip like that
To be like yeah this guy gets it
Who is f***** up
For killing civilians
Overseas
Yeah
It's the hook to get people to
Falling
No it seems wrestling
It's it's
Disingenuous in so
Evil
Jessieville
Imma John Bircher behind like hey it's wrong to kill civilians
Because you his answer is yeah it's wrong to
Kill civilians until I want to you know it's kind of situation and just leaves out that last part
Which in the present day
He
Kind of leaves today yeah he's mostly leaves
So
Will get you a lot more
Flight over trickery
Because I think you seats
Some pretty Stark examples of it later on
Society comes up later then
This is about
Security Institute
And IB system for livestock
Concerned largely about
Vulnerabilities within the food
Ability to
Know if there is a diseased cattle somewhere the causes blah blah blah
Bureaucracy
Sims 3 mocking
The idea of the
Protecting the food supply
That's interesting cuz that does fit the tone of some of the rest of his coverage throughout the show
But what it doesn't fit
Is the town of one of his
Commercials
Are you prepared
Biological
Alright
Can see how can flip
Messages would cause problems for us
Early listeners to the show
Bizarre
Why you're not raking in the cash problem
Very weird Ted Anderson is still selling crap
Survival
Being their best
A spectre to drum up
The fears of
Do the food chain
Food supply
Interested
I think that is
More government
And more taxes and attacks your cat
Yeah
He says
Loving ice
You know I don't know man
School
You like playing games recess
Blackmagic no cherry bombs
Blackmagic if you're out
Means but I remember
Exhaustive
Conversation
Beginning of the
What you first find out about the kid who's like
Oh no he's going to take his balls and he's going to take his ball s*** now we don't know how we have nothing to play with
Remember
The conversation of rules more than I remember for B2
Well here's the good news for square still legal
However
Dodgeball has been
Bam
The girls
Big the Run
Everyone loved
I can't find it
If I rested for Pre-K
School hours dodgeball game stats such a
Hate those by
I hate that ship
How much of the
Like one
It seems silly now not to realize
The dodgeball at that age is
Is essentially a way to facilitate bully
I'm happy playing at
We all know the game we're all doing a great job
The kids you're just
Like so many guys just picked on this phone
Everybody loves to play the game
He wasn't the runt
Yeah I think I like I think it is a game that can
Get abusive
Yeah
People not wanting
Play Mission before
Quiet
I guess if people want to play during recess
Almost Nationwide
Anderson the different way that Alex
The talking about his school days violin
Here in 2000
Very less.
Jump that guy's guts out
The present-day understanding of Alex
Says poor bird
Couple people
It's weird that he be sitting here 2003 laughing whimsically about
Back in the day did I murder
I did kill it
But I did Kill
I hate those f******
Story so much of life
Grew up we used to go out back and get hit with
You guys are all legitimately and say that I think you believe it
Thompson
You did not turn out fight
Do not tell me that story and then not connected to your violence
Present and that's why they're bad
Dodgeball
Of course now
Do you think has been arrested
This is going to be
This is a trivia question what is a variable
Alright get arrested for musical chairs
Yes absolutely
30 to 40 people at a
Time daily
You probably heard they're making
You get arrested
Spell did you bring it
No Rest for musical chairs
I would like to
Statistics on the FBI publish
Musical chairs related arrests
Bureau of Justice statistics
Yeah I don't know I mean I feel like I called musical chairs can't get a little bit
Supposed to
Like you're some kid is fighting with somebody over a chair
Got to deal with this now
Deep into a conversation
Buchanan can't do it
Schools the government
Does cracking down
WorldNetDaily
Girls
Spell Herald
So that's
What's a good story
Are we still doing
Peterson Elementary School in
Specific
What happened was that there's
The teacher at the school who witnessed some not specified public
Displays of affection
Recess
Decided to disallow girls
Boys
From Talking during recess
Obviously this is taking things a little bit far but also Alex is completely blowing this out of proportion
Talk to a girl
Would get arrested on criminal charges
That's totally made-up
Because I suspect even Alex knows the talk about the story on the merits of it
Might come off as a little desperate
To make your audience outrage
Honestly he's missing the forest for the trees here and there is a
Much much better story to be told
That is the story of Sarah Mains and Hannah Guerrero
12 year old girls at the school who took issue with the rule that got made
And protested against
Hannah straight-up formed astute
Committee study
I need the school's rules and figured out the proper steps to get a complaint
They got all the protesting students parents to sign off on
Straits that held a protest to have their complaint
Sarah's mother puts it so Wellness article from The Herald and News
I'm so proud of my daughter the hardest part was to walk
Into that school after protesting like that
I think she learned something important
Heartwarming
Yeah it is nice to know that no matter what era were in
It is a universal rule that
Children are way better people than adults
By a wide margin
Also the principal of the school said no disciplinary action will be taken against the protesters
He's willing to hear any complaints
Some students in Paris
Where you basically have here is a situation where a teacher
Possibly
Probably
Be concerned about
This led to an overly broad being put in place
Switch got students to become active in opposition
Listen to it these kids learn how to appropriately and effectively have their voices heard how to present
Argument through proper channels
Power is honestly an amazing story and I'm so impressed by these kids
What a bunch of
Text story
Really inspirational is abs
From coverage place
Because the story isn't real to Alec
Prove to be an effective for IPs
Details to make it something the government was doing to these kids
As opposed to an Ethiopian Ministry of decision
It makes me kind of sad because the Infowars audiences
Is deprived the story about students getting involved
Direct civicaction
Because I'm focusing on that too much makes it clear
This whole thing about flirting
Becoming a
Criminal act
Complete bulshit
Keeps the audience engaged I mean the story is essentially a microcosm
People taking on the government
Exactly like Alex would want them to do theoretically
However
That would be bad for his audience to actually take civicaction's
Change things
Because then he would run out of money
The students protesting
You know try and change
Do the government by sending a bunny to a blowhard
And then they were like take care of it
Are you just
Tip of the spear going out this teacher one send me money
Pamphlet
Geneva selling
Yeah that would be who Alex's
If you had sex
She's just in it for the apples
How does the still work I think that's why I'm a little I'm a little depressed about going back to 2
2003 because
How do adults still go
Get caught up in this b*******
Look at this
It's the same story that we're hearing about now the same story
Symptoms adults
Are still it's like at no point in time are they like
Have I heard this exact same thing
20 years ago and I'm
I'm fine
I think that you forget
Let me know we're on Christmas happy whatever year
I think it's worth Evergreen things
Media ecosystem is like these
These complaints that somehow the
Do you know
All of the kids are being softened its
School clothes
It's just something that will never not elicit a reaction
Come from
That audience
No of course because if they were to hear that
The kids
Weren't fighting at all they were learn
Using their words
Organizing and then make
Real change in the world
That would not
Fit in with their kids
Airsoft
You kind of look like
Idiot for fighting
Instead of learning
Organizing
And those girls who started that protested got the committee going study the rules
Big accomplish
What they set out to accomplish
And I ain't one of those screw up to
To be Michelle Obama
That's one of the important lessons
Think of being deprived from the audience
But that's how it's supposed to be if you want to get more depressed about 6
About the past a present
Great about how I'm to which you are awake
The British government
Piles of dead animals
You'll see
Bio weapons
By accident
Just amazing
So many similarities
Wow
There's no truth to it
Interesting late in the aftermath of the 2001 brake in the UK
Subsequent investigations have shown that it started on a farm that was feeding its livestock
Country
Stop.
The days immediately after the outbreak
What are the popular theories was it there was a vial of this
Specific strain of foot-and-mouth released
From Porton down
A biological lab
In England
This is an interesting story was essentially the present-day theories about the novel Coronavirus
At various points of the early days of the 2020 outbreak Alex's suggested that it was
Intentionally or accidentally released
From the Wuhan in
Institute of virology
He's also discussed
Race specific bioweapons to bolster his claims
This is like looking into a funhouse mirror of the past
I'm trying to torture you with us
Which act like okay I get there
That says
Is it species or whatever
And people are going to do that you know just because something shouldn't
Exist doesn't mean it's not going to
Right
What you
Can't possibly think it's a good idea even if you could make a race specific bioweapon
You can't think it's a good idea to leave it
Anywhere
You have to have that in a safe
Inside of a safe
Inside of another safe with
Like surrounded by people who've lost their hands
You can't open it
You whatever Endeavor to make something
So stupid and destructive
You would have to keep it in a parody of security
Oops away from all white people
Not okay
And also Ray Pacifica
Guardian
The various theories about the foot-in-mouth outbreak
Unfortunately for the
Conspiracy they spoke to a representative
We have never worked on foot and mouth
It doesn't sound like
Admitting that it was released from there but yet
They don't say that's weird
Colic
This Guardian article also discusses the Revelation that months
Before the outbreak people from the Ministry of Agriculture were calling around getting quotes on the price of Timber
In order to burn diseased animals that is true
How to supporting this has been sneaky and cryptically telling Farmers to prepare Pires
That's about the level of act
Chrissy you should
Yeah kind of close to something
But according to the guardian
Stratfordshire Animal Health office part of the Ministry of Agriculture
Ring around merchants in the autumn
A quotes for timber for tires
As part of an animal contingency plan on how to deal
With swine fever
Hand foot mouth outbreak
This is a requirement of all
EU countries
It happens every year
It's not something that's suspicious at all but Alex
Who's built it into
Trey foot in mouth
Was intentionally released from a level 4 bioweapons lab
In order
R2
Subway
Story that's
It's more about how England was like
Remember when we threw dead bodies
Tams
And then there was disease
We don't do that
It was a smart move on our part
So another
To the the present
To the Past
Comes in this next clip
Just stylistic
All 100
Flowers
Let's just ask
Wow
About to get to it
If if you say that there should be a ticker
That appears
Like this by
Majic 102
Pierce
Everyday the show ends at 98
My Wish
My genes which is just like
Nothing I don't want money I don't want happiness I want
Purely just
If you make
Claim like I'm going to do 100 things
A ticker a b n
Yeah
Calls from a conversation
Drift into talking about
The government
Tracking
Children's cell phone
Buy cell phone
Excuse that it's
To protect the kid
Right
It says something weird
That's interesting to me because that's a right on the line
A minority
That
That's the kind of thing that if you were really uncharitable and ungenerous be like okay so what mine
Normandy group so you talking about is that code
But it's
Yeah it's also a
If you are
Charitable groups that are
Euro it's
It's right there on the line for you to be like oh see how they do that they say it's for the chew
Children and then the next breath is
Seems like I only care about the millions of aborted babies it's about the aborted babies inside about
Controlling women's actions at all sure
Financial advice
To give I will save
Solid Financial advice
Ethical component
If they took
Motorola
It's
You make a baby
Maybe a good
More than 50%
You want to get out of it is apparently IBM owns the Chinese military
Implant Ator and the implant
Sure.
And everybody
Picture Show
What is the Chinese government
Ex-military
Daddy's
An interesting way to diversify your
Okay well we did pretty good with that that almost
Suggest that the computer thing was just a way for them to make enough money as military
Questions that I want answers to like it has it been sold
Baby I'm still on the Chinese military
What does the Chinese government
About military
To check with IBS
Play Space companies
What apps have a solid business plan so they were like well we might as well buy a military while we've got the
Yeah
15 hours a day
You doing articles you put out
Normal
I can't imagine reading for
The number of hours
About things that I would suggest
Realizing
Call disguises
Bulshit
Terrible
Yeah or something
Research
You would learn about how much b******* it is by ozmosis just by repetition
Just like
I've heard this before I've heard this before I've heard this
Play this doesn't say what Alex
I think it is
Indicative of a lot of
His listeners and how a lot of people who get into this world
Their experience of it
Compulsive
Compulsive relationship
Ship with this
Disinformation 15 hours a day cuz your normal bill
People react
To the things that I say
So I went to this point
To make a programming note
Kind of review
In as much as
Tragedies
Traffic
There's a terror event
Radio
Little defensive
I take it this is interesting
This point he does understand
That Dynamic of like tragedies
Lead to more people
View and machete
You should have learned from 9/11
You should know that by now pretty well
I question whether you understand
At this point fully
Obsessing about the
Immediacy of another tragedy happening soon will also speak his words that pretty
Quickly
Don't feel like it at the
Feels like a radio show
This guy sent me down
Nutso rabbit hole
Insane
Wondering if song
Signatures
Redecoration
2003's and
Interesting time for followers of
Conspiracy culture in
The community surrounding
In the present-day extremely far-right Tendencies of almost entirely absorbed that space
It wasn't
Probably agree with some of this caller suggested new grievances
Post about the government
Okay
Machine exist
I was able to find this caller is re Declaration of Independence
And perhaps unsurprisingly I did in fact find some common ground with this guy
Princeton
First complaint
We demand the abolishment of engaging our military and unconstitutional activities
Spreading them out as the police of the world while even protect
I might have left out the part at the end about the
Boarders Inn on Constitution
Military
But leaving that aside we agree the government
Got to stop this war stuff true
A little bit later we find even more agreement
Quote we demand the abolishment of all instances of murdering citizen
Completely within their rights and
Destroying
To disclose
Anthony's crime
I would even expand that language to include non-citizen
Remember that that's where those people were at
Now they're at Blue lives matter
You know you don't know what those guys up to
Immediately
Complaints about you entreaties and calling for abolishing quotes
The post office public education and a
Play a little bit
This document
Completely goes off the rails with words like treason
Starting to pop up in all capital letters
Hair that's where we get it
The trouble with you all caps a word
You are yeah
Part of the Declaration of Independence is charging any individual Lorinda
Industry that traded with North Vietnam
China Russia Iraq or any of their satellite countries
With treason
This extends to literally
Everyone who works in things like steel or
Petroleum Industries but also to everyone who's been an elected office in Congress
Executive branch over the Supreme Court to the Korean War
Yeah you might as well just rewrite that
To say we got to clean house and get rid of all these guys him past let's
Yeah let's
Beginning at
The sixteenth century and we'll start over
Document demands quote all who served in these political positions during any of the times of armed conflict
Question from the Korean War to this date
Compensation
I'm guessing that's in addition to
What about people who supported
The Civil War
The South
Treason charges
4th Federal Reserve
The biggest businesses
Ancillary astralis
Humor this collar
I'm certain that Alex didn't read it but honestly it's so much funnier to imagine that he had
And was still giving the sky glowing review
Here's how the new Declaration of Independence
Ends with a C
They should do next
We hereby petition for a renewal of government
Removed entirely from Washington DC and reconstituted
In another region Alliance
And at least temporarily at first during the
Beginning this
New government for and of the people be redeveloped
From Austin Texas the birthplace of the new people's house with an initial mailing address of
Believe I'll just leave it out
A new government will be birthed
For the Free World mischley and temporarily by the following Patriots of this new age
Alex
Ono Ono top of the list
Alex Jones
Eric rainbow Mike Hansen
Chris f
Autonomous
Kevin Smith and Robert
In order to retain our original forefathers Declaration of our God
Add framework for the lasting legitimate Republic promoting Global Freedom under God's laws
Not a select group of men's
And a complete dismantling
The Tyranny hereafter
Well this wasn't that much
Farther after Mallrats Rothrock Evans
What is the Papua Stephen Kevin Smith
This guy wants to overthrow the government reconstituted in Austin have Alex until of Alex's friends
Temporarily this new Blossom and government
Yeah
In case you don't know those
Mike Hansen was Alex's longtime cameraman
Producer
Kevin Smith
And George Humphrey and Bob Desi were regular Infowars guest
Infowars
Chris atanas I don't know who that is
Rainbow
Is that
And I realized
This caller
Well you're not going to not insert yourself into the pub
If you Google the address that he listed
The temporary address of the new government of America
Ivey publishing address for a 2000
15 book titled
The free Masonic Ark
Architecture of hist
Self-published by Eric rainbow
If it's it's definitely the address of
The publishing of his book that was
Written and self-published by Eric
He was also the proprietor of 911
Exposed.com
The real mystery here though is that the name of the person listed as the owner of that house.
Match
With Eric rainbow
I felt like I was at a dead end my curiosity was itching too strongly
What's this color of the person who wrote the new Declaration of
Government
In Austin
It's really complicated but I looked into the phone numbers and addresses listed for the publishing Endeavor and I
Pretty certain that it was this dude it was actually written under Eric
It's underwater
I found the
The phone number that's associated with
It's someone else's phone number but also at the house phones Associated someone name
James rainbolt
But Eric rainbow is probably living
I don't know maybe
Eric rainbolt has written a couple of other books
Under the name Eric James RuPaul
Stupid
Long road for me to wander down to the reason I still think it's important
Because there's some
Critical thinking
Stop at me and this guy would totally agree about
We both want to end the Iraq War
We both want greater oversight on police
Pretty crucial to recognize that despite our differences we are
Close to allies
Ever B
Ultimately I want to create a world that operates better and more fairly for everyone
Ultimately this guy wants
To be on Alex Jones a small count
Yeah
Also this guy ended
What's 75 signatures on his
Petition datapoint
The last screenshot on the way back
Michigan available the state was from July
Furniture exposure
What the f***
The guy who wrote this
Enemy of my enemy is
Is not my friend if they also want to establish a
Roland Style
I'm the hand of the king for Alex Jones
Situation Bizarro religious experience libertarian nonsense
Some of his guests
Rule the roost
I don't think so I will choose
Other people to work on that if you
Yeah
Anyway
This was kind of what
I'm sure that this guy
That was the beginning of a call
Alex gets another
And it's kind of interesting
This this fella has a plan
For dealing with some of the
Daddy doesn't like
Books like
Hannity
These folks
Who are not
Conservative
Barf
Broadcast individual this weekend
Case in point
The real makeup
Michael Savage is a beatnik
All right here's what we do guys
We got a blackmail Hannity and Michael Savage child record
Interesting
Do you think that's a
Potent way to attack
These figures on the right that you don't like and apparently aren't on the right
I found out public records
That Sean Hannity got it
His civics class
Is that the type of person on the radio Dash is over for him
Hashtag
Canceled
Google cancel culture
It's really weird to hear this kind of Ploy being
Suggested by this caller
And then also
The political framing is so important
Like we have
George Bush
His cabinet there super socialists
Is a
Call me
A boy
Very right-wing people
Presented as
What
So like they're not even moderate or maybe they're supposed to be like tomorrow
He knows if you will Dad that was a
Big Talk
Boynton 2000
3 and ever and Always Forever
But it makes it okay for whatever really really
Thank you what
Sorry I don't know this is just actually normal conservative right all right
Maybe
Sovereign citizen
Is even just normal conservative
Your honor objection
Chili bowls
Sysaid
This isn't true what Elsie saying isn't true
They arrested me simply because I refuse to go down the road without a driver's license
Is an interesting way of putting
I've been driving without a driver's license and I don't give a
Sounds right
It's weird
The Bedrock
Gino's
Aurora's almost 2nd of oppositional Defiance or the concept of rules that art self-generated
DF
Enterprise
Today Alex Jones
1 Tucker Carlson
I forgot so much.
Obviously we heard he doesn't like
You think that Michael Savage is a commie
Coincidentally more important figures
What do you think he thinks about
Fox Fox News
That they are just a left
An outlet
Giving out propaganda for an Obama that hasn't even been elect
Headed to the Senate
Do you think that they are
Savage
Mirena Army that's on the ground today know what's going on today
Don't know
Ultra call me channel Fox News we're cutting all your benefits right now is not a thing that is acceptable for a
To say in a negative way
And you should be like
Yeah they're cutting all your benefits cuz you don't deserve them you lazy pieces of s***
Quit the show I got to leave I got to leave
Ultra, foxnews.com
Play Fox News
Call boy
It wasn't quite what I expected I mean it's it's
It's a lie
Toosii
I think I'm going to have like some really subtle things to Triangle
Sit through
Instead it's just like
Michael Savage
This is great
Cat
That's so
Cuz we've talked about this for
Years of like
If you just abandon Trump you
Space
Of like
I don't trust Fox News they're a bunch of liberal,
B******* you know like it's so easy you could just
Giving a speech on CNN and their whining about some nonsense
5 year old who's got a problem
The proof of the pudding
Is in the eating
As it were
He wasn't his career in 2003
And look where he is now
Like obviously
Signing up with Trump
Massively
Exposed him that's gotten him
A far greater space in the public
Sure
Sphere
He's made it's made him relevant
People
Like at least
Jokingly make
His name friend
True true
Back then 2000
He had like
Position of defiance against the right at the last ride
Pikachu
Pretend it was because he's above the divided butts release
Extremely far to the right
That's true
You're not wrong
Although I bet buddy
You know
I was I'm still of the opinion of like carving out that
Comfortable space is so much better than being like
Well if I hitch my wagon to Trump strained I can become world-famous yes
Better if he had
He lusts for the sun sets tropaz
And maybe that's just
He could never do that whatever it is
Yeah it is it is one of those situations where were they
The actions in context
Completely different I would be like man
I got to give it up to you for a seeing an opportunity and shooting your shot
Has not worked out for you
But within the context and his actions
He's an idiot and I hate him forever
And I want to throw baseballs
I don't know if you know this but 2000
In addition to seeing the end of the Iraq War
We also
Covid-19 Coronavirus
Sequel
To what's going on in 2000
Let's see how it looks see how we handled it if
Maybe the real
Power
So weird to see how the past Echoes with the
The present
But you can get back in 2003
Actually make about the novel Coronavirus
Almost like the actual facts in front of him don't matter
Add a particular details of a story
Decorations on top of his existing reality
It was a big deal it was real and it was not a power grab
At this point scientists have been able to concretely isolate the SARS virus
On March 22nd 2003
At this point when I was making the episode it's only been a few weeks
Ization
Situation is very much
The International Community jumped into action
Quickly identified the virus
And cautionary steps were taken
Bedspread
Because of collaborative action and probably some
Because the right wing
Conspiracy
Manhattan grown to the size that hasn't a present only 774 people in the world ended up dying during the outbreak
Between November
Thousand
In July 2000
The Toronto Star article Alex is referencing his
Bet anything it was an editorial article presented the
Response to SARS has
Hysterical
We can't find some people still
Existing
Websites that Express website
It's hard to say if people are overreacting but the greater Toronto area saw before
First outbreak of SARS cases in the world
Behind China Hong Kong and Taiwan
Really does kind of make sense
What's the matter there would be taken seriously
In a way that might look like a serie
But if you didn't act that way who knows what the
End result would have been
You know I've always
Who is Ben
Bootleg especially week
Obviously not when you thinking about it but
It always
Kind of like
Messed me up
People say off
Hysterically to this virus
And it feels like
The entire human race should be
Be so hysterical about viruses and bacteria conspiring
Killed almost
You don't like it we talk about I'm so scared of war and all that s***
All the people who have ever lived
Most of them have died because of some disease or another
And I think it's not like we should all be
The conversational times when we're not
Dealing with outbreaks
Infections
Stop people in medical community
Talk about
The unknown unknown exact about
Conversation
Disease ex or whatever
This thing
We don't know about that we may ask
To deal with
Really a terrifying Prospect cuz you have to figure out how it spread
What is characteristics are
And while you're figuring that out its
Spreading
Could be spreading
Thick almost
Become more rational
The more you think about it some people that I knew
We're going through some
Steps that
I would say we're maybe a little bit
Further than I would even at the beginning
No dealing with these shorts
The 2020
Situation
I'd rather do this
And look stupid later
Then not do it
And look
Feel like I do I
Taking preventive measures
Compelling argument I felt stupid after
Part of it is just the the
The very fact
It's so many f***
People don't
Don't not just
Not understand evolution
Believe it entirely
It's just like
You realize that if a virus spreads
It's going to reproduce
Billions of times in a very short period of
What time
Exponentially increases the possibility of mutation
And adaptation to
Measures against it
It is not it is a constant battle it is not
Like even now if we defeat
Did you go to the extent that we would all love it if we don't
Completely eradicated
It is going to mutate any
Can come back
Anytime you don't like
It's it's a real terrifying reality
And most people are like at probably witches
We are
Which is it works
For the um totally
Always
You know
I don't know
I guess it's Trump was president
Conspiracy community
Just that the way it does now
In 2003
Sorry
Much bigger problem
Well I mean you think about
Think about you think about so many of you know like you think about Ebola outbreaks you sent you think about those things that happened in
In the past that
In retrospect you realize we're handle
Fire by people who understood and
You were serious about the problem
Instead of a
Actively exacerbating it and the people who are causing problems
Silverspot
Hey you know Alex at this point
It's getting towards
Zeno's
End of the show
We're getting deep into it
Still hasn't come
Howmanyofme
There's no pills to sell supplies
Looking for exposure
If you get three of them
Horoscopes
Emeryville
What about shipping is shipping still expensive at the time I don't remember
Probably probably
Probably
From from
Commercial
Make Me Wanna
4 something
Alarm
New World Order
Horrible
Anyone who listens to our show with any regularity as heard that
Pretty frequently when he gets in a wistful contemplatively
Yesterday he was
Computers but today all the pieces of Come Together release more certain than ever that is a mouse's been right all along
And it's worse than you thought
That's an interesting experience
Episode
From 18 years ago and see him
Pretending to have the same Epiphany that he does regularly
It's a little annoying
Also another reason I pulled this clip
Is because Alex makes a reference to God and to demon
But
I think you can tell how much different that feels
And speak to the present
My ears
Listening to this
It kind of comes off like a man was a religious
Just inclinations but isn't azella
It feels like a person calling his enemies demons as a
The pejorative insult
Not as the description that meant to be taken literally
It's weird to think about but maybe Alex meant it to be heard as literal all along
If he were just giving him an unasked for benefit of the doubt
There's no way he could fix
Demons were real and they were just
Crazy
So we'll assume that
He's beating a metaphorical in this sense
I don't think that's the case but it's fun to think of
Exit possibility
You've been pretty upfront about it
I hate time travel episode sometimes I love
You are you're like a mr. Peabody who refuses to let
Me get into the time machine you just make me watch a movie of the
The path City alike
Oh yeah if we use this time machine we could fix it all but
PW
Four interesting cartoon
So
Another call and
Back in 2003
You know I have a lot of friends that are make
I don't have
Friend
The first place
Driver's license cuz they do not load
They're there for
To work
Because they do work
Okay
What you doing
That's for sure
Exact same response that caller
You know what you're doing Alex
This is the same show we're just an hour ago we were told
You do not need a driver's license
Fright with a caller
Between who
Did not have a driver
Marriage license in Hoover
We have Alex
I was talking about that like if your uncharitable
You could hear him saying
The minority
Minorities
Rope in his mind is like criminals are a minority of the population
About
This is not
The same thing
Yeah
You guys are talking about undocumented immigrant
Proper channels are people who overstayed Visa
They're just talking about the blanket category of people who are immigrants
And this conversation
Is outrageously white nationalist
Puzzling over
Driver's
Santa's which is a bit silly
Alex
Mario bosses instructed to take quotes
Our rights away you got it
Comically transparent here in this walks hand-in-hand with a white nationalist ideas but the great replacement
Stick it through sometime
This is the way that conversation was had back then it's basically indistinguishable
Beaufort
Supremacist positions on immigration
I just see you like a six-year-old Harris
Smithfield and I would be worse than that someday
I want to be more explicit about it
Exactly what I know he is saying I want to take this game and push it a little farther
Further to the race
So bored
So Alex
Kansas big pointed keeps make
He can go on any show
Conservative
There's a board Today Show
Conservative liberal normal whatever
In the middle Center who give
Give the s***
Recalls
Of course they all agree with
He's so ideologically consistent and because everyone knows that bush did 9/11
True
If he gets here and role-playing a little bit as some collars
He's fantasizing about
Talking to on these radio show
Call
Haha
Well
In the shower
Is kind of feeling like
The present is imaginary.
Narrative Arc of these callers
Disgust
It's very
Normal
For decades as dumb people he has to talk to
These people uses caricatures of straw man argument
That's presented things that are complaints about Alex
Use of these imaginary dumb callers
Puppets to introduce these ideas
Because discredit those ideas
Like that use erase
Yeah
You can hear Alex essentially laying out that him arguing that the Republican party is corrupt
Is a way to get liberals
Who can admit the Democrats are corrupt
To wake up
Yeah if you lie about he being hypocritical
Bill wake up
And they won't know you're lying because
You're not a malicious figure yet
This is a strategy
And it's meant to make Alex look closer to the middle
This hypothetical democratic
The ideas for him
Picture where humans liberal have more in common than they think they only don't think so
Corrupt political parties
Books similar
This is not true
How to light years to the right of
Give the GOP
So what is actually doing is trying to pull disaffected people of either party towards the extreme right
For people already in the Republican party this could be
Mean becoming
And extremely right
For Democrats this might mean becoming a
Dated political nihilist maybe a brace in the GOP just not voting for democratic
Ultimately
The political end result of the project Alex's engaging in is best
It's always about dragging people to the right well
Pretending there is no right or left
Which serves the political interests of whichever viable political entity is farthest to the right
Yeah that's
Hiam abbass
Divide an
They want to do all these
Taxes and things and I just want to drink blood from the skulls of my enemies
What what doesn't everybody get about that wake up people of a buffalo
Truly opposed to the left-right divide or whatever
And someone was like
Does suck
I'm going to start exploring
You should be just as into that
I mean
The Socialist state
Present
To write I haven't heard him bring a break and all this episode
He doesn't like anybody from what
Everybody that is like you look like
Gross conservative or communist
Which
I can but I can you can
Totally see
That kind of
Being attractive especially at that time whenever you look at the
Fact that both political parties are like
Warriors Gray
And let's do it
All the time
And you're like a wolf
F****** point I'm having either of these political parties if we're just going to wind up
With a mission accomplished Banner
Something like Alex's superpower
Background
A lot of people who are right
Exact place
That they need to be too
Hiramasa
Did you like that
And get sent down a road they don't know they're going
Yeah I would say it's hard to argue that
You know
Osama Bin Laden didn't destroy an entire country by himself
What's a patriot
A little baby
Traits of course but
It's a little bit like
9/11 really did
Tiffany Tamara
Instastalker
This is where we're going to
Picking Intuit 2003 stop definitely
Definitely be more of a topic
Today
Because
Alex
Please call her that he gets on radio station
He ends up talking about being on a show
UK right
And this is your call
Jail guard
This is evident
Show used to be a family show
Family Show
FCC rules
I would say
Radio interview
But I guess
Either this collars
For this didn't happen
It's so interesting about Alex ghost
Five minutes talking about how you knew this guy was a jail guard
Stone
I get you locked up I want you to lock up
People only have like really want to do it
I heard this guy either
Either
Was a Serial kidnapper right or jail.
Smart kidnappers just become jail guard cuz
They can do all that stuff and it's legal that sounds right I'm fixing to him since this is how I read this guy
Right they just haven't found the right kidnappings.
It's a little annoying
Kind of trivial lefun
It's such an annoying habit of so many people to tell you a story where somebody is
So
Over-the-top unreasonably
That it's impossible to believe
And you know
Before he even started he was full of s***
Calls
Unfortunately it's a terrible story
I'm calling you today
Because my local FM
Even exist
Television
But you know
This is like
My favorite
Thing I love
Going back to this time
The past
And the colors are fuc
Can callers they're not like
Sycophant nonsense I love your brain Force now
I'm not allowed there anymore because I refuse to discuss anything but
50 year old news
I love that
That's a Vibe I could listen to
Like
I could bust that forever
I'm not allowed on C-Span anymore because I won't stop talk about Fort Sumter
Bulshit Alex
It's b*******
The cancel culture is out of control
They won't let me harangue them
For no reason
About Fort Sumter
Infuriated dad
I love it
Call
Society which iatse
Kabob
Alex believe that the John Birch Society
Mostly good
He's pretending that's so much of his ideology isn't based on
People who were in and adjacent
Unrelated iLearn
Separate from the jumpers
I definitely wasn't raised in a household filled with joy Bircher literature Society
That really does
Explain everything doesn't it
Pretty Cuban
So this made me laugh
So f****** hard
If you get what he's talkin
Don't yell it out let this play out
There is a Oklahoma
Iraq
Sierra Leone
Dr. Berg
Mark Walnut
I wonder who is Chaka
Sing about
Because of the Kansas thing
Go on to help Hitler and then he started a crude oil interested
Duncan Oklahoma
Call Rock Island oil and refining company
It's just amazing
I heard about this
Big family
Did the John Birch Society they support
Doesn't know anything about this is real
Babe
In John Birch Society nonsense he does
Know the name
Afraid Coke so infuriating
Do you think maybe if citizens united have gone another way none of us would
Be able to instantly pull Koch brothers name
Wouldn't that be lovely
I don't know I don't know if that's true
I think it's really interesting
Obviously I'm fascinated by
Particularly
That era of
Anti-communist propaganda
Ideology
Mercedes-Benz large
I know about
The first meetings in the
Meet the people that like
Obviously Fred Coco
The founding members
Weird to me that you think
The Alex came from a family
The clearly was virtue
Full-on members
He doesn't understand like
Who the
These players are
Post to B cells
Necessarily connected to each other originally so
It's not like they had a hero-worship of their founding member
Are you at home
And stay in it for all that long
Yeah it's too busy with the Nazis
If you got s*** to do
Can
Koch brothers
Pretty involved with Lake
Ron Paul that's true
I don't know it's
It's weird to have this
He's not saying ignorant
He does seem like he's frustrated that he doesn't
Know the name
But Bert yeah it's strange
Another call this is where we learned that Saddam Hussein
Maybe
Information about the Saddam Hussein
Please don't do that to Dubai
Service
U.s. refrigerator
Credit
Sorry
Sounds about right
He's probably in Cuba
I make sense
You know what I would do.
You know what I would do if I was to die
Closer to the United
Americaloc
I'll take a boat from North Korea to Maine
This person
Is into the birch
Society
So there's a little bit more conversation about that
Is a kind of Interest
Let me say something about
I was a member when I lived in Utah not a member now but I do gets magazine
Information
So you're still want the other day that goes back into 98
And here they were telling about
The world trade tower
In Wichita
Saddam Hussein
The one thing I wanna make sure everybody
People that sing
Things about Alex
Jones and put out in
Information about Alex Jones
Stadtmiller somebody else
And this is the chloride remember back in the 50
Season 60
Birdy
MacArthur I can hear
MacArthur
Story Church attorney pretended Joseph McCarthy was writing is insane, dude
Bulshit
I love thee
The moment
Yeah that is really polite angry Alec
Yeah
That's better than better than now
I would assume that those issues of the John Birch Society magazine that the colors are
I think they have to do with the
The other time the World Trade Center was bombed
You would think I would assume it has something to do with it
I've noticed that a lot of conspiracy thinkers Tintin
Ignore that that
That happened because it helps
Makes sense
Why people would have been talking about terrorist attack on the World Trade Center before 9/11
Yeah it would be it would be like oh so this guy already tried it it would make sense for him to give it another go
If you failed the first time yeah big
The context of
The first bob
Otherwise its course
There's a reasonable explanation
For this boy this really weird because
Cuz Alex is talking about
Okay so
This caller saying there's a John Birch Society magazine from like 1998
It's talkin about bombing of the World Trade Center
That's supposed to be his pretty
Did the John Birch Society stuff from 1998 would make meth addiction that he made in 2001
Also he's told her Bill Cooper
Yeah
To take credit
Some kind of a
Prosthetic
Person in terms of this
Yeah I would imagine
Using that he didn't make it to the 4-year University was
He couldn't keep himself from
Plagiarizing anything and everything in it
If possible
Bluebook borvan individual at this point
That is true
I was not I mean despite the rush
Slimbodi pressure
Yeah
No I remember at that time
My my
My dad had all the limbo book
Books and I was
I was
Inundated with right
Talk news radio
And I wasn't hearing this s*** that's for sure I definitely wasn't hearing this
Some of this is a little
I'm fascinated by how some of it is so
Like what
Similarity
Waze deals with stars
Sayings
They attempt
Released
Mouse from
Bellissimo
Those who learn to act
Exploded in the past refused
To change anything so they can
Continue exploding in
The future dance
For you
That's the real question
I'm fascinated
Beloved
The past
I can't wait to keep
Listening to this specially to see you like how has the
Iraq
Is clearly not over
Yeah we have a thousand for election
When does multiplying in bed so we haven't done monthly invest
Navigations for a long time I just might be open-ended
Forever
Be not afraid
I will still also be keeping up on
Present day and I promise
Will check in and see what Alex is up to whatever his dumbass
Mirrors this
Let's find out how
We'll see but anyway
We are in spirit. No donors were fighting I go to bed
If you could please find a local charity or bail fund
How about
But until then I am super socialist
Paul wolfowitz
Holding