Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for Tenaya Lodge right now it's like I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Just a little bit about Alex Joe
We are Dan what's up today
It might be the same as yours and that is a
It's not okay
There was a lot of fun to see the response of people having a lot of crossover
Between audiences
Chuck Norris the movie
I was so terrified when we were recorded that that none of it would make sense like the plot doesn't make sense of
If you watch the movie Raymond hearing the
The five of us
Trying
No just like
Break down the plot of a movie store
This is not make sense
Listen to enjoy it so thanks for that check that out
Should I go to world very much so I gave it a little bit of a listen and
You know like a I'm just trying to move along as it don't worry about it if you keep talking and we're both like
Man if you don't literally tell us to shut up we're going to get.
We Can't Stop
This literally listed at like
I miss
At least a half-hour of stuff that I wanted to put in there yeah definitely true
No more thoughts
Could have been like what about Rogan episodes
Reservoir Dogs have to leave it just be like
You guys finish it out
And I will guarantee it's not the same as yours because it is
Jay baseball baby
I was going to say you could already know what mine is stupid
Well congratulations on the sticks
Congratulate me it's not like I'm it's not my cup of coffee this year you enjoy you enjoy watching these guys
Guys get out there and play
Play the game America
Think the Ricketts family should have been burnt at the stake for many reasons but what they're doing to the Cubs is
Now at least number three on the list who's looking good this year what teams are in the who you keeping your eye on other than the Cubs
The Cubs well I mean I'm looking at Los Angeles LA Angels
Is my favorite baseball player throw 98 mile an hour fastball
We can hit 500 ft dingers Dan inter better than that how are the Expos look
The Expos are looking dead
Nonexistent
The exposer looking like a blockbuster franchise right now
I got to call my book
Bad bad
Well you'll get there 1999
Who's that
Is Johnny Damon still around
What else you got I don't know
Board games
Albert Pujols
Actually Albert Pujols is on the angels and he's still around all my buddies used to love Pujols cuz he was on
Weird stamps
You'd stand there real weird
Still does yep still does
One of the best hitters in the history of the game
From everything I can
Until right
Have you heard how much of an a****** Albert Pujols is Roberto Clemente looking this year
Resume
I've got bad news for you know
In the present-day Sotomayor
Sing about March 30th and 31st
Them Apple
Oh no that's not going to work
He's good I can tell me you can use it whenever you have something shity to say to me and said how you like them apples
Interesting couple of days
Infuriating in many ways
Typos are in an otherwise there's something that I think is really interesting
That I think
Bears talking about but it also
Alex's position on it almost doesn't matter
This is my way of
As is tradition
Underselling what whereabouts.
It doesn't matter
Before we get down to business let's do some of it does matter which is name some new walk that's a good idea
The first 20
1 Blackjack liquor
I'm a policy wonk
Connect note Writing god-awful Movies as my Kik give me more please sir thank you so much right now policy walk
Text William KW 3rd
I'm a policy wonk expire leadership
Thank you so much
Spider leadership around here
You Mercantile dogs and
Archaeologist
I sold damn we've not gone
Thank you so much you are now policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much and I say that
Is this like an old friend of yours and hate me for like
You have the opportunity in
In the left-hand I have a gun
I don't edit the right hat
I have some weed I don't recall that I know that I have bought weed from a lot of people over the course of my life
And I do know there was one person that I knew
I think it's this
But there was one person that I knew who shall go nameless
Who sell me weed for a while and then later I found out that he was also selling
Oh
I didn't know that at the time
Well I don't think that that's Miss person
7 Bebe
But anyway thank you so much for a policy
People who have been with the same weed dealer for like 30 years
You're like some people who were like I just only go to this one store for my like I'm a Kohl's person
Do you have like a I'm a cold person
Surprised I think
I think you have a bond that's for
Kohl's gets arrested less
Disrupt a relationship sometimes program is a little bit better
So finally like to thank you to somebody who is now a technocrat
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
So much
So Jordan
BFF Oneida County
Text Rob
Alex's violin
Towards animals
And this is right in that line
Sometimes you got to hit him you upside the head with
Willow
That doesn't sound true you have two left with no training would like more context on the situation
Where I have no choice but to hit it with the to buy well contacts drop I could give you the entire context of Alex
F****** Mini Clubman show
Talking about how sometimes if there's like a cow
It's being eaten by fire ants and it's
Pregnant and you got to get it to safety you got into it with stuff in order
I was going to go with pure zombie situation but I will accept that if there is a cow beanie
Away from the fire ants and got hit with a board
And the Liberals would tell you no don't hit it with a
Baby trying a hose
Eastman's probably to Seckman
That's talking about that that seems right
It's outrageous
And I have no Focus
Here we start on the 30th
And spoil
I turned this episode off
It got very boring
Wow
It is official mainstream
That the coven lockdowns are designed
To make us living
Quote save the Earth from carpet
They both said it years ago they had a plan
A few months ago they said how great the lockdowns are have them permanently
To save the Earth at robots Deliver us all our food
Obsolete depopulating
Sure but now the Wall Street Journal the New York Times
Associated Press without me even look
Today
Wait what where are saying
We need to be president never leave our homes again
Cool Stockholm Syndrome
Oh wow
How could this not have turned out to be a banger of an episode
Without even looking I saw these things that didn't happen however
Speak to one of the things about our show that I enjoy
That
It is that you yourself
Something like that
And most of your life
No it didn't
I just felt like
No
I mean you did not say
They want you to be prisoners in your home
I'm fine we been over the territory so many times but
This is just one of her to be like to know
Absolutely not
Go f*** yourself said I give you more than the benefit of the doubt
And you have broken me
I don't feel broken I just don't care I'm going to choose my battles and this is what I'm just going to be like
Tell me what you're talkin about and then me and then woke up probably not
Because I know the only citation that he ends up giving in the first like
40 minutes of the show is a f****** editorial that doesn't say what he says it's there's a problem so I don't care
Anyway this is where we get really misogynist
You heard him bring up Stockholm syndrome there
Speaking is when we get really massaging
They were just going
Stockholm Syndrome
At least 30% of the public mainly women
Will go under Stockholm syndrome because it's no Authority Aryan
I can't believe it's actually happening
They are going to submit to the Tarrant nothing against women and every psychological study
Most women within minutes would start fighting for the enemy
As soon as it
Was clear
They would write out their husbands right out their children help
Secure dumb
I thought it was for the good of the community
Interested
That's why who was the house slave
Rome
Who were the Housewives
He brought women in the house
Get the men out in the field
And that's the system
Wow
That's something else man I don't even know where
That begins
Yeah it's a lot of thoughts and a lot of them are dumb
Alright so
Then it okay okay
Okay we haven't historical record
Up so many cities that were conquered
Have psychological studies from Rome
A lot of armies will show up immediately starts
Women
I'm confused as to whether or not he knows the severe number of underground
Play I don't know resistance movements that were starting to sound
I was like a locomotive maybe they went underground
The clear up Stockholm syndrome is Alex understand that isn't real
It's something that's
Depicted in traumatic movies a lot but in terms of real-life instances of someone exhibiting signs of Stockholm Syndrome
Evenly rare to find a real cat
Yeah what it really is is
The cops are bad and reasonable people are like oh yeah you guys are bad
NM
I mean
You can even find some similarities to the behavior with Adam St
Physically violent
Situations you are Legos parallels
That's not what the
Fiction of Stockholm
Send Revenge
Hit movies perhaps
Invading groups don't kill women when they killed all the men in a particular town but that's not how things have gone
All the women
Sometimes a lot of the time
An exception generally is when he's invading groups would take the women
Property after conquering
Particular group and it wasn't because these women just
Decided it'd be a good idea idea to join the other team
Let's go
Concubine me baby
Also it may be the case that most depictions of persons enslaved inside households in the media are often women
But that's also historically not something that was Universal
Princeton's William Wells Brown and Lewis
Clark are both examples of enslaved persons in the American South were men whose duties were in the house
Both of whom wrote
About their
It's that Alex could learn from
If you'd like
Alex is understanding of history is based almost
Entirely on movies and vague feelings he's gotten about history from media
Literally nothing he's saying is based on reality at all
Feels like if you just kind of assumed
Fiction reality of the same
That's all that's going on here man it is
Grimm
His vision of what
That's that's
Shamefully chauvinistic view of
Yeah you know ND
It's not like
Movies aren't
Entertaining
Take the fact that most movies have been writ
Written by white men over the years is probably ruined a bit of our good historical interpret
I think that might have something to do with his
Ridiculous belief
Could be I could be by now but
Nevermind
Alex has this deep historical knowledge
And I shouldn't be
Poopoo in him so much
Because like I mean he's got a stack of papers
Club just unbelievable covid-19
Just look at this
Look at this
The real Esther you just searched anything I'm saying.
What are the sap
Your normal
Were you really that great in the first place
By Sophie Rosenbaum
This reads like the darkest satire
Written
This is nonsense
But here is Alex
Talking about the editorial a little bit
What are the normal
Were you really that great in the first
By Sophie Rosenbaum
This reads like the darkest satire
Everett
But it's real
Pages of evil
I'm going to read the damn thing on air
Bottom of the hour
That it says we're going to lock you in your house
When we said you can
And it's not about the
Covid
About the Earth
Thanks this is an article by this writer
How much is getting mad at an editorial and pretending it somehow is
The globalist admitting that they don't want anything to go back to normal and it's all about climate covid not even real
Not addressed to Alex
Normal normal
Things to do with this if you read this
Set at Oriel it's not dark satire it's not advocating that we stay in lockdown forever
Hey to this writer expressing that the world goes back to what we're looking at is normal we run the risk of not living as ambitious Lee
We can
A better world is possible in the for things to go back to some idea of normal biking in the way of achieving things
Things that
Or good
From the article
Without normal the path forward is more open
The opportunities perhaps broader
What if there's a whole lot of amazing
Thing that stands to be lost if normal return
What is instead of banking on normalcy we focus
On that one-of-a-kind ability to adapt and evolve
Maybe that's the way forward instead of Simply Red
Reconciling with what wasn't trying to recreate something
That's already had it
It's day
Is an interesting
Position that this author brings up
It's not a unique
Prospective intern
That I've read certainly is lying about
Yeah I know but it's just
Johnson
And it like if he's read it this is embarrassing
Yeah I bring him to be like work
Stuff about it absolutely not
Yeah
City read it on there
I don't know. Probably maybe after I turned it off I told they turned off his episodes
Turned out this episode was
Dislike
That massage neither
The beginning was
Pretty wild
That's astonishing
Because it's not a direct
Attack
You know you're so we're so used to misogyny being directed at women
The present
But two
Create a weird
Fictional like
Adam and Eve story out of all women throughout her
History
Concord psychological studies
I feel like this is not true
This is just not true
Cyclic how would you even think that's like like there a psychologist it's in there on the ground like
Before we hit
Studied it properly
I don't know but it was kind of
Interesting in a
Today
Kind of got interested in like I was just going to continue
Aggressively long
Attracted boring
Stretch of immigrant bashing
In such a way that really really is like
Unacceptable
I'll play a little clip and then
Discuss why I needed
And then we saw Daily Caller reports
Hundreds of illegal
With their children and others and unaccompanied children
The airport
South Texas
Loading on the plane with
No i.d.
Loading onto planes
Bags of cash and envelopes of cash
Disappear
In the god-knows-what
Federal and state law
Lawlessness
It goes on and on and on
The beating up and saying like this
Horrendous thing
About anybody who may be an immigrant
Defective this isn't
Something that is
Is positive
It's not something that even interesting
This is just a
Incitement
Yeah like
When he's talking about these
People who are
Alleged
Tubi
Undocumented folks were being given bags of money and then
The disappear
Interview that's only
We going to make the audience
Suspicious of everybody that they see that they might deem to be possibly an immigrant who might
Have a bag of cash and just disappeared in the middle of America did you responsible as hell
Just be like okay cool you're not see now stopped
Taking forever
It's because that's what he's he's doing
That he's not saying
It's
And it's not something
They can really be
Distinctly discussed outside of review
Yeah it's not something that I have much to bring to
To the table
Other than
F*** this
Amazon accept
Edible we've talked a ton about like specific narratives and things
Betty deploys again
Population
And what has you
This was just like
It just should be turned off
Yeah it's not
It's not even
Like I don't know how else
We should have a
Drop that's just a
Big like
And then it says
Protocols of the elders
And then we just move on by
Kaboom
There was one more thing in this is this is like
Like I was in that place
I think I still needed something else to kick me over the
I turn this off
And this is where I turned
They're waving background check
Foster home
Where they're sent
Coming in no i.d. not with their parents
Years old
Buses in airplane
To be seen again
Not shut down
Open you got massive death massive numbers of dead women and children found by the thousands on the border
Look it up
And it's just
That's not going to be a news item
Not going to be a story
Accompany minors
So Alex is talking about
People at emergency intake centers
Yeah then the FBI waived
Partial part of the background check
They need to be done for people working
He's lying about this story but what he brings up is still an actual issue
And that's where also I feel really
Like I hate him
Cuz this is a real issue agree with him but I'm also not going to disagree
Fully but he is still lying
Right right right
It's true that the FBI's wave fingerprint-based
Background check
People who are being employed to work at emergency intake sites run by the Department of Health and Human Service
That is not a good thing
And I don't support that
But it is not with Alex
This doesn't apply to people who are taking
Can people into foster
It's just for people who work at those sites who are quote
Supervised by federal employees are others who have passed
Fingerprint-based background
Again
Not what I would say is a great idea but it's not what I want to say
Also Alex is claiming that they waived all background checks are these individuals which is not true
They still have to pass public records background check
But they're not using finger
The reason to do this at the
Expedite process which makes some sense but again
I probably prefer that they are on the side of caution
I was really curious about the story so I dug around a little more and I found this story in the Associated Press
U.s. waved FBI checks on staff at growing
19 migrant
That story was from November 2018 under
Trump
Beyond the background checks waiver Trump also reduce need access to mental health professionals or people at the camp
Which was a mess
Even worse
In December 2018 the AP reported on news from an emergency Detention Center in Florida called Homestead
The staff
Being screened for
For child abuse and neglect
The miami-based emerge
The Township's
Alex wasn't mad about any of these things because Trump
Administration was doing it and there's no ability to score points
He doesn't care about the well-being of immigrants and when it's a Democrat president
In charge he just uses the mismanagement of emigration as a
Propped
Enemies
10 prompt as one mistreating
These people Alex isn't okay with it
You support
And and I I don't want
Bring these cases really simple
Census APA
Of trump
And his administration
You can do this as a what about
I absolutely don't want to do that
The score points on Allen there's no point in stopping my frustration with
Like this is a problem and it's
Bright
It's not something that is okay now because
Biden's and truck we need better Solutions
Still monster
Yes and the FBI background-check thing
The aspect of it
I understand the explanation
It's being given I'm not sure that explanation is except
Right
I don't know
But I would be
I've have that
Exact same response
In Trump's instant and now
Yeah and it's
Just defensive
Does he Alex spend half-an-hour demonizing immigrants
In such a way
To potentially put people in danger
And then to use
Them
Mismanagement of immigration
Intake centers like this
Well a prop for him to use
Do attack
Democrats absolutely don't care what
Face or what
Party affiliation you have
If I am anywhere near those people I was screaming they will bark
This is the best you
F*****'-a
This is what your
Going to do
And so you know I just got kind of
Set up and I turned it off
As I I thought like there's probably more interesting stuff to talk about we've heard him talk about this kind of
A lot
That's very
Kind of worn out territory for Alex elderly
So there is some news
Thankfully Alex
The big Bombshells on 31st
Working on the weekend like usual down in the deep end like usual
While we're in the center of the Zeitgeist I barely
The slit in my chair here
Explosive
And so important
Big bombshell
Exclusive
Bombshell
So exclusive so I assume
It when he says so exclusive
I put this story at
Between 1 and 6 years old
No it's current
Okay
I can tell you I've talked to the highest levels of the media food chain about
Photographer
Situation of also talked
Just good personal longtime friend and confidant
Rodger Stone
Iowa
Course he did it
What's going on with the whole
Take over
Coming up
Second
Today
And yet he still getting all the
Hotels together
This is weird
Yeah Rodger Stone coming on to talk about a sex-trafficking incident he's definitely never engaged
Is it in his life before it broke this weekend that the justice department began investigating representative Matt gaetz
Ability that he engaged in a sexual relationship
The seventeen-year-old girl and possibly get paid
Travel are paid to travel
With her which would possibly cons
Institutes extra
Gates claims that this is part of an elaborate plan to extort him and as far as I'm concerned I hate Matt gaetz a real piece of political
Pickled s***
See more about this investigation before I can
Come to any conclusions on the matter
The claimed actions are too severe and I don't want to do a disservice to the Elijah
Crime by using an accusation
To score points
Gets politician I don't like total
According to the New York Times this investigation began under the Trump
From the left
Haiti state
It said that this has to do with a Florida politician who had been an ally of Gates's named Joel Greenberg was he former
Tax collector of Seminole County
These guys currently facing charges quote
Including sex trafficking of a child and financially supporting people Linux
Intersexed at least one of whom was an underage girl
We will see what happens with this is more information comes out but even if he's telling the truth
This is all part of it
Extortion plot against him back gate is still a pile of garbage
Also like if it is
An elaborate plan I really hope that whoever is
Doing this
Extortion against him is
Are you with the things that I don't want is neither of these things
Things to
Get prosecuted with whatever crime is handled here
Urban crime is
The problem something is up and
I don't need an X
Extra layer of crime to hate the s*** out of Matt gaetz
If he's guilty of a crime
Then I hope he's prosecuted and taken care of
But I'm going to hate him either way.
I will see
Also Rodger might not be the best source of information for Alex on this one since he's been photographed at Mar-A-Lago with gate
And Joel Greenberg
According to the times websites run by Rogers Associates had published articles favorable about Greenberg
Tax collector shocking Sue's a mess
Shocking
But we'll see
We lost Rush Limbaugh not too long ago
We had another tragedy befall the right-wing
How much he died
A great guy
Great Patriot great talk show host Great America
Really
The remedy, to Global us we got that
Yikes
Doesn't eulogizing much got this message and lettie's Dad we shan't be I was more like him
Big Bear
Although I think
Maybe our problem is the FBI is a lot like
Alex has his big narratives on the steps
Is that a lot of the prosecution's again
People who broke into
The capital of Storm 2 everywhere
Years ago though the right-wing is moved on from that we're talking about culture wars stuff Dan we don't need to worry about that cuz that
Years ago around and mop it up a little bit
Executions are falling apart and there's a Politico article that Alex can't seem to find
That goes over the
I mean we are witnessing
Historic times
Article about the case falling apart
Infed shocked
They're going to have to drop all the cases
But I asked you what the Politico article is linked to that I forgot to
Tell you about that
Child
Give me that Politico article that
They're going to have to knock
Gel X
These people in the left totally pan
If I can't
Find that down by stacking
I just had it
People aren't
Panicking
This political article does talk about how it might be a bad look for you know Biden's age
Ministration to end up
Having to not process
Secutor give plebeyos to a lot of the people who
Work the Insiders they weren't the people who were
You know actually planning violence
So weird
I understand that
And I I think that
You know in terms of reality that kind of makes sense
Somebody who isn't in favor of
Incarceration
I do understand that and I kind of don't
It would be
In
Societies greater interest
To lock up everybody
Who went into the capital
In the same way that I think that you know drug offenders would be really
I think
I think that there should be
Less people in
Yeah I mean I do ultimate Lee
Functionally it's like
Would you're going after the
F****** mafia-like
Cool you
Arrested a bunch of f****** low-level
Meatheads you are going around looking
For protection money doesn't
Matter
It doesn't do anything you were not doing anything to the people who f****** orcas
Castrated it and inside
Well I don't give a s*** about these people at all
People who you know
Might have just been a long
Bedwetting
I completely understand if I could get him probation or time served or something
If you've been held without bail
Think that
Maybe it'll be unsatisfying to some like
Folks
We were trying to maybe run for office
On retribution
Shore shore shore shore
Put
That doesn't
I mean the people who are like
The people who plan
Did the Southlake
They're not going to get lice
So you planned it
That's the part that said coordinating in like
Stewart Roads as friends
Deep s*** that's what I'm saying is I just don't care about
Because all to all too many of those people are really
Borderline just infected with this
Is terrifying brain virus
That is destroyed them through right-wing propaganda since they were
F****** 6 years old
Alex is trying to pretend that
This is everybody
Even all the Oath Keepers
Since I've had like
Communication
Political articles about everybody
It's mostly about people who are just like
They just walked in
Dance it's trespassing but what are you going to give them
Six months in prison for that Saturday that I think that's a sensible conversation to have in terms of like
What it what gives us the best outcome
Compass Boise
Well I mean is this Society does
Giving somebody who
Epi-no passively
Police stormed the capitol 6
Xbox do anything for the problem
Probably not could make things worse
Yeah it doesn't like to act as a deterrent and now I wish that we would
Treat all
With the same kind of
The problem is not
The treatment
Equal treatment
Beyond
All recognized
Rockets blew up
Hey man don't feel don't care about Elon Musk
But you can't call him a loser cuz he's trying he is a loser
Comments about Elon Musk a little personally
Another SpaceX spaceship prototype explodes during
High altitude flight test
An immediate falling into loser
As usual
Are the people that point
Your fingers
A people that are Dewar's and said that we're the losers now
You are
Sandwiches lump in himself in
With
Elon Musk
Can saying the people who criticized
The doers like me and Elon Musk are the losers
Myself in the same scent
Sentences somebody whose wealth is based entirely upon apartheid.
That's what I want to do people talk about how
Me and Elon Musk are losers just
Because we
Floydada population to make
I'll be told amounts of wealth
I'm in the moment it looks like it was going to go bad for us we ran away to the United States face
No punishment for our crimes whatsoever. Even more wealthy based off of stock manipulate
But no f****** reason I need to be fair like
Like I want you to hang out with Bob Chapman and made all his money on like apartheid told
Lived in Rhodesia
Defending Matt gaetz now
The only way that I would
Never do these things
Is like
Revealing he himself committed across other people that he's built up his Villa
If I Congressman Matt
Son of a big successful billionaire
Wasn't well-spoken wasn't from Constitution didn't have courage wasn't a fighter
I would
Not give a damn about him
Yvonne told she'll I throw it away
Prison
Buddy
Show on
Yeah so just like
His pass
Yeah
It's weird cuz I don't know what that has to do with
You do know
No
It seems like that's the strategy is just
Distract
Read the red sheet over here
Bob Dole
The bowl that is the audience's attention charge over there
Despite the fact that
Of his descriptions
Of
People who
Would drink
Adrenochrome
The only difference so far into
Description between Gates
And everybody else is
Dinar
Next to his name
Hit the son of a billionaire he's in the government he's
But it's also like either weird
Republican Republican
He is weird
A******
So Alex lies a little bit about the allegation
It's one thing for Alex
To take insult again
Elon Musk
Back right
Alex seems to
To be taking this a little personal at sounds right to
Years ago
Enough
Especially when the Democratic Party
And especially I'll reveal for the first time here
Bipoc
Check messages
That 5 acres in a row
So it's on record that you tried to set me up
You tried to
Put on people they got the media will give people money to say anything
They paid people $20,000 to say
I walked around the office and grab the Goldfish out of the
Fish tank
This is a reference to Josh Owens article from 2019 in the New York Times
In the article Josh doesn't allege that Alex ate a goldfish
Version of the claim that Alex uses a strop
Atlanta. Talk about the actual
Complained
Quote Once A co-worker stop by the office
With a pet fish he was taking home to his niece
It's raining circles in a small transparent bag
Balanced upright on a desk
In the conference room he emptied into a garbage
I don't know if Josh is
To claim is accurate or not but it's very
Clear that Alex is making this claim.
The Josh was paid $20,000 by the New York Times
Have to say this about Alec
The reason Alex is using this Pacifica
Eating a goldfish is so he's less likely to get in trouble if Josh Gordon
Set the time Spade him to say what he did
I was condemned pretend you was talking about a different claim made about it but it's very clear this narrative is the one that he's built in response
To Josh's article
If I were Josh Owens I would probably threatened
Sue Alex for
Yeah I don't know
I don't know if Josh Owens is a public figure
I don't know what Alex has no ability to
To demonstrate
The Josh got paid to lie about him
To say anything about him
This seems like slang
Quite frankly
And I think it's
Clearly malicious in a tent
Totally
Absolutely
This person said something I don't like
And so I will say that they were paid to say it how are you sounds malicious
Content
There's no middle ground
Started
Sure
Sure sure
He's he's defending Matt gaetz a little bit like he's about to say what's next are we going to investigate everybody who's did exact
Hollywood
Not that I got but I didn't do it
It's
It's interesting the way that Alex decides to do this
Defense 2
Cuz his defense seems to be like
Hey man cave Flixster party that's what I was thinking it would be
But I made some calls and
He doesn't even know
If he from all parties he was that over the years
And I have the same damn thing
Thousand dollars or I'mma say what you did to me I'm like
But I'm telling you man this is what happens when you're successful in your famous
And it's crap
I'm going to try to get
Leah Pyar restaurant cuz it's not fruit ladies and gentlemen
Suppose we talk about Mikey
Why you keep talking about yourself an ocelot
Also do not sell me on you being a
Tough guy ever again on speed dial
Also I'm a revolutionary is fighting against the American government I think it's an interesting
Looks to be like Matt gaetz go to wild parties and he doesn't remember
Come on you go to the party
You saying it's really strange
I just I think on the one hand
It's a strange defense
Something that
I don't know of anybody
You know it what the reality is about at this point
But that is Eyes Wide Shut masked and then you don't know who's that
It's weird but I think the reason that I'm most
Interested in it is it
Just keeps coming back to
Alex
He keeps bringing himself back up
I have like there's a prop
Foxy that he feels almost
Lingering guilt
Somewhere
I don't know about that
Just weird
It's just weird
Alex
To give Gates summer
Advice
There is
So much more
That we're going to be
Disgusting
We're going to use this to make it about
The clintons
About Bill Gates
And the minute man talks about Bill Gates
And the minute he talks about Epstein
They're going to drop this
Like aha
Renee
I don't know
I don't know if that's
True
I do think
Later on Alex lays out like what he saying is like
Talk about how fun
Yeah
Like Bill Gates run
When's the media you control off
Sure
Starts talking about Bill Gates he'll call off the dogs
Bulbulay
What
I am I am really excited
To see just how fast and how brutal the right-wing
Machine will destroy Gates
The moment
He threatens the grift like
The whenever he was talking to Tucker on that interview and he's like
You know you know how you've done this to its like
Oh oh man you're going to be destroyed
If you think that you're going to get loyalty Gates
You are making the same mistake a lot of you idiots made to end up burning
Like the bridge with Tucker and you'll be left
Hang out with Rodger and Alex
Oh yeah it's going to be brutal and it's going to be fast
Kind of
Convenia to headline the other day
He was like before all this
Came out that he was planning on possibly
Retiring from conch
Nothing interesting is going to happen
In between that article and when he moves
Newsmax
I'm so in the next clip we get Alex
Bestowing the mantle of
The future
Of the GOP on somebody
NTB
Hard-pressed
Surprised to find out that it is not Matt gaetz catherall The Fifth Avenue L
Curious
Marjorie Taylor Greene
The future Republican party voted 75% of the vote
Taco Bell
Hillary's religion and B
Religion
The mark of the beast
Kind of do agree with Alex
XO that she is the future of the GOP
Screeching into the atmosphere upon her Babel Tower as the rest of the world Burns or
Around us to be like a
A good thing
Where is I would say
It's a cautionary statement to say the cheese the future of the GOP I would argue that's that's probably
A correct assessment of the biggest problem many people have ever had
So we get to talk in a little bit more about Miss green and here's Alex
Perfect example
Marjorie Taylor Greene
She's dumb
She's mean
Educated about of the world
Corporate communism Monopoly for themselves
Technocracy to dominator
Stay away from her
Because if they adopt
What she saying when she won by 75 percentage points
The highest record
In ears
Republican
What was she saying
Is the New World Order
I definitely think Alex could be right there Marjorie Taylor Greene was
Infowars
All the times he said that about elected officials this is the first time I'm not going to argue with
Completely making up everything he just said about her life
Action web
First let's remember that use running essentially unopposed
Withdrawn from the race prior to the election
How to claim that you won by a record margin
Because he wants to create the impression that you was just saying it
And that stuff is so pop
Popular
Everyone should adopt
The most popular stuff
Which is info
Or stuff
This is something that he is pulling out of thin air
Green one erase 74.7% 225
Point three person
She didn't win by 75 percentage points is Alex's claiming he just doesn't know the actual details are done
Don't care to be accurate
That's fine though since I can
Think you could be generous and assume he just meant that you one with seven
35%.
Say that's probably close enough and I don't expect him to actually know what he's talkin about every accurate
What's more egregious is him trying to say the previous record for Republican running for congress
Adjustment 69%
Margin or the vote who knows ya
Either it's completely insane
Just in the 2020
10 for the US House
Florida 2nd District kneel-down want to see against independent Tim O'Connor
Play 97.9 to 2.1%
That's a margin of 95.8%
Far higher than Marjorie Taylor greenz margin against a half-finished game of hangman
Green's official margin of victory was 49.4% which is the
The 18th highest margin of Victory among Republican house election winners
Nothing wrong with that left it all out on the field
Alex desperately craves being seen as smart and having a ton of information at his disposal but in order to
Stephanie generally just make s*** up knowing that no one will listening will even care
He'll probably just believe him
Cuz he's a con man
Yeah that would be why I also just because it's Fonda in the 2018 election Republic
Can Tom Graves won the same district seat
The green did
With 76.5% of the vote
Which is more than she got
His opponent received 23.5% of the vote to that means his total vote and his margin of Victory were both hired
Marjorie Taylor greens were
She's actually less popular than the previous Republican who won
The future of the Republic
Looking for
It's what you get when you use in Fort Worth that would happen
We should kill half of the constituents is usually less popular than you might expect
Half of the considering have a problem
The other half use
So we're back to defending my Gates and it just
Does seem to be like
Two parties man come on
Rodger stone is going to have the inside scoop I've got for my angle
My sources that talk
Spell Michelle. Talk to you and yours
Pretty good picture what happened
Extortion
Is he a Playboy was he at the parties wall girls years ago
Truthfully does not remember or doesn't
I know but this is extortion this is a dirty trick
This is not strong
I would say I would say that's a that's a road to conviction
I got drunk and party that was what
I would say
That
I went into this episode
Like the I don't know enough about this case the read the Times article
I read what the people who are the sources
Familiar with the investigation
And we'll wait and see
What comes out of
You don't know
The more I listen to this episode the more I'm like
What are you doing
This is a terrible defense
If this is your damaged
Control X
In the you're doing
I got 250 killed people at those parties look so yeah I don't feel like he's trying to soften the blow
Of something worse because it's Alex like
Operates
Or or what
In the movie bachelor party
Don't don't let Alex anywhere near the
If this happens to her honor
It doesn't matter if he doesn't remember
Your honor I would like to say
What make some calls like
Dwell
Big people
And they said no
Is a Playboy
Doesn't like underage women
Never hit this that he's signaling Ian
Not even know if any of this is true
He doesn't didn't fly with some underage woman that's made of
This is a Shakedown
But the question is do they have
Some woman who can claim
It will she was younger now she's in a 20-something.
You're saying that he might have dated a seventeen-year-old a few years ago
It's not specifically what he's saying
Can you call a character witness
For the price
Execution and tell him to defend
This is a mess man
Hey Alex
We want you
To really defend the s*** out of that gate
How confident are they
Alex
We are going to look prosecutors prosecution
What are behind our back Alex
Look
A seventeen-year-old 3 years ago
Remember
God's name is holy s*** let's see if Rodger can do better
What is the inside
Poo poo
I mean if you had the name the single most effective
Number of the house
In terms of
For the America first
Agenda
You have to be mad gay
Incidental that right here on this show
Only weeks ago I mentioned him
Very realistically as a
Presidential contender
So this is a search and destroy mission
I know Matt gaetz
H-2b a person extraordinary Integra
Was a Playboy coming from you that means a lot Rodger
Met several times and they're very much in love
This is not the matter
Gates that I know this is a
Cheap
Political trick
This is an effort to derail his
His career
Put Matt gaetz his family
Is among the wealthiest families in Florida
Therefore the most
Isn't very realistic
I'm getting so suspicious
The more this goes on
Why are they doing this they don't have to
They don't Their audience does not demand it
Could have legitimately just said this is all b*******
Matt gaetz has he's come out on Tucker and he said that he's being set up see let's move forward
Now let's get to the big news of the day why are they doing I'm not going to
To give this story The
The time that they want me to
Integrity.
Yeah
Wow
That
Broadband
The only thing worse than having Alex defend me in court would be having Rodger defend me and Corey
There's nothing wrong with it I'm Rodger Stone I've done it all looks like
Being like that he's great makes me think this person is knocked
Didn't understand it maybe that's
But the bias of mine
You know not everybody whose beloved by villains
Is a villain themselves score
Sure I mean if I was going to
Put money on it.
I mean I would
Say that the FBI should get
Records
And I would imagine the boat with that New York Times story came out
Rodger still got a text saying
I did it what do I do
That one
It's likely situation
So
Narrative now
McCombs
With Rodger on board
That they're trying to get rid of
Gates because
Skis
The Heir Apparent
To Trump
Sure in the 2024 election Bass
The guy has
Norma's cojones
Usually when you're young and you first get the
Conversate tell you that
Resume super-smart
The alpha male they're scared
Yeah because he has many of the same trait
He's on dacious
He's bold he's a brawler
Take another beating like they took in 2016
So this is kind of what they're doing
I think they see their
Next
The sense that I get
Navigate still weird
Yeah perhaps
But I think it's even more than that
Yeah I think the
They feel an absence of
There
Sort of Idol
Basically
Figurehead
The color lights around and I think that they're feeling
The pressure of the
That there's a crush
That Trump is absent
In terms of being there
He still likes a Hayward Trump supporters he stole the real president they still need somebody
They're all jockeying for position
And I think that
The sense that I get from the conversation they're having cuz I keep bacon wrapped
Are conversations with a bad
And at the sense that I get is that Alex really think
Except Matt gaetz should be the next
Person
And think it's the mantle of the weirdo
Conservative version.
Wow
And so I
I guess he's interpreting this as a preemptive
Attack
On the part of the globalist
If you don't what I don't believe any of that's real and I don't believe that's true but
If Alex
Does believe that
True then it kind of does make sense why he would spend an hour on this story
Still his defenses tarab
Now it's not good
It's not good I mean ultimately his defenses like why can't white men do whatever they want
What can't what can't
Yeah what are you going to judge him
EZ's
Is white neither man come on now
You just let him do what he wants to do you're also he's Rich what are you going to punish him for
What is like
I don't know
Beto
What if it came out today.
Had dated a 17 year old
Allegation
How do you think our to respond
Call Enrico
Yeah and that's but that's the
The point of
Not giving a s*** about whataboutism
We're not going to
Beat that Matt what about it
No there there it's like their bread and butter
No it's just kind of something that can be a little bit
Good funny to imagine
How about you would freak out
Yeah
The reality is
Based on the claims that are being made
Gates
Says that there are tapes that prove his innocence.
Okay should be able to come out
Resolve this whole thing by and I still hate you for all the others
Demand
The tapes
Most importantly
Let's
Ear
We need
To hear the tapes
Somebody in the FBI
Control
Gate was about to have a devastating effect
I think that's exactly right retiring from Congress
The idea that they're presenting now is base
Basically that
There was this guy who by the way
Matt gaetz
Said bye-bye name on Tucker Carlson show
This guy who was a former Justice
Department official is trying to extort
Gate to this family Friday
Sure there's the allegation that they'll come out with if he doesn't pay up or whatever court has those dad
Wearing a wire in order to entrap this person
Because they were just about to nail this this extortionist
Short New York Times got leaked this information about the allegations that were the
Righto Matt gaetz
I don't know if I believe all that it seems like a defense
It's being made and
You know I
If that's okay that should be very easy to clear this up
It should be incredibly
Hey man that person who used to work at the just
Suburban should go to prison
It's not hard
It's like it's like these people don't understand that the that loss if it's
It's to function at all
Is to be applied
Equally
Otherwise it is not law
That is a struggle
Yeah
The New York Times Reporter
Who covered this story
They reached out to Rodger
Send Rodger an email
Part of that is because Rodger was hanging out with
Level with me
Just tell me
Hayride
We have a picture of you and hit him and Greenberg
At Mar-A-Lago
And how say you
Fallout Quest
YouTube
Rodger got me mail and he's got a response
For the guy in this get salad
Really
I actually got
An email from Bob
Michael Schmidt
The
Reporter at the New York Times that wrote
This story today
I'm going to be releasing my response
Because it is quite extraordinary
They don't hold the New York Times to the same
Standards they hold everybody
It is amazing
Associated with
Is
Spend time with
Association
You know I want to hear your response
Yeah you'll get a chance
Touch it up a little bit because
The angrier I get
Alex is like when you get a chance
Could you are gone tomorrow midnight
What river talk about it
I'm awake
Florida
Doesn't that late does not give us know anymore
I go to bed at 4
It's not a bad life
Life
For that
Recluse
What how many pictures with alleged Orkin
Convicted sex
Text traffickers
Can you be in
Before people start certain point you got to let that go
The congregate at Mar-A-Lago
You know if you go there there's probably a picture of you with a perm
Probably another thing we should put a red flag up about
What I mean like it's nothing
You know you go to you go to MOS Eisley Cantina you're going to get a picture taken of you and a Smuggler
That doesn't mean that you're a Smuggler just because you took a picture of you with
Right right like to hang out at the place where Smugglers, and I get that but that's how many pictures do you
To be like
Look I get it one or two and then you see that picture to go who that's not going to look good later on
Then it's just too bad
You sound like
The f****** left
Guilt-by-association all over the place and it's not good
Anyway
On the first episode do we ever
We learned that it was time
Victoria's
Benjamin Netanyahu was the canary in the coal mine
Riddler
5 goddamn years later except I have to tell you it is still time to pray
You're crying you're always appreciate that let us trade
But but let's pray we got a minute have left to break
Lead us in prayer for for congressman
You got to imagine Rodger like
You motherfukers
Son of a
Dario
Are you first off you're telling this b******* about me
Me crying while prayer
Get the f*** out of here I think that's good
For that all there is
Images that I think I think that's fine that's that's the version of the story
The penitent man who
Dry your god king
Naturally
That's what you do when you go overboard with it too
Garments in beating his
Aziz Alex's sort of style
But yeah
I mean luck
It's rude to be like where you lie.
Prayer
On my dumb
Conspiracy theory
Show where we're saying that Matt gaetz
May have dated a seventeen-year-old years ago but who knows he doesn't remember his wild party is
Whatever
I will be mad if you asked me to pray
The day before let alone
5 minutes
On the
Spot
We're going to pray like that
The most articulate but I'll give it a try
My dear Lord
Lotion
You who created both Heaven and Earth yo Yoo-hoo
Stanford Justice and eight
Injustice
Please watch over in the struggle for his freedom
Is a good man he is a Godly Man
Is an innocent man
He is a man of great
Do not let
The left-wing 8
Machine
Destroy me
Talk to destroy General Flynn
Destroy this great
American Patriot
I'm in by the way that's another type of you to come back we're trying to get Splenda right we're back in the morning he's
Okay weird
Just go back to like he was a young operative working with like Nick
Nixon and be like hey
2021 be hanging out with Alex Jones and praying on Arrow
Jewel
Yeah yeah he is a sad piece of s***
This is why I'll just as bad
I don't understand like this isn't something
That like would have more media coverage
Like this seems like
So bizarre Rodger Stone
Praise on Aerosmith
It's like they visit brotherstone still has to be a big bad
Pick me up just
Portray him as this sad
I mean just
Real pathetic
Nonsense man as I say that out loud I think I kind of realize that
Are you to cover something that way
You might run the risk of offending people who are Christian a religious
Like the idea
It's not mocking
Prayer no walking the idea that one is Rodger Stone Tucson Alex Jones Show
It's more than that and I think that tone might not be able to be properly
Yocan Vape
Like if you are
By any stretch
And it hear it too
The intent of the Bible
I would argue that that prayer is
Way more offensive to Christians then any article being like Rodger stone is an a******
Let them do what they did to me you like
Not even God is above the left-right Paradigm is that what we're doing.
Your God is pathetic and shity
Alex's God is above life repaired I mean City Super to the rice
So Alex at the end there was talking about how we want to draft Michael
Planned General Flynn
Run for president
I talked about this a little bit they did him
Not quite on the
What's draft
General Flynn dictated ticket going what do you think
Look I think I made it
Is Claire's I can't
The president runs for the Press
And he has the right to make that decision
And he has the luxury to make it
In his own time
The president doesn't run its
Vital that we have a candidate a man or a woman
Who really understands and supports and
Whitley is committed
Ready in case
Hey Alex you don't suck
Trump pardon
I have loyalty to him for life
Yeah forever got
What forever to have hypothetical
Conversations about anybody else but you have to understand that I will always give up
The Trump is technically still president even if Gates were present
Trump should be
Yep yep
Yep
Becomes all too apparent there
That the way that they're
Conversing at like we're look
Looking for a stand-in
Yeah we need somebody to get it
Dum Dums as excited as Trump did
Back gate to the kind of s******* Who would wear a gas mask
And then get covid
Just don't have any of
Like it
It's very abundantly clear now that nobody but
Trump has the stuff fit
The like
Total
Attributes
That are necessary to pull off a trunk
Campaign
You know
Like Gates isn't going to be able to cuz he doesn't have that image of
Being a successful billionaire
He's an a******
He can't pull off any kind of sexual impropriety
Candle because he's too young and not enough people want to back him
In order to run interference for him
So we're probably going to wind up with Trump is the Republican candidate
So sad and miserable for everybody
So long as the media learn
Any less
From 2016 and 2020
But it's okay Dan if the Democrats pull it
Together and govern effectively there's no way that our right wing
So Alex
Evite's Rodger go and
Who
Very confused
Very very very
Confusing guy get
Generally what they're doing
I can't imagine having any time to prepare
I'm thinking like
This is the defense
Looking to spend
Half of the show
Is
Is bizarre
Have a better defense tomorrow
Yeah that makes the most sense
Halo Roadies allegation
And they're terrible and we're going to look into it and will have more in Rogers not available today he'll be on tomorrow to drive
Rodger could be asleep who knows who cares
It just doesn't matter
Take your time
Alex is also built
Entire story about the everyone whose capital is getting off scot-free
And the leaves are really mad about it is on
Along with his lawyer is going to say you better have a lawyer Fresno
I don't know if his lawyer is going to be helpful
Oh boy
AliExpress
Executor what do you
Think of the Fiasco
Thought they were over-reaching they seem to
Add everything to fit into but the
Just don't say
Support that
I don't know if it was something
Think they had planned because I believe that the
Event was
Funded somehow with antifa
But
I think they
Wanted
Patriots to act up more
Then what happened and then they have continued to try to push a narrative
Set the facts don't fit into
It looks
Two roads his lawyer that he brings along takes antifa paid to do something
Yeah yeah yeah yeah you know I think
I think the past
Few years
I have really taken a lot of Shine off of
The legal minds of our
His lawyer seems insane
Yeah
Most lawyers now starting to sound a lot more and more thing
Geminiman Stewart Alex
They just talk about how like
Everybody on the right is good
That's where all Angels over here and everybody on the left drinks adrenochrome and
It's not really all that interesting or or
Dunno doesn't bring much
Stuart does have a prediction
That was got put on the record
Alright I'll we're looking at the summer of Rage
Their speeding your timetable
That's why it's important for us to understand what's coming
You should expect
Benedictine
A couple of dollar from the world currency and kill the dollar this summer
What you do have to do to become squall
This week
We got you nice warm strong
That means food and fuel
Mission
Clean water the ability to
Self-sustaining you can resist
The compulsory
Taking of the vaccine
Normally eat
I totally agree with you
So yeah the dollar is going to be the
Destroy this summer
Look for that
Everybody who believe that
Take your stuff
And just go into the woods
Create a splinter Society
For if you believe that
Take the dollar
Still has some value
Pay your internet bill
Download an episode of Alex Jones
Songs from last year saying this year will be the summer of Rage
Couple years back when he did it in the every year
Actor like
Years and years in the past USA tomorrow they're going to devalue the Dollar well
Conveniently selling gold help
It helps to sell gold
Outrageous
Oh no
This summer now man I'm really worried
Yeah I'm really worried so Stewart's whole big thing is that the government is going to starve
That's his that's his new thing
But he's pushing pretty hard
It's going to be tough to win votes on a platform of star very one
But we'll see how they pull it off Dan
Counterpoint
Yep here's a great here's a great electoral strategy
Hey you Miss food. Food
What's the word Estrella
Trying to
Triggering people's minds
Anyway
Come to the end of the sentence
It's weird cuz
I think
Pink eye
Obviously I'm more
Interested in
Non present day hours
Alex Jones
Uninteresting person
But this
This defensive gate
Really did
Interest me in as much as like
I hate Matt gaetz
I'm not interested in piling on him to or until we know more
Naturally
Alex
His defense makes me suspect
It really makes me think that Alex knows something
That we don't
And it's bad and it's real
That's what it makes me think that any other impression we don't know that could just be
Tony jerk
Trying to protect your own
Kind of thing
No maybe there's something
And I would say that if this is his knee jerk reaction that's probably just as Illuminating as if he does
Know something that we don't know because his me jerk reaction is like
Come on sexual assault
You know like it
It's kind of a weirdo
Conservative exactly it is that basic
Turner Field
We know how you're going to react
Back to just about every
Yeah yeah it doesn't
It doesn't it was not an enjoyable
Bit of time to live
Listen to this year
Confusing
I don't know who will check back in
We'll see how things
Are going of course saying
Until then
Free website website its knowledge right.com
We're on Facebook
We are visiting your dad was drive-through please find a local charity or Bellefontaine area to help out people doing God's work
Emilio Emilio on dzx
Clark I'm Daryl rundus
Apple
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color