Important
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge
Knowledge fight
What's fight.com
Alex
Joe
Indeed we are
Yessir
My bright spots and a realization that
I've been I've been listening to a fair amount of some podcast
Just for entertainment for sure
Pressing high-stress week or so and I realized
One of them's that are really gravitate towards
There's a through-line through a lot of them
Matt is Matt Gourley
I think so much
How to do podcast
Underrated
Wait
To my listening to Alex Jones all the time
It really feels like that's like a balm that I can I can put on my man
Glue guy
He's like a Phil Hartman he's got that kind of like straight man energy
He's also incredibly hilarious
Really really going to exploit my platform
So now I'll be like this week
Girly girly
I like at work
Let's abused our privileges
Devil
Brights
Play spino the inversion table
The devil break
That's a follow-up to
To Bright Spot
Yeah as unprecedented first we're going to go in chronological order
If you were called then
While back
I told you about a pair that
Delicious
I got two pairs for you never run by the way
Where I'm going to join us but my partner's mom
Both decided that
We got to do something for this so they ordered me a
Rite Aid they realize how to do something about your love upstairs
They had it they were inspired into action
So they ordered me
Burger place
That has grape
To the point where I am
I can't eat it
Looks too much like the tart pan
I don't know what to do with this pair
I mean it's going to be
And then you'll recall that I said something about how my brain was functioning
And black dragon Queen Christy sent me any
Incredibly kind
Always
That is great
Double bright spot
Things are looking real bright
I may have another bright spot
Drupal Brightspot
I am I really got into today's episode
You did you know it's it's an Easter miracle
Just I found something
Was not expecting Alex to be at all like kind of like a like a
Talk about it is interesting
And we will get that a business on all that before to Jordan was take them over to say thank you
The first scrotum the strong
Melissa
Thank you very much Melissa
I remember when I first realized
But Missy was short for Melissa
So weird day
Anyways sorry Melissa
Next track with Tyler thank you so much and I apologize
Very much there are a surprising number of competition Rodeo
Kathleen
Pretty quick
I'm a pretty quick couple of special things going on here
Over the weekend
NRA couple birthdays
It's like to give a little shout-out to probably 3
First Alexander reach that wanted to wish Iris a happy birthday
Happy birthday Irish happy birthday Irish
Isn't this is coming out probably after your birthday weekend
Cat
Birthday month
How do you write how do you not wish Pleiades
Cuz they're the light from Blue 86 several 100,000 years to get to
Well
It just got here
Happy birthday
So Jordan today we're going to be going over April 1st
Through third 20
I really sped up to the homeless
This is Thursday and Friday of last week
And then Saturday I'll expect around 1 at the studio and recorded
Special thing
Sure why not
Once we get going you'll understand why I had to cover that temperature
The first years out of context drops
Today Show
The devil a cool man he's not what gives you the hot cheerleaders in the
And the party in the fun
Actually I thought that was specifically
Try and empty
Picture and he's the one who
Foregoing
Pacific things yep that's always been my tracks
Almost entirely like hey that hot girl you got to avoid her phone in the party at
Terrified I'll do the phone of the partying Jesus hate that
My man
I want to I want to preface this really quick
Alright
This April 1st episode
It was an April Fool's episode
I would admire the hell I was
There's a number of things that go on that you could interpret as being like
Fedora but it's not
Like this this this could be an April Fool's gag
Blast freezer
Particular subject
That robbed
The Rustic root
Pestering me about
Last night and today
Reddit
And it is the Smoking Gun of smoking guns of Smoking Gun
Is it Green Eggs and Ham
Next hour I'm going to cover this big story
Right
I don't do that
Give you just pulled out the big news
I don't have some fanfare
Like a 20th Century Fox intro
British newsreel
People don't
Care to just
Becomes part of the background
Ambient noise
They actually
Condition
To the tyranny of evil
You know I almost did just go off
Are for a month
Infowars
And then if I came back
We might be able to save the
I hate you so much
See what I mean April Fools
That should have ended with should I be saying any of this perhaps
I have the gun the smoking guns and Smokin Guns
Disappear for awhile
That's an interesting idea
Disappearing like he's going to the rafters.
If you love something let it go
Just face paint Crow Facebook
A brutal Galaxy
Bruce Lee's grandson
So he doesn't
He doesn't disappear from
But he does have he does do what I would say is the next best thing
What am I told you
I have
Document
From John Haupt
They plan the whole attack
Planned
SARS attack
Planned the Ebola attack planned
Becoming 19 attack
Plan through vaccine
The brain damage you and give you all timers and sterilize you
And then how they're even going to blame the politicians
Now they even set up President Trump
To do it
I would be
Smoking Gun
I'm imagining
In your hand
Mail it to me
I'm not going to cover
I'm going to put together
And I'm going to come in here Saturday and I'm going to take
For 1 hour
2 p.m. central Lee should have it ready
After hour until I go live Sunday
Easter
4 p.m. Central Standard Time as I always
What is it that's amazing I've got to go get gun through
Saturday should I can't handle that type of relationship
I'm sorry that leave for me Isaac
Wow
That is
Ridiculous
You can come on Saturday that kind of
Kind of presentation is
If you're listening in the audience you have to ask yourself
Why
What kind of fuel persons to lose
The organisation be like we have proof of ever
Everything that is going on in there trying to kill everybody we're going to wait two days
Oceans do weight with it with information that they're not
We got some bobtail s*** about something that LOL
Absolutely not the document that Alex is talking about is a 20-17 scenario exercise called the sparse
Pandemic 2025 to 2028 Camaro for Public Health
Wrist Communicator that sounds like the Smoking Gun
This is essentially very similar in structure to the Rockefeller one Alex erroneously
Recalls operation locks
In that beat Johns Hopkins exercise began with the selection of two important
Variables like
I could dictate what challenges could arise
In a possible future
He is Alex real or is Alex not real
In this exercise the two variables work with varying degrees of access to information technology
Levels of fragmentation among social political religious ideological and cultural
Where is the Rockefeller document explored all four of the possible Futures that were based on the variables they chose
This document focuses instead on just the one
Is that the most challenging terms of medical communication
Okay so there are
More
Positive simulations that could happen with those
Two variables
Creating a matrix
Sephora scenarios
This paper is entirely about the worst possible scenario
What the other ones are really know what they are the real bummer of a scenario.
It's a scenario that is for an exercise for medical communicator
Challenges or they decided Woodway
Most interesting challenges
Is the one that they use
Excellent sorry I just wanted to talk
This was the possible future that they called
The echo chamber
Which represented the scenario where there was widespread access to information technology and quote
Isolated and
Highly fragmented
2 communities
Reading over this document it's really fascinating how there are a number of similarities
The real world in the scenario that was laid out in this exercise
The real world novel coronavirus was called sars-cov 2
Where is the scenario illnesses called spars Co
Ultimately these similarities are all things that make sense
Given that the possible future was laid out by public health experts who would be trying to make as realistic
Scenario is possible
So participants
Explore the communication challenges that could arrive
In the event of a problem
Look Health Emergency
In a world where everyone is online
And a large segment of the population lived in a slightly
Different reality from each other
One of the problems that we keep running into it these scenarios like this document in the Rockefeller one
Are there well-written and engaging
They contained a ton of details
Flush out the world they're trying to depict it seem like more of a prediction than they intend to be
Is John's Hopkins an area relies on a template laid out by Jay Ogilvy and Peter Schwartz
Send their 2004 paper
Titled plotting your scenarios published by the global business
In this paper Ogilvy and Schwartz try to help businesses and organizations understand how to best structure a scenario-based
Exercise
In order to maximize its
Impact in terms of
Of the participants
Being able to learn about how to deal with new circumstances and manage
Exchange
Okay so these guys are done
Yes
Yeah that's what these guys do
The strategy of using a scenario made
Is explained in this paper
This is what both of Johns Hopkins and Rockefeller exercises used
Two key factors Lathan could affect
The possible Futures they wanted
Explore then that list is whittled down to two Central Factor
These factors are plotted on a matrix
Which could go in one of two directions
And that creates
Four distinct combinations of factors
Floor right
An example that's given in this paper is about looking at possible futures
For education
Where they choose to use
Hierarchy versus participation
And inclusion versus X clusion
The two main actresses that were the most relevant to their exploration
This created for scenario
Hierarchical and inclusive
Hierarchical
Exclusive
Participatory and inclusive
And participatory and exclusive
Each of these possible realities looks vastly different from the others
So it's not too hard to jump from there to scenario building
And creating evocative narrative
The characterize each of these so participants could more easily relate
Do the challenges that eat
Possible
Future Wicked
That's exactly what Ogilvy and Schwartz discussing their introduction
Listen to this
To be in effect
To planning tool scenario should be written in the form of absorbing convincing stories that describe a broad range of alternative futures
Relevant to an organization
Success
Copley construct
Did Bolivar
Bull plot
Help managers to become deeply involved in the scenarios and perhaps gain do understanding of how their organization
Can manage change as a result of this
Experience
The more involved managers get with scenarios the more likely it becomes
They will recognize their importance
Less obvious implication
Moreover scenarios with engrossing plots
Could be swiftly communicated throughout the organ
Innovation and will be more easily resemble remembered by decision-makers
At all levels of an
And if the CBC rolls in 18 or higher
Ogilvy and Schwartz are business Consulting
Send this technique
Using scenario-based exercises is a very common one above organizations that want to explore how prepared they are
Two-Face potential challenges that could up come up
Expectedly or unexpected
These scenarios work better if they're written as compelling and engrossing stories and as we've learned
Alex has an incredibly hard time differentiating between reality and fiction
Think about the problem
These are these guys they recommend that people quote
Invent catchy names for the scenarios
Saying quote
When your managers feel the hot breath
The crisis
They should be able to recall the appropriate scenario by name
Dan if you recall
IFC
Suggested to sign in.
Here's the problem though
I have also
Suggested they go outside of scientists
For naming
Yeah but then Alex also talked about how like THX
It's World 138 or whatever Israel
That's not a problem
What's the weather this week
Well this one is called the echo chamber
Okay I'll call it
The shity room fell right you won't forget the shity room now that's true that might work
This technique though creating these names that you remember it
It's a good strategy for scenario-based planning but
The flip side like you have pointed out is that
Names could be
Explain Mary usually
Step is a perfect example of that
Jessica catches Mario name
Which is apparently so catchy that Alex has built a gigantic
Conspiracy around it now I rename it bummertown
You remember it
To nobody's like
Oh they're using bummertown to defeat the bicycle
The bummertown scenario all over again the bottom line here is that this document is none of the things Alex
Claims that it is
Also is 89 pages long so there's no way I believe for a second that Alex's Reddit
He talked a little bit more about it here although he said he was going to wait until Saturday
Talk about it
Right right right
Basically anyone taking exact same for all designer the same thing
He's going to have neurological disorders within one year
Most of the people taking the vaccine will be dead within 10
That is not
In the options
That would be very serious thing for Johns Hopkins
Enterally CR2032
Depicted in the exercise
Some of the outbreak begins in 2025
Houses making s*** up because he knows no one's going to read it and he's got all the elements there that he needs to lie about it
Indian rages it's
Your gold deep
Just rif
Every now and again I like to point out when Alex
This makes it abundantly
Play clear that he thinks that he's fighting literal demon sure because
Is everyone needs
To keep that in
Recalled that this man
Right you know who authored this report it wasn't the center of Public Health. To Johns Hopkins
For the Morningstar you bet he's a master of Public Health but actually got a degree honorary
Well
Obviously this is not a human intelligence running this
After that
Generals.
Intelligence agencies
Because everybody knows
Everybody knows fake low-res a flying saucer
I'm talking about interdimensional
Hell-bent to destroy us
Naturally
And it's not
Fallen Angel
Operation
Alright honestly might have more respect for low revs
Pictures of Alex
Yeah I would say that I am Orkin
Convinced by the Loch Ness Monster
Picture photo
Interdimensional beings are
Controlling
The plan that's not even happening
So Alex lies a little bit more about this topic
Ken's report
Hell on Earth is going to be released
Total collapse
Giant John Haupt
Implants
That our operation
John Hopkins runs the whole thing
Shopkins
All spelled out
Says here just like I surmise by 2030
You did not surmise population is
Dead or living dead
Totally
And then we're going to have to
Take care of people
When did the good people to survive
Will have to join the globalist in Exterminating
Who's left
Because I'm out of control
Whoa
Alex is making that up
Bicknell
Big pass on that one kind of
The passage that
Guess most
Closely resembles what he's talking about
Quote while the federal government appeared to have appropriately addressed concerns about the acute side effects of corvax
That's the thumbs up
Esparza's Skarsgard
Help 9
Largely unknown
Nearing the end of 2027 reports of new neurological symptoms began to emerge
After showing no adverse side effects were nearly a year several vaccine recipient slowly began to experience symptoms
Such as a blurry vision headaches
Head numbness in there
Extremities
Due to the small number of these cases the significance of their association with korvax was never determined
Have a writing in 20-30 longitudinal studies initiated by the NIH of the beginning of the vaccination program
Have not reached the next round of data
The formal analysis of these symptoms has not yet
Been conducted
Furthermore these cases arose from the initial cohort of vaccine recipients
Those in high-risk population
Including those of underlying health conditions
Making it increasingly difficult to determine
The extent to which these symptoms are associated with that
Exclamation yassi that's good dungeon master
But I would
Expect Alex
Westwood Arvada.
You haven't been vaccinated will be forced to kill the rest of everybody
Do you imagine scenario involves a small number of possible unforeseen side-effects in was actually and that's
Deployed to fight
We just heard John Hopkins
It's a complete picture that is just created out of thin air from his imagination
The story that he's telling
Literally has no can
Into the primary source that he's pretending to cover
I can't wait until we get to Saturday
They had days and it's one of the most in common
Play Forever that you heard I'm going to get to this Saturday
Handle this Saturday but I'm like alright alright we'll see you then
Alright I'm going to stretch
Your knuckles a little bit you do a little right here we go
Can I got to say
I don't know
Who here
He's got for this
This Saturday show
It's him Rob do and some dude named Mike
I don't know who this Mike dude is
But he is a weirdo
Holy shiitake
Not to be believed
Alright so anyway Alex
Infinite resources and is it a million years old
Satan's interested in an information
Probably trip
In the 40 days and 40 nights that Satan tempted Jesus in the desert that most of what they talked about was Alex
Well window when
Dude do you know what we're going to have eventually have to
To deal with
Arcadecloud got like all the Angels you know turn against God or whatever it was
Was information Warfare
Convince them that their freedom was stolen by an infinite creator
Who's mostly about vaccine
Anyway Alex is fighting cancer
The operational shut
Of the planet
As we know it
And the decision has been made
The Earth is to be completely sacrificed in the
Main mission they say
Used to destroy the Earth
And it only out of that metamorphosis
Creature emerged
That's what they've been
Old
Universal
Cold it is a ethos it is a religion
They rebelled against God
And so I really don't even know Alexa
Did not
Think I'm going to have to just
Andis over to somebody else
This stuff too big
If people don't know about this
I can't believe
This man
Set alarm
That didn't seem
Oh I had a
The space baby from 2001 Space Odyssey
Is out there
It's going to grow into a thing
Stuff
Ensure
The go Bowser trying to give birth to Satan to walk on rice
Right
Right now that's a mean that's a real bummer
I caught a kind understand wanting to go to the woods
The best of times I want to go to
What would be a bad place
Because Satan's all about the
The fire is on fire
You want more like a black top
Sure move into a park
Great Glass to make
Greeley Great Windows
This could be a good thing
Document that he's not going to cover until Saturday
And they all know what's bull
It's just every
Part of it is a lie
And you're wearing the death
You're wearing the
Admit in the John Hopkins report
They gets an added bonus
Pneumonia
Of the Mask we're just going to really increase their deaths toll
DIY work mask
Ask does not appear once when they were John Hopkins archetypes
In the scenario bacterial pneumonia is a condition that appears to
To be connected to the invented virus sparse
But Alex is completely making up everything you say
Document wow pretty great
That's pretty great
I do like whenever you
You can toss in something that isn't even mentioned
That's always good
So
Who's fighting the devil
Alex's
Bob covered himself in the armor of God
That means
Talking about the bike
And
No this is Thursday
Maundy Thursday
No idea
I can't remember what the there's stairs
Good Friday right
Palm Thursday
Palm Saturday Wednesday but that's different
So don't worry about it where you don't know the week
I forgot
Anyway Alex also has forgotten
Some things about revelation
Play the Bible
No flesh would be spared less God
No flash
Which would have been
None
It says the rich men will sit under the mount
Mattresses under the mountains
Beating themselves in the head
So angry that they
Surfside
SelecTrucks right
Chosen your side
Yeah I like Trump right
Chance
Weird
Delicious
So if the Bible did people would live under mountains thing about the elite
Globalist Ivan underground bases
Hear it
Yeah
Unfortunately Alex is leaving at a very critical part of the verse that he's poorly reference
This is from revelation
6 vs 50
15 quote
Then the kings of the Earth
The princes the generals the rich the mighty
And everyone else
Both slave and free hidden caves in among the rocks
Accident Mountain everybody hit
It wasn't just the rich people it was a whole plethora
Evoke
It's pretty much everyone trying to hide from the opening of the 60s
I like much like Alex just writes fanfiction about the nefarious documentary covers as
He does the same thing with the Bible
Even like a religious
Everything is just a prop
Yeah I forgot to use
Want to know
If you were fighting the devil that is
Would be your best
His knowledge of the Bible
Sure I seen that in the various
Norris movies
Yes
Indeed we have so Rodger is coming in
Again
Great which we saw on our last episode
Interesting. I got really weirded out by this
Rodger Stone
Delete a national movement to run for president order support Trump
Regardless
Flint
I just need to
We should draft Meme here on the show
We can't wait for Trump
We can't wait for this Santa's
We need General Flynn who is a good man in a patriot or sales going on
We need him to do this out Rogers a dental appointment
Bauer
Episode the conversation was about trying to draft
Twin or Gates
Sure
And Alex is just
Pretending with that wasn't a conversation
No we never defended that guy he's a real Criminal
Dial mean not to his credit
But Rodger is still like
He's innocent he's being set up
Good Rodger move boy has a deflated
Quickly spent over an hour on the last episode
Love you just like to party
We had opposed
Be Breezy got this one and we decided you guys
Did not commit any crimes.
Someone got bad kept going the way it look like
We're going to go in
I can walk away from this at this point
Going to go to buy
So I got the sense that like
Rogers f****** with Alex a little bit which I
Second kind of enjoy
Dustin may
Play a secret
It's on a class letter
My email doesn't work anymore
Gmail block
Bono's really is
The full weight of the government works against
What's the country to imploded
Alright
Email doesn't work
Rochester
I don't know why Outlook isn't working right now
Occam's razor tells me Rodger is f****** with Alex
Do we get another headline
Such a quote
Refuse to wear covid
Clearwater Florida
Even a conservative City
Star teaching
Critical role
Naturally there's a story about Clearwater High School and honestly if I were to use a different word than real
Educate no manual
Kingsbury easy
Students who do not wear a mask when it is required to refuse to
To do so should first be re-educated
If after the re-education occurs they do not
Apply for student
Administrator
Should be contact should be
If not done so if behavior is not change
I'm in this whole thing goes away
The word re-education is up in the means a lot of different things in different
Context
For Alex the word means, he's taking kids to
The camp to do nothing for
Clockwork Orange
In this context
It's really clear that what they mean is that if a student is refusing to wear a mask they should be given a chance to better understand why I'm asking him for
Boarding school room settings
Before any kind of disciplinary actions even
Considered
This is essentially what the kids get a warning
The right-wing blogs are covering the store use this quote but seem to leave off what comes immediately after it in the school's plan
For the new Academic Year
Not wearing a mask when
It's required is not a disciplinary matter but rather a health and safety
Concern
Administrators will contact the parent or Guardian for
Support if the refusal continues the principal must
Contact the area superintendent
Option
Which include administrative placement into one of the other learning option
Displacement is a non-displaced replacement and is based on the health and safety needs of all students and staff
Do the same document literally says that students who refuse to wear masks
I won't get in trouble
And if it's something that can't be resolved
Then accommodation will be made to allow them to
Continue to go to class remotely
That seems like going above and beyond to cater to people who refuse to wear masks in public gathering settings
Re-education so this is somehow about critical race Theory or something
And is really well-thought-out
And kind of consider it and perhaps overly sensitive you know
But it is better than my plan of if a kid decides not to wear masks you go to his house and scream and his parents faces
Until I leave you alone forever
Comfort a codified into a rule
Better that I wouldn't use the word
Give Less meat for our
Rodger comes on after the dentist
Do not talk about my Gates
It's much much
The day before
Surprise eggs General Flynn to announce that he's running
President did Rodger trying to explain to Alex that there's a game they need to play
Rodger saying that if they're going to do this
The first thing they need to do is gather massive amounts of data about the people who would support Flynn
And then they need to somehow get around all the social media bands with all this s*** heads like Alex have
That limit their reach
Right
It's a farce of an interview and it seems pretty clear to me that there's going to be
Free summertime to coming down the line
Try to replace Trump
But Flynn has the figurehead of the Infowars Idol cult
Rogers trying to subtly and plant the idea that
When is like Eisenhower
He's a military hero of the people need to coerce
Into running for office because it's his duty to the country
Rodger seems to realize that the only thing that's going to work for someone like Slender the fully
We realize storyline
Porsche the campaign
And it's character work so that kind of Arc
Regardless of how disconnect
Reality it is
It's the same thing they did was drop pretending that he was a successful businessman would never had any interest in politics who won the presidency on his first try
Thrive
When compared to reality
Bulshit but it's
Compelling storyline for the bass to enjoy
Flynn being a
Candidate whatever similar complete bulshit narrative
If it were to get off the ground but could be effect
I am wild out wild it out by the idea that
That anyone would want
Anyone Who Had
Any command during the Iraq War
That's weird also pledged Allegiance McEwen.
Immediately disqualifying like I don't even care what your politics are
You were involved with commanding in the Iraq War you are already a
Failure before you even
Began you should maybe take a seat you should go away
So Rodger wants
The build-up to the subtly and softly
Where is Alex's a little bit list
They're just going back
Conforth about how Flynn needs to go on the attack immediately that's what Alex
Rodger comes back with
Helen finally Alex's just had enough
Here's the deal got to do it
He knows it
And
And so he's going to run for president I drafting him
The American people
Quiet event to 10,000 people here 10,000 people there 1,000 there
Quietly has that are packed out
Need to tell him you're doing it and I'm not being
They want you and I in jail because they know we'd
Felt like fire
What's wrong
They know that we're not afraid they know we got lightning in a bottle and they know that
Lightning don't strike the same place
That's how
We'll invite guys.
Wait what
Obviously I could sell off the sunset right now it's almost ready to buy me off like that I could Snap My Fingers
Billion dollars
But I'm not selling Humanity out
He needs to listen to you he needs to announce soon
Alex is sick of the bulshit many watts of the hero figure 2
I got wrecked
It turns out without his
Indubitable platform
Trump s*** talk
Walking doesn't work yet. We all that good as the center folk exact
Alex Jones
Need to be someone else's hype man
Totally that
That person I'm hyping is absent now.
I'm really flailing
Mead
Dad
You are one
Hundred percent correct step that is exactly what's going on
Flipaclip means nothing
But I just thought it was kind of interesting to hear Alex describe
The plot of Romeo and Juliet
I think he'd get some of the Beats right okay
I'm really really interested in that I'm going to be honest this is the first time in a while I've been like
I'm going to be on the edge of my
Literature recap
Reading a
William Shakespeare
Play
Read before you know you turn the page and Romeo and Juliet
Tell me you read their parents
Problem
By the end of
Commit suicide
You know the play
Starrett
Well
I mean I mean he's not wrong
Exist
Venerated play for hundreds of years because of that plot synopsis
Skeleton is there
There's a ride out of the kill themselves to parents
Read before
It does not sound like you've read it before Easter
Map of the Leonardo DiCaprio version and then woke up at
You're one of these literature major types though like I'm from the streets right
Surely there's more to it
I disagree
Okay well that's fair
That's fair
Yuca
Could cut out a lot of those dogs a classic the classic tale of people meeting
My family is being mean
It has it does have an arc
Yeah so Alex cares about the theater cares about classic
Literature
Money
You don't know why I feel so upset
I've never cared about money
I would make enough money to fund the operation Atlanta
But now I can tell you going to the Future
You'll be able to Stave this off a little bit longer but not longer if you do that
This is a world civilization ending event
Yeah they are talking about
Everyone vaccinated is going to have Alzheimer's including children
Box
I knew this was all coming
This is scarier than my film endgame
And they roped
Oh God do they get royalties for that
Don't even know what to do with this
Displeased
God
Babies
Wwoof
Weird God
Dear God
So just a quick fact check there's literally nothing in the Johns Hopkins report about anything close to what Alex is making up here
The robots cleaning up their body stuff is just from Soylent Green
Enjoy
The word Alzheimer's doesn't even appear in the document
Public health communication challenges that could come up in the event of a disease outbreak
Comically stupid for Alex if there's a chapter on how everyone's going to be dead robots
Clean up our court
So made up
Really weird flourish for them to do
Just be like oh and also the vaccine
Gene causes Alzheimer's
That's a clause
Also Alex loves money
You should be
Swimming in a Scrooge McDuck
Dial yeah the April 1st show Alex interviews James O'Keefe about some footage apparently God of Emma
In poor condition
This falls under the heading of a subject I care about and it's a political issue that
Memes
It's something people should be paying attention to
But I do not trust the person delivering this message
Fuchai is act
Singing good faith
Oh no I don't
I reserve the right to ignore anything James O'Keefe
Also f*** him
Let's move on
April 2nd
Yeah 100%
I could have seen that being an April Fool's episode doubt the way Alex is like
Until Saturday and Eli's a bit about it little touch-and-go on it
Existence
Does Joe has Rodger and Alex
Serta pretend
The conversation didn't
Involve Mac Gates Today Show
So we get to the second
The tone is completely change
Everything is totally different
These headlines
Infowars.com
Structure bill
Includes 20 million to destroy highways
Racist
If you're not aware of this
Choking
Here's some of the headlines
December
Cold
Highway removal in a black neighborhood
One person calls
Acrostic
White House
Singled out
Announcing the highway is all the jobs in
Will be destroyed
This is so evil ladies and gentlemen
We covered this back in the endgame coverage so I don't have to go out too much on the subject
In case Alex is listening
The history of the placement of highways in
Incredibly racist
The fact that he's laughing at the idea and mocking it really only reveals that he has no idea about the history of that subject
No one's calling for all highways to be gone so there can't be business or travel anywhere
The conversation is about how the ways that highways have been constructed in the past often has been done with absolutely no regard for minority
Communities and often to their
There's tons of primary sources Alex could read up on if he's injured
Listed in the devastating impact that practices like Redline
Communities of color in this country in terms of social impact
And the destruction of economic power over Generations history of redlining
Cargo in Naruto
Fuct
Stupid stupid bigger
Who doesn't actually care about reporting accurate information or depicting reality shows
He's just
Protecting
The Notions of whiteness
And I am
Demanding
That Joe Biden
Destroy all of Illinois portion of roots
I want it all gone you don't want anymore on my route
No more historic Route
66 I want all the
The science Aiken down
Dave
Asphalt
Dug up I have no skin in this game
I don't have a car
66 is what I wanted crocodile
Does the Dan Ryan survive
So
Tyranny
Yep you heard of it
It's speeding up
And has been speeding up over time
Doesn't sound 100% wrong
Were there
Journeyman
This is what they like
Like to do
And they're doing it to us
Raw
Domination
And we sit here with our open Society model
Does it move show
10 years ago we were going 5 miles an hour
5 years ago we were going
50 miles an hour
Who that's fast
3 years ago we were going 100 miles an hour
Well if you think about the time in between these speeds that are a very slow Excel
Alteration parabola
Two years ago we were going 200 miles an hour
We were going 500 miles an hour
And now we're going 10,000 miles an hour down the rattle that's because that was
Million miles an hour
Billion miles an hour
Gilman
Confidence going
People submit and like
Domino's
Killed everybody
John Hopkins
The collapse is going to work
Either going to be so many brain-damaged people from these vaccines
Natural
Big Mass Reclamation centers
Green
What's people
You signed the paperwork while your son and your daughter in
Your mama
20 years old party results 6 years old
Cuz I could have just given him something
Something that
Wipes you out
They wanted to be something that
Waze on everyone sorrow in the
Painting
Medical system
Everything out of you
Squeezing your drive
. none of that is a in the dark
Yeah
He describes something from soil
Green and then says that they
Satan the document like in Swahili
That's real convenient that it is it is really helpful for movies to tell you what is in the duck you
But you're talking about
Yeah
I could describe any movie and then just
Exclaim that is what a document says investigate to like
It doesn't matter
The Rockefeller report on 30
10 Going on 30 and body swap
We're all going to swap with our I read that document out of the aspirin into the
The two top body-swapping major Bravo
Right
But the people who don't learn those life
It's going to create robots in the street
Cleaning them up displaced within other people
Immigration inside a body
That's a lot of new regulations
I appreciate it
So Alex isn't released
Supporting gays
As much
Mostly because it was a
Aggressive
At the end of March
Those last episodes
It was
Yeah over-the-top what I didn't mean to say that
And defensive Matt gaetz I meant to say it's okay if you f***
Nope that's not good either.
So
Rodger was
Still defending Alex on the April 2nd episode
Sort of
Supportive but haha
Little bit
Gates with no proof why he's got to be removed
Old girl $1000 one time
Dona Lolita Express flight
Caribbean island
An hour-long it's not a seventeen-year-old girl but
It's okay
Cuz
Pembroke Road
What there's a moral mean
I'm out of the bus like that
That's not what happened
Also got new experience
Of course I said
Go ahead your lies
Of course they don't
Still meeting
To bring himself into it
Unnecessary
I want
If he says something like if it's real I'll throw them under the bus I want a cow
Countdown clock are right over there
Just like Tad
The different town
Before I sit this is the dismount
Skulls and get this one caller
This is sort of
The call wasn't
Interesting but he said something that I wanted to play as well
This is the type of person who believes in Alex's show
To give you a nickname
The club of Rome was founded in 1968 in the UN began in 1940
Because they knew the club of Rome with
Right
I mean you understand like there's just this
Did this is the sort of thing you're not understand
Do you do you want to leave the club of Rome he's speaking about
How tall boy
Is Romulus Auto
And the wolves
I mean like okay so the Antichrist needs to get its power and that's why they made the um
13 years later the club around
Was found dead
Images of make any sense
Anyway alexsa in between calls with rainbows a little bit about how God wouldn't it be so great if they you you
Us and Russia became best friends
Medically
It's over
Go to Country
Dominate the world for good
A new golden age
Last week
That's not
Works
The Dragon
We all know what I'm told
What
So now the war that now the holy war that unfolds is between the United States and Russia
I guess so
But also this is a real
Strong argument of predeterminism
No freeway
Seem like that
It does seem like weird is it dipping into
Calvin territory this is a this is a horrifying are you
Revelation
Yeah you do geopolitical for us and Russia teamed up with
Dominate the world but we know from Revelation that's not good
It's such a f******
Cop out
F*** you
Fair enough
How dare you
The Book of Revelations doesn't also include like
100 years
The prep time for the Antichrist arise there is a revelation about how the devil's 10 years by
So well that was an interesting thing for John to add
So we get another car and this dude is on every
F****** episode
He calls in all the time
The dude named Carlos
But everything that's going on right now isn't a con
Christianity
What are you obviously I'm going to cover the John Hawkins.
People sick
It's a society collapses
Incredible
What is there big endgame why are they so Savage
What are they moving ahead with something so incredibly dangerous
Giant mask rhymes
Because
People doing
Good Friday
Think about it
Worldwide Moving
By individuals
Automatically
I don't know who this dude gets on everyday like almost everyday
It it makes me think that either he has a priority number
Sure they don't get that many calls
All the f****** time
And Alex
Why is a Bazaar level of deference
For him
For quite a while
Carlos
Seems like a guy that is in the
Yeah yeah
I don't know maybe maybe he's just letting people talk
Too much now because he he's he's get another color and I will say that you let this guy talk too long too long
Little bit too long
Not not the same kind of problems with Harrison Smith
When people talk too long
This guy just sound
A little bit Sovereign citizen
We have some really big
Issues
The original
You know this whole thing
Is about the legal fiction
The Congress created to our birth
At work
Representing.
So
So we're operating under color of law
Color of law
And until and unless
We
Refute their presumption
Stop representing. All caps name
Find an explanation of
Dacosta Colchester killed
Send notices
Beautiful brother Stephen
Beautiful
All caps when you spell the man named Dan
Beyond that standards
The original post office
That all wars are Wars between post
Did you not know that there has been
100 years secret war between post offices
Ever since one guy
And his horse knocked over another guy's horse
Started the great post office War feel like probably there were
Earlier times some feuding
Queen
Between Capital primitive post office
These days
Lil Debbie
Big Show sucks
This episode is not good
The image of
Just a regular post office driver
Just drive it other with the
Door open on the
Wrong side in your life isn't that cute you guys are driving
They get out and then there's suddenly attack
Another post office
Frozen into the open window
Boys jumping UPS close
So
Alex has
Who's another reporter baby
Find the skies
Voice
Incredibly annoying
He's on to talk about the Border
And
Talk about everything is
I'm here
Just started and where I turned it off
But also some of the culture War stuff
Things that are going on as they put us onto this
Virtual economy
Yeah I mean I'm pretty sure your viewers are familiar with
Bad baby you know she's the catch me outside girl that was on dr.
You're feeling extremely viral
Totally depraved
She made an onlyfans
I got to go
Don't know I don't know what good is going to come of this conversation about the cash me outside girl
I don't care you know that somebody in a viral video has an onlyfans
AccountNow
Did I know
Goodbye
I don't I don't care to listen to you I guess of a best-case scenario
Shame someone for being a sex worker
Like I don't give a
How dare you
Have fun
I hope no big deal 300 Yelp
He's on to talk about the Border
Culture wars if someone has an onlyfans account
I'm mad about it
I have to leave
I can't
I'm not going to take you seriously
That's a dynasty level offense if I had a glass of wine in my hand I would throw it in that guy's face her burial service
The temerity
Yeah and plus
I mean realistically
Saturday's just
It's right around the corner
You've got an hour of
Meats and Gristle
When to start off
With with Alex
Discovering
The
John top
The most
People are informed of heard about event 201
They've heard about operation lockstep
They weren't about Crimson contagion they weren't about diseases
And the UN drill
But have you heard about summertime
2025 20:28
It is all of those plans together
But not set
In the near future
Previous drills were
But set
Add a few more years in the future
Super Bowl 20
2028 with 2020
The 20
And it is
Exactly
What's happening
I love the idea that Alex has a job Johns Hopkins an area to pick things exactly as they're having a real-life is Superman
Imposed on a different date
Also nothing funnier than
It's not a little bit the teacher interview
Future ideas in the near near started
That's a bad dismount
Real life just a little few years off of a few things
Intentions of the Hopkins exercises messaging issues around a drug that was believed
The effective against bars called
Tallow severe
Severe
There wasn't a drug that the government was trying
Make a push for the treatment of covid in the way of the medic
Local community Gets behind cattle severe in this exercise
Maybe RAM does averre possibly but
I mean
There is like
But his messaging hydroxychloroquine
Pushed hydroxychloroquine so hard
It doesn't fit for this and I don't think that room does of your does either in terms of
The waves
Depicted in this the exercise
Read to me this is a black one really big problem with
The scenario match
Real world history
Second backlash to cala severe begins in February 2026
64 months into the outbreak
Like when a video of a child projectile vomiting
After taking a dose goes viral online
This did not happen for months into covid
Even metaphorically
3rd in May 2026 a made-up rapper named bz suffers a public
When trying to promote sparse treatments to his audience
Sweating a people who volunteer for vaccine trials to participants in the Tuskegee experiments
This did not happen in the real world
Exhibit a in why scientist do become rapper
Are fictitious rapper's name
BZ
Examples of things like this not happen in the real world exercise
Because the point of the events that happened in the scenario is
To create situations
We're messaging challenges would arise
But the exercise participants
Could reflect on how fast
Respond
The inclusion of a situation like this rapper making a public gas in this scenario doesn't make sense out of
When you don't see this exercise within the context of why it exist
It seems really weird
But when you understand that it's designed to assist medical Communications professionals brainstorm the ways that
They might need to respond to various events in a crisis
The picture makes
At the same time that bz makes his comment
That's the fictional former president Jacqueline Bennett gives a noncommittal answer about whether or not she would give her grandson
Palace of the year
Which creates a similar but slightly different messaging Pro problem for the exercise port
Dispensary
Anyway the point is
A bunch of things that happened and is very differently
Name is Imagine scenario that have happened in our real-world Opera
Houses just trying to pretend everything is the same because it's more Fun and Profit
For him but
It's all made up
So icy
Because he's supposed to be a
I was I thought Jay-Z
I mean but the very public gas would suggest more of a Kanye
Circumstances are they are they saying that Kanye is going to Taylor
Swift covid-19 the context of the scenario exercise bz is one of the people who
Who is enlisted
To help get messaging out
About the safety of the tree and then he said George Bush doesn't care about black people
Enlisted medical community
This document my friend
Is a timeline
Short is what you need to understand
Actually timeline
But a few years off
EmbroidMe or near to basically you just transpose
The beginning of the outbreak
The outbreak in the document
You can tell what's going to happen
In the future
And unfortunately
We are six months away from
Now here's what's
We're about 13 months into the simulation
That again it's not really a simulation are using that
Cavaliers
Operations
Case I get caught with the documents I just say
It's part of the grill
Operation
Also.
Classic by Health agent
They say that within six months to a year of people being inoculated
Experimental
GMO
Gene therapy
That you will have massive brain damage
And spongiform encephalopathy
She basically
Prion disease map
Good Times
Six months to a year for
Don't worry it's b*******
In the exercise there's potential basis for a vaccine discovered in the form of an animal vaccine for
Respiratory virus developed by a company called
GMI
This condition was similar in many ways to sparse so researchers began looking at whether or not it could be effective for human
What are the initial downsides was that quote
Data provided by gmic
Suggested that the vaccine was effective at preventing
Illness in cows pigs and other hoofed mammals
But internal trials revealed several worrisome side effects including swollen legs
Severe joint pain
Ed Encephalitis leading to seizures or death
Right and cows learning how to do
In this scenario in May 20th
A group of parents
The size of the group is unspecified they sue the government
Because they believe that their children got Encephalitis from the vaccine
The claims are not presented as necessarily Acura
It just more detail added to make this a more
Real scenario
Since his mirrors real world
Anti-vax folks
The challenge to the message
Virginia's required for medical communicate
The scenario does say that quote
A showing no adverse side effects for nearly a year several vaccine recipients slowly began to experience symptoms such as blurry vision
Headaches and numbness in their extremities
Do the small number of cases these significant
Today sociation with corvax was never
Determined
As of this writing in 20-30 longitudinal studies initiated by the NIH
Beginning of the vaccine Nation program
Have not reached the next round of data collection
The formal analysis of these symptoms
Has not yet
Been conducted
Furthermore these cases arose from the initial cohort effects
Recipients those in high-risk populations including those
With underlying other underlying condition
Making it increasingly difficult
To determine the extent to which
These symptoms are associated with that
Text Nation
I read this earlier but I wanted to read it again
And because it just brings up an important point
And that is what these elements of the scenario it's
It's left intentionally open end
Yeah because it exists
Suppose a question
The
It's not to depict a reality that actually exist
In that scenario how does a person in a position of medical messaging
Respond
How do you convey confidence
Stone the medical side of things
Well still acknowledging certain
Uncertain
These are the sorts of questions of this story arc is meant to
To bring up
Because Alex knows better and he's a psychic he's realized that this is actually the globalist
Estimating that they're going to give everyone mad cow disease
Encephalitis
Is really just a the animals act
Axion right
The GM I created
In the end it's
Encephalitis and animals
And then there's some
Parents who allege encephalitis
It's not actually proven in the
In the case of the
And that's maybe the most important question for the study to ask
Which is how is it that we can tell people
Honestly
We don't know
And at the same time reassure them
That
They can trust or to Turtle Point out is
Exploring ideas of how to beat
Compassionate
About the Unser
Cuz it's alright it's alright feeling for people to have and how do you
How do you mix
That compassion about the uncertainties
With the confidence
MSN
Spell science
The challenge
That's why you do EXO
Chris Isaak
Yeah my message would probably not be good I would be more
Sing like listen
We know Pat
Public education has failed you between 1st and 8th grade at
Least you wouldn't make it through the app
Fixes connecting this
Study
And he's found
Right so they say encephalitis
Scenario right
And what what that's like the zika virus right
I just mentioned to you spongiform encephalopathy
Prion disease
Microbiology infectious diseases Journal
Covid-19 rna-based vaccine
And the risk of prion disease
That was put out
In 20
21 by prestigious scientist
Whenever you hear Alex say that a claim is being made by a prestigious scientist
That means he has no idea who the person is immediately
Known quantity but he wants to elevate this claim
Because it works well for him
Share this claim that the covid vaccine causes prion disease was entirely on a non pure review paper by a guy named Jay Barker
No one agrees with his conclusion and he is not a prestigious scientist
According to USA Today quote in 1999 he claimed the influenza vaccine cause
Type 1 diabetes
Acclaimed
Proven by Johns Hopkins University
Institute for vacuum places whenever there's a vaccine
That needs to be smeared with IBS
So now Alex is there he's rolling deep though with
With crew
Decode Beezy
Play Daddy's got robbed deuce
So Rob do isn't
Studio
The corporate representative Rob do
He's just
Blown away by this document
Yeah so the parallels on this are
When you looked at 911 and you saw the parallels that
This is got the same thing in it
Massive power outages you got a male and female president
The president who's a male
Stops
After a few years artist
Female who she's only in for one term then she leaves
Then the male president takes over we kind of have that going on
So first of all biting Isn't step-down So this isn't actually a similarity at all
Exactly like that where it's happening
You don't
I don't know if the Infowars universe is just so convinced that it's going to happen any day now that they've just decided it's already happened but
This is just a similarity in Rob's had
So in this scenario the president does name Randall Archer
He previously been the vice president daughter Jacqueline Bennett
She didn't step down
She just decided not to run for a second term after being president from 2020 to 2024
At which point Archer ran and won
You guys
As you were
You still actively involved being an adviser but was not up to seeking re-election quote to do to help
Concerns
This is the case
In the scenario because it creates an interesting Dynamic where there's a new president but also a fully-functioning an intact staff at the department of
Health and Human Service
Interns with the exercises designed to explore this make
Text total stats
Essentially former president Bennett exist as a
The prop so she can be a character that makes up media gas
Where should give that noncommittal answer about Calla severe
The character that said should be a beloved
Public figure
It works anyway.
That's too weird
Telephone for president
Looks great in order to make that scenario work
She would have to just had one term and ideally she shouldn't have
Just lost an election
Seems like the best way to get to that story beat we just
Sequel Electric
So the Gap would carry so much weight that they would be influenced by it while at the same time
You couldn't lose an election and have everybody be able to be weird
Yeah you don't want to be their current president because it makes
The other specific that Rob uses this power outage
He's in the scenario
There's a massive power outage in the Pacific
Northwest just one week prior to the rollout of the vaccine
Which doesn't match up with
What Rob wants are two in the real world sure
He's trying to compare that to the Texas outages which happened well after vaccination programs
Began our reality
Again it's important to understand why this specific detail is included in the X
Exercise
This is all about medical messaging in a public health emergency so this power outage was added to the scenario so participants could
Or what methods they might employ
If they didn't have access to things like social media
With a massive power outage one of the main methods of communications is less effective
You need to continue helping the public through so what do you do
This is super clear from the exercise if you read it
But if you just want to make random connections I guess you could do a Rob do is doing
That's really embarrassing
What it says in the
Quote all communication about the vaccine rollout was published in electronic form
Consequently many individuals in the affected areas
Where initially unable to access information provided by state local and federal health authorities
Regarding korvax dispensing
Immediately after this there are study questions for the participant
In the document
Like quote
Well greater
Use of electronic media open
New opportunities for broad Outreach
What Communications vulnerabilities exist that could impede communication efforts
Violetta
Tronic Media or the other question
Quote
How can Public Health communicators remain flexible when multiple disasters occur at once
In their paper about designing scenario-based exercises
Ogilvy and Schwartz discuss the need for stories that follow various
And one of those common archetypes is Crisis and response
This plot element is about introducing a big problem and then the participant
Let's get to respond
The paper discusses an exercise they ran with shell that followed basically this
Exact same path
Quote first comes the scenarios Christ
Initial signs of environmental degradation lead reputable scientist to conclude that an environmental disaster is faster
A few leading governments and companies change the way they do business
Disasters begin to occur in countries they could not or chose not to adapt
And there's public outcry
The playing field
The organizational operating environment is suddenly dramatically alter
The Innovative firms that learn to make difficult changes in their beds
Practices to avoid environmental degradation
Are now positioned to become market leader
In the Johns Hopkins exercise the outbreak itself is the initial
Crisis
Then things like a power outage in the Pacific Northwest or the video the kid vomiting
Represent new crises that
The participants have to deal with
This is the context of what Alex and Robber lying about no makes total sense
There's no way to read that document and not
Understand but that's what it is
That's so funny to me
That they missed
The most important
Of having that kind of power outage a week
Before the vaccine rollout
Which would just beat simply be like
Okay an astonishing number of people are going to think that God is punishing us for this vaccine
How do we deal with that
Or did you are all the proud boys accounted for
Is this witches
People are going to ask us
Why God punished us with this power outage before the vaccine
You know what that isn't in the exercise but I think
Subject
It was made in 2017
If it was made today that might have been irrelevant messaging question
But yeah okay
Beautiful organism meteorologists are witches
What do we do about that
It's interesting to me that like this is how Rob do starting it out he's talking about like these similarities
One is not a similarity at all
In that fight
Hasn't stepped down and it said where
Even if he did
It doesn't match
The scenario
Kick it in the
In the exercise
Completely
Text total sites that a power outage would be in there
It creates a border
Teaching moment about
Using non-electronic Rapids
Everytime do goes to a diner he has failed
The
What are the three different
Picture
Geodude ever gotten one of those I get cereal boxes placemats it doesn't know shut up another great idea
Okay okay
Play overcooked
Cook meals around or whatever it is
I have a new idea
Steiner try and figure out puzzles better way to eat
Overcooked
How old is defeo
Interesting Lee
Don't waste your time on
Please do so Alex
Steps to starting up reading
The the
And this is fun
I love this
Let's go ahead
And again here
Here is the project team
Who is Ronnie
Top eugenicist top globalist
From around the country
John Hopkins Bloomberg School
Appublichealth
The team
Talk to Janice
It's a five senior associate with the Johns Hopkins Center for Health security
A professor from Texas State
Masters of Public Health candidate
From Columbia University
How do you get any of those things without a proven
Open track record of top you Dennis
Alex has no idea who any of these people are
You know who they are
Directly affect interact with these people know who they are Columbia University grad student
Generation eugenicist
Store
Earlier there was a squirrel a weirdo coming up Nate Mike
Mike the swirly weirdo don't know who this dude is
Employee might be Harrison Smith roommate sure anybody but he is
Tennessee Tractor
Weird
Oh and alive
Okay
I know this can be found inside of this far so I can work for work
After showing no adverse side effects
After nearly a year
Vaccine recipients slowly began to
To experience symptoms
As Time passed and more people across the United States were vaccinated
Claims of adverse side effects
Began to emerge
As investigations grew in intensity
Several high-ranking
Officials at the CDC and FDA were forced to step down
And withdraw from government
They're setting up the health
Officials and the politicians
Take the Fall For This
What Mike is reading here
It's definitely from the document but he's made a classic Infowars moved here
Havanese taking two unrelated passenger
Just from the texts and combine them pretending they're about the same thing
In order to lie about this document
The part about people experiencing side effects
After years from chapter 17 it's on Page Six
The second part about government official stepping down as chapter 19
It's on Page Six
It's completely unrelated
Previous chapter
First conversation about possible side
Here is the paragraph about the government officials info
Quote
After action reports government hearings an Agency Reviews following the pandemic were too numerous
This account
Emergency funding appropriated by Congress to fight the disease became available partway through the course of the pandemic
But federal state and local public health agencies struggle to manage
The procedural requirements
Suspended that does sound familiar
As a result
Significant amounts of emergency funds remained unused as a pandemic while I'm down
Has the investigations grew in intensity several high-ranking officials at the CDC and FDA were forced to step down and withdraw from government
In order to quotes
Spend more time with their family
The investigations that are causing uses
Investigations are causing these imaginary officials to step down or not related to possible drug side
Clearly about mismanagement of funds
If this guy's read the document as he's presenting himself as having done
Then he knows fully well that the two passages he just read as if they were one paragraph
Are actually two completely different
Sections of the document
If this document actually said what he wanted it to
He wouldn't have to lie like this
In order to make it look like it
Met his
Needs
This is bulshit weirdo Mike
Yeah that is funny that even in the Johns Hopkins
Report it's like listen we all know at least
15 to 20 Saturdays are corrupted
We're just going to
Put in that some of them adequate
I mean it's it's
I think that the
Scenario
Paints
A very realistic portrait
Things that you could expect might happen
We'll deal with another one of them that robbed you thinks is maybe Wizardry
A little bit later but I don't know
Ferris options that are made and then also some ones that are like
That's a little silly
But they're all in service of what the document is for
Exercise medical communicators rise to various challenge
Now
Think that clip right there where Mike is reading two different sections as if they were the same
Because when he's talking about these b side effects
Event says as investigations grow in intensity and that's mentally the audience very clear
Split those quote
Yeah but then combine
Send them together to form a
Single quote believe that the investigations are about drug side effects
And that's how they're
Going to set up the politicians
Take the fall for that
Has nothing to do with
He has to know.
And this is the point at which any reasonable person would just be like f*** this absolutely misrepresenting
And there's no way that that is an axe
There's no way you did this accidentally
Well I mean
It's it's
Somewhat similar to Alex's synopsis of Romeo and Juliet in safari
A bunch of the middle between those two things no it's not
No no no no no no I didn't be like if you threw a little bit of Hamlet
Mike Mike
Gets to being weird some more about the passage about vaccine distribution
To determine how to best
Distribute limited doses
Of korvax to members
A priority groups across
The country
The US government Resort in New
Controversial tactics
Notably heading Healthcare
Care providers access
Patience electronic
Health records
To determine the number of individuals
In high-risk populations
Receiving care
Chico area
This passage really undercuts the argument that this document represents the globalists plan cuz they
Didn't do that
Also while we're on the subject of things that didn't happen in real life that do happen in the scenario we can look at chapter 10
The big
Giant
Gigantic
I'm going to come up with more words
What are the big public messaging crises that come up over the course of the ex
Gojira merch
From the ocean
No that's chapter 12
A huge public backlash because doctors and nurses aren't included in the highest priority group for the disc
Division of the vaccine
The huge public
They even designed to fake tweet
But it was straight the outrage
Those happening in the medical worker
Communities
There's a strike in Milwaukee among Healthcare Providers when they won't go to work
Unless they're made of acxiom priority
And none of that happened in life
Yeah I know that's a totally reasonable thing for them to do where that unreasonable thing to occur
Also in the scenario there's a Groundswell of college activism taking place in the social media app that's created
For this exercise called unequal
From the exercise quote
Another group that was not generally affected by the government's corvax promotion efforts were college students
Especially those attending school on the 8th
Easton West Coast
Public Health officials had no explanation for the lack of vaccine uptake among this population until protest
Began at several college campuses
Including uc-berkeley the University of Washington Reed College
Harvard and the University of Chicago
The focus of these protests with a lack of access
Corvax
Particularly for populations in less developed countries like Haiti Guatemala and Cameroon
The college students involved declared they would not accept corvax until it was made available
In terms of both
Access an expense
To everyone in the world who wanted it
This to did not happen in the real world
Yeah the reason these events are included in the scenarios the same as anything but doesn't
They presented opportunity for the participants to wrestle with challenges in the field of medical message
None of it's real but it portrays situations that are close enough to semen real for them
To be effective and role-playing
And that's enough for Alex
To think that it's all
Secretly real
Yeah I mean
It seems
It seems fun
Whenever these studies predict event
That do wind up
Occurring
Because you're like
It's really just based on the s*** we've already
Racine
That's going to almost certainly happen again
Because people don't learn lessons
From things exactly like the thing that were right
Leaving now
Mike is a weirdo
Decided
Happened he read this passage
Again
Like if I
Normal people would have
Checked out already
But I'm not normal
You still want to hear more
I mean this gets worked out severe side effects including swollen legs severe joint pain and encephalitis
Potentially resulting in seizures
Seizure disorders or death
Occasionally occur dwarf reward
From the document
We're going to handle the beer older that
Mike is failing to mention here is the passages reading is about the side effects
So it's pretty corvex human vaccine
It's on the section about the vaccine for animals
There's a bit of comedy and that he's reading a quote from a fake email that the scenario created in order to depict an exchange
Give information about an animal vaccine
And I'd like to dumbasses pretending it's a document talk about human side effects
Just amazing
That is
Is real real bummer Town level ship
She read in contacts
What the actual thing says
In 2021 the coronavirus caused an outbreak in region 7
Parenthetically Southeast Asia
Population
Our researchers developed and produced in-house ineffective vaccine against the info
His subsequent approval and use
Successfully end of the outbreak in the region
Wow largely effective in preventing infection
Severe side effects
Including swollen legs
Severe joint pain and Encephalitis potentially results
Begin seizures
Seizure disorder or dad
Occasionally occur
Given the millions of vaccinations required for Regent 7th this resulted in measurable losses in the animal population
This is critical to understand
If this document actually said with these Dum Dums or claiming it was they wouldn't resort to tactics like this
This is so manipulative
Yes nonsense
Insatiable show
If it were truly a Smoking Gun they just be able to read it they wouldn't have to pretend
That they were reading this
Fake email from us from the document other than the real thing about human sex
What's the point
Having
These things
If you're just going to highlight like
One paragraph from
Every other chapter and then just combined them into a
Single
Double space
Page
You know like
YVR
F*** off
Bike
Mike read the passage about conspiracy theories that go around and Alex
It's so excited that he has to read it himself
I think it's because you like
I want to maybe use a
Cod of me saying this later like in a John bowne report right to have this weirdo reader
I wanted to be in my voice
Conspiracy theories also prevalent across social media suggesting the virus have been purposely created
Introducing the population by drug company or that escaped from a government lab
Secretly testing bio-weapon
This isn't 2,000
And 17 right after fauci says
A virus will be released
It's going to happen to judge challenge Trump
It's going to be a surprise operation
Thought you didn't say that
In the speech that he was given
Then we talked about
Cuz he was talked about every Administration deals with an unforeseen Health crisis conspiracy theory
Sounds that it would escape from a government lab
Just
Twenty years after Alex started thing that every 4 months
We went to that we listen to that 2003 episode now to think foot-in-mouth came out of Port Townsend
Like yeah of course they would add that scenario is that you do that's one of the things
Of the world exactly
That's not even
Like
It's just mentioned
After the
The entire course of the outbreak
In terms of the document
Call me when conspiracy theorist in this paper decide to inspire people
Overthrow
Mike
I mean look
Some of this stuff
I don't know like someone who's
Really generous
Might be able to say he's just
Sloppy
Intention behind the US
I don't believe
Biak
Someone incredibly generous neither of which are we
No
Also
Pink
I heard this and I
I got really worried
It took me two weeks to read by the way
The warding a weaves everything together so you're like
What is going on I just hope this is an exercise is real
I was just trying to do the best I can to extract everything so if you had 5 minutes you can just understand what's happening
Oh my God
Omigod Superbad
God more than 5 minutes
That's a good thing
Sure sure I can't imagine taking two weeks
And I'm coming away with that sort of sewn together quotation that misrepresent
I don't understand like being able to look at this and not be able to understand
Fairly quickly what it is
Like I understand if you if you see it out of context completely out of context
It could be confusing for a bit but if you only had 5 minutes to hear about it shirt
Down and actually read a couple Pages Friday
Explain
The exercise
I don't know it's 8
Dear Alex Jones
Please
We're explaining the exercise you've literally can't use this for your proper
I don't I really really don't understand the idea of anyone sitting with this for an hour let alone two weeks
She's had coming away with any confusion
About how also there is a disclaimer that Alex
Shouldn't use this
This is a hypothetical scenario designed to illustrate the public health risk communication
Challenges that
Could potentially emerge during a naturally-occurring infectious disease outbreak
We're going to the elemental distribution of a novel and or investigational drug vaccines Therapeutics
Or other Medical countermeasures
The Infectious pathogen
No I just didn't Alec
Medical countermeasures characters
Social media post
And government agencies responses described herein are entirely
So there is a disclaimer
That does not stop
Diaz.
Doesn't sound like you
At 10 it's about what they're not
Here's Mike
2 weeks
Who started
7/10
He's going to bring back up
The power outage
A week before quarterbacks was released for distribution in the United
The power grid at the Grand Coulee Dam in Eastern Washington State
Experienced a catastrophic
Failure
Volume vented not destroy any infrastructure or result in any desk
It did cause widespread
Power outages in Washington
Oregon Idaho Montana and British
Columbia
The power was were
Restore within a day of the initial outage blackouts continued
Play Muse areas over the next 3 weeks
And the Resurgence of the band Widespread Panic
Put that in a vaccine exercise
Because they're all behind all this
Things are showing off their people
Mike seems okay
Confused by why they would include something about a power outage in this document about a medical situation
But if he'd actually read it he shouldn't be confused
It'll literally spelled out in the exercise
This is very
Clearly to get participants to consider how to be effective in getting message
Sitting out in a real non-digital world
Promise Mario
State and local public health officials scrambled
Deliver Flyers printed and copy that local emergency Operation Center is using backup generators
To explain vaccine prioritization and pod information
This extremely time-consuming effort exhaust
Did the public health Workforce already stretched thin by the epidemic
Response and several years of budget cuts
But it was ultimately
Successful
Early vaccination rates in Washington Oregon and Idaho were very similar to other states
And in some cases above a
In spite of his success the incident underscored the shortcomings
Associated with relying solely on electronic communication strategy
That what I just read to you is immediately after the park he was reading
Yeah it makes it
Very clear almost impossible to
To misunderstand
If there's no way to believe that he took two weeks to read this and couldn't understand what the
The point was
This is either someone who's deeply Disturbed and needs help needs like mental help
Or he's a willful liar inclined to believe it's
Yeah
I mean
It is this is not a generous
Interpretation but
The idea of these people reading a document
That tells them what
It says absolutely does confused
Like on a deep level
Yeah yeah cuz they can't just be like
Oh
Like that's not a thing they can do they can't read an explanation of what's happening in route
Oh well they're being honest
I understand
Right
If
They were
Copy and pasting
Various parts of the document and its representation of what it says
If they weren't pretending that side effects in animals where they actually humans
Because they weren't doing stuff like that then maybe
I would be like oh this is just suspicious Miss run-amok
Yeah but there is there is work that at
It's been done in order to misrepresent this document
Not two weeks worth
Spider has been
Now
Jordan
RAB do
He's about to have his mom
Mind blown
This document
It's crazy
Let's go to the next when you look at the
Similarity to the name
Sparse
Covid
And then we have SARS covid 2
Okay
Same almost same exact name and they wrote this
Three or four years before the number
Manamana just
Rattler.
It's really crazy
Where's the
It's almost like scientists are interested too much
Indifferent naming conventions when it comes
Viruses
And instead it's almost a classification
It means Saint Paul acute respiratory
Pretorius Endo syndrome Coronavirus
Which is similar to SARS covid 2
Yeah sure
The reason that this is the city that it popped up
I had this whole thing
About not naming things after
It's because that whole thing is a World Health Organization
Convention name something after the city exactly the location where it came up
And the World Health Organization isn't involved in the sector
Because that would give a massive
Incentive for people to be like
Never f*** with those people ever
Exactly. This was in 2017 which is
Is fairly shortly after the World Health Organization changed its best
Practice is about that whole thing
So there may have been some lingering
Confusion about naming
Convention
I almost guarantee that if the World Health Organization had made this scenario
He probably would have named it conditioned Stars Cove 2
Hey Rob do would be abhorrent
He would just s***
F*** it I might
It is not weird
Know-it-all know it's it's a convention it's a naming convention it's like a
You know it's like
Kingdom phylum is 8 hours
In terms of like a
Conspiracy theory this is the one that rises to the level of
How about that their names
That's how they named stuff
There's another connection with the real world though
They want them to name viruses like they do hurricanes like this is
Virus Maria is that what they would feel better about maybe
Brings up another thing in this this next clip
That's a
Kind of similar to
Real world
Then we have the inflated fatality estimates initially
They write in the scenario
CDC fatality rate
Almost 5%
Who fatality rate
14 and a half percent
And then the fatality rate of over 64 50%
This is fair
The inflated F estimates are in the scenario
There's a few
The first is that the scenario supposed to
Pick reality and the reality of dealing with
A completely new disease is it sometimes you get some things off
One of the main reasons is actually spelled out in the doctor
If you read it
Look at the outside of the sparse outbreak
Physicians understanding of the disease stem primarily from
Extremely severe cases resulting in pneumonia or hypoxia
They're required hospitalization and extensive Medical
Mild cases of a disease which produced
Symptoms including cough
Fever headaches and delays
We're often perceived as the flu by people who had them and consequently often went untreated
An undiagnosed by medical personnel
As a result early case-fatality estimates were inflated
Is the real Dynamic play out in the covid-19 outbreak
But it's been true in other past outbreaks as well
The issue is you can't always assume that it's going to be the case or else you're putting yourself in a position to get blindsided by a
Super deadly condition that you happen to under arrest
It's far better to be over cautious with
With new diseases then took
Just let him go and see what happened this is what
Diseases of killed almost all of us
Be careful.
So the other reason that this isn't a document is B
Because it's made of
Exercise for medical communicator
And what could be a greater communication challenge than having been wrong initially
The study question for the Section 8
How can Health Authority's best meet public demands
For critical information
In such as what is the health right
And what do I know about it
When the crisis is still unfolding and not all the facts are known
If you understand this in the context it was written and used all the things that they're trying to create paranoia about
Just sound
Talking stupid
That's awesome
Yeah he's awesome
Dude
Thing that they trying to make a couch like a conspiracy adalah
Holy Ship you guys are dumb
Let's go to the antivirals is the next slide
In this scenario they write they have one called
Bellossom
Alright
Is it and I are
Side effects nausea headaches vomiting and body aches is actually a viral video
About a boy in this scenario taking the closet here and then immediately projectile vomiting everywhere
Go back to it
Then three years later it's Rim desert
And this is not the real name this is the name they gave it later
It's actually got a different name
Same side effects nausea constipation
Smoking Gun
If these dudes cared at all they could learn why these drugs have similar names
Insomuch
Generic name for the drug which is to say they're not brand name right
The convention for naming generic drugs is to have the suffix
To the word indicate what the drug is
Princeton's antiviral drugs generally end in the suffix
Vir for viral
This isn't Universal but
Most of them end up with this this
And that's why these two.
Sure
You know if you can
Did you go down the list
And then also like penicillin
Derived drugs have selling like amoxicillin
Dip powder ovarian
Done that way on purpose to be simple Soca
People making the scenario we're striving to fill it with realistic
Details so they followed except
The convention for naming the drug they made up in it
Alton robbed or so stupid and so addicted to think
Coincidences mean something
That they take that as a sign that the document is mocking
This is
Not yeah
It's like
Just such
A
Just
Don't talk and just scream repeatedly
I refuse to learn anything
Just now they're both in denial
Read the first
Page of Google
Change the few letters
Type
Any of these questions into Google and the
First result
Would tell you what
Yeah it's really easier to understand something
This clip is just where
Everything turns
Aperitif
Rob is in the middle of complaining about like a medical ads and
Pressure washer
Yeah and then you have the native a switch
Put out by the vaccine company saying the vaccine safe in effect
And that's all they do
Vitamin mineral Fusion is a remark
Google products
40% off
Infowars
It's almost almost like that is a joke
Bats
That's just too much
You complaining about like a medical ad
Too much
These people all they do is put out these ads and say things are safe and effective anyways let's go to come
Commercial of Alex saying that his stuff is
Safe and effective
Oh wow wow
Ciate Dave Steve gone
I've got a while now and Alex realizes
We did it
We have not
Oh no
Your world
Humans roll
People to care about freedom
I get upset Rob gets upset
We spent weeks studying as we finally get on Erin it should
He's covered 10% of what's in front of us
Every bit of this is just as insane or insane
I've even gotten the part where they admit they're doing this
The kill you and save the Earth
They admit they're doing this
Apart is not
They specifically say they're not doing
Although they introduced a very interesting medical messaging
Okay let's say in this scenario our secret plan that has
Got Mouse
Oh god of the least reliable and
Incredible
Credulous versus now what do we do Let It Go
I guess
Hit the panic button
So yeah
This is this is where I
Checked out
That's a good place to check
Oh okay okay
That weird Mike
Was doing that stuff about
About that
Cut and paste job. I got to get out of here
And here's where I was like Alex go f*** yourself
Justin summation
Of the Bombshells have been released here I mean
Give me the strongest thing is
The drug names the same before drug even exist
That's the same before they release it
Them running the lab I mean
This is Smoking Gun
1 in
85 trillion quadrillion
Wow
Saudi
Things
Zipfizz
So convincing for Alex's that there similarities in the name of
That far is Cove
Ansari's Cove 2
The end to the
Name of two antiviral drugs and the same suffix
Yep
Pieces
Alex started promoting this on Thursday and this is the best you can do on Sunday or Saturday
Defensive team professionalism blew me away was
That naming conventions
Can be used
In a fictitious scenario also
I never would have imagined that people
Would have done something so insane
Nice to stick to
Basic
Borderline universally standardized
Convention listen to over an hour of this Saturday
Alex said that
And then Rob do brought up also
They use some of the same hashtags in fake tweets that they have on their the people used in real life
I got to go help throwing things
Immediate throwing of things memes
Except
So anyway I got really excited
Because
You know
I think after our last present day episode
I was in the doldrums I felt bad sure
I did not care for Alex's very weird
Defensive back gate
And this was a promise of a primary source
We found
But Jordan I mean like
We were
Talked over the weekend I was telling you like
I really think that you know I we've got a
Stay in the present for Sunday I should go
What is probably going to have some
Something something
I thought for sure this Matt gaetz Fenwick
Continue as Matt Gates has
Has had more information
Can come out
It looks worse and worse I thought that Alex would either have to double down and triple down
Or he'd have to cut bait
I didn't know what he was
Going to do and
So I was like well I think in the interest of keeping people up
Up-to-date on the
That the goings-on of this
I did get in there
Here we are here we got it we got a new lockstep document
Because you know I think I think sometimes one of the things I enjoy the most about doing this
The opportunity to understand
And something like
This document
That scar causes such fear
4 people
Like to be able to
To see this
Freddy Krueger it on paper right
I understand it for what it is
Understand
Like some of the very interesting lesson
That actually could have been learned in nn
You know that the people are doing these these kinds of exercises that probably
Enough
Of the Lessons Learned on a granular level in terms of some people being able to better
I deal with the challenges
The came up over the course of this
This pandemic right is probably helped a lot
Right
Yeah
I appreciate that I like getting
Yeah this is a little bit like if Jamie Lee Curtis was running away from Michael Myers the whole time
Time and then at the end it was like
Lady I've been
Trying to deliver you this letter
From 15 years ago
This was a complete waste
2 time for everyone involved
Why are we here I honestly enjoy
Having my time wasted like this
Are boars and I enjoyed
Sounds like you're having fun running away from Michael Myers you know you're not just sitting at your home being like this is always hot.
Calories burning
That's good stuff so thank you Alex
I don't look forward to him
Constantly bringing up this document
Cuz it's a big old
But you know Hey whenever these things happen
And it's often good for us to spend time looking at it before 8
Gets too out of
Yeah
Could stand to have Traction in other other communities
Are conspiracies faces
Hopefully Tucker
Covers
That would be funny
Hi hubby
Anyway
Wheeler back Jordan
Will we
Yeah we will but
We.com
We're also on Twitter
We are attorneys and I wasn't ready to go to bed Jordan
Also on the fake social media app from the scenario on eco
We are on I-80 going to be like today if you could please find a local charity
Bellefonte deteriorated
People doing God's
Text Clark I'm Daryl rundus
Holding
Alex
Kristen color with huge fan I love your work