Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge
Knowledge fight
Acknowledge
Nick.com
Recognize right I'm damn
Looks around ignelzi Beverages and talk a little bit about Allie
Alex June
Indeed we are.
Quick Quack
What's up
My brakes today Jordan
Finally got an appointment to get a vaccine thank you
It's been I've been past due in terms of like the grouping
Find a place
I swear I can go get a shot
And I finally asked people are listening to this
Comes out on Friday is that true
Tomorrow
To get my shots
I'm excited about that
Chapter of Life are free
Excavating
B b b
I don't know if there's going
To be you do any kind of side effects like a fever or
To give myself the weekend for
Self-addressed recuperation
Episode I will actually come out on when
We're going to push that back
Just for the sake of
Safety better-safe-than-sorry at Eldora
It's baby be overly cautious from time to
I want to I want to be like that image of my parents
Thought I was doing when I stayed home from school sick
Watching The Price is Right like everybody else does
Sipping soup
Little boy cat on boat
Set my
Resume my app
You got it
That's exciting
My bright spot Dan is godspeed You black Emperor
Yeah you're telling me
And it is
So good
They're on like
Almost
25 years of the band or something there in
Credible
It's fantastic
They still got it
I feel like you and I were supposed to do something and you couldn't because you had to listen to the outside working
Hey work
Can't get done diary I would that look I would love to help out at the album so I'm going to have to
Listen to this 40-minute open
I understand
Today we have an interesting little bit to go over I don't know if you've been able to keep
Unaware of
Some of the news
Alright so we'll get into some of that
Hello
What was great
First person
How to pronounce that
Radio
Also we're kind enough
Mentioned that it keeps tell me about
I know that that's coming up in Oklahoma all kinds of weirdos
Speaking
Ant-Man
I want to go
I believe Mike Adams is giving us all I really would like to go but I don't think
Going to be able to make it but anyway thank you video
Paw Patrol
Next
Thank you so much and I'll probably want
I'm a policy wonk
This person also wanted me to give a shout out to the knowledge Fighters
Apparently this Discord
The server is called
There's apparently a place where I live
Congregates in chat
I've heard it's a lot of fun
Just now finding
Next Justice pronounce
Thank you very much my dude that is our rallying cry again
EBay executive Journal policy walk
Next
Edgar Edgar thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk very much
Gordon Kerr
I think they said that they wanted me to
Mispronounce
Zapruder's Earth
Brodozer Rose Dozer
Dozer
Only hear that Branigan in my headset that's what I got
Text Jackie
Definitely killed his daughter Chuck Norris wasn't wearing a wig thank you so much you an apology walk
And finally I like to give a shout out to
Trademark
Journal
Money off that heroin
Is freakishly large
S***
I forgot the name of
Are the Donald I really hope that he really wanted to get a get out there
Jordans
Snooze
I've been already
To go back to 2000
I'm 34 today's episode having fun
Learning about the past and what-have-you last-minute all my plans
You got thrown into whack
Alex went down the borders looking for a soul to steal
Costing somebody
I was transporting some children possibly recklessly in the back of a station wagon
Alex and maybe it was more of a van I don't know I don't know car
Types
Anyway Alison is associated with the guy driving the car about how he's been
Smuggling people sure and it is
A huge mass
I don't know what all the details of the situation are at this point but I do know that I don't believe for a second that Alexandra's dumb Posse found someone
Smuggling children casually
I'm going to wait to dig into this
Until there's a little bit more public information
Can because I can see this going to couple different direction
And honestly Alex better keep his
Fingers crossed because it looks like a couple things in that video that he released
Could be crimes
He's sitting there banging that like on the roof of a car trying to physically stop it from leaving
Which could be a problem
He is
Acting in ways that some might interpret as defamatory
Irene
Does a little bit sound like Alex Jones just started attacking Clark Griswold on the way
Theme park
I'm not illegal
Expert but it really looks like his videos an open-and-shut case of defamation against
What's the charity that is allege
Be involved
In this muggle
This is
Catholic Charities RGV address and signs
Clearly shown in the video that's on the accusation is
Very clear from Alex's actions
Is essentially a front
For smuggling
This organization is he Catholic
Charities of the Rio Grande Valley and the specific building that Alex was staking out was
The humanitarian crisis Relief Center
They began operating Last Summer
According to their website this is the at the Sacred Heart Catholic Church
To McAllen Texas
And quote
The center provides a place for the countless men women and children and intron refugees to rest
Have a 1
Mila shower and change it to clean clothing
As well as receive medicine and other supplies
Continuing on their Journey
So Alex was like
Quick someone's acting christ-like destroy them
If you look into the specific charity becomes a little interesting that Alex would do this one
Want to focus on
The organization was started by a nun named sister Norma pimento
Who was a very
Pearson critic public critic
Of Trump's border policy
She was also a vocal opponent of Obama's policies but that probably doesn't matter to Alex
She wrote an op-ed in the Washington Post
In February 2020 titled cook
President Trump don't
Ignore the suffering at the border caused by your polish
In 2019 she was invited to participate in what was called a Roundtable
Conversation about issues at the border
Withdrawn himself
Called
Back in the habit I believe
Sister pimental was disappointed by what she experienced
As she discussed in an interview with Texas monthly
Ask every single person at the table
To say something
And I realize that when they were speaking
They were just reaffirming
What it was that he had talked about in congratulating
I realize that the Roundtable was about listening to and reaffirming his
Plant
He didn't really give local people an opportunity to say any
Anything that isn't surprise
Very recently in March 2021 she was featured in an article in the Rio Grande
Guardian
It begins like this
The executive director of Catholic Charities of the Rio Grande Valley
Thanks
God for President Biden
Decision to reverse the Trump
Administration's migrant protection protocols policy
Sister Norma Pimentel
It's God's plan
Do you have a request of unaccompanied minors
From Central America
Carefully processed in the United
Sure
Mere days ago on April 4th
Sister pimento was interviewed on Face the Nation where she discussed how Biden's changes
The Trump's policies
I've trained
Games for work
Okay so you're saying that a
Few days ago
Just a few days perhaps even
One or two days before this incident occurred
Play around
The person who
Began or or started the very charity
That Alex
Accosted
And defamed
Who is a longtime public critic of Trumps policies
For the sake of
They are giving it up
For morale
Clarity
Obama's policies
It is a Critic of these new policies not going far enough
But inasmuch as they are representative of progress
Areas
Right if she works in
OMG it's congratulatory
You are just told me is that this was a
Completely extemporaneous event
Alex was wandering around
End
Purge The Cult
The action
No but you're actively ran to stop this human trafficking from a Keurig
Totally believe he doesn't know any of this
I actually cared only believe that two could totally be a coincidence
I was looking into this charity and like trying to understand a little bit more about it like all the
These things like this is a person who
Someone who Alex absolutely would.
Despise
But at the same time I can
Totally see this just being a situation where
He went
To McAllen Texas
Was hanging out outside waiting for the Optics
X2b rice Penny created
Here we go
Yeah that sounds about right
Federal doesn't go to court
Because I think you can make a pretty compelling case
That's a Alex
Has a reason
To have animus
Storage
This organ
Innovation based on
Are political
I'm struggling to live in a world where a judge might disagree with me on what is
Is very clearly an open and shut case I don't like living in a world where a judge is like
So I don't really care to deconstruct
This video of Aiden of it
Just Alex yelling at a guy in a car
On April 8th
The Catholic Charities release
Statement hoping to clarify the various defamatory claims
It's made by Alex
There's box makes total sense
The only thing that guy
The only thing that I think is missing is a threat of legal action
Yeah but again this is up to everybody
To deal with on their own terms and decide whether they want to go
Through that rigmarole and that
Public embarrassment
Oh yeah I would
I wouldn't wish that on my worst
Mom
Nevermind I do I would wish that on my worst enemy I wouldn't wish whatever the person suing
He would have to go through all the
I understand why some people are
Reluctantly
Totally but boy this seems like a
A pretty easy cake shouldn't shouldn't take shouldn't take too long.
I can't imagine Alex giving a
Blustery speech about how he'll fight this or die and then a week later issuing a public apology to him
Nuns doing all their business
The nuns are good people
Did you see Sister Act 2 back to the habit
Video In-N-Out
Itself might be interesting to see what happens on the 8th
This is you know this
Thursday the
This is after he's
Had the
Social media flare-up for this video
Punjab
Yeah I wanted to see where you was at on that the short let's see what happens or contacts drop from this year
And if anybody
The good guy in Ukraine
They've been killing each other for so long Eastern or Western
Ukraine
It's a it's like the Badcock & McCoys
What
Is anybody the bad guy in Ukraine
Is a
Dark
What you're focusing on a different heart than Ibuprofen
What to do with the half dachshund The McCoys
I just heard that and stroked out
I know the people misspeak and whatever I'm at a contact drop first of all
And second of all
Anything that Alex is Persona should know a lot about
Fascism
Yes
Man I want to start a game called to have Cox
And just never explain the name
I'm sure people are just like what it what is it called in the half
Cocci
To get windbreakers
Related to this conversation entirely
Steph
We're going to start here on April 8th
It seems like Alex is leaving
About the Border this video
The alarm Belzer
China has now with air
Scriptures over 100 shift
Lordship thousand total
Encircle Taiwan
Heavy bombers flying over it
Taiwan East say they may start
Firing missiles any minute
That was this morning
Last night there
All hell is breaking loose
Russians are massing troops on the edge of Ukraine because Biden sending and heavy weapons
And there are major artillery battles going on
We are not the
SMS
So we got we got to World War
Together here
Marion
Nicole mind seems to be the lion
But Alex
Taking that which I find interesting because
Couple days prior he was
Really going hard on the
Sparse documentary
Right right right
And now it's World War
This is it this is
Music
What I am hearing while he speaks is the advice of a lawyer in his are going
Don't explain
Anything about that
Talk about you talk about it
You remember what happened with the million-dollar Bounty do you remember I mean you're wrong about that but it isn't
It's weird that he start
What's the show like that
Corsage
So if there's a lawyer in a zrt
Forget about it very quickly. They're at all times of the reasons that Alex
Is going on and starting his shows or the leading with this idea of that world war and all the
Is because that day a bike was giving
Speech
About
Skunk
Controlled regulation ideas sure and
Borin
Those
Sex
I'll make more clear what I mean a little bit later as we go through
But the beginning of their show in a large
Portion of
At the top of it is
Alex playing Biden speech
And then just a Ramblin over it
Thanksgiving the courage
Fast and Furious killed
Done running
It sat for awhile it's pretty annoying
Eight sides
It's a little annoying
He keeps insisting that fast and furious as the Silver Bullet that will take down the
Obiden Administration how long do
To take to get there I seems like that should have happened way early
He kept calling by nobama
Batman
Together for a while he's in calling itself restaurant
I keep calling about Obama's cuz it's AB to run it was right there
It was right there
To get there
This is Alex doing his
His level best
Stop being Rush
Is terrible company they can't even
Pickup
Found joke
I would say that if Alec
Six-word to get sued
Over this video where
He has been
But in my opinion probably
Defaming this charity
One of his best
Defenses might be that like
Not many people saw it you know it's no big
Big deal
Unfortunately here he is bragging
What happened yesterday
We put out the video
Look up Leafly
At the login repeal off
Great job they've done and then there's
Catholic Charities
McAllen Texas
And they are loading little kids Han
Luggage
We stopped them illegal take them out
I don't think you will
Forthcoming
I will see though how many people saw this which works against ooze
Eventual probable argument that he's going to need to make
Yeah he's he's
But then again if he doesn't get sued
There's no legal trouble then I guess
Yep
Anyway Alex has this
Bee in his Bonnet about the idea that people are saying that he staged this whole thing
You went down to the border and he staged
It seems like he didn't like
Capture a coyote
Has found people who
Doing exactly what they said they were going
To be doing
And then how does
Literally dozens of national newspaper said
I'm probably stage this there are no crises
McAllen Police
The trunk
Xan
Joe Rogan going to pay for it
Top directors out there
Alex couldn't think of One Direction
Spielberg now he's a globalist Scorsese now he's a global intern Tina I hate it
Rian Johnson
The fan of The Last Jedi what else do we still bitter that I wasn't in Guardians of the Galaxy
Clint Eastwood probably
The media didn't say that
About Alex April 7th
I couldn't
Find like any media Outlet even really covering this
Publicity stunt
The actual video of Gateway pundit
What the word bunch of random people tweeting
About it I think that Alex was just pretending
Tweet saying that he probably stage the videos the same thing is
Dozens of media Outlets
The national newspapers covering it
What is New Media other than
It's going National man
I think I've come up with
Situation and that is
Random tweet
Plus narcissism equals
Literally doesn't professional newspaper
What's going on
So Alex is saying that everybody saying that he's just made this up and he
Staged
1009 radio
Albertville to Birdman
And everybody said that he was make
Get it up
And the New York Times said
Did not exist
Schizophrenic breakdown
In the parking lot
Bilderberg
Was all over the news
Bought it two years ago I didn't believe it it's just
Looks like a stroke
But
Exposed all that
So f******
Can stupid
A quick search will disprove the idea that the media claimed the Bilderberg didn't
Exist until 2008/2009 earlier when Alexandra
Disposal
Princeton's Thursday September 2005 article in the BBC titled quote
Inside the secretive Bilderberg Group
Or you could look at
Did John Ronson's 2001 book them adventures with a
Extremists
Excerpts of which
Were published
In the guardian
And it was accompanied by the release of his TV show secret rulers of the world featured in episode where he at
Alex Jones go to Bohemian Grove
No the other episode of it was about the Bohemian the Bilderberg Group
No tweet
There's also a reference
To the Bilderberg meetings in a 1999 wired article you can easily find alright alright
What Alex said that the media said that he was imagining the whole thing what do you mean is that no one
Accepted his imaginary framing of real life event
People didn't say that the meeting or the group
Itself didn't exist
Just at the stories that Alex was selling his audience about them didn't
Stand up to scrutiny
That's the accusation
Nothing made up of the Bilderberg
Excuse me Alex
You're full of s*** can mean many different things
Also I'd like to learn more about how the Drudge Report was secretly sold
The CNN 2 years
Sounds like another thing that Alex is pulling out a fitting f****** are about that did you
Did you look
Deep into that
You didn't did you reach out to Drudge
For comment I looked for
Tax filing
Nonsense
What is overlap.
Between this idea of like
When people are accusing Alex
Taking stuff out there not talking about like
Like the actual event
Video that he shot down
Same thing
You didn't make up
That someone got in a car
You're just lying about the surrounding
9/11 was an inside job you're full of s*** you don't think 9/11 happened
Obviously
You may have actually said it didn't happen at some
I got to review all the tape
So when Alex is making these accusations obviously
But there are certainly ways that he could make the situation worse
Decides
To do in this next billion-dollar
Irwin
And
If I had the money cuz we're maxed out right now
McCowan and in Brownsville
Idiot Wild Wild West
Insane illegals everywhere you go buses everywhere you go
We send a drone in there they had a geofence stops we couldn't show them in the dirt but probably croissants that folks in there we have
Children being rape inside the facility we broke that on Monday
About it I mean
Helicopter
Flowers flowers flowers display
And that's why you need to go to infowarsstore.com
We can stay on here
Wow
Has
Infowars
R6S
So you understand why you
Radio station
Better like
Missionary
There's something a little bit disgraceful about using this as a like directly as a fundraising
Holding your audience hostage yeah it also will be difficult
Look for Alex were somebody to sue them for that
28mm to argue that he's not using it in order to make money
Because I did literally what he's doing here
And as far as the criminal malicious intent towards the Border
Saying
I'm not going to tell the system how or when I'm going to get their names like admitting to a certain amount of suspicious activity
Know if you want to escalate this evening
Further
Alex has a great idea for you
And that is one of his old
I have to tell you ladies and gentlemen
Anybody
I don't care about the school
It Ben Shapiro wanted to go down to but
Tucker Carlson
You'll sit there
You can't swing a stick
Check in the dark and not it Smugglers down there
There is a sense
Alex is giving off that is like you should go
We're all going is going to be a great big fat goes down there will immediately find proof
Illegal
Human trafficking ring
And you need to know how all these people say white in French
Spearhead the
The nerve to do it
You could get the scoop I don't care about getting the scoop
Everyone to go YouTube
That's a bad thing
To do when your when your escalating people's suspicions and believe that they're fighting the literal.
Pulmonology
To such a height
Points and I'll be like all are you all should go down there you'll find
Direct evidence
Pensive all this.
For trouble
He has every single time of the past
Like here's the thing about you know you don't want to get into like slippery slope argument with restrict
Acting speech of course
So what I think we should do
Is Right a very very narrow law
That puts out
Step-by-step what Alex did
For pizzagate and that is like you just can't do that
All of that stuff you can't do it and then Alex wouldn't be able to do this s***
Always gets a little bit muddy is it like every time
Horrible outcome like a shooting
But
We have proof
Yeah. Doing the things that live there
You
Going to or have bun
Inspiring people to go
Terrifying app
Have you really
Any consequences
Exactly
I would say you've been in
Rewarded
Exactly
Anyway
Choked
I don't spend a lot of time on this episode talking about
Trying to take the guns
Guys fighting has some ideas about it is a little bit
Terrifying the prospect
Acts of
Well you know being able to get kit
Where you can make a gun
None of the parts have any kind of serial number how do they back boobie on
Untraceable guns it's blade something
In the wrong hands
Could lead to a lot of trouble also the ability to adjust
You know
Buy gun
Guns on the internet I mean they traced f****** cold medicine
I'm not the biggest
Sport in the world
When I was listening to the idea that
Didn't sound like anything that we
2 terrifying
Find
But anyway Alex
Try not to strangle
Use bident
4A
Provide specific reason
Civil War
This will trigger Civil War
There you go that's what's up
Everybody else
This doesn't make any sense
Now the global is plan is to start a civil war
At the behest of
China for some reason and that's going to
I guess kill a lot of people
I thought the plan was sucked killing everyone with vaccines and then having an orderly extermination and if that doesn't work then their plan B was
Broly Super bio weapons
Just to kill everyone off
Yeah but that was last week
How did the Civil War or World War fit into that planning
Exactly like
How is gun regulation apart of the bio-weapon
Can plan it would be a really dumb Civil War to have it
Like while you're fighting it half
Of your army is just going to drop dead from the vaccine at any moment
It seems like
The plan was these bio weapons of the globalist
Didn't care if you have guns
Eschewed a virus
I kept this clip in to illustrate have none of Alex's narratives mean anything
Everything is self-serving and meant to escalate whatever he's decided to make his audience afraid of that
Day
In this case Biden
Giving a speech on gun reform ideas and dust
The thing the prophet up making the listener scared of
His gun confiscation
That narrative doesn't really match up with the whole thing out has been doing the vaccine fear-mongering
You can't really say that the gun regulation is part of the whole biome
Darcy pretends that this isn't the entire thing he's been ranting about forever
War that we need to be scared about it's the summer rain dance
Also if all Alex's enemies were working for the literal devil it seems like they wouldn't be all on such
Different ages
Like if the devil had this plan that they were supposed to be trying to carry out why would China mess around with Taiwan
When I could only really get in the way of following through on the larger plan
That seems really weird and I would love Alex takes
Explain what it is so it's
What it is it's a Japanese
Please management strategy that the that the devil is using here alright you have many different divisions and you don't share
All the information because they're all working
For the same end goal but
They've got their own strategies it's how you create
New solutions to problems Dan
I feel like the devil this devil to be
Singularly folks
Just on one objective
I don't know if
There would be a need for teams to be working across purpose at you haven't been reading Japanese van
Benjamin model you do make a fair point
Sunnyway b 14 gun
Sure
He said that he wanted red flag laws
But that didn't happen so weird
I was being sneaky and it was
Porsche
About the red flag laws
We got Biden saying
Anybody about you your guns are gone
How's the time
Civil War civil war Civil War
So this is how Alex wants to remember Trump's comments on red flag laws but that's not what Trump said
This was in 2019 after the mass shootings in Dayton and El Paso
Trump
First we must do a better job of identifying an accident on early warning sign
I'm directing the Department of Justice to work in partnership with local state and federal
Media companies
To develop tools looking
Can detect Mass Shooters before they strike
That doesn't sound like a judicata someone is mentally ill that seems like
Talkin to like social media taking the post
Social media to identify people who may be on well and then getting their guns taken away
Almost like Alex thinks
Reality is whatever
Fits his narrative in it
Honestly would Trump was talking about
Way more invasive than
Draconian anything that
Trump lied on
We must reform our mental health laws to better identify mentally Disturbed individuals who may commit acts of violence
And make sure those people not only get treatment but when necessary involuntary
Confinement
Seems like Alex should be against that pretty
Strongly
These people have not committed any
Any crimes but because some globalist doctor is saying that they might commit one we should have laws that they get locked up
Pre-crime a truck wants to bring in the guys in the cat Tom Cruise movie cogs in the mission
Visionworks
Boris
Trump continue quote
We must make sure that those judged
Suppose a grave risk
The public safety do not have access to firearms and if they do those Firearms could be take
Come to Rapid due process
That is why I have called for red flag laws also known as
Extreme risk protection order
Today I'm also directing the Department of Justice to propose legislation
Ensuring that Those who commit hate crimes and mass murders face the death penalty
And it has capital punishment be delivered
Decisively in without years of needless delay
Yeah
I have a Libertarian type
Open someone who's insanely anti-government
Alex should be really afraid of a president calling
Expedited Desitin
Especially since Alex thinks
Most people who commit mass shootings are secretly Patsy
Also that was the speech where Trump said quote
May God bless the memory of those who perished
Toledo
And may God protect
Because you misread a teleprompter
Shooting was a
Hey way the point of this is that Alex has created an ageist oracle version of Trump's response
The mass shootings in his public support
Red flag laws
Because what tribe advocated is directly counter to a lot of what
Make sense as Alex
It's kind of messy
I think it's
Easier to hand wave it away and say the past is the past
So let's move on and think about the future Trump as a president anymore
We don't need to think about all the stuff he's
He said it
Even sputtered through that in that's what we don't learn from history here
That's not deal with what was said realistically about
Have fun
Who do you think
The world's most
Powerful.
The world's most powerful doctor
Doom
Sure
He has his own country
Exactly he's pretty powerful I don't think he's very
Rich's house I think you really cheated the game there
Has lightning powers right
Super stretch man to the doctor to he's more powerful
This is why people think that I don't get I'm not amused by think you said I was just laughing really hard but silently
Naturally
Superwoman was a doctor to write
I'm not doing well today
I'm not even a dork and I know these names
Honestly I was going to call her mrs. invisible
She married to him
I think so
Military guy
I think the Thing and Human Torch word like
This is like this card is beyond.
Military guys and then Invisible Woman and Reed Richards
Where doctors
Still dr. do more powerful away
You know it
My point is that if you Google it you'll get a different
Who runs the UN
Who is the most powerful doctor in the world
Who is the most powerful it says Bill Gates
Powerful.
He is in charge and he will do what
He will to you
So this is actually true
If you Google the words
Who is the world's most powerful doctor the results
D'usse Bill Gates
This is because the Search terms identically reflect the title of a 2017 Politico article titled quote
Meet the world's most powerful dr. Phil
It's okay
The article itself is highly critical of gators outsized influence on the World Health
Organization
Has a major donor
But it's not critical in the same way that Alex might be
For instance the article points out that quote
Rather than focusing on strengthening Healthcare in poor countries that would help in their View
To contain future outbreaks
Ebola epidemic
The agency spends at this
Proportionate amount of its resources on project with a measurable outcome
The gates
Prefers
Such as the effort to eradicate polio
I don't like the fact that this Google search result comes up
It's a web
Flight Enviro recently
As it has in the past a couple times
I was probably just about on social media now he's
Complaining about
Michele watches
Really sad
Read the Politico article has he would recognize that
Actually would be like
This is
Kind of critical is gay
That that kind of doesn't work
Yeah
It really seems
Far too obvious
To say that a billionaire shouldn't have anything
To do with
Just about any decision
Regarding
Well
Especially
Health in the modern world
Yeah I think it's a complicated question and I think that
Based on the fact that there are political articles like this there are people in the appropriate places ask
Can go sort of quest
And wrestling with it
Anyway
Because Alex has found this Google search result that he thinks
The real cool
You let himself off
The chain in a little bit
Powerful doctor in the world
I'm going to kill your ass Bill Gates
Meet the world's most powerful doctor
And for
Search results Italia
Call Laura
Family Shelter
Family Show
I'm going to put it in yet
Not something that I want
Repeated anywhere Nas and it's not fun
So title
Is ironic
Or sarcastic at least
With the world's most powerful doctor Bill Gates yes he's not a doctor that's the point of
The title you said this is not
Exactly
He's picking at you
Sarcastic headline literally
I just wanted to be sure about
You good
Reading comprehension is he
Jam
Someone else is good at
Like guitar
And being a real creep I don't know if he
Google is it though
Things
Looks collar I don't know anything about this
Nugent on the show
I got to say
Uncle Ted sounds like a
A bit more of a lunatic
Then usual
This is an incredible time to be alive but I'm glad
Ted Nugent is there
Always saying that seriously
Priorities
I think we should quote
The greatest philosopher of all time
Dirty Harry
When he said a good man knows his limitations
Against the curse of self-inflicted
Creature that
Commander-in-chief is crazy
The Nugent
Family is living the American dream
He always sounds like he's on coke
But he claims he's 70 years sober
My immediate
Thought was he got about
Halfway through sentence
And I was like whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa you just slow it down there already
Going a little too fast to be taken serious
It's like yeah
Sounds nuts
He doesn't live in the Motor City anymore
Part-time
Wild somewhere in Michigan
Making this metaphor
It's pain
I think
I think in this metaphor Old Yeller is the
Okay
So you're lucky you're setting this up
As we're going to take a long trip
To get to you and Elizabeth if you back
Cambridge showing in our are suing me
You know it's a war
Has been hidden from Generations
When Old Yeller for
Texas from The Cougar
Old Yeller brings us the newspaper
We give Old Yeller
Old Yeller
Beginners
We know what we have to do the Old Yeller
Brace
Difficult
Discomforting decisions in life
Of the Germans
What happened side
There are Americans today that are hiding
Everybody believes in Freedom
You have to be a member of the National Rifle Association
Association
Second Amendment organizations you have to communicate with your mayor
Auto weekly
Slow down you are just
Guitar player sir
Throw the United States
Write me to put it down like all the gallery on regulation now
The government just let you have all the guns you want
I would like to know
Ted Nugent interpretation of Romeo and Juliet I would like his explanation is
You might fall in love Panther Maine
K Styles.
Yeah that was weird
Kill the governor
Strange metaphors
Interesting
So Alex has gone and done this possibly defamatory video about this Castle
For charity
Newton I might not want to sign off on that video.
In case I don't get ensnared
I don't want to actually be on
Like public records
Hey that was an awesome
Something you did and I'm glad I helped you playing it with you
Peacefully
Communicate on a regular basis
And all the different incredible
These children
Doing it
He plays dumb
We have to spot
Cockroaches
These devil cockroaches
This is not good
This is very not good
That's not
A couple of
Is clearly talking about Alex's.
Absolutely there's a couple of huge problems I have with it number one
And obviously is
Ted Nugent
Is not allowed to
Traffic ahead
Traffic
Unaccept
Pitbull Behavior
Animal behavior and I want to know the spelling of demonic
Because immediately following dumb
It should be dumb onic right dumb
Yeah minutes on paper properly
So is God jumping from Zaire
Is endorsing Alex's video we got to flush out these
These folks the demon
How are you
Started saying it didn't need to kill people who are like the people at Alex's video
Dedicated
To save
These devils
Q4 that they're more more people
You can't identify
Told me that the mouth
Dogs
Then go back to your garden
You have to deal with the rabid dogs you have to eliminate the rabid dog
Collier Wildlife Control
Call somebody
Set metaphor Fowler Park
Yeah
I think
We're listening to
Ted Nugent
Taking these sort of ideas that Alex had about everybody's got to go down to the Border
He's going one step further it right you have
To take action
Against the people who are traffic
And a boy
You know that
Get really out of
If your standard of whose trafficking people is as low
Alex's
This is this
This is directly inside and see this is really f***** up
Do a pizzagate it's against the law
He was just talkin about literal dogs about a dog has
What is pi
Have like some stuff on your glasses and then you just
Is murder a dog
Maybe you should think a little bit more I can't stress enough how like
I saw that video
Like this song
But you know this is Alex doing what he does
I hope you get sued for it
He's kind of encouraging people to go and do what he's doing it
I think that probably bad that seems like
Kind of behavior
You've done in the past
Nothing could have prepared me for Ted Nugent
Coming on
And making this pained metaphor that he's so much worse
It seems to imply that what people need to do
It's come down there
And kill people
Who are trying to help
Asylum Seekers and refugees
F***** up yeah I don't know if there's any
Thing that could prepare you for a sudden appearance of Ted Nugent telling you to murder
In a bad metaphor
That's it that's that's something that I
How to Kool-Aid Man levels of surprise
Now much like the Kool-Aid man he barges through walls
Also you know that
We're about to get someone else barging through walls
And that is
Ted Nugent
Sun
Sure actually do
Talk to him a little bit
Here we go
Rocco I don't know your particular person in your own right
The great son of Ted Nugent what what is your view on all this
Physical aspect
The terrestrial
Who's really behind the cabal
Lacking energy
They're installing slaughterhouses that are
Yasso Rocco
Ted Nugent son is in
Spiritual side of this another new laws I should be against the law to grow up rich
What I heard right there
No
So I wanted to understand a little bit more I never heard
Ted
Son I've never
That's fun
Thank you so ever
This guy's Modern Life
Hahaha apparently
Consists of putting out YouTube videos
Are you driving while you're driving
This was terrified
Hello
The download to be shared today in this phone
Wow
The highways being driven on
Is a message that just came through
The reference point many know as Archangel Michael and my
Archangel Michael
He's almost been like the older brother that that you didn't really know because like you were really
Young when he was at home and then he left for like the military or something
Then you like grew up and then he came back he's all Western
Transform and then he leaves and never comes again and so it seems like this
Discipline
Bigger brother a dead bolt to your Highest Potential
He has this sword at least in my interfacing with them he has a sword that he carries around with them
A sort of light and it seems Seems also be a sword of the Divine
Elaine personified in
Any device in a moment as a sword to predict
Everything
I believe he's saying that
The Archangel Michael has a lightsaber shaped like a penis is essentially what I'm hearing
YouTube song put that videos where he Rambles about how he talks
What's the angels
Yeah
Cool
Wow okay so
Spirituality that is kind of
Untethered
And a little bit Project Camelot
That older brother who went away
Join the military and then came back to you and also has a giant lightsaber sword that looks
Like a dick he gave him a download download spoiler alert
The greatest fomo if you're missing out
No the Grado
No you do not know you do not
Continue series
The greatest fomo
Is missing out you could have been if you didn't get
Get your s*** together earlier
Really really
Really need to
To throw a thing
Archangel Michael
Blow Minds
I was thinking like okay I can play some more things
Things from these videos that are just kind of silly that just kind of
Kind of
Content
Is the kind of stuff that I'm like
I got to go I got to get away from there
Better I could tell you
And that is
The Ted Nugent son is also a rapper
No no
Oh God
I had lost my face
Hello
Myself
Windows
With that I
Yeah I found that is a little bit to make a compelling argument for there being
Too much autotune
Yeah yeah that's that's
Definitely the man
How much would it suck to not even suck as much
Is Chet Hanks
Slug that's bad I feel really bad because I don't want to like
Mock someone's creative Outlet
That's bad
But also I want a Moc rich kids out
Creative app
But I'm fine with that
I mean I think that this is not Quality Music
Not. Even the best
Worst son
That's the worst part about it man
Morocco
And his Modern Life
Yep
They leave
The Nugent family leave
Prince wife is a really
Qanon support
Good Times
So I believe
Lights
A literal Campbell
But maybe it's also a metal
I'm being honest and listeners are the metaphysical 3090 God's real
Fire on yourself you got to share with other people like
The panel
Lighting here in studio
On TV and radio with a simulcasting
America's Plano
Republic Supply Mound
I can't do it we continue to share
But if they're able to realize this and make it speak
They don't have
Power to do that anymore
Alex is becoming more and more of a prop
Yeah
Yeah so he's doing like one of those
Christmas candles where you only burn it for the let you know it's like red green red green red green and every day before
You burn the red one off
And then you turn it out
And then you burn the green one up
But it's for the end of the Republic
Something like that
Yeah I just like
You know what he had that skull and
Yeah
Goblet or whatever
And I'm asking you what is this
Because I want to talk about
The metaphor of a candle but I also want you to be able to see it
I just
Become yours Bowman
Before this where he screamed at some
18 year old
Get me a candle
No problem
Pretty good chance
It's not really covered a lot of news
But he has a lot of articles in a
Sackbut
Who cares
Read articles
A little piece of it
Talk about our works
About a Howitzer deployment
You get caught
Forget your God by giving it all your attention
Whatever comes out of these
People's miles is myth
Kill your ass
Wow decision.
What you need to know is that I need you emotionally aroused at all times but if you learn
Anything that will stop
I don't think
Think that there's any better encapsulation of Alex Jones's
Stars 02 style than that
Spend an hour on this the information all the
Pokemon new to get really into the Wii
Ewok
Yeah we can really get into this but just know that whatever they're saying they're trying to
Really there's no point for me to have
Any of this in front of
So instead
Nopales
Call CY
What you could do
Roanoke or trying to kill you
Instead of
The weeds and really figuring this out
He decides
Spend his time
Course means complaining about Saturday Night Live
We never are.
What is the ID for Saturday
But but they're like
Coming up on Saturday Night Live
Black people won't take the vaccine
Do they have a black guy with a British accent like he's smart
Black people aren't
Pull up
YouTube
Briana Manson on fire
Black people BBQ
In watermelon
Southern Voice
You are no Sully sullenberger
Literally them
Pictures making fun of black people
With a black guy with a British accent
The big races to them
Because of their acts different when they are saying they're fighting racism
These people
Pierced me off man
What
Okay
So
One did you see that I said I'll sketch
I I saw the first little bit
Yeah I got it
You got it
I think there is some people who took umbrage
Rightfully so that was probably a poorly conceived
I think there's people did not enjoy it you can find articles and all
Sort of media
Expressing that Center
Maybe poorly can
Instructed
And conceived
Alex's point about it
Is outrageous
I think he was trying to say that it was a racist sketch but he did so by being
More racist towards
Yeah yeah
Person who's hosting
Hallelujah
Yes
He's not doing the British accent in that sky
He's not know
Specifically
He's not doing a British accent
Having
I think that what happened is that Alex just saw like
Outraged compilation of like Thomas's jokes from the model
He knows that the guy is British
It carries over to the sketches while would understand how the structure of Saturday Night Live works
No absolutely
If you haven't seen the sketch the idea was
And his family won't take the vaccine
Game show
Why do
Get them to take the vaccine
He keeps offering money
Yeah
The correct answer would be yes
One of his family members played by Keenan
He
He asked what he would do with the money if you want
Johnny says I'll roll up some
Smokes weed or shows of big barbecue block
Rock party going get a new grill
Or whatever and that Alex has extrapolated out into being like
Trying to entice black people with BBQ right watermelon
We even more race that's what I was saying he didn't mean to add the more races fire
You know like you get it because they were creating that caricature that they love
What to do on Celebrity Jeopardy
But what actually happened is they
Relied on
Stereotypes to make fun of
So I think the Alex thinks
That
Because
This sketch
Is clunky
And possibly
Someone defensive
It gives him carte blanche
Do even more race
Give you the Bible
No
Show
Do you black people solving BBQ
This is what I'm talking about
Everything they say we are
Is them
What about fentanyl for Dragon I was going to say also
Kind of sounded like he slipped into fentanyl the dragon there
Accident exit 92 slipped into a racist Chinese accent so that's great
Aliando
Tries to play the clip
Antifa
Heritage
Ready
You guys get pulled up real quick
Computer messes up about 1% of the time
Million-dollar computer
What is locked
Bushwacker
What
YouTube
Backup
You know
You got to restart it I mean it's it look
Get the million-dollar machine but it still runs Hot 100
It doesn't even run on Windows 98
I wonder if like
What actually happened was that there was like
Producer in his ear during that long silence is like
Hey there
Those voices that you're doing in the way your characterizing his catch if you play the skin
You're going to be shown
You are a race
I wonder if that's what happened
Makes sense
Based on the incredibly long pause
And then eventually they do play what Atwood I think is
Be outraged compilation that he's on
The only thing that he's aware of
Right which is the clips of the monologue and then
Short clip of a trial right he's written the story about it in his head
It is more races
Suspend the original
Wild wildly racist
Ria
So at this point
Alex has a reporter named Sheila Gunn Reid
On his show
She is a reporter with
Rebel
Sure sure
Trustworthy
Great yeah she's on to talk about a certain Church
In Canada
For having me Allison Stokke
Your ongoing interest in the story with the Main Street
Believe
This church
The Flash
Point
For Religious Freedom
During the pandemic
Was arrested and incarcerated for
435 days
In a maximum-security
Provincial facility
For refusing to limit his congregation
To 15%
Capacity as per the
Public Health order is
Here in Alberta he refused to comply he said
So he was taken into custody
He's been released
Has not stopped
So this is the grace Life Church
And Alberta
Like Sheila was saying the pastor this church Dreamcoat was arrested
In February after repeated breaches of covid safety measures
He was given multiple opportunities and Warner
To follow the rules and they refused
To do so
So he got arrested and then released on
The condition that he stop breaking the rules
Which immediately preceded the break
Literally everybody involved was like
Dude we don't want to do this
Well obviously you want to turn yourself into a f****** martyr in response to his trouble
A group of 28 Community leaders from various religious backgrounds released a statement that quote stressed the need to pry or
Vertise the well-being of all members of society over individual needs during the pandemic
Had to follow the directives of Public Health officers and the
Someone acting crazy
Tell them
Jeff this week
The Alberta Health Service shut down the church by putting fences up around it
Until the church
Demonstrate the ability to comply with Alberta's chief medical officer of Health
Do you hear what they said that you are timeout put you in time out
Till you can eat your goddamn vegetables you don't get to go to church use the phone
Prank call people or whatever
Are they closing the churches
Kind of murky territory honestly and I'm not sure how I would proceed if I were in charge there but this is
Is Canada
If a local folk there in Alberta a terribly posted is closer than they can work on that with the local
Will government but from everything I've seen
Pretty much everybody outside the church itself seemed
Spine
Yeah
The fact that they do know
You're not going to follow the restrictions they're not even
The restrictions are 15% capacity
Live stream
We don't want to put you in jail they would be stupid this is stupid you're a child
Ways to work this out anyways that work
Look for everybody
15% capacity that he's supposed to follow
But you're not everybody has to
Percent of
But the Walmart
30%
A fire
Or if you're going to
Praise God
This is embarrassing
Pretending to not understand the
Capacities
Four different things
Like I would
Totally back
That Walmart would have a 15% capacity order if it were a place where people
Congregated for long periods of time
Satin Place insane
The things you do at Walmart while you're wearing a mask
Which they didn't do with this
Oh that was released
I assume that they all still warm
No that's required to wear a mask to enter the Walmart
Around
And leave
That's why
Dababy you could have 30%
Capacity there safely as opposed to a building where everyone sits
NSYNC
Yeah that is that is like
Listen
I know the word is supposed
To be mainly Gianna
Madrid-based but you are being
Up to
That is
So Alex gets to talking about his sparse
Conspiracy a little bit I thought he was kind of done with with Sheila and
The church
But he does say this
And I think it's silly
Broadcast world
125 2028 Dodge Demon
2000700
73000 views
Sounds great
I'm not doing
And put my life on the line
Mexican border where they shoot helica
Shoppers
Doing all this
Yeah I think
Illustrative to it's like Alex's gauge of being able to beat the globalist
To do with his meds
Traffic-related we will win if we get 100 million but then you won't Global it's just
Watching The View
S*** he's at 99999999 illusions
Ridiculous
So
I thought it was a little bit irresponsible that Alex is
Largely
At least
Southerleigh
Maybe not-so-subtly
Encouraging people to go down to the border and behave as he did
Yeah
I just took cost
People trying to help. I think that's a
Humanity is generally
Widely-recognized to evolve Society
By killing people trying to help the only effect that that could possibly have is escalating the situation raisins
Temperature beyond the point where
It's easily handled by
Multiple people
This is not the only instance of him doing this on the
Everyone in Canada can get there I said of USB reporters are so controlled
As your legal alien
Everyone should go there
Pizza
Thousand people show up
It will turn the tide against
Don't you agree everyone should come there tell us where it is
That church is just
Just west of the capital city of Edmonton Alberta
A couple of miles outside of the city limits
It's very easy to get
It's theirs
Get there and the landowner
What is the address everyone must go now
It's Grace
Church
Everyone's got to go
I want to go to the church
Christian Woodstock
Haha glad means jars of
Play will be performing sure
Going to reunite
Red Hot Chili Peppers is going to play with just the socks on and engine sun is made of
Yeah it seems irresponsible
It's kind of worse
520 or 5
A Range Road 262
Spruce Grove
Baby
That right
Yes
It's going to be like on cuz you're just like me
The preacher
Okay you're under attack store we
All of us need to go there if you're in Canada
Near the borders getting legally go there peacefully give Aid and comfort
Thunder Tricom
Governor
Pack the chai, agent I just showed you him pledging Allegiance is easy painting
Trudeau
Everyone should go there that they're scared aren't they
Trudeau did no such thing
Yeah it's this is irresponsible and certainly help
Nothing ends up happening
Bear that Alex might
Badin
In hindsight
Giving the address out
Soliciting an inciting people to go because of the church is under attack by the
Communist Chinese and Justin Trudeau
Bucked up
Yeah there's no other way for that it's like it goes two ways
Is it goes with
A bunch of people showing up and being like
Dogshit this
Or a bunch of people showing up and getting whipped into a mob and like let's go down to Miles and start wars
Can literal devil
It seems like the latter is more like
Yes I don't know I don't I don't think
Is good
Obviously
Alex I've never ever seen
Overt satanism
In real life
Good
Satanism like that
As you and I both
Through all kinds of people
This person drones
Bring women and children
Who is church there looking at me
And this guy screams
Churches being closed
And he says to them
Even the church
Follows mask
And that's what you should do
As a Christian
If you're telling me that
Kristen even we wear masks
That's
That's the level of
That she's
Man
This is the weakest of
This is weak. I would even have bought it if she was just like
He screamed out the window I love Satan
Because then it's like yeah of course you say that s*** there seem to be as willing to let it fly
Hi is Alec
No
Do what it do you just like hey guys
Ostensibly you're most
Evil
Worshippers in the world are still
Where's more concerned with Public Health in our fellow man than you
Don't want people to die of disease do you die do not understand
You are in this situation
Satan
Truckin around
That sounds more like
Like that
And all this is going on
Until Alex
Encourages something
He should be careful with his language
I'm telling my listeners I'm showing them
If you live in Canada whether you're 500 Mi away or 20
You must go there bring some muffins bring some food
Support these right people
Because the system is wrong the line here the enemy
Online at your church
Is there Stalingrad
And I think we should make this their Stalingrad
Weeaboo
Chosen this is their Stalingrad
Stalingrad
This is what
Also not for nothing the Soviet Union 1
That battle
The communist
Metaphor
Also Stalingrad wasn't
Incredibly violent
I don't know if Alex wants to evoke
Responsible
Imagery surrounding
What he's trying to incite
People to go be a part of
Yeah I'm going to be I'm going to be honest here
Okay
Here's what I'm putting together on this very episode he said
Literally like
Everything
Everything they say we're doing is what they're doing
Right right
Now I would say that that is revelatory about what he's doing
End
I'm going to say that he worships Satan because this is the only no no no no no
I think it I don't think he stopped
That's the long-term theory of yours
This episode is really
There is
Multiple incitements
Yeah words
The Listener is going to
Two places
Better Alex
Seems to want to
Get out of here
Yeah
A little bit
S******* pastor of that church I would be like Alex no no no no no we don't know what that
Support
But you're the
Your bad support
Really honestly
You know Sheila wants to
Bring up it
This could all be
Solve this
All the Pastors in the area where
Against this guy in the area
Isn't this church
Sacrifices
Mozart
God knows it
No boy
These are World Council of churches
Rockefeller pants
So this is
What point of the episode where I was sort of Lost
Thought
Started
Interesting thought
Experiment
Rhetorical question
Sure do you think
Did Alex Jones good name of Living member of the Rockefeller family
Absolutely not
0% chance
Pretty good now
I do like that this this also
Please into what should be very obvious to anybody is if it weren't for
Immigration and racism
Christians would be murdering each other left and right they hate each other
They don't believe the same s*** they're all nonsense
Well I mean like there are letter of the 28th religious leaders
In Alberta that they were all
Like I come on
But seriously take this seriously
Even the Church of Satan is with that letter was delivered from a truck
It's rare that you get you know the Chris
Jin Muslim
Buddhist
Communities
Walking
Arm in arm
But this church
Is enough of a pain in the ass
Oh my God guys
What's a bad name
Alex is trying to get people to go
XXX Church
Be there Stalingrad
Someone stalling
Anybody
In order for this to sound better
If you want
Sheila
What to do it
Tell everybody to go that
Absolutely somebody else in your crime
Is Alec copes
Copy what I said
5000 people tomorrow at ten thousands weekend
They jump the shark
Call Eureka.
Beautiful beautiful soul
Oh my God.
If people are going to come to support
Cummings company
Peacefully
They would appreciate your support they need it now
More than ever gave their church has been seized
I really don't want to see either
I'm saying that everyone needs to hear that you call for that I'm going for it
Absolutely
Super religious group
Journalist
To do
Hi Galaxy
Reporters do they come on shows and trying
Murders
I mean if she
She's supposed to be covering this story it doesn't make sense for the interview to end with him begging hurt
To call people
Come to the
Church
That's weird
This isn't any kind of
Reporting
Suzette best activism
Hayden reality
Excitement
This episode is nuts
Sheila's you're a bad person
I'm happy
I don't know enough about her to relive
Full picture but
Crying
Just a little more neutral that I wants right to I do agree with you there he doesn't understand that Alex
Like she's talking to a guy who's
But a parody version
Right-wing media Outlet
Oh boy she's used to
You know
Seriousness
I don't necessarily want
Get sued
FIFA care
Is where I clearly walk people to f***
Mtume
I fear consequences
Is an Alex
Apparently doesn't
Canada we might get consequences in America Alex receives done
Alex has learned over
Over the course of his career not tours
Back to the idea
Of chickens coming home to roost
Then that's why you babes away.
I listen to this episode and I was blown away by like
Okay I thought that video was bad
I still think
I think it's legally actionable and you know whatever
I didn't expect for the episode afterwards to be worse
Yeah I was I was
Surprised I thought we were going to have a little fun clowning on that dumb video I hadn't seen it so I was you know I was waiting
For the show obviously
And watch to see we got a concentrated bouillon cube of race
Resume and incitement to violence
Yeah
And I really I mean
I mean this
I hope that nothing happened
Yeah me too
His behavior in the past has led to people
Going
And f****** with people and victimizing people in Waze
That re respond
Possible and terrible
And
For him to have
Targets of like everyone's got to go to these places
In one
Day
Is really really scary
What it could be
It could lead to nothing
The danger is there
I just don't think
Yeah I mean
Can't you see in a courtroom like
When this trial we aim to prove that Alex Jones another
Pizzagate
But so
If we prove that then he goes away forever right that's good
I don't know I don't know
I don't know how you do that
In court but like just dropped
For the sake of like a Podcast Addict
Explores the same to her
You can definitely say
You behaving in exactly the same ways
Has he has one things have gone bad
Not good we should learn from the things that have already have
I think that would be wise
Yep now
Fingers crossed
Things work out okay
And I guess we'll find out. Go to the Border
I strongly call on everyone do not do either of those things
I'm in favor of people
Cocktail
Better than going to the Border or a weird Church in Canada
I think so
Monday
But
I'm feeling better my put out a little funny fun thing on Monday we'll see
Go to bed Jordan
If you would like to download please find a local charity or Bellefontaine area
Do I help you
People doing God's work
Until then
Lonely Island ezx
Clark on Barrel run.
Apple
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color