Damn important swetik
I have great respect for knowledge babe I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Acknowledge
The Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
We already a question for you
My break is that I have been
It all taken care of and I'm okay
That's indeed at this point
I was an interesting weekend
Actually I got my date wrong
And I ended up getting the vaccine on Saturday
I had heard from some people
Some friends who've gotten
Coshocton
They've told me about like the next day
Pretty bad or like I had a little bit of
Some effect
Kind enough to drive me to get
The vaccine in that I went
And immediately I was
Very cocky
I wish I was very much I want to be part of the team
I appreciate it very much
What's the the hubris of communal experience
Of the side effects
Yeah it's evening
The return of
Consider WrestleMania
And there was this weird resonance but
Between
I got vaccinated
On the same day as wrestlemanias heaven
Crowds return a swell of emotion of like Norm
Normalcy
You can repeat the her I head over
Chicken
He got hit by
A train of a fever
Locomotive
And so I had a little bit of
Fever
Through the end of Saturday night Wrestlemania
And I went straight to bed
Sunday relief
Real stupid
The communal experience
Side effects Daniel
Vaccinated I felt really stupid cuz I was like looking at my text
Do you realize like there's no side effects
Is there anybody in the Superman
Valeri like resentment towards you I was just sitting there going to like all I've heard some people don't have side effects
Will be one of the ones
Something something
Going to happen too bad to like it wasn't even like a really bad fever I'm just
Kind of week
Very soft
A little bit of a fever and I was just like
Heidi Citgo
I need to put on a little hat a little bedtime hat and goes yeah yeah yeah
Feel like I should do this a little review of Wrestlemania
Cebu
That was a very little review
Wow
Real bad
How did the conversation about the Bray Wyatt
Did they do what we did they would do a movie like that
We don't go inside of it
What happened
Listeners who don't watch wrestling
Bray Wyatt
Was a guy who's a swamp hillbilly called later
It was a lot of fun
Unofficial
Mascot of this podcast
Yasuke used
Be a swamp hillbilly called later and I was a lot of fun.
You gave rambling sermons
And then he went away and he came back
Is a children's TV show host
Show at the Firefly fun house
And then he
Possessed by a demon called the
Brightside made him
Nearly indestructible
And there's a bunch of convoluted nonsense storytelling
Then at last year's WrestleMania they did a cinematic movie type match
Where I was called a firefly Funhouse match
Deconstruct
Did John Cena's ego and higher career weird
Psychological
Constructivism a song about wrestling that I've ever watched
I told you this was actually very very good it was a lot of fun
So over the course of this year
The fiend
The demon
Guy
You got burned
Alive rain trench
Randy Orton
Set him on fire and burned him alive and he disappeared for a bit but
By that point
Doctrinated Alexa Bliss
There's another character on the show into the dark
Sativa whatever
And throwing Fireballs at him
Throw Fireballs now cabin
You burned a man alive you might as well give his buddy the ability to throw fire
Fireball
At the last
Pay-per-view
Alexa Bliss
Did talk to Randy Orton
Turn into a match with her
And of course this was all a trap
And the fiend came back and he was all burned and everything
Chart up
Oh my God
Sherry Sherry Sherry
Three other ghosts
Tubidy really following
This WrestleMania Night 2 they had the match
Between the fiend
Is it going to be
I'm already burned him to death
Bone match I was like this is so stupid
And so actually
It during the pre-show of night
I was yelling at the screen
Open WhatsApp
The worst idea why would
Would you ever open the show with that match
Terrible idea
So dumb they opened a terrible idea
Yeah
It was really bad
Wake me up
It started with the Bray Wyatt
Chard
Walking down the hallway
Which are dropped off Hammond
I would
Explain what happened in the match but I don't really understand it then do is dump
I will say my high point if this is
Damningly WrestleMania with faint praise
My high point was
The rapper Bad Bunny earring a lot of people say positive things about a wrap
Yes
It might have been when my fever was setting in but she killed it
Is a lot of fun to watch him have just
The best time to have a lot of fun
Leave that that didn't happen I checked with
It's the people before the show and they were like
Never been on WrestleMania Dan just had a fever
Stay on your fever was so bad
Oh no brain was torturing
It's a fun night to that
Like a little little piece where Bad Bunny comes walking up on
Like onto a street
AAA Triple H's standing there with a
Briefcase
Did great at WrestleMania now you go do what you do God no hands
No nothing I don't even know anything about that bunnies music and I have been won over
Anyway this is been my project
Brightspot new Jordans
Did my bright spot of all things
TV show called maid4luv
It's for someone who's Birds Death
Comes back
Surprisingly close
Billionaire
We got some stuff it's quite funny but
The main thing is Ray Romano is in
Incredible
Oh yeah he has turned himself into an act
With good you wouldn't expect
Everybody Loves Raymond to be this guy and to pull it off as well as
Who does Andre Braugher men of a certain
Quantum Leap
Dracula still alive
I remember that you're being all right
I might be wrong about that it was a show and I thought it was like like USA
Impact to Wild Hogs is Armageddon if it will
Came out the same year kind of thing
Haematic
Overlap
Joy
Asian
Anyway
Jordans
Today with an episode to go over
Was that what we're doing
So I have this this weekend
Your notes
Recovery and what have you and
Convalescent
Public bus
Nearly is
In need of that is
Thought I might need to be
I appreciate everybody Lions you know be cool.
Monday on Wednesday this week
As I was getting back to work I was like I don't want to
Do this
I didn't want to look at the present
Stevenson's shootings
Police involved
In Minneapolis
I just I just didn't have the stomach to jump right back in
And that without
And so I decided we're doing
2003's back in
We'll deal with the present day on Friday
I needed to I have something
Thing that I had a little bit less steak
In order
R22 dive back in on
Out here in just a moment before we do
Signed up
How far to Fairhope
Scatman
AKA thank you so much
Apologize
Brought up to me that I did say on an early episode
And if we ever made it to a comfortable doing it podcast
Illegally time I'm not going to be able to do that
A lot of money on not making any money I do keep up
The possibility of a Scatman John tattoo
Next Willard in the policy Factory
I'm a policy wonk
Maybe not a walk-in but I wasn't a Nelly song
Thank you so much
Good to know that is not a walk
That's not a walk
Got no
I don't know where I would be with you anyway
Spider-Man
Toco thank you so much and I'll probably want
I'm a policy wonk
SpongeBob cakes
I'm a policy wonk thank-u-next evil, which definitely coming for your guns
I'm a policy wonk very much
I am finally
We got to go
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
April birthdays
Myself
Doctor gum
Stop buddy doctor gums also has a April birthday
Brad how's it going Brad
Happy birthday Brad Tyler don't touch with us and wanted us to wish Brad
Happy birthday happy birthday
Say Brad didn't say when your birthday was though it's just an April what's your point
My birthday is in April
Cedric the Entertainer
Kelly Clark
Okay
Any White's Jordan today we are going over May 5th
2003's episode was
About May 2nd
The 2003
What the hell why would you
We aren't jumping
Okay
May 2nd was a Thursday Alex took off Friday
Now back on Monday
He doesn't have a Sunday show at the
This point we're just back on Monday here
And here is another context drop
From Today Show
Yep kids are being arrested
For stepping in water puddles
In water puddles
Saudi I want to know I would another regulation
What pools
What is the pool of water in this circle
I regret to
Inform you that Alex does not get into the
It does not get any of these
Specific details
So Alex
Begins the show complaint
About the bass
Is being put in all the
Positions of power
Amanda Rock
Retrospect sounds
Really right on he's right about everything
He won't you will shortly be very very very wrong
And then we get additional for the
The game
Where in
In the world
Is
Saddam Hussein
Has no comfortable living in Russia
Okay so episode
Haiti or the Cuba
He was believed he was in Cuba
The last couple days
Indiana jones-style interstitial where there's the play
In the red line going from
He gets around
Nobody
Nobody is seeing him get on any of the
These flights
Cuba
Russia
Butthole
That bih
Exactly
Travel itinerary
Yes this is interesting
The way that this is this is playing out that Alex
Cuz very much
Omnipay Jose
I do the best party is going to be in charge of everything at
It's just
Could be very very wrong
Very short.
His career
He's a different Alex Jones
Then he is in the
In the present day
He's the same
In some way
In 2020
Be a real
Dum dum on Aaron
Being very sad and
What is job history
He's still in a million-dollar Studio you still got the LED screens behind him
He's the kind of guy who shows up
Bull horns at events
He didn't organize and DC and people chant his name and can't afford
To hire at least 50
1518 year old
Do you can draw crowd he can leave some people
From Trump's rally to the capital in a way that might look bad in hindsight but
In 2003 was a little bit different
What kind of book
Alex was taken back.
Silence is basically Z100 radio
There's maybe minor league baseball games
Going to be appearing at I was wondering
Cuz it's just going out of his way to go to the station
Seems weird
Can we find out about this
This place
And
Well there's a 2020 article
About the station today
I was a little bit in
Think how things turned out for them last year
Okay alright
Pete Shartel
Radio
Sputnik
They are they're broadcasting for 6 hours a day this station AM 11:40
For approximately $60,000 a year
You know it's tough keeping her mom call radios
Station alive though I don't like you got to you got to find Revenue
I got to do what you got to do
Interesting interesting not necessarily
Anything weird
Prior to this this station was hearing people like
Alex Jones and of course Rick Wiles
Who you may remember is that fundamentalist assholes who called the Trump impeachment quote
Juku
This line in a kcur profile about the him and the station is actually kind of stunts
Shoretel acknowledges that kcxl has it
Who quote seem anti-Semitic
Churchill said that you thinks his listeners are welling
To decide for themselves whether they think something is
Antivirus or anti-vax weather it's based on prejudice
Burp on someone's wrong interpretation of the fact I feel like you're misunderstanding a real issue there
It's up to the listener
To decide whether or not they believe it is anti-Semitism however it is and you put it on the radio sir
I certainly says it's
Real good to go back to put it on the radio
And plenty of your lister's
I'm taking up time on my broadcast to are Nazi stuff in I'm in Oceano
LeBron commercials during ashcorp
I trust that the audience
Guess what I don't like this
Forum I'm just going to give them a place to spread their views without any pushback
Station that Alex's
Going to do good
Great stuff
So Alex's
Some grapes
Ben 2003
You've got some issues
Is above all of them
The Green Market
The biggest issue that the truth movement or whatever I engaged
Faces these
Opportunistic radio people who talk about the real issues but then mix in stuff like
Aliens are let's say exit
Four-dimensional demon while fighting the literal death.
One one could say that he has become everything that he hates most of this
Future Self
Got to love it
I heard that and I thought like well that's just
It's good fun
This actually leads
To what I think it is
A really interesting moment later in the episode
Okay there's something
Rises this up
211 love relevance
I have otherwise
Alberto
Get to that Alex
Complain
A lot
About how they're going to Outlaw homeschooling
Blue
America
What
Amarillo
Interesting
Wow it worked back then about the Muslims
Panoramic VR Taxi
Okay yeah
So all the terrorism
Without bars gold or fake Muslim terrorist
I think that there aren't really any except for CIA
Ranma
Some terrorists
Others interests
They're going to get rid
Homeschooling
The calling it abuse
I mean I have a problem with
Skooly get as a way to avoid learning
That's a big issue were there like I don't want my kid learning any of that devil math
That's an issue
I think kids should learn the math of
The Spheres
Homeschooling in and of itself isn't necessarily
You can't be an elementary
Abuse if you are keeping your child in a
Raising them in some kind of
Absurd way
Could be an element of that decides to homeschool
Does not necessarily
Equate
To that
Likes to play the margins
Did everybody is saying that homeschool is
Intrinsically inactive
If abused
People are making
You know I mean I'm in my small community growing up we had a couple I had but I have that but I think we had both ends
The spectrum of homeschool kids the kids who are home-schooled
Who were clearly
Play overachievers and you meet them and they're six years old near like at
You shouldn't be in with the rest
Of the chattel you need to be raised by your weirdo parents
That's fine and then the other end of that was the like
Well okay
So they know everything about the Bible
And then beyond that were in real dicey territory
Sure the difficulties and challenges of homeschooling
Cuz obviously like socialization
I think people that figured out ways around that was like
Groups and portly
I don't know
There's some homeschool stuff that's bad
Alex on the other hand
When he looks
Sure
It's all bad
They're weird examples
Yeah this is a very strange dystopian
Infant that were real
Put some very weird adults
Doing some weird
Stop
What does a hole
Yeah I don't I don't know how public education
Teaches you to be and I I don't I don't like this
But as I was just calling it a crack w****
I don't track sex worker I don't
I don't know what the educational curriculum is like
I also
Fake obviously tag and dodgeball that's just those right-wing
Surround assignment periodically
Whenever they wanted to play those
Yeah it's weird yeah I remember any classes growing up there was just like okay we're going to watch The Wire
And then you figure out what character you want to be
Build a curriculum based on that I don't know
Glasses ever have been like Christianity to call Tonneau here's how you become a Muslim
Picture of describing a women's studies course in a very wrong way
Advertising examples like the way that this is out of
Control in the school
Schools
Control
Trying to get everyone
Years ago
Themes
If true
Outraged yeah I don't believe this
The first thing that I find
Troubling about the stories that are weak is a pretty quick recovery time for a kindergartener to get over pneumonia
Strong kindergarten
I would ask you this question what is
Truancy if you're a kindergartener
4 and 6 years old or even able to skip class
Alright they turned around
If there's an unexplained
Signs of a child in kindergarten that's an issue with
The parrots
A six-year-old is not responsible for getting themselves
To class like a high schooler might be
Maturity is just ridiculous
The kindergarten hires a guy
To drive around outside all 7-Eleven
You're one day you got to be in school
According to the Texas Board of Education there are a bunch of steps that are taken before any kind of
Courtwood coming to play with truancy issues as a
It stands now
These rules were
Change that to get rid of any possible criminal charges back
In 2015 but even prior to that the worst it would really happen to us
Is it would be charged
Do the class C
However
Could get out of
Control
I feel about any of this but I'm also pretty sure
This is only something
Lady of dawn
After their attempt
To resolve the truancy issue and noses
The failed
It's not even how this stuff works
Anymore
Interesting things
Things about Alexander
The past though
He's actually covering a murky subject but he sensationalizing it
It's so far past the point where I could be taken
And seriously
Thoughtful people can
And should discuss what approaches are appropriate to take
Improves of encouraging attendance
In school
And how chronic truancy is often an indication of a larger problem
That should not be
Be ignored
Need help with yeah it kind of truancy the problem is not
You're not in school often enough
The right is a sign of something that's
One could use
Some kind of assistance
He's imposing fines on ice coolers and skip class all the time a good strategy or is it overly punitive
Counterproductive
That is a fine conversation
I think that
It's worth having
Where it falls apart
What is a terrible source of a
Information about anything
Is the point where he makes this about a kindergartener read pneumonia being criminally charged
For being out of school
That's absurd and even according to the debatable
Leave to harsh rules that Texas operated under at the time
These truancy rules only apply to students in
1st through 12th grade
How does making up an
An extreme example of some
Image in the audience's head
About this policy that he's looking to demon
He does this because that's easier than it would be
To look over data
Come up with an argument against
The policy as it exists
If you can just paint a dramatic overly emotionally-charged picture in your audience's head
You don't have to do the work
Making an actual
Yeah
I love you like I remember whenever they took away 33 ad a PRACK
Says when I was in high school do in football and making the kids soft and all that
Add stop
And I
Yeah that was probably the best
Decision to take that away but this would be like if Alex got out of it was like
They said you only have
How to do two
V103 anyways
So they f****** kill them they just
Problem is like a bin process
Also by Framing the issue that Alex
Is discussing like this
You can sidestep the uncomfortable reality that
Program
Millie victimizes stood
Without me
If you skip
You can't pay the fine
What happened
Then
2015 article on BuzzFeed
Discuss the case of an 11th grader in Texas
Jail credit
At a rate of $300
Per day
This is an incredibly flawed system
And the conversation about it is done a disservice by having Alex Rider grandstand about imaginary kindergarten
Bank Weiser other adults
Discussing these sorts of issues in terms of reality
And adjustments no thanks
Idiotic fake address
Yeah
It's such a huge issue to when you consider the school-to-prison
Pipeline and housing so many things are meant to
Criminalize children
At an early enough age so you can just
Keep them criminals forever
The fuel for the capitalist
Mill
But Alex
Clearly one only
Here's about white kid
So there's a problem there
N2 is just
But he's not
Dealing with any of the larger problem is
Kindergartner
Intersection of
That school-to-prison
Pipeline ideas which is definitely real
An issue
And also
Misguided but
Well-intentioned
Ideas
Cuz I do think that some
People who may not
Be trying to criminalize children sure
Okay if
You're in high school
Can you skip school when you get a fine
Maybe you'll be less likely to skip High School
Sure
Behavior the wrong way
Yeah I think that there is
An element
Does that even suck no matter what
Where is
More of the way Plies
Whatever Alex is doing is pointless
No and you can totally imagine like I can give Inside the Mind of
The person who offered
The kid like
Oh what's up
Will give you credit for doing jail and that person was
Probably thinking they were a genius
It's like see you
You can't afford to pay it
You just do some jail time helping you out instead of somebody who should have been
Slapped in the face the moment they had that thought
Yeah if you don't feel like I do sometimes
In jail instead of paying me the money that doesn't make any sense for you to pay me in the first
Reading that kind of stuff
It doesn't
Make a lot of sense why
You would
Continue down this road of this policy
Alex mentioned a guy named Chris
Chris klick
Who is a lawyer for an organization
That is a staunchly
Conservative Christian organization
All about homeschool
That's terrible because I would listen
Listen to MC Chris
Chris klika
Instantly I would listen.
Mixtape
Go to pose actors
Weather
They're trying to
Do whatever mean
Oh yeah
Okay
So yeah this is this is the way this manifested in 2000
Mixtape is I was hoping
No no
That was not the coloring books
A lot of this stuff with the schools and the truancy and Punishment
That gets me so
Social Services involved in all this
Some part of it
Is it there's a major push
Take your kids and give them the
Sure
The edge of a conservative
Yep
These people are silly
It's so weird to go back into
The past
And listen to these people and think you're still allowed to talk aren't
People still listen to you
You listen to that and you're like really were doing that back then you're still around
Free Wild
If it's just in conservative
Chris
Middle is just so
Endless
Just slightly different
Window into the same stew
S*** so if you go to the hospital
Social Service
I'm going to take the I know I'm going to steal those kids and I'm going to give them to homosexuals I believe released
Don't know what it means
I don't know
I honestly don't know what do you mean
It does not mix true
That's true it did rain really does
Doesn't make any sense
Nope nope
I just don't you know
People listen to that and they don't hear
People who are whining like
Crazy people
Like this isn't set like
Do you know what's going on now I went to the DMV to re-up my license
And instead of giving me a new lights
In my mouth directly into my mouth
Literally
Brighton
Children
Yeah yeah it's it's
Wild
You talk about that it gets into
Okay
Obviously Alex
Would call them
That's what you would do nowadays
In 2000
3 people who makes that stuff up
Father
And pills too far that's how you make the Patriots and all this
Caller calls in
And wants to talk
The social service workers
And he thinks
But they are demons
Okay here we go here
Alex's
Respond
Statements that these people are
Fireball
Just listening to you talk
The guidelines
We're totally
Script
And Alex you're right
Money with that
These people
Program
When you're around
That's kind of measure
This isn't news
Interesting
You trying to walk a line
He knows that like I can
Can present myself as a guy who sang it
My enemies politically are devils seriously
I have some
Pretensive
Thing to be respected
Oh man I think I might be able to get a show on an actual Network
At some point
Yeah that is very interesting
I mean what kind of interesting about it is that at the
The time I say
Vicky's right
You couldn't
Be out-and-out
The demons are coming
Kill us all
Take you serious I think I look certainly didn't
A big enough career
A big enough star to be able to
Absorb whatever blow my come from
And then I would say probably right around what like the
The Tea Party Movement
Whenever they swept in 2000
That's really wet at all was like
Started a change where you could just talk about demons all all you want
Restaurants in Cortland
Get weird the weird turn tomorrow here in Pro you got wet
The normal is that
Tea party on the right
Yeah whatever you are as Alex Jones
Yeah I don't know I usually don't know for sure if that is when
More
Over conversation about demons and it was later
I think so
We did not seem nearly as much
These people at the f****** devil longer looking
2015 true that is true
I think I think it might be more Reese
But I find I find this Glimpse at
2003 really really interesting
And it's mixed clip
I think Alex has to stop himself
Interested
These people are demons
Okay and this clip will not stick out to me at all if I didn't
Noah
What he does now
What you're telling me is that
Like a demon trying to get out
What's to call these people be putting that out there
Wentworth family and friends
I'm sorry
I'm trying to get through the future
You were there the whole time doesn't that sound
Almost like
Someone had told him
Dude
Don't f****** save your fighting
We need like Teddy Anderson told him there's no way we're going to be able to sell gold
If you yelling about the literal devil
Sorry literal
Long pause
Sorry
Wild
Hey Pete this is this is a piece of evidence
I'm sanchal obviously
Not definitive
But it works towards
Answering the question that I
I had for a while
Which is
Is Alex's I'm fighting the devil thing a new thing underneath
He was pretending but that wasn't what he believed
And I kind of thing
This looks like
Doesn't really sound like
Track gumshoe
Feels like that is at least in minor indication that Alex
Has this idea that his enemies are literal demon
He was covering that belief up
For the sake
Appearing respect
I'm interested to see if there's any more
Flickers of indication
But that made me
Laugh really hard
That clip would not be
It wouldn't sound off any alarms
Unless you knew that 18 years later everywhere
That's so ridiculous
I'm mad at him and the best
For lying to me then
If you think your enemies are literal demons you should tell me
Yeah I think it would be more responsible to the audience
Tell me that you're hiding that their literal demons everywhere because you are supposed to be
Truth-teller on your own show and you're pulling back whenever you know that literal demons are killing every
Trojan Horse the literal demons at the talk of like the Federal Reserve and all this stuff that's not
To the audio
Totally
Anyway
Alex is a guy who's again
Totally totally
Weirdly fine with the idea of deposing Saddam Hussein the business flow
Great
Route
Operation American freedom
In the mold of operation Iraqi freedom and that involves getting rid of social workers
Okay we did it
That is
Complex series of steps you need to get to those three things being related to each other at all
I don't like it
No
Because guest
Nope I think these people are literally even
No no no I've been hiding that belief is old-time
Bad
Demonic side of it
One-place
The scripture where
Messiah
And these people are not letting
It's called math
Weird
Weird questions to ask
Play where are you by the way
Yeah you think
This is a bit
It's more than I expected
Cuz I think the prison
Temptation that Alex has is very much like
And I had no problem with Islam or anything like
I got the sense
It is is a anti-islam stuff kind of
Escalator
Yeah that's coming from his collar
But
Yeah
Yeah that doesn't
Surprise me I would be
Islam in the schools
Who sing that Islam is
Multicultural
Crap yeah
What the f*** is this
Freedom fries just
There whatever you want
Just just f******
Yeah so this girl wants to know where in Virginia
Chris's organization
How to find the square root of something roots are in the backyard my friend that's devil worship that's what I'm telling you right now.
Find the square root
Get tickets
Go find a switch
Sweetheart
They chat about where they are in Virginia and Alex have to be like
So unfortunately they end up stopping
Conversation to take another call that might have been
Mistake
One dance
A couple of questions
Cuz I know that there is
Change it
Sandpoint
That does not answer the question
No
Seems like a fair amount of sovereign citizen collars at this
How is his career it is it is funny because it seems like he also really doesn't like
Noises have silly a lot
Are the arguments are they make it look bad without doing
Making a show that is this
The catering
Directly
Play to Sovereign
It was just too all over the place but good
Maybe half hour of this episode
Is dedicated to Alex
Arguing with a collar about the Republic of Texas
Should secede
I tried to
Support all that stuff
But everybody kept declaring themselves the present
It's really funny but it was
Cut Clips in a way that would make it work
So funny
Ahsoka Tano
Anything's going
Fruit cake
Fruitcakes to describe the Republic of Texas people like
Maybe
Five or six times
Very specific word
Made me think maybe
He has a personal beef
8 City
It's kind of funny
Little bit like somebody like
Starting a roller rink
And then
Like
Just hated people who roller skate
Yeah like Heating
Hating people who use like in line
Yeah yeah yeah
The law says I have to let you skate okay this is America to the Magna Carta
What
Chris
Chris leaves
He was not that much of an inch
Sing cast
Just kind of like a very reactionary against social workers
Pro homeschooling
Did not drop a mixtape did not
Take your time
Very different
Cool
So Alex gets to some headlines
Is a lotus
Behind Bars
Salix is misrepresenting this case said that he's covering to make it appear that it
System is now just have to put
Criminals
And punish the good
People which is
Code for white gray
Hey if people aren't committed
So this is Tony Martin
Man from the UK who shot it to
Two young men who were breaking into his house
Which resulted in the death of one of the
The issue here isn't that Tony was wrong
To practice self
Defense didn't believe that he was acting in self-defense
In the shooting
The incident happened in 1999 at which point Martin
Not have a license
Thanks for the shotgun
Used in the shooting
You lost it 5 years prior when he supposedly found a man stealing apples from his Orchard
Shoot at him leaving the hole in the man's vehicle
Point of order
You you
No
Added to this was Martin publicly known hatred of the Romani people which was referenced in a guardian article from
Some 2,000
Apart from Steve's Martin
Pet hate was gypsy
Norwich Crown Court heard that the farmer had talked to put these in the middle of a field surrounding
You got anything
The article goes on to say that Martin had said quote Hitler was right
About these people
And also points out that Martin's
Uncle Andrew fontenot's one of the founders of a straight-up fascist measure
Right right right
So you're not
The problem here
The prosecution successfully argued that the shooting was not an act of self-defense but that martinet laid in wait and shoppies in
Intruders without first giving award
This wasn't the sort of case that Alex's portraying it
Get to be where the burglar is
Play someone
Legitimate self-defense
I meant Sue's the homeowner for it
Hit clearly unhinged lunatic with a history of shooting at
People with a clearly race
Has passed
Deadly force
Intruders to his home but not presented a mortal danger to him
According to the British
Escorts that
So I was
Natsu except
Use of self-defense
So I don't know
Yeah you know if someone breaks into your house and they slip on a banana peel they can sue you
No they can't no no they really really can't
You have to
Kind of go
Way out of your way to be the one who's convicted of a crime in that scenario and that's what this guy did
Yeah it's someone is like
Presenting a danger to you do I have the right to self
Does not
Weather in your house
You have to tell them
To leave
Before you shoot
Took that I would try I would I would open with
Excuse me
Alex has some
Interesting similar problem
In his life
2003 the present
One is it
These calls just don't work out
The difference though is it a 2003
Handle it
Sure
Yeah
Mike in Illinois
Claire
Wow that is such a
Breath of fresh air this is a minor setback
Not a big deal we're just going to rebroadcast
Everybody bear with me
That's the vibe that I got there everybody bear with me I suppose we're doing a live radio show
Sometimes a little bit of a hiccup
This happened
Normal
This present day
Another was that talk with the Texas
Folks about
Now they're all weirdos and everyone's president now it's hatred
But everybody can secede if they want
Sure I was very procession 2003
Because contract
But but but
Civil War
Realpolitik
That's correct
What
That's true
The Confederacy was full of globalist I do like
How people who study the Civil War
Change their story all the time
Quite frequently in the story because
We were in the pic
Picture is easier to understand
And you have a full awareness of what's going on
New World Order moles as it seems as though the Civil War involved
Whatever it is you want
To be at any given point
Time even if it's the difference between same day
But what if you find something that sounds more
How can you be Global how can you be Confederate royalty if
Your royalty is just
Infiltrated by New World Order globalism it's not like
Everybody was New World Order
How is it possible for everyone to be as so
Well-informed Wyndham National rate of
10%
The new world order was running
False flag Civil War
He said it was a false Flags
Everything is fake nothing except
Conviction
The truth
Subway
Confederate false
Flag Civil War
So there's a commercial for the Genesis Communications
It's not working or anything cuz I just wanted to play this a little bit of it
Cuz it sounds really
What is our real interest
Gcn Radio Network
Are you tired
Well so are we and we're doing something about it
Where the jury
You're the judge
We've already
Decided and you have to pass
What's the sentence
Executioner
Doesn't talk
Prosecution
Metaphor
Your honor the jury has something to say this
Nova Jory.
Where are the attorneys
You're the jerk
Jerry just stands up
I could do a better job as lawyer in s*** hit this prosecutor out of
Kuester is an expression is pretty good
Think about it
For even one second
No
Amazing
Good job gcn
Probably wrote that
You got a bee in his bonnet
Because
Is it holiday
The bush
Bright evil one
Yeah
You got this holiday
You got this holidays off
Not about that
Accommodate
Memorial
That's terrifying
Google world
Grabbed all natural resources
So two things
Is the jumped out at me there like the first is
Clearly
Fully aware of the
Colonial exploitation that is part of our country's history that he completely denies
In the present
And second thing I was thinking is like
Totally fine with the holiday called Loyalty Day if it was like a nationalist
Extreme right-wing government everyone had to be loyal to
Royal DJs my favorite day is
If it was his
Thanks
A f*****-up thing to have a Loyalty Day do you know how that's so f***** up
It would be like if
Every
Morning kids had to go to school and recycle
That would be so f***** up be very weird
Point out that Loyalty Day is a holiday that's existed
An attempt to replace the Communists leaning mayday
Whereas it's also known International workers day
That holiday marks the date of the Haymarket Riot which was something that the American government in the early 1900s
Eager to not glorify we do
You talk about Workers United
We are still mad there's a weekend so yeah they didn't want to endorse workers rights which of course
Was communism in so there was my idea
Ceeday coming in on May 1st
Take over
The holiday itself didn't catch on until 1950
T5 during the Cold War
Official holiday in the United States
And every
Is recognized
Reclaim the holiday
See if you can guess who said this
Quote
Now therefore I Donald J Trump president of the United States of America
Proclaim May 1st 2017 as Loyalty Day
Disloyalty day I call on all Americans to observe this day with appropriate ceremonies in our schools and other public places
Including the recitation of the pledge of allegiance to the flag of the United States of America
I also call upon all government officials
Display the flag of the United
It states on all buildings and grounds on that day
Who said it
I got to go with clay
So close
Every time
I thought you were trying to trick me
Very ideology to create Alex Jones at the same ideology the created the idea of a holiday called
Loyalty Day
Express loyalty
Did the United States in the face
Communist Manifesto
How to understand so little about the hits.
The here he is
Is rambling about the direct result of his ideological forefather
A time to get some kind of it
Evil event Bush wanted
Create
He's much more palatable and seems happier in two
Freaked out when he can't get to a collar button
You still a total idiot
Yeah it's almost as if
Conservative reactionary ideology is essentially an Ouroboros
It creates an outrage
And then later on gets outraged when their outrage
It's created a thing for them to get out right
2017 there was like
Some people who are you know like
Is creating loyalty
Self into thinking that this
The first one ever whatever you deprive all the context of it
You just using it as a
As a prop
It also seems almost a little insult
Isaac
22 imagine that
Whatever year it is that way
Was the first year they thought of Loyalty Day
Listen
We've had plenty of fascists running America for a long time they thought of a loyalty
EBay every time workers tried to unite
They were like okay here's what we got to do pledge loyalty to the 120 Hour Work Week
Like that's what they were doing
So is Alex
Exactly
So stupid
Yep
The differences
When I was looking at this episode.
In present-day Alex
Some back then
Is he seems like
To understand that movies aren't real
At least
It's like that
Yes
Similar to this media reference
The plan
And they were not telling it to you
By releasing that movie
Yeah yeah it's
Disconnect
Between this
Idea that's represented in media and I reality
The merging together in some weird
It's using Alex
Gestalt
Yeah yeah it's people know the
Prince between movies
Season reality
It's comforting at least
Because
When I listen to this I can be like
Alright
We all agree
That we breathe are that's their time moves
Entropy is real
That's comforting cuz I feel bad
It is it is a real bummer
Going into the past and finding things that are more positive than the present
Because you're like you want to live in a place where hope is
This but we do this we're like
Man
Isn't that nice
And then you remember where it goes any like it could happen
It could happen to you
Yeah that is a bet is a little bit scary it's enough
Should all be careful to not tired baby
Secretly think
They were fighting demons
Elsa
Try to keep it a secret for too long you turn into Alex
Don't buy you are what you pretend to be
Going to figure out a way to make an infomercial out of that lasted not sure
PSA
So Alex believes
Is the u.s.
Sure
There is a problem
Confused
Car warranty
Loves Country
When Alex fake cries in 2003
Clinton Phil Hartman doing Clinton
Set a Wonder
I really heard Phil Hartman that sounds like
I think that you're doing a great job
Ridiculous
So silly that was weird
Completely artificial presentation of
Emotion in sometime
But
I started think like Okay so
Patriotism apple-pie
And all this
Is it is a facade
And underneath that is just rotting maggots
And what have you
What do you love them
Like what
What do you think
But it's right there in the title
Countries evil
But it's a rotten
Cafe
Lid on it
E82 saying iPhone
Yeah he likes me why not make the whole plane out of the black box and what do you what do you not understand I don't fully
We understand what it is that like he's hoping
Hoping to
Save this
Rotting underneath with a fake
It seems like
You expose that you take the lid off and you'd realize
Yeah maybe we should go
I don't need I don't need what's in this
Rotting
I don't feel fully that I understand
Yeah yet from listening to this iPad
What is Entrada
Right I would guess that it's gone
Sure
Property rights
Loyalty to your country
Absolutely
Hating
School shooter
Whites only
I don't have a full grasp of like Alex's entire policy set in 2003
Like I think I understand a lot of
Stop
Through the prism of
Thousands of hours of his other content but like
Some stuff that's going to be surprising and I don't want to make too many assumptions
Yeah you know I was
I was listening to that clip
And thinking about
All the stories of people who listen
Listen to him at this time. We're kind of drawn in by that and I was
Thinking about my understanding of politics at that time like
As the Iraq war is going on
It totally felt
The first person to discover how evil America was
It was like
I have been told all of this stuff all the way up until I'm 16 years old and then the Iraq War
Or happens in there like maybe you should read Real History is and not your school stuff
And then I really did feel like all men
But this is before redpilling became the meme that it was but it did feel like that and then you listen to Alex go like
This is a rotten thing and you can
You can really get that
Sense of like
Yeah that's how I feel yeah you don't have sophisticated political opinions yet I just know that this is some
Bulshit
Yeah yeah pretty surface-level their presentation that is almost
Perfect
For exploiting
Disillusioned
Yes it was definitely a period where there is a lot of people were feeling alienated and dissolute
The world
As they had
Been brought up to understand that
That you and I though we're a few years apart
We're both
You know a certain man of a certain age when they're Wrecking Ball
Where were you
Amm. Where people are generally
They go through. It just illusion
I meant to have that compounded by something as
9/11 and the Iraq War
Yeah it's
It's something where you
You know those feelings that you're having
You could see them mirror
Maybe something like Alex talking
Sing about the
Core
In the Passat over it
You could you could
You could gravitate
Towards that
Interesting to
Think about how much goes along with it that you might not realize that you're also accepting of course like that homosexuals want to take
Children
Absolutely cuz you know that's what liberals got pricked and he wasn't
Driving you you're listening to this you're you're on a 20-minute drive right
You papa Anna Infowars because you're like
Disillusioned and disguise
Pretty funny and
And you only get 20 minutes where he's doing the anti-iraq war stuff and you don't listen to the half-hour he does with
The games are coming
Steal your
You know and you're like arguing about the Republican
Only be sucked into that it's much more believable
Like
The notion of like him having a large audience
If you listen to the present
Yeah what
In God's name that's much more believable when you look back at this
Petulant Lehigh
Outburst
All the time
The presentation of emotion is generally within like
Where he would want to be to make a point
Yeah and
He still got that dynamic range of like heat
You can get it up there hi and he can
It's not out of can
Control
Although it is silly
Training sincerity sounds like
Is a little bit
Weird I don't know
You know the Civil War was a false flag
So we we learned this
Yeah it turns out no in grocery stores they're putting
Self checkout line
Wow
Eventually
But first
They're going to transition the self-checkout Lanes
Into fingerprint
Scanners
Where you're going to have to have some sort of a mark of the beast or whatever notify grocery
We're never not going to do Market
I want to be done with Mark of the Beast
Can't we do about telling you what
At at the grocery store
I meant
You're going to have some sort of a Christian
It's going to go bomb
Biometric false flag
Presaging our people are going to bomb 5G towers and it's going to be a false flag
Already
Worst
What
Okay we're we're talkin about
Picture
What abortion
Yeah okay so all the abortion clinic
Attacks that we don't know if he's Mighty don't even know if he's mine
Controlled
So it could still be the Feds that one's on the fence
Hello boys closest I get to admitting that
Could possibly not be a false flag everything I was on there
That's exhausting
About this sir this is a glimpse into 2003 is like
Everybody is a f******
Concomitant
Everything is fake death
He's talked about like
All kinds of
Folks bike
Joe Scarborough
Ultra communist
Well that's that's turned out to be a prophetic
Who's the other person
Do you label the Communists on this episode
F*** I can't remember it is another is another right-wing guy
The pettiness of
Like
Chris Matthews
I just love the Lakes they're putting finger scanners in there
They're going to do all this s***
Second problem I don't want to do my own baggage
Patty right now that is not the Patriots main complaint
Girl girl
Is a convenient I always put the eggs in first and then then they went
We ever get 10 eggs
I've never been a train. A bad thing
Do people have training
Silly
Also great prediction
That they put in the self-checkout stuff and then
Next
Finger thumb scanner
I don't think that I've ever
Scammed by Thelma
Skating a credit
8 years old 8 years on self checkout pretty ubiquitous
Not even really in the conversation I don't think entertainment
Problem with self
Checkout line isn't doing your own baggage
Find somebody who shouldn't be using
There's too many items
Not just that whenever they're clearly
Not bagging material if you will wow
I don't have many complaints
At self-checkout
I kind of take everything in
Stride
So yeah everything's false flag there's going to be Christian
Places in
Going to be all fake
All these predict
Fantastic
Just constantly right about Atlanta
I'm going to be real mad if the when we do start getting those biometrics
There are biometric
Make things in Little Alchemy
Message you can have you can put little
Electromagnets in your finger
And stuff like that
Sooner or later we're going to have an implant
Turbo chips
Some sort
And some that are available now
One that will be
That final that like iPod moment
You know where all the sudden
This thing didn't
Exist and then it's everywhere
And it should be called The Mark of
The Beast I think
It's possible that that that
Technology will go along that line but it's
Equally possible that
I don't
No I don't know
I don't know if there will be an iPod Moment Like That
But it better be called The Mark of the base we got Soylent that's real
Yeah
And we don't talk about it start I don't know
We got to find out how to find that episode of our to show he's going to be furious about that
Definitely
Okay guys going to be
Go get the bodies
Yeah I'm taking the piss out of bed
Episode really DeSoto Market
Some of this is stupid
It is but
You have to write
And if I slip
Welearn
About
Something that maybe
Isn't in the history books but it should
Alex Save-A-Lot alive
Do you laugh
You got okay
They didn't do it
Now it's stopped
A smallpox attack by publicizing information
In about smallpox attacks
You stopped it
You can't I mean book
He said it
Obviously it's true
He saved so many wives
IQ
Lucid hearing you laugh and it's better hero who are the benefits of having a narcissist
Personality disorder
In that you can invent your own crisis is to become the hero of
I've never felt like a hero
Maybe maybe
Probably make me feel better
Do the costume like a pro con
In the pros or things like that saved the world
10 times over
No matter how many things you've bungled it easy to convince yourself it's
Plot positive red
It's all worth it. I save the world from a smallpox
Love that kind of stuff
The app
So this was this was little bit of a fun
Trip
2003 in order to
Ghetto get our toes back in the water for 4
Probably an unpleasant present-day episode on Friday disgusting nonsense spouted by a Munster
Looking forward to it
It will happen
Now I think
If I had to solve this up like
The reason that I thought the fifth
So it was like
Really
He
That moment where Alex says literal
Cre
Yeah
He stopped himself from saying literal demon
It's so
Import
Right there
It is
If we can demonstrate
If we can find more instances of Alex stopping himself from talking about the literal devil in the past
I'm going to
My mind's going to be
So you're saying that you're going to be the jury and I'll be the judge
And then
The audience
Executioners
I don't know I don't know how this work
We will
We will be court reporters
The audience can be an audience
Can I be the stenographer I want to play with one of those ticket can't use can't type fast enough
With another episode but until then
We are invisible to iTunes
People I do agates
Omniome Leo I'm dzx Clark I'm Daryl rundus I invented Liberty day
Alex