Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge b b
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Acknowledge
Dot-com
I'm talking little bit about Alex Jews
Bead we are damn Jordan
Quick
What's up
Today is a little Slice of Life moment a little Slice of Life
Explain in bed
Celine
Comes over
Stares at me while I'm laying there
What are you doing
Cat you weirdo
And then she just
Jew standing
With no warning
Flops over on her side
Like a horse that was tranquilized
Immediately deadweight is a cubit
I really enjoyed it
Last night
I didn't like how that battery goes out where it's not then it's just off
Therefore like maybe 5 minutes and then get bored and go lay somewhere else
Come on with this really nice
Beautiful Android
How about you
It's a lovely Slice of Life
A bright spot is a two-fold one brockhampton has anuel
Album out
I just found out that there's this show that I've never heard of that ran for
6mm Artisans or something
Sing like that called Superstore
And it's actually at Walmart
It's kind of a bummer it's like a
I was surprised to see how much labor issues were never heard of that never heard of that show before
I've never heard of it all over the place
Where where was it all over his rally what network TV
Dumb
Dumb comedy
Sure
But even if somebody come after you've been like hey there's this show on
Basic cable that
So good you got it
Check it out even like golf
Fuckyourself chartists
Prestige television first run of Full House was on basic cable
Shows that everyone
30 years are two examples Craig congratulations
Yep you got it I'm glad you're enjoying Superstore
Describe
So Jordan today because chaos is a foot
That's naturally I will get into some of that chaos here in a little bit before we do
I take a little moment to Chris and some new walks
The first
Dr. Destructo Dome thank you so much right now if I was Ewok
Kick-Ass
I'm a policy wonk very much future joke
Gwendolyn thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Switzerland
Did the Sheep Mafia thank you so much right now if I was you walk
Do thank you very much cheap Mafia
Stay first
WTF is an nft you
I'm also confused you sure that's only right
And backyard Widow Farm thank you so much you are also a technic
Business
Money off that heroin
Large
I don't know if you know this but there's two April birthstone
Me
The doctor go correct and also who could forget about Kelly Clark
Forget about those two
We missed this email has been sent to him that I missed it and I apologized
You're welcome to the pantheon of April birthday along with myself doctor gum
Kelly Clarkson
Cedric the Entertainer and Mandy Moore
Everybody remembers his birthday
I'm sorry I just I have it I've heard very little what you said cuz I can't get past backyard Widow Farm
Sounds like murder right I don't know I think it's a farm
I like to believe
The farm
Maybe run by Widow
I don't know what you can put a benign soon or however you want to play it
Bad temper because I went Ama
When is first day of Alex Jones is content
Is deep about the Border a document from Johns Hopkins and apparently the smoke
Open gonshor which is nothing of the sort
I was really worried that I would get in
Today's content
Rihanna would start
Looking at this
Stop back in the present
He'll be so boring and repetitive like these
He's a lot of these issues are things that we've done
At least three or four laps with Alex on the floor
Lot of recycled narratives
Just about
Fairly
I present issues the word ad nauseam come to mine
Yes
Attanasio
Jordan on Tuesday evening
At the end of the war room
Alex called into his own show Ono I'm home
But whatever the case
We got big breaking news
Children music
Gentleman
On this sub
13th today
Thomas Tuesday translation
Twerking videos
Newswars.com
Soda break
News
Is it Alex Randall too long in a special report
About this breaking news
So the well-produced version of it isn't going to come out for like 45 minutes or so
And Alex is going to have to come in and I'll do it on some
I'm struggling here
If I understand correctly
Alex is going to give us a thing
That he already knew
In the past
Yeah but yeah
He talked about it talk about it for
42-minute Special Report here
Tulipan
Irritable two larger than an hour later you're going to see a better version of what he's going to do
Airnow exactly
So important
You cannot possibly wait one more hour we have to get into live programming
This is Infowars goddamnit we can't wait another 45 minutes for this
Feel like if it was as important as you think she could have kept it tight
They get a special report together
Also great Victory Rush has been dead for
For two months and Alex is already spilling his aesthetic
I think it's a good idea
Feel it up I do like that clearly wasn't Alex's choice though cuz he
He calls it out
Oggy cartoon ruined Volusia that they weren't stealing there is a secret hero on the
Swear the more music we here at the right time the more I'm like somebody is watch
No he rainbow too long and that special report that he tried to shoot but we don't really know what this means is that so important
So let's say let's see if he
Get to do it once we go
A lot of this
But now here it is
Sam Montoya
3 years
Honey I love you
He just he just came in Breaking Me
We can't wait
I'm sorry
This report but it's not ready yet
Force.com
Okay so I guess the news so far is that Sam Montoya is a really good guy
And the Galaxy starting to innovate noise you can make it show impressively unprofessional
Kind of incredible it really is
It really is so far we have spent
It's far more time talking about his daughters than we have
The breaking news that he had to
Call
I talk too long about it
This is
This is good
Good stuff
Oh man almost
Disparity
There is a story
Sure so let's see if we can get what we go
Can I talk to a lot of smart folks
Sam Montoya
Going to town
Virginia
Executed by the way we don't know the name
The police officer
Just got a traffic stop
Along with this
Systematic criminal operation
Here's the deal
The story that Alex is trying not
The cover is that Sam his cameraman got arrested and charged for his actions on January 6th
The capital Shore
Alex doesn't want to just say that so instead
Here he is just reiterating it's a good guy
He's trying to come up with every possible dogs you can think of an order to not deal with the reality here
That clip was less than a minute and hear a list of
The qualifiers that Alex is trying to bake into the story before even telling the audience give me a list
Sam is a good guy
The capital on his own never seen him before in my life
Force
The capital of Dominica cording to what Alex
Claim the same told him
Frankly I'm pretty sure he's a ghost
5 Sam was the first to get
Footage of Ashley Babbitt being shot
I don't think this is true
And if you watch Sam's livestream from that day you'll see him trying to negotiate with John Sullivan AKA Jaden Acts
Who captured footage of the shooting
Get the footage
For some reason it's nefarious that we don't know the name of the officer who shot but we do know the name of the officer who shot
Minnesota
I have no idea what that has to do with anything that has nothing to do with anything but it's always a good idea to Django the keys of races
Is it my way from the very real problems
Dealing with ya
His primary motivation in telling me stories to make sure the audience knows that's a good guy
Wasn't wrong to do it
Fairly certain
Even told the audience that Sam got arrested
We already have multiple claims that Alex had nothing to do with this s***
This whole thing is a simulation I put the world on trial
This is f****** shadowgate
Greg I've never heard of anything no idea what
Please talk about good guy
Speaking of shadowgate I realize that the Matt gaetz thing
It could be the Gator game
It sure does I don't lie
Like that I think we're in a situation similar to that I imagine it took Joel Greenberg exactly
5 Seconds
To give up Matt gaetz
I think I think it might have been even less than that the FBI went to his door and he was like
Y'all want Matt gaetz
I'll give them to you Sam Portnoy is not
Protecting Alec
Likes in this circle
Mia and me and a friend had this joke
That we would always tell each other like we would
Smoke together weird
Bouncinbooty sitting around passing
Back and forth and having fun
Always do is like
Tell each other about how we were going to rat each other house
Republican
Absolutely
Artifact over each other
That's that's how I feel like
Matt gaetz nobody never even
Finally get to the park here at this episode
Special breaking news where we find out that you got a ride
Sam is a wreck
Long story short
Late for that
I got a call.
FBI was 30 people that raised his apartment
Pier in Austin
Employees
Rob
Cool
Rap beat
Samogon in
But he's okay
Not only was Sam arrested
30 f
Bi agents came to get him another before staff have been harassed
Max's totally free
I've been trying but I can't find any proof that the arrest went down the way that Alex
Has claimed
He's shown a picture of
That is a hole punched in it but I don't know if that was from police ramming it or a random person
I'm kicking it I have no idea
Iceberg Jaden X or John Sullivan
That's what I was going to be out
His main defense
Sunday longer special report that he rambled too long.
How much is the side of the John Sullivan led the attack on the capital with
News by CNN scot-free
That's definitely
Sullivan has been released with conditions
But he's definitely still facing
It's a very serious charges
Is and they have not been
Been dropped
The brain is just
Yeah I know that's
It's yet
System you can you can get out while awaiting trial
CNN did not pay Sullivant
To be applicable
How it goes on to repeat the figure $70,000 is the amount that Sullivan was paid but this is just a misrepresentation of the facts
CNN and NBC
Both bought his footage from inside the capitol each for $35,000
There wasn't a pre-existing contractor agreement it was just
CNN and NBC acting
Exactly the way
Did Alex's Caravans Sam did
When he tried to get
The footage from cell phone
Sullivan inside the capitol
So yet but I do I don't know
According to CNN's spokesperson
CNN was contacted by a reputable agent regarding an eyewitness video from the Capitol Hill riot
The company entered into a one-week agreement for use of 44 seconds of
Picante
Which is attributed to the witness on air
What his role in the event was later called in
The question the company informed
Amstaff to seize all use of the video
Strategy is going to be the point of John Sullivan in pretended Sullivan instigated the riots that you paid by CNN.
Deuce out an idea isn't facing any consequences
Your poor Sam the cameraman is getting arrested just for being in the hood
Reporter
It's all nonsense
But it's about the only angle you can
Can take your the Titans the feelings of aggrievement correctly
And you can profit off of
Yeah
I mean I can't even really think of it because you don't want to turn Sam into a person
Accusation
Too much
You know you don't want to turn in my out as long as people give him hold on
I mean like you do want to make him a victim if I could make it really all about your
And we are dealing with a world-class making about himself
I wonder if that's what you behold next episode
Anyway here's the last clip from Alex's
Breaking in
Into the War Room
Coming up soon again
Where the country is all showing on WhatsApp
It's not a detailed report and we're not going to listen to it cuz
It's just longer but about the same
Stop yelling about dropping
So now let us jump
April 14th
Cuz I wanted to see how Alex is coping with the situation sure one of his employees just got arrested what's the new story
Things that I think is really into
First thing is that
We've been aware that Alex had that cameraman who was
Inside
Like we do on the
It wasn't really much of a secret around it and they release the footage of him
Yelling infowars.com while he went into
Well that's because the FBI
Is just full of great investor
Well I actually kind of figured they probably were aware of this and it just didn't rise to the level of someone they would want to charge
Like that actually kind of surprising that there was a charge
I don't think he's going to get in any trouble I think you'll be probably released
Maybe if life on the wrist
Who knows
It is kind of surprising to me that they they did end up charging
But I'm not
Surprised
To hear that you know
That they're cooked
Anyway Alex
I just don't
I didn't know how
Was going to land
Outside of those pretty sure he's going to make it by himself
You know John bowne
Has been a long-time boring voicemail
Special Report
Yes he does
How to play those special reports generally in the first six minutes of the show go out on the raid
Your vegetables out of the way a lot of stations are their own soda station identification
Stuff at the top of the hour
This is kind of no man
Play some John bowne reports there with his dumb boring voice
But there is a
There's a guy who's been really Making Waves
Haha
You never heard of
He's another guy who's got these special reports
But he does another little video maker in Austin at the Infowars
And he I think he's making a run
The crown of the weird voice
Special Report
Immediately following the death of Nikola Tesla
Engineer with the National Defense research Committee of the office of scientific research and development
Emily President Donald Trump's uncle was called
Officially concluded
Speculative and did not include workable methods
Tesla's papers disappeared but his work most definitely quietly continued
I hear that B driving music behind you
About how Tesla's work is that the underpinning for Jurassic technology
Confirm hidden from
The public I didn't know what was going on but I was
Excited
I always liked this is how the shows started this special report that is weird really more interested
Hidden Tesla than I am and whatever other b******* they're going to Sprouts
So Greg Reese
He wants to blow some Minds talking about some of this
Physics stuff in wireless energy serious stuff figured out
Steve Bruce diplomas spinning ball experiment from 1970s
Repeat two steel balls are repeatedly launched with equal force
The other is not the spinning ball consistently flies higher and Falls faster than the other
This is in direct violation of both Newton's Laws is relativity
Really
Major league baseball pitcher throw a curveball you know one of those things that's on TV during the summer
162 X is amazing
Plenty of explanations for why this phenomenon can be seen in different rates
Tissues that there's no difference
For these objects when you try to conduct these
Experiments in a vacuum
Do you know like if you didn't have other forces at play
Then they would travel to same speed whether they were spending or not but because
And nature in the world and other forces that come
To bear on the object
Not stupid
The force the gris-gris is ignoring here is called the Meg
That's a fact
The reason why pictures can throw bending pictures or why tennis players I'd spin
The spinning object in the air exerts a force on the air that it's traveling through and in the process
A path of motion is effect
Is it a well-understood phenomenon
Completely compatible with Nutella
I guess Gregory's didn't really look into this
This before deciding
Spinning balls or somehow they
Very hard to research the American baseball
Stores that you can find countless videos of people doing this like dropping
Things from really high heights
It's because it is really cool
Be cool to look at
Anyway so this spinning for stuff that no one
Explain Tesla
Maybe but we don't know John Trump didn't look at
John Trump
Trump's uncle
He's involved in the cover-up to know that Bruce DePalma is interesting
Nope
I also don't think that's
Apparently
The
Creates this
Electrical force or whatever
We're going to use this
Horse somehow
Sure
To create UFO
These patents look very similar to what whistleblowers claim production for years
Manufacturers such as Lockheed Martin Skunk Works the same UFO lightcraft whistle
The Blower's claim are being prepared to stay alien invasion
So we got a fake alien invasion
I'm coming
Proven
These
Spitting
Knuckleball Dam
It's a it was an interesting Special Report
I think that the music really does a lot of work
I think I think I think
Greg
To think our greatest science
They're going to use of split-finger fastball to develop
UFO
Yeah that's that's
So pretty fun also I would question
Turn what this has to
To do with the globalist
Plans
I don't know how a false flag alien invasion
15 with e
Larger schemes
Yeah we're supposed to be afraid of
Play BB and kill all of the people with kind of mixer by 11 for the UFO
That would just be like
Hey look we're going
I'll do the Superbowl weapon thing
But let's have a little fun
I mean you know what I will give it up to the devil
Innocent it does seem like
He's got a lot of plans up in the air at the same time and if he's juggling that many plans
That's a talent of itself
You know I think
Did stand-up you know sometimes you to have somebody who's like I'm going to start my own clothing line going
Start a video blog
What you got yourself a lot of plans
You're not going to do any of those maybe that's
Species of the Devils running into the old Volkswagen
You didn't even kill leave
You know what was the boy
Now
Stupid
Also what
What do you think
You should be more afraid of
Extermination or world
Depends
Cuz I kind
Cervix cervix because I feel like in Alex's scheme now with the devil's Bland
World government is not a necessary step
Towards exterminations true
That is true so I don't know why the devil would
Need to push for that anymore
Well if you had okay
Okay so it's the devil
Hanes world government
He's gotten through the loophole that God said
Keeps him from limiting
Human free will maybe
I don't know
And he just
Gets to exterminate people
I don't know man this is what happens on Gregory
Starts the show problem with with both I guess
UFOs Anza Bible
Comes in
Breaks things off with like
Some real serious
Head lice
Let me tell you what we got for you
Everyone is starting to
Call out South use a fraud
Mainstream news
Worcester now confirming is where
Covid-19
Absolutely huge
Version 2 and version 3
Super deadly version
It was just a drill
So Alex is just talkin about a washing
10 times headline that doesn't prove
The clams that are in the head
Speculated about Medline
Yeah that's all that is I was pretty disappointed he doesn't talk about it
Waze later
The CIA Woodruff
Fused
Confirm that it
Wasn't
Creating a lab
So people have taken that as speculation
Badger
Probably
Intuit I guess it all along it's not
Polluted as a
The possibility but we're not the most likely possibility
And there is not evidence
That it was
Right that's the issue
There are a lot of issues
Anyway
And I do trust
I didn't know whether or not we were going to get into the same issue early
We're late I didn't know
I turns out
Dive Right In
Rated
One of our
Coming up
The media is just an actor say oh my God we're so close to arresting Jones
Take us off the internet.
Try to block
We want Jones in jail he masterminded
Capital Tax
And now they're just
Fixing
The intelligence to
Go in line with all of that
So I guess this is the first instance of him making it all about himself
Immediately
Today they got
Sam which is actually about me as always
I would be happy about this virus a.m.
Insult
So Alex gets to talking about his charge
TS2 with charger
Any might be a little bit off
Infowars reporter Sam
Arrested for
January 6th
Chapel riot
Making Wild utterances
Wasn't charged with making loud other ince's
The charging documents Republic in East Mesa
5 charges
Entering and remaining in a restrict
The building sounds like it did that to disorderly or disruptive conduct in to restrict
The building almost there
Three violent entry and disorderly conduct in a capitol building
Competing Passage through the capitol grounds or Capitol building
Bia map of mob in front of the door
5 / 8
Menstrating are picketing in a capital bill
I could be wrong but I don't think it's a going to get in any real trouble about this unless there's some kind of information that the state has
But I'm not privy to like where he was in Greater coordination with people than we know
I don't know
Unless that's the case I would guess he's going to get a slap on the wrist and maybe not even that
What are the charges about disorderly conduct and violent entry is described like this
In the filing
Quote
To willfully and knowingly otter loud threatening and abusive language or engage a disorderly or disruptive conduct
At any place on the ground
Or in the Capitol building with the intent
Impede disrupt
Disturb the order the conduct of a session of Congress
Or either house
Congress
Or the orderly conduct
In that building of
Overhearing before already.
Deliberation
A committee of Congress
Or either house
You can't go in there and
Scream go f***
F*** yourself
But framing that isn't getting charged for loud other inches is
Fun because it makes it seem like a government's trying to punish a
Super yelling go f*** you
Yourself to Nancy Pelosi
That's not quite as the context
Text of it
Is making loud utterances
Vickers 5 charger
The documents are right there
Stop playing games
But look man everybody's trying to jam Alex up
What is the part of it
They had all the major mainstream media Wall Street Journal New York
Most people in offer money lie about it
Cowboys
They have done Facebook scam searches
On any
People take selfies
Restaurant
These women will get a call
From The Wall Street Journal
Betty wants to photo
Okay will do
So
Thousands of
Call by The Savage
Criminal operators of just
The actual left
Intelligence agency crime Lord
They control the FBI and order the FBI
TuneIn going reverse engineering
So these media entities the mainstream media are essentially leftist
Crime Lord
They run the FBI right here comes up with his stuff and then
They reverse-engineer investigation through the FBI
I2i Jam someone up
I think I think the Alex
Is used to people he knows
Like Jacob Wohl
And James O'Keefe operating like this with attorneys
Traps
And that's the news that we're doing even though we are the ones doing it and they are
Because those people that are in his fear do this stuff
Did he think
Did everybody does
And I think that he thinks that's how media and news operate
Which is
One of the big things that we can
Can see is a problem with
Jacob Glanville
The elk
There
Because that
Undermines confidence in any and all media Outlet
If you are
So brazenly corrupt about it
Yeah and and if
People have it in their mind to it
Equate the two
The
The people on
Are in anyway and elegance to the media journalism is lying
Your way into buildings to surreptitiously record people and then edit together
Misleadingly
That's what people believe
That's great
That's good
That's good for the 4th
Thestatebank
An article about Matt gaetz the Gator game
And
Well Alex actually read this article
Attended
Party for drugs
Maybe some huge party in Miami or a big hotel suite party
And the women went to the media to say he was really nice and he didn't give us money
And we didn't even see him using drugs woman said I song Take a
Who won
But he was really nice and the women were all 2530
The end of the article
Another woman's I'm getting offered money to say
He's a smart guy
He's admitted he's a party animal Hailey's for drug legalization
That is the doesn't need to go down like this
It's unnecessary you involving yourself in the story will be like that's fine there's no way out
Places involved with his math game story if you wouldn't keep involving yourself of the booze
I'm an alcoholic
So the actual headliner this again
Story is in payments after late-night parties with Gates another
Does seem like a different headline than the one that I like really really different
These parties of gates behaving
Like a frat type of party boy
Sometimes taking pills she believe we're recreational drug
Bills
Ever believed to be recreational drugs whatever
Alright the article mentions these women being paid by Joel Greenberg but not directly ever by Gates
And they quote
Never saw anyone at the party who appeared
The underage
Additionally the women disputed the characterizations of what they were aware of
Happening as being
Sex trafficking
Could just need sex work
Yeah I don't know why I like I said Alec
Even like
Just
Touch the story get into at all without like
Some some personal things about himself
Very weird
Yeah it is it is
Feeling a little
A little like
Oh no my son is in trouble I I kind of I gotta protect
To this poor idiot
It's very weird
Yeah I wouldn't
Do that no
I would do anything else
But get involved and then tell everyone I'm an alcoholic on it
Speaking of things you would or would not do
Sure if you were Alex's lawyer
Did you tell him to say publicly about the whole Sam issue I would tell him prob
Probably to say something along the lines of
We don't believe these charges are accurate and we are fighting against these my lawyer has advised me to say nothing
Beyond that
If you were Alex's lawyer and you advised him not to say anything
You probably wouldn't want to hear this
My lawyers I would not talk about this
Closest
I'm not going to sit there
I'm going to put out a million-dollar bounty
Set the record straight
My lawyer told me alright alright here we go
Shoot that shoot that shotgun bulshit out us here comes Alex
Here's the story he's going to be sticking to it I'm trying to kind of freaking sister
Fully
Carnival atmosphere
I told Harrison Smith
NexTrip
We're all there
He's a good guy and said well I'm going to go with them
People
Pasta
Find out later he's in the capital that day I got the
So
Alex said Sam couldn't go
Alex says you are
Sam can't go to need to stay here and
Road to us while we're there I know it's going to be a carnival that you got to work
Yeah Sam says f*** that imma go talk to Mike Lindell
And apparently goes to the
The capital with Mike Lindell
Let my pillow peep
Okay
You are so then
Everybody that works for Infowars I assume is now an independent contractor
Completely unaware that Sam has gone with a My Pillow People
Finds out
Sam is in Washington DC when he finds out that he has footage
Correct of the woman being shot at the same time
Sam was along with Tyler Hanson at the
Time
Who was burning a black lives
Matter flag
Troyer the night before shared a hotel room with Owen you would think
Mitre
Text messages
Or maybe
Sam was there when they burn the Black Butterfly or seems like it might have been hanging out
Yeah that's really cool bird in the black black lives matter flag
Kind of puts it out of
Carnival atmosphere it or into bloodthirsty mob atmosphere I don't believe for a f****** second that they were
Worthington awareness that he was there in DC it's it's ridiculous
Just now I don't know what it means that he went with the Pillow People
Mike Lindell that's who you like that
You should go see the My Pillow People they're the ones in Fort Worth
Mad that he didn't give me the footage
I wish you'd give me the footage but I'll tell her this moment when I
Definitely
B o a
The next day
6 * 7
Alex
Hey dude
It's f***** up bro terrible idea
Bro
Gonzo
Hey buddy
It's all good look up with the My Pillow People now it's all good man
Gemini Sam
Talk to you soon
We'll see
Here we are
Couple months three months later
DC what's the name
Unfolding
Soap
I really don't think
The people on the right
Really understand what unfolded on January 6th
And if they do they are lying about it
Well I think one of the problems is that you know
The ripples of the
Fake s***
That they came up with to make excuses about it
It's taking a while to catch up with the reality of
You know Reality Tea
Keeping on exist
Yeah it keeps going
Whether you like it
Alex heard
Sam got arrested
And even though
He told him he was going to be in trouble on the 7th
Right Alex then
Last night
In 2021 last night
He interrogated people
Heading forward Studios what was Sam up to the f*** out
Interrogation
People here last night
Messages
Sherlock
Well he told me was going with my pillow
Akwaboah
Okay
Usually when facing legal troubles
I really want to check the messages and make sure I'm telling the truth
I've literally no control over anything
Nobody knows what I'm doing
I don't know what everybody's doing
This is an anarchist outfit legally no one was
I have never met any of these people talk to Sam
On January 7th
Amman in April
He's interrogating people
And checking messages about something that he clearly knows what happened has no idea
Hey Stan I don't underestimate podcast
Navigate Sam's involvement
The piano app serialized
Yeah if it look dude
I mean
This story doesn't
No it does
But
Who cares
Low-level
Family Guy been there three years
And sure enough
Went on his own volition when I don't say that
To lie Beyond even
What's wrong
It really sounds like Alex is trying to be like I didn't have anything to do with this s***
Story that Avon barksdale's lawyers tell
My client has never been anywhere near drugs he's never seen any of these people before I don't know
Businessman and a large character in
Community quite frankly Bode is second screen
I would tell you he was only a mid-level manager he didn't have much going on selling drugs on his own and even if he wasn't
But he wasn't any good to hear that
I would be real unhappy
Here I am in prison for Infowars and Alex
Yeah I think we're going to see a little bit of a shadow gate fall out of this was
Unfortunately Sam has been let go
If I were Alex I will be going out of my way to
Say everything positive about this guy
350 you know what Rodger Stone said about Trump when he got hurt
The nicest things anyone has ever said
Oh my God
He prayed for
Look at it the other way Trump said nice things about Rodger when Rodger got arrested
Anyway
What's with the lawyer from
The wire Wynn
So Sam got jammed up because one of his family members
Tipped off
The
Enforcement
That's a family member
I guess they weren't watching Infowars
It's not something I would recommend
But Alex is all over the place talking about like
I was this close and I said you don't see a nice guy
I'm not going to I'm not going to
Even though
Family member we know who it is
Family dinners because he's
Big Trump supporter
Videos
Andre shop
This is all over the place man it's weird
Yeah a more important person somebody not on the second
Can string would be getting a nice little defense fun boost we're setting something up to help him instead Sam just gets a nice
Obviously we hope he's doing well
He will definitely be working here when he gets out of jail 100% I will not be firing a video
But again it's important to remember that what's
At stake here and what's real about this story is not
It doesn't even involve
Alex
Course
Capital
Presidential
Media
Pass
It's all a fraud in a hub obviously
For non-violent offenders
Wow
It was a lot for them to have a
The goal of sherbet
Alex can't process this story accepted as it being
Part of an elaborate plan to get him
If I were Sam I would be a bit worried about how my arrest was being used as a prop
To justify Alex
Is completely out of control narcissist
I want to take this circlet piece by piece
Okay
The first little piece here is that Alex is claiming that Sam just said America standing up
That is not true
Quotes from the charging dock
Okay
We've had enough we're not going to take you
Your f****** vaccines
We're not going to take all your b******* people are standing up
That sounds like something he might say
Here we are the US Capitol in Washington DC in the Capitol building
He's been officially it is officially been stormed by Trump supporters
Again the US Capitol building in Washington DC has officially been
Storm by Trump supporters and here we are taking are the people's house back
I wouldn't want that anywhere where people would have that on
Recording I especially wouldn't want
To say be recording myself while I was saying those things
It's not in the list of quotes in the charging document but my favorite quote from Sam's livestream was when he was walking in entering the
Capitol building
Hey doesn't plug for Infowars store
It seems weird like maybe if he was there with my pillow he should have plugged them but ever heard
I didn't send him down there but it's also a one-way Street
Second string
That's brutal
Pieces that Alex is claiming that Sam had a press pass
That is also not true
Document
The directors
Congressional press galleries within the Senate press office
Cuz didn't name check on Samuel Christopher Montoya and confirm that no one by that name
Has Congressional press credentials as an individual or via any other organizations
I have no idea what Alex is trying
To claim but there's no way that Sam had a press pass to be where he was
That's complete bull s*** and there also wasn't any other like mainstream media
Videos that have come out of in that there were played on other outlets or things
People purchase
From the folks were there legally inside
The middle of this
Bloodthirsty mob
That hate
The media
I have one of those hats with a little card in it
Real Outlets it really feels like Alex
Is heightening this to a point of absurdity
This is my area of interest in what I cover and honestly I don't think I care nearly as much about the arrest as I do about Al
Alex's respond
It's complete
Someplace sensationalization
Where Alex is trying to walk this interesting line where he has nothing to do with actions
Consequences that are coming to say Marcy
Secretly an attack
On him
This is how a narcissistic mind would interpret
Something like this
A Galaxy's blameless
And all negative consequences are secretly applaud again
And if I was a
I realized
This is a plot
And I am being you
I would immediately go Oh he's a vicious narcissist Ono
I think that he was anything but that who would help me out in my hour of need
No but I mean look
It's all about getting out
How much calcium show there are now hundreds of news articles proliferating like mushrooms
USS Pearl Harbor
Pearl Harbor
Again Alex is making this all about him
Self
I failed to find any mainstream media articles that fit the
Nobody's talking about it again
If he actually means random tweet
When he says media articles then there's nothing I can really do about that
It's just the delusions of a liar
Also about that Pearl Harbor
This is just Alex misrepresenting comments made by Chuck Schumer after
Storming
It's very very difficult to put into words what has transpired today
I've never lived through or even imagine
An experience like the one we've
Just witnessed in this capital
President Franklin Roosevelt set aside December 7th 1941 is a day that will live in infamy
Unfortunately we can now add January 6th
To that very short list of dates in American history
They will live forever in a
Alex is taking this and twisted it into Schumer saying that the storming of the capital was worse than
Temporal
But he said no such
Interesting Lee there was a recent comment about Pearl Harbor
That you might find interesting
Quote
We went through the worst attack we've ever had in our country this is the worst attack we've ever had
This is worst
Then Pearl Harbor is worse than the World Trade Center
There's never been an attack
Like this
I'm going to go with
Paul Ryan about something 10 years ago
No it was Trump talking about covid-19 in May of last year
I'd like Alex's comments on that I'd like to see what he thinks about Trump saying the covid-19 is worse than Pearl Harbor at 9:11
You know you don't need to worry about
The things that Trump says
About the Bible
To give right right right
How does this
This vibe
Right
Sure Sam
I'm so so Alex
Has nothing to do with this
However Sam was there the night before with Owen
Well I don't know I got actually I'm not a hundred percent sure Sam was there the night
When was in the capital
Tyler Hansen was there as well that the singer was with other was sharing a hotel room
Black lives matter flag
It seems like there is a very
Clear associate
Chain
Sorry about Sarah
Announce that this Vibe it's like it's unfair
Like other people protest at the Capitol and they don't get arrested
I don't need to say that I didn't send standing there
And I needed that cabin all hearings
Congress people on the elevators
Walk the elevators at all that stuff
And nothing happened to those p
They don't all deserve to then be indicted
When the police officers wave
What's the second time Alex has gotten his name wrong
Motel
The guy who is a good guy
Play If I was a sandwich
Racking my brain
10% that the unrelated to any crime
Fox one time it was Alex
As for the Kavanaugh protesters it feels like no one got arrested there to Alex
Because he doesn't care
Right
In reality you can find articles about Mass arrests took place around the Kavanaugh hearings
CNN article on October 5th
2018 about 293 people being arrested
Police for unlawful demonstration
Motherjones article list the arrests
So at cavanal protest and if you add them all up
Not including the group one from that CNN article you end up with
662 arrests
The Kavanaugh protest
That's a ton
And the main difference between then and now is that he's a
The Kavanaugh protesters
Didn't try to take over the fuc
In capital how many people did they kill
Alex pretends that don't got arrested protesting Kavanaugh because if he acknowledged
They did he'd either have to argue that they shouldn't
Have and then be defending evil left
Or he'd have to accept that there were consequences for people's action
Concurrently Sam is experiencing what a lot of others before him have
It was a risk that he either knowingly or unknowingly accepted when he decided to film himself going into the capitol with a bunch of lunatic
And recognizing that Dynamic is a big threat to Alex's entire pitch about how they're all victim
Yeah the right has
No idea
What it means
To actually protest
No like they just
They just don't
Get that don't like the idea about accepting consequences that you put yourself
Shelf in these situations
Yeah
Accepting that something will happen to you
In order to
Stand beside Acosta people
The cause was
Is important enough
That you risk
Whatever consequences May Come
80 legal to occupy
This space and sit
In the capital
And
You do that
Knowing that the consequence
Could be that you get arrested because he will bring attention to whatever
Cause
You are there protests
Whatever they
F****** want yeah
Yeah it's so bizarre for people who are
I just
So if
Interested in personal responsibility
Do not understand
This dynamic
Oh well it's not
Bizarre people who are really interested in personal response
Possibility are usually really interested in
Other
Yeah baby
So I might down for this because it was
So weird
But another defensive Sam is that he's got a lot of hats
Is wearing hats
He was wearing a Maga hat when he was there literally
Because also wearing a journalist hat and also just like hey I'm cool guy
He got really really dramatic footage
Because he was operating as a journalist there and try to stay well
He's not a journalist when he's
Everybody can wear
To be out playing golf
You can be a Star Wars premiere
I'm guessing that Alex is referencing Gary Player
But man that the weird pool for him to make as an example of somebody wearing two hats
80s come on man just
Hellboy
I think it was on Alex's mind because Trump gave Gary Player
Medal of freedom Road ever
Victorville
There's a slight difference
Between a golfer giving a unpopular opinion
Or you making some kind of a political comment when you're on a red carpet
I think the writer little different
In the middle of inactive
Participant
In the storming of
Have the capital but you're a journalist because you have a camera
Yeah they like to pretend that it wasn't a massive bloodthirsty attempt to take over the entire country hope
Hopefully triggering Trump to in
Institute martial law so you have everything under your
Control the circumcenter
To deal with that
What the circumstances are a little bit weird to me because it's not analogous to someone had like a movie premiere saying something political
The reason that I
Could be really funny
Is there still gold was let's say
Storming the capitol
They were wearing like Godzilla vs. Kong merch
They argued they were just do it for motion
Have a marketing major also I am attempting over there
I think I remember that whenever they stormed the Bastille came out with
Copies of his book at
He's like just while I'm here
Where is there going
Bmore Free Press attention than it is storming
You want to get the word out about your movie
That's the place
Says it has anybody ever said no press is bad press my friend cuz that's the truth
I don't think it is argument holds up
In my mind
That he's wearing two hats
Legitimate advertising strategy
F****** Disney is like okay here's what we do
We're going to storm the United States capitol
And then after we've done all this damage we're going to remove our shirts all at once
And it's going to be the next Pocahontas movie everyone's going to blame soybomb
So I got this real sense
It's kind of a normal son
Answer get in situations like
Obviously making this all about himself
Duct
But
Hello
Talk anymore I Really Got A Feeling
Kind of felt like he is mad
It's not him
It seems like he wishes it was him who got arrested
Disrupting would be blocking him blocking the door
Shutting down the hearing
Quickly eyes talking about when he went to Congress and yelled
Did Sundar pichai
I don't believe you should do that
Angry also because
R45
Angry hours
And they said my name at least 67 time
Congress people
Bring me up the back row
When Rodger Stone going there's the Russian
There's a spice right there
Fire trash
You know it you're the globalist butcher in this country
I did
Was
Ten times more aggressive than Sam
I deserve to be indicted
Or what happen
Fraud
Stall application of it's a fraud
It's garbage but please arrest me please I want to be a martyr it would get me so much of
Secondary attention is not good enough
What is this what is this just a second
Considering cameraman that's getting the rest of my name into a martyr that lead to movement worse
Confidently knowing he won't be arrested or inconvenienced in any way
So we get now to that Washington Post
Washington Times
Headline but Alex was talking about earlier in the episode
Is dr. fauci the father of the pandemic
Credible Washington Times article
Just yesterday
They had hundreds of groups funding it but
His program was Obama continuing under
2 years before
Covid-19
Intuit
That's the fact
Those are the facts
Exitos
I think that makes Trump look worse
Incredibly stupid if any of that were true which it's not
That would make Trump like
A willing
Participant
Biowarfare guess cuz it's not him just letting the program
Continue it's him being like I got off this program and then a couple years later than being like
Come on let's kill everybody
Real bad yeah yeah
So we know from looking at past episodes of Alex
The show that
When I first learned about Anthony fauci
Towards the beginning of the
Man among men
He's going to test personally the fight
Cuz he was Alex thought she was saying stuff that work for his
Conspiracies
On the bus
Also we know from listening to pass
Episodes
Steve pieczenik
Used to think
She was one of the best in the business true
Cuz they went together now
That is true
Right turns out we have a new villain bags
Story
Copies in shark
He's been involved by a weapon attack
Kelsey is the guy that runs the operational program
For 40 years at least
A week before I'm uh
Dirty mouth
Get out of the un's dirty mouth the whl's murderer
He's the one
Okay
Look at us
So dumb
Can we date
So fat she's been running bio-weapon attacks for like
40 years
Steve pieczenik the great Insider who knows everything and is overthrown country right equally
The Forrest Gump of world history
Thought he was a great guy until like
Just now I know I would say that's a genic. He was a great guy
Until he was the
First person to be
Kid with covid
He cured himself
So once he got infected easy realize
Fauci
Had been lying to him the whole time he even since he was young I don't buy it
He was actually recruited into this program
Woody was 0 years old he was
Is grown in a lab dance
Since he was
0 and a half years old
He was also exactly five foot eight
I think I proved it
That sounds right
Yeah I feel like the more and more you try to
Parody what Alex is talking about
Yeah it's a
It's not far off enough to actually really funny
Far I can go
Comic book territory
So Alex
Complaining about this article really dealing with it at all but the headlines fun for a picture
Another Hadley
I continued dog from that
And does it continue on from the continuation perhaps ride contacts for this headline
Is the first line of a meme post
It's been going around on message boards and Facebook since at least early December
He was initially attributed to an anonymous doctor but sent
Has been claimed to have been written by dr. Rob Oswald
A virologist an immunologist at Cornell University's Department of molecular medicine
Cornell is out of its mind
How about dinner
Right that he doesn't agree with the sentiment
More easily when you pretend to someone effects for
Forties in a particular feel the same something
As opposed to some random idiot on the internet
Tristan said that this is what Alex is covering it is stack of news
This is something that passed the test which should be printed off and covered on this program which is just
Pathetic. Oh my God it's not even
It's not even new
New memes are just old
Memes waiting to be reused
Straight
Something else was getting reused as Norm talking Patty really
Nor Pac-Man
Lawyer extraordinaire guy who had to sit
Silently and awkwardly while Alex put a bounty out on
Is a Sandy Hook
Enemies there's got to be it. I think at this point Pat has has to be in it for the stories
You know like
20 years from now he
Sitting at a bar
Just been like
I could tell you Tales
And I suspect that maybe he's flown too close to the Sun
With Alex
Might realize
It might be starting to realize like a
Thing that he's trying to write like you know how some some strippers
Or sex workers of the like they like I do this and then the read a book and they go on Oprah
Ignore bad is going to do it I don't know cuz the
Boars that I hear norms
The more I feel like he's being more willing to say Infowars
He stopped before it seemed like he had a little bit of restraint
National he seems like a real f****** s***
Introduces him
Also gets
Sam's name wrong
Again
I wanted to get Norm
Criminal lawyer and constitutional lawyer
And also does work for us
On the 1st Amendment
Issue
He doesn't know all the facts
Limited
Songs about
With our Infowars
Wow
Sam
You got to listen to
Broadcast
I'm just going to change things for you this broadcast put you on a path to a better life trying to do you dirty
Funny things about Norms appearance here on the show is that
You get a real sense
But he's kind of trying to reassure Alex
What's that like
Your clean your good man
What I know and mr. montoya's k
Cases that he was arrest
Induct on the capital that day
I understand.
Federal authorities may or may not be aware of that
Mayor may not have
From all the cons
What he was doing that day
Question that will have
To be sorted out in a court of law
You obviously my pore
Primary concern is you
I do not believe there are facts
Excitation
Tom 2 warranty
Further
Nation of you or and much less than an arrest
I'm a p
When the time comes
Ithaca
I don't know it's from everything I can see publicly-available
Probably right
He was
Promoting Infowars while he was live streaming going in
To the Capitol
Who's
To say if Alex asked him to do that door he's even aware that he was doing that
Tubi
But it is interesting
He's going to have to go to court
You're cool
Hey buddy
My primary concern is you
He doesn't pay me
You do
And let me tell you something right now you keep saying what you're saying
You never met the guy
A good night
Get to talkin
About the shooting of Dante Ray
Is Minneapolis
Minnesota
Yeah sure I want to get my lawyer buddy on
To do that
If it takes
Saturn
For the
Let's talk about this is just now breaking we know the name of the female police officer who said
And then
Keyshot until Dante write
He's in the middle of rioting
Easter
For armed robbery
The city's burning the police station shot up
Employees filing she accidentally shooting
In the fog of War that's what happens I'm not glad it happened
But he's a frog waving guns around on the internet
You know all this
Somebody
Probably one person got killed
Alex is making up almost all of the details
He was pulled over for having expired tags
Plates and having a hanging air freshener
The boxes mirror
You wasn't playing with the police though does appear that he's trying to get back into his car before he was shot
There was a misdemeanor warrant for Wright's arrest
The body was unrelated to an aggravated robbery charge you gotten in December 2019
It had to do with missing
The court date for a misdemeanor of carrying a pistol without a permit
Something Alex should not think
Conversation to have about the shooting
It's literally impossible to deal with any of the real underlying issues if you're like Alex and you insist on creating a
Completely fictional version
Events to tell your audio
It's important to understand that Alex does this all the time
Real events become sticks
Chat with hesitation
Tons of details and subplots that are real
And it's critical to understand how he uses
Fictional augmentation of real story
Because it's one of the easiest ways to
Duffy is biased
When is the black man who's killed Astoria supplemented with all sorts of
Extenuating
Stances and details
The make it's so sad
But the guy kymatica
We seen this play out over and over again recently with George Floyd and Ahmad Arbor
The opposite is done when it's a white person who's killed
Abby's also grotesquely in the case of
Kate steinle
In reality and immigrant found a gun wrapped in a rag that he didn't even realize with a gun
He picked it up the gun discharged
In a ricocheting bullet accidentally and tragically hip
It's dynamite
Alex's retelling of the story became Mateo where
This immigrant sauce steinle with her dad
Who the Immigrant thought was her older boyfriend and the Immigrant was
Jealous
That you was with he was with someone so beautiful he couldn't have her so he killed her
These strategies are in touch
Because reality is not what the real
What the real is this white supremacist ideology and archetype
You can try to justify by using real life events a tragedy this prop
And you see that
That's very teriyaki
I mean
One of the things that I think is really
Important whenever we're talking about Alex Jones
Stand things that he does
Oftentimes
It's it's less important to look at what
Is being done as like the structure of why
These things are being
Alex is creating side
Stories
Sim details
About the story of the shooting
In order to make it more palatable for his audience
Any does the reverse
Wipers
Who is been shot
It's just very obvious
Whenever
You know
Alex said something like we're how am I racist
This is this is the key Grandpa
This strategy and this tactic
Is
Fingerprint
Immediately obvious simply because
His argument even if he says it
It's not okay for the cops to kill p
His argument always boils down to it's more okay for the cops to kill black people than white
His behavior is behavior dictates
Has to be
Tripped out in his
Situation so
There you go you're a racist
Piece of s*** Alex is taking issue 2 with
The fact that the name of the police officer in Minnesota was released
And that the author
Professor who
Shot Ashley in the capital
Has not been really
Sure
And then normal
X in
Gus's closes investigation the death of Ashley Babbitt
Investigation like
Social Security
CIA
They close investigation with another person's name
President here
Norma what do you think's going on here
No idea
I mean a nest
It's not transparent
I know that had she been black
And there were no charges no Transpo
Guaranteed there might be more riots industry
And then we'd be
Talking about the need for a soap
Called racial reckon
Are you a lawyer
Did
Man that's cool a dorm
The bar is not as hard
Pool Norm
Jesus Christ
Wow
A racial Reckoning
Yeah I'm saying that the reason that no one is concerned with who the capitol police officer
I don't even know if I'm going to allow that
Yeah stipulation to stand
I'll be saying that to be with everyone would be up in arms if it was a black person who got
Wow
This guy's a lawyer
Nope
If there's ghosts
To the neighborhood
Neighborhood
I would call the Ghostbusters
That is correct
Who would other people call
There's a wrestling in your house
Good night maybe the house burglary who'd you call
I would still Call the Ghostbusters
Those proton packs
Can powerful
Do they affect people
I don't know I've never I mean if you cross them they'll make something come
The life I guess
You and Norm
Calling the police is essentially attempted murder at this
I'll tell you something if I hear Russell
The door tonight in somebody's trying to enter my home
I'm calling 911 I'm not
Call in blacklight
S'matter
That's the kind of statement that I hear in my only response is
Okay
Alright
Alright man
Yeah
Cool
You call black lives matter someone breaking in your house they're not a police organization
Irishtown
I just don't know
Are you really going to use that as
The thing that the
Acceptable to say
It's really bizarre
Because
I think I think we might be dealing with enormous trying
To get into a second
Line of work he's looking for that Millie Weaver slot that opened up I think he's trying to get into stand up
Oh no
Try my debut at stand-up
Comedy the other night at a small club in Connecticut
And I buy ended my wrist
The following hey you know I tried
YouTube I woke Insurance the other day
Crowd looked at me what's
Smoak insurance
Assurances
I'm reading the paper
And everything in that wrong with this country is my fault
Insurance
And we're at a point where
Sort of humor
It isn't necessarily
Farcical any longer
He's going to fit right in in
Standoff
Wow
Listen
Eddie's a bitter white dude he's going to go straight to the top
Or at least
Straight to every single open-mic I've ever been to in my entire
Vanessa's going to keep on growing
Wow
I don't know I feel like if I were interviewing
My lawyer and they
Decided to get into racist hacking stand up
I might be
Considering a change in representation yeah yeah yeah yeah
I guess I'm going to call Saul Goodman from here on this is
Not good that's not good
Don't tell me
That you started to do
I don't want anyone to tell me they started doing stand-up nose
Norm f****** panic
Market B
Sia
Yeah I would go with
The structured if you're buying low Pinterest
Okay let's do this let's say you're awoke insurance agent
Right
Girls meets rury
It's the right okay so I need Wilkinson
What is the protector
It protects you from if
People are writing so flood insurance
Sure that is like
Okay so if my house floods right this takes care of this
Is this this money that I pay when it doesn't
Floyd
Is so whenever it does flood if it does
I'll have money
My flooded
Totally
I don't know Scream the n-word people
I'm not that doesn't protect you from
From that it only protects you from the racial record
So if a racial Reckoning occurs
You're going to want Wilkins
Okay so your immune
From these quote-unquote racial Reckoning if you've paid your dues to your woke
Why would we have woke
Insurance what do you think this is some sort of scam
I don't understand what it's for your light man and you need
What do I need to tell you
The world is changing Dan without this woke Insurance could be left
I think a better way to tell this bit if she waited normal
Wants to do it would be
Something like a protection racket
You know it's not insurance it's Insurance like the mob
What kind of Russia
I mean isn't that like more the vybes drink
You said the n-word if you play if you don't pay your woke dues and I'll come and get you or something like that
He's trying to do it would make sense I don't understand
I mean I think it protects you from being Dogpile down for being a racist
Sza said how
Well if you get dumped over being racist there's a potential loss of income or of course open
Your pay
Mario mod
Bright
Eyelid whenever you get dog piles on for being the races position you harvest company comes around school
Find out this guy gets a free rental car we cover those
I meant but do they have to be like it's cool it's cool stop the dog pile or whatever
That implies a imply
That the people who are doing the dogpiling
Rite Aid for the
If you hold as a record Insurance Company
Runs the world
Yeah this place could use some work
His delivery could use some work telling people a stand-up joke outside of
The context of a comedy club is a bad idea it is
Yeah song from Bad stand-up B
Stu biblical analogy
I heard you say before the brakes
Itasca
Listeners to go to the Gospel of John
The story of the
The chick man
You just want to
There was a man laying beside the
Newsela
He was begging for somebody to move him so that he could be touched
By the water Jesus said why are you here
Wannabe into the waters he said that every time the waters move others beat me there
Jesus wept
Did the manatee didn't create an affirmative action plan
Create a
Program for a racial or disabled Reckoning
He look at the man and said words
Did I don't think we
Often enough to one another
Bed and walk
And the man did
The Power Within himself to take care of his own situation has I believe we all do but my view is the next
For something on account of your skin color
You're working on a Thursday night in mid April 2021
Almost glad that he got cut off by the break and we don't know what he suggested you tell people
That's good
So when you are alone
You do realize that other people do not have the
Capacity within themselves to defeat the law
Does that make sense
Take your bed and walk
I feel like that's at
You are advocating any at all personal responsibility
And also I just don't see Jesus being a man
You can't walk in
I'm thinking this requires a top-down structural change I think the whole point of
Jesus was
Time to stop the whole thing about Jesus is that he did miracles
Isn't it
People got healed by Tasha
Periodically
He was always covered in what are you alright
What's left out of the Bible that Jesus was a very wet man
I would say
Oh yeah
That
Basically with Norm is doing here is using a biblical story where
To get the message
Across two people to
Stop complaining hey you know what
I think if you ever see if I saw
A Slave
Obviously
Play I would go up to
To this would be like hey we need some structural changes here because I'm a slave
Look at him and I would say get your bed and move
See
Everybody has it within themselves
To solve their own problems no doubt about that
Your stick
And get the f***
Is what Jesus
Jesus said
By the time that Norm is on hand to Alex's talking about a story about
Patrice colors one of the co-founders of black lives matter
Apparently of some attention is come to the fact that
The cheese bought some houses
I recently and Alex
Vista CA
Blacklivesmatter
10.6 billion black lives matter cause last year
Prednisone do investigator
I mean
Do you moved into all white
White supremacy
Call Rouses in the most white bread
Because she's trying to recall
Colonized
The continent that was stolen from Native Americans into
Can fit her neighbors
By showing that we're here and we met her
Oh boy
Hey
Forever is what you might as well just said
Kind of saying like
If this person so worried about whites
Supremacy
Bolivar all white neighborhoods alone
That does seem like nuts
It does seem like the point he's trying to make as if you're worried about white supremacy you should leave our country
Patrice colors have released a statement on Instagram about
Assertive
Questioning of her her money tour
And she said that she has a number of different careers in Revenue sources but they quote I do not receive a salary or benefit
It's from black lives matter Global Network Foundation
She didn't say that investigating her or questioning her is white supremacy
She did say quote
This effort to discredit and harass me and my family is not noon or is it
Unacceptable
It's taken away from where the focus should be
Ending white suit
Damn that's Pinterest
Dubai Alex to say hi
It's white supremacy that invest
Norm takes off
I think that was one of his worst
That was one of the most blatantly racist things I've heard Norm say
Yeah I mean the stand-up bit alone
Yeah that way
Like maybe
Third on the list
Comes back and
He decides he's going to take matters in
It was on hand
About this whole thing about the
Non releasing of the name of the cop see if he wasn't such a
It's such a bad lawyer I would say Norm pattis should be there for that no normal to get out of there
Responsibility
To release
The name is
Reno
You know everything
Information
I believe the public has a right to know
Okay I believe that
Yeah
Yeah I would say generally speaking if you just have a hunch
That somebody is a person of interest in this case
Report that
Here's what happens a lot whenever
Somebody reports the name of somebody accused of murder and says
As best we know this is the purse
A lot of times it's not
Can you really
F***** up there live
Yeah it's
It's something that you can't really take back never they can't really predict what the audience's response
To your
Shity reporting will be totally
I don't know what you expect people to
To do even
If you are correct
I don't want anyone to go after this person what else could people do you give them the name
I don't understand
The people have a right to know exactly the person I totally don't want you to Target I am however giving you the name
Strangely enough I'm going to read off the address as well but I don't want people to bother this person
Listen at all
I am
Getting a sin
But Alex is pissed off
That he's not being
Oppressed like his buddy Sam and so he's going to throw a wild curveball
And try and dock somebody and see if it gets him in trouble so he can be the real victim
And also he wants to
To be clear
This is
Just because he believes that
The capitol officer is black
And yeah that makes
Stomach
Okay that's what he did
I know is
We know every white cop
That kills a black
I want a black person kills a white person we
Don't
About it
Holyshit
I would say like
Demos
Emperor of motives are being expressed here in terms of
Alex wanting to save this person to me
Very much open
That's
That's one of those things where it's like
You can
Not say that
Yes
You can you cannot say this person's name because you can't prove that it is the right person
To single them out
Second you cannot
Say on air that you're really just pissed off
Are they race
Issue
Your white aggrievement is a is a racist anyways I expect
It gets racist more
I guess
So when a white police officer or a police officer shoots a white person
Person person
But when a black man
White woman it's never open is
Because
Only whites
Exposing
We're not listen
We're not saying insert the only reason we would be saying this
We're not saying it because of that
We're definitely not saying it because the only reason anyone could say this
Outrageous
Now we're not saying it because of this
The only possible reason we could have for saying
Jennifer differ
Alright
Galax wanted
This to
Blow up pot maybe get him in a little bit of trouble
Seems like the one that much trouble
So you have the Fall Guy he's never met before
He has a fall-guy it happens to be the guy who was in the capital with sales
Tyler Hansen
Pretty good investigative journalist over the years
And Michelle before he and others
Which
Boss monster
You don't normally see that do you like some citizenship
Reminder backyard
Sometimes you don't
Sometimes names aren't released
Yeah
You know I don't know
The sound
Evolution
Fast moving vehicle
The mint meant to carry
A bunch of people
Yeah
The Tyler should be hearing right now
Cuz it's covid
Rocket
Trouble don't worry I'm just repeating what Tyler Hansen told me
Also also the guy who burned the black lives matter flag with Owen Shroyer
Very good in school.
Pretty good pretty good
He's a pretty good advantage
Paint sprayer
Kind of so f***** up that it's like if I have to
Explain to you
The difference
Between
Running down
And chasing a child and shooting them
Or
F****** choking a man to do
Versus
A mob of
People
Storming the f******
Capitol building
Trying to
Tear Down the Walls
Running with people with
Guns and God damn
Everything if you can't see the difference
Between bat
Type of shooting and not
There's no point
Talking
Intentionally obtuse you don't for me to communicate with you if you don't
See the difference
Assuming that
The person
Who was the police officer in the capital was black
Trying to play
Pretend event V
Relevant difference
Between those two issues
Is a racial one
Statues
Absolutely absurd
But it's whatever was want to do because it helps
With the white agreement if you will that
So Alex
Is going to name this guy I don't believe it and just because
I looked into it you can find it being like
I like
It all goes back to
Two-timer handsome
He tweeted it out it's out there it's public so it's not like
You're not that I couldn't really find
Easily I might believe it
Rush because I don't want to add to this
Sure but
Just for the sake of demonstrating that Alex is
Completely under
Confidently
Not knowing at all if he's correct
Naming someone as a shooter
Not the officer
I sure you
The foyer
Now that's my lawyer to do it
Avascular 24u
Because we have a right as depressed
Right2know
Taylor Hanson
Twitter
So again
Handsome said
This name
But I'm not saying granny of those insert reason
Way larger platform than Taylor Hanson
I reported but I'm also going to say that maybe it's not the guy
If it's not him maybe
He could call them and correct me about it
You accused of things
We're just asking questions and if these people would come forward and tell us the answers we wouldn't need to ask anymore questions
What is it definitely not something we're saying in bad faith you've never heard this before
Say something
Similar to this
A bad face
Claiming that Bill Gates
He's in the Council of twelve or whatever because he posted on Aaron Bill Gates
Dakota Lee if he waving wasn't in the Council of twelve he would have
Call
Incredibly deferential
Because he's powerful and I am a coward
This is not how it works
I like the idea that he does California foyer
Like whatever
Towhee
He understands that that's something that
You might be able to do
Meniscus
Because
The investigation has closed
And so there may not be a legitimate law enforcement
The reason
Not release the name of the person short
Now if you do that
You could report the name
Exactly
You can't do
This
And then be like hey
If he's not the person
He should tell us
Meanwhile damaged
But done by me saying that the person
We're never going to do confirm this later on
With a foia request request something that we
Do so often
I pronounce it correct
Like I said it's clear that his entire premise here is that he's just mad
That the white
Cops game shop reveal
Can we do Nokia
Potter
Black Warehouse
Police station burned down
That's okay
Candlelight download she deserves
So there you go
I mean it's just too obvious
That's like what is animating this and what what motivated him to behave in the ways he is
Like
But without that motive
Did this behavior is unacceptable
Having this
Kind of a reckless irresponsible
You're going on
While it's being so obviously motivated
Buy feelings of white identity
Security +
Hood
It's multiple layers of unacceptable
I can't believe
He's this transparent
Yeah I mean
It is kind of a truth that if you cling to White
Miss eventually that's the only thing you're going to have
Like clinging to the color of your skin as something important
Is going to push
Everybody out of your life
Eventually
Or it's only going to unite you with other people who are
Clinging to White
And they'll tell you until you find a difference between years
Exact until it's time to shut them out for not being
For colored hair
I think it many ways it comes down to two
Just like having a mentality that is so entirely based on exclusion
Yeah he's going to exclude
Yeah and it's going to
It's going to
It's going to go that way
Now at this point
Alex Costa
Owen Shroyer Who's down by the border
Trying to get more footage
Stopping
Smugglers
I guess that's where I would want to be
Bi would be what I would want to be near the u.s. Mexico border if I was Owen Shroyer
Now just like
I'll take a little step over here and now I'm not in trouble.
Come and get me
Extradite me for this
I didn't care for any of that
I'm not going to
Play This Dance Now
I got really mad
It Alex
Because of how
Disgusting this
Display has been
For most of this episode from the first hour
Then I got really excited about
Any just f******
Teased me
And then separately I mixed into my sax and I can't
You guys
Get me the
Do John Hopkins
Documentary Jamie White Road
I got the document but I can't
Polygon 2021
Mobiletron stimulation of coming cyber pandemic
Freakonomics
This is the blueprint
John Hopkins is like the main horses
All the global sugar tester drills at Greek Mayweather
Top of their field
Computer science
Psychology
You got a headache
You have to hit that you literally have
The hit that many didn't
That's the most important story I've ever heard
Cyber polygon 20-20-20 one I got to know
So great the great reset it happening and it's through this a polygon 2021
Play found the documents and everything and then I was never brought it up so I don't get to talk about it
Anyway
I thought someday soon
We will talk about I want to talk about it
I think the struggles with his like I got really excited there's primary documents here it is actually
Something interesting maybe we can talk about
But I'm not going to bump things Alex doesn't even
Get to yeah that's not fair that's not fair you
Vague
Anyway what we talked about cyber polygon
A very excited to say about it
It's always good to be one step ahead of the
Roadrunner
Unsatisfying though cuz
I'm listening to this b******* about Sam
And then Alexander getting racist as hell I hadn't like
At least I've got cyber polygon to look forward to and then it doesn't happen
Oh man well s***
I
I'm telling you
I think second string Sam should have been on the second string for this episode
Should have been cyber polygon 2021 all day more time on that been trying to
To make Sam's arrest about himself seem like it
I think
I think this is
Yeah one of the first times that we've had an
Active Infowars employee get arrested
And so that's kind of interesting that was one of the reasons why I was
Like we got a we got to get into the
Millie Weaver got arrested
Did but she was I think that was unrelated
Totally unrelated
Is not law
Honestly never met her before
Bing
You too tired
Pretty quick
Very quick and then like Joe Biggs got arrested but he's a former employee
Rodger Stone
You know he's he's Rogers
What is a lot of immigrant
All right but they can work it in for
I don't want it back
Another episode hopefully covering cyber polygons
Who got something to do we got to do something with that
He's from now on
Eventually we'll get the trailer polygon
But until then
Twitter is ethnography that go to bed Jordan
We are busy
You could please find a local charity or bail Fund in your area to help
People are doing
Arrest for loud
Utterances
Alex
Birthstone colors
I love your work