Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
Investigation, I'm rushing by investigation into Alex Jones
Think about Alex
So weird
Megyn Kelly interview we have done and now this
Post-game interview
I'll tell you what
She fukin nailed him to the wall
Dammit
What I think ahead of time
It's very predictable
Haha Alex Jones does
Knock-kneed tape
Secretly made of these
I don't want to call Megyn Kelly ship
Because
That's not fair and she has
A career behind her
She's a trained journalist
And it's easy to armchair quarterback
Right the reality is she
She got so close
She got so close and also so far
There were a couple moments where
Couple moments
Push it push it
It's clear that the intention of it was Sandy Hook
Right it's clear that a further intention of it he's too
Make more
Explicit
The connection between Alex Jones and Donald Trump
Okay things are very clear
I wouldn't
Say it's necessarily a hatchet job
It's just
It's not good
It's not right it's not what she should have done was it
Was it an
An entertaining interview like this she accomplish that
Not for me but I know a lot about Alex Jones
You know so I ate for me
There were a couple moments where I was in
Impressed
You might have listened to our ship
Certainly not but it's like that's outside the mainstream but cuz there's a couple things that have reached a zeitgeist
Niceville
Turn frogs gay
Call
There a couple moments where she pulls out tonight
Islamophobia
The entire report let's just started off we go with we're sheep again
Pregame interview that was
Sticks and a half hours long
And if you cut together the entire interview this time
It will be
Some suggestions of what I wish you would have done
Certainly and I'm sure you'll have some of your own but I think
I think we can probably get it done an hour I think so
First tonight
Our report on the incendiary radio host
Alex Jones I'm already out here is Jones has been spreading conspiracy theories
Claiming for instance that elements of the US
Allowed the 9/11 attacks to happen
And the horrific Sandy Hook Mass
Tucker was a hoax
Some thought we shouldn't broadcast this interview because his baseless allegations aren't just defensive
They're dangerous
But here's the thing
Alex Jones isn't going away
Over the years his YouTube channel has racked up 1.3 billion views
He has millions of listeners
And the ear of our current
Presidents
We Begin our report with his reaction to the recent terrorist attack
In Manchester England
Introduction to the
And I really don't like the town of it
Because it sounds like she's
Yeah there is a submissive not like a woman
But there is an implicit like
You guys
The president
I just I just wrote down rationalization
Like
The first thought I had listening to that intro is she
Heard all of the criticism
Cuz I'm assuming that this was
This was recorded after
Exactly
So this whole thing is like
We are. We did this interview you told us not to
But here's
Why we're doing it
Gree with the basics
Premise
Hey guys take him seriously
That are Prevost didn't come from
Is not
The president listen
To him yet millions of viewers
Because I didn't Powers him
Write the angle
Hewlett out-and-out bigger
He is a monster
He lies all the time
Which is very reminiscent
Of the president whose ear he has
Right but if you make that lines though
So they're going to do but who make such a big deal out of that then it
The dumb people kind of reinforces our
In the same way the press credentials are in a loser anything with you can just get them
Done
It reinforces him in some people's eyes I think it's the wrong way to go
Over
A billion
This man is
Powerful
I have reached
He has
Millions of list
Regardless of whether or not
Is in order to make the premise of her peace work she has to build him up
To take him valve course
Kind of foolish
Because if you have the introduction being like
He has the ear of a strong
President
He has billions of listeners Bible by all this
All you're doing is
Making your job harder
If you say hehe
To him
But people who are being lied to
Clearly demarcated
Most of his narrative
Have to do with bigotry
Most of them have to do with
You can come at it from a more robust
Perspective
A man away that doesn't
Explicitly empowering
Butt cheek
Open
You could I could do it yes but
Keycaps
Probably not
Yeah probably not it would be would be like
That would be a fuk
Flamethrower across the bow
Yeah
F*** out please
He's an emotional guy and he does
People on an emotional level
Because really it's not on a rash
Oh and Megan tries to play some of those games that emotional
Post office
It's a completely in in effect
If she induced
They wanted to start
With the Manchester
She gets into that
And here we go
Alex Jones with nearly 5,000 miles away from Manchester England when it's 2
Suicide bomber killed 22 people at a concert less than 4 weeks ago despite the distance and width
Jones
Mouse first into controversy
He said it was a bunch of liberal trendy's
Who were killed
The same people who are promoting open borders
Bringing islamists in
Yes
In response to which many people looked at the victim
Transformers 1514
I'm sorry I didn't warm up
Either
Rose Russo
8 years old that she was a liberal trendy
I guess that's what you said about the victims is what has people upset misrepresenting
Clipping
Right out the gate Alex
Heard about it
The age of the victims weren't even known
But they were saying it was
And I said how crazy is a liberal trinis are now the victim
And then
I certainly looking up
Horse Canter kids
Call Reckless accusation by vacations
Is classic Alex Jones
Megan is giving a little bit too much
Leeway to the audience
To draw their own conclusions
Straight up just admitted there
I've made a video and I made these claims when I didn't have any of the information I didn't even know anything about
I didn't know any of the details
She should have pressed incredibly hard on that
That's b******* about that
Weird
Said that it was the parents fault
That their kid died
The parents
Who supported open borders
Were the cause of their own children's death if you were to bring that up too
I'm not talking about how to parents off at their kids died
Deal with this for a second
Before we get to it
There's a lot of Sandy Hooks up here and apparently I have
Seen it but I saw on Twitter
Sandy Hook videos
Tonight
I'm not 100% sure on this I should I should reload his channel
And see if there is a video
But he has put out but from what I understand
He was going to put out a video
Speeding to
Father's Day message
Call f***
F****** cry
Apparently play mainstream media
Start a dialogue directly with them witches
F******
No but itself is abusive to these families so
It look if it wasn't about murdered children that's great Rollin
But it is
So it's not
He said about Manchester even in this interview
Yeah just allowing him to lie on television
And not pressing issue 2000
You just said that you didn't know what you were talking about when you
Posted this video that people are going to listen
Right people think it's the truth
But you
Yukon
Say that you are always
Incorrect
90% of the time you are always proven correct
Dumb dumb
Anyway
She gets into discussion with Trump
On The Fringe
Shouting his conspiracy theories into a microphone. On Austin Community television
I want a deposit for a second because the way she frames at the entire time is
Conspiracy theory
Exactly
For the last 6 months
The beginning
No absolutely not
I know that you got it
The limitations of newsmagazine shows
Understand you got to work with internet working
You can't say something that could get you sued because
It's so reductive
Typical him a conspiracy theorist what are you don't follow up with
Most of your conspiracies
Really dovetail into racing
F****** masculinity
Yeah
Did you think that's interesting out
Absolute
She doesn't really get into that kind of
Just like we I don't know if we talked about this on air
Text about
No new station
Directly come out in
Say
URS passing whitener
That's not going to happen
Nope I'm not the only thing that you have a channel
Even if they interviewed like
Spencer they wouldn't be like
You've you've
Declared yourself a white
The stuff that I saw
Charles Barkley giving a side eye
Berkeley being surprised by things that Richard Spencer
Look I'm not going to say that that is
That's another issue for another day
Tina's company Infowars for years
Producing radio shows and webcast
Which reach
Million
He attracted a very famous man
Presidential
Donald Trump
I just want to finish by saying your reputation is amazing
In December 2015
Offering praise
Promises
I will knock you down you will be very very impressed
And I think
So
I think there's a really
Bad missed opportunity
Tea2go
Like the investigation that we're doing it
If she would have just something
Run bedtime.
And heard Alex saying
Donald Trump is a con man
He's a front man for some
Consortium
East Coast
You could make this part of your interview really much more interesting
Because
Praising him and their soup
To be like what's the deal with this right
Then there's no there's no pressure
Amazon
I mean I hate I
Truly believe this
If you are researching Alex Jones for Megan
Gene Kelly
You are dipping into
Get what you want and then you are getting
Like legitimately if they knew about
Yeah because we have done it already
We have the information
Chicago sucks but it also
This is me sucking my own dick a little bit so
You may I mean
Again
I still you're the only person who listens to Alex Jones
Critically
Yeah well
I mean
I would imagine that a lot of it is
Is just
When you're listening
Because this happens
Tons of people who would listen
The radio
You just phased in and out
You're listening
Something I really like something
So
Anyway you don't remember
He deals with an emotional level
And so you don't remember the dumb s*** he
Really easy to Just Add Water
Exactly what you remember is
He made me feel like I would had a voice
Yeah why
Remember when his narrative was a complete b******* like
But the damage is done he made you feel that way
What is the serotonin your brain the dopamine receptors
The oxytocin
Some came out like
You just had an orgasm
Barack Obama
Common sense
Was good for Infowars
It's 83 million
In November 2016
More than five times higher than the previous November
And when mr. Alex Jones
To the seat of power
For the first time
Mr. Trump called him after the election
Thank him for his help
You have said that it's the real
To say something
Couple days later
I mean but
On July 22nd Infowars video
Show drug trafficking
We don't know what it is
A drug smuggling operation from Mexico
So that it's from episode it might have gotten lost in the sands of time
We discussed this in our investigation
Went down to Laredo and Merriman and then lied about being chased by Cartel
She found
Whitten kids you never hear what maybe a lost episode where may. You may or may not
The point that I lovingly made was that if they had caught a cartel
They would be f******
King beheaded by
Fingers
Oh
Prince dog
Made up there.
Yats
That's good because that's not something that's necessarily wanted to attack
April 2015
That's cool I forgot you so
Slater Iowa
Guy swimming across the
Big bags of stuff
Trucks
Swimming across
The river
This was Infowars previewing the first presidential debate
And Hillary Clinton
I think she's going to show up
And on drugs. Not long after
We should take
Donald Trump Ally infrequent Infowars guest Rodger Stone underscored the connection between Jones and the
Trump campaign last spring
It read
Alex Jones
Helps make the Trump Revolution
All that's another good
Because a lot of people aren't talking about the directions
Stone and John's right
Char cell I mean yeah it sounds like a very good TV show
God forbid it ever happen
I disagree I think people are aware that Rodger stone is on Infowars all the time
Know who Rodger stone is
Beyond that all of those things
Again buttress his credibility
Or buttresses import
Right
Repeating him
Rodger Stone
Trump
Is that they were
So the quote Trump Revolution and now there's a little piece of the interview that she plays
I think my tan first
Glance soundbar
But I don't think it does
Donald Trump
Call Michigan contact with the president
Radio show
He downplayed it in his interview with us
Claiming the mainstream media has exaggerated
Msma said
He's just called sometimes
Would you describe yourself as friend
No
And how many times has he called you
I want to get it all
So that sounds bad because obviously
The numbers very low
Yeah
Did people who
Are inclined to think Jones is pretty cool
Would be that is humility
Discretion
I don't want to talk about that
That's not important
Well I think
My initial reaction
He was saying
I don't want to get into that
Because the number is so large
Like that's the idea
He wants to get off
Is the perception he wants to leave
Because
It happens
You know it happened
More than you would expect
And more that you would be happy with
Well I sure to the beginning of exaggerating
And what's the point of that is today the Trump is his own man and I can't influence
Clip
Out-of-country
Which is very much like
When he was saying that stuff
He was also saying
I talked to
Trump all the time
Like at the zoo if you recall if you call the stuff that we
We listen to
He's saying you know
I have
The ear of trump and then later on that
Turned into
We don't talk
But he's just doing the same Americana
He's office game
Is it a lot
Is it a little
You don't know
Exactly
Like you can tell that it's additive
I don't think there's anything that they play that is misrepresentative
There are in the video
That's how you make
He is not doing it
A terrible job of setting up those clips
Prefer less of an nprc
Yeah it's a little it's a little in that wheelhouse
Cadence
It bad that kind of tone and the volume
And whenever you
Sort of allow him to he's going to lie
It's a little bit later there were a couple of
The couple events
Listen to the fur
Can get flummox
A little bit
You need to go in for the Haymaker
I need to knock him out she just doesn't have that right hook
She just doesn't have whatever punch
Is needed
Maybe it's a lack of information baby
Mabel
Or McDonald
Maybe that won't this the
And it's not
Like is it entirely
Possible that
Well
What we've seen from Alex of chess
Constant like aspiration
It's the end of the world
And what is
Like maker and they just didn't cut it in
It serves everyone purpose in terms of making money for them to not demolish
Exact to shame him emotionally right
Anybody's purpose
Actually
Dealing with the problem about
This is conspiracy territory for us
Do like the idea that it is like complete destruction
And Alex was super scared that was going to be in the
And that's why
Whenever they were doing their live broadcast on Infowars of the
Champagne
Yep they were drinking
Champagne dessert
Cheers and champagne glasses
That thing that would have destroyed me isn't in there it wasn't it's not Mike
Conspiracy theory so much as it is kind of building off what you said earlier
Which is that
Or not earlier
Earlier episode
Know what it is
That's true
Like that could be one of the problems there is
And this is
Live in that world
Like they don't understand globalist
No wealthy that's
Yeah there's no call them notice
The first thing you should
Say it
For twenty years
Open yelling about the
Global
Which is
Either evidence that she works
Or a complete unwillingness to unpack that
Because I think it it does become maybe too difficult for newsmagazine television
Getting to like
Dude yeah
Are you serious
I mean it's possible
They wouldn't they're coming
From an
Almost answer
Illogical
Already
Discovery
Kindle why almost
Fair
Yeah
Even when they get into their bout to get into Sandy Hook even that is almost
Nice to him which is weird
Cuz
Cuz he's a f****** mom
So here
If somebody tried to cut down our stuff.
They would have to go through
What
2:00
Route 27
What is the do you think about Alex Jones that President Trump
Find so amazing
Is a conservative writer and contributor to President Trump
Obviously there's a conspiratorial
The presidents
His imagination and darker impulses are fed into by Alex Jones
Jones has 4 hours a day
6 days a week
Can be vulgar in Hicksville
Like this one directed at a member of Congress
Schiff looks like the ark
Kite
Archetypal
And there's something about this f****** around Boston
Tell Congressman Schiff
And all the rest of them
You want to sit here and say that I'm a Russian
You get my face without Beecher MSU son-of-a-b****
So again
She plays that
Are you
You're crazy drunk
That is
How many ways are there to learn Alex
Where is knock
Went through so much just watch that f****** episode 2 you're taking this clip that everyone is being commedia matters bush
So much more
Of that episode
Who gives a s*** about that ramp episode is bananas it's even the one that has begun
Did nobody actually watch that or do they think that it's not going to be
Palatable Isaacson Illinois
I think that everyone just saw the clip that
I got posted around when I roll
And they don't think
What's a complex
Happening now
Oh he's crazy he's yelling he does crazy Yelp
Drunk
Solely
Fascinating
Are we are we may be the only people who have been like
I've never heard anyone else talk about anybody else bring up the other fun
F***** up stuff you said
The other the other is that there's no way to
Conclusively prove he was
Suggest it
Excuse me Alex
Well you went on that
Text Whitfield
Also they didn't play my favorite part which
Which is that he should fill his
Were you
Chick-fil-A
How much Wild Turkey
You drink noted podcast the knowledge fight posted his picture
Don't don't
They posted a picture of you with a drink in your hand
Easy for him to get away from water
Tired
Know the context
Of the cliff
Gotye live
So
I killed with a brick he was trying to beat me up right
But then I was like
Picture of a mom Susan a dog
Like all of those little things of like
How is it that you have dealt with your violin
As a child
Do you not see how that it carried on
From maybe not
Physical violence
But it's loose
Type of
Aggressive
Emotional by inflicting emotional violence on your audience
And eating bystanders
Like everybody who was in Comet Ping Pong when I guy came in with a gun
Yeah Meghan Kelly does do a pretty decent
Job of
Ping-pong all those things and making Alex responsible for the
But not really
Not just pressing
Not really to his face
She doesn't in the MPR voice
Conspiracy theories as a teenager
He grew up the oldest child of a dentist
And a homemaker
We went to high school in Austin Texas
CIA definition
After a brief stint in Community College
Jones found his calling as Public Access TV in Austin
Went into business for himself
Sounding Infowars
Prospect
Million
He got a
Public Access
TV show
84s
Just throw that in the first the first radio
I actually think that's part of the
Overly fairness
No discussion of how his dad bought him
RadioShack
No discussion of how he started Infowars because he got fired from a radio station
To Fair
Enterprise's who started Infowars
His narrative though of like
I am a self-made man
And so you put that in there and it
Megan
Was told that by him
Of course because didn't she didn't do research into it
G
Just bought it and
Didn't know like nana nana.
Yeah your CIA dentist dad bought you
We all know that what great question that would be like your CIA dentist
Reason you're successful right now
Come out shows your host Infowars makes most of its money by selling products
Like males
And
Jones himself
I'm going to cost $45 a year to run
How much money do you make
What am I
That's
The f****** missed opportunity
That is so messy
Like
Press on it
Don't give me Vig bulshit most of the money goes back
How much are you making would you say you're a profitable
Yeah I don't even need to do like
Give me a number just like
Do you
Do you feel like the company itself
Makes money
Do thought you feel like you're financially successful business
Yeah I know
Exactly
Deprived
I have a buddy who are you
Is Brenda mine back in Missouri
I want his big things with you
Whenever you meet people
Just to get aggressive
Hilarious
That nobody really knows
Other than a classic
Because nobody wants to
That there's a class
And how I understood it I don't know this to be true from
Version of that
The way you get around that is After High School
Cycles are so sexy
If you say I went to X wires
You know a lot about them
Went to
America's
We're pretty great
Epis point B interview skus into the controversial topics
Jones uses that money to spread his message
A message that had caused enormous pain
What is Donnie's he gives inject
Disorder toxic
Paranoia
Into the mainstream of conservative thought
Would have been inconceivable a couple of decades ago
Somebody who traffic
Some of the
Thickest
Spencer type
Siri
At the top of that list is Jones's outrageous statement
Set the slaughter of innocent children and teachers at Sandy Hook Elementary School
One of the darkest chapters in American history
Was a hoax
Conservative rewriting
Drive me
Like this sucks dude
Deer that
There hasn't been
A massive amount of toxic
Paranoia
Built entirely around race
Like rewriting history of like
Oh Alex
The first guide
Pedal View
Toxic paranoid
So you're right
You're totally right but he I think
The stand-on in terms of how much
It's been Amplified after Waco
After Waco and Ruby Ridge there was
Theme
But what are we talk
F****** go back to the goddamn nights with super predators
Go back
To the eggs with
Epidemics go back to the 70s with all of this
Comes back
Erase right not the story they're telling
Yeah that's true
You're right
Psyched
Garbage write-off
I already I already I can
Read that dude's f****** backstory night
The f*** that guy before this interview was saying that they gave me villain lighting and what have you
It's just Alex has way more jolly
Another chance
CC and this is this is what I was worried about
Yeah is that
It is a
It is an excuse to why
How bad this guy
Like Megyn Kelly
He's a spouse that's a
Birthright
Megyn Kelly when she was on Fox News
Did not do everything possible to
The fight against the birth
She changed
Hunan that
But when the ship was going on and she was on Fox
He was definitely
We feeding into that no true fact that she ever supported
Explicitly
Everything that's done on the same TV network you're on
I also
You're totally right there's way more she could have done to push back
Thing is that it wasn't
Just part of an institution that
My point is that she was doing that same s***
People are saying
Obama was not born
Right like she was amplifying that narrative
In the same way
She wasn't
Explicitly say had to be fair to just did
She says it was fake
Time in this report
Trump
No and it's another
Excused
Hens that this is
New
This lunatic
Is the one like
Conservative
Because this guy is
Is Morrissey
Damn
Like that's that's what I'm hearing so far
At all of the all of the
Criticism
Is going to come out
Be like you shouldn't give this guy a
And the criticism should be
You should have
Subway take it away
I think you should give him a voice
Inasmuch as like
We sat on the pre-interview thing
Episode that we did
Play that
Play the screaming
About Muslim
Play that anti-semitic caricature
Play that
Stop
Do any of that
Right because again
That's
That's not the thing that they wanted
Play him
Rambling about
I mean hey
Get this
It was in the trailer
Isn't in the interview
Really that's not even in the interview preloaded work
About the chimeras
You worthless
That just
Yeah yeah
Which doesn't mean that there is more stuff in there
The right NPC has
Something
That
Is
Really really good
On Alex
Jordan
You know what I just realized what
We got to do a National Treasure
So you're saying we got to break into the White House
I'm Nicolas Cage you're the other guy
We need a hot chick man Kelly The Hot Chick
We can go in
Diane Kruger right we go in we trick her we somehow replaced the footage with another
But first I have to become president
I think that's what we have to do in order
How to get to the truth
If all of it is just this
Of course not
And then
Seeing him celebrate is very
We won
We beat them
They edited it all
We can we can deal with
All of it
TV shows that it
Stop that
Unreasonable
But the points
But they end up making in the angle of attack
Of the Peace
I don't mean attacked
How many angles detectability
When I write a joke
Angela
Intrinsically flawed
Either an unwillingness or an inability to understand the psychology
Of how to counter
Propaganda and how to counter Alex
Specifically
Sandy Hook
I buried my son
I help my son with a bullet hole through his head
Neil heslin son Jesse just
6 years old
Was murdered
Alarm at 9
And six adults
December 14th 2012 in Newtown Connecticut
I dropped them off at 9:04. Can we drop them off at school
What is bookbag
Hours later I was
Picking them up
A body bag
Alex Jones repeatedly claimed that the shooting never happened
Siri is on Infowars in December 2014
You said
The whole thing is a giant hoax
How do you deal with a
It took me about a year with Sandy Hook to come to grips with the fact
Set the whole thing
Was fake
I did deep research and my gosh it just pretty much
Happened
At that point
You're trying to have it always
If you wrongly
That's wrong but what I already answered your question
You didn't listeners and that other people are covering this I didn't
Alex
Des Peres
One after the other
Devastated
The dead bodies
Corner autopsy
And look every position and play Devil's Advocate
Was that
The whole thing as a giant hoax
The whole thing was fake
That is a bit of a
This is
Play the hate
Yeah because Alex is
Really scrambling
The calculations going on in his head
What do I what's my what's my
I already
He just said that that was basically
But I'm trying to opt
The skate and say that I've played Devil's Advocate about stuff
And put the direct question
You saying it's fake is that you playing Devil's Advocate
I'll keep in mind you already said in this interview
You can
How do I get out of this
His response
Is busy
Week week is f***
I don't know I'm not saying that Megyn Kelly didn't
Do something
The playing of that clip
Which is what we
Didn't think she was going to do
Play for him
Ocheyedan play for
For him know that was just in the Bronx
Impactful
PC himself say those things
But still good
It works clip that we use cuz the one we use it a little bit more
Like really explicit
Yeah but it is the same
Sentiment
It took me a year to come to grips
That was
Sounds good
That the point is he's realizing
Just a direct lie
And maybe Megan had a good rebuttal today
But his answer is just like
You shouldn't let him do this on television
Yes because I remember
Then saying but then
Some of it looks like it's real
The kids going in circles
I watch the footage
It looks like a drill
When you say
Faked
Their children's death
People get very angry
They don't get angry about all this
The Marriott Harbor covers all the evil Wars
That doesn't excuse what you did
Italian
Look at all the angles of
Long before the media even picked up on
Is Inari
I tend to believe that shoulder probably
Did
I can see how other people believe that nobody
Of course
There is no evidence on the other side
And that's fair but you're doing that invoice over empathize with her because
Would be exhaust
Indications are that she was trying to go
Get to the point he is just dance
Messing around
Exactly
With that kind of an
How do you
Forced him in
A corner there but
She also let him get out of the corner
And I think that the approach that
She thought would work is appealing
Human decency
As we've already discussed that.
Not going to be with that's not going to be a good approach
That's again like
He lives inside of a world
They can't
He is a
Psychopath
If he doesn't
He doesn't hangs out with Mike cernovich
He thinks he's cool
Yeah he doesn't
He doesn't care if you take a
The human diesel
He's just going to go back
It's not
Like his response to it
Isn't
Isn't her it's it's not Tara
Like
This is a
Relatively small-scale events
Like
Steve
Sandy Hook
Yeah
Monster that is well they're half a million dead Iraq
Okay
So so his response is
It's like mathematics
I'm not that bad
Like that his
Response
The death of
Somebody
Iraq
On what
I absolutely agree with you
But I'm just I'm just saying that his argument that b******* because in order to make an analog that works
You have to have a conspiracy theorist
The sanction
About Iraq
And Dumber To
Denies that the half-million people who died are real
Then I'm better than that guy
He can say like no one's
Accusing him of killing kids
Right when he says that no one's mad about a half-million dead Iraq
People are
You are mad about that happy about that
You're pitching yourself in the wrong part of the equation
Yeah I agree with you
It's nonsense
I agree
I retract my earlier statement
That it wasn't
The next approach
Moving the goalposts
What about that
Soy protein
Tries to get into for the pieces
Consequence
Consequences
Sandy Hook tonight
Board of Education
Imploring the president to try to stop Jones and other hoaxers like him
Towards our town
Almost four months later according to the board chairman the president has yet to respond
Real-world consequences
A Florida woman was sentenced in prison for
Her defense attorney says primarily motivated
By Infowars
Other victims family members have been harassed or threatened
The family say that Jones has words have caused
Lasting pain
And they fear the harassment will continue
It's disrespectful to me
Or in fact I did lose my Sean
And the 26 other families lost somebody
Could I take that very personal
You know this
Pieces going to air on Father's Day
Correct
What is your message to him
But I think you've flushed to have
Abbas children
Spend the day with
Speak to
I don't have that
That's heartbreaking
That's very heartbreaking
Journalism
Alex
It's really easy to just deny that to
And who follow him
Anderson
Good looking to make a gentleman cuz he's an actor
He's on the fake news
Humanize this fake event
With a bunch of actors and why should I care about this guy Kelly show
Which is unfortunate because
If you have
Cuz if you live in the real world
F***
How
I guess if
That stings
Cynical
How can you listen to that
And not feel
I don't know
Like that's f******
Even though response
Being not f*** you
The response being you should be
Glad that you have your kids
Because I don't
And
Empathetic
Response to
It's a trauma and then dealt with it
Italy is on the other side of
Unfortunate
There has to be another side
If we can
Take a step back
Not dehumanize but take a little bit of the emotional
Peace out
I think that they
If it's a
Again it's a good approach
And I see the perspective
You trying to build
You she's built at the beginning this
Connection with Donald Trump
Disconnected
Like you
Reported on Manchester
Nation about it
There was a sort of bedrock
And now she's gotten
Sandy Hook
She called him a little bit in a
You aren't really being
And clear about what you were reporting
Connected that
Himself
Jason
You have the
The power to help us out here
Yeah and Trump has done
Is there nothing not even to make a steak
Not even
And in the consequences year will be the next Blue Line
I think on one level is a good approach
But only two rational viewer
Viewers will see like
His
His actions and his wife
Why is that he puts out
That these families are being victimized re-traumatized
Who publish their phone numbers and email addresses
I am so cheap
She uses that
Detransition
Into other
Conspiracies and other
Instances of Alec
What is nonsense
The consequences are not limited to Sandy Hook
Conspiracy theory
As pizzagate
Infowars
And specifically pointed to a Washington d.c. Pizzeria
The photos and videos inside these places
His listeners to investigate the case themselves
Did
Bringing a semi-automatic rifle to the shop and firing several rounds
No one was hurt in the shooter was arrested
The pizza shop owner
Facing the possibility of a lawsuit
He did
Tom and Jerry
Oris employee
About it though you know
There's no interview chunk
About about it
She just
She just reports that and then
No and that might be because he wouldn't answer questions it might be because there's legal ramifications
Like that right there might be thing where he doesn't want to get food whatever
Liberty is only in criminal trials
Civil Trial I kind of get I kind of get it
It is fair it's it's okay for the news Beast
You've established a hook
Stop the quinces
You're linking a direct
Consequence
The guy throwing up with a gun
I am then he have him having to apologize
Which if you are awake
If you're watching
You draw the correct
Conclusion
This guy
Is doing a lot of
Dammit
He's not just a conspiracy
If there is not just a liar when you get
The real world
This guy
Is a
Twerking real threat
Real
Roshe is in as much as
You know unstable people who listen to it
The Hebrew
Yeah
And that's good
And she likes it to another in
Justice spring
Chobani yogurt after Infowars
That Chobani employees in Idaho
You miss stated facts about Chobani owner
Which you could have found out your credit report
Hold on
You are lying
What Megan said there was really good
You could have just had a reporter look into
And then you wouldn't have had to apologize
You could have anyone do journalistic
Okay good question
This is my statement on that
We know that was basically a PR of them
Reported sexual assault
You are the one who said that
You were wrong
About Chobani
You said that
Well that's
Because
They chose to
After me
And so I simply
You don't sound very sorry
Attack about stuff about settlements
You said things about Giovanni and his owner that were not true
Are you sorry
Again there was the media of really was upset that they said that there was a hoax
Car wash
So what did what the media did and we know it was the medium
And we have the puppy eyes in a law firm
But she said she Bonnie was real happy to get out of that lawsuit
What's a lawsuit
Clear Infowars was the only media Outlet to report the LIE
John to apologize
And with that apology
Chobani considers the matter closed
This is such b*******
Nonsense
Now it's the idea that your Bonnie is glad to be out of the lawsuit
They got what they wanted out of it they wanted an apology
So in that way they are
Sure yeah
Lawyers and all that s***
Time
Energy
All of that s*** we went over it in the April 25th episode of the show
Chobani lawsuit
The issue is that there were lies that were being reported on like Breitbart and world news WorldNetDaily threat
They were
Really salacious scandalous stories about these child
Sexual
They weren't reporting what Alex
Was reporting Edward David Knight was reporting
That was
Straight up
These immigrant rapists are being imported by Shivani
That's why I looks got in trouble
Whatever Breitbart was recording of reporting whatever all these other places were reporting
Was wrong
It was
Salacious
But it didn't say
Specifically did those that's why he was in their crosshairs
Megyn Kelly would love for it
To just be
He didn't do the journalistic work
Conversation
You could have sent a reporter
Listen Megan
I've never sent a reporter goddamn
What's a reporter
Which actually weaves
Where Megan brings up the question
Do you think you're a journalist
Which is a fair question to ask
Do you think of yourself as a journalist
A journalist that work for me another journalist work
There's no script
Instead it's a free-wheeling spin through piles of articles
Straight off the internet
And then
Disgusting
Ascertain the veracity of that article
We all get measured media has got a big problem
Yeah
That was that
But we all get that Hillary was 15 points ahead is a legitimate answer to the question she just
Alex's Tire narrative
Whenever someone attacks who credibility or whatever he's always wrong
Hillary's poll numbers
Question
To just repeat that
Is the ultra bad follow-up to a great point
It was really good
If you don't have any ideas
Discussing it for 2 hours is nothing
Well we all know Hillary was 50
Points ahead
Is there
After this clip is there like any follow-up question
No not at all
Maybe in the
Indiana
Lying about everything
I think
If if I were to go into the heads
Megyn Kelly and her producers
I would guess that what they thought is that that looks so silly on its face
But it's fine to leave in as a crazy
Recognizes is at least 30% population
Of course that the mainstream media
Too but that Megyn Kelly has
So she's already off the books
Anyway she's not realizing but that actually is kind of
A good punch back
Write to some people
Now we're coming to the end here there's one more clip
Disappearance
Number one ding dong
Owen Shroyer
Roped into this
Because I would say
I would take that clip and run
The f*** with it
Oh yeah because it's like
Okay
Lights out
Which I really think is a large
Of what this
Profile is about
But just without spelling
Pulling it out without being like you guys are f****** shill
Also in the unedited interview Megan
Kind of gives him an elbow is like
Hoveround
Now Owen
Your you're
You're great
I really love your racist Muslim impression the other day
We all know Hillary's
The Infowars staffers we met have free reign
To cover
Whatever they like
With virtually no oversight like Journal we spoke with some of Jones's employees including Owen Shroyer
How do you
On a day-to-day basis figure out what you going to do
Wake up
I look at the news
Hi. Pray I rarely get directions from Alex or my boss pretty much leave it up to me
What you consider yourself to be a journalist
You don't like calling it that I'm going to be human
I'm just a human this looking for truth so I'm trying to reach out and be what people want
Music people
Queening
The deplorables
The flyover country the Forgotten American
We're going to get to work immediately for the American people
With the election of Donald Trump Alex Jones has plans to expand Infowars
More Studios more shows
More employees
More influence
Said that I
So this is what we just got to be Chad
So I just started a war for me
Alex Jones with a powerful Ally
Just two weeks ago the Trump Pence campaign
Notice
At the bottom
It's a link
To Infowars
Set the end of the Peace
Quite frankly
Is the equivalent
Puffy's
Bequia
Application
Batman
You guys
We're we're giving you
Like the the if you're rational you look at that and you see that last
That last thing that you said
Is
Oh that means Alex's dangerous
The beginning
That means Alex
What is dangerous
All of that stuff
All of that stuff is built around the idea of giving you the impression of
And at no point
Time making a goddamn
Point
That was it
That was the whole f****** thing
Earlier than I thought I would
Who's going to be you know why cuz there's those glimmers
There's those couple of moments
Yeah are like Alex
The Trap
Anna Anna
They never say never
Yeah something
And if
I beg you
MBC and Megyn Kelly
Give me the tapes
I will find what Alex is afraid of
Right I guarantee I can find it
I know his head
Unfortunately
So am I am your savants and BC
This is as disappointing as we kind of it
Expected it to be
I've too bad that I'm going to be up all night attending this
Expected it to go the other direction
I expected it
To be something where people
Before the interview there's this like
You shouldn't are this interview
They were clearly committed to Aragon
Which to me suggests
They thought that
They had something where
They would not defy airing the interview but then they would get
Praise
For doing such a great job.
Taking down this propaganda
And this is like you said
That is a puff
You would think
And to them they think that's really damn
Yeah I did a good job on
Covering that no one else is
Cuz a lot of people are covering
And the people who are
Are doing a great job
Bible degree with that
Again
Who gives a f***
He was
Drunk
Ways to learn
The interview
Play there's all kinds of stuff that you
But
That really pisses me off about that
Is because
The real trick
Getting Alex
Into a corner
A talking about what
He wants to
Talk about yappity will f****** go on and he damned himself
Totally
Like
If you can
Muslim
It's like that first thing on the Manchester
Just go into not
What you said about the victor
But what do you believe about
I need be like
Banana
That's on you and that's all you would need to show like all the stuff was like
What's the same thing that pee
Blonde Twitter
The same thing that Media Matters is which is
Going like
Hey
You need to
To talk about this
And if you just
Let Alec
He's going to destroy himself
So the document is not
You not what you think about Sandy Hook
Not anything like that Alex
Worst enemy is himself
If they've shown an interview Alex did with him
Yeah I think that that's why we kind of thought
That it would be worse than it was too because I know that
But he has very little self-control
When he's baited
It would be pretty easy to Beta
Absolutely I agree I think you should bring up Muslims I think you should bring up globalist
If you ask him direct questions
About is globalist ideology
Here to be like
He go off
Yeah a two-point where you get to the end of the road it would just be
The vapor
Nothing
You don't actually have a real concrete position here Rothschild
Nonsense
The Rothschilds
I mean what real
Santa real
Thing anymore give us
Any kind of credit
That we don't necessarily deserve
But
How do you do that interview
You
Give him rope
You let him talk about his
Globalist ideology
You let him talk about how he feels about Muslim
Utah
You got to talk about masculine and then all you do is instead of your voice over Bay like here's this
You just
Point out
Not true
Sure
That's basically what we do
We turned him into a joke
Let him talk
Yeah
And that's what we hope for that mean
That's a big fear that he has
Start listening
The same fear I have I'm kind of scared
Warriors
About
That I can disprove but I don't want
I'm sure he has the same fear but in reverse that like
People will questioning about these things that he's vaguely talked about for years and years
Would be disaster
Yeah
I just don't
I'm disappointed because of
Opportunity law
I just now Alex is never going to do this again
I think you're absolutely right
In that
No
Because what he got was
Exactly what he wanted
Based on all of the last week
Lead-up you so scared
Like right
I don't think he put himself through that week again
And if you did
I mean if you ever learn any lesson
Alright I'm going to be much more careful about what I say
Beer was driving in
You got three empty control
Be careful about
Strew
Did
Was
Put him into the pub
Public conscious
For a day
I'm at the
Yeah there's nothing there
Yeah
The end result of this is Alex Jones has propaganda
Play with now I mean you can
When this pretty well
I am
There are the fear that people had about enough
Complaints of people were making
Before it that you're giving him a platform
You absolutely are I think I think they're
100%.
Certified now she makes a good she makes good points
About the consequences of his rhetoric but it's not
That's not enough that's not enough
Do necessarily make the den
You need to make
Justified
Yeah no you have platform him
You've made him mainstream and you've allowed until Ion Television
That sucks
And all you've done is
Make him sex
Somewhat because
Look at that look at the powerful
Fullman
Look at this powerful man
He's connected
Got millions of
He's super-rich
All of this is exactly
And
You could be able to
The Pierce
Allstars reinforcer
God
What a bummer
Static-X
Release the tape
Releases text Babe
Those tapes would be the most
I have to be
Listen to review
Coming on the heels of a possibly losing it episode
Makes me wish I was dead for one person
Not that
Who's this one guy
This guy named JP's an old friend of mine
I am
Alex