Air Jordan
I have great respect for its knowledge B
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Fight.com
Novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex
So Jones guy mr. freeze
Mr. Holmes
My bright spot today is
Granola baby
Tarantula
Espresso vanilla cream
Granola
Oh my God your business Lovgren
Which is made with espresso and ice cream
Oh okay it's very good
It's nice I'm trying to I had like this. I think I talked about it in some previous price
White spots where I was going for the
Bizarre a cereals going to like the fruity
Pebbles with marshmallows
And I'm
I'm trying to get back onto a more like
Alright I've indulged minor child a little bit here
Espresso vanilla cream
Chelation so it's not like it's
Departed
Core granola
But I'm working in that direction
I feel like my breakfast
Could be better served
Is based on Italian something I supposed to
Long a hair metal band would have released in the 80s.
Nazareth Love Hurts
I'm assuming some people have found out by now we were in the New York
How fun is that
That's nice
Super Bazaar
If I hadn't liked it been aware that this was coming I would be like this is
Psychiatrist
Bizarre Bazaar
Philly
So Jordan today
We have an interesting UPS
April 16th 2020
This is
Friday's
Episode
Alex
No it's not
It's not great
It's not
It may not be the most
Groundbreaking of episodes but there are a couple things that happen that are breathtaking that are
Amazing
Alright
Go to sign up recording the show
The first of the Reverend
Doctor sorrow thank you so much for now a policy wonk
Hrds
Thank you very much provoked agree with half of that
Borderline
Shoutouts to throw at Williams
Heroin
Freakishly large
Ewok shoutouts a little bit short on this episode cuz they have another little bit of business that we have to get
Very important
Tomorrow Tuesday export when
And that means that it is the official end of the year of the Celtics
Where did we wind up at 3:50
Yeah right around 3:50
For people who may be around podcast two more recently
Last year around 4:20
I decided that I was going to drink 500 selters in that your kind of
Eleanor facegooo seems like there's going to be this. Where there was the
No covid
I didn't think it was going to go as long as it
I did not either it's kind of felt like that to kill some time with drink a bunch of Acro and all these weird
A years too long
For a novelty
It was very much a an emotional rollercoaster ride because it started off as a
Then a few weeks later he started off with a roof with a lot of energy behind
Say it is you got
And all the sudden it started being a lot of filters just popping up all over the place
And then what was it a probably Behavior
I got a hot tip on a shelter we got to go to the South Side to find it
Six months ago that your enthusiasm drop
I can only release
Well I can say that a big part of it is the
Difficulties involved with covid
Events at personal life stuff kind of disenchanted
Did me a lot over
No. Of months
Akira smoke
Govana filters are not very different
Yeah I think you could take his 2-year in 500 if you were on like a Japanese
Game show where you have to live in a place where there's nothing but Celtics are a rock me all of the Seltzer's Isaacs
50 whogivesacrap
I definitely could have I don't know
This is fine
It sucks.
It's not that bad
You really lose the enthusiasm to like
Hunt-down new
Seltzer's unless you've already had everything that's at every store within
Did a couple miles of Rider
Eddie can't find anything else on Amazon
Becomes a real
Was a stupid idea from the beginning
All of our ideas
Yeah I learned a few things
One is the wide wide world
Movies out there
Make sure and the ones that are Morty like are better I think
I enjoy them more
The flavor at
And so
In order of ending the year of the seltzer
For today which is the center of Bonnie
Sunwing
Sparkle Urban herbal tonic is
I believe turmeric
Related
Tom Richert
Pronounce tumeric with there is an r in there
That infuriates maybe I might be a silent r
Continue this is sunwink lemon Rose uplift
I feel like it is now is a good time for some uplifting
Lemon Rose
Taking a sip I noticed
You playing around with that bottle before the show and normally you have a bit of an energy
Drake right
And how did
Is really good is really good
Nice yeah that's very
Do you like
It's reminiscent of those those ones that had to flower
Oh yeah yeah
Girls real good
Thank you Mommy and I thank you everybody who has enjoyed the year of the
I don't know if I'm going to do a year of anything else ever again
That it's humiliating
B&W got the round 350 shelters if you would if you would set your goals
For 300 Delta
Unattractive number though
Indie Maybe
Probably
Look up viewer decide sure
Jordan today April
The Ides of March
Do-rite Juno by checks
We're going to start off with Alex talking about some headlines
Bad news for the
They denied all of this and Mainland
Animal
Human
That's always
Embryonic
Condition condition condition condition
The CIA was quoted in the Washington Post
Body
Tatooine
Earrings
Happy things you said all the things you said
This is all actually in different Publications
The CIA encouraged everyone to get earrings
Tattoos really weird for the CIA to finally start admitting stuff and choose the stuff that I guess
Take them down the most
Yeah
You know what are you
Yeah I don't I don't know about this
Also
The latest news on the animal-human hybrid front is it there was an article published in the journal cell
Researchers injected human stem cells into monkey embryos
Which that say observe growing
Three of the embryos
Survived up to 90
18 days but they didn't create clones or anything like that
This is a field of study
But it's not with Alex's
Describing and the scientific community
Is far from reaching a
Amazon it
There are tons of debates that go on by the ethics or even the need
For such research in
You can find people who have informed opinions on both sides Alex is not one of them
Can transfer the bioluminescence
Straight to another creature I was like well get rid of all of the research
Until I can
Glow-in-the-dark
All science and tell everything doctor gums used
Furious with me because I would
Constantly demand for him to explain to me why we can't
Photosynthesize
But why can't we get a human that has photosynthesis
I really think he had a compelling
Full answer and I was too high to Remember When
I don't remember
90 * 2
Story you know the whole thing about the human-animal hybrids and stuff
I like to take as an example of actual
Alex
I all along Manchu or remember is it's his version of this research
It doesn't match
What actually exists
The stories that he tells are different than reality
Just remember we were talking about fish human hybrids in
Tanks quit sad human eyes
That's the kind of stuff that Alex talks about them
Embryos full-grown Fishman
Wandering around RC
It-it's
It's very attractive for people to take
Headlines and then liquid out of context Snip-Its
The things I would say
It's not really a cure
It's fun game though
You know if you want to be someone who plays this game that I was right about everything should I have bad news
We will all be dead soon
There is a scientific law
That is breaking away from Humanity
As it breaks away in extract all the resources of the old civilization
Poisons us dumbs us down divides Us in Concord
Into the jungle
Urban Jungle
Welcome to the Jungle
We got fun and games
The time
Those of us who haven't joined them
Feeling very hard-pressed to survive
Without joining them
And those of us that
Habit join them
Will still only survived because the glove was killed everybody
We're not on their side
Be prepared
You might be able to survive and not join them
But I think God is going to
God doesn't like cowards.
We have to stop
From
This is very weird
Well I mean
It seems strange for him to say that God wouldn't like that considering the most popular Christian book series ever written
Was about the small number of survivors who made it through the Evil apocalypse
Kirk Cameron to Global
My bad
No I f***** it up
It's an interesting version of Alex's
Is fear narrative
About to happen
Taking over in a blah blah blah
So it's coming up and almost immediately and
You are probably going to die by
If you make the Right Moves there's a way that you
Can survive
Better the wrong moves are joining with the global
Of course that's fine
You could survive if you did that
Even though why would you since everybody you've ever known and territories dad
I don't know
You cannot join the globalist and still survive if you get really lucky and do all the Right Moves
But God will be mad
So you can die in the Apocalypse
Can survive it for a little while knowing you've ever met but either way you're going to hell
But I guess that this implies that there is a third fourth fifth option and that is fighting
To stop somehow stopping
It doesn't matter is Google's have a plan B I was already explained that
Doesn't seem to be a good
At this point this is really dumb
You know
I think that their jobs in the world
Bratz
I have more power
For people you know like
Career
During a career that takes a long time to master let's shower
Turn over your house then
Some unskilled profession
Maybe have higher turnover rates
Comedian
High turnover rate
Very high turnover rate higher
What do you think about the high-ranking globally
Here's what I think I think it's got to be like the politburo level of like
Backstabbing murder
All the time
Because I really am understanding
They get to keep all the money and power
They then
Turn against
The nose people
I have a voice though they get shot
Oh okay
Convenient
The globalist in the high-ranking levels have
Tracy's
Crisis of conscience and realize now f*** this noise Alex's right
So they quit but then they get killed so what are you going to do
Hey it's
As everybody knows from watching our government phone
Obviously the people who run the world have
Consciences that they've been to it all times
I don't know if
I can think of any examples of anybody
The Alex is ever discussed as a high-ranking globalist
Who turned on the global incident.
It's a fun story
Explain why there aren't defectors of the
Picture for I guess Leo zagami
Which maybe Smiley dad
Mike Lindell got rich and Powerful so he's probably
You turned against the globalist I bet he was a high-ranking
Globalist for a while
I don't know otherwise you can't get money and power his point is you can only
We get money and power
You join with the globe
Or if I guess
If you sell
Or pillows
I don't think Mike lindell's
Alex's employee who got arrested at the Capitol
How does come back up a little
Okay
My pillow was storyline is not brought back
Might still be there but it's not fun center
Here's the thing
Globalist to have a high turnover rate
6th and then end up having to kill the former employees who are
They're only going to kill you if certain
Conditions are met
Never work for new alarm
I never signed a contract with the man ever actually run the route
Will kill you
Sidestep the more
Don't follow orders
But if you've never sold out tonight
Metaphysical rule
They'll just try to get other
Other people
Or they will try to kill your name or discredit you are
But they say don't
Often
Kill you
Unless you've been involved with them and made some deal with him at some other
That's why I've never met
Any deals
Protective
I
Are you going to make deals or else there's going to be some kind of an infringing of metaphysical rules with sound really
Dumb problems with this
If it's the medic
Metaphysical rules that govern the universe are so dumb
You can ethically sidestep Murder By like
Vincent somebody else
To kill somebody and then you have a negatively cleanflight
I don't think
These rules are good
I think that they are ungrounded am I are you telling me that Mark rich
Cruz is innocent of all crimes
According to the metaphysical metaphysical rules of the universe
I think there might be a flaw in this metaphysical rule
You bet that I think there could be
Yep
I don't I don't I don't know what I feel about this other than like anytime he brings up his metaphysical rule ID
Because I just
I want to know more I want him to actually get into the fl-1a paintings of this really breakdown
What
Must be true with a Miss ethical system
Oh know if if he worked
The one thing that I want from him is a full accounting of his
It's just it's just brought up brought out whenever Things Are
Convenient I want a book
Of him like
Codify I want Alex Jones version of the Bible
That's what I want
I don't know well that's what I
All caps
Alex has all these ideas
If it's not it's not what they're saying
That there were human stem cells and embryos
Oh no no no
Technology is 50 years ahead of where it actually is all this stuff you know who thinks they know what's up with
The globalist f****** military intelligence
Army intelligence military intelligence
They don't know
Oxymoron
Military intelligence
Totally compartmentalize
Weapons
Atomic weapons are 120 years old
They had all the equations 130
That's all that's all
Max being phased out there is really in the military
Hollywood movie much super soldiers he's really
Cool badass dies in the movie
Nobody you know you do.
None of that exists is all gone
It's all robots and clowns in all robots and close
Fun alright
So I guess you saw Bobby Bowden
Kirkland
Nobody
I think Bob Odenkirk as a lot of range it's been unexplored nomogram good for him
He's incredibly great
I think
You know it's
It's kind of an interesting dilemma
Because you do see the possibility of a future
Where a lot of warfare is done
By way of robot
You know drone certainly are a problem
Escalate towards
The point where like actual
Troops are robot
That's right then eventually you're going to get into a point where
A negotiation between countries that is robots fighting robots
Is really just
The financial thing is like I'm destroying more of your property which is robots
Then it almost has a
Potential to be like well we could
Couldn't negotiate through this easier.
Exam
Fighting
So I don't know I thought it through but it's
Interesting thing with
It almost seems like it would lead to a
Vast reduction in order
Well I mean
There have been a lot of really interesting cuz that's something that I've read about you know that's
That's one of those things that futuristic
Been describing
You know Kurt Vonnegut
You know that kind of stuff
And
There's a lot of people who were like War doesn't mean anything
If there aren't people died
So you can't really do any you know it'd be like a video game at that point
Are you better at video game
So mathematically I win
Before we even fight
Yeah
Yeah I guess it doesn't
Lycra
Like robot drones and stuff like bombing apartment building
I thought that's still
They're still a devastating human toll associated with that
But yeah I don't know
I don't know what about the Clones part
What would clones be doing in this scenario
I don't know if you seen the prequels
Star Wars prequels
Ultimately closer not as good
If you're going to use them for Warfare
Robot
You know we're not sinking
Sing about
Because those are stupid
They're giant lumbering moron
Quick Mobility all of these things human beings don't stand a chance against
Again
Tapped Out
So
Alex hasn't complaints
About the Pope
Does full communist a sharing
Prosperity
They're going to direct how you share
Select
No idea what the bankers have to do with the Pope's opinions
Is that the Vatican either
News
For Alex
But Alex is complaining about
Francis is behind Jo bar
Naturally so Alex gets a little bit about the
Vaccine
And that's something that I find
Flagrantly respond
You got all these countries in a stop at either shot all these coming to stop
You got all these deaths. One death of the one woman died
Like 3,000 or 5,000
Not sure
Covid-19 Illinois
There's a gigantic unsupported claim that Alex is making
If you have some kind of evidence that the covid vaccines are responsible for a high number of deaths
They're being called covid-19.
Unspecified stupid
He knows that he can't back this claim up which is why even though he's saying is a meeting with nonsense assertion
The difference between 1 and 10
Huge like that
Irresponsible
Spectrum to be pointing
It might be a little bit
Anyway I'm going to need to see the sources on this
Santa until I do on the goddamn a limb and assume it's his
Dumb imagination
As usual
Thousand percent more
Could be anything
Last episode we got them
Of the Mind
It's between Alex and
Fresh
A hot on the same comedian Norm pattis lawyer
He's finally breaking out of the claw game got pursuers real passionate
Stand-up comedy
Going to be able to be the funniest lawyer cuz that's every comedies being already has them
Funniest lawyer in Chicago at least
Not to be outdone by the s*** head of a of a norm
Coming on
Is going to be on this episode
Patterson without Barnes being like you got a book me soon so he's got to come on and this is where Alex teases
They're going to talk about how the Chauvin
Trial is nonsense
Coming up today
Open trial up
Minnesota
Christmas tree
Not the type you I put cook
Cookies and milk
The Takeover in the police are not getting rid of the police
They are bullying me
Event that happened
Oh my God
God armed robbery suspect robbing a woman
Even guns around everywhere
Isn't attacking the police
The melee
The cop pulls the wrong weapon and shoots
What do you think happens when you die
Speed car chases
But now you see we have more Riot for that trial got to have more cuz he just goes on and on
What was Police Department
If you everything order says an erector political enemies
Commissars
Well then
Mike Flynn
Where is area
This is your last
Read a chance.
Fires all over the today and
Got it
Fun work people off about Christmas tree with cookies and milk
Vitamin
Hey listen don't turn around
There, sire
Isn't
Yeah
So Alex has a story that he hits on number of times throughout the show and that is
Maxine Waters
Apparently told Jim Jordan
To shut his mouth
Yeah
Seated in the chamber
Congressional
Language
I would have preferred she
Beat the s*** out of him with a cane cuz we've got one there's a precedence of that happening I guess right
Look we've got one you get to beat and anti-abolitionist borderline to death in Congress that's
The rule I think Alex might have the wrong
Angela
Let me do this
Jordans
Marshawn shut up
Tell him to shut up
That's like
Half of Alex's show always telling
Black women to shut up
It's the most important thing to you there's some kind of social justice related activism
Tell people to shut up
Can you imagine if I was some sort of football player who was blackballed from the lead for speaking
Out very obvious truths that
Seem so obvious that no one
YouTube even borderline imagine
We're going to go. We're going to get some
Some flagrantly races
Stuff about Kaepernick a little bit later
Baxter covid matters here's Alexandra
Some dumb s***
Or something else
It's the same
Scam
Everywhere
Cuz it was never really kill themselves
Pneumonia or the flu
It was an actual virus
94%
Hospital coded
As
Coveted
Thousand dollars
So this is just Alex misrepresenting how there was a figure that came out where was like
6% of covid-19 death didn't involve the person who had an underlying
Condition they might have contributed to the garish
Considering
Things like obesity or smoke
Can could be underlying conditions this isn't
Surprising
Alexander Delco just use that stat incorrectly for a year to argue that the death numbers are are.
That was thinking about that
Android
You know that idea that the hospitals are in on a get-rich-quick
Skiing because there's a certain amount that they get paid out by Medicare Medicaid
Based on covid-19 patient
Tremendously stupid idea I was just thinking about it
Does Alex
Think that those
Like hospitals don't get payments for other conditions
Like does he think that like someone getting
Like if they have
Aggressive cancer
Also pay out
What's your what's your name to standing and I don't know if you've been to a hospital NY
They pay everything on a flat hundred dollars
So if you
You've got cancer you're taken all kinds of stuff
They pay a hundred bucks for it's been awhile since I've been to a hospital
Starbucks or everything but covid
It's just it's one of these days I'm actually going to
Sit down
And try and figure out like what other
Payouts are
Alright
Let's do this but that may be needed for another day because today
We're going to get in
Operation cyber polygon
I'm also lying he doesn't bring it up at all
It's son of a b****
No
You always have to then
Like when you're excited and you get a letdown do you have to just pass it on to Mega it is a little bit mean of me and maybe
I just want you to feel that disappointment
Complains about things he imagined that Anthony fauci says
You can buy the clip he wants your vaccinated
You can go out and not wear a mask and go to restaurant that's fauci
Because every year
Doubled their wealth are taking over
They're not going to stop
This is mostly about defending Tucker Carlson about attack
It against him for his
His segment that he had where he was talking about like
I was told that we
We could go back to normal
What people replacement
We've moved on from that you can just get white replacement for like a person Smith
I think people might have gotten the sense that things would immediately return to normal after vaccine was released
But that's not what was being said by a
Experts including dr. fauci
This is a straw man position that the right-wing media types like Alex
Some Tucker been using recently to argue against vaccinations while pretending that they have some kind of a principal
Old Point
He's basically a child whining that their parent promise to buy them a pony if they got good grades on the parents
No such thing
In December
20 facts you said quote
Let's say we get 75% 80% of the population facts
Fascinated
If we do that if we do it efficiently through the second quarter of 2021
By the time we get to the end of the summer i e the third quarter
We may actually have enough herd immunity protecting our society that when we get to the end
We can approach
Very much some degree of normality
That is close to where we were before
So that's what you were saying at the end of 20
No it every time they've said even after
But you've been vaccinated continue to wear a mask about least of which to stop this
But also just
To make it
Falling for people to wear masks
Outside
In September after you told Healthline quote we can be greatly helped by vaccines but it's not vaccine alone
Let's assume that we get a reasonably effective Acts
Not measles vaccine where you have a 98% effective I think that'll be
Be too much to ask
Ask for
Let's talk about seventy-five 80% of
Effective vaccine
Would you be really good if we did that
If we did that
Ultimately got everyone who should be and could be vaccinated I would think that
Together with not necessarily abruptly ending measures like masks and physical distancing
If we could get the majority
Community to adopt
Those Health measures together with a reasonably effective vaccine
Then we could get the level of infection down so low in the community
The end of 2021
We could start thinking in terms of normal
Alex an idiot friends don't live in reality
They fabricated fake one that adheres to the storylines they want to tell them that they profit off of
Alex's story about the vaccine at the globalist
Trying to force it on everyone so it's
It's essential for that story to involve in
Explicit promise
From the villains of the story that
Everything will go back to normal just as soon as you take my emails vaccine
That's not the actual messaging two people like that after you've been engaging it but it's how it feels to Alec
Because that's the story that he tells for a living
You can see by the
The false portrayal
Silly
What a dick
So I think it's important to recognize a few thing
One of them is that I'm willing to address
It talked about like
Factual issues like
You know cyber polygon where to bring it out
Operation lockstep monoxide
Yeah I'm very happy to engage in those
But
I will also
Say
Anybody who wants to
To take Alex Jones
As so moving
Who is a good provider of information
We'll also have to
Explain this all right
Kind of thing
I have always
Address of the god
Sold
I have been having experiences now.
Private
About the Holy Ghost the comforter and all the rest of that
That now
I would be pleased to be crucified upside down at Orchard
So thankful to God that I've been in a lot of pain
It really upset over there
Pray to God bless you much
The take the Warriors
Done that
Call Shogun
Cuz I mean
Cost of the door
The door now
I thought you're going to that are just
Ecstasy
Describe the beauty of it
Purity
And the level of this is just
You're in God's mind
It's all good well to have like religious beliefs and stuff
Normal to believe
That you're having visions of being in heaven when you dream
Having just been an angel are you shiting me
Sissy I thought women were
Hey this is lunatic level Behavior Archangel Michael visit
I've been in the god of mine
Turns out all angels are gay
But this is silly
And I think it's a stupid
Who wants to take Alex
As any kind of
Sincere
Good faith
Actor
In the sensitive like
Conversation about ideas
Woodstock
Eminem's kind of
Maybe personal attack
I cannot have you I heard him say was I am having good dreams
More import on it than just someone saying I've had good for
Little bit
Everything about it
Did I take as much more functional and grounded
Is
Alex says at the beginning
He was born again
Eight or nine when we know that he was a Satanist
When you were born again
When your bored again
At 8 or 9 had you already paid for the abortions or would that come later
Yeah it what is this before or after the
Satanist try to lure you and you you were a functional yesterday rate
Eminator night I was a Satanist it's it look
If you're not
A sickness when you're young the problem with stories like this
That are obviously
F****** artificial and not true
Played up for
The presentation of this
The person that Alex wants
That people to see him as
If you can't keep it straight like it just doesn't make sense
Timeline is
See how he was born again at 8 and then went to the devil for a little while
And then
I came back
I don't know
That's why all mythologies wound up in books
It's because they were like I'm telling you I think Zeus did it this way
Changing stories a little bit over time because
Different ways that
The different tellers would tell stories
To this goes on
Alex keeps talking like a
Deranged lunatic
And it is just
Last night
Whirlpool
Please
Please help me not
It was just it was just
Unbelievable
No way
Describe this
And I've never seen any of this chart literature
In order stuff I've seen in movies and culture
You are missing out
You have no idea
What you're missing out
I just it's unbelievable
Stop right there
I want to stay on air
I need the temporal fun to do this and we spend a lot of money run this operation I pay the crew pretty good
And I don't want to
Have to do a lot of things
David long rant about the god-given vision
Satanist
Have no
Concept
Of what it's like
So what I'm going to do
Is immediately take the lord's name in vain and ask for your temporal money I am go
Going to tell you all about how great the Lord is and how naira
When I go to bed go to bed maybe have a memory that you replayed your head
I go to heaven
Absolutely I didn't come back down and I break Commandments left
Turn right because I'm so good great
Yeah it's really great
Being on Earth
I want to know what the
Those things are
That's like a lovecraftian description of something
Yeah
Art and literature does not
Contain these archetypes
You're saying but also you don't describe what
It looks like
Does not belong euclidean geometry
Find some literature or art
Acute but acted as if it was a tooth
Standard model
And it turns out there are more particles
Alex gets into talking about covid
How's the globalist attack
Nightcore store
You know I really wanted things I really appreciate about Alex
Texas
Good priorities
What they like
You're going down track
Cancel been more important comes up you buy a tank
I kind of got to go for
Italian lawmakers
Charges of crimes against humanity and more scientists were more lawyers are coming out and saying that
Weaponized
Currency monsters launch this
The sooner way.
But that's
People on earth
And
He's a liar
What
Defamer
The platform
Myself
He literally stopped
20 + advertisers
And what use is a sack of garbage
He is
Already
But we're going to talk about covid-19
Of all people
Brian stelter is our big bad today you know like it's super weird to me that
You have such a like a hatred towards like Conor friedersdorf
You complained about him so much less than Alex
Does a Viper that's what I'm saying
Breeders free Alex needs to take some cues from you in a while ago
You don't need to be so mad it's filter
Although if you if you believe that
Yes then his anger and hatred Selter is actually
Paid some dividends
Years ago calling him an enemy of the people
I didn't know this was a certain
Tacos
Trump took enemy of the people from Alex and he was talking about
88 Bakery
Like a freeze like that
Has never before been uttered in literature or in any kind of archetype
That is brand new Straight from Alex's mouth
To Trump's ears
I don't believe this first of all
Second of all
True
Not something I necessarily
Pretty bad so I gave him a phrase
Complaining here
About
Some stuff sure I might down for this cuz I actually think that this is really hilarious this is one of the funniest things I've heard in awhile
I know the average
Man watching baseball is buddy's eating pizza and drinking beer
Sounds great to me
In football
Boxing I like
You know what
Do it because the whole thing coming down on us
Is reading
Here are the reasons I find this hilarious
The first is that Alec
Constantly pretends that he hates
Sports because it's just the media's way of pacifying men's instinct
Conflict in battle
He gives a speech about it every single Super Bowl Sunday
Particular everyone
This is how long it took Alex to come up with um document
Finally this is hilarious because this entire show is based on the idea that nothing is ever going back to normal
And yet here Alex's
The crying how the average man is watching
Sport to the bar with her friend
Alex can't do because he's too busy with you and doctor
Should the average people he's mad at not be able to go to a bar and watch sports cuz of bounties dictatorship be what it is
The government has you they've been keeping you inside for a year and they want to keep you inside for your now obviously everybody's out and about today
Tonight
This might sound kind of like but it's really more something that I want to use as a demonstration but how deeply seated
Alex's narcissism is
He presentation of himself as a superior person because he fights imaginary globalist is more important
Staying consistent with his ideas
If people can't do normal things I go to bars with their friends anymore
It's you see the priority is there anything gets in the way of Alex saying he's exceptional
It is
Out of the way as soon as
Alex will
Give up on
Narrative
For telling you how great
Tucker Carlson is coming under Fire from Chelsea Clinton about these vaccine
Mean comments and
Alex does the whole like
If you're vaccinated why should you care if I get vaccinated review what you write
I know it works
Some folks
He's doing that he's going through this
Avenues remembers that George Carlin bit
Oh no
Suggestion Addison to deliver it
Swimming in swamps
Give me the area you live in
That mean
In sewage
Katt Williams swamp as its what
Buffalo with a deer in the bobcat
That's the Florida
Don't swim in sewage this is not good advice
Alright not revolutionaries you should not instead of getting vaccinated it's not a good idea just
The jump
Alright you get this little cocktail
You put some Ebola in it makes sense
Expect much more from somebody with a
Thanks Mike Adams is a good doctor
Sewage tanks
It's not good for you and swamps are in
Ecosystem not just
There is a Tesla
The toilet
Swamp Thing wasn't
So this makes glow is a little bit
It's a little sensitive to clip
From a protest
I don't really know what all the circumstances are in it
But from what I can tell from the limited amount of context
A
B some organizer at a protest
Took issue with some of the behavior
Have one of the wiper
Participants of the protest
It was probably not in line with what the
People who are doing the protest
Wanted to be
How things are presented
You how to protest
Tested PC
There's a way it could be disrespect
Go to the larger point of the protests
The people are working at cross-purposes
Seems like
Is going on in this video
Alex
Takes this
And gets
Wildly race
I don't hate black people because there's some races
I judge people according to what they do they are
Martin Luther King statue
That's why America believed what he said because it was true
Brotherly love
But I have dozens of videos just to
Beat up because they're white
You're not welcome here because your wife
And the hatred of these young black
People's faces
Is giz notice
Most the time
What's the weather like
Mulatto
Kaepernick
Your parents
Are white liberals
Anna baseley.
In black folks that are
Really anti-white
Adopted organ one of the parents
Revolution
Hidden behind black p
So they can do this in clients for black
Peoples
That's pretty eventive just on the surface level and I don't feel like
You know we need to break down exactly why that's
Incredibly for you if you want me to just scream her about fitter
People who've been listening to our show for awhile
Would they recognize this isn't necessarily and
Uncommon sentiment for Alex Express
Despite it being
This were the first time that we heard him say that
Go back and listen to the first time we've heard him say stuff like that started barking and go about my window
Really pulled this clip is because the mentality that Alex's espousing that these people who he's determined are not really black
Enough for being used
To push a communist agenda to attack white people
Is exactly it
I mean
Exactly
The argument that his spiritual predecessors like Gary Allan made
When they opposed
The Civil Rights
Allen's book
Communist Revolution in the streets
Glazed out this mentality
And it's clear that Alex
Explanation of any kind of
Social justice related active
That's not interesting on its own
Oz of dumb big
But what's fascinating is how Alex isn't stupid enough to argue again
Since the Civil Rights Movement
Cuz he knows that he couldn't
Back up that kind of claim
It looks a little bit to transparently bigoted through present-day eyes
That's what I was saying a week ago or whatever is like it you can
Measure the same ideology being
Forced
Ever so slowly to be like fine you want on civil rights
Fine we don't get slaves anymore
Fine I'm still going to stay the same s*** though I'm going to do it
The book Communist Revolution in the streets is mostly an attack on Martin Luther King Junior so
Forgive me if I think it's
The little bit funny for Alec
What's the signal some imaginary support
Brookings ideas well using the exact same Playbook
His Heroes used to attempt
Discredit
And demonize King himself while he was alive
This is
Is bulshit but it's important to recognize this
When Alex has glimmers like that there is
Severe racism
But it's also the same ideas that have been bubbling under
These
Hard right forces
Do that were in favor of segregation they were against the entirety of civil rights
Same mentality that
It's still underpins Alex
Smart enough to know
That he would be called
Some horrible accurate names
If he argued like that
But even then it goes
All the way back
To f****** slavery goes all the way back
To being like
Oh well see
Whenever you allow miscegenation
The ones who are more white
Are more likely to cause you any it's just f****** slavery it's the same s***
Yeah there's that sort of
Influence
SMS other influence the songs in
Yeah it's all just very
Shocking
And horrible
You know
Do Alex but it's important to recognize these things when they
I wonder if it's all white and God my bet it is
Hidan you might notice from watching Alex's show that all his gaster
Complete lunatics who believe mostly the same things he doesn't
Say not only that but Alex Haley to great
And I like to flatter
You love to win
And you might think like why doesn't have other guests on the show
Affirmative
Well I have a lot of red guest on the show we invite coming at the globalist on it won't come on but
Everybody we have on regularly are smart
Lawyer Barnes
So smart
Yeah so, you have been invited but
The RSVP comes back
Not attending yeah you know I believe that
I don't know I've been saying good work Barnes very dismissively but now that I know Patty
Tried stand-up he might be the Dumber lawyer
It really lowers your invites
People on like I don't know when lately there's been anybody who would be an inch
Trysting booking
Sure the people like David Rothschild
Or like
Weatherman yeah yeah.
The moment you asked me for a Poulan
I could have pulled it two seconds ago
Yeah bill
Bel-Airs
Those interviews that have happened
And like
Alex comes out look
Book a terrible at
And so like
I guess maybe in the past he would have put out more feelers for globalist
Then, you think
And his
They don't go well though
Now because
If somebody
Comes in
And he starts getting religious
It's going to get bad
Imagine if you had David Rothschild on now and I was just screaming what the f***
Real f****** devil I mean Bellaire
Woah clean
You're the devil
I am with God I've seen his mind
Wow yeah right
Barnes trial is a show trial
Are you doing
Two parts one is the children had agreed
Guilty to third-degree murder before the trial
For twenty years
And it was
They were serious about
Getting an outcome
Good meat the facts
So this is very much
Just soviet-style
Show trial
Simply because they refuse to do a reasonable plea deal
Did the trials
Consumption
Entirely
Derek Chauvin had offered to plead guilty to third-degree murder and William Barr
But the details of the situation are being captured by super lawyer Robert Barnes
One of the primary issues is that according to an ABC News article of Chauvin
Quote asked to serve his time in a federal prison and wanted assurances that he wouldn't
Face federal civil rights
Charges
Because he was asking for federal guarantees the deal needed to be approved by the Department of Justice
But bar quote
To allow State prosecutors to make their own decisions about how to proceed
Seems like that's stayed upon anything Alex and his buddies yell about all the time being put in
Into action and also Barbie and like I don't want to touch this
Yeah you guys deal with it also the fact that you're going to bleed to third-degree murder
There's probably not a great
Know if you say
He's willing to plead the third-degree murder
Wouldn't you want to then defend to the murder charge instead of being like the whole trials illegitimate
Also like
It's a show trial because they didn't cry
Accept what is a reasonable please
And that's a
Your
Determination bar
You have determined that this is what would be a reasonable play that's not necessarily what the prosecution believes
Or the state
So Justice doesn't exist unless
Equally applied
So that's it
Did the real issue those if this trial is just happening because
The demonstration
Wants to put on
But they can do whatever they want
What is the left looking for
Want
Kim hyung
The left wants him legally Lynch analyst was the show they can use and weaponized
The prosecutorial process
Indicate their media narrative
To help push a pretty
Circular politicized agenda
Exactly
That's the point
We can do it anytime we want any place we want
Even to a police officer
I think that there's other issues like
The guy was
The guy died
Well there's that anyone anytime I think their specific circumstances that are
I would imagine that in this case committing a murder is probably more important
Peripheral for for the
The left
Well I mean
Not we want anybody they wanted any poison over they want as long as you
You murder somebody we can burn the s*** out of you
Anybody who murders even pops
As long as there's a body they can just Jam you up
It just lie about how you murdered somebody you know
So you know we got on the right
We have a lot of groups
People like The Oath Keepers who like the proud boy who actually didn't like that
I'll be at these group
Well-documented
The interaction but
Between them in law enforcement
Overlap
Even
But Robert Barnes wants you to know
The people I can't
Are actually
The Nazi Brown
That sounds right
Glmm
Use the military
On the people don't
Internal Civil War
Well I mean the real model there look
Looking at is not so much
The Communist Soviet model butter
Is the fastest model the 1930
Sure
The Long Knives
Your paramilitaries
Supporters that are outside of the governmental
They can do
That you can't do that you can use it
To do what you want to do
You create false Flags
Or you exaggerate of it
The January
Being treated like the right
White Starfire
It's the same except there was
Violence and less damage
You know who the only person I've called I've heard to call that the reichstag fire
F****** Alex Jones
Alex spent like all week
Talking about inaccurate information about Hitler's rise to power and the reichstag fire and how it was the January
36th
Storming of the capital they were the same thing that Barnes is trying to say that the life
Is doing that what the left talking nonsense
I just
Like I have very little patience
This Direct
Pretending
That's not easy
Entire strategy
Yeah you know it is
F***** up
They
Apply to us
The Cara
Turistic
That most Define
And their thought process
And then describe that thought process as disc
So it's like
Hey
If they did do what we were doing
We would really hate
Cuz it's
Evil
What they're doing
That sounds like what we're doing
And how we feel
Wida test
Totally if they did
The things that we think Stuart Road
Decided to overthrow the capital
You know
Unfortunate saying
I've seen popping up about the idea of liking America first
Caucus sure there's no historical precedent of this being
S*** just call yourselves the know-nothing party and never read history
Just do it it's a little much
Running around writing and depressing people you're the know-nothings let's go
It's a little bit
Frustrated
And scary
And I hope that it
Live be nice but you know Alex is on that tip he's on the Vanguard of America First Shore
America first
Kind of guy
Calls Rochester Lisa
Because they saw
L
Play far by a long mile
Completely reasonable
Compared to the way biting his baby
Changing his mind every other
So this
That they're getting into some pretty serious like that foods that is literally
We starve
To death and his body is falling apart and shutting down
In prison
The main political rival of President Putin is being murdered by President Putin has
We speak to be fair he's been consistent on that Friday
But also
America first
And Alex I would I would take this more seriously and actually discuss
Some
Of the issues surrounding
Maybe international relations
But like I don't feel like
Position
Deserve the respect
Being taken seriously I mean listen to this nonsense
By the way
It's all a bunch of weird Harvard women
Man
It doesn't make sense
Mike Tyson
It's it's
It's kind of a silly way he's trying to
2 formula formats
Formulate this thing or it's like yes these women
Feminism run amok and that's why they're mad
Because too much of a man
Yeah
Hi
I despise Edge
Educated women
Leading a military what I want
Is bloodthirsty murderers
Who went over to a different country on Ally and
Who killed people for no reason
It's better to be running things damn sure
Alex is going to insist on
This kind of an idea
Like myself
Having a very similar response to a lot of stuff
Nope
Yeah that's one of them nope
Kind of expect
We're going to get into
Cyber polygon we didn't I know it was never going to happen
Apologizing for you
Alex has more things to say they're having a little discussion about how great
Russia
Nationalistic
He's he's he's Russia's version of trump
That's why the Deep
Just insane.
We should be aligning with Russia
Pisses me off Barn
Literally
Kissing contest
Russia's Christian now
So they see it like the Midwest and went blow it up
This all just like
Essentially
Projecting identity politics
Ticks on to anybody
Critique of Putin
It's Behavior because he's Christian and or it's just weird women who think he's too much of a man
Yeah yeah it's happened to me all of the identify identifying identity signifiers
But Alex has
Play Feels himself under attack
When people criticize food
It's just like a rank level of narcissism
It's not geopolitical analysis
It's not
Meaningful and anyway it's
He
Identify
Highfields himself
Yeah I can't think of any reason why people would be mad at what is Funk
Believe the richest man in the world
Even if you're just Alex and you're like
Hey I don't believe in
Dynastic
Stick rulers
I've been to democracy
And I definitely don't want anybody to rule over a country for let's say more than two terms
You should have just alimentary problems there but he doesn't
Nope no I don't know I think I think
If you look at it realistically I think
What
Mostly is
Who is Alex he's a lot of his identity
Mirrored in poop
A lot of those things that are the surface level
I'm a white male Christian
And I think that she is a strong
Person there Piggy
Lacks
As someone to follow
Performative masculinity is what he's
It's really stoked about how
That's not to say that he's going
To like
You know
Dumb
Boutin's
Number one guy
Sanding and trends
I bet he's at he's pretty over it though like that
Develop fast
These America firsters
Yeah it's it's hard to go back and see the vomits with which he did
Despises Putin
And then get to the present day where it's like
Probably the best thing we've got second of course to our god king
Wow but he's Russian
Wow yeah so I guess he's the god-king there and I wish we had him God kicking us
America
1st Street
It does it feels that way a little bit
Stupid
I apologize
For another episode in the year
Future that's the plan
We will see we'll see where the wind blows us we may be back
In the past help for cyber polygon fingers crossed
We do have looked at
We are going to bed Jordan
We are on Facebook if you could please find a local charity or bail Fund in your area to help out
God's people
Still protest
Still fighting
I'm Leo I'm dzx Clark I'm Daryl rundus
Eyemed
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work