Downward slide downward slide is it a couple of
Reethi overgrown man children's podcast called knowledge fight
Alex Jones is podcasting hecklers
Knowledge 5.com
Knowledge fight stuffed up
Actually talk about they don't actually say what he actually says they don't actually into his sword
Forces of information mr. frieson mr. Friesen I would live
Numskull their league with sensor
Cult leader called saline knowledge fight mocking Infowars every single day
It is really just incredible it's hard to comprehend knowledge vice.com
I love you
McDonald's
4th or 5th
Absolute episode with a little special DJ Tanner keep track
Stay tuned for that.
What's up
Jordan
Past couple of days
Last night
My partner was like like I'm just vibrating with Fury and stress and all the stuff
And she's like
No you should do should take a bath
So
I took
Downright
Static
I absolute
This makes me
Furious
Cool thing about self that's twice
As much as you supposed to use maybe deep relaxation
What it was called
I had the Cubs
What's game on my computer I could watch that and I had my vape pen to my left and it was the best
I'm happy for you although this
Really really sets me off because I do like
No no that's not what happened
I do have visceral memories
Of me telling you that's great Emmanuel partner comes in and she's like
Bulshit
I guess
I don't know I guess
Is that kind of a bright spot I would say that's kind of a bright spot don't give a s***
Like okay here's the here's what I would say I guess
I have a lot of anxiety about the prospect of getting noticed
Infowars
It was always in the back of my mind is like being a little
And I
It's great
Best-case scenario
We got some kind of like fear that I had
Acknowledgement
Email address
It's not like you're listening but you're a little bit more Security on
Emails from your personal email account
Straight
I think a lot of people and hoping to hear like sort of a
Naturally
That's kind of its kind of a big deal
Yeah I think you'll be
Disappointed super
I have no interest in really talking about Harrison Smith breakdown
Reasons because it wasn't critiquing our shows
Critiquing an article
Sorry
April 20
Almost I almost did Ice Ice prize myself
We're just going to do business as usual my birthday is this weekend
I was going to treat myself
Going back to 2000
Free
I just felt like you know we've got issue with the Chauvin trial probably
Go ahead and talk about.
Present I can give myself then to do some work
Sojourn
The first Paul Joseph Watson
I'm a policy wonk Paul Joseph Watson
Next
Bigsby Smalls
That's a dog
I'm a policy wonk
Big Thief
Next
Gives me hope
Lego
Fed by a
Growing stronger with you
Next this one's actually
There's two possible Pikachu
First is of the most delicious hamburger in the gout
And the second is Simons
Disappointed dad first or second
Second just for Nan
Personal reasons
I'm a policy wonk
Dad
Eyebrow razor
18.
I was straight you Jordan
Couple of folks
To technocrats in a pot
We got to go
Business
Money off that heroin
Ashley large
Publicity
Kicking the
Policy wonks lost it
I was trying
Also hate this weekend
Coming to theaters
The Mortal Kombat Mortal Kombat
Shang Tsung got in touch with my cat
I just sent you an email from Shang Tsung
All this publicity been getting
All this publicity
I got to promote the movie
No this weekend very exciting
Call myself out on
Naturally I made it
In complete note
About what kind of shout-out this is
So on the 24th this Saturday
This is Shannon.
Either having anniversary
They're getting married
Zubat that could be your zero with anniversary
Maradona
Their anniversary is this is your anniversary
Cut this out
Play it next year
Play it at your goddamn wedding
Congratulations
Congratulations either way and thank you for helping me remind myself I've got to write more specific notes
I like the idea that you like when you said I wrote it in
Incomplete note I had this mental picture of like that
That Civil War note where the guys being murdered is like
Jordans
20th and 21st of April
Short
Text before we get it
The game show that is taking over the
Who is Alex going to tell to burn in hell
A couple times 3 can I get rstlne
Andy
None
Do none of those letters
No don't let her know
No
Those letters
Why wasn't
Alex gets on the 20th
Of course in the afternoon
Indy
Anticipation surrounding that people were kind of aware that
Closing arguments have been done at the Jersey
Deliberating
Maxine Waters
Come out
Made some comments
Of course this will take up quite a bit
In the show
He doesn't have a problem with black women speak
Not a pattern
It doesn't matter in the scheme of things
George Floyd
Chevron
They're both humans they're both have red blood God made them both
Are just Pawns in this game
George Floyd
Set an alarm
Guarantee the cop that turned out with friends with him and works the same club with him
Human
And so we're flawed and things go wrong and bad things happen
Divide
Conquer Russia
Turns out they've gone to the former home
One of the
Leather interior
Pig hedonist
Blood
Michelle you all that
Coming up next
Resident
I went to the other jurors home to CBS yesterday
CBS said here's who they are
So you can go harass them
The Maxine Waters commentary is going to be a major part of this
Begins is this
CBS
Dachshund
Spokes
And other outlets
The defense Witnesses former home did happen
Still seem to be embellishing a tiny bit
All over
To be clear I am against this kind of thing and it's counterproductive
According to an NBC news article the people responsible are being sought
And our quote accused of
So there's a decent chance someone's going to get in trouble
That being said I would be remiss if I didn't
Fake outrage
In November 2020 Rodger Stone was on trial
Potential jurors
For sure that the person he was naming on his show was actually even potential
He was still going to go ahead and put a Target on them
I am so
Nobody else or lease it
Appears to be
Appears to be who this person
Right I just still really feel like once you have put out a
Bounty on somebody
And now they're mistreating them jewelry
Do this whole big thing worth of Rodger Stone
You lose forever goodbye
Naturally Alex
Insecure about his actions
Because it's a very clear attempt at dirty
November 6th
Keep in mind that Rodger would be found guilty until November 5th
Teeth
This trial was still ongoing
Media Matters goes Jones
Messenger
Completely legal and lawful
What time was the public figure
What if
Call Doshi
Chelsea Clinton
One of their minions
We're going to release
Because that's what the Press does other than war on the Preston
Hillary Clinton butt
That was just desperation talking
Rogers guilty Escape
She was really killing it she got her big break with Thelma and Louise yes convenient
Whenever you can just redefined public figure
Dominion of my imaginary enemy
It's the people who threw a pig's head at that house
And I wouldn't be okay with that at all
That would fall into the same kind of category is Alex's Behavior
I'm still against
But the person who's former house
For the defense
30 given their testimony
You could argue that it was a retaliatory vandalism and I suspect that's why it's being
Considered a felony
I do think that's different than trying to Intimidators
Which is what I like
Like 6 months ago
CBS also didn't.
Anyone
Be local Minnesota Minnesota affiliate published an article that discusses the jurors brought speaking
Just vaguely
Details like
Their Age and information about their fur
Perspectives
This is not the same thing as what Alex did
If Alex can show actual
Instances of people showing up
But the jurors you should do that
But I can't find it
Consider any of it
Cancel that being a real thing
I suspect he's just taking that defense witness story and then make
Picking up another story on top of it
More fun I'm a huge fan of people who
You know really taken to Heart
The historical lessons about
Intimidating Witnesses
Misses being a thing that puts you on the side of
I think that's real history
Intimidating Witnesses very positive
History
Rodger when he was on trial Alex did this whole thing
Nonsensical
Is hairball his show
Interesting when he doesn't bring this up when talking about the efforts
But some people have made to intimidate
Surprise
Instead
Talking about how
When he's spitting
Trial situation
I'm sorry the media is trying to
The situation
And said if you don't do the right thing
Got your ass
Corrupt
Corporate media
The enemies of this country
I guess Alex
Thinks he's a terrorist
I think Alex
Interesting
Episode
Critiques
Has Maxine Waters
Chewy
Publix
About the sheriff
Trial
Grandstand
Seawater sets
That's what civil rights looks like
But she didn't say a word about
Muslims
A million
No no no no no one of the 14 black man killed
Each year in wrongful situation
She'll make a huge deal about that all day
She's a monster
30 years ago in July
This country
Plan
Kill
Weed
What
She really fun
Is the Republican Party exactly that
I just started on them
You think I feel strong as human watching them brainwashed
Joe Biden
Those real
Is that Beyond
Dying
Ugly and they're stupid
Christian or Catholic
The Dirty Youth bear was my bad I spoke too soon my bad my bad
Is a loser
Come on man
Appreciate
Conversation
Dislike
The carceral state
End up becoming rant
It's about owls are all from the Devil
The devil
Autism
Yes it looser is devil is doing great so far to be honest
Also incidentally Maxine Waters has spoken up consist
Don't lie about the human rights
China
On September 30th 2020 house floor in support of the weaker Force labor disclosure Act
The 2020
The government of the People's Republic of China falsely refers to these concentration camps as vocational
Make no mistake the truth is that today
2020 BMW concentration camp
Weatherbeeta
Starved enforced
To work long hours and conditions
Describe
Thank you man and we haven't even gotten to America
Their relatives often have no idea where they are or whether they are alive
Each day due to the cruelty of their living conditions
Chinese government
Which executes them with impunity
Incidentally that Bill had five
All of them Democrat
Some of the house who voted nay on that
Louie gohmert
Why not
People like Maxine Waters don't ever deal with the issues that he wants them to deal with because
To trivialize things like the George Floyd killing
The reality is however that Alex is just making up everything
He says
He has no idea of Maxine Waters has spoken out publicly again
Chinese human rights abuses
But the idea that
Hasn't is the only option that fits into how is content is supposed to
Is that feeling is more important than accurate reporting
That feeling is reported as fact
Messages bad work cuz it's how we operate
It is the most in
Yuriatin part of the right-wing b*******
It's fear is that it's like
We only pay attention to these people whenever they do something we don't like so we have honestly no idea what
Whatsoever if she's ever spoken about China doesn't matter
I am only mad whenever
She speaks out about something that I care what is the disclosure Act of 2020
OK Google
So I know sometimes
I think you know now they were
Vaccines are going around there's a possibility of like a meeting a friend
Right
Kind of a
Excited
There's a game in my future and I'm very excited
Kindness
Syd Barrett
Unless
Very bad you're like Alex
Dinner with James
Really great guy.
Fantastic crew
Cool of Liberties are indomitable
And it'll fighting Spirit it just makes me feel strong
That it was really great
I'm going to give you a big explosive tomorrow
Another terrorist icon
That is breaking
10 minutes
Infowars
Dot-com
James O'Keefe operates on
Sing only and that is attention
If you're ever in a position where James O'Keefe is offering
Exclusive you need to ask yourself
Some very serious questions about the legitimate
Embassy of the story that he's trying to give
I am
100% sure
This man whose entire career is based
Off of lying to the people that he is speaking to at any given point in time for the sake of attention
A prophet I'm sure there's no way you would have Alex
But you like you got to be asking yourself like
Exclusive up on Project Veritas Alex
How is it
Possible
You can
The Infowars itself is blackballed on
The major right-wing conservative news network
O'Keefe can hang out with Alex
And then still be like Fox News is like look at the new O'Keefe Master P
Good beef
It's not
Project Veritas
What significant event
Terrorist
Mexico
This is the third one in a couple weeks
This shutdown
Get the article out
Kara project even if everything that's being said.
I don't care about their scoop
I suspected terrorist was tracking arrested when they tried to enter the country
That's just a story that tells me the border security is pretty alright again
It's a failure ministration is ruining everything by catching terrorists
Whatever they cross into this country
Also if I were James O'Keefe I probably shy away from stories like this about terrorists
They run the risk of reminding people about that time in 2014 when he dressed up as Osama Bin Laden and walked across a stretch of the Rio Grande
River supposedly illustrator
Get to the country
It was super embarrassing and
I think this is a great idea
Mansion in the world again
And then I will say this
Player for costuming. Seems to be over in James O'Keefe's career
Over to dress up
Earlier
Dress up
To wear a suit
Dramatic
I hate him so much interview weirdos
The worst
Yep
New social media censorship
Going on here
All the usual
It also probably isn't true
Remove post by breonna Taylor's mother
Criticizing black lives matter say never helped
And they're full of crap
So now the mother and Brianna Taylor was killed wrongly
Big Houston
He gets beat up
That's a lot of
Protector
So you can see her Alex's position on the killing of Brianna Taylor his chain
Black lives matter
Because he's using the mask of being sympathetic
His attack on black lives matter
Zerorez
Back for it
A couple quick fact-checks here though
Taylor's mother did not say the black lives matter was a fraud on the Louisville chapter of like
Matter what you said she also has never dealt with
Also there's no indication that Facebook took down her post
It's entirely possible that she removed herself there's no verification
Turn on that
Paul was beaten up by his neighbor in 2017
And reports on the neighbors trial have called over a lawn care dispute
Taylor was killed on March 13th 2020
Retaliation for passing laws
Makes no sense and he's just grasping at straws
Also
Paul's Payless 395 Vincent
June 2020
It is a dead bill
Paul has not succeeded him up for 3 years prior
I think
That's a fun with a long hair is it I think it's
They would be described as an existential incident
Insofar as I do not appreciate his
So that would just be my
Sure
I feel like you might be the sort of cat who would like
Repeat
I just feel like it would be you would like
Put poison on some of his yard that would spell out something really offensive maybe in the grass
David I would never have a pet that is still good
Trim his Bonsai into offensive
I think I could
Probably get it
And then you do like that gag
You got the bottle
Bucket of water on the door and you like
And then somebody gets all that's terrible I get a crane
But like a really tall and then when he's walking
Getting out of his house in the morning I
Just pee right on his head
And then whenever he's not sure what it is and he looks up
I would say that if you're doing that
You'd be playing with fire
Playing with fire
Are you real bad
Play with fire
Call George
What did he say
He said
Isn't dangerous
Fearful master
This isn't a real watch
Nope
The structure of discussing fire in this exact construction with the serpent master
1637 by the website investigator
Was traced back to 50
The first time this
Your turn of phrase accredited to washing
Engine was in
Science journal
Consistently credited to wash
Washington since then
Just another example of Alex
Man I think that one
Probably goes all the way back to like 150,000 years ago whenever it was just like Ugh and that man is hot
Runaway
You can use fire for things but also it can f*** you
When I got really excited cuz you know
And the way that Alex was doing be like
Don't play with fire
I learned not to play fire
I got really excited and then
Sure the ones
Fire
The one letting it out of the box
Almost always the one burned
Fire at doesn't sound true at all
Safire
You are not in command of the fire
I wasn't ready for the fire to be the devil
I really wasn't
I reserved posted on my own
How silly it is to use
I also changed
Spectrum
All right you don't embrace it your respect
To the devil
What do you think got to keep Bucyrus think of that candy login.
I always appreciate it
Really lose
This is the thread while trying to do lyrics
Combines turn this into
A block a contact but then I have to do the last work
That's all
Spoken Word album is
Coming our way once he's off the air
Disclaimer
This for me is just like
Every now and again you need like that cute moments
And I think that this is really
Because there is a war on for your mind
No no
Raleigh State Controller Tennyson
About out of them
Yes
PC has to start whistling in the middle of a sentence
That my friend does a human moment
That is very
So cute
On this episode
Except a little bit of a story
Divorce
From his wife
Fungi
I think
How is it possible to turn this racist
Because I feel that's where we're going
Deep into that later is more
I don't even know what it is
I think the story Alex is trying to tell
Is
A couple of really hot ladies
After he was getting divorce right come on
Hot lady
I invited him to a drag show
Women
Divorce
Condos
Said hey what
Contest
No no no this is this
Was it North Austin
I'll go with you
Gorgeous
What the hell this is like that these are men
I was there with all men
Be a few here let's go
What
This story makes no sense
Incoherent
Yeah I wonder what the reality of the story
It is it's it rings
True in the sense that I have no doubt that a certain point in his life
Someone invited him to a drag
Show
That I would be
Feel strange
It doesn't sound like he knows what a drag show
It's possible I think he thinks that it's a burlesque
Show Maybe
And it's not a drag show
It's taste
Man
Isn't it sad that there's a certain part of me that's fine
It's so sad that if you're a
Conservative
Christian white nationalist
You can't enjoy a drag show
Which is one of the most joyous
Places that I've
At a drag show
This story may or may not actually be true greatly embellished because
For him to get into bashing drag queen Story Hour
One of the things that I noticed that he does
All the time is basically says
Reporters
Who captured like
Pornographic
Footage
Of kids with
Naked man and stuff like that
Antic
Do you have
Everybody everywhere
Playing it on yourself
What children happen
Kaiserslautern
I just couldn't imagine child
All on drugs are all sorts of crazy hormones
Doing all sorts
Grounded
Fifth
Team minutes
Physically sick
Wow
So much of that doesn't need to be part of the story
So much of it is like
Does detail still help with your story
It doesn't matter
How big is schlong
Any size long it's still illegal
I don't know if you
He said it was a major
That means
1-ranked away from giving him information
Is not a lieutenant colonel song
Yeah I don't know
Skip back to talking about
Anticipation is building
Maxine Waters
Said sum
Comments
Is not into
But the judge
No he's interested in making this a mistrial
You see that judge up there
We all just listen to a congresswoman
We don't we don't need a mistrial
Do you just have
Their houses last year
Blood
Shepherd's pie
About lawlessness in terrorism
And this mob French Revolution malice
Bolshevik Revolution
Revolution
Alex has yet to demonstrate or show any instances of jurors being Doctor Who
More seriously than I did the first time
There's another interesting thing
Found not guilty
Some clips from newscast civilians in Minneapolis who are expressing that are likely Beyond
His chauvinism
It's really important difference here and it's one that I think Alex refuses to acknowledge
If the news goes out an interview
Use people and they say that they are
Likely be protest
The chauvinist found not guilty
Does Alex think that the new Supra
10 that they didn't
The goal is to represent the opinion of persons on the street that they talked to
It would seem like an irresponsible level of censorship
Just edit the responses to reflect what you would want them to say
But that seems to be what Alex wants to happen
Well be okay
So the person being interviewed
Specific
Quickly that if Justice in this circumstance has denied it's so overwhelmingly obvious
It's what the verdict
Then I'm going to
Help people
No longer have a police precinct for a little while
And that was edited to be like a
I mean like really what's going on is
Essentially
This is how Alex creates contact
Alex
Looks like blurbs
He has because the narrative he wants
Supercuts
Do you think the right way
Has actually convinced itself that the other side is doing what they're doing
I think Alex is probably the only
The same thing and
Pretties alien differ
Picks and chooses
Call me
Explain what you meant by the end of that sin
Amazing
Alex is not racist as we've discussed
Anytime
But usually in the reverse
He is
Yes
2030 White People three or four black people
That use a front-of-the-line
And then the black controllers
Allies in the back cuz they don't want them seen by wanted to look
The scapegoat
The blacks Wally start the race war
Wow
Really
That was your chess game right there
I would say three moves is all it takes
Snowed a little bit more regularly in recent days
Is this a social justice
This causes are meant to incite racist backlash from
Orchestrated to do that by white people
Escape goats
At the front of their action
This is a pretty outrageously racist idea
The last episode
This is very much in the same prediction is Alex's forefathers who fought against
Be civil rights and
I realized in hindsight that maybe I should explain my point a little bit
Further
Texas kind of giving me an opening to do just that
Alex's favorite book
The one that turned him on to the new world order was called conspiracy by Gary Allan
A few years later got a bust
Pregnant
Honestly the timeline doesn't matter
This book is a primer that is
Has been cited by many people
Richard Belzer
Is being a revelation
A longtime member of the John Birch Society and wasn't his first
Facebook
Sleep Revolution in the
Switch is a scave
Very racist attack on the Civil Rights Movement
The idea we're secretly not actually black
Actually communist
Front
Typically run by wife
Just in case any white people reading this are concerned about unequal treatment
Treatment let's just
100% get rid of that idea that race even existed just white people versus
We arrived at the interesting possibility that the black Muslims were started by the Communists
Knowing that the majority of American Negroes felt a kinship with Soviet Russia
Establishing a religion based on
A revolutionary
States without the majority people realize
Significant
Probably surprisingly
Never actually just
Defies this cloak interesting possibility
Because as he goes on to say
If the black Muslims were Communists set up from the beginning
It's doubtful that any but the very top oligarchy were aware
That's some classic style proof right there
This thing is true and I can't prove it because only the top level of the conspiracy that I swear is real has that
Because previous and former professors
I mean you could
All of them are dead
Can trust that I'm Gray
You understand this
Construction that he's using his basically to prove the basis for my conspiracy in the suspicion
Assume the existence of the very conspiracy that I've failed to prove it
It's it's
No it's him
That if I'm right
You would already know or if my information was
You would have already
This runs constantly throughout his book
Vegetation by revolutionaries civil rights leaders
We're willing to trade the citizen safety
For the vote of a minority block
Every group is
The front every event does Inside by communist
48 / 0
Thesis
Quote
The Communists have been working for over 30 years on in America
Their efforts of usually fail because Negroes
Prove to be loyal America
But this is not caused it communist
The slacking
Because they see civil rights as America
Achilles heel
How many grow is the sacrificial cannon fodder
For a communist instigated Revel
This is the exact same rhetoric that Alex Jones uses
Civil Rights Movement
And Martin Luther King back
60 up
Challenge Alex to reflect on his moral lesson 121 overlap between his
This protest
Used to take social justice
Protester my country's recent
I mean you could again
This goes back to slavery this goes all the way back to them being like well there's no way that slaves could ever
Organize on their own
So it must be white
Because they don't like us having all the money it sure it goes all the way back
Yeah
There
I choose to focus this
Because this is part of Alex's intellectual tradition
Anti-communism had
This is the world that Alex espouses
Very deeply communism stuff
This routing of something that he needs to
Stop
Bike
It's nonsense
You can't have
You can't play the exact same game but your forefathers did it again
Civil Rights Movement
And pretend like
That's not what you're doing
It's not about communist
So Alex has reflection and everyone in his orbit pretend
Books like
Communist Revolution in history
Don't exist
Because they make it too obvious
But like I said communism
Call Justin
They used to hide behind
Yeah absolutely whenever Communists as use it as an excuse to Jews in Hollywood
It's not like J Edgar Hoover was like
This'll never work against black people
Just to give you some
Idea
Little
People want
People to read
Looks like this
It was very hard to find my phone
From another
The University's private Library
But I got it for like a week and was able to photo
Costco
It's
Buried
Because it's super sensitive
Terrifyingly racist thing I've read
Very similar to
Loretta record Alex Jones
These are the things like backlight replacement Siri in there
We'll get there sooner or later
Alex Goes to College
It's going to happen with this verdict
What do you think
Okay so
Hungary
Scared
Skinwalkers common
Even though
Phone is blowing up on trial
I think they told her to do that to hang with Sherry I agree to cause the blow up
Okay
Precipitate
Here is going to be really upset about that
And it seems to be fairly consistent
Things change
Statement where he pretty much
The liberal media
Buying a boat
The whole time
Bill Maher is now a secret Patriot
I can't
That should that the breaking
Pretty much
Regular Democrat
Before this
Shooting range
No heat
I can't think of a
Where is he
Isn't that political philosophy
Before
The only reason anyone would be some kind of a super liberalism position
I'm listening to Alex gallo.
Also Alex Tucker Carlson
Years Alex's used things
The whole thing globalist wanted to crash the economy to hurt Trump
That wasn't
Tireli based on a joke that bill Barr said on one of his shows
What does use Bill Maher's comments to such a prominent extent in his conspiracies
Explain bilmars role in global operations like this
Belmar
Results
Ventriloquist
Yeah it's basically a global
Program
I was just going to say whenever he said some people have been
I'm like
That is bring your job for 5 years
Cheese's
Reversal for Belmar
If I believe the word that Alex
Bill Maher should be super assassin Squad
Ventriloquist dummy or some dumb s***
But it's made up that has matter something that he said on his last episode
Can guys eventually leave the globalist with other milk
At this point
Norm
Stand-up comedy
Nobody else
Isn't schachter's
Okay
Black lives matter
Did the call
Again
Great Bear
What if your wife
Consistent
Sure people know that hey
Black lives matter to address burglary
Just to make sure everyone knows the number for black lives matter
Significantly longer than 911
Call the police to deal with racial Injustice
No deal with advocacy for cause
We've made an amazing point
Had to do it
Again
Two back-to-back UPS open
Cuz little bit about the idea
Surgery for minors
Less important
An exchange that happens at the end of this book
Is
So heartbreaking
It is so sad
We cherish
We were in a situation where parents
Could be accused
Risk of injury to a minor
Their minor children
Exchange operations
Absolutely insane
And I don't really know who
It's from
Well if young doubted that would be mine that would be one candidate
Oh my God you're a f****** lawyer
Wilbur
This case be thrown out
Seeing as how half of the jury is
Fakeness
How embarrassing would it be to be like
Well
Taken seriously sitting here with this dumb f*** out
Cui Bono is Satan
Seriously consider that perhaps somebody would benefit from not having the remote
Social life destroyed by their real
Star Pizza Temple
Alex has a disease
I think he has a
Compulsion
Sickness
Benediction
And that is
Whenever Norm pattis is on the show
Can't help himself
Make declarations that
Volvo million dollars
Thaisub she's under light
Press conference
And she's got almost pure pupils
Talk about Maxine walk to
I need those eyes are
What the hell is she on
Bright lights in somebody's eyeball
95% people
Understand
Pupil dilation
It's remarkable I mean
Still not a pattern
Norm has been honor for two instances of Alex offering a million-dollar Bounty Zone Fitness
Turn or might be like it's me about me am I so boring but I would hate to spice this up with millions of do
Dollars on the wall
Well I think she's on self-righteous
That's because I am not going to insist
That she is on drugs
Man
Interesting
Appearance
What is interesting is it
Well the lawyer friend I think it's because
Veterans Elementary
Buchanan there are only two who will
I might have accidentally skipped a minute or something because like
Alex is in the middle of talking to Norm
And then
You talkin about
Cheapest
I couldn't tell and tell them back-to-back
4 minutes
Kind of figured out what was going on
Is to not have mobs
It's the
It's the remedy
Inside
Jury
Into a mob
Jury trial
Maybe they're gold
Will be to ultimately replace juries
Assault
This should really threaten
This is just as bad as going a free-speech or Gunn
Control
Is the jury system
Because it's ordinary
Everyday People
Coming together how are the Judiciary lies of the people
Is in the power
The jury
And it's a check on
To check
Media wants a power to misquote
Miss miss
Misrepresent and then
The media wants to
So I found this really interesting
So what's going on here is just coming on the show
The game of their playing
I thought was really over
What's going on here
Beer that Alex has been building up to is one of a hung jury or an acquittal
Because then there's going to be
Naturally
This trial was essentially a setup to get people to the point where there will be riots
That's where Alex's callers suspect them
He's even said that he believes that Maxine Waters statements were intentionally made
Deposit mistrial so there'll be riots
But what if that doesn't happen
You don't want to put all your eggs in one basket
To provide the alternative narrative
In case things don't go this whole episode
In case Chauvin is found guilty
Ameritas in place here
Did Maxine Waters comments were essentially the creation of mob to replace
Jury trials
Until the verdict is read if you're a listener of Infowars you're being asked to believe that Maxine Waters comments were sign
Chinese Lee and Bob Costas
And also and needlessly complicated conspiracy
Meant to cause a mistrial
Infowars needs both of these to be true until the verdict come
It's a Game of Thrones rose bush
I do appreciate how is the audience
Maybe he'll all of conservatives view everybody on the left and so far is
Never speaking to them they know exactly what the left is going to do is truly amazing that if you never
Ever learn anything
About your political enemy
You can say whatever it is you want them to
These narratives established
Pretended they were ripe
Regardless of how the jury decides
React to the verdict being read actually determines which of these ideas
Yeah if Chauvin is not guilty I will say the waters cause that to start the right
If he is guilty that angle will be quickly
Sister of the mob rule storyline
This is an important to recognize
Doesn't matter
Someone like Alex
Just things that he incorporates like
Props into the story
Add a story with the Chauvin trial is that there's no outcome
Actually good
They're all just
Useful
Alex
It is
It's
It's very annoying
It's very annoying that they can just
It's like a choose-your-own-adventure book based on the story
You know like they've already got where they're going
They just have to give you the difference
It's like pathways
To go down
Then you have to start over
Okay well now they're going to start a race war
Next time
But this time it was a Maxine Waters it's it's basically like
Consistently saying both A and B
Which are contradictory
Talking so much about
Yeah yeah yeah
A squared plus b squared equals
Either A or B
Barnes
He has some comments that he wants to make but how Society got to the point that it is
No although Alex
Should probably be mad at him
What did we do
Colletti's wanted to
How do we counter people like this
From culture
Better
Kindergarten Elementary School
Securus
False
He was saying it's a satanic
So Robert barnes's
Main contention
Is that
Conservative right-wing outraged imaginary problem let us into a circle
Stance
That is
Almost entirely conservative outrage at a made-up problem
Yeah or less
That does make sense
Should be mad about this is it Robert Barnes
School try on
P******
He believes the Ted Gunderson is the most viable Source ever
I wonder if Barnes was stopping himself
Because you can hear him say
You stopped him so I didn't want to be too specific
Like
Pissing off Alex there's a rule of life
Don't don't
Tread too closely into Alex's
Zones
You know especially not with
Specifics
Especially
You can't
I would like to Bear the indignity of agreeing with Alex's stupid
Book
Noted
Strokes gilo
There is also gambling on the side
You know how what you want you want from your lawyer is also gambling
To Barnes Barnes is a kind of guy who's going to make a definite
What's going to happen with this
50% chance
The trial
People
We're the Bad Guys
That would make me
You know
Sedgwick
Tiana jewelry
The main thing that protects us from a mob rule system where he
Centering the actual Justice he would
Take somebody anybody comment in the media
Call decision to exist entirely within Oppositional Defiant Oppositional Defiant his decision-making
The facts of the case the only thing
Maxine Waters
Jimmy Kimmel
Also
Congratulations bars that are 50/50.
There's a third possibility wishy-washy nonsense
I found this
Very busy
Zarbon all that bizarre
This phenomenon going on where
You had these two possibilities and these narratives that were built up towards the end
The show
Where you have
You know Maxine Waters is trying
Cause a mistrial in order to
Kid Rock eraser
Haven't
To create mob rule in order for the
The jury to be cowed into guilty
These things are kind of
You know it's tough
You have to disconnect
Right and what I thought was really interesting as in this
Next clip you can come
Cialix tie them together
Yeah alright
Believe
Acquit or disorder order they Bow Down
So now what Alex has done is he's taking these two things he's
Together under a similar umbrella
Feel like they're connected
Alex has decided that the deciding factor in this case is whether or not these three have been successful
To the case or even the possibility that any of the jurors could find Chauvin guilty unless they were doing
Such thing as the merits of
The case
Conversation this way
Conclusion isn't the right verdict of acquittal that's just a suit
A guilty verdict is that the jury was afraid of
Because nonsense
I said this makes Alex's narrative
Feel like they're connect
But they're actually not if you take a closer look
This new cleaner framing leaves out the entire thing about Maxine Waters specifically making the comments you did
In order to cause a mistrial so there would be right
Backfiring and
What are the differences between a really major to you would think
Because it's
Part of the globalist overarching
Plan right that's the problem here why are we adding this element
That destroys
The plan that was already working
In the conception of how Alex was talking about the verdict earlier in the episode it was pretty clear that the globalist want
Because their goal was to incite
With a guilty verdict
That is
Case the need to be so over-the-top
Did a mistrial is guaranteed in the
However in the new framing
It appears the Globus actually want to be found
Guilty
Lamar Brewer
These threats are either successful in which case
The verdict is guilty
Or they backfire in the service
Achieving
A guilty verdict
If you pay close
Close attention
Over the course of one show Alex is completely changed
The primary motivation of his imaginary villain
Because he's just making this up as he goes along
None of this means anything
This whole
Like this whole thing
Is basically just a lazy idiot engaging in an active really long
Respected improvisational storytelling
So that was the tale I think of
Of the 20th
I am in the evening
Afternoon
Pentagon time zone
What you going to do
Chauvin guilty
Yes
Also Ted Nugent
Got covid
Other news
You should go he doesn't he's got
He's got to go on with covid that's got a half
Absolutely find a way to be like this is
Coming on the 21st now ask her
The verdict
Has happened
You can tell a little bit of a
Studio
5 Wednesday
What's a Lana Del Rey
We watched him murder somebody
It's not an attack on whiteness
It's not an attack
There's so many reasons to attack whiteness we didn't need this one you know how you were saying
I did
So you were before the bath
Because of this
Quote unquote
So you had to listen to Lana Del Rey
He loves this album
Man I tell you what
Free Christian album
Christian
Sure
Avant-garde The Cutting Edge
I'm guessing that Alex just saw the one of the titles of the songs on Lana's new album
Tulsa Jesus Freak
Who's Alex forgotten that just three years ago he was spending quite a bit of time I show yelling about how Glenville Ray was a
Evil spirit spells against Donald Trump because she said in an interview that
Used witchcraft against Trump
Delena remember her the entire right-wing was up in arms about her breakthrough out being called Born to Die
That was
The other outrage machine time that was back then when the outrage
Machine was cranking out that b******* it's just it's so interesting I feel worried for him
When he's playing about to land.
I don't appreciate
But it's okay for him to love Lana Del Rey publicly
Star Wars
Yeah he still feels the need to be like
Sublease
Exactly someone you would only know only exist in the books
Something it would be impossible to be immediately.
Because Star Wars
So in Christianity
Yeah I guess that means Christianity is having a great time
Satan is real
Okay
You are
And this is not a simulation
That sounds like something a simulation but right
Consciousness
Exactly like what somebody the tribulation for today
The universe the seed of
It's not just giving away
Pretty lady
You must
Detested
We tested
Maxine Waters in the front
What
And the Rockefellers in the Bill Gates
The world
These are people
Failed the test
Held in Mindless clown like
Bondage
Mostly keep that clipping for the turn of phrase to sound like
I like bondage is not bad
I mean it's just
Spiritual does seem like we're going to get esoteric Christianity
Deal with the coverings
There's a lot of racist to cover that
Probably just talk about
We are in the process of
I'm not human extermination
The slow destruction
All carbon-based life
Forms on
Is the goal of Satan
Does that matter though
Animated
Image of God
And Satan
Rc-20
Why
Humans are
We are beautiful
We can experience
The universe
Communion
The Creator
Poems
The eye of God
Gods
Castle
We seattlr
Todd system
Experience
I don't want to be any
Nothing Satan do
Never changed
What
I don't know I feel like maybe he should have gone to college
Jim got high maybe we'll work some of this out of his system
You know Kevin like you know you're annoying conversation
1 this life
Yeah
Hit it again
This is a test and that's all it is
Because
God is testing you to see if you can come
And hang out with him
I guess
Is the person
Entity
Doing the
The testing
That's he is part of God's
Planned
If you're like Pelosi or Prince Philip you have failed
Potassium
He's been doing this for thousands of years
You know the devil is like I'm already part of the plan and gods like he's not going to succeed in destroying all of the people
We've got Alex fight well because the last 999 years is 1000 year plan
Leading up to this
Well that's why God gave us
Sort of
Biasly people have about like
The immediacy order currency like
The time
I'm tired
Every generation of the last generation
Exactly
Obviously there's reasons to feel that way sometimes
From that in a way.
Travis Scott
Sounds like that
Like maybe
I started to like
I don't know
Explorer Elementary
Yeah when you should have that, your head is empty your big dumb dumb you should be smoking weed and having dumb conversation
The same time when you're not smoking weed
You should be reading books
Struggling with reading comprehension
And then you won't have to have those conversations ever again
I love and never having those conversations damn
What is really bizarre
Immediately after this
Conversation about
Elements of God's eye
Experiencing things
For God
Also tentacles
Cone
In the eye of God
We are
Gods
Castle
God's tentacles
Todd system
Experience
Nothing statement
Will ever change that
So don't let the enemy get you down
How do I get to Baytown
It's sad
Religion of race war
Worshipping
On the surface
Really felt weird
Did you want to do
I don't
Feel comfortable now that makes me feel very uncomfortable that's really gross because now you're
Transforming the
Even the slightest modicum of racial Justice
Into a holy war
Against anyone who would try and get a modicum of
Also the pronouns that are used for a little bit
Strange Music
Eyes of God and whatever
Them
But he does seem like what he was doing
Very different view of people based upon their skin
That's just me I could be wrong tell you what
Is very strange very weird
Is a very easy explanation
Just talking to white people
Dammit
He thinks he's talking to a diverse audience
That's weird
That doesn't matter
That's not cool
Anyway what I'm saying is that we
Alex's buddy Gary Allan
You know
I always like to find these kinds of moments where there's all its branches
What is the possibility for Alex and I too agree
Delegation is always even if it's superficial
I kind of thought that maybe Nancy Pelosi is very
Unfortunate
Poorly
Really putting your name at the top of the list
Yourselves out and
Referred to
George Floyd's murder as
Sacrifice for justice
What are those
Realshit
I thought that maybe there would be an opportunity for Alex and I to come to some sort of an agreement
Yeah it seems like it wouldn't be hard
That's the level of s*** that if I was Nancy Pelosi's a Dye wood
Immediately
Play tackle her off the stage if everybody will like you more if you get hurt for this
Excuse of like ice
Unfortunately
Layout for Alex
To get me to agree with him
But somehow
Only miss the shot he broke his ankle
Critical failure
She said yesterday
Breathing through her face diaper
Life
Terramaster
Baby fake George Floyd for his
Sacrifice like he was a veteran
Jesus on the cross
Drugged out
Male prostitute
Devastated Leon happy
The world
Until the moment he died
Just missed
Wow
Staffmark
Incredible
Justin credible something so
So easy he's too racist
To even criticize Nancy Pelosi when she
Wow
Level I just didn't expect
I just didn't expect
Withers disappointment
And then there's this point
You can't even clear that
Critiquing Nancy Pelosi
Yeah that kind of bumble dare she not be racist enough for me
That's that's not good
So the feds
Which means actually the UN is in charge and we have no cover
Okay
Loc I'm bouncing the globalist UN control
Meaning you and Jacob
Speech
Policies
Military
We are now
Concord Nation
I didn't really realize we're Concord
Unified against their evil week
Usually take government
This is just about the Department of Justice opening an inquiry into the Minneapolis Police Department
Sister dramatic little baby into the UN running the country
Bodies
Yeah
Diculous escalate things a lot quicker whenever your big bad is the devil
You know you can't be like this is just going to
He couldn't even possibly like they're just going to root out the Patriots in the in the police state
That's why it's bad it has to be a
Fleet overthrow of the United States
Sure
I don't I don't know if you're aware of this
But we live in a Multiverse
Do you know that we live in those universes simultaneously
30 Head East
Not just live in one dimension
I want open the phone number to the barber the next our constitutional lawyer joint is going bad
I'd like to shift the dimensions do that
How do I live in the dimension where Norm pattis isn't coming back on the show
What's up what's
The quantum suicide
Can you just call suicide at Universal
F****** building Asia
Ridiculous
Pour milk
Do it
So I wouldn't tell you
Not a good
If you're saying that now after where we've come
Well
This has to do with lead in
To conversation
Conversation about the shooting
Sure sure
Good
Islam black young people
But they're highly impressionable and what you should do
I just saw video this morning
Columbus Ohio
Little black babies
Looks like she has a McDonald's cheeseburger
How far
Where are you
Woman and a black woman
With a
People call the police
She did keep stabbing people
And because the white
Devil
Shop the Black Angel
Black lives matter protesting and rioting
There's a lot of details to be sorted out about the shooting
Assess the situation
I'm going to leave that to
More information to come out
Time to process and what-have-you
I wanted to play this clip however to demonstrate how opening for Alex
Begin by discussing how
Reasonable black youth being taught to attack
Actual details of this case are secondary and not nearly as important
So explicitly racist
His show are this is
That's outrageous.
That is so fat
I just don't know how you for very impression how can
Can I don't I will never understand
Quite how
Easy it is
Is 4
White race
Get to like
Well
If you're 15 in Black though you're big
Right here bigger
Then
15 year old white people
Also whatever happens
I just
How
How do you get
There
Like
It's just unconscionable
I don't disagree
Like for all they're screaming about pedophilia its
Kill Dobby
Because they're black
And that means there
Or whatever
Unreal it's
It's pretty breathtaking
This Racist
To not be
Like
It's amazing that it exists
Yeah it's a really it's shocking
Did it exist
Stem isn't dealt with
The proper
Contact number
It's not related to as like
Printed sometimes it's a clam show sometimes they talk about other things
Maybe the clan had to talk about like anniversaries in like we have a new kid
This is so pretty
Pretty out in the open
That's unreal
That's just unreal
Alec
Completely different idea he thinks the show is like full of sophisticated information
I've always believed in
That's why I said
Populist program
Put out
Very sophisticated information
All so simple truth the same time
Believing that
The level of information that
Understand
Not done the information now
Wow
Government Style
PowerPoint
Just go over.
That is extremely effective not just like General Flynn
I can tell you
Bannister's world leaders
2025 20
It was done in a briefing
Not a f******
I feel like this is a simulation because there's no way a human being could possibly be that unself-aware
Images
You can't possibly f****** believe that anybody took that chick Siri High
Sparse video that he did was so f***
Offensively clunky
Who's so dumb that Michael guy with a total weirdo
Taken line
Completely out of context making
Completely false assertions about the document
Anybody who actually read it
Like without
Already pre deciding that Alex was right
Oh my God
Not a f******
Here's the thing that I have to like the idea
But he has another speed
Right I do like that idea because I think it's
Funny when he does that
You don't have that picture anymore
Maybe never did
But he was certainly better at looking like he did
Earlier
I like that because I would like for him to take this way more seriously
Cuz I will too
I-don't-want-to-talk-about-it
Conceptions of the devil give a s*** you don't even know how fast your fast
You been hanging around 75 like
Sooner or later he's going to get better at batting
It's just it's frustrating and I would like
That's it that's kind of interesting though because
Once you find out like the FBI was listening to Joe Biggs I'd like
Antifa protests
You realize like all these people are morons
That the CIA had meetings on it because
I don't know if I trust any of them to do a fundamental Google search
At this point we're all insane
If I worked in the CIA I might want to have a meeting on it
Pizza
We're going to put it on the big screen
It's time for the big enchilada
Let me hear phone calls
Public with their money
The medical system
The media system
World Council of churches on with all the churches are just
Country Club field groups
Spotify
It doesn't matter
Hollywood
Orthodox Islam
Israel
South Africa they got everybody
Wow one thing you don't have
You
U.s. military
Stop going on
It's got its own problems
Getting a divorce
Chivalry
Chopper
Cars race riot
Military police
Get control of them
Not this makes sense why would they have
You don't need to take over the police
Also if Alex is
They don't have Russia
What know what they got everything. Everything got everything is the 2nd of the police
The fact that you're putting those two together
Kind of makes you realize what the police is don't you like this is ridiculous
Like even taking the serious way
There's still plenty of white nationalists in the US military in the police
Stillwater heavily-armed whereabouts
So
We got that
Yeah I don't know this just it feels like
It just felt like that was what was going to like
Work for him to say
Match with any of the stuff he says
It doesn't make sense
I feel like if you were somebody who
The police in the military
You're a fast
That's what I would
This is just
Splake
Improvisational storytelling
In storytelling
Sometimes
The hero is doing well
Sometimes girls doing
When Heroes down
You had a tear for them to come back out
Or whatever it is
I think it was a couple weeks ago
Usher
Georgia
They are now losing
I'm not like the Q people tell you everything's fine we've won the war
We're losing
Everything's collapsing
And we have no future
Launch accelerator timetables
Was Jeffrey me Reckless they were 10 years behind
Hear this over and over and over again
He's got to get a new bit
Like is this B is
Tired
I just
Feel like I can handle this
Infinite battle between Alex
And his evil enemies right and everybody is either accelerating or decelerating
On his mood is putting their chips on the table
If it doesn't work this time I guess they've been defeated
I don't know
This Mexico
Yeah I would say
Get Alex institutionalized
There's a lot of things that he says that are like
Offensive
Really offend
Shunned
Yeah
This
If she really believe this
You should be putting
The padded cell
From them on I am here
Vision of the enemy
Alex is taking on the sins of humanity
So he can see the globalist
Playing like a crook like you've taken on the role of Jesus
Frederick
The globalist
Is not
Blessed Alex
Is
Very close to declaring himself the new Messiah
Because he was
Getting more and more comfortable with talking about himself as a prophet
Over the last six months or so at all
I must make myself of the Christ so long before you want that next
Okay
Go to called
Decades
Two volatile and paranoid
Pedophile
Call slaves and China's evil and
Everything is propaganda against the white man and
And they're right.
And everybody was
Just tell me I was
Freedom and guns and private property as the white man
Communism is the black man
Good
Call Brandon
Even in commercials
Like abusing my men and women hitting them and just it is just always just trigger
Several years ago I hurt you for the fur
First time
And I realize I'm not the only person that sees that you know I thought I was like
The bumbling husband probably dates back a little further than married
I guess
It's better than if they were like I think we should go back to The Honeymooners when it was
Your wife
The character trip with a dumb husband
He's going to really hate when he learns about all the other historical characters of people who
Call boy
Little bit
Fathers are kind of idiots is because
Easiest way to make
And flexible enough to
To fit into the comedic
Premises that are required for a sitcom to work
Most of the situation of the characters get into probably wouldn't happen or if they
Did they would be resolved in way less comical ways
If one of the characters in charge wasn't a goof
You could make every show like Father Knows Best
But guess what Father Knows Best
Suck
Show
But you know what I also hate the depiction of white people in films
Being stupid which is why I hate Breakfast at Tiffany's
Do you know what I hate about Breakfast at Tiffany's
Who is definitely meant to read his wife 100%
Yeah this is
This is not to
What does make sense this guy would have these
Clearly
Racist feelings towards media
And everything that you eat
And then he said he's like I found my people
Of course
No s***
How old
All white people have had it
F****** p****
Aesthetically
Easy for so goddamn long
The idea of one
Appearance in movies or film the white guy is the bad guys like
How could anybody do that
Alex would beg to differ based on his own
Millions and millions of dollars
Any black people
75 times by white people
Hospitalized
I love those folks I love the ones
Yeesh
I want to go back
Whistle
Do you remember when you whistle did I appreciate that was great
They gave it all that's what they should do if he gets done too much of a race is red
They should just start playing
I'm in your blackberry
To get like one of those intermission
Images and it's no it's photoshopped Alex's face
Holding hands with young Richie Cunningham
Opie carrying carrying a fishing pole piece of s***
Hey I'm a huge racist but also I'm going to brag about how
Good I am
Batman fights and put them in comas
Sure
Very strange what up
F***** up dude
I'm just saying I wouldn't be who I was
If I would put in the hospital and broken legs and broken arms and
Subdural hematomas
I really want to fight
I'm not going to pretend to not understand the point Alex's
Just trying to make your portal
Being like battle-hardened
Thankful for the struggles that he went through the movie is today
There's a fine version of it
Black people
Specific people he got in fights
I was generalizing to the larger black population
Here in a way that is incredibly
Listening to this I'm not actually even sure if Alex realizes he's doing what he's doing
It is embarrassing
Yeah that's
This is been a real sucker
Can highlight reel
This is this it's nothing really
Good
No
I would say that you
Might as well
I'll just come out and be like
Feel like I can't be too far off
If you can try and justify as racism
You're not
It's too late for that
Yeah yeah
All we want my script here in a little bit of
You know
Sleeper happy we're sure
Who's calling in Fallbrook
One of the last holdouts in Brooklyn
Strong
Read that how you welcome
I live in a beer
It's an Irish
Italian term
The last
In Brooklyn
What they're doing is there
People from
Culebra
What does it mean
Shut it down
Restaurant
Illegal immigrant
Brother industry
Yeah
Been a little while since I've heard Alex eating lunch
Yeah I mean look
You could really expect from this. Other than like
Some pretty
You know like I don't
I don't
Think it made sense
Based on real-life conditions
No
Yeah
It sucks
I'm going to not listen
Next episode
Over my birthday weekend
I can spend my time in the past as opposed to
Focusing too much on
Compromise
Sucked
Yeah that's
Batman it's it's like that
Candle
Like I got it weed
In order to move forward we have
To get rid of
We got to not do this anymore
While we're fighting it they're fighting so much
So f******
King hard it's in
Insane
It's insane
I don't know what to do
F*** races
So
Until then
More importantly
Let's go out on a positive note
From DJ Dan arti Hellyeah
I will catch you next time Darrell run this blah blah blah
Canon Georgia
Knowledge
College vype.com
Miller Miller Miller
Real real real real