Damn important
I have great respect for knowledge B. I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
MoneyGram
Dot-com
Beverages and talk a little bit about
Alex Jones
Did we are Dan Jordan
What's up I have a quick
Yeah what's up what's happening
What's the price for today
Vibrates but today is staying humble
Hashtags
Ball boy
I don't know about classic rock
And apparently I really stepped in it I thought I'd said that that's what I'm playing with fire is that about it
Many people have pointed out a lot of whenever you missing something about
Music
That's on me I don't know a lot
My parents were pretty
With that music growing out his brought up in the past
So my first album that I ever bought was Alanis Morissette's Jagged Little Pill and my mom made me return it
Bad influence
Probably
Probably everything by The Rolling Stones was a mysterious mysterious thing
Discovered some Beatles songs from Beatles Rock Band
I was going today it's kind of level
Naivete I have about
I would imagine that the Rolling Stones earlier
My dad might be like
F****** around with like
Pete Seeger
That's where we're at your dad in the secret prog-rock genre of just like somebody who would know
No one's around is like time to listen
Send it yes
Like I'm going to give you my money
Okay well you know what you talk about that Blood Sweat and Tears
You did like Chicago and Iraq
I don't know
Was he in the marching band
I can't remember anyway
My point is I'm sorry to everybody by disappointed by my nan
Knowledge of
So how
Okay
I will stand by my position that I don't like the doors
You claimed the song was the doors
It could very easily have been a completely disconnect what I was thinking about trying to play that game but then
Sincerity and aboveboard I have to admit that I did
F*** that up yet
Anyway Jordan
But I have these bright spot.
Attaboy
We had a lovely time we got together and go about that
Mortal Kombat
Spotify
Fantastic time and I have
Decided that it is the worst movie ever made
It's the worst movie ever made but I was disappointed as hell
But In-N-Out this is how I'm thinking of it
Alright
Godzilla versus
This Kong
Have you know what I got
I got Godzilla
Versus
Raider game
Promise
And it delivered
And what I hear Mortal Kombat
I want a goddamn tournament there this was what I was screaming most of the movie
Spoiler alert for Mortal Kombat there's no tournament
It is a warning
Everything that really bothers me is like okay I get it some of these movies are such that like
Maybe the tournament will be in the third movie
Yeah they're good
It's cheap but whatever
It's not fair that this movie open
Opens up making a big deal about how the
The fate of Earth depends on this tournament
Infuriated
Furiated
We are going to lose that sponsorship money man we are
Nextaff K-12 videogame will not be
Announce
Through us it was still fun though you know he likes it
I like the idea of getting overly excited for no reason almost as a bit about a movie coming out
It was fun to do that to watch a movie like
That was new
Yeah yeah I should have really long time we haven't watched a movie together in a long time
The forever this was your idea you were like
We're watching Boardwalk
Yes you did
It's the worst movie ever made
So Jordan today
In the past
Continuing our March through
That time so we can learn I realized as I was
Listening to visit one of the things that I probably
Beasley I'm the most
Interested in is
Seeing if that sort of
Bizarre Christian extremism
Exist
Within him back
Eventually he thinks he's fighting the devil
To be what I'm most interested in
Because if that's
Been going on for 18 years
Someone should have
You know
We should be
We should have a societal understanding
That this guy thinks he's the
F****** Messiah
It has nothing to do with bank really totally
It's fighting the devil
States
It's complete nonsense
With a little thin veneer of political Intrigue in order to trick people into thinking that what they're involved in isn't
Extremist
Missing signs and they've been simmering light
Slight little bit since you were being ungenerous perhaps you could.
Put that in the in the
The holster what happens here on May 6th
See if we can
So we can find any more clues and then I get a better picture of what's going on
First I got to give some shout-outs to some blocks
What year is the Jordan need to livestream
From Chrono Trigger pretty please
You're not about to walk
I'm a policy wonk very much and that's a good idea got to require a premium
They also screams from Chrono Trigger
Is it
It's pronounced 88 even Tie fighters are now
Tie fighters thank you so much of an apology walk
I don't want to play more development through the
Halloween controversy
I'm a policy wonk
Twosome technocrats
So first we got Jewel see thank you so much you are now technocrat
Damn I love you but the Rolling Stones wrote play with fire not the f****** doors
Thank you so much you're now technocrat
And Brian
Technocrat
Heroin
Freakishly large
Thank you so much Joel
The music skull Durand Bryan
Answer I think I'm going to change my bright spot to just now
I love you so
Where is narcotics drop
Hyperplasia
Contact
More terrifying go to just somebody in a monotone yes I'm a maniac hasn't been earlier in this the episode before that
Open out at all no
What could you listen to presentations you like
This guy is
Being crazy
No you're not
Serialized content
But he has been a maniac
The best
At least we're aware of the bathroom
Siberian the future I will be so nuts that I have to apologize now
Exactly
Three starts off the show and I honestly think
I'm working on Siri this is another thing I'm tracking as I'm going back to the
The past
Make Joe Rogan might have ripped off Alex
Crime
Bacteria
So I think I think Rogan might have stolen calling his show powerful
2003 this is before the Rogan Experience powerful Joe Rogan
Experience
Powerful broadcast here
I don't think so
The bechdel group
Took the story here is Alex's talking about it begins by Jane Mayer in the New Yorker
Where she covers the connector
In between the bin Laden family and the back door
About to be Global Construction and engineering company to which
The US government recently awarded its first major multimillion-dollar contract
To reconstruct war-ravaged
This was because
Laden family head invest
10 billion dollars in
In a company called
Fremont group
Which began as a subsidiary of Bechtel but it been a separate entity since
Since 1986
Some of the board
Members of Bechtel we're also board members of Fremont but they weren't
Connected businesses so
An investment in one isn't necessarily an investment in the other
There's a lot of reasons
Point fingers at McDowell and spec
Spectre not above board in their dealings with this tenuous connection to the bin Laden family is not one of them
Even if you connect them conch
Greatly to Fremont then you still need
Need to demonstrate how the money the bin Laden family invested in Fremont
Has any connections to the actions of Osama bin Laden
There's so much work that you still need to do to make this a CV
Conspiracy
And all Alex is doing is just like pointing at
Someone else's headline and then just
Construing it
More like
Oh I heard
That the McDowell group was into some s*** or I'd be like oh yeah of course they were most business
Does commit Financial crimes
I don't think their financing
Terrorism
More expensive than just committed Financial crime
Conspiracy that there toward the train
To dance around without explicitly saying it is like
So this Bechtel group they do a lot of
Construction project
Multimillion-dollar
So it was about the Twin Towers
If they were actually fake and they were made at it was a small model that was
No no okay
Like
Funding of this is related
To causing the need for the construction should have closed loop
The conspiracy of being hinted at without actually overtly saying because
Okay now hold on if you were to actually assert that
People be like
You can't you can't prove any of this
Like Alex's doing then
Yeah we kind of get away with
Approving a case when you haven't done anything
Follow the money
There's a
Few million invested in a small company that's terrorism okay alright fine
So Alex is this guy who
Has always been right about everything and he's
Just like
Just waiting
To be proven right
All the time
So interesting to see how clearly above the left-right Paradigm Alex's back in two
Can't trust any liberals
Consistent about how the left right thing
Just going to lose definitely doesn't seem like a dishonest manipulative
Extremely right-wing a******
The truth is that Alex does dislike the left and the right
You can tell
But it's important to recognize what he's
Complaints are
He hates the last because he hates
It's the right because he doesn't feel like they're far enough to the right
Mother secretly humble
Wright also 18 years later on our passports do not include iprint
Things Alex has not always been right about
What's this time. Alex
Wants to hear George W come out and be like segregation now
Then and then he be
Well above the left-right paradigm
Certainly Beyond
We have another echo of the past that certainly plays in the present-day quite a bit
That is the idea that you pay with cash
Somewhere
Your
Going to go to prison
So that is not happen
Yeah
I mean Debbie didn't India Fraser old paper money
I didn't know motor just be like of one daily
Just like no paper money
I am not sure if that's been a full and total
I know the during covid there has been a lesser use of money
Use paper money totally fine
Drink that I am enjoying right now
I was kind of
Suspicious about this and
It takes him until
The end of the episode to actually
Talk about what this article is about we can close this way
He's reading this anyway it sounds like
Poorly written
An attempt at humor
But also know that like
I got editorial kind of thing
Here's basically what's going on
Bromley
Mutant
I once again I misinterpreted
Find something lady
So that's the story
Some guy was
That you learned that at Saks
They don't accept cash on things over
Sew in
Infuriated
Just can't imagine what
Opening something
The mail
Hey Rick if you can't find something more than 350,000
That's fine that's totally fine
But I'm slightly annoyed people buying things more than 300
$50 also if I were someone who was
Running a store like that I might be suspicious
Someone paying $1,000
Attached
Of course
Why wouldn't you be
I wouldn't judge them
I'm too much but I
This money might be dirty
So Alex gets to talk
It's more about the bin Laden family
He does not cover this story about Bechtel in-depth or anything
What does ramble a bit about
Bin Laden how do you CIA
I love the song Ramble On do you know did that doors
That they carry out dangerous world
Ygopro
Amanda her magic
I thought that's a lot of stuff
Being sad
You have to be on the moon
Did not know that he's committing worldwide
As we speak
Not at all arise didn't simply quite strongly that did londres
Steve some training from the CIA back in the 1980s
When Bin Laden and the mujahideen were fighting against Soviet communist right
You can even be
Real pretty reasonable and assuming that there's some of that financial support from the USDA to find its way to Bin Laden and
His fighters in that. Short as part of operation
Asian Cyclone aimed at fighting communism
Broad with the help of proxy arm
A strong argument could be made that the formation of al-Qaeda was at least partially the effective blowback
From these behave
Indian operator
The thing is that one can accept
The conventionally understood history of Bin Laden and his connections to the USA Embassy I am still recognize that
The claims Alex is making
Are unfound
Sing that stupid geopolitical decisions in
Inspired by the anti-communist
History of the Reagan Era led to a
Racine and severe consequences
Is not the same thing as saying that I was Sullivan Lawton within the CIA
Very
Yeah it's wild to me to go to like
Osama is still working
For the CIA instead of immediately assuming that the CIA made a stupid and short-sighted
The decision
That is
Perfectly in line with literally every decision that
Yeah yeah it's pretty say makes sense there's narrative
Consistency there
So the second Play Metallica's making in that Cliff is that there's no construction that happens in the Middle East without the involvement of
The bin Laden family
Not why
The bin Laden family is a majority owner of the bin Laden Group Global holding company
Formerly known as Saudi Bin Laden
They do have interest in a lot of construction in
Some incredibly high-profile projects like the
The Jeddah Tower pure but it's a little much
Pretend that they run
A complete record of all these
Orchard project to the middle
Does not want to learn about Sovereign wealth
A Forbes Middle East estimate recently put the total value of project in the Saudi Arabia and
Construction Market at one point
Trillion-dollar
And that's not even considering like
713 billion + UAE project
578 billion in Egypt
It's a fun story to tell the bin Laden family has a Stranglehold on the market and no one makes anything without their approval Natalie
Vix
Not real
It's just a cartoonish exaggeration with the news that was reported by the ties between the bin Laden family in the back door
Inflate
Into being something
Completely different than it actually is
There problems with the interconnectedness of these boards and you can make some good arguments about the way contractor beta Don and doled out
Another sort of conversations are completely
Impossible
If a point that you want to start from his opinion
You're trying to understand the real world
And that's what Alex is
Ushering his audience
Extort
And also like
Construction Group
In Saudi Arabia are run by the government
Yeah it's not the bin Laden family
Governments
Using this for their own personal gain
Either way that makes perfect sense if you know anything about the history of that government
Jordan
We've heard a lot about Alex
Predicted 9/11
Sure email
We know that
About a month before
He did Bill Cooper saying
Exact same stuff on his show
Several times
Times before that Osama himself was probably
You could assume that if your
Alex
Text Cliff doctor little bit about where he got some of his ideas
Hardball
Sorry Gary Hart
Chris Matthews having a MoMA
Yeah it was this a segment on the show back then but the CFR moment
Alec saw this
Latency for moment happening in public
That there was going
Tubi
Sunday
Is a slightly different story
Bloody Jay
God gave you a vision
A little added
Get on my knees
That place and then
You can actually see everything going on in the universe
Plugging directly into the source
And others that time but he went on Rogan show and said that he got it from a dream yes there is that was a two-hour
You think I did it in July 25th
Romanatwood on Erin's World Trade Center by know she is up and load them on Shelly's Wars
And I said I just got this from analysis information but I can
Having a drink
I love the of the towers smoking on us
I love the idea that in the present day when he's talking to Rogan to try and be interesting he's like
I claimed back then that it was based on analysis but I just had this dream
Over Dover gets looking back at
2003's saying that is based on analysis
Episode
100%
Strangely conclusive proof that maybe he wasn't lying in the Press
I was like in the past
Okay I'm coming clean on this
No matter what I do it's pasted alive
Yeah I don't know
Quicksilver
Did you ever notice how a narcissist
As time goes on like
The people in their story send
To disappear and it's just
Them
You know that Gary Hart just disappears into the past
Don't worry. To worry in the present-day was all me and God literally everything it was
Going to happen so spectacular
He gets handjobs from the Arcana
Angel Michael yeah
So we have this in
Interesting dynamic
Back in the past
Alex is still trying to
Pretending the left and the right of the same
Kind of game
To get into that a little bit and I
I think it's a little silly
Okay
Sounds like the past
I do like
We can kind of boil it down to the conversation is still between Liberty and tyranny
You're just pretending that the right doesn't associate with tiridates
That's kind of your problem here
You guys just ride to Institute a theocracy
I think we know what the left-right Paradigm is Liberty versus freedom
It's a little it's a little bit strange
Yeah
I would say that the superficial
Analysis at bat
Love you
The way he's trying to do
Take the left and the right has the same
Is essentially meaningless
I don't know I don't know
I don't know what how he knows what they were teaching at universities 100 years ago
I would say that he is not somebody I would take
As a as a credible Source on that
Sure
Assessment
Care too much of
Simplistic
Left-wing government that have eroded ended
Dictatorships and right-wing governments have also wrote it.
Dictatorship
Play some superficial similarities
Between them that doesn't mean that they're all.
Policy wonk
You think that he would bring up specific things
That they agree
Do superficial things like those big jails in
People in by police in black black uniform
To keep us in mind typically speaker
Someone is trying to tell you what there is no difference between X and Y
There's a really good chance
Exeter super on the side of X or why they're usually not in the middle or no
Neutral extremist for x or y
Usually they go from
There's nothing between me there's no difference between X or Y
I know they put
She strongly towards X or Y
It does seem like that is about
So Alex is trying to make this point they're like the last
In the writer the same
Blah blah blah
Fascism and communism
Same thing
And here is how Alex
Makes that argue
Nazi operations
No help at all
So Alex is really bad at his job
Pink lips like this
Yeah I mean by Prescott Bush
Almost all the Nazi operations globally
Did he run the cloning program and Brazil to totally okay good
If you pay attention to that clip
Do you see one of the ways that Alex
Flies
You take something that is true mainly the Prescott Bush did indirect business with the Nazis and embellishes it and
Completely insane way like claiming he ran almost all their operations globally
The assertion that Alex is making his nonsense
He's saying the Prescott Bush profiteer by trading with fascist and that other Rich families of profiteer by trading with communist
This must be the same
Same thing it means
Nothing is a silly Ark
No difference
The argument that fascism and communism are the same because Alex believe them both to be
Commanded
Control Sim
System
Equally meaning
Alex threw out that term a lot but it really is just a military term that the Joint Chiefs of Staff defines us
Quote command-and-control is the exercise of authority and Direction by a properly designated Commander over assigned forces
Anacapa
Schmidt definition
The term has a broader understanding outside of strip
Strictly military
Situations to me
Someone direct other people to get a task
Done seem very self-explanatory whenever you just
Think of words
Concealed how they mean thing
If this is a big
Similarity that Alex has the teeth
Thanks makes communism and fascism the same
Have a short list of other things that also must be the same as the Nazis
School
Any job where you have a boss
Troop Hospital
A form of acting where there's a director
Every country in the world
That last one
My focus on what he thinks is the only relevant factor in these two systems Alex is actually
Obscuring the much more real and much more important difference
Between them
I think what Alex is trying to
Expresses the communist countries have what's known as a command economy
Where the government decides what should be produced
And how much as opposed
Letting go
This is a defining aspect of Communism as an economic system
The problem is when you try to juxtapose that with fascism
Isn't an economic system
Don't know if you look at the fascist countries during WWII for example you can see massive differences in the economic models
Employed
What Alex is trying to
Expresses the communism by definition involves a command economy
And that the Nazis also had a fairly
We command base
Economy
The differences that within communism is an element of the economic ideology
But in the case of group like Nazis
It was just used because it was necessary to run an economy Olmos
Entirely based on War
We did the same thing.
World War II
Yeah it was alright was great idea
Workout for everybody involved face is not a meaningful substantiv connection
Between these two things
I'm really like I was listening to this episode I was trying to give
Alex Affair reading
Ride it
Just what are you saying doesn't
No I mean based on his definition of
Command and control
Fundamental idea of laws
Because that is a designated body telling you what you can or cannot do
Like that simply cannot exist
Austin Hays
Concept I think if you went
Too far with it yeah you probably
Get to that that argument
I think I
I could get him to that
Oh and other thing that's
Commander control
Judges
You're right all law should be abolished okay Alex that was
Mypoints
But fair enough
Socialism
Always leads
Fascism
The more accurate
Call work
But this conversation
Probably impossible to have cuz I don't think Alex is using any of the
These terms in the way that anyone else would
Is it completely made up claim that I was paddling they can't backup at all unless he uses completely absurd definitions of the word so
Socialism and fascism
I think anybody would agree with him whatever it is he doesn't like
And if you can Define it as something
From that he will tell you that that's
The secret way they talk about it
Cover up that what they actually mean it
Sure
Alex
One of the big breaking point in his career 10 times the
That communism is
Half Baked like one of the most
Argued about in
Books over and over and over again
Refined and reinterpreted things
Is half
F****** babes like
Karl Marx beta 3 3/4 of Das kapital it was like
That'll do
Like I tried I'll put it out there and everybody else can finish the last
45 different between I disagree with this Attitash picked
Satisfactory that's alright
The beat that dead horse real
I say
May
Nope
Alex girl broke into Bohemian Grove right story
Nobody's around
And
Now that we're in the future
He did it completely by
Itself no other journalists their whatsoever who were also documenting this
Tilex in the present-day would like to say that he was going to pay the first person to ever break the story wide open but it.
How you'd read about it in the mainstream British media
Him to do the story not think of this by himself whatsoever hear you're a weirdo
Never do it from the British media these are some of these little differences
Past version
The stories in prison
Seems like things change
Sure but something that doesn't is weird
Alex has a herb store or like
Like a
I don't know I guess they have some colloidal silver and shower
Sure they sell videos he's running an ad for
And it ended in a way that shock
Sign up on the website
Exceptional products
Is natural alternatives in education
Christian identity herbal shop
Oh no
Catalog also we've defeated
If you call this number we will be able to send you this Cadillac what you shouldn't have thrown this
What did you just say yeah yeah yeah
That's a that's interesting
Code to be in this commercial
Play Spotify
Maybe Alex was
Why would you have that as a
The sponsor
If you if they weren't like
Like a Christian identity
I type of herbal shop
Natural place recipe
Very weird
I can't get over the idea of like Kellogg's just
Cornflakes Thousand-Year War almost ended
And if you want more Kellogg's Cornflake we will defeat
My lucky charm it is strange
Tough time with the Iraq War and all this
Because he hates the people who are doing it sure
David David George Bush
Not really and all that
And I think
Value free talking a little bit too much I think that Alex reveal certain ways in which
His ideology is in
Consistent with what he wants the audio
Dance to believe it is
So Alex seems like he's
Fine with the idea of colonialism
They're installing democracies apartheid
Sure only in the case
The government was
Doing the things that he doesn't like
So I guess it's a position can't possibly be to meddling in the Affairs of other country
For regime change in nation-building
Write something to eat hypothetically okay with but he will pretend that he's not
Yeah
I would be interested to know what Washington would consider a hemisphere is argue Alex's argument again
Iraq War
Seems to be
Vaccine
It doesn't it does not sensible
No no no it doesn't
People like he's like a
Hey
We should be colonizing
Central South America is what we did no other hemispheres watch
No I think he's saying that if our country was run the way I want
Tattoo
Yeah we could go ahead and put into my procedure on the Worldstar
I just don't like these people
It's a it's an incoherent silly ideology that problems really fat
Yeah it is to buy Greenland Trump is in office
Phuc yea it's
It's that kind of nonsense if I call that is kind of what you believe is long as it's
As long as it's your idealized
Christian
Authoritarian government
Government with all kinds
The colonial expansion everything's one hemisphere don't care at all about the idea of
Freedom
Termination
Yeah
It is like okay I get that we both
Don't want the Iraq War but I don't want it because
Millions
The people are going to be slaughtered
For no reason and you don't want it be
Because you don't like the guy
I don't think we necessarily agree.
I don't think that's a good
It's very sense
It makes sense
This is kind of how I'm not if I'm not ascend
Ended by this necessarily sure advertising
His product
Which are like his DVDs and
Make sense
To be like there's more information
On this
Makes more sense than him
Constantly throwing
2 pill commercials
At least they're still hypothetical in
Information
To be found here although I think
So I just documentaries he proved that the globalist
Scary dolls 911
911 I don't recall that
But do you recall when he did that interview a couple years back
With Patrick bet-david
And Patrick bet-david ask him
Who did 9/11
Who was really behind the 9/11 would what's your studies over the years
And Woodruff
I don't know
Oh are we using watch your DVDs then you should watch the the proof
You make
It seems like you would stick to
To the proof
I would say that maybe
Maybe you were wrong
Have you didn't prove it
Okay my documentaries going to approve everything
World war is coming there.
Now I mean obviously the capital gains tax
Should be about 45
50%
Temperature in there
It's it's fun
Forget that he proved who did 9/11
Seems like a big thing to remember
Oh well
Palace Casino
I think I've watched those DVDs and I don't think I know either
His proof
In quotes yeah I would like
Redacted page
This is what I
Here's our first indication of
Something not being quite right
In in Austin
Sure
Alex is going out to break
Okay there
The forces of Satan
Could pull that off as being like look at him he's making that exaggeration come on we've all used
Flowery language
And it's going out to break
Pump up cardigan
It sounds like a reasonable thing that you would say if you were just pumped up but it also does feel like this is a little bit more than I
I've been
Giving a pass
Edgewater
Icon fighting against
The forces of Satan
He's not
As literally
Saying that as part of
A 15-minute Ranch you're sure
It is just going out to break but it made me worry
It could be hyperbole of course of course however
You can't miss the forest
It's for the trees if you will Dan VA
So Alex Goes to calls
Like I think I brought this up before but there's such a sensible formula to his show at the
This point and that is he'll rant about something
For a little while
And then go to calls
And then maybe the caller says something that he can talk about for a little bit longer he'll read a headline or two then go to a car
Call get maybe a reaction
Revival lead into a rant there is just a fluidity to it that makes sense
Where is Maui
Such
F****** long jumper cables
Lowe's
Much easier
Answer this call her that Alex goes through
Displaying the show brings up Rush Limbaugh
What do you think Alex
But Rush Limbaugh giving him something to steal
Play driving in my car and
Turn on
Rushlight
Carolina
He was talking about
No
So kindly rushlimbaugh.com
The communitarian Rush Limbaugh
Yes Note 4 left
Call me
Leftists
Rush Limbaugh
Right standing next to Bill Maher's
Is people who are left
Beyond all reason
You get this sentence like okay here's where the denial of the left-right Paradigm is
Just take a hit at
Somebody on the right and then you're good
And it doesn't have to be a substantial hit you
Stuck as a real dick
Hey I'm above the left-right paradigm
So Alex bring up
The going to the World's Fair in
The 70s
Shoemaker
Might have seen some like
Russian propaganda about ecological efforts
Okay I don't know I don't know what
What's going on anymore
Talking about
Propaganda
Before I went to the World's Fair
Farwest
Ecology
The worst
Again.
The Russian
World's Fair
Through the Russian exhibits
Good morning
Pollutants
Queen
Exactly
But now we're turning into the
A system
Before in the world
What did you just say
Family
Are the federal
Enemy combatant
Sure
I think isn't
I pulled it out was because
This caller is it
Expressing his idea that they saw this Russian.
Display
74 worlds
I wanted things
He brings up his like there's no pollution
How do you flash forward to the present day in Alex Tucker
Think about how coal power plants are all totally clean perfectly
Interesting to see Alex
Becoming this thing that this caller is describing
This horrendous Act of propaganda elected members in 2003
Just
Don't Alex Alex's
Sweetly delusional about
Accepting
And recognizing and dealing with
The History of the United States
He's even worse
Then probably whatever that Soviet Union
Russian
Display was
Yeah that is that is one of those
Things about fashion
It says that
What's your in the vinpower
All of the
The past is changed to whatever you want
You know
If you're as long as
Trump is running the United States government
The United States has never ever done anything wrong in saying so is an attempt to undermine Trump
Oh you're going to bring up slavery again the exuberance
Exactly yeah you're screwed up our good time we're trying to slaughter Innocents in your really make
Canis bummed out
So hey we got this idea
That
Left right
Same thing
Last two
Clinton
Bush no
Prince there
Puppets
Sure are they equally respond
Constable Papas
Borscht
Enjoyed all of it
Beer we got these two presidents who were both Papa
Right
The Last Samurai
She would somehow still the one that's on the left
Pinocchio situation
Clinton is when Pinocchio was turned into a donkey for a while
MW is still the
The puppet but he's not yet a real boy
Sure then Trump is a real book
It's just a remarkable to to look at this and be like Oh yeah this is this
The active
The left or the right of the same is so thin
Almost anytime there's a comparison
Between someone who's on the left
Authorities on the right
You can see like
Some sort of derision towards
Is way worse Alia inclusion is what makes
The bush
Ee gave a warning
Sure I'm to the US's
Supposed enemies
And
Text believe that these are actually the global
And here
We get another
Wonderful prediction
So this is one of the problems with
Relying on quote-unquote CSR moments that that sort of thing as being
Addictive of what's going to happen the world
Alright something like we're worried about smallpox cases in American city
And you read that as
There's going to be
To justify Another War
You're just making s*** up
And that's what we see here
There's
It's the most powerful
Type of making
King s*** up proper
Again. We're in somebody trying to
Protect you from a thing that happened
You have turned into the person trying
You caused this
Thing that's happening
Ensuring that the thing they're worried about almost certainly will happen
And then you get to b**** about how they didn't see it coming
And then you know
Do you have these kinds of instances of things
Litter Alex
His career
They just things
Is never happened
Totally talking out of his ass
Of his career
Well the last time I visited Denver there were about four people there after
To the smallpox epidemic
Destroyed most
To the city
Sure but they were really cool to hang out
There's only Lone Survivor
They did try and eat my leg
Another caller
This guy's got an interesting I'd
Terrible Alex has to end the conversation by saying
I don't speculate
Real estate
Headlight did I don't know if
Department
Not yet
In the head while back while I was sick find out a little glass
Speedway
Coincidence
Little girl
Kidnapped
And just so happy
Your last name is
Smart
In fact
If there's a smart
Her parents
A parent's assigned Amber Alert
And
Wow
Hey listen I'm going to take wild and speculate on that
But listen
I'm going to Rattle off things that are
To give Justice
Application to speculation behind I do not speculate
Whether or not the Alyssa
Smart kidnapping was an elaborate globalist
Obviously that plan is
Play could do it at any point we were told they were going to be silicon chips
Have Amber exactly
Fine art
Jeff fine
Fine
I think that's
That's the type of theory if somebody comes at you with you just have to roll up a newspaper and be like no
Bad
I I think that I would love
To just like I
God
My dream job at
Infowars just
Changing
I want a clip of Alex and I don't
Speculate speculate
Stop it it's just a repeat until the speculation
So 9/11 was
Proven
By Alex to have been people he can't remember who they are though
But
There's some sign
Tell tale sign
How you know
That
The man was
Behind door
What
Zero's went on
9/11 New York Lottery
Call 911 one year anniversary
So I'm not sure I believe this
Urban legends
Kind of situation does
According to the CME website does the name of the Chicago Mercantile Exchange when there is no listed as publicly traded
CME Group
They didn't go public until
December 5th 2002 when they had their initial public offering
Stock price
Persei me on September 11th 2002 Sunday weather
That was a real sneaky move by the globalist, I don't know what you
Referring they really nailed it
I don't I don't I don't know I
I think you might have seen a meme or something level of b*******
Did you see that George W bush has been complimenting people a lot lately
Another word for that is
Lauding
He's been doing it repeatedly over time so
You could say he's
Bin
Laden
What is that mean we nailed in something
So people have looked into the lottery thing and that one actually is
It's true but it doesn't actually mean
The state lottery in New York does
I think they pick to pick
Three winners
Each day
The numbers
Any 3 digit combination coming up his one and thousand
Because there were two drawings the odds of 911 hitting on any given day are 1 in 500 which really
Interesting coincidence but it's far from proof that the globalist
Did it to show that they
They control lotto numbers
It's it's fun but you might as well use that as also like
Oh I had
To call 911 that day it's a miracle yeah it's just weird how much of Alex is supposed
Proof of things relies on like June
Just denying the
Yeah well they don't
It's a little it's a little annoying
A real way to argue that
You can be like well the statistical odds of that coming up are not really that insane and
Don't know what you're talking about with the Merc
Alright go off
How do I I was just talking to this caller and they got into it and argue
Call her in that someone in
Their life
Because
Didn't agree on
The Federal Reserve
Well who can
Interesting theory about what
What's going on there
Boring conversation
Your income tax money go to the ins
Federal Reserve
I want to show for it
Pappadeaux
Don't you
Whataburger
So I guess you anybody
To talk to
I guess anyone argue with an indication that you're right now
You're wrong just laugh at you
No it's all God
Yeah this guy
He was told
By someone
12 just believe the news
That's not what this person
Responsibilities Sotelo
So I don't believe that this caller is reporting things accurately that is friend
Just said
Watch the news and believe it
Going to let's let's imagine that that's actually someone's
That is crippling level of naivete and lack of critical thinking that you're approaching
Information that
And I would
Opposed
To what this
Yeah supposed person set
You know what I would even argue that I would be above the left right
Paradigm in saying that that is a bad way of
Consuming media
No Alex has
Couple of options
In terms of addressing
The situation
You could say something like that like a
Your friend should engage more critically with the information like Avenue and you should as well
He could have blanket Defiance I think that would be a better way to go is just as stupid
I think it's just a stupid tumbok the idea of ever listening to the news or be like
It's not determinate
It's it's not too it's
It's a pendulum swinging too far the other directions
Yeah it doesn't matter how you get to
Consume whatever it is uncritically whether it be
Eating it or denying
Yeah weather in whether it's
Cnnr WorldNetDaily
My girl
You want you want
He wants
Them two
Except WorldNetDaily uncritically
And hostility towards
Things that are saying the outer anybody else
Nazi
Germany there
Sure
It's a bad path
And I would I would say that he's not setting
Bring up his list
It's a strategy that won't get you
Into a better engagement with information
And it'll just make you
Believe something out loud by something else
To your information source
Yep and then you'll be like
I should give him money because he
He's saving me from the rest of the evil media and all the sudden start believing that
Is the messiah
Actually fighting the literal Den Miami he will believe that
Control
I'm so Alex
Is is right about something
This
In this episode
He is right
That
Stupid
The people say that they would die for
I think that is
Call warbler
Mike walked up I wasn't there
Georgia
Into a time machine with me Jordan come to the presents
Megaplex
Cachet
If you don't
Come out
Going to blow your brains out I'd say pull the trigger
Yeah also I love how
This man was
Threatening my cameraman
Curse words and he said that he would hurt me physically
Family Show
Davina.
God
So Alex has another caller
This guy he had a similar vibe to me as that
Is 8 a.m. in China to have to get up I got to drive to work
McConaughey
Coronavirus
The same Vibe with the AAA this was a caller who like
Like Isaac you talk some more
Then the same way
Alex a good day
How you doing Jeanette Hansen this morning on the peacock Channel
I love it
Are you man is great
I just imagined that guy writing that out blinds on hold
Pops into mine
That's that
Well-practiced
That's either a mirror or a thing you have said to a lot of people to board
Yeah I wish is called as more interesting but I did
Enjoy that
So Alex
It's two talkin about story that his cousin
I don't know if this is Buckley
I don't think it is
Sakura bnha
Yeah it must be another cousin
Unfortunately
All
Well you'll see
Okay
The Border
18 years later
Right military isn't all chip
AR all
But I was right about
Every single military member is
Upon
Haha you know those guys the recruiters at your high school
Every time you shake their hand they are implanting you with
Computer to have one of those little assassin's blade exactly
Get it in there like haha was not a funny joke
And then I stare deep into your eyes
Can program you write write you out of your trance flower on their lapels quirky with water
That's how you wake up slip on a banana peel walking away from you
What is getting chipped
Still waiting on this one too
Come around
Discolor
Has verified our two-story because
Because they have also heard
That
The military print out there
World leader
Yes I see it exactly
Interactive
Improvisational storytelling like
I was just coming up with a story for them to get excited about on this day
Sister scripting this stuff so that's how I can predict
Naturally
Okay
Anti chip
Here's what's interest
I think I would be opposed to mandatory
Oh yeah I haven't given it enough
To really heavy
Strong position on it website
Whatever Direction I would fall on it
Aspergillus
Thought
I have a pretty cool hand
Yeah I would I would want
Cupola
Assurances up like
First Quest
Are you going to mind control
Rack Attack
What else would I ask even if it's nice
But I got to look
Ebony Eyes
Sure mind control
Exactly what I don't mind control
Electroshocks no good
No I think I'd be fine with a little electroshock here in there you know but as long as it's not somebody doing something to doing
4weird Ruiz
I think you're going to have to really litigate what's weird
Well I guess we're going to sit here we're going to talk about it but I'll look him in their evil eyes
Episode can be going over the conditions under which you would approve of Chip
Play what all heaven
Full release
Dorkness out
For Alex
He's supposed to be
We totally agree
Mark of Beast
Unfortunately he is inconsistent as hell
What group
Wait till but why would
Special Forces getting a few setting a precedent control Special Forces
But you understand this is silly
Staunchly opposed to giving microchips to people in the military and molasses
Green Berets have computer chip
I don't understand why
I don't get what the relevant differences
Between people in Special Forces
If the argument is that I was just trying to make which is playing
Is it Savannah become something that goes to
The citizenry
Now
You could just take one step further be like I give it to special forces that normalizes it for the military at Northland for the slippery
Only work if you start where I save a stop
It doesn't make sense
Just cuz we're starting in the middle of the slippery slope meeting that we've already had to go
From somewhere to get here is pretty dumb
So a 2000
3 with a very different time
Anti-vax
Destination community
No wasn't no I didn't
Thanks it wasn't great then either
So some of these ideas
About
Autism
With vaccination
And like Mercury the preservatives
Less
Uniform
In the anti-vax
Community had a lot of the other let's say maybe
Even
Stupider ideas shot down
Right was this
Jenny McCarthy was
This is
After she had coming up positive about her timeline
Yeah I don't know that either I'm not sure but I do know that at this point
There are
Anti-vax
Proponent
Yahoo are making the argument that mercury
In the preservatives
Is
Has a link
To auto
Now
Point
Alex
Doesn't think
He's trying to steak
The Clement something weirder
Okay
Not standby today I don't think
Resigned
Brain development hormones
Alex doesn't say what this hormone is and I'm not sure not going to go on a wild goose chase and then just assume that I found
Whatever he's talking about we'll talk about it
Greater depth
The argument is being put forth to him but there is Mercury
This is
That is pretty close to his current position
On anti-vax
Destination
Safe territory for him now
But back then
He didn't have that he wanted another he wanted his own version
Jump it up wasn't just a Mercury
It's a naturally occurring elements
You can drink gallons of that
Know what it is
Is they grow
Hormones
In labs
For brains
Incident put in there
And that's what does
Yeah I think that's interesting I would like to know what he feels about this now that would be still believes there's some weirdo
Actually behind
If you'd like to interview some of his weird
Text friends about that
Interesting place nearby that nonsense
Get the caller this was this made me so happy
God dammit
Make me happy
Young man household was arranged this caller is the same person who
You called and Alex argue with him about the Republic
Look up Texas
Alex
Is clearly annoyed with this guy really
Get a bike
He doesn't become a
Clear
Did Alex knows who he's talking to until the end of this collab
Atlanta weather
This is great this is just so good
Later on
Crap goes down
Will meet these people on our side
Took this real quick as a as an introduction this caller has said that he
He took one of Alex's films
Do the Aspen Sheriff
Department any woke up the sheriff
Okay and everybody on the
Before Center like now
It really does sound like it
Doesn't it
Feels like that's how they get
Good2Go
Beginning of this called
Constitutionalist
The New World Order
Hardly agree with you
Republican
The Rocky Mountains
Colorado
Robbie chronic Colorado
Okay Alec
He did
I like the red that's going through these episodes that I'm getting to a driver Alex's
Pissed off by Republic of Tea
Texas people
It is nice
I do appreciate that
Because he has this whole thing is like
Texas has its own country
Secede
What is a country and it involves
A bunch of place to the north we got most New Mexico
Colorado
I don't appreciate how that Community is still allowed to have
People that are too far out there
Y'all are crazy
Don't don't
Judge them for being like
And also the Northwest Territory is ours to
You are mad because
Your ideas look
Just as ridiculous
This is theirs and theirs make you
Feel
Yeah yeah they think that is a part of it
Something that I really enjoy
Alex's ability to sort of play with
The guy
Back. That's true
Alex could not do that now
Texas or Aspen Colorado
Doubling down on Micah hey man
I just
Just go ahead and say exactly what you and I both know you're about
To say I recognize your voice
I'm going to ask you this question
Aspen as I know I've heard name of Aspen before is that a city in Colorado
Texas
So we get another caller
And this fella is really
Lauding
Alex and Kim
About opposition
Into the Patriot Act
And so there is a there been some places
That have passed resolution
In some cities
City councils and what-have-you
If you listen closely to this clip though
Color is congratulating Alex for doing something that he
He himself
Is literally saying was done
Buy communist
Democratic primary sponsor
EPA were talking about rushing waters
Standard would think it was a city
Call me a city government to support the Constitution of United States
Goodnight cute
You calling these people
Who wrote the Revolutions in the communist government
Pastor
But somehow Alex is responsible for this
It's outrageous
This is
This is kind of amazing
That's that's
You know what
I get it
Every time something good
Because of the
Left ideas but you can't
Allow the work that's done by actual activists
Primarily on the left
It's sometimes yelled about
And taking credit for by people who yell
Like Alex
I mean like that's all he does
You just yelled something because
Popular
Oh man is social security Medicare we can't let that stuff out of naturally
When it was being passed we would have called it a communist
Landgraabs trying to kill us all and steal our money but now that it
Has no we have it in the worst wow it's our favorite program
If there is a phenomenon
The end of this episode gets a little bit into his own head
And
Is
Talk in a bit about how like
People asking why he's not dead
Shoreline the globalist
Sure I would have you
You talked about being ready to die
For freedom
It's remarkable how that's almost
Exactly mirrored by
If someone had a gun to my head and told me to denounce
What's trumps
I'd say pull the trigger
Freedom
God
Family
Hellboy
Kind of depressing
Super depressed
31 Westcliff Jordan
And it was clip
Alex is in a bit of a rant
About
Being alive
Right
He had felt
Suppose that I will accept that as a
This is getting a little bit
Bit closer to that territory of
Religiosity
That we might be
Keeping her finger on the pulse
Okay
I'm sorry
Can your heart
There is not even a question
When you go this player
New World Order
Things that I always loved the idea that to Alex
Like I no longer feel human emotion I no longer drawing
The bad witch other Mortal man now
Because the fight won the globalist is so strong in the New World Order
I found
That clip to be really on the line
Argument
You can still be made that a lot of that is
You know it's
Kind of
Christian is
Yeah I know God's in your heart is on the 700 Club
Sure that doesn't that's not as a
Stream is certainly a lot of
Sure Maurice
Sunday is right when he says that you're up against Pure Evil
I could still be metaphorical flourish or as opposed to what we know he believes now which is
Literal demons invading people
Yeah yeah that is true
I do I do think that should come out
Much sooner in a conversation and should be something that you have
Have to leave it like if
If you're doing Alex's show
You should have to lead with like
I believe that our political enemies are literally controlled by the devil like everyday
Yeah just like if when I meet somebody there like
You should have to
To tell me if you believe this
The biblical flood story is 100% true
Okay fine then you don't get an opinion on back
You don't like it
Get it out of the way
So we can move forward I don't
Need to know anything else about you
How do you say I think it's more like a situation where
If
If you're going to like
Let's say
Start dating somebody
Or whatever and they don't tell you that they think the Earth is flat
So where are you at
Irresponsible
I think that Alex
As a person who's conveying in
Information
I think it is it is relevant if you believe that the devil is behind the
Gears of your enemies
I think you should be
Upfront because it gives people the ability
E2
Consider that in the totality of the information you're presented more seriously
I honestly
Quite tell you
Yeah
No I agree
There's more indications than I was expecting
Yeah it's probably not coincidental that like this
God is real God is there right isn't he
I think that he would leave the episode with it
The stalwarts
Skateboard
For him if you have a disclaimer for like a video game
Trailer that's like
Some scenes are not actual gameplay
You should at least have to have a disclaimer for like
Also believes that the devil is real you know like that should be there
Bumper is coming in from break or like
You know like do you want to fight corruption well soon as he's like
That's not what this is about
Do you believe that you're a crusader against the literal Christian
Devil
That's a good show okay okay alright well then now we get it
Do you think the demons jump into people and make them go black
Yes I do sir I will listen Otis app
There we go
Yeah
It's an interesting
Interesting
Progression
And I'm fascinated by this and so much more
Cinebowl
In the past like a totally
Totally
Absolutely callers are weirdos in a fun way
Is not a show that is just a man unraveling really fun and creates comedic tension in
Mike Fraser
Is that some of the colors are annoying today
I know what you're going to get
Yes
Keep solenoid that's so funny
It did yeah enjoy that
Adele
I hope every episode I listen to you gets into a fight
With somebody who believes
Just slightly the wrong
Yeah
Man it's so ridiculous
That you think that the Magna
Carter is still the law of the land
Unless you're in capital letters and it's
It's Corporation
Spell obviously
The literal Christian devil is sending demons into
People's brains
To control their Acts
Sure
Anyway
Learn this has been an episode
Indeed
We will be back
Checking in on the bread
I believe our next episode
We are what we do have a website
It's knowledge
Fight.com we are on Twitter than it is at knowledge underscore fight
Go to
Too bad George
We are on face
Facebook if you would like to
To download the show
Please go to please find a local charity or bail Fund in your area to help out people
Until then I'm Neo and Leo on dzx Clark
Horned owl
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color