Important
I have great respect for knowledge B B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Everybody was making a little bit about Alex Jones
Scratch that like to sit around
Worship at the altar of Celine and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Jordan
What's up
I got a quick question
Who's the deity worship and to
My bright spot
I feel like look
I took a lot of beating
From people about this whole doors
I do look where is where is straight-up Alex and territory where you immediately started with
Look at look assholes took a lot of pummeling over that perhaps
I've decided to open myself up to even more criticism
Walking down the street the other day and I got it in my head that I was like
I haven't listened to Methods of Mayhem in a long time
I do did I happen to remember that that exist
Long time
And let me see how does it hold up bro I listen to three songs
There was like a shelf it was nice I like it I like it when I was younger I did not
Kid Rock Beer
So I listen to the Kid Rock song
News
Not good
Also it seems like
The theme to The the song
That is supposed to be about like a noob
Beginning it in like sort of like finding a new piece sure he's famous for metaphor and not get the memo
Universe has nothing to do with this
Listen to was getting naked
And that song is embarrassed
I do here that's your response but it's more embarrassing even then that like what you're how you're responding
You would still be like
Oh my God
No plans
It's gross
Weird
Find somebody who's all kind of Ian sex positive I think everybody
Is that how creepy no no that would be
Current kind of embarrassing uncomfortable
Now is just rude
There's a song on there called a proposition
F*** you
I think that one was actually that actually holds up
Black Blade prop 21 one of the boys in blue running up on crew you know what to do
Alright well
Now I understand
That you previously you said that this song
Was good
I think it holds up and then you just said we a little bit of
Haha
Strongly
Two different icy I feel like it's I'm sure it wasn't intended as
Satire of
Of political outrage
Expression of like
Some kind of I don't know if
There wasn't a greater statement other than f*** you whenever we were off for three Graves
It's the machine
It works on that level
Methods of Mayhem
Well I have a hard time
With this as my bright spot because it is going to be unrevealed but
I have completed a new
Oh Great Gatsby Arapahoe time.
Will be a s******* with Tommy Lee
And yeah I'm very excited about it it's it's a whole new thing for me it's something that I've wanted to try
Driver long time and I finally stepped down
I'm excited about this project as well
Now that I know that you're also involve more work
This will be almost a complete reversal of Fortune.
Little bit for the listeners inasmuch as it is like a
Huge huge teeth layoffs will be great I hope so
Bright spots
Score
Do today Jordan wear back in the present we talked about April 26th
2021 B
Be first I think you said to work faster
I wanted to do for this episode was
But I got kind of caught up in some of the Alex stuff
At the beginning of the week
Sure and I didn't want to get mixed up with the
Giuliani got raided
Kind of news of the end of the week or I thought like it would all be too much to cover in one
So the end of the week will cover on Monday again we're going to cover today
Breaking news
Tomorrow
Good today
Usher
Hello's doesn't
One avocado
Text drop cuz I tooted
Here's the first
And now here comes
Robot
I have a question. Does this involve also the
Alex with gun
It's because if you combine the two
You're inside your Unstoppable now I was thinking about introducing
I don't know how to pronounce
Village
View whatever you want shunli happy birthday was on the 29th
Shout out
Non-binary twin
An apostrophe on their eye
Use myself reading
She has nightmares of Alex Jones voice because I listen to your podcast too much
Thank you very much and as always
Let's remind you that if you are listening too much we are fine with you taking a break.
We got will and thank you so much you are now.
Technocrat Preston l
Bob the human animal chimera
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
Thank you all
Thank you very much to the three of you on episode
Right after we finished recording I got an email
Of course I got an email from Ashley
To give birthday shout out
Do item
Okay was on Tuesdays birthday was able to do
Like sheep we can't do that
It's not your fault so now in the past Matthew I know your birthday was on
Tuesday but I hope you had a good one hope you had a great one
I hope things are going great and
You got to know how old Matthew is before I open
27 I hope he had an okay birthday
I'm just hoping for an okay brownie 727 down birthday
Got a younger one on the way coming soon
Quaker sneakers dropping
Guys got a birthday new baby drop
BabyFirst
Listen to Eddie Tommy Lee albums
Now or in the future or otherwise
I hate to say it but
I mean
Do you want a basic political identity on proposition f*** you maybe there's something to it
Alside with y'all
So happy birthday
To you
Jordan
I've contact.for Here Today Show
I know major Cattleman I served under Baker Fatima
Could you sir
Alright
Here is the beginning Alex opening up
The show here on April 26th
And it is a bummer
Saturday and Sunday
Myself on the computer
Facing our neighbors dad
Species on this planet
Information
And here's the
Equation
If we don't have a
Total away
They call a post-human world
Then we don't have any shot
Understand the process of industrialization
It's in the process of modernization
Boise
Ignorant
Okay Unabomber.
Each generation going forward
Obvious is less human
Let me tell you about
The force of modernity has Nigeria saleski
Each generation Subs
Squint believe will be less because of
Computers unsurprisingly
Alex is that guy at a party
Listen imma look
I'm not saying that the Unabomber was good
But if you've read his Manifesto I'm not saying he was wrong
He's got some stuff to say
You got to be smart to do that that guy at a party is a bummer that guy not
At a party also about
What's the
Let's remind ourselves
Movies about a weird mood
Unabomber is a weird mood yeah
We heard on our present-day episode Bill Maher
It was quite a shift
Purple
He really got
An upgrade from
Ventriloquist dummy with the globalist
Basically Tucker Carlson
Here's the other reason that I know for a fact
Alex is a huge fan of Star Wars
Retconning is his mate raison d'etre
A name anyways the man apps
Absolutely refuses to stick to Canon
Yeah that is true it's especially when things are
Repeat in my world
I have better news
We are back
To Bill Maher being off
I got the point
Where I can't watch
A CNN P3 would have Bill Maher piece or any of these
Propaganda pieces because I see the riding that's involved in it
I see the multi-layered
Deceptions that are involved the level of
Panda
I've gotten even more sophisticated
These are very skilled
Very distraught
People doing this today there's something
Run for Bill Barr
Almost less than an hour
Work so stupid
What's that's good news
That's good news
Dalton
Being man
Alright
But I can't watch it
Because the secret Patriot is to seek
In the circumstances
Yeah or maybe you just talk
You said the other day when he's like I've heard from the higher-ups kind of like Tucker he's a good guy
There's good news in the world
Amidst Alex's inability to watch news anywhere sure
Yeah there's also a lot of positive things
Weis
Igor reaction
But I
I really don't know
Risen above
Miami
Disgusted by I'm a lawyer just like them
Defeat them
So that I can be the top dog if you'll be above them
In this pile of skulls a sentence
Long time ago
Spirit entered by
Body
But now I really transcended oboy
Oh boy so the good news is that Alex has transcended his enemies over at did transcend them when he was a baby
So we're on the same path is like David Lynch
Now we're into Transit
What you need to do is trans
Okay
Ye shall
I was like this is a this is a mood
News
To delusions of grandeur
There's something they're interesting way to start
Show ended now
That's nice
We have to really transcend
Work for you
Still
Resistance
And still say no to it
But not even give it energy when we do it
These are like sad mad dogs with rabies
Foaming at the mouth
And you know they're already got
Done for it
So you need to just
I guess that means communes
Is that what he's trying to say
Let's visit the world in the globalists and all the Minions are all
What are mad dogs out there you just got to keep him away from biting
Your children and stay away from
The Gutter Guy is their own
Sure he'll mess or whatever
So yeah,
I don't know did Alex get a phone call from Michelle Obama and she was like listen Ali
I know you've never tried this
This before
But
When they go low
We transcend
I don't I don't know it sounded like,
And I doubt there's going to be
Technology their base
His earlier statement
Seems like he's trying
To go back to pre-industrial world
Not only not only that
He's also going to shake up
And I will say that he has actually done this
Make a better show but he doesn't
I'm your host Alex Jones
Pharmacy Hewlett
Avant-garde
Transmission
Transmission up
Woodmore your calls more
Gas and more special reports and more
Live
Commercial free podcast
You have my commitment
But here in the home stretch of going into the next level
Working harder because things are
Believer
Something I never do
Storiesig
Farting
Make sure your family and others don't get it
Then I usually barely plug at the end of the hour but
Couple big guns
We won't be really shaken up the show
Broadcast surrealistic
Except that I'm not going to do I just want to let everybody know I'm going to need
You do more ad
Straight
The adverb of the broadcast
I honestly don't
I think he took any calls on this truck
Why does that not
Surprise but I wouldn't drive any of the guests as being quick
But he did go to a plug
I got that weird mood that he was in and then right
This is f***** up
Alex
It's two talking about
What's some news
And it's
Sort of what I believe is the new development and evolution of covid
Conspiracies and narratives
They're still almost completely shut down
Tens of millions extras it's a footnote have starved to death
Ian
The third world
In India
In areas of Asia the Middle East
We got those
Any virus will kill them
Antivirus
Is Alex a specific date on this he should really discuss it because you just
A references having this day too and I actually talking about it could be really illuminative
I suspect he doesn't have any actual information he's just winging it and ripping off comments that were made by David Beasley
Do you want food program executor
YouTube wrecker back
Can September
This is definitely a serious issue
This is definitely right
Call attention to but the way he calls attention to the problem
A food insecurity in the developing world doesn't deserve it
Did the idea of actually helping on
Understand
Resolve the problem
And that's because Alex doesn't care about the actual problem
He cares about using the impression that he cares about it to attack people who believe
The covid-19 is an actual problem
Food insecurity around the world is a complicated picture
You can't just say that lockdowns in the US or Europe directly leads to worst
Conditions in other countries
For instance this past year countries like Kenya Ethiopia Uganda india-pak
Pakistan and Somalia
Is an incredibly severe Locust
Swarm said it had nothing to do with Coronavirus
Or any countries response to it
Affected the world situation to make things worse but there's a larger picture than just what Alex wants to cover which is essentially
He's all the businesses we just opened back up everyone would be fine
It's really troubling to see Alex try to get into the game of pretending the covid deaths are actually starvation
Ocean deaths that are being covered up
The basic problem here is that Alex just making that up as a way for him to go
Continuous denial of this major pandemic
But even beyond that the numbers
Just don't work
Concern USA released a list of the end
2020 of the countries facing the greatest food in
Insecurities you compare that list to list of
Countries in
Aldi's
You don't come away with the
Conclusion that Alex wants you to
Chad is the country facing the most food insecurity the most severe food in
Security only been 170 deaths
From covid there
Demoralize
Is number two on the list where there been
3 covid
Madagascar is number three where there been
N600
13 deaths from covid
Haiti's number 4 with a red
Mr. 250
Before covid
Only numbers 9 and 10 on the list Afghanistan and Nigeria respectively have over a thousand deaths total
From covid recovery
Until early March
The US was seeing more covid deaths
That's per day than any of these countries have had throughout the
Fire panda
If Alex tries to redefine codesa secretly being starvation deaths
He's essentially trying to use people's deaths as a political prop for his own narrative
This behavior is nothing new to Alex but it should be recognized as
Endeavor people
Understand the disrespect
That he's operating with towards people
Humanity
Yeah you cannot
You just can't trust anybody who when you're talkin
Sing about engaging with a serious issue just goes
No we don't need to do that
What about that
Because then what's the point
Only ever going to be talk
Talking about whatever it is that you think is important
And no matter what I say it's going to change
Change based on you not wanting to engage with
With what I'm saying how are we supposed to
So this
Is primarily being deployed right now this narrative
Because there's a lot of news coming out about India
How
Take the situation
The devastation
So Alec
I wouldn't say he's doing the
India
Will you look at the end and thousands a week right now extra
Concentration camp
The common cold is killing them
And then the media tells you that covid-19 data
When India is starving to death now
Well there's a
What
Always had outdoor cremations they've always had mask
For the poor
Friends and family bonding in the other documentaries about it
Outside
What are you talkin about
What are we even doing
Just saying there about Indian deaths from malnutrition being called
His own feelings and asses about things
The situation in India with covid Israeli,
Okay. But there are number of driving factors the people
4.2 in terms of what's making the
Mr. Right now
Incredibly horrific
The first appears to be level of unprepared
Healthcare journalist
Vicis down the car Road apiece recently and sad news that
Explain this element of the situation
India's early success in nearly flattening the covid-19
18 curved in 2020 may be the cause of
The current Calamba
The spider rickety and funding starve Healthcare infrastructure
The country's ability to manage the first wave of covid-19 look Lauda balazs the United States Canada
And countries in Europe real.
Under second and third waves
The pandemic
Then things went awry
The turnaround raise false hopes
The virus had run out of steam in India and the country would be
Be spared a second
That lets people unprepared to deal with a heavy blow that was coming
Modi declared Victory and held massive political rallies
At the same time Hindu pilgrims amassed at the Ganges River where quote
As many as 2.5 million people took part
With scant attention to
Do covid-19 safety protocols
By the time an avalanche of criticism cut short the festival the virus has infected thousands of pilgrims
Who took it home to their neighborhoods in Philly
These types of massive Gatherings of people allowed for a broader spread
Nothing would have happened otherwise
Discovery of the new strain of High Park
Contagious virus in India while back in
In-house D Healthcare
Infrastructure is pushed to its situation
Like we're seeing now which is
Terrible
There's a humanitarian disaster
Are going on right now and
Dendi people of India need all the help that the international
Community camp
Provide
But trying to pretend that the dancer Dulce Georgia
Just malnutrition deaths
They're being secretly lifted
It's covid-19
Booking disrespectful to the people of India and what they're going through
There should be no greater thing
That is no greater red
Red flag than any
Right-wing reactionary politician
Declaring victory over any worldwide problem immediate sign for everybody in that country.
Snowdog
We're going to die
That's the first thing I scream whenever I hear a politician
Play mission
She at
Sissy with Alex
Is a coup
Completes need
To Justified
Who is audien
Right because it
Can't be possibly covid
No edits India's Trump
Too so we can't be right
Yeah what I fail to understand that I would love
Explain this is
What's the Indian government's motive for supposedly calling these malnutrition deaths covid
I understand that Alex thinks
The US hospitals were in a
Get rich quick
Steamer they called other desk covid cuz Medicare pays them a certain amount
Covid treatment
Does he think that's
The casein every country that does he think the doctors in Indy RC
Scamming Medicare globalist to have a profit-sharing program for this kind of scam must have
Yeah it's whatever
Really really bizarre and
When you start
Look at
What's actually being said it just doesn't make any sense and it's route
It's dark
Well I mean I suppose in his conception
Any and all
Profiting or or carpetbagging
Goes into one big
Pop for all the evil Global scams around the world so it's like
You know it all scams are fungible
Jess
That's dumb
Real dub
So anyway look there's people starving
I guess
According to
Alex all these people that have malnutrition
Shoreline
Sure and also in Venezuela
Peopleadmin
Nutrition
Venezuela
What's 1000
5 pictures of extra
It was 2,000 last number that came out resume
Thousand
People
A week
Call it starvation
Your statistician or doctor you'll be arrested
Malnutrition
They work
I would like to challenge Alex to produce any of that
Information details up
In India are being called
Shoreline
Also food
Security is a very real issue in Venezuela and again the particular contributing factors are
However it's important
Recognize how even if all of Alex's imaginary
Conspiracy was actually happening
The numbers don't make
Sense
Venezuela has recorded a total of just over 2,000
I'm covid-19 related that
Shouldn't the number be much higher if Alex
Does Duncan spiracy were real
Roughly
250,000
It's important to recognize what's going on
Alex is trying to argue the death listed as covid in India or actually just malnutrition deaths that are being mislabeled
In order to defend this baseless claim Alex points to Venezuela where they're apparently tons about attrition death
In order for Alex's argument to make any sense it would need to be the case of these malnutrition deaths in Venezuela being reclassified as covid-19
Because if that were the case
The bring of Venezuela means absolutely nothing in this
Alex's brain works from memes
Not information
When there's a story about malnutrition in the right-wing media the meme the audio
Been trained to respond to his
Bring up Venezuela
How much is no point did he's even make
Everybody knows that if he just says it's like Venezuela the listeners will just
Not in agreement with said
Unless you think
Cares I would be
Be hard-pressed to get to a point where I do but well this this will be this will vaccinate you for a vet
Impression taking Bowl
Oh look
The Indians are starving to death
Find
People outside
Why online
Bobby Brown
Wow
You know I don't hear just a such a simple
F****** go f*** yourself on
Okay if you're going to what about me with the Indians are starving and we even know age group
AA groups are saying the Indians are starving
Alright
So you're going to tell me that that's it
Issue you f******
Care about that the Republic
Party cares about
If the Republican party is in power they should at the very least
Mentioned that they care about Empower but when they are in power
Forget all this building a couple of quick clarification
One very important to recognize that right now
Alex's brand is moving away from the Republican Party
Because it does not look like a trump nominee is going to be the
The 2024 candidate that people are going to coalesce by
So I believe there's that fracture
Fracturing
Happening
And Alex is soon to be above the left-right paradigm
We'll get back to that
Who won wriggles out of this b******* whenever you want to say like complaints about the Republican party yes
Absolutely valid criticism although Alex will be deflecting that in the future
Trumpet
Party Patriot party whatever the
Until they have an official name it's going to be difficult to make these darts hit the right spot
Further notice
That's fair enough
So yeah I also like the idea that Alex is talking about real world
Presumably real world
Let me get back to what I was talking about
You know what else we got
We have some pills
So this this next Clippers is fun
This was a something that I decided to
Have a little bit of
Addicted to the bottom of
The whole lot
Sure I remember it's out reading a headline
Permanent
Infowars.com
And it links to BBC CNN
I could have told you that
Bill Gates the last year
He said it's never going to end
Applebee's
This is a Paul Joseph Watson
Sun article on Infowars
And I found this to be a great opportunity to illustrate how Infowars misleads that doesn't actually cover the news
That they're even
Pretending to
The second half of this article to Paul Road is just the standard antemasque stuff you find it pretty much any article on their website today
Do with masks
So I'm just going to ignore
All that
The actual headline is quote
Health experts
Encourage CDC to implement permanent mask mandate
This article does not lie
BBC or Sienna
In fact the entire story is based on what article from
The Providence Journal
This is an outlet from Rhode Island published in December 2020
With the headline quote
I think about life without a mask
Think against a Rhode Island experts North Korea hit those boat balance
Leaving aside the fact that this is almost
5 months old as an article in Infowars pretending it's news
If you look deeper into how the original article is misrepresented you get an even better sense
The propaganda that's being
Deployed here
The two experts at work
Consultant for this Providence
Journal article Nicole Alexander Scott
And dr. Leonard a mermaid
Neither of them at any point seemed to be encouraging the CDC to make mask wearing permanent or May
Dory
As the headline might lead you to think
You would think that's where they would be going right
Here's the part of the Infowars article the quote to dr. Alexander Scott
Quote we've seen benefits of masks
Americare Health director Nicole Alexander Scott told the property
It's Journal
So there may be a new form of normalcy wear masks
Don't necessarily have to go away
This is all good and well as that passage does appear in the actual Ark
However consider that Infowars Lee
Their first line of the story is quote
Health experts are insisting that the CDC
Should Implement permanent mask mandates even after the covid-19 pandemic end
That doesn't seem like
Alexander Scott is insisting that the CDC Implement anything
Commenting with her maybe utility ink
Continued mask-wearing
Obviously to cut down on transmission of
Annual flu
This Sensational rising of almost half a year old comments made by a Rhode Island doctor that Alex apologize Watson
Never heard of before
That's bad enough
But if you go read the actual articles there's another quote from Alexander Scott that Paul is intentionally leaving out of the article
Cuz it doesn't serve the purposes of the propaganda
She was like woah woah woah before you take me out of
Text I know Paul Joseph Watson is reading this
I can't hang
Providence Journal article
Quote
Alexandra Scott said State Health officials have much.
Consider before taking the final position on whether mask-wearing should
To continue after
Pandemic
I want to reserve the ability to research
And see what are some of the things that we've introduced because of the pandemic that are valuable to continue
She said she hopes
The public would see
See the benefits of mask-wearing if it's
Continuances recommended
Quote my help would be
My hope would be the folks would
See the value of
Continuing that you said
It's unlikely to be a definitive mandate
But we want to be driven by the data and the Sia
That's like
What if you're heartless soulless monsters corporate boss forces you to go to work regardless of whether
Or not you were feeling ill perhaps
Instead of the old way
Waze before the pan
Pandemic where you would just show up to work
Sneeze all over everything
You should try wearing a mask
Or if there's no reason for you to need to go into work
You can work remotely why not feeling well and you can be just as
Productive at home
Call any of these things are possible implications or ideas of what she
Could be talkin about seems like every work and it's important to recognize that she's very clearly talking about being driven by data and
In science
So that's clear
Do you know that
She saying that they
It could be advantageous
There's not likely to be a definitive mandate
That position
Clearly articulated in the original article is
Completely misrepresented by the Infowars article because they are liars
We're doing this for prom
The second expert in the article is Doctor marble
Here's what Paul includes
His comments in the Infowars article
And it begins with the including a mistaken reference
It's to dr. Alexander Scott as his
Stop
His sentiments were echoed by dr. Leonard a verbal medical director of epidemiology and infection
Control it Rhode Island
Who said making people wear masks all the time was worth it.
Stop the spread of viruses other than covid-19
Quote within the lifespan system we're seeing far fewer of the respiratory viruses than we are used
To seeing at this moment in the calendar year
So it's impressive the covid prevention strategies are having
An impact on other rest
Pretoria viruses
Which just makes sense they spread in a similar
It would not surprise me if that became a recommendation
From the CDC Eastside
It's a pretty low price
To pay to try to reduce the risk to oneself and particularly loved ones
Maybe it had a particular risk for these sorts of
Infections caused
Nothing harm he added
It would not surprise him if the CDC made a recommendation
Continue wearing masks
Does that justify the weed
Quote health
Experts are insisting that the CDC should Implement permanent mask mandates even after the covid-19 pandemic end
Does that justify that you didn't hear the tone of voice with which he said it
He said hey
Wouldn't surprise me if the
CDC Macy's mandatory forever because I was insisting in behind closed doors
My question about whether or not that's Justified is not
Rhetorical
It's not this is bulshit
Make it even worse as well because he also said some stuff at Paula's just conveniently ignore
From the Providence Journal article
Clue was dampened significantly in the southern hemisphere in those countries that had aggressive public
Lookout measures
To reduce covid risk such as asking
Myrtle said
The southern hemisphere Act
Timer
It's winter
And Lucy's I'm coming six months ahead of the winter in the northern have a
Preliminary data shows the United States having a quiet flu season with recorded cases lower
Then each of the last
Sears at the same point in the season Marvel set
Quote at the moment
We're seeing mirrors
Let's hope that continues to be the case no guarantee he said
Right now we are for this time of year see very low prevalence
But again
It's very early so it's hard to know what to make
Wow is covering dishonestly both of the experts cited gave very general comments
Defective possible that wearing masks could be helpful
Hitler in cases of the flu
But it was too early to say that we should let data lead us to our eventual
Conclusion
Neither of them were saying that the CDC needs
To make mask wearing permanent
No one was demand
Any kind of mandatory mask laws
This is pretty much always the case with Infowars articles
There may be an actual news Outlet story that they're basing their coverage on but
Diversion they're covering is a
Funhouse mirror
Of the real thing
Distorted so it'll fit the bulshit narratives they want to push
I chose to cover this one a little more specifically because
Is pretty glaring
It's super embarrassing
Nepal didn't check
The date on the Providence Journal article before cranking out his outrage blog post
He's honestly hilarious
And here's another a paragraph from Paul's article just cuz
I'd like to poke
Keep in mind experts that he's a rapper
Printing
Two Doctors in Rhode Island who spoke to a local paper
5 months ago
Ears business from Paul's article
Came out this week so let me get that let me set the street and let me set the scene alright
So we've got these two doctors they're on the phone with a Providence of local Providence Rhode Island Journal
They're they're busy there at the house
Hospital they're dealing with s***
They're talking to this person alright block of times.
Then
Cut 2
5 months later
Alright here we are
Medical professionals are still attempting to have mask mandates become part of the new normal despite dr. Anthony fauci
Acknowledging yesterday
Little B common sense
For the CDC to start relaxing measured
Wait till now fauci is
What do you understand what's going on here there's a war going on
Understand
Sloppy s*** man you know how sometimes I'm like damn we can't let scientist named stuff cuz they accidentally made
Really intimidating things or we can't let scientist
Two journalists the same way they would two other scientists because other people will twist it because they
I can't really quite
You know and it's not there
They don't have that too
Kind of socialized
That kind of thing
In this circle
There's nothing you can do
There's nothing you can do well I know I agree
Because the doctors did not convey information
Really they just
Still we're taking
You can't do the stuff that fall does
It's like no one can never talk again
Felt like she named it murdertown
Fictitious plates
Temptation of something that did happen in as much as
Two Doctors in Rhode Island talk to a local paper 5-month
No it's free
This is this is 50
Give people hearts
Naturally
Fifty Shades of Grey
So Alex on the new on the show here in April
All right get some other song
I'm sorry
Stanford study results
Facts
New study suggests
Where in Imagine effect
New study highlights face math problem
Was safely in
If you're paying attention you'll notice that these headlines
These three add lines are all just different dumb blogs riding around headline about the same underlying story supposed Stanford
Study that says that mask
So bad
If you're not paying attention
As I was already in
Almost never is
There's a flood
Study showing that Master dangerous
You were right all along to be against
Three studies at least he's just name them just just
That's the impression I was just trying to create by repeatedly hitting
As if it's three
Fun stories
Also this paper that mask was written by a guy named Bruce
Ventra balance
Visiting scholar on matters unrelated to this paper
Between 2015 and twenty
16 at Stanford
Other than that he has no connection with Stanford and Stanford his work
Direction to take her name off this b*******
This is an important point to bring up
People like Alex in the right-wing media hate authoritative
The mainstream media the enemy of the people in the universities are just full of liars trying to push
The globalist agenda
And yet
Whenever they have the opportunity to pretend that one of their narratives is backed by the authority of the gums
Top scientist top scientists all over this way I want ever they can
Back there
Appealing to the authority of our real mainstream or academic in
Associate their ideas with a respectable source
Bulshit we normally talk about anyone who thinks that people like Alex or legit
Should really question why they do that
Yeah yeah yeah
This paper was published in a journal called medical hypotheses
Which is basically exactly what it sounds like
And outlet for French nonsense and
Unsubstantiated ideas
Neighbors trash the conclusion runs at odds with dozens of other more rigorously design
Studies is being falsely attributed to Stanford Notre to elevated
Credibility
It's basically the norm
Comes to information sources that Infowars use
Nothing
It's because
The underlying unspoken thing they're saying there is look
Even people who do work
Believe this and even people who work on this ship believe
Princeton Washington Post
You know it's true because they actually have to work on it
Bulshit
So you're saying whatever you don't
You're a mediately implying
That you're lying all of the time
Except
Pull out 3 months ago
You cannot produce didn't want to get pregnant
Come on now causes autoimmune responses
Allergic reactions
Labs
Said
We suggest you don't take vaccines and you just get hurt immunity
Oh really
Make a vaccine
Babe brought enough for the protein virus
This isn't true
I was just making up his entire story about Weimar
Decided to spend their efforts to develop covid
In reality she actually read their statements it was a situation where they had to Camp vaccines
Switch the test subjects responded well to but quote
The immune responses were inferior to those seen following not natural infection
And those reported for other SARS CO2
Covid-19 vaccine
Start from scratch on new vaccine candidates were there already other promising vaccines coming to Market it would have been a waste of resources
For them so what they decided to do with a just a research strategy
Focus on therapeutic
But they might be able to
Develop
All of Alex's story about them saying you shouldn't take backsies in a vaccine for covid 2 possible
That's just completely made up from his imagination and it's fun
I'm sure the audience enjoys it but it's not real
Halo
Does bulshit anybody trust him when he says
Anything about virus
Like honestly just tell me what a virus
Steven looks like
Before you're telling me what viruses do
Diablo
The red horn
Fabfitfun
That's also true
You nailed it
So
Alex narrative
Is trying to rationalize the covid deaths in India
Andre contextualize them
I'm as what he's
He's calling malnutrition
Don't worry about this week
Midis
Ajm covid-19 Supply
Salmon continues also in India
The reality of covid in India right now
Scary and it should be something that creates feelings of
Concern and care for people for the people in India
It also creates a real sense of the steaks the people are facing when it come
To the virus
These realizations are dangerous rally
Alex because his entire last year of workers but dedicated to minimize
The covid pandemic for-profit
And help is God King Trump not look bad
The informers audience cannot be allowed to think that the human tragedy in India is real because that threatened
The bottom line of Alex's operation
You see what you see here
Complete rewriting of the
Situation
You can keep the feelings of concern and care for
For the people of India
You're being lied to about why you
It's not about the virus
It's about malnutrition
You can keep that human empathy
But Alex has to protect
The business
You can see a sleight-of-hand really clearly here
In order to make his argument that all the covid deaths in India are secretly just malnutrition
He's referencing a May 8th
2020 article published by the Atlantic
Cancel warning of the possibility of salmon due to supply chain breakdown
The actual headline is quotes world food program David Beasley warns of dire famines in Africa Middle East
Hey covid-19 supply chain
Damage continue
But you see how Alex amended the headline to add India in there because
He needs to make it look like that for the narrative
The word India doesn't appear in that article at all and even this article isn't just about covid
It's also about other influences on
Food insecurity like the flooding those happening in Sudan
And the massive locust swarm
It's a complicated humanitarian issue that demands attention
But Alex's attempt
To hijack that attention
And use it as a prop for his covid-19 with narrative
Which is Google
Ghoulish I say
Yeah the
The fundamental thing that the right-wing has to do first
The Earth
Your family members could people you know you're like
How is it that these people who are
Person in in conversation so empathetic
And caring and
And kind
How is it that large National issues
Monsters
And it's like the right-wing has to redirect that empathy otherwise
People will never buy
People are never going to be like
Hey yeah I think we should steal money from the poor and kill them you know you have to redirect
Yeah absolutely
And it's what you see being done here
Yeah and it just destroys people's brain
Really
Destroyer
Crippling of your ability to care for other people
In a meaningful way
And it's held up in
Supported by
Constant
Miss goose
Information
But another art
Coronavirus India's lockdown turning into humanitarian crisis
German news dwu
6/8 months ago admitting
How did lying about that article
The headline is real and is a real article
Frompw but it's about a desperate situation that many migrant workers and
India were experiencing due to covid lockdown
Maybe you found themselves without work due to business closures and they were far away from their homes and Villages outside major cities
Dad to that difficulty drains have been closed
And although there was eventually a plan put in place to help Transit
Going to stranded workers back
Back to where it was not smoothly implemented
This article doesn't admit that millions of starve to death
It's a report that's meant to bring attention to an issue that some might not be aware of
Analysis lying about
Defenders indefensible narratives all the covid deaths
India Arie
That's what he's doing
Wow
You know
Guess what
It's just as horrific whenever he's doing it about a
Truth never changes true I don't feel different about it because he's lying about Indian said the United
F*** him
So
This clip is we're jumping to another topic
I don't have set this club up
This is weird man
And I wish you any harm myself I'm not called revolt against you
It's already
Publicly
I think Prince Charles self
Ourself
Maybe he's right
Start the operation
Which is the final mop-up
Operation
Is that plans see the drawings of the nerve
I was not a biological with
Along with him I was like this is a bit
McCobb But ultimately
With that
But then we got into that then he was like and if they killed themselves
I would agree that so everyone else should die
Kind of weird that's what he said right
Terms
Of the secondary
My
Political position
My beliefs
Are not influence
Spy public spectacles
By political enemies
Kill themselves
I will join
Is his voice I respect how I read it I got it
My beliefs are so fungible
That's all it takes
Trump liquor gets up there and slaps himself in the face
Still juicy what I do for this country
Now that he's not president
He has finally become the president
The United States
What the hell is this I mean I I obviously don't believe him
But he's still saying it
Tweakers say out loud
So we have high-minded issue
The cover on the table 20
6 show
Disagree with you but keep going
Because that was me because
I'm pretty disconnected
Pop culture as a whole even realize the Oscars happen
Write priority
I heard about the Anthony Hopkins
Insertive kerfuffle
I have no interest in the Oscars didn't before and I really hate Oscars drama
I don't know if it's not it's not something
Necessarily a huge part of
The stuff that takes up space in my mind totally
Alex hates the media he hates movies he hates Hollywood
He thinks about it
The most important thing in the world
This is
Regina King
From actress
Call pissed-off up
She's a good person she's up against those bad white people
Thunderbolt Sodom March against
Wear fancy
$5,000 dresses
Private jet
About evil America
Produce so much wealthy live like that
Africans are starving to death
By the tens of thousands every day
You can see how Alex is criticism of Regina King is 100-percent racially-based
Know anything about her as a person or what sorts of
The charity works you may be involved in
Always uses a black woman
And saying something that he doesn't like and his response is racist outrage
So in her intro speech
The king mentioned how difficult the last year has been
And how is the show converted the different she might have traded in her heels
For marching boots
This statement is experienced by Alex as her saying she would have been marching against the evil white people because
Everything in his life is filtered through the lenses
White victimhood
Yeah it does seem like the people
Yeah that's not good
Also don't come after
Regina King
Somebody want to come
She's amazing
I don't think Alex knows anything about her he knows nothing about her
Doesn't even know
Who this next person is declaring an idiot
Telling people that there's an
Disproportionately police shoot black man
When it's actually the other way around
On average the police in America everyday kill three people
About a thousand people a year
Those people happen Edition fortunately
James Baldwin
The most despicable thing a person can be as indifferent to other people's pain
I just ask that you please
Not feeling different
Please
Don't be a dick
Literally up there wearing
Clowns
I guess I wasn't being indifferent to people's
Spain as much as he was being hostile towards it and buying its validity
People's Bank
Alex is wrong about those
Statistics because the very important word he doesn't understand
Proportion exactly
You refuses to
Statistic
Incontact
It's because if you do that his arguments fall apart in
Also that was travel on free
The writer-director who won an Oscar for best live Act
Action short for two discs
Austin strangers
He's just another idiot
Because he's a black man attempting to appeal to the better side of people's Humanity
Almost comically racist Behavior Analysis Bart
It's not surprising at all
I mean it's just install gnashing
How
Portent
Skin color is to him
While at the same time
He is that
He's not racist
Like if you bring up the color of someone's
Skin
That much
Yeah
Just spend a little while
Complaining about the Oscars butt
Well sure there were black people represented at the Oscars and we can
Back in my day we used to win an Oscar for films like Birth of a Nation
Because they changed film set of our forever and that's
That's why the only reason I look better
Sure
He gets on to another topic
Or does he
Here's video ladies and gentlemen
Tennessee
Police officer
This is just crazy though to watch this on phone
We have some very exciting news
Best selling products is turmeric we have
Humanoid
You forgot the store you
Not sure what I'm supposed to talk about
Just in case you were wondering turmeric
Okay bye I forgot the story so I'ma Do a plug
We get a little visit
360 friend
Lewd
Declared it over for Humanity a year ago
Lone Survivor
That is been born
And now he has a new story
32 towel
And it also is understory out
Dominos.com
Health Ranger post
Microscopes
Covid-19
Mysterious
Others have scanned them
And found similar
Weird things
There's also German
Researchers have tested
What's in the Pfizer shot
Hamilton
Intestinal cells
Clearly this is getting weirder
And weirder
A stranger
So I don't know what this it has to do with vaccine this is just mic test
Some pictures of masks
Send swabs
Stop the moving
Stuff in the swabs and
That's not from studies
That was from a Tik-Tok
A video that came out in January
It's been pretty debunked by scientists with the underlined claim that video is the people were being intentionally given Morgellons disease
Covid swab
The conspiracy was so dumb and evidence was so laughable this one didn't really stick what it did get a lot of attention
The kind of makes sense for someone like Alex or Micah try any of
A little bit
That's if you can whitewash it a tiny bit put a respectable son
See if you can make some money off this fake
Tik-tok-video delusions
The grandeur
Allah Allah
However it does
Seem like these guys wake up every morning and they're like
What could I do today that makes
Jordan fantasize about owning a flamethrower
Jordan and Elon Musk closer
Let's see what it really is going to take for Jordan to buy a flamethrower
Natural news articles this is about a little self-conscious about
In a caption for the microscope image supposedly of a fiber and some Masky was looking at
He adds quote
We do not know why these fibers are there and we are not claiming them to be more challenge
Viber okay
Alright I applaud that attempt to be taken seriously although I
I think it's difficult when that other captions for an image of a mask says
Quote some areas of the carbon
Fiber strands appear to surround exact looking objects
But they might Simply Be bumped Textures in the white
Fiber layer
Oh my God that's that's like saying
That we don't know what the screenshot is from we think it is absolutely an alien spacecraft
It could be from a video game that's also possible
The Weeknd Mike released a series of completely meaningless microscope images of things that he speculating RC
One of them was that picture of fibrous Transit amass
Ask which I may be exact or maybe bumps in texture for
By Monday
He published a blog post on his website about these images
An exact same image has this text along with it
What is this
Exactly
Structure in this first photo look carbon-fibre Mass
Gone is a very sensible suggestion that it might just be bumped
Textures
To push this exact ideas being the
Primary in the listeners and readers Minds
I'd Solvay this is the same s*** though like I don't understand how it is that you can have any page
Be a f****** moron and everybody's like nah look at that idiot
Space but then you let Mike Adams talk about microbes
Difference of big versus small
You're not wrong
This is essentially what I would call self-driven narrative escalation
Mike is engaging in
In the first instance you implant the idea that something might be really suspicious though there might be totally normal looks
Donation for it
When you touch back on the idea the normal explanation is gone and the speculation entirely revolves around the
Suspicious possibility where the burden of the conversation
Becomes this
Proving that this is an egg sac
Instead of the responsibility
A being on Mike
To prove that it's not a bump
That's basically the propaganda smash
Guitar playing
Where the burden
Proof is ignored and maybe your problem instead of theirs
Without using this rhetorical tricking ones like it people like Alex in Mike's game
Collapse immediately
Anything that they say to any kind of reasonable standard
The pope was arrested
Year ago the fake Pope prove me wrong
Do you recall that it was over for Humanity in there would only be lone survivors
Feel like
We are some of the few people who recall that many people just ignore you might also recall that Mike Adams was
From Infowars for months because he and Alex
Disagreed on whether or not covid was real
It did seem that there was a disagreement there
Advocating
Take Veterinary products
Is Mike knuble
I want to I want to say something really a
If they had done nothing
Because natural innate immunity would have already caught
Record this
Alex
That would make Jordan want to buy a flamethrower
Guess what here's what it is everything I've ever said is a lie I believe the opposite now is over for Humanity
Going to be Lone Survivor but now nothing
Then everything will be fine
Cool that that really is something that's just rated
Should get you like that should be more against the law than yelling fire in a movie theater
Like you can't do that you just can't
I just think everybody should boom I got them that's why
The reason that rich people avoid poor people
Too much Brewing
I think that my
His progression
From the initial article where he posted these pictures to the Monday
A blog post
That overhyped
Escalated thing
I thought that was pretty responsible now if you listen to this his appearance on Alex's show is
Is going to be taking
Swings even a step
Further
It's mind-blowing Alex there are little hooks
There are little gripper
Fibers red and blue fibers
In the nasal swab
I did Altra Violet photography I did iodine standing on some of them to show the contrast
It is mind-blowing
What's in these Mass
This is all getting inhaled Indian songs
And the little hooks are grabbing onto your lung tissue
These things are designed to cause
Not to help
And they do not block
Virus transmission
Where we are Alex right now
So give me a riddle post with a pictures
The game was asking
It even answer the Declaration that quote
We don't know all the
It's all about making you worried about microscopic
Images
And speculating about what they could be well hiding
Behind a very clear statement that we don't know what these things are
By Monday Mike Stone had changed
When was the Declaration that the answers are still on clearance place was this declaration
It's clear that the masks in Schwab's are transferring
Materials to the body not merely sapling materials are filtering materials
In other words masculine swabs are themselves medical interventions
With unknown health
It seems like with no new information and no real explanation at all
Micah gone from Quest
Straining to definitively stating thing
And now your duty is on Iowa to show escalating these definitive state
Mitsubishi can't backup at all
This is how the game is played for these people
They're Liars
And there lies Escalade
Because that's how you
Continue to profit
The well-established game that they've played
Many many times
Can we watch
Cowboy
Flooded find them in a restaurant
Like I really don't know how loud I could audits why it's a priority
It's one of those things Dad where everybody knows up very loud
But because I realized
I have no idea what
The ceiling
Oh you don't know the basketball
Really let loose I would like to know how loud I could be and if I saw one of these people in a restaurant I think we might
Discover it's like in Mortal Kombat being pushed to your limit to find a time
Grow mechanical arm
So
You know we got two people getting vaccinated Mike says don't do it
Don't do it
Doubt
Sure sure
Going to be a dying off
Vaccinated people in the fall
Find something for Humanity who got vaccinated there will only be non-vaccinated people find yep that's
Kind of it now
Alistair going to see the hospitals in the fall
Probably filled with people who are dying from this
Dependent enhancement
Side
You nailed it
If you check
It's only going to be people who have been vaccinated
Better in the hospital's at that time
In waves
It is not a good situation other this is part of the depopulation agenda
This is play out of the next 2-3 years
Is no undue
There's no undue
Play some
Miracle
Bill Gates in the UN have set things in motion now
Turn off my
You can't turn this back
Okay well I guess
When you're wrong this is
Over for Humanity
I get so frustrated
With this bunker and whether or not it's setup cuz I change it
Either set up or I haven't finished
Full of survival food
Take off of work
Corsica is f****** with people
It's insane
Also if he's taking off time in the near future I would suspect that it's not because of Bunker preparation
It's lawyer
I think maybe that
That's more more likely it's
It's funny how it's almost like a
Glitch in humanity
Where we never really think about how much
We rely on shame just alike
Living in a society where if you have no shame it's almost like a
Glitch in The Matrix like you can just get away with
Anything
Because people just assume that a human being
If they said that he was over for Humanity
Movie Lone Survivor
I've been with so wrong they didn't
Get to go back on the show for a while
For them to come back and make
Similar claims in the opposite direction
Are you human being would feel shame over that here you would think that somebody would be able to regulate themselves if I like
I should just
Stop listening
Watch it because I think it if you were that wrong the correct response would be to reflect
You wanted him to be like
Why was I bad what is it about my method of finding information
Discerning truth
What is it about that that was so wrong
Is it that I don't have a process
Oh no that's a problem
You know what happens when you're in when you're making one of those papers
For a science for school
You know or or
Go with earlier
The Stanford
Situation
They felt shame attached to it
And we can't let it happen
Right
Cuz they were
For no reason
Mike
Pretty shity
Sure
Alright I believe the
Rapper DMX die from
Covid vaccine
That was in diagnosis a heart attack
Write this would be an appropriate time for you to bark
Yeah go fuc yourself
Mouth yet
Get his name on social media but there's no evidence
The DMX got the
Covid vaccine
And even if he did which
They don't even know
There's no way you can
Approve that
Contributed.
This is just
Disgraceful
One last clip a mic
I hope he's gone for long time
Tell my parents on your show today
This is an extermination agenda
They will come for you
Sooner or later
Already
You need to get out of the blue cities
Get out of the blue States
Get to someplace where you can have some self-reliance
You need to get real assets because an economically
Collapse is coming
They're going to confiscate all the dollars in bank account
Get to get scared of everything get out of the Cities get to
If they're all the money is gone
So this episode started with Alex Zhang that he was going to switch it up
Yorkshire
No
Didn't take any calls
I'll talk to you a dumb idiot
What's the name I got them
Complained very racist Lee about the Oscars you got it human tragedy in a foreign country
Free zone
Prophet that's the way to do it that's a real that's a real What would
Call that Triple Crown
I would say
For the cycle
No
So we get to the 27
Starts up
And totally different man
Totally different vibe
This is going to be an incredibly jam-packed historic transmission I know I didn't think
I got deep research and I've had major
Epiphanies the last
24-hours movie my bed
Major Epiphany is in the last 24 hours
Unabomber
To then being like the next day I've had some major of hip
It's cuz that makes me feel like you've just escalated your Unabomber planning you're feeling better about it makes me wonder if
What's the
It keeps doing the University
So many shows begin with
I had a vision last night
Spoiler alert
You know something
Really should
Annoying
Is that
How often he says that he's transcended things
You realize that bite
Any definition of transcending
You would not be
We doing your show right
You would have stopped yet
Because you're above
That's how it work if you want to be like so bothered by petty little things
Regina King Oscar's giving a speech
White identity feared victimhood
Derek at the office is a real f******
That's where you're wrong it was
Okay bus fare
Blues man that's why
That's what this is such a big
Here we are
Very calm here because this is so important and so huge
And so illegal
Over the top
That if we just
What does information out there it'll become normalized
We must soak the shin we must cogitate on
Mold around psychologically spiritually
We should pray about this
Cuz this is all now
Revealing itself
Coming out the open
I want to beat up whoever taught him to work cogitate
Really annoying
Yeah
What I was listening to
Alright
Hit me
I'm ready totally somebody
123456789 10
11 12 13 14
15/16
Install Stock
24 stacks
You're so mind-blowing so
So important that
Shutter
Properly
Document
I will just Direction
Cool boy
Oh boy
That's a really weak of his like
Tonight Show we've got a great show for you today we're like shoe
It's fine it's fine we got a good show for you tonight sure
Yeah I noticed that I have this little take where I say two things are interesting
Realized
I have news that will shake the foundations of reality it seems almost too easy to point this out buddy
If you weren't interested in it
It would
Be in the shower
It's true so it is still a little bit
Here's the first story that Alex
Alright let's
Let's do this man
Rapid fire baby
We go out until a the master never coming off until you say no
Bacterial pneumonia
It's psychologically screws up children
But it doesn't protect you
Call Cindy's now saying that
You need to go out
Walmart
You need to stop
And he's been too liberal there the point is
This is child abuse
Walmart okay
Alright
Easy just really how quickly the party of
Personal responsibility
Turns into the party of
Children because their parents can't
Take care of them they're wearing a mask
Yes stop them from wearing mask
The party of personal responsibility
The first story is a Tucker is antimatter
Great okay
Here's the Second Story
Here's the big super supreme enchilada
That to enchiladas
Medical doctors all over the world from Germany to Canada
Let's say they are being arrested by the police
That's coming up
The children are endangered
In their mental physical and spiritual well-being
This headline appears
On a page
On the web
Website
Daily General news.com whatever the f*** that is
I know that I need to go to the general
To get some insurance
Also the one of the problems is that this webpage
Is no longer there
The 404 page doesn't exist that's a problem snapshot back machine
And I find all of this
Quite suspicious
Interesting Lee I found an article on Gateway pundit
Clearly about
The same story but with a
Slightly different headline
German police ransacked the home of
Judge after he agrees with evidence in court the children are endangered in their mental physical and spiritual well-being
Location to wear face mask
You notice a difference
No longer physician
Yeah that's
No I think police should read
Felicia braids
I can't find any news sources on this that actually find credible of about the story but the narrative is presented on Gateway
A pundit type Outlet is that this judge named Chris
Detmer
Had his house rated as
Retaliation for ruling
The covid-19 related cautionary measures
Like masks
Could not be enforced in school
It's only related to two schools
In this area
Happen I think I I can be
Be comfortable with
Something that I've seen on that
Applicability or
Good stand-up air to hearing in a higher court that remains an open
I can't find any information about a possible Ray that I feel
Believe in something as suspend judgment on this until there's more detail
That said
Alex is telling the wrong version of this story
He said it's a Doctor Who provided evidence
The story is that it's a judge who handed down the opinion in the case
I suspect one of the Alexs interns found the story on a site like daily General news before it was fun correctly
So he's reporting the wrong version of that story here
The big supermassive enchilada
Great isn't it such like a small emblem of his world
I've just like
This is happening all around the world from Canada to Germany
Near like okay
Hydraulic up their country
So here's the what's another
Chilaquiles right here
Joe Biden house yesterday he's going to send Aid to India
It's not vitamin C if not vitamin D
Lockdown
It's not
Oxygen bottles
What
Is the population
Nearest shipping
Millions of doses
Fast food
First things first the Oxford AstraZeneca vaccine is actually developed by the Sarah minced
Attitude of India
Andy's produce there under the name Covey
Windshield
That vaccine is always been
Been approved for use in India wasn't one of the country's that's
Suspended it
The reason we're sending a bunch
India's because in order to make sure the vaccine
Could get made countries like the United States agreed to purchase a ton of them in advance
Along the way various countries got to decide which they would approve
For using their country
And it resulted in the situation we're in now
Arnold doses of the AstraZeneca vaccine
But it's not approved for use in the United States
It is effective
Music nature
It's one of their approval
Send it to them
As opposed to letting it go to waste
What's good
Nonsense all he wants but
Not the story
It's not that what he
Do we have one more also it's
Just to be clear
It is not like
They're putting them all in
Boxes right now and they're like
Getting all these little thyroid millions of vials and all these big boxes there
Visa expires they don't even exist yet
Okay
So that was the chilaquiles then what are we got a chili relleno I got another another dish Saturday
Schools around the world
Experimental
MRNA gene therapy
Because it can cause the spread of real
Viruses
Not even your precious Wall Street Journal
Big
Deal
Ladies and gentlemen this isn't true there was one school
In Miami called The Center Academy
That's been vaccinated teachers I'm interacting with students
It's a private school that was opened in 2019 and it appears to be run by nuts so I'm not too surprised to hear
But it's pretty funny that Alex is exaggerating this into a phenomenon where all over the world schools are Banning vaccinated teachers
Ridiculous
Wow
Man
You can just be a dum-dum anywhere and Alex
Will find you
So we had our boy the health Ranger unless episode
And now we got another
How we going to up
The game
Off of the internet as we know it
So he's not banned off the internet as we know it
He still has a verified account on Twitter banned on the internet as we know it
If his own pages
Yeah it's still up there verified confirming that I
Checked out his pint
Sweet Woodruff caption video proof that I'm on a no-fly list
My experience with this is a little bit different
Here's a little clip that maybe like that or no
And there's no way I can get on this
With Southwest
But maybe
Delta Maybe
Did they give you a reason
It's a no-fly list you said
Next video coverage
Tell the truth gets out when you speak out of you take cash
Here's the article from infowars.com
America first found
Put on
And I told him why
You were at the Kappa
Even in the
Capital
Himself at the airport doesn't show the
I'm saying why or even that he is on a no-fly list so
Weird it's weird it's weird the proof that is being presented doesn't seem to
Bulshit the time that I saw all that trending nonsense about
That what that's all based off of
What
That he's on a no-fly list
His own video
Am I guess you act will Google talk about a little bit more he was trying to go down to a DeSantis rally and
Florida he wasn't allowed to fly
Better theories as to why
I want snakes on the show
But Alex has to spread some other b*******
They're intimidated
Witnesses in the show on trial and throwing Pig blood on what they think their house is
11 with the mob intimidating
What do you think you're not he's got to go free I'm G black or white
Because of that
Alex has this story
Completely wrong
I still see no evidence of any jury intimidation in the Chauvin case but Alex's specifically lying about one comment that was report
Where did where someone referred to as a Chauvin juror said quote
I did not want to go through all the rioting in
Destruction again and I was
Concerned about people coming to my house
If they were not happy with the verdict
Liars like Jack Pacific
Quick started passing it along on social media understory spray pretty far that way
It's almost certainly without
What's the covering as real news here
The problem is that this person wasn't a jury in the juror in the trial
Choose an alternate
Play definitely no role in the
Good sighting of the case and the comment was taken out of
The full context of that quote is her response to a question posed by a local Minneapolis news Outlet
About whether or not she wanted
To be a juror
I had mixed feelings
There was a question on the questionnaire about that and I didn't know
Because the reason at that time was obviously I didn't know what the outcome was going to be so I felt like either way the outcome was your go
Going to disappoint one group or the other
So I didn't want to go through this whole rioting and destruction
Then again if you know
A little concerned about people outside my house if they weren't happy with the verdict
Discussing the idea whether or not she wanted to be
Epoch time
Totally reasonable fears
Stu has been Twisted by
Liars like Jack the soba can be misreported by Alex in order to try and argue for
Getting
Chauvin
Of course
Because of course
So are we get to Nick Williams
I just do that cuz Alex likes to pronounce his name
That hard you and I
And he's going to tell the story of
What happened to him
Airport
And I will say that I don't know I don't know if this did happen it certainly not in the video labeled
Proof that I'm on a no-fly list
This is his proof you think it's
Be in the video story
It sounds like the story that someone like him would tell
But it certainly doesn't match that
Wow
Cuz she said you know is there anything
American before
Nothing like American Airlines
I've been flying pretty recently
She said okay well I'll give them another call
And they relay the same message I'm not able to
You know honestly the political guy
Because I'm not supposed to say that
Stuff is out of control and corporations
Yeah sure okay psycho these are absolute
Absolutely
Lunatic
This is not the video but this is the story
He goes to United
I guess what this isn't in the video either Comstock
From someone from Southwest
I went over to United I went all the way over to the other terminal I booked
10:40 a.m.
To Palm Beach from O'Hare
I went up to the counter and she told me the exact same thing she was on the phone with
The TSA for half hour
I'm sorry
And she goes and you know what I just Googled you
And I think I know why that is that's what she said
I'm so sorry but
Can I go to the TSA
Nobody could talk
Talk to that's it
So I'm on the no-fly list and
Capitol on January 6th
Okay I don't see
Indication that any of this is real.
Suggest
A bunch of nonsense
No but I should get at a
Text alert if I know he's in Chicago
He lives in Chicago I know but like where I can
You know
You know what I'm saying like Homeland on Prime is sending me something right now
I'm not going to say what it is Amazon Prime free with this if
The only use of that information is avoiding wherever he is absolutely
Been like this kind of talk man
Recaps Nick Story
Two giant assumption
Spell in here
No fly list they admit it's because you weren't
So no fly list
Recovering the capital
Those are the assumptions
Right there's no reason to suspect that Nick is on a no-fly list because of the event
January 6th
A lot of folks might have forgotten by now but
In December 2020 nickname
Big deal online about getting kicked off a plane for not wearing his mask correctly
I told the guy on the plane. f***
You and eat s***
Bat-Mite
I have something
Things to do with it
You were in that first clip that Nick was talking to that is it something to do with masks
Obviously cuz you got kicked off a plane Alex months ago
I don't know if he's on a no-fly list I would assume he's not since the simpler explanation is that he's a public figure
Who made a big deal out of an altercation he initiated on a plane
6 months ago
Stunt
Yes I would say that maybe Airlines alike
How about that wasn't on my Airline
I would maybe not let him on
Based on
Soda public
I don't want to deal with that I don't know you have the right to refuse service to assholes so why would you want that
Even the possibility of that happen
Coming against you know that he's a provocateur
Didn't happen is really funny
Him trying to be like oh is there a mask
No I said
It is next clip Alex
Channels Reagan
In a very inspirational Way You Are
Ronald Reagan
Call Matt Walsh
Figure
Not mr. Gorbachev tear down that wall I say
Biden tear off that mask off your dirty bandit face
I don't think that's going to resonate through time
Inspiring
This is inspiring
To be one of those that you know when those montages where they do like
All the greatest Generation kind of s***
And they go through all that and because there's a big most to history
That is going
50 years old I'm 50 years from now that will be in the real
Show me your dirty Bandit
Do wrong
So Alex at this point talk
What's to a Canadian
Preacher
Who's had the police show up
A couple times
Because he's not following covid
It's not the
The same Canadian Churchill we talked about
How many Skippers cuz it's it's
Who cares
Another
If you're free to go. Infowars Europe
Piece of s***
We have also Alex
Just getting into this weird thing released
Planing about
The last enjoyed they're all they're all demons out
I'll describe yoy
Friendly's with their masks and I see them with their hatred in their pedophilia and
Left into evil now
Little superhero the kind of mid-level
A leftist is Robert two purposes
A devil worshipping Google I don't know what's happened to him
All the main cities
Black matter
Do dinner even the low-level if this is just
Trickling down just be like the top level is.
No now we're all demons
Every single one of us. Good and we're gone
For us
Thing that can be done for us dad
Bat-Mite
You know
It doesn't
So
The beginning of this episode.
Albertsons
Promise you had an epiphany
Skip 24
Stacks of paper
I haven't gotten one today
Jame I mean
Take it over
By the way we don't find ourselves and won't be here
A lot
Avenue Great t-shirts get through those
24 stacks
You know what a certain point I think you would recognize
That like
I never get through the
First Act
Maybe two stacks is the max
Everybody needs a little setback you're delusional
Many of them have that bike on the desk you know they're wearing
Lapel mics
It's like you okay do you prepare a meal for yourself right
And every night you make
Temp service
Through
Three-quarters of one and then your eye
Play all their food
Event
Next day you're like all I got all this food here is it going to be great I got all this food
You get through maybe half of a service time
Cuz baby you're not hungry that night
There is a there is a paper mill in Oregon that relies on Alex
Exclusively that brings me to my next point
He better be f******
Recycling
We have another guest
Champion weirdo hahaha
Goddamn
What a weirdo
I am Alex Jones your house and the great stevequayle.com
Filmmaker one of the first big survivalist on the top
Survivalist
Thought some of the
Who's a little extreme well now
It looks like
He's been
Dead on
What are those extreme conclusions
You know what here's my new pet
Here's my new pitched and all right before these assholes get to say a goddamn word about being a survivalist
You have
To go on Naked and Afraid win
That is it if you call yourself a grill
I don't think Steve would make it
So I love that Steve was on
Because I've been
Play this clip for you
Sequel was recently on the Jim Bakker Show
Just this clip I was going to make an episode out of it
So boring
Find it you are thankfully rightwingwatch
Head cut out this
Particular clip where dude get ready
Steve Quayle for giving us an excuse Mike down okay have your mind blown by Jim Bakker and Steve Quayle
Zombies
That are on the Earth
Are disease like any other disease that affects people and they become like
Zombies
Is that right
Forgive me but that's only part
Two-story zombies
A zombies also have the
Evil
Spiritual entity known as demon possession
Okay
Because there is no rationale
With a zombie
The best way to explain zombies blood loss desserts
The appetite of demons Express real human
It should be astonishing the people that the richest people in the world not all of them but some of them
Are into a call ceremonies
Where they have
Did you know
Blood
Bats
That's extract
From a tortured child
Abasi
Appetite
Demons Express true human
The ancient world
With monsters mythology
Call Andrea
And this is something that is
Really
Important to get through
V
Disease
Basically
Destroy
The human defense
God gave us the fastest human
To resist the devil and he will flee
When your
Inviting
What's the word I want
Embrace
Abject
Demon possession
Giving yourself over
B & habitat
Bebe
By the demons who them become your inhabited
It's a too full what I'm saying Jim
Yes they can induce
Zombie-ism at least the appetite
At the end of the thing it's
Both hands right hand
Simply is
The evil spiritual possession
That
Zombie
Steve Quayle just this month was on Jim Bakker Show
Wow
I do appreciate how much of Christianity does seem to get their idea of the
World from like the hellblazer comic
John Constantine is also a
A factor
In Jim Baker's reality I would love that conversation
Taking place outside of a televangelist studio
Disgusting
What does make a zombie a zombie
Maybe have that conversation
Zombie Baker and Steve Quayle
Position on that
What
F****** weirdo
This is spam
Christian's all uniformly be like
We can't be associated with this
Because if we really do allow zombies
People are going to put that together with the rest of the bulshit We Believe
Other be like maybe Christianity stupid
Or you know like meme that Jesus a zombie
Exactly it's like okay if you start the if you start adding too many mythical elements into it at
Especially ones
That are referenced in Night of the Living fukka
King dead what your best
Best order of business
Is if your religion
Don't incorporate any universal monsters
No Mommy
At no point in time to Jesus say we're coming to get you Barbara no Dracula that's not going to happen
So anyway I don't respect Steve Quayle
At all no
And so we just have a series of him saying things and talking to Alex that I have
No interested
Tree that's real
Consideration
You think zombies are real
Depopulation agenda
This is what's really important
Ladies and
This is all about one thing
It's about the depopulation the world
From 7.9 billion
That's a reference to the Georgia Guidestones with Bradley
Steve Quayle believes
Sorry live
Sir
I do love how
The globalist
Love around number that
It's easy for
Ridiculous idiots to understand
Convenient
How ridiculous idiots are always given
Nice round number
That's great
It's great so that no one can ever find
Certainly proved a lot of stuff
Steve does to
Got the sense from listening to this that Alex's whole story about him seeing fish people with human eyes
Story crib
From Steve
Interviewed
One of the Intel world's most famous
Assassins
How do you say laboratory summon the most Seeker
Places
Deep underwater in the jungles
Borneo
I've seen things in kg
Half human half
By the way the lion men of Moab
Liberty
But he said these creatures were calling out to me
Help me help me I'm human
Any start a week
This is a CIA guy
But there was a human
Stop
Makes a stick in my spirit
Okay so your story
That you're telling me
One of the best assassins
One of the best assassin
For the CIA someone
Who's the best
Killing me
People yes
And especially for the CIA so you know there's no morality within this person
I wouldn't assume so if the other details of this
The story are correct
What is Breaking Point
Panera Bread
Was
Half man half man half life
By the way
No reason
What's the weather
To a dandelion memorable apps no cuz these are genetically created now right not the lion
Reconstitute the goddamn lion Manuel
You know that might be part of his argument in my blood
Steve's argument
Is
That is
Biblical times before the flood they were making human-animal hybrids
Emmett history is repeating itself now
That's where we're at
Yeah
Yep so anyway if you're a Christian you got a cop to The Lion Man that you believe that lie in Metairie
So
Look there's some similarities
Between what zombies alignment already in
Steve Quayle
Okay
Some similarities
Between with Steve believe
And let's say
Today we insure
Could be he thinks that there's a
The difference
Between
Exposition
Is my position is
Before Noah's flood
Incorrupt
Now we are seeing in The Book of Enoch that people used to say wasn't true
But it got leaked out
The Weeknd
The Dead Sea Scrolls
What
Anyway yes Steve breaks off from Ancient Aliens
You love
I do love
The combination of
Defensiveness
Confidence in his position
Wild Thing something so abject Lee ridiculous
You are trying to be taken seriously and you need to clarify your position against the Ancient Aliens position
You're underwater man
Look these Ancient Aliens people are crazy
I believe
That before the flood
Aliens came down
That's stupid
See what happened is Before the Flood
Interdimensional Angels came down and built the pyramids shows up
This fiddling around with human and animal of the hybrids and what have you created
Right
What's going on
Golden time
And it's going on again
I'll just let this Blake
The Human Genome Project
What's to ID
Angel
Have sex with Earth women
Produced a hybrid hybrid
World of Warships
Obviously
Now
We're coming to that point where we're messing with genetics
So I see you scribbling notes
I just I just want to make sure that
Forever
Throughout all of history written down in this notebook
Is the Human Genome Project was about
Ameri clarifying the Nephilim DNA or whatever
Sure that no matter what happens what it was all about man the Human Genome Project
Who's trying to find
Thor
Trying to find
Heracles
Make
Since I really really
It like
And I I mean this
With
All
Non respect
This is sad even for Alec
Text to listen to
Yeah cuz it goes against his interdimensional theory
I think that all of its own on
Specific that you you have a really hard time
That's a good I think you should keep that in your backpack I understand that because you work from sort of a grounded place of reality
Speedpaint
Yeah I think they could make this work
If it matters
When you have no shame it's like a glitch in humanity you can figure it out
Yep
Steve is this guy who like I really think
That I mean we've listened to him a little bit in the past
And he has
Worst version of think
He's a prophet than out
Like
He legit emedley is
Just like I know all God
Story is that God gave him a vision of everything but
These things up
Justice like
This clip
I think is just a guy doing an impression of a prophet
The day will come
Mark my words when even vitamin
Will be made it illegal
Possession of item
Speak in the name of Jesus
Capital offense
Everything is going to be a cat
Our schedule
To be terminated
Terminated
I would like to mark his words about
Possession of vitamins
Becoming
B12 get it out of there
Summary execution
If you have riboflavin
Vitamins in just food
You can't have it
Are you talking about regulations for the supplement industry
And I think that's something that terrifies you more than
Anything in the world
Little bit different
This is a nonsensical interview with
Who has a bunch of really stupid ideas about dumb s***
Was about
Angels
Great
Also zombie scientist
Bobby's got together
We can't not know about these angels
Who f***** women
In the past to create Thor we just can't not know
Zombies zombies are also in play
And all this is gray
But
I think there might be ulterior motives to this interview
This clip
Took off my headphones and walk out over yourself
I want to talk about
A work phone
I don't think you
You know that we're having trouble finding ourselves you said listen is one of the best deals that I sponsor someone for many years
It's not why you're here you just mention a new function
Excited about osher sorry you got me a satellite
Talking about your dumbass ideas
Wow
Wow Alex you're really willing to let him go that long just so you can sell a satellite phone for you
Yeah that's not good
I don't know what the deal is here with the
This phone exactly but
Infowars phone.
Redirect
Stewart website satellite phone store
I don't know if they have it
Infowars promotion going on but if they do they're keeping Infowars and Alex's name the f*** off at
I don't I don't know what's going on I guess Steve Quayle got him a sponsor and now
Getting meeting
For that company whenever they're getting together having like
Okay
I have
I got Alex
Sound on the hook for about 5k
Alex Jones
From Infowars
Are we
Are we there yet
Are we that far.
We'll take the only explanation
That's outrageous although I do think there is a a certain
Delicious
Of the
Trajectory of a guitar
Just saying the stupidest s***
You are feeling bad for that day off of courses
Well I really really feel bad now
Jim Bakker
That satellite
The phone sponsor
That would explain his recent airtime is a middleman
Hey I get you this
You get me some air.
Yep
Anyway Jordan this has been an exploration of the
The beginning of the week on Alta show I'm excited to see the response
Monster the Giuliani real
And I apologize if we don't have that on this episode of it is just too much
With this
With this bulky
Bulshit but Alex is doing
No we're either going to have to focus a lot on the Giuliani raid or it's going to be one of those things where he mentions it
Says that it's unfair and then does not speak of it anymore might say that it's the end of the world and he might not talk about it at all
Range is Uno's
Yeah but we will find out soon enough but until then we have left
We have our side, also on Twitter
We are not go to bed Jordan
We also are.
Find a local charity or Belvidere area
We will be back but until then I'm needle I'm Leo rdcs Clark I'm Daryl rundus I was dishonorably discharged when I say
Served under major cat
Holding
Alex
Kristen color my huge fan I love your work