Damn important
I have great respect for knowledge B I'm sick of them posing
Knowledge
Acknowledge
Dot-com
Ceramic novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Giordano wait sorry we were supposed to call Joseph altar of the solenoid
Dion Jordan
Quick question
What's today
My brights you go first when I go visit around a little bit
You can't say granola granola
My bright spot
Mayonnaise around this time of year
Ever you're my cousin and I get together and we go to a ball game
I don't know if you know this
Not Dan but I know you love this
I appreciate
The game of baseball gloves
And we can get to do that last year and this year we just got
The tickets and we're going to a game
It feels so amazing so amazing
I'm I'm like shivering with excitement I can't wait
Hair
I also
The Pirates
Becomes a terrible this year so again
Who cares
All right they're probably going to lose
Alright let's see what do I got
I guess I don't know what stuff this is sort of a hypothetical bright
Right spot alright I'm listening I think
Think I feel comfortable enough
To maybe try
To check outage
You know like it weird
Yeah yeah yeah that is where
I could feel comfortable whereas
Is going to look before
Certainly there was no ability to kind of space to the gym was
Nightmarish hellish
It was a little
Scary to see that level of
It was a
Passive manslaughters has worked out better than better than pads Advance Auto Parts
Certainly was not for lack of trying do I do if your responsibility going on it
Did not care for it
I feel like it's about
I feel pretty good about that I always enjoy going to
The gym spring
Get the beach of
Lakeshore
Your shirt off and really just the other day
Wunderground.com rocks
Considering
Commercial with
This is a nice day
Today we talked about April 30th
This is an unforced error on my part
Back I think so either of us
We're going to be covering the end of the week
Rudy Giuliani
I couldn't
FaceTime with that
Because
On Thursday
Newsbroke
About Rodger
Stones involvement of the Mack Gates
I don't recall everything Beyond somebody thinking
Here's what I'm
I'm going
To give Rodger Stone
Rodger
I have a tattoo of Richard Nixon on my back Stone
Incriminating evidence
I'm going to write a confession letter and give it
Nikki Rochester
A single word
And I will keep
Snapshots of offers of bribes to get a pardon
Yeah there's a star to call the vet
Pretty pretty bad looking
30 lookbook
Anything good
Beef a dog
I know it makes a white here's why it's so believable
Because everybody's so stupid
Nobody's doing anything like
Even a half-assed attempt
Googling how did not get
Arrested for these specific
The crimes would be like
Don't give it to Rodger Stone
The part of it that makes it even more believable Zahn on
For me is that like
Here they have their app
WeatherTech
Sing apps delete the messages
And Rodger followed through with that
That's good
That came out of
Friday's got to be f***** up at work
His buddy
He's like
On the hook
Restart achill
Talking with
This guy eating to having sex with a seventeen-year-old for money there's a problem to get Rodger
Alex's body
To get them apart pardon from Trump and it appears that
Rodger
250k
Wow so big news day for Alex
I am going to put
$250,000 worth of bitcoin on Rodger Stone not calling in on Friday
I will I will I don't spoil that
Rodger is
He is not to be to be found
My lawyers
Who told me to pray more we do get a lawyer
Show all yeah that's not surprising
Jordan
And I will get into this
And see what Alex has responses before we do I got to take a look
And a welcoming some walks
Someone tried to catfish my bum with a picture of Alex Jones and now I'm here thank you so much and I'll probably walk
I'm a policy wonk
Are you very much either Tsum the path that everyone took to our show
Text actual biblical
I'm a policy wonk
Onyx human cat trimera
Very much human Coronavirus
Bootsy Collins
Thank you very much for
Bianca. Thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk everytime I read a name I can't not think
Think I'll get dog Bianca.
I do not remember what a great time and culture
You know what's weird every time you remember something I get sad
I don't know why I need to retain the memory of Honky Tonk Badonkadonk other things slip my mind
There's so many things
You know that's one of the main reasons I hate the doors
All right at the episode where we have two headed after that that was perfect you want
You won you won
I'd like to take that win and transition it over into wishing happy birthday
Out there
I don't know when his birthday is but okay
Yeah I also don't know the name of the person who wish them happy birthday
Like you've been had sometime in May
Personal there
Who has a birthday
And also an anniversary with a person who screen name is dancing
So it's big
What I love about
Chose wouldn't
That's what we're doing right now
But two shows that did do this what do follow-up stuff
But you that's why you come to us
Us for us
Vaguely know a little bit enough
To be like you are great
Like that
Jordan
April 30th
Alright
Friday
How to show started with some
Troubling news
That comes with Matt gaetz don't know news that comes in the form of
The voiceover
Coming to you live from the infowars.com studios in the recapture
Joe
I'm glad you responded that way cuz I couldn't tell if we've talked about that before or text me now
Okay
What did they recaptured I don't know it was occupied
Yes 41 Tire careers in occupied
Was liberated for awhile wasn't
I don't think so time where they were like state currently turning blue
I guess it's been real
Yeah maybe that's meant to be like recapture to buy democratic
I don't know I mean that. More latinx people are allowed to vote
Texas the more it is being recaptured from from the colonialists so that's nice
It was strange
I think I might have heard that before in the past but it's
It struck me as very new and I don't know what it's in reference to I
Alex
Start the show off with some Lana Del Rey
Allowed
No it's it's
It's more aggressive than the more
More
Symphonic movie Wednesday
But
It's too loud
And I did not mix
This well
Diner House downtown
Extremely honored
Call
Very small plant
Hurtling through space orbiting
Two-thirds of the way out of the spiral arm Milky Way go
There are 7 billion people on
Nebula see themselves as Guardians of the earth Guardians of the Galaxy
What
Poisoning dumbing-down
And then calling
Human population
Sure
The EU has laws in place for the decade
Slaughterhouse
Anybody selling pardons for money. What do you got to say
And then you butcher it
Drugs
Radiation
Separating us from God
Gerardo
And then we'll be so stunned
So disease
So much in Bessemer I sleep
Brightburn
Choppa Style
Nicely
No it's totally super
Editor's
Ryan
I think I just heard
Did Matt gaetz was going to
I don't know what you heard all I heard is just stuff you can just say no
No
I don't know what
Humane practices at slaughter houses have to do with
Cuz you got it in the slaughterhouse
No Country for Old Men that was a book
Anna movie I just I just hear Alex saying things that I just
Yeah
That's a
It's one of those things where somebody stealing time
Screw your delcamp
Or exactly what you were doing
Seems like you'll be talkin about the all of them crime
Just talking through it
Just got to get through
In
2A
Possession
Total control
And that's what all of this is about
But you are the really huge
Issues
Everybody needs to be aware of
That is
Many of us
Removing mice
Into a post
Human
World man
Special Report just starts playing
Somebody
Somebody in there is I'm telling you Dad
When the music was too loud we've seen too many appropriate song Choices
I'm telling you there's a secret Patriot inside of
Studios the problem
Here's the problem it's bit like
The line but
Queen f****** with Alex and incompetence is indiscernible
I mean
Just up that moment
A real resin
Ignatius
This is how it is he's too tired to even get mad as how it was
How it was
How is going to be for the future. I love it
So Alex has a special report that he wants to play and it might have been that one that's different
Daily Sheriff
That up
Last night
Will you stay late tonight and tomorrow morning
And get out a report on this
That's because
Investigative journalist The Washington Post
That was two days ago
Didn't get any coverage
Because I know it's true that
Which is true which is huge
I have this come out in
If we can force the story out
This is really
Devastate the New World Order their whole operation
The recently Rogan hunting
An episode we talked to a guy named Josh Rogan
R o g i n
Not really
As a reporter who works for the Washington
Post
I watch the relevant part of the interview and I don't find it too
3 super convincing
That said Josh was explaining to Rogan wife
The theory that the virus started
Completely crazy
He doesn't prove or even claim definitively that he has information to talk to you or the lab is
Is responsible for the outbreak
He's just reiterating information that's been widely publicly discussed
Over
The entire life
Substantial evidence
Makes people think that I got loose from a lab
There's some circumstantial evidence that makes it look like the virus was naturally occurring
That's not even a new or controversial thing to say
It's just
Generally
Experts who looked at it
Feel very natural explanation is far more likely
Yeah I know there was like two weeks ago there was another story where it's like
DOD cam
Rule out the possibility of course not they're bunch of really really hard
The binary possibility right-hand you prove the affirmative
Very difficult and so
Obviously
People who died
They're talking about this seriously
Deal with it
Only unserious people would be like
There is no possible way I
Clara pot
Create of their opposition
Another opposition to argue again
So just kind of seems like a little bit of a dick
Only because
I don't believe
He's unaware of what he's doing
Like he's not some guy on his first
Recipe renzi's a guy with a career in Media
He knows what he's doing is lending The credibility of his mainstream media credentials to be used exactly how Alex's using this clip on
Show now
Unless Josh had some
Some actual evidence of
Of anything
The behavior he displayed in that interview was at best
Irresponsible
This next clip from Alex's show which is complete
Bulshit
Is the direct result
Of that kind of yours
Possibility
Bombshell Friday live Washington Post medication
That's falchi behind Wuhan leaks and he's the main suspect
So now it's turned into a Washington Post investigation
She is the main suspect in there getting rid of that getting
Wolf say I mean all you've done is create
Proven by the conversation that happens with Rogan
What what extra do they bring to the table other than
Surname Washington
Didn't post report
That's what they bring to it
Embassy Washington
Logan gets caught
Not introducing a new idea that like
There is a slight possibility
There was a lab origin
Not that that's not new
It's normalizing
Conclusion
That it was
Stop from a lab
No excuse just irresponsible and I just don't believe
It's somebody who could have the level of career that
He does
Would be able to go on Rogan and not recognize that your behavior would be interpreted by lit
Listeners that way
Well I mean
In that
Situation there's two things
He's going on
One if you have any credibility that you've
Built up through being a reporter of any kind of
And you go Ian Infowars or Rogan or whatever
They're there to steal your credibility
They don't give a fuk about
Your credibility is what they
They're stealing so they
I can do that
And you're there
To get
Attention
What's the deal maybe sell something you're selling
When you're a reporter for the washer
Post if you don't know that you're there to sell something in there they're too
To steal your credibility
Your
Stupid
Like that's
Beyond The Pale
Cuz that's the only reason you would go
Not because Jose fun
No no no cuz Jose such a good to Jamie's
He's a cool dude I don't even know anything about
Never heard of her to Google
Alex
From across the pond
Who pays a visit on this episode
Paul Joseph Watson
Sure
Play this is
Is really just all about the anti-muslim agitation
I was Wonder
Oh boy
Take a picture of stuff so what
What
We are
Call Frank tomorrow
London is London Stan
Okay so
Is the game
To the UK and the rest of Europe
In the world
We need to stand with the French people
They're good people
Whole thing is essentially that extreme
Sense of anti-muslim
Programming it's pretty it's pretty
Just geograph
How could France be the Gateway
The Chunnel
Is that the channel from France to England
Gateway
For Europe
Like France
Like if you're looking at a map of Europe
Right right
And you got the whole year up there sometime
For the Gate Park
Africa
That's what is it
Creole
Real eels real
Does that argument
Scarier
Cuz it's not throw it away there's 50
10 countries between them and the gateway to London
What's going on here is that there was an open letter that got published
In France
That was about
The fear of
The Muslims
Well this is a no
Noises from
Military personnel
General
Warning about the situation on the
Edges of the suburbs of major cities
Lacrosse
Do you have this
Parallel Society
Bye-bye is completely undermined the
The French government
Essentially what government
First of all Alex's entire libertarian identities based on the rejection of the state have in Monopoly on power
The entire reason that the Second Amendment so important is that if the populist
Can be armed
The state can't Attain
Complete Monopoly of 4
So weird here bald
Be concerned about
Rex for the Monopoly of power of the
The French
That's why strange
Yeah anyways this open letter that Paul is talking about wasn't insane letter that was published
The far-right magazine called valuers actuality
Hi in French
Interesting Lee was published on the exact 60th anniversary of a failed
Coup attempt against
Charles de Gaulle
Back in 1961 the idea of allowing Algeria to enjoy self
Determination was put to a vote
And Algerian Independence won the day overwhelmingly
Naturally many former generals / 2
Particularly those in
Algeria didn't like this
Suneva sided to form a hunter
And tried to take over major cities in Algeria
Didn't work out for these generals but it did lead to many of them forming a group known as the organization Army sick
Which was a terrorist group and a destabilizing
Situation Algeria
In order to maintain French Colonial rule
Because what
Needs to eat so you want
The government of Algeria to not having the Monopoly on power
Make sense
So it seems like this may be more than a coincidence
Set this letter warning of an Insurrection was published on the anniversary of a failed insurrection
Aimed at maintaining archaic
Particularly when you read that one of their stated
Complaints about various
Anti-racism group
Is it they want to tear down statues of famous French
Colonialist
It's a little bit
It's a little bit I grow
That does sound a little bit like a memorializing the day mishma tried to over
Overthrow Japan nice little letter like Emperor Hirohito was pretty great I don't know if you guys remember that guy's pretty
Naturally noted fascist Marine Le Pen has voiced support for the letter and it said signers
Which is very clearly a part of her push towards running again in next year's election
Against macron
So
Good
Hey
Hey you know
With
This is just a Muslim
All I know is that you admit
Doubling 10 years ago Christian persecution
Anywhere in the world the Muslims are killing you including
Paul Joseph Watson about what's coming next day with us there are very legitimate issues about
Persecution around the world
Recognize that org
To deny that or minimize it
The answer is not
Oppressing Muslims
No it's not that
Turning it around
Okay
Okay now I see what you
And when you say that you think what we're going to do is we're going to break the
The cycle of violence
Have you considered though that on the other side of that
Cycle we're the ones
I'm committing file
So like as long as we die before the cycle turns around again I will I will say that the
Depending on which side you're on
Feels very different but it's still bad
Yes
What is it
Is kind of becoming a
The thesis of mine
Overtime
Xavier
Repeated
Over and over and over again by people
In the Infowars fear is that I think one of those
Characterizing
Elements
Of what makes
These people in this world
Is an inability or an unwillingness to recognize the difference
Between fiction and real
That it's
Just
Something is
Inability
Yeah
Think that's the
Or maybe maybe not unwillingness so much as all of the incentives
Bush tour
Why deal with
The incentives are towards
Believing in false reality
So why would you
You go back to real reality you have to get like a regular job
Alex isn't going to just like bad groceries
It's not just Alex I mean it's Paul
Find French author in intellectual
Published
I have the Charlie hebdo Massacre
And he predict
Muslim Community
Friends
Isis literally puts out
Festo
But I can make an alliance with the
I also hate
Joey Bosa
Warning the
Beacon traxsolutions moles would be in a Muslim
Thanks power
Compromises to get it all under control
So this book by Michelle
Started predict
It's not even a nun
It's a novel that
Resent a fictional future
Weather socialist and a Muslim Brotherhood political party
Set band together to resist the rising
Empower from the extreme right-wing
National
Right that's the plot of one of the driving forces of
The plot of this
Fiction novel novel there's a right-wing government suppressed
Sing everybody the type that somebody like Paul Joseph Watson would appreciate
And then they banned
Together the Muslim Brotherhood in the left
Until Paul is taking
That as a no
Attack on the
Real world right way
I don't I look
Some people inside the book itself
To be like fairly islamophobic and
Some troubling tropes but I'm not really entirely sure cuz I have
Read it I just read a
Description of the plot
I do know though unlike Paul Joseph Watson that this is a novel
Not a prediction
Things to come like
This dude looked in
The gods I like Alex claims to
This Saturday
Vision of the few
Future
That kind of it so you're telling me that it's a novel
Right
Pulses
Okay but
If you're right
That means that all those dragonlance novels I read when I was younger aren't going to come true oh no
Jordan
I bet
No
Happened in the past
That's not the future That's History
So Paul is
Just a real Realty
Piece of garbage
The French government literally
Before the first coronavirus lockdown
The ministry theme
Interior
And said that it shouldn't be enforced in these migrant
So again
Blissfully creating a separate Lowell weather
Enforcement the lockdown.
Oppression imposed
Is north
You can hear Paul's angle on this story which
She's a poor migrant communities are being Exempted from the Draconian in fascist
Accruals that the white man of Europe were being subject
Higher class
The people to the global
Interesting Lee there's another side to the story and that is the one based in reality where the
Particularly in France
Allocate funds
To provide assistance to
Poor migrant community
Nongovernmental organizations were working to advocate for
Establishment of mobile clinics near areas where migrants
Camp but their appeals generally went on
John heard
The accommodation of people experiencing homeless
Tragic at the beginning
The pandemic and they're still serious issues now
You can see how Paul is rewriting governmental negligence toward the vulnerable population
It's actually secretly being them getting favorable
That sucks
Also how do you
How do you force a hawk a stay-at-home order to people who experience a coma
What are you even talking
I don't know if there's anything more right-wing then
Having
White people ignore immigrants
And then blaming
Yep that's the right way up to
Play Sabaton.
Spell Alex drop something that I thought was really
Really interesting
Confused me
A lot
Hot potato salad
ABC Australia
That
You will get your freedom when you have your vaccine
The moment of freedom for you is when you get your vaccine
These are the quotes everywhere
And it gets even crazier
Top scientist epidemiologist you never coming out today
Yale medical doctors
Hospital
Telling people
We predicted that hear it
It is ladies and
Like your freedom comes when you get the vaccine
Somebody on a talking head show that was
Discussing how some people are not motivated
Goodbye the idea that you can
Text other people by getting vaccinated maybe appeal to people selfishness of getting people
Go to recognize the
Getting up
And I understand what this person saying I also think it's a misguided perspective by
I don't think
Think they're taking the advice
One person on CNBC
As if it's V
Google Alexa
Global position of enemy faction
I do but it's up to
People should take
The things that I say in
Extrapolate them and put them upon every single person
It's a little silly over and over again
It doesn't prove any point yeah that's annoying but I have no idea
Statistical majority people who are hospitalized now or their due to the effects
Sexy not from covid
And because he's not providing a source there's nothing I can
Can do with that
I would I would argue that if that were true
That would be the biggest news in the history of ever
I can
Jordan tell you that
55 and older
Divisor and moderna vaccines were 94% effective at preventing hospitalization
Which is
Produces day. Be happy to look at it but
At this point all available information
Asian points
The exact opposite
Set Direction
Yeah especially considering how sensationalized it is whenever things don't
Work
It's like you just said oh it's 94% effective at
Stopping hospitalization
But how many times have we read an article that says that but only but instead of saying 94
Affected they like
6000 people in the hospital now because of vaccines
And then you're like out of how many
You know I got it
You guys suck at
If that were true
Imagine how the sensationalized news world report that ship
Everyone dying
Alex worst Broadway
This dude very well
Is Mother Gaston and it's
Preacher for
From Calgary
Amazon Arthur powlowski
I forgot who I guess
So yeah talk about this
But we are we mentioned it
That he was on
Is the other preacher there's the greatest the other dick there's the grace Life Church was is the one where Alex is trying
How to get everyone to go another guy he wouldn't let people into
A bunch of
Complaints about them having
Services are not following covid
Right guidelines answer you just
We just want to
Talk to you about
That's what you become a preacher
It's freaking people out of it all the time good for you
He's on
We'll talk about this a little bit this time
But I wanted
Preacher
Thousand homeless people
We can you as his music as a little charge
By the provincial police and others
CA was on Monday
Other services are coming out this weekend
Any others
He said he's going to go
Places like Walmart
It's kind of interesting I'm not sure
Based on this interview if he's
Saying that he's going to do this like go preach at a Walmart on April 27th the last time he was on
Alex said
You've got to
Walmart's field
Bacon
My parents
The church
Because that's against the law.
I can go with my church with my friend
Do Ikea and have a
Walmart
Say you're going go in and then hold a church service there you'll be allowed to question they'll throw you out that be great
Great stunts
The reality is that this preacher has taken out
What is advice for a stomach bug
A couple days prior
Yeah I remember my favorite parts of the Bible where where where when
Jesus got ideas from the devil in the devil is like man
You should really try that out that's great
I remember there was a couple chapters that really stuck out to me when I was a kid a Bible
I will study about God making dang
Dank memes totally total
Absolutely
So this Preacher Man
I don't I don't care for the way this guy thinks
Inspectors received
Permission
From a judge
To use any Force necessary
This story is no
7 billion names
They have found a judge
That is a family of Bill Gates I don't know
David Gates the judge here in Calgary
What
7 billion
Upser
Grow up
There are not
Dad we have had to reuse a few
Is it can I lose Jasper 900,000
The health department guy
To enter his church
And
The person who signed it was gate
What
What are the odds
Probably zero and critical incident
You know I'd like if I was in it at church and I heard him
Just go like
And it's the same last name is Bill Gates
What is that tell you I be like oh no I guess religion is fake you personally are so
Go stupid
I don't believe
Believe in God anymore in my faith
You're too dumb no
To be re-evaluated you're suggesting that all people named gates are related even if it's just for fun
Still crazy
So Alex and this dude
They get to
Discussing how the left right the last
So it's us
Is there using
The budget
Jordan order to get the police to attack
That's what's going on
Why are the police so happy in your area
And in other areas
I will other churches to put
Fences up around
Soviet Russia
Because the mayor that homosexual
The police
20 million dollars
And then after about 2 I should get
What the police shutting down churches
Not stopping
That's exactly what
Right now
Hoobly
If that is on the table I will absolutely hold the police officer
That is on the table
Somebody let me hold the police hostage I will do it right f****** now just a little bit though
I was on the table
Are you got these
This
This guy
He's worried about
Zone
Don't repeat what he said about the
Yeah yeah we're all worried
Destroyed
I think that's
My biggest fear
You don't ask yourself question that is
When you going to rise up
I mean Wednesday
Where are you
You going to rise up
Never going again this until people say no
That's right
What we know about bullies
Stop bullying until
You stop the bullying and that's for the day
Get out no
Get out
For the New York Times and Homeland Security
Prices for Christian
Vaccine
You're off.
Program
See what I'm saying
More people
Then
Virus
Hoo-boy
Whataburger
I don't know what are we going to have I don't know it sucks
The very interesting perspective
Deceived
Actually I think the only thing that I really find it
Nothing about this is how how much it may
Make sense like
Alex started
They sort of their closing down all the
These churches get with the grace life
Iran from Rebel news
And she wouldn't go along with his like
Everyone needs to calm right right alright and I don't think I was fun for all
No so now he's found Artur pawlowski
Yahoo is like everybody got a rise up
I don't need any of your Rebel media reporting bulshit I want to stoke
Plastic terrorist I think that this guy is exactly what I was
Totally talking about the grace Life Church
This guy is
Exactly what Alex wants
So apparently
Alex gets a lot of emails
About
Big medical news
That
Never
Never really makes it to the show and actually I think that's good because they would just be anecdotal stories that show who would be meaningless
Our email is full of.
Doctors and lawyers and teachers and nurses
Where they are giving people shot and people are dropping dead
The vaccination centers
It's not just from the Kobe shot
Show me the flu shot for killing a bunch of people
Going on here
Yes yes we knew.
When you the gates
Becky wants to eliminate 6
A billion people
Now I got
Judge
Issuing
Got the rights of freedom
We know something is going on at Grisham
As always being
In opposition to genocide
Have you
Please send all the proof
Yeah it's sort of never
Call Sobo
Come on
Rocks in Georgia
Yeah man I really don't think that I would like my Christian preacher adding a little
Georgia guidestone in there every now and again you know you don't people added
Making another reference to
Do I got this judge
So
The kind of guy though who's not going to be.
By this sabbath state
What's the Bible verse Pastor I forget
The Gates of Hell shall not
Christchurch
That's exactly that's why tomorrow I'm opening the church
Tomorrow I'm going to be preaching
Let the whole world see what is
Happening
Contra virus
And at least let there be thousands of people with
Tell us what time and where
Website as well
Interesting Lee Orchard have his services
Next day on this Saturday
How to get pigs and go well
I'll just be here from an article in the Calgary Herald
Community members living on living near Street Church say preacher Artur pawlowski and his followers of threat
Brighton neighborhood violin
After speaking out
Against the congregation to disregard for public health measures
And their hateful rhetoric always been against
Violence
From this article
Our neighbors here have been threatened
For at least seven weeks by these anti-maskers were violating Health regulations
And it's spreading messages of hate
Said Michelle Robinson who lives in the neighborhood
Is a very similar thing to what happened after the big uproar surrounding
Grace Life Church
H2
People did show up there and who knows who was because of the Rebel news reporting order
Some bloggers Alex who knows exactly
But
Elizabeth Simmons the deputy director of the Canadian anti-hate Network told CTV this
After quota monitoring
The crowd
It would be accurate to say that the event attract
Conspiracy minded individuals for sure
This is important to understand
There's a reason why Alex is trying to ramp up in height and
The tension surrounding churches that refused
Cooperate with public health measures
This isn't intentional strategy meant to create a stand
That will lead to a galvanizing moment
For the extreme right
Business super dangerous situation even if it doesn't escalate any further
The neighbors of this church are having to deal with it
Incredibly unfair Circa
Come stand assistant preacher
Clothing is a creating a
The Powder Keg in their front lawn
Like it's just inappropriate
I need to I need to understand that this is an intentional thing whether or not Alex is sitting there with a whiteboard
Trying to dry out how to create
A martyr
Conflagration
Put a billion I'm putting a million-dollar bounty on whoever
Can start a holy war
It is
He's trying to ramp up
Pretensions that would lead in that direction and hoping
Cooking for the worst
Yeah well I mean whiteness didn't work
Working America so let's try religion in Canada
Think is what he's trying to do
It's
It's pretty upsetting and I
I hope for
You know all these these situations
Navigate
Delicately
Good luck
So Alex
It's done with this dude
And take it back to the news
Hugo
F****** bombshell
Are butterflies
I'm working on for a while
About
9 minutes out
May 2021
Spring 2021
Or just break
Total proof
Joe Biden has dementia
Handle
Wally has eventually stole the election
It's just unbelievable
So I've so many guess I'm going to have time to Arizona show today
Really
Do you have proof weiwei video that prove
Does Joe Biden both has dementia
And stole the election
But you don't have time to
No time to time
I got a proof of it
Fasting
We have
Perhaps the most
Piece of proof
Of the 21st
The game is being played here is Detroit Drive traffic to his website
Yeah that's
Videos of this isn't worth his time on the actual show
You do IUI
What one thing that people haven't really gotten
Me with yet is
Why I should care if Joe Biden
You know like
I kind of
Don't care if their Weekend at Bernie's in
Him
Right like so far
It's it's like I don't want them on Ark
I don't want a president whose
Doing all of that stuff fine if he's dead
I'm fine if he's dead and they've got him enough like a scarecrow stick figure thing behind
I'm out and deep faking his speeches I'm fine with the I feel like
You speak
For at least
The segment of the population
I think we should get some polling on that
He think everybody would be fine if you're just weakened it burned as they don't know what the temperature of the country is
Will be fine with a Weekend at Bernie's president
We'll see we'll see it let's put it up put it out on Twitter pull out
So anyway back
Statistic
Sorry sir
Do you know about statistics
Bombshell
60% of new covid patients are
Vaccinate
Harvey rice
Medical doctor
On new patients diagnosed with Coronavirus
More than half have been vaccinated
Having autoimmune disease that they're having allergic responses
And the hospital's retold Paulette covid
Course they test positive
Because the PCR test is set up
Just like
Terra Nostra
About to drop a little bit of a
Specific piece of information I can tell you what he's talking about
He almost certainly just saw this in a meme that was going around on social media now it says no idea who Harvey righteous or
Where that quote
Comes from
It turns out that it was from an interview that Rice did on
Bannon podcast
I swear you said quote
What clinicians are telling me is more than half of the new covid cases they're seeing
How to treat
Is people who've been vaccinated
They've estimated 60% of new page
Since they've been treating have been people who have been vax
This is
Best secondhand estimations base
Presumably on anecdotal information being thrown around on Steve bannon's podcast
A lot more trustworthy than
Data
According to the CDC as of April 20th there were 7150
87 reported cases of people who are vaccinated
Who still contracted
Covid
That's out of 87 million people who have been vaccinated so that is not really that's
Surprising of a number
A CNN article from earlier in April had to
Figure at approximately
5800 breakthrough cases
Of which only 396
To those required hospitalization suit
Hard to believe
That these numbers could be
Accurate
It's tough whenever you're working on numbers that are such a
Huge scale because what we should be saying is
396 only 396 needed hospitalization we have Miracles we make me Rich
We create Miracles and all this
God bullshittin
You keep talking about
Is insane because only 370 think we need ice
Cp2 make a song about this
So the numbers do not match up unless there's more than a second-hand story being told on Bannen
Broadcast I'm just going to ignore this
But it's important to recognize that
This is the level of backing
Can go to claim needs to have for Alex to take it as gospel
As long as it lines up with a narrative
He's currently profiting off of
The only thing that really matters
Is that all about
Podcast
Regardless of whether or not
Previously was
A very respected Yale medical doctor
The moment you go on
Steve Bannon
Very and respected are removed from my baby
Vocabulary jail also published something
Nephew number of months back in August that was like
Critiquing
And the denouncing his
Fervent support for hydroxychloroquine Isaiah covid cure
Yeah yeah I'll put out a look at this f******
An a****** sorry
Weather Reno
So Alex believes that vaccines are going to be mandatory
Man he says something I think is really weird
Once they get
But you wouldn't do it so they're still covid-19
What makes a computer
I know when you died the other viruses are things are actually releasing
6 months from now
2 years from now
Humans will probably die in 6 months
And I are in a month
Humans
That's math
Transitive property of Fire
A human dies in 6 months a year
I hate you I hate you so much
What you doing
I hate you so much
I hate you so much damn talk to you. I hate you
You
Yeah Alex
Can say that you were supposed to keep me away from that s*** no because it's important to recognize that.
He thinks dog years are literal
That takes your breath away
Yeah if a dog dies in a so he thinks that
When we talked about dog years when I just talked
About relative
Have time that's banned for life
He thinks that we literally mean that's the only way I can make that
Approach this from a number of different Direct
Because
I don't know if he knows this but different animals have different biology
Nope not true
Everybody either toxic 27
All Creatures some respond
Animals have
It's just timing
I want
I just can't today I just can't real good
It's 80s
Good stuff
There's something admirable
About a man
Who can so consistently say something
That floors me
Yeah and confidently and he repeated us multiple examples of how animals have different life
Multiple examples
Of the same wrong
Example that may
Makes no sense
Good stuff
So
His remarks
For Congress
I need mentioned something
To the effect of white
White supremacy is Terrorism
And
Alex and Ani
This just went up on infowars.com I told you this was coming yesterday nobody else was talking about it with your buddy
They told you
Who's bad
White supremacist
To be clear I don't think
I would say
Support any new laws
For domestic terrorism
That the idea of taking white
Supremacy seriously as a terrorist
6th right
Is something that is a long overdue
It is also not surprising why
Tucker and Alex
Where are the people on the Vanguard of their attire
You know
Their money is made by white
Victimhood
Yeah your best bet there for them is like it's a slippery slope argument but even then
You're arguing for white to Prattville
Like DIA
That's what you guys are doing you're not
Cuz it don't pointer they like
Well what we should do is focus on the extreme Elements of Life
None of that
None of that is like it you're talking about white people I will kill you it's really
Interesting that you say that
Because I think it even because
Becomes more clear and figures on the issue
Adam Schiff
The rest of the Chinese spies on his committee
Predominant
Nationalist
Broccoli
Because
Politically
But some of the folks are part
We have to stop there really quick
Because I think that Alex
Just tried to Divine white nationalist as just
Not global
That's not good
No
No I don't believe that he doesn't know that that is a compound noun that is
Specific meaning problem there are some people like
It was one of them
We Believe doesn't know what white nationalism
He thinks he's a nationalist who happens to be white
And that makes you understand
Alex
Does
Died do not confuse
Discuss
Ideas
Couching that there is the opposite of global
That's a problem
Yeah yeah that is interesting because
Dave is astonishingly stupid
Yeah but Alex is stupid
Astonishing
Yeah
I want to say
Giada CIA
Cyndaquil team
What's that mean
Is it
It is the Twilight of our Republic it is
That's not that's not necessarily what that means
To be clear what's going on is that Alex's defending white supremacy and white nationalism because he knows that it's a part of his power block
He doesn't like the people are discussing how these things are
Problem
Unwilling to separate himself
For my nationalism because it's his bread-and-butter
People keep saying that I'm a white nationalist
Android
Way wrong now I would just like my supporters to
Continue sending me Nazi coin
That's the new official branded
Cryptocurrency I only accept conflict diamond
I also think
Actually thinks that swalwell's name is swallows well
That was something that was the name that Rodger gave it to him when a couple years back when Rodger was mad at Adam Schiff
They have that blow up
It's just doesn't realize that that's not his real name
As a joke
Can we live in a
Dictatorship
When
The man who is telling me we are living in a dictatorship
Just told me that he has proof
The dictator of said dictatorship
Is
Dementia
And animated video
Yeah I wouldn't really be a
It weird one would be a strange one
Speaking of weird ones
We shouldn't be seduced into that
Thinking that because we're white weed ride
And you don't win an argument
Manipulating definition
Do you agree Norm that you're a racist
Well now
Well that's because you're a race
Lenore Pattinson's back to be a really sensitive
I guess
Just to remind people in cake
Look I'm not noted stand-up comedian I'm not saying that Norm is racist
Because he says he's not racist
I think he's racist because he doesn't think I like the best two weeks ago
Buick standup
Comedy the other night at a small club in Connecticut
And I ended my wrist
The following hey you know I tried to buy
Insurance the other day
Assurance is what you need if you're white Matthews I'm reading the paper
Wrong with this country is my fault
How am I going to pay for all of this
Insurance
And we're at a point where
Sort of humor
It isn't necessarily farcical any longer
I think in comedies are some things that are evergreen like I could probably hear some
Mitch Hedberg one-liners
I've heard a hundred times that still make me laugh
Guy tried to give me the insurance for a donut I said I don't need insurance for a donut
Still am but I used to
Racist Mitch Hedberg of the new character
Norm Norm hamburger
Norfolk
Don't let him tell you I just cuz you're why you're not right
Directions to Daiso
Norm is a is a real
Sensitive gentle
Escalated
Okay I'm sorry I've got to get lots of that for a while
If you get inspired please feel free
Wants to pair up
Francis Boyle
The guy who
Directed 28 Days Later
To talk about the Wuhan lab and
All these people are not
The scientist and what have you
He wants to get Francis Boyle and Norm
Come together
Have a lawsuit against
Sure do it
Yeah let's get it done too that's pretty funny
Because
Alex explains to Norm the vaccines are dangerous and Norms response is hilarious
I got to get him with more passes our lawyer so that we can go with this
False a religious exemption
First Amendment Shropshire BS totally reasonable
Shoehorning
Totally different system in
And called it a vaccine
Why don't you want to preach at your Norm
I just really pissed about this
We Salute You
I got to get you a doctor boil tomorrow
Clock tomorrow
I'm going to send it to you imma get you his number
Imma stop
I don't know enough
Intelligent
What it what what you're telling me is that
Significant portions of what has
Been sold in the name of Public Health is actually a
For something else
And handsome
Implicit dangers
That we're not being warned about
If that is in fact true that's an outrageous
Violation of trust
Look what we have
Laws in the United States
It says a person is
Free to refuse medical treatment
And in order to accept
They must give informed consent
No I took the
Double-shot to Pfizer nobody warned me about any gene therapy or anything like that so as far as I know
I was taking a bath
Maxine that was
Tested
Under exigent circumstances to meet an emergency
Think I'm alright
Maybe I'll be here tomorrow maybe I won't
But what you're telling me is
It's that is is base
Basically paid better attention to what's going on and I'm ashamed
Marathon runner SIU Masala during the breakout cuddlefuck up
I saw you eating a salad I thought you hated
I love you baby
You eating a salad I love the idea that I like all this
I got the vaccine
No
Oh no
It's funny when people take Alex
Seriously and try to restate the things back
And try and act like they give a s***
Oh I took
The vaccine and now I'm worried I was so scared
I had no idea that the guy
Who show
I have been on
Nobody's distantly
For the past
Several years
Said that vaccines had something inside them that could kill you
Breaking information about the guy who weirdly on his show a whole bunch
Has been
Eeyore saying don't get this vaccine I got both of them I got him immediately
I could drop dead at any moment
Goodnight will say that he has the acting chops with most
Comedians that I've met
Sensitive
That's right in there
Oh yeah
Another guest after after Norm bales
Cuz he's so worried just got to get this
He's got he's going out there on
I imagine that's what what you figure
You're that does sound right so he has Alex now has another
Person on
And who who
So doctor
Thank you doctor
By over here is a
Charlotte
Play ZZ Ward
University Hospitals and Clinics
So Carrie Maday is not a prestigious Doctor Who's been right about all this vaccine stuff the way out
Going to try to present her
Peter qanon lunatic who's committed a series of public embarrassed
That the audience that people like her and Alex are cultivated their praying to ignore
An article in Vice pointed out of
Particularly sad in
Carrie just believe in whatever bulshit she saw online
This past summer she was convinced that a long debunked website advertising the cannibal Club restaurant in Los
Was in fact a real Eatery serving human flesh
We taste like pork she tweeted dear God help us change the world for the better
Terry is an osteopath which on its own isn't necessarily a bad sign however being an osteopath on Alex's
So who also believes qanon should means
To me that this is
Is a person pretend
Yeah I was really I was really fascinated when she was like see
What happen
When's is if you eat a
Ferret but then go to the cannibal Club it takes
The year to digest
True person it only takes a week see it's reverse
Situations
It makes perfect sense
And also I don't know if you remember this
Cuz she has popped up on the
Before but her big decline
Wasn't saying that like covid vaccines are going to kill people will rise to prominence is based around a very not true claim that
The MRNA would alter people's DNA
This in turn would
DNA into something that would be patented in advance
Someone else's intellectual property
It's a real dumb
That's what you wrote that's the way of she wrote in
I am really bummed
It really bums me out that these people don't understand
There are way cheaper way
For corporations to steal money from all of us
Absurdly complex
They're stealing your money at a regular low boring level
As long as things like
Check cashing places exist or at least
Exist on regulated the way they are right whenever need to create
So stupid
I mean you're you're evil Bill Gates who's the most evil man in the world
Who hates everybody is creating this vaccine to kill everybody is against
F****** making a generic version of the vaccine
Gibby sent around the world
He's actually doing the things that they say he's doing
You're not doing
Yeah it's complicated
Carrie is on and she has some bad news
About.
In one day I asked
My members I said does anyone have any problems with their menstrual cycle and fertility Etc
Send
Being around someone who's been
Vaccinated and I had over 700
Responses within 6 to 12 hours
It's unbelievable
This is anecdotal and I do not
Press the reporting of weirdo carryminati followers online
This is just one of the new trendy things that are pushed
It's the idea that people who
Vaccinated or shedding diseases that are affecting people around us
This is why Mike Adams insist people stay away from vaccinated people and why that dumped school in Florida ban teachers who have been back
Akinator
A recent article in the New York Times deals with this ain't no answer
Certain terms
Vaccinated people can't shed anything because there's nothing to be shedding
Dr. Celine gounder
I am Texas disease specialist at Bellevue Hospital Center
Remember president
Transition
Home Coronavirus
Go to the people who said virus are people who have covid
So if you want to prevent yourself or others from
Virus the best
Way to do that
Vaccinated so you don't get covid testing
If he wants to make those conspiracy steaks he's basically going to need to create
A new theory of Medicine
Which would be interesting
I've got a new theory of Medicine
For you,
The Lord's
Will
So what about what does God think about
Nanotech
Another thing that is a very interesting possibility is
It's because we're using nanotechnology because they have the ability to
To be like antennas or uses biosensors
What if
They actually are emitting some kind of
Frequency out there
This is what's on SyFy but it's a
Possibility
Not to sound dumb
What if
What if he's shot
Noatak into us
What if
Damn
Alright
Now hear me out on the
None of our left
Speederia
All of this everybody has
1 ft
Right foot only the left foot
All Nanobots
Created by the devil
How does this what is this half
To do with the human
Genome Project
Being made
To get Nephilim DNA
Well that's where they got the nephelym DNA they removed all of our fee
Is this bastard
With your b*******
Yeah I really can you just had Steve Quayle on the other day like what are we doing
Struggling with all of
The bulshit you guys are expect
Take me to and it's a lot
It's a lot
These are really serious concern
Now I was kind of surprised to learn
The Kerry is still worried about people having
Patented DNA
And everybody needs to know this
That is
Any of these synthetic genes which the Spy
Protein has
Synthetic genes in them
If the synthetic genes
It's integrated into our genome which
Can happen because we have enzymes in our body that can do that
If that happened
You and the owned
By whoever owns that
Patents overnight
The Supreme Court Justices ruled that a human being
And Beyond
If they have a synthetic gene or genome inside of
Interesting interesting interesting decision for Justice John Roberts to of
Wait are you
What's a court decision
I would like to know
Supreme Court
Look I don't find this person
All that info
I think that she is a coon on weirdo who has a bunch of a really dumb ideas that aren't based on
Anyting
But
This interview devault
Okay and it turns into
A story
Of her getting inducted into
To the globalist
Cult or something
Unclear
On
Clear all right
Now you're selling me
Here we go
Describe that meeting where this whole scientific dictatorship
Tried recruiting
Yes this was actually a business owners meeting on VIP bus
I sent you the location our cell phones were jammed this is around 2,000
And we were locked in the building until the meeting was done and this was
People seeing and etcetera etcetera I was a small fish
I didn't hear that
Talked about how they were going to change it modify
The behavior of the people of Georgia
With using their smart device
The health app on there and when
Somehow getting didn't tell us how
A substance inside of their body that would be used
Biosensors
The ideas they felt people here are too racist and they're not amenable to different cultures so they took it upon themselves
How to change people
And they
Inside these injections because that's how I learned about them
They said
Thoughts your emotions
If you're lying by a voice inflection app
Also they knew if you're lying by
Polygraph test with your sweat glands they can do that
Also your blood sugar level your life drawing
Breathing I'll so you know what you're having
Sucks they are interested in that if you're
Drinking alcohol after taking drugs they know everything about you
Literally they said they could do it
Analyzes data and they had an algorithm that a computer would
Being charged up
And every time you lied even a little white lie about where you were
The smartphone would know it immediately by these parameters and give you an instant repercussion
I then also overload say one two three months all the lies with the added up
And then you would be considered either of good human or bad human in the computer with a lot you
Social credit system
Or cryptocurrency
You said this on my show this meeting happened
Man
Hubble
Yeah
I wonder like
If I were in
The position that she is in
1 ways that I might make myself seem a little bit more credible house that provide
Details
What's the name of this organization who else was there
CNN
What
Why was CNN there you said was he in English
Smiles
What does that mean
Okay you never there okay
The goal is to make people less racist that's why they have CNN
Truth
Siri go to MSNBC
Shouldn't the story be that every time you're racist you lose points in your credit score else isn't only
You lie what the f***
He's going on. If you're lying about being racist
You will be shocked
Romello
Right
Higher Love
I love
Confidence
And the worry
With which she tells the story
People
Really just
Figuring out how magic works and using it in any and every pot
Because all of that you just said it
The magic yeah I would assume that what you went to was like
Some kind of a get rich
Motivational seminar or something like that
Like one time I went to a Cutco
Needing accidentally
Yeah
And I was the same kind of
Can't leave
Maybe that's
I don't know this this all just seems like nonsense
Timeshare because that's basic when your presentation eventually you're going to think
They're trying to kill everyone
Oh no they're going to try to make
And I bet that you were saying something races then someone's like a calm down
Trying to make people this week
Car right Sunway Alex's
Super into this story because of course
They tried to get him
Population
So Alex revealed something else here that I was unaware of
Go back to how they were cruising this cuz I do have a lot of roots
Do they have your eyes closed
Obviously not disclosing anyone
Because they did this on 9/11
Tacoma day before it was an emergency
They put them all at 6 a.m. in there
Jumbotron TVs the towers being blown up
We don't need that they told him this day
They followed orders
The way
Secret
11 inside
Way way way way way was this
The day before or was it on 9/11
Brought before
And they had a nice evening that I like a little mixer
Right and then the next morning they get up there all in line for the Continental
Hold on one second
9/11 happening
Now let's go
Follow order
The story that I heard
Boy I don't even like
I've seen Loose Change I don't remember that in there
Different things happened in the intervening time. Between when they did and did not happen
Very weird
So she talks a little bit more about this
This meeting
This is so sad
Stupid
Well I didn't really know what I was getting into I thought this is just email from more for political reasons is a good idea to join
Play nidus for a year
Three different people in
Courage man finally I went to
The first meeting which I just described which
I was completely taken aback
I got no one prepared me for that
I tried to leave the building and they laughed at me
And they said go ahead when they unlocked
The doors my cell phone still didn't work and I
I didn't know where my
Car was obvious
And there was a non-disclosure in general that was signed but not for that particular meeting
But did you not understand
And then decided to try to bring you in real first-level wow
Yes and
I don't care if I had a non-disclosure in the general sense because
These are crimes against humanity
That's why there wouldn't be one
Yeah that was
Just a regular old pyramid scheme
Disclosure agreement to do not cover criminal activity everyone f****** knows that yeah
How would you ever
If you were running a
Secret
Taking over the world trying to control people with anti-racism the app
It will monitor their sweat and
Dock their pay if I was going to turn the person in but then before I could testify against
He married me so it was against the law for me to testify against Ball Z movies
I was going to blow the whistle on a Hitler but I'd signed addendum
How you know you win some you lose I told him I told him
Ndaa
Ironclad
That's the part of the supervillain
Suck stories that are two
Just so
So much contra
Inviolable contract law
Dealing with the literal Devil Himself
Known for deception somehow
Contract law inviolable
Almost
Certain this was a
Better now that's absolutely a make way too many times
This is Nigeria JD's
Yeah
So here's what we doing everything makes sense but
There's a year
Yaakov of like
People
Okay you should come to this Tupperware party or whatever and yeah it's really cool
It's not you're not
Not selling anything what you're doing is you just get a discount whenever you purchase something
And then if other people use your numbers
They'll get a discount
But you'll get a little bit of that
The globalist
They're like busing into like a Convention Center or whatever makes total sense
God if you want to leave because I want to
People to
It seem like they're giving up
Help something's are foolish to leave
Everything is
That is it
Exactly how it works.
I love how Alex
Get so excited
About it as opposed to
To dealing with this critically like
There's no f****** way
Happened like you said it did
Absolutely
I think is really thought about her
Now we come to the end of this and
What's that does not surprise me.
Grand Theft Auto
Initially
It's so important that you had to insert your own personal stories into
Seems like now in his hour of me
Dad in the most crucial juncture of the mouth
Greenberg is Dunham dirty
Something new and I know he's lying
Shocking shocking
Was not covered
So weird weird
It seems like that would be
Opticover like
Alex and Paul Joseph Watson anger at Muslims or
Ignoring highlight away
Sensitivity about whiteness or
Doctor
There's people with DNA I peed and now everybody's going to die because
Yeah they still blood
It just one of those things too that I've I've started to recognize a notice about these older episodes that I've lost
Listen to Like These 2003 ones one of the real changes
In that I've seen is like
There are so fewer guests
Back then
And I think it's B
Because Alex don't have to do s***
Like you can eat a sandwich
Or you can let me
Dum Dums talk
Hey I'm like
It's just so easy for him
To have
5 gas
Stoner show as opposed to
Covering
Anything
No senioritis
In his defense
Yeah
It sucks
Your show sucks
The people you work with suck and you suck
Of course it's
Yeah you should be having a bad
Bedtime
Come to the end of this
Sam's man
Just embarrassing
What about this
Episode where the Bears
Anybody who was
Looking at this from the outside would be aware that news
Set broken that's super relevant to Infowars
Snooze
Have doubtless
Already these RV saying that Matt gaetz
Text party
He loves to party
It seems like
Kind of thing
Might want to follow up on
Especially considering
One of your
The on-again off-again
Employees
Is that in the mix well and here's the here's the funniest part
It's not funny
I get to really f***** up
Situation what's funny about Alex
And them being so insistent
On this is a guyot
Just likes to party
Is the the more.
Details you find out the more you're like
He didn't know she was 17 at
The time
Oh you know where that kind of s*** happens
If you're a guy that likes to party all the time
Maybe you don't ask questions first
It sure seems to be a reasonable situation instead of one Warrior
Making it so ridiculous with this guy could be guilty of this crime
The story
Anthony
Sex workers
Stigmatized
Consenting and everything
That's that's not but
Anything I would like for you
Shame anybody about
I'm more in
Interested in the selling of Pardons
Here's the funny thing about that
Are you almost at like I saw that and I was like oh that's totally a crime
And no one's going to follow up on that part
They're going to be like gay
Get them
Get them not the
Everyone knew that Trump was selling Barney
Vermont
Everybody knew that
You could
It's about it
Poor
People in Trump's orbit we're selling influence
The other is
Is 88
It appears to be what
Fly that conversation
Was about
That's f***** up man that's one of those things where
Trump would be like yeah if you weren't trying to sell
Stuff off of
Of my abilities
Is I would be disappointed in you your shame on you
I'm stealing
You know what I'm
Confident Alex
Going to cover this on Monday
You are way too confident you are way too comfy.
Until Rodger maybe get the rest it again
Cesar incendies bed frame
Texting for hey I got 250 rephrase that
Never met the guy
Never heard of
Its.com
If you could please find a local charity or bail Fund in your area
No I'm Leo I'm dzx
Close
Yeah I'm Daryl.
The sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color