Damn important
I have great respect for Tenaya Lodge like I'm sick of them posing as if through the good guy
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
To get together drink novelty beverages worship at the Carlton
Celine or the altar of Celine
Smooth intro
Alex
I will
Jordan
Nice to meet you
Remember pleasantries out of the way
Might be obviously the release of my super secret project
Posey want John
Believe it
John
Probably
Handwriting might be an issue with John
Say if you are someone with bad handwriting who sent us
Pathfinder rulebook
To you later Rubik's and all sorts of other
Like figurine let me not cool not like
You know it's not like a Warhammer figure he's a little stand
Campaigns all this really cool stuff
Figure that one out eventually
Just to give a little behind the scene until
I got overwhelmed
Bye
The number of
And I said Jordan pisses on you
You lyrics
You need to finally do sober
This is your job now
Figure out what to do with it
I couldn't handle the idea of using cracking one of those books
And then getting lost
Because I probably would
No one needs that
Yeah I rather
It's very hard to do
So we
We decided to do as close to a Pathfinder
Champagne suppliers by this
Yeah yeah
So we've got you then we've got our brilliant friend
Marty and Sarah love wrestling and then we have the lovely and talented
Who is absolutely fantastic and we are all playing
Campaign that I wrote
Yeah
I mean we're not really playing
In the game
Yeah the first episode of it is on our patreon right now but it's not like
Unpaywall record
Just a reminder everything on our patreon
Behind
Projects in Gasport
Yeah but
Wings places
Joyfully this kind of dovetails into my brakes by first of all of him semi bright spot I really did enjoy
It's great
It's certainly outside of the realm of what I normally am
I'm comfortable with in terms of
Airplane characters or whatever but
Everyone character is so fun silly together a bunch of middle-aged people who have never
Stand-up City
I am excited to see where it goes
Also in relation to this
Pathfinder books
Everything's game
I realize that we you need
Catch up a little bit on
The mailbag yeah we were going to do like some more bonus episodes we haven't really been able
Go to bradlyn now this secret project has been unveiled
Begin that's behind
Zip the mailbox
Characters
From a bar at the same time
We are not going to make Thomas the devil
Come after anybody
Also Jordans
We're we missed this one a little ways back
Who sent that to a little poster of likes
Chicago venues
Yeah it's that you do all that
Another person hear a Sara M
Excited about this thing that came in a little while back
I was asked
Some honeys
They were there there
Metal honey
Is the name of the company
I see honey in like a really
The floury Elixir one
They're fantastic and so I wanted to say thank you to Sarah
Thanks for those
And also the hot sauce of the month
His continued to roll an absolutely delightful
I don't think we've had a Doug some of not been as good as others
But I got to say this this one the Marie Sharp's the other habanero 14
From Belize
They came in
Pat is Ben
Sweetie those ones are pretty in my wheelhouse yeah
In terms of like an everyday sauce those have been
Been pretty
Pretty heavy in the rotation
I feel like there was actually one in autos of the month it was kind of disappointing but I don't remember what it was
There was one called Illuminati
Like a naughty like that
I don't think I like that one
Maybe it was just bitter about the pain though
Are you being unless you were in the illuminate let you know like unless you were like Jay-Z or Beyonce I don't think it's
Defense
Do you know I also I also should say this came with some X
Can pandas figure out the honeys
So cool thing that apparently is a signature of the metal honey brand
Would you have course I certainly need more candy
Repeat cast
That's what they're going for also I'm way overdue checking the mailbox
They're probably some more coming up in the near future
Jordans
We got an episode
Yeah we do and I got to say
It was difficult
To decide what
To do
And I want to walk
You threw my thinking
The first thing I thought of was I don't care about Alex's take
Akon Bill Gates getting
I don't care about anything to do with Bill Gates getting a divorce I think it might be interesting to see him try and weave that in
To somehow it's part of the globalist
Why I'm sure
I don't I don't know I don't
I think it's also a little bit
No matter what it'll be disappointing
I don't care for it much
I also started to realize that like our show right now is becoming like
How much does
Goddamn anti-vaxxer
Like
OneNote
To certain extent
I got I get I get
I just burped
Buy it
At the same time
Sure we've been looking
Had a realization
You know where we are in 2003
May
Yeah
May 7th
Which is the Davis episode comes out
What is a rare opportunity
If we go back to 2003 today we can cover something 18 years ago to the day
Okay well now we have
I felt like I had to
Yeah there's nothing we can do but that so today we're going over May 7th
Everything the music was revolutionary it was happening people are having meaningful conversations
Alma Street
The heady time in America
3 Stankonia or the love below
I want to watch that was around then around that but I could be wrong
Outkast albums in case you were wondering
Think it might have been
When was Bombs Over Baghdad wideout was Adam
That was
I don't know
Bombs Over Baghdad
Okay will do probably around 2000
I'm more of a the time in my life that I would consider the salad days are these southernplayalisticadillacmuzik
That's really where I live
Fair not fair
Tomorrow
Get down to business on our trip to the Past
Looks like a little more Jordan to say what up
Does new walk
So first written Hannah this is for you
This is for you the goddamn
The shadow to you Jordan because of baseball season
The goddamn Pac-Man wanted me to let you know go Padres
You're not about to walk
I'm a policy wonk goddamn Pac-Man
Know the Padres are
Fernando tatis is one of the most exciting and probably maybe the best player and they stole you do well when I say
Do you Darvish from the Cubs what I mean more as the Rick
Ricketts family through you Darvish into the ocean and was like San Diego you can have him
For peanuts
Dad
Alright
Text Taylor and I'm definitely a witch
I'm a policy wonk
Sprinkler
The parrotheads
I resisted this
Shoutout mostly because Mike has
Secret agenda
Night is to see what kind of overlap there is
Between our podcast Phantom
Jimmy Buffett fans and I'd rather not know
I hope not too
Next
Technocrat
Alright William P thank you so much
And also
The baby Blaze
What's about Blaise
Who is a punk
You're not with seconds
Business
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
Blaze
I don't know why I've lost my mind I just had to double-check again
Of course it's not on Stankonia it's on Bob
It's on babe Bombs Over Baghdad
What am I stupid feel like I'm losing my mind
Okay
So Jordan we start here at the beginning of the day the show as Alex
To the beginning
And I have got this
Pieces that I'm working on.
Continues
To see more and more accurate
And that is that
Joe Rogan stole the word powerful from Alex
Broadcast
Rihanna
If you were born on the date of this episode was recorded you can
Vote
Best powerful
Powerful
I've never done what would this what say
18th
Anniversary what would that be in any
Well I don't I don't know.
What do you mean
Well I mean The Aviator Millennium is 1018 while he'll
People without their aid
I thought you meant like going to like it's a paper anniversary or like a gold
What's the what what's that one
Think I don't know
Papyrus
I'm not in that list
There's a
The spatula here
I mean I could look
I could check
I don't care
Undoubtedly. Acclaim
You could take Joe Rogan
Going to small claims court for stealing
The intro of a show because of the powerful tree
Transmission you know I think they've gotten a lot from each other out of this situation
Text can be mad at Joe for what he's
Contributed in raid response for getting powerful
Furthers
Argument that I hate to say I kind of agree with this show is a sneaky snake
Petro powerful Sneaky Snake
Okay get rid of Alex
Alex has powerful over him could be
This might be looking to discover but I think we might have figured out
We got it we did a ruption age
This is why there's an intellectual dark web
JoJo stealing the word powerful
Oh well
Let's get into something
It's a little more meaty
By now admit the privately
The doctor
So for the last few days here in 2003 Alex has been touching on the story of the alleged Rescue of private Lynch
Exact position but it doesn't seem like there's much here passport
Saturday night clip
His position is that the rescue was all just
Hollywood theatrics and nothing
And more
The story of private land is actually a saint
Plastic example of the precise problem with what Alex Jones does for a living
And how easy it is to get seduced
Austin his way of thinking
For some background on March 23rd 2003 Lynch's Convoy was ambushed outside
Arena Rock
And she was taking off
11 of the other members of our group were killed in the Ambush and Lynch was taken to nearby Saddam
There she was treated
And on the evening of April 1st
She was rescued by US forces
From this point forward the story is one of
Sweet malpractice by the media
Where's sensationalism LED coverage
The story
Unnamed sources claim that you've been shot or stabbed but
What do reports came out
Doctors who said
Such wounds
Even as media Outlets ran with us
Sensationalize version the story other out
We're digging in
What was
And was not the truth
April 15th Outlet like the washing
Good post for beginning to critically examine their own initial coverage
And questioned whether their account was accurate
Washington Post headline
Whoops
Really should have done a better job on that one
More or less
Yeah it's
It's interesting and gradually
Things fell apart in the truth of matter came forward
When Lynch was taken to Saddam hospital she was given appropriate medic
Local treatment and when US forces arrived to rescue her
There weren't any wrecking forces there and much of
To the characterization of her is a rainbow type
Was based on Overdrive
What is Asian and misstatement
It's absolutely true that much of the media can play
F*** this story up
Horses that were pretty excited
But they were f****** it up
The war in Iraq at that point was not full of good news
I like the bush administrative
Administration would have wanted it
To be any idea that they would try to take this story and use it for their purposes definitely seems like what they did
If you read the house report that investigated the
The flow of information about the rest
Skew titled house report 1 10-8 58
You can definitely see instances of members of the Department of
Defense giving inaccurate information about the rescue
Which fed into the heroic drama that was
Was being sold by the media
Are you telling me that warmongering politicians
I'm not telling you that I'm not
And I think that's important
But in this report that there's one in
It's on April 2nd a brigadier general
Send Brooks a spokesperson for
Centcom
Told a press briefing quote
There was not a firefight outside the building I will tell you but there were fire fights outside of the building getting in and getting out
That was not true
Unless you take a very Broad
View of what
Getting in and getting out
Well we started the war a couple of months
Citgo fire fights for us
And then whenever she left
April 3rd Navy Captain Frank Thorp was quoted in the military time to saying that Lynch quote
We do have very
Strong indications that Jessica Lynch was not captured very easily
Reports are that you fired for M16 rifle until she had no more ammunition
None of that information is accurate but if
Feeds into the creation of a story out of the movies
Republic to enjoy
Lechona
Tell me another
That was another thing that was in that house investigation
Misinformation
Surrounding
The thing is
Those people
And their statement
Brigadier General Brook
And navy captain
Are not necessarily the people who gave
The statements are named to the washing
It's not
Like these people statement
As inaccurate as they may be
Are what fueled directly through media sensationalism
Anyone
Possible to prove this definitively
But you'd also have to be kind of naive
To think that it's
Impossible that someone within the department of
I've seen the potential
Spin the story
For some much-needed good press for the war
You could have that suspicion
And you can point fingers at the media for bungling the story
If you do that you have to be careful about where you
Appointment
If you damn the media for their mishandling of this story you also have to
Credit the media for doubling back in quest
Reminder own coverage with new information came to light
This doesn't necessarily excuse the sensationalism
The characterize the initial coverage
But without actual journalists continuant
What do the story
Even if it meant embarrassing themselves
This bread would have been much harder to untag
Second
If you believe that the dod was definitely trying to pull propaganda games here and pushing the false story
You have to ask how good they are at
This was a relatively easy propaganda story to pull off and it fell apart in a matter of weeks
If you believe that this was all government spin
Then I would suggest this story serves as a
The terrible argument that the government
It's always lying to us
Kind of more firmly supports the idea that
When the government tries to lie on a scale like this
It doesn't work
What's up in people's faces
You know at the time they just lied their way into a war so I bet they weren't really caring too much
Much about whether or not everybody
Caught them lying
I mean and then as far as
The competence with which they do things go
They are just incompetently lied their way into a war that they were fighting incompetently they were
Still fighting in comp
So it would make sense to me that the
The government
As it was
Set the time
Would very much try and push
The story so incompetently that it would backfire
Pinterest
Most
Something about this in the most important aspect to really
Delve into is where one thinks
The conspiracy
I don't fault people for thinking that the Bush Administration would have
The vested interest in The Sensational version of the story being reported
And the possibly unnamed us officials
Fed the flames
The story to the media
So you can suspect
I know that they may be wanted to mediate
This wrong in this
That's a different thing than the narrative italicus
The story that Alex is telling us that the entire rescue operation
In itself was a contrived theatrical Affair which is
Wheatley unsupported by the
The dod Office of the Inspector General Kentucky
Did investigation due to the insistence of Rahm Emanuel of all people
Into the allegation
Seems that the rescue is quote premeditated fabrication
From the report
Based on the results of the preliminary inquiry conducted by the Inspector General
United States Central Command
We can concluded that the allegations were not
Substantiated that no further investigation
Was warranted
During the inquiry the inspector-general uscentcom review numerous classified operational documents that were not available to the media
And interviewed over 30 Witnesses many of whom had firsthand knowledge of the events
A tissue
In addition to this Vernon low but one of the writers of the first Washington Post
Story
The actual first one the dead office in Station live coverage
He was interviewed on NPR's fresh air in December 2000
In that interview he clarifies that the information he was getting that the
The story was based on was wrong but It ultimately traced back to bad intelligence
From the field
Inaccurate information was
Conveyed collected from intercept
Misrepresented and misinterpreted details
I meant that story was reported
Kind of
Puts a little bit of a hole
In the theory that like is all an elaborate
Miss handling
And if you want to get a conspiracy about like
Hey
It works in certain
People's best interest
That there was this Miss handling
That's not crazy
It seems
Almost
The impossible to think of it as anything other than opportunistic
Idiot
Bungling
Murder story
You know you're a war hero store if you want to keep it in that sort of territory
You're on
More
Like not
Totally unreasonable ground
Cuz doing it
This idea that it's
They had premeditated intentions
Zup creating this fake rescue
In order to trick people into
Supporting the war or whatever
This is a conclusion that is unearned unsubstantiated
You can't back this up any
It's nonsense
And if this is
Point that I'm trying to make
When you have this
Suspicion
And this like
I don't know I don't trust these people pushing a f****** war and this story it
Like it was mishandled
Some level
Inaccurate statements were made weather is
Because of bad information being
Conveyed to the people making the statements or
Some kind of
Yeah Miss handling
Who knows
That suspicion is not bad
No it's not
Unnatural to have that healthy distrust
Distrust gets transmuted by someone like Alex
Into conflict
Assertions
Of
Conclusion that is
Based in reality
And that's where the danger is
Even with this
2003 Alex this
It's a far different Alex than the present
In terms of
Some of his methodology
That is true
I mean
But it's just so
It's just so
Easy
Especially at the time
Because they literally lied us into a war that
Never going to
The end
That's a conspiracy
On the level of something that is so
Huge
I mean an actual
Invasion of another country
And it was a conspiracy
And it was a lie
That it's hard to imagine anything's Beyond those
People you know
Why would
What do you really think it's
Beyond the people who lied us into a Forever War
To fabricate one small thing
You know like that seems like a reasonable over-reaction
At the time
If that makes sense do you know what I'm saying
Right but what you're describing is essentially Alec
What's Jones is
Indoctrination
Yes it is
It is
Compelling
Sing and
It certainly could be persuasive to say what
Related acts why wouldn't they do
Something else
And that's fine but then
Alright
Any argument
It's gone like yeah
Why wouldn't they do
Do you like to justify 100
Conspiracies
And it's just
It doesn't work
Yeah I know I don't I don't think there's any way prove that someone is morally capable of an act
I absolutely agree
Hijack is what Alex uses
Sprite
They are morally
Capable
Bratz
Just not that's not
Not reality
Yeah it's hard not to think that
History is going to look
Get the Bush Administration
As
Infinitely worse than anything Trump ever did
It's hard to look that it's hard to think that history won't look at Bush as one of
The single worst
Genocider there's ever been
Feels like Trump has sometime last though that's true that's true he we will see if he can still catch up
Interesting
Predictions that he make
This episode that seemed
Reminiscent
The present day
And they're preparing a national draft
Program
Environmental
We've been in the new world order for twenty years yeah
Yeah
No it just it just occurred to me that
It's like when he says
All of these things and then
They don't happen and he's like see we stopped it
Like
Yeah but now I
You've been foiling the same plot
420 yes we're reading like Batman serialized
Put in the draft and I was going to have tattletale Squad Batman Obama was going to have a draft
Exactly Obama youth or whatever
The Joker back in Arkham Asylum and then a week later
Joker breaks out with the same plant
And there's a whole lot of immediacy every time every single time
The only difference I would say is that within the world of DC Comics
The Batman and Joker
Purdue exam
Is that man was making up over and over again
And did not possess the creativity to come up with new plan you have got a new take on the Batman
Main character it's a rich
Psychopath who is inventing supervillains in order to play out this massive fantasy
That he has
Is it being a superhero
Oh my God that sounds real
I know I know a guy who could write that
For you
At this point in 2000
Three there were some
Beginnings of
Democratic processes
Being attempted
The God within a rock
Bandai Alex has some
Interesting takes on
Relieved
Been there Hitman
Will
Northern
Able to find articles and Outlets like the New York Times and LA Times about the Mosel election
Formerly made
That they have is a lot more
Restrain that Alex's
Presenting at
The New York Times article starts like that
Rock tickets
Its first faltering step toward democracy
See today when
Technically diverse group of local leaders held an election to choose an interim government
In this North
Northern City Iraq
Third largest
They're boarding recognizes it as a first step in
In a process not necessarily the end result
Itself where is
I feel like Alex is trying to pretend that the media is saying that this is a job that
You like The News-Herald wasn't does agent so I
The CIA or whatever the
The fuk Alex's
It was a group of
240 tribal leaders and local resident
Groups that make up the population of the area
These 240 selected a group of
24 council members who then went on to
To choose a mayor
I'm not going to pretend that I know whether or not this was the best way to handle the preliminary election for an inch
Interim government
But my point is
From everything I can tell Alex is misrepresenting what's going on
It's great to be opposed to the war
Cuz you should be
Your opposition to be base
In reality
I don't I don't feel like there's a lot of
Dealing with the war as a
It exists
On his part
Yeah yeah
It seems like if you don't deal with such a massive
Thing going on and instead
Create Toc
Toxic
Conspiracy theories about it that
Push people towards the
The far-right I bet that's going to have repercussions later on
Yeah I don't
I don't think it was the right way to express opposition later on we're really going to find out that the
Results of those things combining are really going to be bad for us
I think my parents
Friends who were hippies
Might have had a better handle on
Expedia
So
You know I do last episode about 2003 I think maybe it's too bad
Alex
Was going to go to Missouri to do a radio with
So foreign from
Alex is Pres
Keep telling the truth
Power everything else
I kind of believe that he probably would turned out of money to do a radio
Yeah
Yeah it doesn't it doesn't
Fuel insincere
I don't like it I don't like it Dan but I do buy it
I think I believe him here
I don't know though I don't
2003-4 think there's a possibility that he has reason to believe he can make more money selling DVDs any
Whatever his appearance rate
It's still a calculation
Maybe baby
Is lowered lowball enough that it's your pride would be better off
Denying it
You're an infant take
Apparently he was willing to go for free to a radio event in Missouri back in 2003
That's intense
So at this point
Alex
Not only going to radio event
For free he's also doing
The work he's doing the like
A lot of work
You want your order
Infowars.com
Decided
That it's been too long since we've done a documentary
And
As we're back in 2003 Alex just released this documentary
Oh not you like it's perfect time and we've got it we've got to cover police-state we're going to cover police
We might
I got I got I got this you know
Is that wind energy of
Was that the one whenever a bobcat
Was it his star was really starting to wane down after
23 was that the one
Mission to Moscow
I don't know bobcat bobcat nicest guy in the world
Yasso Alex's got this new
Maybe coming soon
Also
Jordan
I don't know what so agreed
Just do me
The idea of going online
Add pudding
Dramatic
Documentary titles such as police
3 into your leg
Order cart
You're just staring at
Police state 3
Clicking by like you got to smell like that it got kind of feel like s*** if you're not buying please say 2 + 10
Important
Chanel knows that serialized are we going to miss it out I don't know but if we do cover it
Not doing the other one
Super background
Don't know if I'm going to
This point Jordan wood
We know in the future
Alex's enemies
Oh boy the list is ongoing
Literal demon minions of the devil
Interesting Lee here is who the new world order is in 2003
Mine
My wife
My
The European
Does European bankers
Is the New World Order
Not too and that's what my chair the devil
The literal literal Christian devil
I mean it's nice that
We haven't seen the enemy at our gate
So to speak
I think it's interesting how he's
We have visitors
Is this bastard looseness
Yeah
What do you actually think I don't know
I don't know
I don't either I don't know interesting about this because we know in the future he will
Be fighting
Yeah and there's some slight indications that we've seen for 2003
He seems to Victor's
International
European Banker
Which is which is exactly the sort of presentation that he wants people to death
This is about the Federal Reserve this is about fiat currency
You know this is
I don't know I want to know if he
Actually thinks
The devil back then
I kind of think that they are here's what I figured
All right here's what I'm going to go with
I'm going to go with its necessary escalation is what happened you know like
Iron Man came out around 2000
You know it's just one dude fighting against his is
Director
Or whatever it is he's doing
Real low-stakes by the end of it we've got to restart the universe
You know it's like
Call European Bankers are at and then 20 years later
We're fighting the literal devil
It makes sense
Yeah but look
Dude if he's essentially doing the entire Marvel universe as we
In an Ironman
Like Robert Downey jr. wasn't pretending that he wasn't fighting Santos
He didn't know he was fighting Thanos
Alex seems to have some awareness of the devil
There is that
Santos didn't hatches plan for another 10 years or whatever
I can't quite get my finger on it yet
So Alex Goes to call Sandy Texas
Let's talk about
Dennis Miller sure great
I just do I sell them
Tonight Show last night
Dennis Miller
Was on there
And I always seem to I mean
Real quick Ultra socialist
She was on The Tonight Show
Praise and accolades
Fair enough
Yeah I mean
Football
I think I might have been a few years earlier
This this is
Sure promoted the Iraq war is Shameless
I think time has shown us a date
He's stayed on that
Conservative pathan was pretty in favor of trump follow-up followed a lot of similar path
This is a secret socialist
Ultra-left person
Trying to
Tend to be conservative
You know the Trojan Horse
George Bush on us
That explanation that doesn't make sense
Tonight site
Dick lost
His mind
Yeah yeah real dick
Real
Sites to know that no matter what era we live in
Right-wing commentators will still have
Very strong opinions about,
Don't matter
It's pretty Universal in
No one like that
Coupler
What about interaction that did not
It's not globalist in a hot tub
It seems to be a
Nazi at a gas station
Jokes
Don't think this happen
About
You're not part of the
North Korea
From at least 2010 onward all the way to his running for President Donald Trump was
Wheatley preoccupied with the idea of taking oil from countries where we've been at War
An editor's note in an article from The Brookings Institute called it quote
The most dangerous and irresponsible of all the republican nominees policy proposals
Ben Alex Justified it when Trump had the egg
Exact same perspective
You shooting down his dumb basheer 2003
Also I think it's
Weird
That Alex is saying that
Being a Nazi is trendy
I don't know what kind of company he's Swinging with back then but
Honestly
For Alex
Add that guy was ahead
Give the time
It's really he was out at the Forefront of
Absolutely loved the right way
Eventual cleavage
Kerouac of the of the beat movie you know he's there early
That's Tuff
Yeah I just don't like the idea of
Looking at somebody with an iron cross tattoo
F****** Brandi
I look at my friends who were too into Tiger King
Absolutely
F*** either that or he's just like I'll look at you
So many goddamn Nazis with their iron cross tattoos everywhere these days
I'm lately bell bottom right
Text fad
So I think it one of the things that I keep
Keep getting a sense of
And these two thousand three episodes
Is a lot of Alex's opposition to George Bush comes down to
Complete feeling that bushes
She's going to take all of his guns
2 also known as the Justice enhancement domestic
Security Act of 2003 was introduced by Tom daschle
On January 7th 2003
They probably died
For even receiving about
Clinton signed the federal assault weapons ban in 1994 Sunset Clause after
After 10 years so it was abandoned only
Existed
Until 2004 when Obi re-examined
And it expired in 2004
Bush did not renew
None of these listeners scared of
Happened which is
Kind of the case always
Yeah
Well distraction
Turn the stuff that is
You don't want to get in
The waves real
It hurt true
So
That's why you don't make Shadow gay
Dan you don't get in the way of the real stuff
Whatever you do don't talk about Rodger
This account takes another call
And this guy has a perspective of like
You know we're over there we're trying to bring tomorrow
Proceed into the Middle East countries in
What have you and I don't see anything happening here
Don't see anything happening in my life
And whatever
Alex do something really f***** up after that
You said before
Ha he keeps saying it trouble
You know what's funny that you meant
Nothing about
People scaring in the
How I was thinking
3 days ago
Into my head
Wait a minute
Benefiting The General
Population of the
What's going on
I stopped and I looked around
Gas prices
To the store. Advise a Wawa
Disabled
It's not that bad
He is a very conditional idea about colonialism
Not seem to have a principled idea against regime change
Against nation-building.
I think he has
It's not
Is conditional it's about whether or not the people who are going
And taking over other countries
Leave him alone or not right
If you
Just didn't take away his gun
Yeah I know he's against regime-change except fairy in the right conditions
Just like he's against the capitol 6 riot
Because it wasn't the right time I wasn't the right
Preparation here that to me is really a real glaring hole
I can't
I mean I guess
A lot of the times people who'd be listening to this may be back in
2003's listening to it on the radio wouldn't be listening to it as critically
That's early as I'm listening to it now
That seems like something with it
Should be a real problem for him and his listeners
The idea of the key would be
Be okay with a war emperor
The same way that George Washington would have now obviously abolishing the Constitution
That would be a
Discussion
Like
All of his intros are like you want to end your knee will so does he
This you understand that this is exactly the way that you know
Rationalize Alexa
I guess Reese
1:10
When Trump was empowered wanted to
Colonize space
I know right
Man I heard that s*** so much
Do those people who call in and they're like what do we get out of this war
Do they not understand how Psychopathic that sounds like
Hey what do I look
I'm sure it's
What's my bottom line
That's gross
Let's imagine like a president that we were
Supportive of
Just coming out of being like
I think I'm going to buy Greenland
With all of the other policies I'm going along
You know what this is a good idea how galatea cannabis
Here's what
Carter is second about right the gas crisis is going on and he's like a
You know where there's gas
Me neither but let's buy Greenland I'm going to take next week
It's ours
Which is sort of a scene so far
In a 2000
And here we come
Lawrence
There's a few things that really concerned me
About this intro that Alex's reading
Dennis Cuddy
This is the exact wording that you'll find for him on pretty much all other websites
Just don't sound right
When someone isn't been employed as an actual Professor their bio probably wouldn't say that they've quotes
Taught at the University level
Would almost always specified
School where they were a professor
Relevant
It's the University of black
Honestly I've given a few lectures at colleges so I guess I could technically claim that I've taught at the University level that it didn't mean any
You could get on info
The second issue that I have of his bio is that he specifies a major and a minor in terms of his PhD which is a little bit
Bizarre
Typically that's the language that people use to
Just got their undergraduate education where is if you reach the graduate level
Doctoral program
You be unlikely to have a minor
You probably discuss your area of emphasis and as a way of discussing
You know your credentials mr. seems really really weird
It sounds like what you would describe if you
Didn't get a pH
HD I was worried about that
Yeah or if
You purchased one from somewhere outside of the United States
Well I was concerned
But I was able to find his dissertation was we published in a 1978 issue
Of the Journal of American History titled quote
American Immigration to Australia 1945
To the present
So it does appear that
He did complete a PhD program
But I'm not sure what this area of study has to
To do with qualifying him to be an expert in the New World Order
If you check out his bibliography
Books about the New World Order been not so many books about Australian immigration
Still active as a conspiracy weirdo to this day
Beers that he's been pretty
Pro Trump which raises an interesting question about why he's not
Still a figure
Went out to show I thought maybe they'd
Didn't hit it off
But they get along pretty well
Interesting yeah I don't know I don't know what happened but he's that I recognized
For many of the press
Send a text
Sunset
It's always covered baby just got out of the game
No you still in the game
Maybe he got out of Alex and maybe you got out of the Heat
I believe
Anyway this guy's got an interesting shredded
Convince
People like I know you can't
Discriminate like a universe
The PHD program
Can't discriminate based on religious beliefs or ideology
Could you be like sneakily like
Hey what if you wanted to go on Infowars would you go on Infowars and if the answer is yes they like
To be fair it was 76 when he got his Ph.D
Infowars did not exist
2 years old
We can't do it look you can't litigate ex post facto
I've heard that from Subway
So I look we want to give you this degree but there's a two-year-old over in Dallas
Do something weird
Look if the devil has been aware of Alex Jones from the beginning
I don't know anyway
Dennis's got this interests
Sing trick that he uses
Because he wants to like
Cut through the b*******
Like if
People people don't don't agree with him right
Cuts through the b*******
Is it sneak
New World Order
The first thing
Therapy disposition
To think you're a nut if you talk
About conspiracy theories
Suppose I told you there was a power
Somewhere so complete
So pervasive someone Owasso watch Road
Speak above your breast
He said that
First of all I can't imagine how little I care about having a Woodrow Wilson quotes snuck up on me
Yeah I think I would be like
Secondly and more importantly what this guy's doing is misusing the quote from Wilson's platform 1913
The full quote
He's going from his quote
Since I entered politics I've chiefly had men's views confided to me private
Some of the biggest man in the United States in the field of Commerce and manufacturer are afraid of somebody
They are afraid of something
They know that there's a power somewhere so organized so subtle so watchful so interlock so complete so pervasive
That they had better not speak above their breath
When they speak in condemnation of
If you continue reading it super clear that Wilson's talking about isn't the spooky cabal of globalist
But be completely unregulated nature of industry and how people
We've already amassed a certain amount of power can use that
Stop at people who are just getting
Start it right
Come a little later in the text
And this is the country which is lifted to the admiration of the world its ideals of absolutely free opportunity
Where no man is supposed to be under any limitation accept the limitations of his character and his mine
Where they're supposed to be no distinction of class no distinction of blood no distinction of social status
But where men win or lose by their merits
I live very close to my own conscience as a public man whether we can any longer stand at our doors and welcome any new
Cumbers upon these term
American industry is not free as once it was free
American Enterprise is not free
With only a little capital is finding it harder
To get into the field more and more impossible to compete with the big
Why
Because the laws of this country did not prevent the strong from crushing the week
Antitrust issues were really big topical politics in the 1910s and that's with
Yeah that's why I was
Plank and Wilson
Agenda
You clearly in favor of taking power away from monopolies and giving a better chance
Smaller upper up-and-coming businesses
And that's what this passage
From his platform is all about
If you just take a look at the section the Cutty is reading out of context
It could sound like they were saying there was a group of villains running the world or whatever but if you take it within its proper context you read something
Very different
He doesn't favor regulate
Boy you know a guy who says that
Who also
Made
The black
Servants
In the White House
Hide
Whenever he walk
How to buy
He didn't
Steve mikula
Maybe if you say that
And do that
If you got to go back in time and kill this guy I'm not I'm not I'm not here to litigate Woodrow Wilson's career
Totally I just hear it in my head
And know that if
At the same time without losing my mind because that reaction is difficult to hat
Playing using a quote
I don't know if I can
Except that he doesn't understand that
I find that difficult
The cut
Yeah
I find it difficult to believe
That he would be able to read that quote read further in the text
And not understand
What this is about
Now if possible
And it's also possible that the depth of his research doesn't include
Other paragraphs after maybe he's just seeing this
In some other texts in the same way that everybody
In the right-wing is nozzle
Exact they've only read stuff from like skousen talking
Sing about tragedy
Did that this quote and it sounds really good and sweet
Freak normies out
Check this out
But I don't know I find I find it to be a problem
For me to take him seriously
Any white date there talkin
Alex
Bacardi and one of the things I like Aziz doctor Cudi and that's Lisa Edelstein character on house
Oh okay
Alright
So they're talkin and they get to conversation about Bohemian Grove
More details about how
On heroic is breaking in Hawaii
Whataburger
Are you aware that the Bohemian Grove
The video where a guy
Okay
That certainly fits with the holocron
Something you were just allowed to walk in
The story seems a little more dashing
Is it now
Little more humble
Back at this point interesting
So this
My town for this clip cuz this pissed
Me
So Alex is talking about Bohemian Grove any wants to bring up the satanic element
You want to talk about their dude
And I'm like hey this is one of the big things I'm interested in 2003 are you fighting the devil
We got to know this
Text me off
Element
People running around
Weird Behavior
Holder
I'm guessing they were just drunk and they like peed on a bush
Yeah that sounds
Urination ritual of many a Cubs game
Before and thought I got to get this weird urination ritual done real quick yeah I've been to bonfire party
They were just full of weird urination rituals
Hey Google a word
The reason I'm pissed off babe
Question
Sidetracked by talking about Peter
God dammit
I wanted to know about the satanic element
It doesn't seem like it's that big of a deal
If you're just going to get distracted with urination red certainly not important enough
Come back to us immediately
So this guy Cudi
Prediction
Yeah
Thanks
This site aches
Did not age well
Situation
What I tried
War
Will happen
Or it'll be over
Star with relatively few casualties
Took the stage War
Hoover quick
You know that's
Really comforting
Cuz I was worried that it was going to blow up into a thing that d
Destabilizing
The entire world
Yeah this this is bad sinking
Other possibilities
Everything that's happened
Would have happened differently if it was a real
This is just
Terrible
Wow
To learn the past
About Australian immigration
Are doomed to repeat that
Extra other
So that one of Alex's big
Reason
Seems to believe that 911
Was an inside job is they were running
Drill
Yeah yeah yeah drills are very important to Inside Job
Man that made me laugh really hard
Because
Cuddy accidentally punctured a giant hole in that theory
By trying to help
That morning is that very time
Pause
That causes great
Is staring daggers
What is the man who just got
Slice to shreds with a glance
It's so important for us
The theories surrounding the
The drills
That they're not
Be drills regularly or similar grills that happened in the past
Picked up on it there
I'm so helpful because
I do think that
As much as
Another still a bunch of dumb dumbs
Back then
They're people who are less on the same identical script
Yeah like when you listen to these present episodes it'll be like Alex interviewing is
Is Bucking lawyers
We're doing yes and the games with him
Basically just not only that but
Alex Wright
Not like
Puncture anything
You're not saying anything that could be like well
That's a reason why this doesn't
Makes sense
In this moment that guy is
Just thought that added to the
Attracted actually
GloZell
To shred
Makes it look bad
He was like a retriever bringing you the paper after stepping in a
Pile of s***
I'm so good
I brought you the papers I like you
So earlier Jordan we learned
The Dennis Miller
Is a big-time social
Lifetime play
The game show that is taking
Country by storm
Who
An Ultra,
Every episode dammit
Bastard I don't know it could be anybody every episode so far in 2003 I think we've had Alex out to somebody
Add syrup
Interesting
Starting out a little earlier with a
Ultra calming
Alright
Michael Savage
Bill kristol
That is what happened baby
That is what happened
When you
Don't find Curly's gold
Alright
You become adults
Call me because it's clear that the ruling class has taken the gold before you got there
Wrong bill kristol
Earlier
We got distracted by
Urination ritual when Alex was about to talk about
Satanic Elementary
This is like a prank
On me
I swear to God
America
Okay
Mike
Went off in the middle of him saying Satan literally I know it is it is a little bit of a
Cheez-Its
It's like this isn't admissible he could have said everything he could have said everything
Literally
Literally and you know what that means
I can't wait.
Then you're a witch
It is you're a witch
Becoming troubling today the level of these
It is dangerous
Yeah but it is also pretty funny but it might just went off and it's got this like what's going on
We needed
To hear it's the one word expound on it more you know
Michael Ross
Are we go anyway this is a catastrophic problem disease
Economics
Finger job
That you're willing to
Just because more
To use them.
Old fashioned
Patriots
Hoo-boy
Yeah that's not good
Yeah it is
I mean it's just screw up my can
Conspiracy theory to know the
That this kind of thing happens every year at that dust
Bother
It makes me worry
I don't know I can't be I can't imagine
Well he is 2300 bad Tech back then
I kind of understand videos bad take back then
Sure
What are things that I think of
Cool
About 2003
Big problem
On the radio your mics
To go completely out your guest is left
2 trillion
Tread water on his own
How many got to go out to break
Alex deals with it Grace
There's no like
The globalists are trying to take us off here cuz we're too dangerous there's no
F****** freaking out and leave and he's laughing you know that guy got a tech problem
Normal
Person responding to difficulties that would be expect
That's true
That is true
Now admittedly I will say that
There is that would give me
Certain justification
Super allergic reaction
If
I say I'm having later problems after spending
Billion dollars on a studio you know like
If you're still having those problems you should be angrier than if you have
City Tech
Yeah it does make sense
Yeah cuz then you really can't blame it all on the
No but it is on you it is definitely on you cuz you have not solved the problem
Outburst in the present day
It still is
It should be directed in words
Supposed to be screaming at the
The the audience
I just prefer to see this
Dislike
It did it's not like a child lashing out
It's
You're the huge problem that happens on your show and you're able to laugh
And come back brakes
Good on him being able to take us out to breaking
Handle it no I know sometimes
Genesis feed goes down
Sure
And everybody likes
The VH1 part of Behind the Music where there are the
They're on their meteoric rise but they're just beginning and they're playing their show at the
Dunbar down the
Street and little bit everybody know what he
He was going to do so
Yeah this is fun
So Alec
Gets to talkin amor
About the democratization in Iraq and the government
She's coming in
We do from hist
Again
Very shortly after this episode
Dbats
Vacation
Good idea
Nickelback
Wrong is wrong wrong about that
Quite wrong
It's just interesting that these
Consistently going down this road and it does setup and weird
I don't know what's going to happen as
You know like
Maid comes to an end and I continued
He was like how is he going to
Navigate that territory
It is ironic
Even that
It is almost his
Exact opinion of the bath
That
Was echoed in American
Policy
Well he's
Criticizing them
India
India that they would
Do they opted
Opposite of what
Facebook
Yeah it is because the way he's presenting things
He doesn't really have
Good leg
Get to stand on
Opposed
2B pacification
He has to be in favor of it run to comes along exactly willing to be
Strongly in favor
Certainly
No as things go along I don't think it will own the consequences it didn't it didn't go well
No
So
I would say that listening to this episode
There is
Very little
In terms of news stories
There is a little bit of like a couple of headlines grown out here and there
He talked a lot about Richard Pearl hui-k'o
The Prince of Darkness
Sure
I think this
He's obsessed with that dude cuz I've heard him talk about that dude in the present day
Constantly
When you get too drunk on WIC
Rogan show and stuff he'll talk about the darkness
He would go around to go around at parties and tell women that are like he kills people
You think that if I could get him aroused and
And stuff
He brings up this dude
A lot
Alright
Anyway
There's not a whole lot I do like a lifelong Grudge
That's your admirable
Realizes
God that was uninspired
That was boring
Go on guy before he started doing his Churchill impression
We got to
Get up
Yes I want to join Alex comes to the end of the show and realizes that he didn't cover most of the news as opposed to it happening
An hour before the show ends
And then. Still no more news of govern
You got a minute
He wants to really hit on is
They're people reaffirming
The Bill of Rights which is very meaningful and important
This is just the same thing as in 2009 all the Tenth Amendment resolutions
Yes okay we have to have the state house has passed these things
They say the same thing as the Constitution
I don't know babe
What up
To what extent
Do we do they describe God given rights
You know what like
There is River give me a biblical
Explanation of what rights
God specifically gives us don't recall him writing the goddamn Bill of Rights
I don't know if it
It's derived
Directly from anything in the Bible but this is
This is a pretty standard
Element of anti-communism
They they have this idea that
Communism seeks to
Tile or religion and get rid of religion
And in doing so you get rid of God
Write if you get rid of God
Then there's no more Justice
Application for why people have right
By the Creator you have no rights
Sure communism
Gets rid of God which
Gets rid of right switch
Makes you all
The important hinges for the god-given right
I just feel like
If you want to win the mark
Marketplace of ideas you should
Kind of write down what rights
Your pad
What they did and we'll compare them to the other thing it's in the Declaration of Independence Constitution
It's those right
Those are
Constitution god-given rights that are protected
By the count
Constitute
Even dumber than I thought it was
Sort of
I don't know what's an argument that you can run into a lot
The
The notion of like does all morality stem
From religion
Obviously
Thousand years to think that no morality and ethics are impossible outside of religious framework
I don't know I don't I don't buy into that but
Kind of a colonel at the base of their ideas
A lot of his associates contraction of right
I just didn't I didn't
Quite understand what they were talking
Sing about because it generally speaking whenever people don't like talking about God
I appreciate it if they have some sort of biblical basis for it
It just sounds like it's just guns
Man people love the
Their guns it was
The eleventh commandment
It's just there
Fan comes on
Commandant was guns
Baby
And the Let Jesus said
The last ever one of you will betray babe
Before the cock
Exploration of back in the 18 years
Ago today 18 years ago
Today what an idiot
It's very nice
Is it go sucks
Wrong ideas about what was going to happen
Such
Misguided nonsense
Not good
A weirdo presented as an expert
Pretty normal
More evidence than Alex should sue Joe Rogan
A using the word powerful I think it's
I don't know
I mean I think
It'd be tough though to win a lawsuit whenever you've got that oh Alex just said we're going to play that
That clip of Alex saying he's going to gut him like a pig and I like
How are you going to win that kind of lost free-speech man I that's fair
Infuriated
Bye
The
Is it going to urination talk after Mike's cutting out right around when Satan was coming up
Personally
Very funny but I'm excited to see if the next couple episodes I have anything that will help clarify position
I'd be more funny if somebody actually
Cut off the mic
Whatever you're the best they literally like
We can't have that out there boom Redbox
Move that fast
We'll find out more in the future but until next time
We have website
We are also on
We are infinite sadness. I go to bed Jordan
Please find a local charity or Bell found in your area to help
Until then I'm Neo I'm Leo and bbx Clark I'm Daryl rundus
And now here comes
The sex robot
Holding