Damn important
I have great respect for its knowledge fight
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Looks around
Worships Elaine
Added this earlier on maybe in our 300th episode
Guess by now I just need to also be more mindful of
Novelty beverages out
Saline Inn
Need to be some attention to a word
Well I'll be a legend
Hey came back to life
Give this s*** whatever
Your own way
So Jordan can I have a quick question for you what is your break
My brakes bought today is actually I think
Okay so you know how like
In school he back what am I ever going to need to use this
You talk about like math or any
I sometimes feel that way about this podcast
Dillard's
Forever come up in anyone Bailey life going to have a lot of natural sound in conversation
Information where it actually came into play and it felt really good
Okay what happened
A lift
A ride
Coming home
The guy
We were talking about some of the like
Difficulties
Of the covid
He ran in alvesta
Conversation veered into talking about like Pub
Like that
Guy
The Fed was started by 3 Saturday
Just that are like China owns half hard
Without even missing a beat that's not true
But not nearly that much I've looked into this
Mostly
Stuff we owe ourselves
I am one of the few people who would you here I've looked into it and you
It was a rare occasion was like
This is the hill I die on
What year was my first Cubs game in two years
Why was that why was that why was
Don't make me do this happy birthday daughter this weekend happy birthday
Yeah
I went to the game it was
Fantastic
I have a I have a very fun story that
Is going to sound self-aggrandising at first but
It is very much not about that Frank Rizzo said you had the best armor in the game
If only
Headphones
That is first name
It's Anthony
Frank Rizzo is a guy
Who is Frank anyways
There was this very everybody was socially distance in the park it was it was good stuff
And a row behind us about Tennessee
Pizza Wave
There was this dude who showed up
Wearing a
Goddamn
T-shirt
It was it was a nice day
But
At Wrigley
Whatever it is outside
It is 20 degrees lower than that is yours
Tyrell on the think so this guy is absolutely freezing and then the Sun goes behind
The cloud
Everybody is freezing everybody is curled up
And I keep turning and looking back
This f****** guy with his
Bear sleeves
You guys like I'm losing my arm
Bob losing my mind right
So I have to go like I can't do this anymore so I'd go and I buy him a f******
You know like
This is not me being generous this is me like I can't watch
The f****** game what you do something so it's either you get a blanket
Temecula
Zarape
Negative
Not a self-aggrandizing story at all
Basically what it was
Frank Rizzo was the racist mayor of Philadelphia
Notorious
Firenze as mayor Rizzo Philadelphia schools
And I prevented the
Construction of public housing in majority white neighborhood
While running for a third term Rizzo urge supporters to quote vote White
You know I think
That says a lot about us but the first
Rizzo's that come to mind are in your Center
Anti-communist
I did mine also ratso Rizzo
Today we have a present-day episode to go up
Our last episode
May 7th
Now today we're going to be talking about May 6th and 7
Stop for a second to see if the other with you at first
Well that's like you know when you really like get to the door the same time somebody
I was letting you go excuse me
This is the interesting it's it's a fun
It's a fun stretch of time and I'm excited to get into it
Harbour Purdue Jordan
We got to walk into technocrat to give a shout out to
First
I'm a policy
Dirk gently's cast
Juvenile
Technocrat
Money off that heroin
So good
Freakishly large
Happy birthday
You only a few policy want your birthday
ShopRite
We're doing may all at once
Not all of me but it turns out there's a cluster right around here they were
I think it's because
Love you naturally
Steve
Happy birthday throat that
There's over the weekend
Alright
Happy birthday
Come on Mother's Day
Meet people detailed information my passwords aren't that strong oh no my wouldn't resent those
Also Karina
Happy birthday that's coming up on the 11th
Coming up in the middle of this week happy birthday Karina
Tom
From his brother make a Ron
He's just 10 Runs put together into one giant
The Queen's measuring people
Metric
Metric I was going to go with Power Ranger
Megazord
That is also on the 11th happy birthday Tom
From Mega wrong
Something that I missed in the mailbag last time we got together
So this was something that actually had on the list that I was going
To bring up the last time but I have forgotten the note
In the other room that this note is too good not to share with the world
This is for the preservation of wrecker royalty have determined that I am no longer fit to be
Region
For this Raptor princess as I am
And moving too much
To keep her safe
Then I hope she doesn't
Eat your chocolate
Jordan I hope Dan
Thank you so much for your wonderful broadcasting for the cool community on Facebook
You guys help me stay sane
Happy
Euphoria chocolate in
I think euphoric chocolate in
Currency
This this
Ceramic Raptor princess
Is just the coolest thing
I have to
Macaron found this at like
Thrift store picture of this
It's just it looks like it was made
With love somebody made in there like
This is going to come in handy 20 or 30 years from now this looks like it's
From the 20s
Wow that is old
It's gorgeous and thank you so much
Also this was the package that came with all the candy
That was marked
Add an Stop opening Jordan candy
If there was some candy
A bunch of
You opened it
That was the best part of this is the first message it was wrapped
Really really have a late fee on the first message was like Dad this
Is Jordan candy don't need it
And you just gave it to me from there so I took
Get home and I start crying
Record should show that I did follow the instructions
It's that important
Because there were further instruction
Convince you opened it up
Down on the paper was written like
Dan if you've made it this far you need to stop
Further was like damn you've stolen Jordans
Andy at this point
I was just guilt isn't imaginary how ashamed I would be if I saw this
That was the best part the best part was I was like
God dammit
It seemed the second note
It would have been
Just he would have spent
Today's thinking about
It's a test I didn't know I had passed
Oh that's great
Fun
Insult do I think it was
Testing you pass it as a senior now was King Arthur
Taken care of on our cell phones
Curiosities
Jordan May 6th and 7th I should say that this
Is
But little fun for me
I mean granted it is like I buy you brought up like
Weirdest
Fancy back bowls
Whatever
But there's a specific in this episode that allowed
Me to take in a little bit and I enjoyed that
Today Show
Jones
Might be able to use that truck in the future
With that one
Alex is starting out May 6th
See if you can think of a children's story
It comes to mind when you hear this
The information I got before the broadcast started
Tours of top scientists and other major study
Read study from an extremely
Prestigious
Power Research Institute
And the University of Texas Galveston with a level 4 bioweapons research
I was completely blown away
I have trouble even being on air
This audience has millions of people urine
Credible crossword
If I said I have total proof
That they knew
Covid-19 vaccine
Virus Vector delivery system
The Pfizer mRNA and then the AstraZeneca
Juniper classes
In the main literature
Yams that it causes massive autoimmune response in the brain
And in the cardiovascular system
And they recommended.
I'll be done because it caused massive death in the lab animals
I had that info
Lost in the background noise
Instead all this Saturday I'm going to a special show
For 3 hours commercial-free everybody TuneIn
We would have millions and millions of people that tune
Specifically
For that information
Very seriously
There was a restaurant waiting for me
Fanfiction with others
Mentally
We are also incredibly influential
This is
At this point
I can probably just go off air
And or have her come in and do a great job posting
And just go show this document
Yeah it so I just keep hearing the boy who cried wolf
This is a guy who
I have said that I have
Every problem too many times and now it's
Just background
Can't really do this not really doing it and now the only way for me to escalate things
Show on my day off cuz that makes it look like I'm serious
Diminishing returns
As if there was some sort of law that somebody wrote about diminishing return also I don't remember if I pulled a clip of this Butler
Later in the show so Alex is saying that he's going to have to come back on Saturday to cover this thing is mega bomb shelter
Can get attention I'm supposed
To take my daughter fishing
Anyway
This man is truly the tip
Details but he's more right than he usually is
Yeah here interesting this is a study about stars not Stars Cove too but
In terms of the level I'm used to him making things up I was surprised
In the study and see this
In the conclusion sex
Quote these Stars Cove vaccines all induced antibody and protection against
Affection with stars Coronavirus
However
Challenge of mice giving any of the vaccines led to occurrences of
Th2 type
Immuno pathology suggest
Hypersensitivity
Thesaurus coronavirus compound
Was it induce
Caution and proceeding to application of SARS coronavirus vaccine in humans
He's indicated
That's pretty interesting and AutoZone it sounds pretty scary
Like the idea of
Making a coronavirus vaccine
Humans
He's something that shouldn't
Be done
But it's pretty important to recognize that
This is a part of medical literature
History
And that's not a static
Yeah
This probably doesn't need to be said
But changes have been made
Additionally the circumstances were different with a worldwide outbreak happen
Running now creating
Necessity which
Of course is the mother of invention
Naturally
You can find some discussion of this very study Alex's referencing in more detailed write-ups about the path
The research is taken in terms of developing a coronavirus vaccine
Going through Sarah's Merced now SARS coronavirus 2
If Alex is just looking for flashy ways to smear science
He could find all sorts of studies from the past that have shown difficulties with vaccine development
That game relies on pretending the people don't learn from these studies and then adjust their approaches
One important thing to recognize
Alex's referring to
Which you can find by Googling the title
Immunization with SARS coronavirus vaccines leads to pulmonary immuno pathology
On challenge
With the SARS virus
Hobbit the title of
It's about
Completely different vaccines than the ones that have
Developed in response
Covid
If you just read the first few pages of the study you see that the vaccines that were tested in this were two varieties
They were inactivated whole virus vaccines or virus like
Particle Max
The visor in moderna vaccines RM RNA base vaccines which work entirely differently than either the types of his study
There's no direct relevance between the shots
And this study at all
The Johnson & Johnson vaccine is a viral Vector vaccine
Which is fairly similar to the virus-like particle approach
But with a very
Important distinction
The virus-like particle vaccines in the study
The structural elements of stars devoid of any voice viral genomes
The trigger an immune response
The people where is the jnj vaccine uses
A non infectious virus
To create the spike protein of covid
Which then teaches our body to recognize that's
Incited
Pointier is it the Study Island
Discovering is not a bombshell it does not require coming in on Saturday
If you don't
Too much attention
You can kind of look like it supports its narrative
Yeah but it's all bulshit
This
He's going to be one of the things that he talks about almost 6
Exclusively
Amazing
To see how
Munchie just makes
She just making s*** up
It's amazing
I mean look
Okay
You can tell me the challenges
And the things that were wrong
In 2012
Bright but if you tell me that they're the same now
How many iPhones was that ago
What was that for years
We're better than that now
People were still talking about the Mayan calendar
Fine okay don't tell me that in 2000 and 2012 they had trouble making a vaccine so
We should stop
There's a lot of variables that go into it and actually color of the
Progression of
And some of that will discuss
A little bit later but look dude
Alex found out about this
And he is
Bucket
Mad
This could save hundreds of millions of not billions of people
I thought it was over
For Humanity
Again
I'm unable to continue the broadcast
I just can't do much this morning
Controller
Actress latest
Maybe
Okay
Point that I suspected Alex was in a bad mood about something
Maybe something in his personal life was
Not exactly to his liking
Why are so many people willing to follow somebody that publicly
It's like a whiny baby
What are you talkin
Jordan
Resist
Jordan this isn't a drama
Someone brought this
And now everyone
Got to die
I don't I just don't remember alive
Corvara in the middle of the Revolution to be like
I just don't even know
I just don't even care anymore I don't want to leave this revolution
Quote Castro
Wow
Cheese's
So Alex wants
To protest
About this study man he wants to get out there and
Like his routes
Like
Get back to Wookie was in Waco
Life
That image of a guy driving around red in the face hero
There's no doubt about this is a maskil operation
No.
We should all go protest at
Dell Children's Hospital
North Austin
What you do
W draw attention and bullhorn
Prestigious
Bio weapons research lab saying any
Maxine for the coronavirus family
Autoimmune response
Blood clots
Look at this
They studied it on a whole bunch of animals
He killed Mass numbers on this
So there's some basic Alex's telling about the study just in that little ramp
Specific things you lying about you can see his motives
Really clearly
The first thing to be very clear about is that this study only had to do with reactions to a vaccine advice
At the end of the study they even say quote limitations of the present studies include their performance in my only
And uncertainty of the relevance of rodent models to
To Saars coronavirus vaccines a human
Alex is skimming the study so he's only looking
Give me the first page and abstract
Basically
If you only look at that you don't actually read it
You might
Is there more animals involved
In the design section of the abstract
It says quote
For Kennedy vaccines for humans with or without Al imagine
We're at evaluated on a mouse model of SARS
And a VIP vaccine the vaccine given to ferrets
What's a non-human primate
Another whole virus vaccine and an rdna produced as
Protein
Ferrets and non-human primates
Primates are reference
But not as participants in the study
The context of that is that vop vaccine
Are typically the type that are given to those animals
If you weren't paying
Attention to the study at all and you just wanted to use the appearance of it as a prop to scare people
If you really easy to see multiple animal names in the first page or just got to run with it cuz without
What is doing that like
12 Monkeys
Picture where there's all these animals in cages in like a dark lit there
Somewhere yeah
Second Alex is making up
Set the study showed that mass numbers of animals were killed because of the vaccine
Massive numbers of my Cymbalta begin with
And if you read the study you know how the
Scotty was design
They vaccinated the mice with the different vaccines and 56
6 days later accident that's not entirely true
56 days into the study
5 MI
For me prove were killed to assess how well the vaccines at work
And 2 gauge long as you
Exhausted
The remaining bison each group or challenge with live SARS and then killed two days later
So their lungs
Baby study
There's no indication that lung issues are vaccine concerns killed even a single Mouse
Cinestudy
How to making that up to make a story seem more in
Interesting to Azadi
Bird
Alex is making of the F the effects that the study found in vaccinated mice were faced with the Stars challenge
He's including autoimmune conditions in the list because that's been a big talking point on Infowars for a long time
Sota meant to give him the appearance
Being right
Strokes heart attacks and blood clots are included because these are things that people have been discussing
Is possibly related
The various vaccines for covid-19
There's not evidence of a causal link but a public conversation about concern surrounding those issues has
Been going on
Analysis trying to exacerbate those concerns and scares audio
And in the study as we know the only real result was all of the mice had increased blood
That was not in the study
Are you sure
The actual study doesn't involve any of the conditions that Alex was listing
The effect studied were entirely surrounded
Damage to lung tissue
One of the following
Must be true
And I cannot stress this enough
Alex is either not read this study at all and it's just making all this stuff up
Has read the study
And he knows that he's lying to his audience about what it says disc error
There isn't a middle ground
But I will say that in that first
Possibility that first category is
Skimmed it and read a few words more like
Still just making up what you think
Those words
Bulshit
Yeah I love it I love it he looks at a
Article
Probably looks
Like when you and I look at
Something to read we like see all the words
Right
I imagine every time he looks at one of these it's like a redacted document in it
His brain like his brain just about all the words that aren't likes
Usable it instead of the black bars it's like demon face
Clowns walking on cleats
The brown bag
I got to quit drinking instead of word that John Cleese silly walks but if it's a weird clown
So Alex is going to leave
You got to go maybe.
You know what
I'm just going to read the whole damn study on their house that's no
What sounds good
Music study
This spells it right out
In the summary on the front page
University of Texas
Level 4 bio weapons lab
Galveston Texas
There is no way he's reading this. You hungry
This whole overly-dramatic breakdown of having to go off air and then deciding to stay on there and read the whole study
You come off a lot more genuine if it hadn't followed the whole part of the beginning there were Alex's complaining that no one pays attention to him
Unless you make a big
Do you have
It almost feels like this
Fake struggling that he's going through it's like a
Piece of the necessary performance that he has to Cairo
Carry out to make anyone believe that this
Pizza supposed evidence actually means anything
Yeah
Yeah you know it reminds me of when James Brown
Blanket over his shoulders and be like I'm too tired I can't go on anymore
Performance I guess
But you know he's coming back especially if you're on tour with him and you've seen it
I basically on tour with Alex
B r boring
Small point
Pretend years
But UA
That's true that is true
They put out all of their shows if people listen to them
That's good point
All anyway small Point here during the lab at the University of Texas Galveston is a level 3 biosafety
Labannata level 4
I feel like a
Stickler for pointing that out when Alex Ida was level for but
Difference between those two and also that information is literally on
Page 2 of the starting so
If you made it that far you know what level I was
In in in history
Ain't going to do it
I kind of
Going to do it
That sounds like
Die
And they bled out though
They what
What are brain M sinus
Whatever stomach
Flat out
Just like you shoot somebody with a 12-gauge shotgun
Beyblade out about a minute
Best way to bleed out over the next few years my
Wow
Everything to read an accurate scientific study that was just like
There was blood everywhere
It was bad luck
Everywhere we would God have mercy
I don't want to minimize be like
Gross Ness of
You're keeping his reading this
Now they've all these mice are euthanized
Completely different than with Alex's describe it
People injecting mice
Swiffer vac seed and then
Suddenly
Exploding kittens
Blood-filled watching them bleed out
So Alex is lying about one line that I think someone must have highlighted for him in the study
Mice where I nest
The tized with isoflurane and then bled from the retro-orbital sinus
Plexus
He's taking the second half of that setting
News about bleeding and then pretending that it didn't follow the first half where the mouse work
My swirl put down in accordance
The methodology of the study
This doesn't mean that the mice died bleeding from their noses but that's the image that Alex wants to use these words
Prefabricated
Introduction
God
What have we done
That's too long whether or not we could
Make mice bleed out
Yeah
Alex makes up some more
2012 highly-respected a review
University of Texas long-term study
All sorts of different
Finding massive blood clots
Brain damage
Heart attack
Oregon
Ossining against vaccine
For the Coronavirus
So that clip is 23 seconds long and here is a list of I bet they're more but
Maybe
I got six big 16 bit
What error is that is
It was not a long-term study
Right to it wasn't on all sorts of animals it was just my
3 it didn't find massive blood clot
Go for it didn't find brain damage
They didn't find heart attack show
65 Tashan with proceeding with the application of SARS coronavirus vaccine in humans
That's all good and well but it doesn't match
What's the what I was saying open Pandora
Totally
Might be splitting hairs the photos major research study but I just gave him
Just on account of beating out
Whatever you think it is
You're a gambler
I'm a gambler
Alex's brief summary of the study gets
So much
Completely wrong that even if you didn't suspect as I do that either willful liar you should be really worried about Isabella
Bodytech accurate information
From primary source
Even if you think he has a heart of gold and he means well and you know he's a good guy
This is a staggering display of inability to do the job he's tried to give himself
Sometimes
I'll check in and I'll listen to these like
Find a primary source going to be like
This is bad this is bad work this is funny
Yes so embarrassingly bad
This Is Our God this is like
You should have you should be
Begin the segment
With that carnival music but in a minor key so you know we're entering into a real
Locked up world
You know nothing
This is topsy-turvy World nothing's going to be real and it's all going to be terrifying
Just coming into
I agree
The man I can't even be
Begin to tell you there is a punchline
That
It's Lord milk
But now you
You must think of the mice
Mackerel
You want to read
Here
Overhead shot place what happened to the mice
Bleeding out my sinus bleeding out their brain
Waiting out there
Young Mike
Middle-aged my
A mice young mice
Middle-aged nice
Those nice picture you have mice or just getting ready to go off to college with their whole lives ahead of them
Mice that were two days away from retirement totally planning a life after the career at the software development store
Probably maybe going to get into the puzzles
Do with your old are your spouse
God dammit
But you got to think about the Adolescent mice
You just made the cut for the varsity football team scores
Cut down in their Prime
He he was almost going to make it in
Three
Tragic tragic
Middle Earth
People really really paid take a picture
Superman who killed that many dogs how dare he try to make me care about
What assholes again
Just to be totally clear I have reservations about the way animals are heaters
No I agree I don't want to unpack that right now then busy laughing at middle-aged
Quarterdeck
Middle-aged
B o b they come for us all
Continues to make stuff
Neutralizing antibody assay
What happened to the animal
University of Texas this year
Cjis
This is the University
Did a long-term study on a bunch of vaccine
AR virus
Just skimming the paper now and he saw the headline neutralizing antibody acids
That's just the section about how post euthanasia of the samples are taken from the animals and processed into
Such ways to preserve
Antibodies that might be detected were from the vaccine right there was given as polite
To another
Source
Alex has no idea what the words he's saying even mean but you just knows that kind of sounds scary
Also this study has literally nothing to do with mRNA vaccine
None of the four vaccine studied where that type analysis
Who just throwing that in
To make the audience
I'm scared of current-day covid-19 blacks
Nation course
Because
He has an agenda
Boy
Although again
It's it's
It's a lab
They're put down
It's not like Alex
Is making it sound like everybody is like okay
We injected them with the stuff and then they got a giant meat cleaver and they just
I don't know maybe there is a little bit of that but I think the image
Is that they injected them and then just watch
Probably
Counting the time
Very bizarre Twisted nonsense
Yeah
I never have a vaccine for
What's the most common when the most common family
Because it's a freaking protein that your bodies made up out of
What else is
Address
Giphy some pages of a pentagon
Supposed
Also the reason there wasn't a coronavirus vaccine prior to now is
Primarily because it's a challenging thing to do and money wasn't there for the Reeser
Most coronavirus is are not generally very severe and the two previous times there were series
Relatively
Containment measures and proper protocols
I never got to the point where money was flowing in as an urgent solution was needed
Recognize
Right
And thankfully we also had some preliminary work done in
Forms of studies that were done in the wake of
SARS and MERS
That helped inform
Current efforts
Going on
Of course coronavirus vaccine probably could have been made
When the past
It just would have been a question of marshaling efforts and resources into the right places
And that wasn't the something that was seen as a good investment
Until
Hopefully
Yeah yeah you know I would like it if more people realized it's
Science
It succeeds is
The culmination of failure
And not like
A a simple moment of single
A brilliant inspiration that appears out of
Nowhere it's the culmination of
Years upon years upon years of work
Overly simplistic Lee like 100 things
Could go wrong and then
Could lead to something that's really huge you know you're not going to make the playoffs
If you have Owen 100 record
We're trained
To have this win loss kind of likes
Success failure
Way we look at
It's a different paradigm
It's completely
Different Paradigm the goal
Cuz if you
Fail all the time then when you succeed your like holyshit this is real
Yeah
So Alex
It has a bit of
White identity based
Sears around
Carol Baker CDC spokeswoman telling a giant
Amphitheater both scientists and doctors and nurses
Dad must be got rid of
Because I don't
That's what this is coming from and I guess we do have to have an Irish Scottish
English
Thousand Years a war
Between those groups in Kingstree
Nike where the Magna Carta
And injuries and basic rights come from yes
That's what white people
Really
Wow
I don't even know where to begin with all of the things
Wrapped up in just
That likes just saying that means like
You extrapolate
It means if this is real
Serta white people creative freedom
Just a stray thought maybe he was in too deep on a sentence
It's fundamental to his worldview that no other culture
Has ever created any system
Afridi Afridi
Freedom is essentially a white creation
Cannot possibly believe
Anything else happen
It's outrageous
Imagine him reading a book about a matriarchal
Society
Matriarchal societies that have existed in our past I can't even imagine
And how much
Better they are
Better is relative
Systems that work better for
Circumstance
I'm sorry my anthropology
I respect
Like it
I just
You are very troubled by that
That's really f***** up
Yeah yeah he's talking about about doctor Carol Baker
Clip posted all over right-wing media it's
And it's a Doctor Baker is saying that the solution to getting rid of vaccine denial is getting rid of white
This is not at all being suggested as a serious solution it's clearly mad as a shock
Statement that furthers a different argument
Which is conveniently added out of
The clip that gets posted all over the media
Most of the places to find this clip of it where they post it
Super vague about where the video comes from sometimes just a year
And it's often the wrong gear
I suspect this isn't intentional strategy to make it harder for the audience
To confirm the claims that are being made about it
I tracked down the full video when it's from a panel discussion being held by the national meningitis Association titled quote
Achieving childhood vaccine success of the United
It's not a giant Amphitheater but that doesn't work for Alex and the audiences
Just going to accept whatever dumb shity says
The larger context of the comment was in terms of a conversation about
Strategies
Increase vaccination
Another panelist had suggested media training
For doctors and there was some disagreement about whether or not the media training would be impactful
Dr. Baker was
Expressing that at that position that the discussion to get children vaccinated as an individual event that happened
And over and over all over the country every day we get training
Might not necessarily be the most helpful thing
The conversation had also touched on Multicultural issues like communities
The claim exemptions
From school vaccine mandates
The comic Baker
Made appears to exist in the intersection of these two ideas
It's kind of a freewheeling panel discussion
Kind of go off on some tangent short makes it a little bit difficult to know exactly where she was going short discussion
Absolutely certain
It has nothing to do with
Appealing to White.
I don't know I don't know that sounds like this nonsense
I feel like maybe the CDC is overreacting a little bit to the Trump years but calling for white genocide does she was
With the CDC at the time I believed I think she was of course
Snapchat
Previously
Let's just live
Yeah but Alex Boye
What a mess
Yeah that's not
Oh man he's in a mood
Man
I mean
English Irish and Scotch thing
They invented
Freedom
Like there was no
What's cuz they were fighting about Kings or something if you want
Goku
White nationalist claim Rome 2 or what
Yes yes the people who we most associate
Freedom
I don't know man he's in a mood and I think I might be able to tell you why
Hearing today
Wonders of family court so that's why I take some
Because I got to go
There is a so much to cover and so much to get
WonderFest do anything with his motive be a bad mood might be why he's fine with everybody dying
Could be fine I could be something pretty sad that I like
The mystery becomes clear
This is like this scene in like a Poirot thing where it's like the name of this town
This is this is the dinner party
I will slowly revealed
Perpetrator of the kayak to go to Family Court
Caught him
This is why this is a bombshell no one pays attention to you and everyone's got to die
Yeah
Great
It does not stop hours
Even though he has to leave
Early
Don't stop him from
Continuing to be wrong about everything about this study
Headshot Place well this just got brought to my attention I went checking on the University of Texas website
This is the University of Texas
Biological Research Center level for when the most prestigious in the world
Immunization with SARS coronavirus vaccine
Pulmonary
Autoimmune response
In response to the end of my
What's the weather
And then the photos and all of it
Control group
Lowe's at work
Challenge got really sick
What
Wait what
You should not
Vaccine
Show me those f****** photo
Mercy
Texas
So glad isn't level four
Amino pathology does not mean autoimmune
Nope the article has nothing to do with autoimmune condition correct
Alex is making up how he imagines this test with run
The only mice in the study were not challenged with the live stars were the five from each group there were killed today
Two days early so they could have their lungs
The entire story of the vaccinated group getting
Sick after the challenge and non-vaccinated grouping fine
That just comes from Alex's imagination
There were no photos on the study of hearts or brains because
The only about the lungs
That's the word Alex keeps tripping over in the study
Title
Pulmonary
Alex is making up with the other photos are there or maybe he hallucinated them I'm not sure
Also they tested
Before vaccines in the study I was just thinks there were three because he was skimming and he saw the line
Three different experiments performed for comparing
Different vaccines are reported here
On page 82 that's the word that quote comes but the beginning of these study design sex
In reality there were four vac
Then we're the same type of vaccine whole virus vaccines but they were
A differently
Adidas different adjuvant
So they were experimental lead singer
Also none of the vaccines killed any
Writes all nonsense
Alex cannot
F****** handle
Doing a
Again I mean
Just want to read that study
Weather like
Bucket Man
There are brains with holes in them dude put it in the sky
Sarah Grey
Awesome
He continues lying
I'll get Bill Gates in the UN and the globalist this they've got the size of the Grand Canyon
Teton
Lab level 4
Falmouth all coronavirus vaccine
Cause bleeding analogues the brain the heart
Blood clots
Police Department
No pathology
All the challenge subjects all the ladder
That is from
2012 there's a bunch of the reports coming out they knew this they did it
When your loved one has a heart attack
Please don't forget Wurlitzer supported turbo Fortune
Holyshit
Oh boy
That was 90 degrees
Goddamn
That hurt
I feel like I was in a 30 mile an hour car crash
That sounds like a guy
Walking like a cat
You got to go to court with his ex-wife
So Alex has next winter
On for a little bit and I point this out on our last episode but
When the two of them were talking
Alex said that Nick Fuentes was going to get a channel on banned. Video on Alex's site
And I just took that to be straight talk because he said that you almost everybody
Almost everybody who's nuts and a problem
Yeah Nick has an America first channel on Alex's website
Or actually that's better
Keep it all there get rid of everything else
Stop so he's also got another iron in the fire but he's going to
Explain here
So I was on your show last week to talk
Talk about my placement on the no-fly list which we
Political reasons
Rappers that Mina Kasich
Guess the TSA and
We're going to take it to the chords again to TSA in the federal government
I guess stand-up didn't work out
Wow
Huh who is running
Norma's running a good game
I don't know about that
I need something about some idiot just suddenly calling you because
Alex Jones and being like
F*** it yeah I'll run your dumb lawsuit that's not going to go anywhere you
Idiot
Yeah I guess there
There does appear to be a space
For like
I mean
This is
Stam
Absolutely not a real loss
No it it's
A fundraising opportunity for Nicolette
And if Norms going to skim some of that off in like a billable hours over
That I guess that is a career path you could go down as look like Larry klayman did that for years violin
Frivolous nonsense lawsuit
I don't know anything about
I don't know a lot about it. I know it seems like
Return to the races play Blake
You know getting a bed with
That's just being associated with a deeply like
This is just what happened it is
Ends up like
It gets ruined doing interviews
Stefan molyneux
The norm doing racist stand up and hanging out with Nick Fuentes
Yeah you just can't you can't do it
If you can't you can't
I mean I want to do something else
Can exist in the modern-day without being awake
Anyway so
So Alex goes off the family court
And
Yeah I know he's off the family
So comes back in May 7th
I mean not when his shows on you like them showing up like for the War Room something
Resume he came back and had a little bit of a
A business meeting with a bottle
Sure
This is very little doubt of that there's a lot of work to get done around the office like that chair needed to be thrown over there
I redecorated
You know what the problem with that wall was
And there were zero holes in it
It is
An Unforgivable
So Alex Alex comes back on the 7th
And it gets on air
Hi
I was
Lord by how boring
The first like half hour
He says
Nothing
Treading water
It's just like here I am
Tower of I'm about to
Kind of but I didn't actually feel like he was about to
It felt like other people might be getting to something he's not.
Here's a little clip
Government outlaw
The government's Criminal
Global run
Following its directives is now
Crime against your family matters
Idiot is unconstitutional crap
Any of the contact tracers any intimidation have inoculation
Body
Literally the engineer this whole damn thing
I listen to stuff like that and I just I can't understand how anybody could listen to Alex
Take him seriously and not recognize that
Terrorism is the directing
That's
The state is basically
The only logical outcome
Some of the things
But he said if you believe the things that he's saying
There is no solution
You're fighting the
Devil
That the devil doesn't care about court
Election
No
There's no
Making peace with the
The devil
You have to eradicate
Yes and then the people who follow him and he's surprised all that's left is
People are your friends but I guess I'm not being totally fair because the other conclusion could be complete isolate
Like you could have communes in the woods looking like that complete
The only two legitimate outcome
Good luck political organization is meaningless
Right okay
Now the government is
Outlaw
Any kind of rules
Come from the government
Are not to be followed
Why would you run for office couldn't do s***
Azure by the devil
B
I just
I was I was thinking about that cuz I was so bored by the beginning
Images
It strikes me that anybody
Like who
Takes this seriously
I just can't
Or if they would be doing something horrible
Pixelmon this okay they've already tried to topple the government and it didn't go well
So try isolation
Everybody in the right way
Just needs to go away
Well I I would recommend isolation
With another individual for about an hour a week
Chatting about
What do you think
I just talked about the problems another person
So Alex
The day before his Mufflers lying about the study
And I'm not going to lie you doesn't work
But today is different mood
I would describe his mood as being very similar to a guy who went to Family Court the day before
Fuel prices
Exploding
And that's why I said to do a basket of commodities
My B myself
David Buster
A place in the country.
But away from people
Having your own game
Your own people watch each other's back
Universe
Jesus Christ
So you better get ready now
But I really planned out there to start a race war
Economic collapse
This is all a battle plan
We know what they're going to do we should have been able to stop it
Didn't listen now
I don't say that
Impressive it's just know what you've done peeping is on the air
The big show called government
Schedule
Amazon
What
Kohler Company
Lisa betting
Frogs
Pedophile operations at Industrial Level
Like a combine cut sweet
Mail day
Your similes unclog
Don't turn this around by jaw
With
What I do myself
Percent off
Lowest price Rd out there
Next week
Okay Wednesday
Absolutely end
Just incidental
By the way
Unplug this
Hey while we're here
Look
It's a favor
Really think about it
You think about it I am
Gifting you the
This plug
Is a blessing and so
In order for you to repay that
You need to buy lots of
Now
Dallas.com or just find a subsection
Food
I buy more ammunition
You said you have none
Selling my house in Austin
I'm telling you right now he's dealing with that
Sure
50 million
90% chance
It's all over
I never talk like that never said everything about you
Said anything like that
Roughly 7 billion people will be exterminated only 500 million Arlo
I never talk like that for almost all the time
Sayre
I'm not that's not my thing
I'm not the kind of guy who likes to scare you also boo
Now you should be terrified of all the people coming
Kill you
Ensure
They look nice
I say nice things and they're exactly like you and they're just normal people but they're actually working for the devil in you
You should murder them
Road Warrior
Android
Road Warriors 9:55 yet manual for 9:55
Oh yeah
Oh that's right
Yeah but you know
50 to 100 million
That seems pretty good for a road warrior
Situation
No I'm kind of green
That was the worst Road Warrior was going to get it I feel like it could be worse
Fair enough
So
You know it's glass half empty glass half-full half-empty
Everybody does that
Alex
This study
But he found he was lying about all day yesterday
To a guy who works
UT
Who knows who this guy is
The guy and I just thought this was really silly
What's a heads-up and apartments University of Texas
I know this person for a long time
And when I don't respond
But he responded back in about 20 minutes
Hey Eugene put out this big study under the federal government
I didn't even say
They said it was bad don't take
K
Thanks Maxine
The 2012
I said hey
You keep without this interesting report
Adecco
I'll show you a text
Okay the name
Texting me
Very technical
But
Obviously
Vaccine at 8
This is a warning
The study was a war knife
Dirty work out in public
But I really really don't give a s*** about what anybody on any board
I also the guy saying that he's not going to entirely sure what all of his medical issues
That he's like
He's probably not a younger person
And also they had covid already told them
This is what he reads from the text message they already had a lot of
Antibodies sure
Naturally occurring from heaven
Covid-19
Get a shot which is
I don't know I'm not a doctor so I don't know but that's slightly different than
Don't get the shot that appealed to kill you
Pictures of holes in your brain slightly different pieces of advice be a different angle
This is a warning
It's just so dumb of it so dumb
I'd like to warn Alex
No
You should know what you're talkin about arrest you sound really stupid like that
Good morning
Elimination
Sartre bars vaccine leads to
Anybody ology
I'm challenge
SARS virus
Emu
Challenge
Autoimmune
Responses and their hearts and lungs.
White holes in a minute.
I feel like I'm flogging a dead horse or
Possibly a Deadmau5 here but
I can constantly hitting his drama valix not knowing anything about the study that he's reporting live but he just keeps being wrong and new ways
He's wrong about the details of this study but I think it's more disturbing that he doesn't understand basic terminology that
It's used
Which makes me think that he doesn't even have a handle on the most Elementary conversation that's going on in terms of
This study
As well as any others that he might be
The term challenge refers to the group of mice
Vaccinated as opposed to the ones that were not
And that's not what that term means
In case of this study there were groups of mice that were given various non-experimental injections
Deserve his control
Princeton
Control group got actual live sorry
Another just got the address
Sure the term challenge refers to taking
All of the mice
An experimental
And control group
And challenging their immunity by exposing them to live sorry
That's what this experiment did
And it's critical to understand that concept
Understand the study at all
To any degree
Really dumb and it's funny but
This instant is almost getting it
Embarrassing
Like this this is
Disqualifying
I think
So far his
Description
Suggestive like
Here's what US
Study is
Give me great
Just like
This is true with
Just about everybody
Who is like
Just describe how you do a study
After this is supposed to be after he's read how they did this.
Port over it
Tell me how is his coverage give me a simple like
Here's the
Beginning of the study and explain to me what you think sign
I mean I don't I didn't see this but it turns out that this
Studies actually
Giving
The vaccine around
Going to kill kids
Now they're going to Target the little children and mess them up or lie
Oh man
Wow
My goal suddenly all these
Bravo's
How do the University of Texas says don't do it
You don't care
Got sick and died
Blade
Liberal
You're saving me
Not care because I'm liberal
I don't care cuz I read the source
Well that would
Don't you remember where the source was like
Baba Yaga
Video without holding their brains and then rats broken
Ain't nobody San Jose or exploding given to children that
Villanova delayed
Address where younger as an old rats in this circumstance
Make this more comfortable
Proof
At the end of last week the world
Is reeling
From the news
Bill and Melinda Gates where I get a divorce
I didn't care both into the sun
I didn't care for Alex's
Ruth I thought I did
It turns out there's a massive conspiracy here
Why would I
Robert Barnes has shown up
Alex is now explained
How does all Alex should know how family
Play courtworks
Pretty well well
I mean what why why was Jason them crazy enough to do this I think it's cuz he got busted with Epstein
Operation lockstep on the Shelf
Okay
What are words in there
She's basically
Probably
But yeah he's very adverbs
R2
Batman
Siri is essentially that Bill Gates got caught up with Epstein is all going to come out
He's going to take the
The fall for it
Right now
And so his wife divorce to protect
The Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation
And
She's confirmed it probably
Basically
Probably pretty much
There was a story I saw in the Wall Street Journal that will I was about how
Melinda Gates was mad
About Bill Gates having an association
With Epstein
Why
Does good actor actually strike
Some people have made comments about that but
I think the the bridge that Alec
Texas Crossing is a little bit
Yeah
I mean well
Here's the big
Here's the bigger issue
Is there
Yeah
She knows he was hanging out with Epstein any went to the Isla
It would be insane if she was not at least
A little bit
Concerned about that
You know so that's not really a story to me
We all know
He spent time on Epps
Kings Island we all think Bill Gates is an evil
Bastard
What is fine you know I don't care why they're being divorced I just want them shot on a rocket into the sun
Sherbet
You have to understand that the divorce is a Critic
Copart of covid
Existing
Definitely not
Pick understanding that because the divorce is protecting the Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation now that Bill Gates
About to go down
But
Covid was released
Because
You know the Epstein connections were
Coming out in like 2019 shorter
F****** panic button
Right and then there was a worldwide plague in order for Bill Gates's
Why is this the first I'm hearing of this particular aspect
Conspiracy considering
As Alex has told us
So
Many times
He knows exactly how this is all going to play out
Because this is
Improvisational storytelling not actual
Snooze Aretha possible
It seems like a fun wrinkle for Bill gaither's character a good way to contextualize the divorce
Yeah this is character development
Barnes
Isn't it also Alex calls him Barnes
And I feel like don't fuc
Can call your lawyer by their last name that's just not cool
No no no I want to get my lawyer and Nick
Call my lawyer Dickie
You are f***** if you are that familiar
With your lawyer
I want to call my lawyer mr.
Professional distance between us
I don't want to be like
Survivor lawyer with a question about something else
I don't want to text my lawyer when I'm drunk
Hey Dicky come out today come on buddy
We'll go drink
So Barnes of got some news
Barnes is about to give you exclusive
Information
Here is the exclusive
As Humanity
Yes I want to be filing suit
The next 2 weeks across
Country against three groups
Governments
Employers and educational institutions
Attempting to force or coerce
So Barnes is going to go spread a bunch of attention-grabbing lawsuits around
Special
I just ice
I find it in
Possible
To believe
That you could listen to this entire show
Here Alex
Say that
The government
What is an outlaw
And then listen to Barnes he's going to file some lawsuits and be like you get them yeah this is going to solve this
This is an exclusive that I wanted to hear about it I can't wait to throw some money at Barnes please
Support these lawsuits Windows to
Ben will then we'll put his plan off for at least
Warriors
Comical nonsense he's asking the audience
Yeah wild I don't think much of Barney
Boris
You have to go away get ammo
Food
Hi prepare for the road warrior
Weave
Sell some of that Amo
Jesus man
Rodger Barnes
And I wasn't like really all that worried about the
His lawsuit going anywhere
Is not going anywhere
Tell well working with Bob
HobbyKids
And others
All of the legal issues related to these cases and the Constitutional issues
We will have the suits filed within the next two weeks
He's working with Robert Kennedy the anti-vax
Kingpin
Yeah it was not going to work out
No I see I feel like Barnes was doing that to cover up the stink of the name Robert Kennedy
Robert Kennedy Jr
Sirhan Sirhan actually hiding or what
Another person I don't want to be on familiar terms
So
I'm going to skip ahead real quick
Because I want a barn
Explain his loss
We are suing under the Ada
The Discrimination Act
Perceived as disabled
We're going to be doing the same thing
Because my view is that
Requiring someone
And then treating them differently based on
Perception
Is discriminating against them based on
Your perception of their disability
In-state analogous laws that are also similar
So the fact that Barnes is working with Robert Kennedy and the idea that
Keystone of his argument combined to tell me this is not a case he expects to win
To be in court
The day
Says those exact words
To a judge
Just on its face I suspect this will get thrown out but there's a huge element of disability law the barn scene
To be pretending
Doesn't exist
According to the government's page on disability discrimination they do make a
Very important caveat
The law requires an employer to provide reasonable accommodation to an employee or job applicant with a disability unless doing so
So would cause significant difficulty or expense for the employer
An undue hardship
Even if somehow Barnes were able to convince
Record that not wanted
Can you get a vaccine with legally analogous to heaven
The disability he would still have a really hard time overcoming the argument
But having people potentially spreading covid around a workplace or
School
Doesn't represent an undue hardship on an employer or
Educational
Institution
You run the risk of yours Workforce or teaching staff falling ill and that's not even considering the potential
Haven't
Shutdown
Factory or possible bad press
Second come from
Being a site of a new outbreak
Pride month
Nick Fuentes trying to sue the TSA this is not a
A serious case
There's a griffin a PR stunt disguised as a legitimate lawsuit
It's all just grandstanding and attention-seeking behavior
It's wasting everyone's f****** time
Yep but I do I do also
Want to be in the
I do think you'll be pretty funny
It's never going to make it to a courtroom
Absolutely.
Like I do get that lawyer ring is a
Shannon lawyers
Text each other and you know
Judges don't often hold lawyers in contempt
Of course more
Say
I don't know going on Infowars
Isn't saying that the stated reason that you're doing this lawsuit is based on magical nonsense thinking that you don't
Understand what soap
Clever
F****** talking about
Yeah you know what I think the issue is Barnes is
I think that he's less a lawyer and more a guy who has a page on Dave room
Patreon clone called local
That sounds like it and I think you promoting his locals page
With the looming idea of these lawsuits
Great I think that he's just trying to sucker people into supporting him on fake patreon
And yeah bro how did that lawyer Collective
Constitutional lawyers
Workout
Remember that one from a few years ago when he was going to start that group of people
Yeah I don't know if that
Bad ideas I'm actually kind of glad that
It didn't seem like it happens to get a lot of money for it
What happened all that bull
Oh
Well
Hey would you like to know how the Chinese people make covid
Subject
This clip is nonsense
Okay
Milan
One that got the got the virus
Bullmastiff
Did you replicate that the pig
Can you do it then used to extract the blood
The viruses you one now you got about growth of viruses and you keep rolling them
And then you release it
In the human population where start
It wasn't free Marshalls
Five on steroids
Before everybody
Call Michelle
Of course oh my God it's so obvious
What
It's so obvious
Look Occam's razor tells me that's exactly what happened
Alright
Sci-fi come with a warning label
Like a warning advisory for people who cannot tell the difference between reality and
Steve is really going to f*** you up like what Alex just said
Test before you can read science fiction
Maybe we need to have some sort of comprehension test words like listen
It's like a family video
Do you know like they got those they got the room in the back with all the foreign you got to be 18 to go that road
Library should have that
Forsyth
Expands people's minds in such a way that you know as a young boy reading like Ray Bradbury or something
Unlock a lot of creativity
Added me as a young boy
I think that's the case for a lot of people
I think that the good outweighs the
Because I think
The case of Alex is showing
Stop saying 18 I'm saying there should be a test
I don't want to limit the excess of sci-fi to the the Young
Kids out there
Might be Overkill might be Overkill
As far as I know there is only one person who has a relationship with sci-fi like Alex
Very bad very bad reality for a lot of people to live there and it's
Very profitable
I don't think that
I don't think we need to regulate Syfy
Might be an overreaction I bought that that boss
Blue Sky
Reasons for this man
He says that they're going to feed a pig to another pig to get the
The first
I do like the idea though that Alex explains all that
Obvious
Barnes's react
Exactly
What are you
People
In your brain
This is what I'm talking about when you go back to 2003 and you have these gas
That are a little bit at least like
On their own turf
They're not these bootlicker
So we got to learn about a false flag
I think Barnes might be wrong
Digging deep
Find out the claim is not an organic
The clan would rise and fall
Locations in power supported them or not
They were weaponized tools
The Establishment infrastructure local to the community
Organic group
That's why you don't need that supposedly
Clan made up of poor white people
Those poor white people that have been some rich white
People hanging from trees
Hoo-boy
Hellboy
Want
Barnes
To speak
And now
That he has
I regret
Swag my friend
That is
Yeah it's a bummer Bellboy
So also he thinks
Not only that the claim is a false flag
Antifa
Is
Was legitimately in an artistic group
Why have they never attack
Good
University
Not natural fruit but also
Like there are people who associate with anti-fascism
Are capitalist
There are people who are anti-fascist cleaning who
Are Anarchist or believe that there is a place for the stage
It's antifashist
Feel like he's missing that
Crucial aspect because I think it's I think it's intention
No you can't be like if antifa wants to be an anarchist group
Without immediately stopping and being like
Does the antifa want to be an anarchist did they name themselves
Anarchy Anarchy
Eastgroup
Anti-capitalists
Like sure we can do all of those things but if
If you were describing it
It's called 84
You can be for capitalism
Philadelphia
One might argue that the eventual Road will always
Fascism but
That's a conversation.
Different
Feel like
Prior to becoming a
Nationalist
Stefan molyneux
Spine hanging out with
Anarcho-capitalist
Anyway
How many Wall Streets of you f******
Occupied
Dumbshit
They ever gone after the Fed
Wow
Sure but that was a false flag
Oh that's true
Barnes
Skedaddles out cuz you got a lawsuit going to work
So Alex Goes to call
And just call her
This little 10 sec
Can clip is perfect
Booster shots Ruby patches micro glass that goes in your skin so they can track you if you know that
No but I
I mean I believe anything now and I just
PSU will oh no no no
That was a perfect moment Alex says something like I didn't believe anything
Yeah that will do will believe anything
Do you listen to this b*******
Yeah
Um probably run and win office as a Republican
If your if your slogan was just
You'll believe any old should I say
Call God if you did something that would be like
Universally
Decried as offensive and horrible
I'm going to run for office
But I'm never going to wear
I'm not a shirt guy
I say it like it is
If you're really confident about it I bet you could win on a Gob probably
Yeah
Cuz they just don't
F****** care
They don't act
Suggest
Hate the left
I stick it to the libs
But I insist on every public appearance that I have I'm wearing a snake on my neck
Here's what we got
You want to stick it to the libs
You go with me
Shirt or no
Would you want to not stick it to lose you vote for one of those other assholes over there they're not going to stick it to the lips
Now probably wearing
Suit
No shirt no shoes no service
Nolibs is what it is no shirt no shoes or lips
No shirt no shoes no
Make ramen.
Landslide
Alex has been having a good time on this side this episode but
We kind of sucked up
He went to play a bunch of videos of antifa pretending
Bixby cops sure sure that sounds right
I'm sorry antifa pretend
I really want to spend a half hour today
I never bother you
Going crazy I'm about to play a few of the clubs but I'll just have to
Winter stories and I've been doing pretty good job
They want the shutdown
Economy under going to use
The cover for the collapse and then blame that
Raipur
Wait what
Martial law
But your calls are actually a lot about that
Research
Today
Wow
That's difficult to follow just
As ideas
I guess you really take issue with his the idea that obviously there's going to be a global collapse
Calming natural in order to
To make sure the bankers don't get blamed for the global collectors
But your calls are more important naturally
Absolutely
If I were a color I would take issue with that I just don't even I don't even know how to hear him
Just saying words that's exactly what I
Like when he's when you're following along with what he thinks is supposed to happen it what
Certain is supposed to happen everything he's doing
It is insane
It is an insane person
But that's what I'm saying is this real or fake it doesn't matter
If you believe this stuff is crazy
He doesn't believe this stuff he's made me more insane
So Alex does end up playing
Some videos of antifa acting like cops either
Major I didn't want the audio
And this is a surreal thing if
You are just listening to the audio
Because
You can't see what
The on the video and he does
Say like
He doesn't narrate the deal at all. Kind of bumbles
About violence
And it's very upsetting
Watching stopping
Renata just beating people up
People I mean
Unless it's just trash
I'm sorry man
Reflect your throat
Johnny
Are you sure you don't want to file a lot of that around like a real problem
You want to punch my buttons be five or six people Center
When the big
What's the weather
I just destroy each person Awana time
Whoa
Okay
Is gone in a Direction
Yeah that's not good you go to Family Court
Self-esteem whatsoever is in the only way I know how to express that it's through fantasies of viola
Plants which makes me a healthy person is everything kosher my audience that it's easy to kill people
Is that cuz I'm a man
No I don't have a governor I would not like
To see this kind of conversation on any program
Like any program that
Trying to be political or talk about issues
Mumbling about murdering people is just
Goof
Whoever
I've been what lawyer was it that
Made it so that they could
Didn't show
Clips of his show
Barnes
Cuz whoever did that
Man
Imagine just going to Family Court
I'm just being like hey
After we went to Family Court last time
I'm going to play this clip of aleksandr show it's very easy to kill I do not have a governor
Most people think it's hard to cover themselves on the other hand
Use with murder could we please keep this man as far away from us
Possible
Of course
Simon says something about murder that I actually kind of think is
I mean it's not news
Young
I know why you have that Intuit
No
I think we know that and we have known that for a long time well aware of it kind of been the whole thing
About you
Types Alex's that you
Very clearly want to kill us
Won't stop talking about
In Injustice
Just amazing how in a very short. Of time you can save
Trash
Obviously I could kill
And I want to
And I don't know cuz I know you do too and you could do
That's the problem that's the problem
Obviously I have no Governor or immoral
Said him and I'm willing to kill despite being
A Christian
I am ready and willing to kill with no Governor I have no governor and the left
Think
That they're all safe
The veneer of our politeness and murdering is starting to slip
Yeah buddy
It slipped while ago remember when you stormed the goddamn capital
Are the United right Rally or
All the murders you guys do
Cooking burgers
Talks
Yeah
Yeah that f****** psycho
We want last clip here and take the call
And I just
Want to play this because I think it's unhinged
One I was going to
See if you could like
Hold a call in
Fashion show
Time in H
Like on Sunday or Sunday night or something like that
Power Sunday
Dedicated
You're right
Thank you thank you
Is on October 12th
And I prayed right along with you on that
Prayer B
Yeah I think our prayers got Trump elected
This is just like this is great
If I were out I'd be so pumped about something like this Wednesday
Okay the audience is starting to suggest
Did I become a televangelist
Yeah I can make this transition work is just push a little bit if I can have a proof-of-concept
Where I start doing shows that are entirely she or religious
I can make that profitable
I can stop this whole bulshit
Man I can stop doing things that are going to get be sued all the
Hi hi just want to scream at the
These people I don't
Why would I wish I wish I did not have any
No biblical education
I just ate
Drives me insane like I was hammered into me so much
Sofa
Talking much
Now that the idea of
These people saying oh we're so f****** Christian in the left is evil and immoral and ship
Read your goddamn Bible
Do you imagine can you imagine Jesus
Woodfield
It's an if you made money off of praying to him
Hour-long show just about prayer for you and then he's going to plug in the
God dammit
You're going to tell me your Christian
The s***
Play Smite the globe
Dammit
I hate this f******
Please
Smite my enemies
Amen
Also. I should tell you it's 45% off
All these bodies on the real
The real
It is just it's just sitting there and I see some
Yeah I think
I think it would introduce a difficulty for me in terms of like
If you're sure when
It's full televangelist
Google having me here no I think I'd have to keep
Doing it
Right I have to keep following the show
It's a new frontier for us
I don't think they necessarily that's where he's going although I do think it would be a
Smart decision
Probably just why whenever they're sort of
Indications of
An instinct to go that way though
Take that off ramp man probably smart
You can survive these cases that you're in the middle of now
Televangelism
Your golden
The speaker's been scamming for
Decade
Prison. Even trying
Triage
Went to prison in just smoothly walked back into it he has a compound in the Ozarks
Everybody no one talks about it into the middle of nowhere
Jim Bakker survival food he owns people who live in is Campo
That's real he can tell them what to do whenever he wants
Oh my
My God
The hammock retirement
It heads like Alex a Dream Most
I thought this was fun if only because you know this
Study was
Just at Justice
Travesty
Of Alex
Just being unable to
Yeah deal with any kind of source material that wasn't even rejected that was lit on fire before he even had
The Chancery
It made me think of you frequently
Maxwell.
Nice bookends
Full circle there was a narrative
Through line and you close it out
What's wrong with spouse Mouse
How goddamn
I am never going to Top Spice Mouse
Hilltop sprouts
Spell spouse is not that good
I like your Vibe you tired
Jordan will be back
Another episode
We have website
Sorelle salon
Please find a local charity or bail fund
Check for new episode of role-playing it's middle of the week
Another
Of ducks wild saying in French
Goddamn Wizard101
The play on goddamn I assume there's a wizard we're going to run into eventually
So enjoy that
Look for that
But until then I'm near I'm Leo I'm dzx Clark I'm Daryl rundus
The sex robot
Alexandra first in color with huge fan I love your work