Damn important
I have great respect for its knowledge by I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Need money
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
I'm done working with dudes I can sit around for The Elder of Celine and talk a little bit about Alex Joe
The second time we drove because something happened
We ripped do I'm not a one-page guy
That was as a cover-up for a better on the second arrest
Girl you're a little in your head on the second take because you were disappointed that the
The first take was so good down in your notebook not a one take
Cut you off at the past
I made a return visit
To the legend
Ballyhooed know I don't know if anyone's ballyhooed
Store here in
Chicago
Crystal balls and books and probably tarot cards
For Sheriff Sage that you can burn to like purify places and what have you put the oils are those selection of bats.
And I have gotten bad
That is true that is true
I have a bag
That has a promises psychic powers
And I have not used it yet
Because I'm afraid
Ascribed
No it doesn't know Mel psychic powers
Why haven't used them yet
You risk too much power
Movies about sat
Hearing everyone's thoughts do you think it's a good one of those classic monkeys Paula type situations
Do you know be careful what
She wished for and I will never wish for second power
Yeah so that's that's on my near my bathtub as a in case of emergency
The brake light Powers but for now it's just
For now it's just drink quility and
I like that
That's a good spell
Coming coming up soon coming up soon Rafa
In a bunch of a he's playing on Clay right now getting
Ready to go for
Inevitable next French Open win
And today for really tough
Match with Chipotle who is also one of my favorite player Canadian
Gangles
In the
The present tense
Okay incredible tennis
Best player though
Fantastic match
Walnut in the tiebreak
Raphael
Just great
Is great morning
Very exciting
That wasn't for you this morning I just
Do we have
I was going to say it's interesting
We have an episode to go outside
That's what I want I've been broken
Still got to do a shower I don't know what to tell you that's not fair
Stephanie ERB
Becoming endlessly
What's ground down
Is May 11th 2021 blackjack
And
Close out that
No that was brutal
I'm getting ground down by is
Is that
Think we've already talked about this show is
Incredibly OneNote anti-vax nonsense
And
When Alex comes through with something exciting like
One of these primary source document
Like actually
This is kind of an interesting thing to look into this thing we can learn here short middle-aged device
Fantastic
What fun we can have there
Other times Alex
Just
He's got nothing
Sure and sometimes but nothing comes in the form of a bombshell
Tired of non-existent
Haven't heard anybody polygon yet
I'm sick
Pic.of
The like
The biggest news in the world being nothing
And just like that
Burnt out something in your brain you know where you just like something to be so fake excited about school
Something I don't know I'm going to be in the pasture the next episode
It is a little bit
Exhausting
You can only be guess what so long
Before it starts to break your believing Alex little bit
It makes it less painful but the process is still there
Frustrated
Completely inculcated
From
Kind of results today's bombshell was just like
I'm out I'm going to be out for a while so
I'm selling this episode real well
Jordan take a little moment and say hello
LeVar Burton host Jeopardy in July
I agree with you on all front but LeVar Burton
Matrix practitioner of clown-like bondage thing is much of an alibi was he walk
Thank you very much
The foxy is chicken Emily thank you so much you and I'll probably walk
Rizzo jerky
Thank you very much
I don't want to say this
Oh well don't whisper it into my ear and also
I'm not going to do that I'll just bite the bullet on this
The return of poop Feast 420 thank you so much you are now both
I'm a policy wonk
Installment
Technocrat
Freakishly large
Exactly sometime
4 birthday
Sometimes it's kind of difficult because you do it at the bottom of a well
Private that's right there on the pennies
Breadboards birthday I should say everybody who we wish happy birthday to I do throw a penny into a well on your behalf
I'm not sure whenever someone's birthday is on the weekend
Whether we should do this on
Friday shower on the Monday show what do you do
That's parent do it after the fact or do you wish them happy birthday a couple days early Patrick's Day when do you celebrate
Observe
I never quite now but I'm going to go ahead and go
Ahead of the game
Cameron's got a 30th birthday Nicole would like to wish you
Congratulation
Happy birthday hope you have a great one
And hopefully doing this
If you'd heard this on Monday like I've been like
Wow that would have made my birthday a lot better if I had fokken heard it earlier but what if
She's so important to him but now the rest of his actual birthday is just going to be huge let
Down everybody's going to be like
Happy birthday my birthday was when the knowledge fight guys said happy birthday for way too long
This is the risk we take
Jordan there's one bit of news that's been going around that it won't address doesn't come up on this Epic
So but it did something
At the beginning of this week and that is that Alex's back in the gold game my man infowars.com
Alright it's about time
I've been seeing indications that he was getting ready to
Start this back up again but I wasn't
I'm sure if he was ever going to take the plunge
And that a large portion of the show on Monday with an interview with his new gold sponsor a guy named Drew Mason
From St Joseph partners
A precious metals outfit out of Pauli
Pennsylvania
I don't know too much about this guy or his business outside of the fact that he decided to get into business with Alex Jones
The 2021
So I can't say much about what's going on with him but I know he's not cool
Cannot give this cold away
Partner with Alex
So I did find it interesting I was looking into it a little bit and there's no physical address for Saint Joseph's partner
Available on their website
Text
Struck me as a little bit curious
Dancehall with a chest buried in
Backyard with the contact information is literally just an email address
Here's where things get weird
See if you click on their contact us page
An image of a Google map
That pops up
With a marker at the address
The Green Dover Delaware 19901
However
A tax shelter Delaware
Thursday
If you Google st. Joseph Partners you get a different ad
Lancaster Avenue
Paola Pennsylvania
This is the address for Pauli Plaza to the strip strip mall of shops
Looks like there's a real
Good luck brick-and-mortar location for you pulled up
There is a Rita's Italian Ice
I think they said
Specifically may have chosen
17 seven
As a
No I don't think so I think it's a coincidence
How is a city with Japan population of like
Just over 3502 why would they have a
Chopper it's ridiculous
It's a UPS drop box
Better
Ugly already realized
Delaware is attacks
Haven type
Yeah yeah
Eat the green and Dover is a pretty notorious address
It's me location that's used by a company known as a red
Mustard agents
Incorporated which allows people to incorporate their business in Delaware
A lot of folks do to avoid
But it's actually not
That it's not all about tax
The LegalZoom has a breakdown of the advantages and disadvantages
Incorporating in Delaware
When you file in Delaware you don't need to do
Disclose your directors and officers names to the
The state allows you anonymity
That's way better than not paying taxes have people for that option
This became an issue was New Years back as was covered in the Delaware News Journal in the SEC
EBay Stylo please
Fighting games
In fraud
235 companies word issue
24 of them were based in Colorado other restaurant Delaware
And most of the businesses in Delaware where run through a registered agent Incorporated
Anything that's explicit wrongdoing but it's a it's a bit sketchy
I would say that the only way Alex we come up with a gold dealer I'd be less inclined to do business with and Ted Anderson is if it were
Who was the guy with no apparent physical address suicide appears to be
Explicitly saying that he got a phony incorporation in Delaware
How do you clear this and if anybody out there is actually interested in investing
Singing precious metals
Have to assume that there is a safer better option other options that aren't just a weird dude with a
UPS drop box
It's there's at least
Three other option
Renting a boat
Going under the water for Sunken Treasure
That's out that's in a way better option
Of course there is
Globetrotting and stealing ancient artifacts from Egypt
Turn the Lights sure that's always a good option
And then I guess this
Alchemy
Yeah you're right
There's always four ways to learn
I don't know I'm not excited about this endeavor I think it looks really sketchy as hell
Incidence of Alex having like
Landing pages
With other people s***
Cuz it's like okay sweetheart Infowars gold.com but that just takes you to St Joseph St Joseph
Yeah basically
So we get to May
Garnet off the show
Alex has
Big news
Does he ladies and gentlemen it is Tuesday May 11th in years 2021 and
This is undoubtedly the most important news we ever broken today
Few hours I was pleasantly surprised
I got home and turned on Tucker Carlson to have dinner with my family
That he's robots
Yeah I know that was 11 ruling upsetting image
I have the biggest news of my career
And I got sleepy last night
Honestly you know
Around 11
Xanax kicks in and I'm just out
I'm in a life-and-death battle with the Devil
And
I have the
The Silver Bullet that will defeat the Devil
Yeah I mean I think that's one of the devil's big advantages he never seems to get tired
So I was curious about this big nose
Decided
That day that I
Got the biggest news ever we already had the biggest news ever like twice this week
Enzo's
Happy bag
Tucker Carlson
Fauci let the Coronavirus
Why isn't there a criminal investigation
Well we have the Smoking Gun or the director
For Bill Gates and for fauci
Who created the five and one super virus on video
Episode of a podcast called this weekend virologist
Do you produce by the American
Society for microbiology
The guest is Peter dancing
The president of ecohealth alliance
How much grams is a director for Bill Gates but this
This clip that's from the actual interview seems a little bit at all
With that
Do you have support from
Say
Gates Foundation
Gates money
Thanks
You guys have a struts
AJF
Specifically targeting things that like
Incident
What two diseases
Neglected
When will they consider
Anyway
Big mess up there are the Giant news of the day right out of the gate yeah that's not that's not a good story
This is a really interesting interview that Peter Daysha cat
But it's been completely misuse by Alex to paint the picture of a guy confessing to created Stars Cove
Go to
In reality the ecohealth alliance of the nonprofit that works on global health issues from the perspective of what Peter calls
One Health
This is the philosophy that every condition has a human component an animal component an environmental
Component
Trying to approach any condition without considering the intersection of these three is not going to be as full of a strategy
Hitting the folks
Picture into my
Beacon Health Alliance grew out of a conservation organization
That you can make pragmatic
An economically sound
Free collage
Conservation
For instance in the interview Peter brings up the unexamined health cost of deforestation that massively outweigh
Prophet that are made from
The practice right
If it can be made clear to everyone.
Decision-makers that
Not only is
Destruction of nature bad
What is also not even in the best interest
Prophet
These people believe that they can make Headway towards conservation Act
Right
I watched the whole 35-minute interview and essentially what it comes down to is that Peter discusses working with labs in many countries
Including China
Where they do surveillance of animal populations
To try to identify any
One of the concerns he brings up his coronavirus has any disguises
How you can manipulate coronavirus is in a lab
Pretty easily
How to take a nap statement to be
Confession the Peter combined a bunch of viruses together and then at least them is SARS coronavirus 2
But the reality is really different
It's really just about crafting lab test
Assess whether or not newly discovered viruses can even info
Affect humans
If I were Peter daciuk I would immediately Sue Alex.
Totally there's a video with a picture of him with a title quote
Smokin gun video fauci project manager confesses to
Creating covid-19
That's a definitive analysis reporting
Outrageous
Yeah then I can't imagine
How
Unsafe
This is to do to somebody
Exactly what the line is her like public figure
But I'm not sure that I would put the president of ecohealth nonprofit
Celebrity or someone
I guess an argument could be made that he's
Become somebody who goes around on
Some news program
I'm talking about
Autovision
Alex force him into becoming a public figure by giving him the attention that he should never have had in
In the first place
No I think I think
Even without
Some of that he would have been seen as somebody who would be gone to for interviews
On on the early days of the outbreak are
Made some media rounds
Forget what I'm saying is I'm not sure exactly where that line is
I'm not sure what side he's on but I would be
I would be quite literally
You worth discovery
You can't just do the
Vista people
No I saw a little bit of that Tucker thing
And I just
Began spitting
Like I
The idea of him
Doing that
After being
The cause of us
All being lock
Lockdown for a
F******
Year
That's grounds for immediate slapping
If you see him you get to
25 Tucker Carlson in the face
Viva Tucker piece was largely based on that article that Nicholas Wade Road
Even that
Doesn't claim to have a
Occlusion
The second or third paragraph of it is
I have no direct evidence for either Theory whether it's a lab origin or natural origin
It's being used
People like soccer to
Push the it must have been made in a lab
Alex's version is far more you respond
Possible then
Then we'll talk or should I
Totally totally
Which is which is normal but
He's anyway Alex got scooped by Tucker
I told you I was coming out
Tucker Carlson
Broke it last night
About 20% of it
But the clippy didn't play we're going to get to that after we played undergrowth report apart of
Is that the director of the program under fauci and Gates on record funded by them
Volume box for justice program
Gave an interview and admitted they were slicing five viruses together
As a bioweapon didn't produce the club vaccine for
Emergency authorization to do it
Game over for these people as gentleman
Give the public ever grasp this
Game over
Cost of being made up in that clip
Alex plays
Tucker clips
Most
Like a lot of the first hours
That's a good job and I don't make a big enough deal out of this but like he plays
Lot of time
Tucker Carlson
That's great it's
Salata
Play some special report
Sometimes I love it I love knot
Having to do my job
And that is a perfect
Encapsulation
I will just let a
Famous person
Bill in time that's great escape myself with him
It's brilliant brilliant marketing
I found this to be a little funny
Your Tucker Carlson will come back
You're never
Taking off the mask
Get ready for a lifetime of
Tilting wet
Cotton covering your mouth
Reduced oxygen flow to your brain
In a world where every stranger looks the same because no one has
As a face
When, Harrison her husband kiss the other day while wearing masks
They were giving you a
Preview of your daughter's wedding
Human beings net worth
Yub f****** babies
I don't watch Tucker Carlson that much so I don't know if this is like
Indicative of his style
Holyshit
Do you got some
Maigari dramatic writers
I'm going to watch instead of signing
Language there should just be a picture and picture of a guy making the jerk-off motion just totally
That's a lot of dick
And I mean like a visit just like the next day the CDC released guidance that if you're vaccinated
Criminal
It should be criminal you when you see him in the streets
The dangerous precedent
Your regular walk that back
There's only been we will only set this precedent for one person not sure I can sign off on that
What is
You're never going to be taking the mascots Huskies mascot
Great and Alex are the biggest news ever
Ladies and gentlemen on Alex Jones your house we're breaking the biggest news we have ever brought
We are incredible what's happening
Lab manager
For the covid-19
Added move when the scientist in Wuhan
Midtown video to merging five viruses together
To be able to then
Your poison
Was listening to this and it didn't match
The interview
Yeah it didn't
Seem at all accurate
He's on video saying 12:55 viruses
Were combined
Play that
What
A bombshell he confesses to it
Really confused
It didn't seem like it was what I watch so I when they watch Alex's Special Report
About this
Patrick was talking about how some of the coronavirus as they discover didn't have known
The interview asked
Interview interview
I'll ask the follow-up question about that
Discusses how
Because so much of it involved with protein you probably want to create a vaccine
That was effective against
Multiple Coronavirus
Sure he was just
Just got to get in terms of like that lives that seems like something people would do if they were going to go that route
Not at all is a template
I've used viruses together
He's like Alex's pretending is guys like
Together with viruses
He's got some magical sci-fi technology words spinning around
Incredibly clear
Strongly point
Did to that
Alex is talking about this with
Premeditated intention
Of hurting people
With the idea of shutting down the economy the idea of
Killing people in the developing world
Any saying that this guy
Is admitting to doing that
By way of creating the virus
Stocks are CO2
And I think you should be safe
Algebra suit call the man responsible for what would essentially be maskell murder
So
I would hope that that would be in Subway to Fable 2
Real playing with fire
Especially considering everything we know about Alex's audio
Okay
This is not a bomb
I talked about this quite a bit
Amalfi Oaks
Pipeline shutdown
Food shortages
In Florida
Grocery store
So Alfie Oakes is the guy who owns that grocery
Restore that I work at 2 in Florida for a week
A while back
Former oil pipeline expert
Not but I don't care what he has to say
However it should be noted that he's only relevant in any way
Because he's made a big deal out of how no one has to wear masks in his grocery
In a completely unrelated story I would like to inform you that Ted Nugent tested positive for covid just one week
After doing an in-store appearance at Oaks grocery store seeds
Table
Prior to this Oaks it appeared on Ted Nugent YouTube show called Spirit campfire
Exit quote
No one is getting infected here no one's dying I want to get
The fraud it's a shame
And people have to wake up
These people
I'm starting to think that believing that
Witches are responsible for your problems is a recipe for getting covid
So Alex has this idea that no one else
Says posting
Tucker Carlson Sega
Hey and Sookie
He's going to put it up on his website
Because he's
Content or anything
The whole thing posted
NFL player Carl Ruiz
14 minutes
Supposed to
Pinterest
Boston Amanda
Reference
Historic referee
Copyright
Gone in an hour
5 minutes from now
I am going to
Right here
This is all the documents you talking about and the videos
Total open-and-shut case
Where's the grand jury in America
If I had to show them this in the clip
Would not indict fauci
Have you really funny to see Alex trying to
Cicuta Grinch
Yeah you know this
This Alex doesn't have
Is hardness
It doesn't he realize I think he didn't actually read the story
I get a sense that a lot of points
That he didn't
Doesn't really have a handle on
The details
And he can't really weaponize the
The story
Like this video
This podcast
The interview was
Munsell
It may be a year old
March
And if you going to look at it on YouTube months back
People are commenting on it like
Oh my God that's smoking gone.
Been in that spaceship for a while
It's just that Tucker brought it up the night before
How to make a bombshell out of it without actually knowing the story at all
And so he just
Kind of rushes
The air in it
Stupid
I find myself
Just incredibly uninspired
And
At the same time I think it's
Incredibly funny that Ted Nugent probably got covid by going to This Guy's Grocery Store
Both guest on the show
Today
Tweakers
That's
I don't even know how to deal with that honestly in like a real Universe where you believe in real like where you accept real
Reality
I can't be in the headspace of somebody who thinks
Any of
What happened
Is okay
It's funny but it's not great
No
It's not the kind of funny I'm looking
Going for in the past for a little bit so funny
Anyway
Fauci
That guy
Tony fauci
We looked into the beginning of the pandemic end
Yeah that all star he's a legend deduct
The doctor Steve
One of the best one ever existed
But then all that went away really fast
Anyway he's got to be executed
Don't tell you them are going to be lucky they just going to let restaurants in prison at
A lot of them
It doesn't sit down through the courts I'm not calling for
I believe
They should be fried
Recreational biological warfare on the Nuremberg code
Oh I thought you meant tired to work for us
And we'll see who wins in the end of this but I know this time of God
God watches
Battlefield number Our Lives of our children
My soul
Into Christ
Orbitz
Commit my
T'god
We got Albion
Boat coming on Bittersweet producers
On the East Coast
What's really going on
When a Giant Food price increases
Don't forget
You have until
Tomorrow night at midnight again
To get last year's prices on microwaves work
Ready to ship to you within days
Convenient
May
Yeah
You're going to have another chance to get last
Winx Club December you'll have a chance to get last year's break
Easter sales December
So yeah I just I said that to be
Like
Right
This is how it goes
Violent fantasies towards his enemies
Daf blah blah blah I love God
Food guys coming on to scare you I sell food
Yeah
That is that is really really late
It is really lazy
It's such a stark contrast between like
The bad David surrounded the middle-aged mice
Because at least like that
Bunny is
Chalazion
Funniest
Minute Podcast interview with a guy from a year ago
But Alex
It's doesn't have a handle on it
Do much with it it's just
Sister grocery store guy and
Bill Nye
Yeah both of these guys
The other news in the world
Pipeline
Backpacks
Yeah I heard the question my response to it was
Okay Alex
Vine
Can you got the
Keystone XL pipeline
It was opening a few months ago it.
Close friend
All the oil from
Around the Midwest
And then set up a colonial pipeline
Pictures of Shadow
Suspect is
I have made up that vitamin is the Prime Suspect
Reporting is the most likely possibility
Interesting historical analysis
Play bigger bombshell than anything else
Bombshell
President
Max owned by flight
Yeah and also I can
Can't help but like
Now that I know that Alex
You know back in the past would say that is prediction of 911
Was based on historical analysis
Sherman research
Cooper said that
I can't help it hear him say stuff is based on like research
You're probably lying
And you probably had a dream
You watch the net the night before and then
Transposed Biden's besan to Sandra Bullock which is a nightmare I agree fell asleep watching Tucker and now
You're a little bit of
NyQuil
You're f***** up man I
I still can't get my head around the idea that the whole family like gathers around it
Dinner table and they have
Carl's in
I bet they do
Of course they do
That would be a
That's the worst thing I can
Can think of yeah I bet they don't do that I bet Alex sits alone and needs
All the time alone watching Tucker
Take notes
So I'll be okay
This is on and it's mostly just about to fear
Spreading fear about food
Wingstop
You also should know that if you want to take that seriously you should know what else
Alpha bully
We know that
Agenda
Is lockstep with every single thing that these globalist want
They're take over where the last Beacon end
I do feel I've I had I do it with all this
Doing that we see I do feel
I do feel very confident that we're going to
The country back this time it's not going to be
Easiest not going to be as fast as everybody wants but
Are American Spirit is still there
I stopped you
You know those eighty million people that voted for Trump and then somewhere in the 61 million
No thoughts Taylor let's talk about solution
Sue Trump actually won
I'm working to get the country back
Huh
Does he seem like a really credible source
Burger kind of guy you want to hang out with
What
Is it about
White man and undeserved
Is it come from then actually is looking into a mirror I don't I don't know I don't know if it's confidence that
This guy is undeserved
Cuz I think he's asleep
Possible sleuth
And I base
Is that on this next
Clip where do you live out of
Conspiracy
Almost certainly true
Probably
Not come
Come close to proving it
Anna might also tip his hand a little bit too much at the end of this month
Maybe
These companies like Masonic
Monsanto in particular by bear
Think about this for a long time and that you used to be
Conspiracy theory
Bike putting real fertilizer in the ground like organic fertilizer there putting this
Mpk that
What universities are okay to use
Bent
Because it's not nutrient-rich it grows an inferior product
GMOs.
We put in our bodies our bodies are starving to death. But we're not
We're starving because
The food that rating
Is not nutrient-rich
And then guess what
We get ill
And guess what company is selling you the
Pharmaceutical drugs
Supposedly make you better
It's the same company
It's a vicious cycle
I don't know if they were that genius that created or if they did they'd just been
Let It Go on the way but
But this document where they give us the oldest has to then give us a treat
Exactly
It's a hundred percent
And this is why I'm not
Because I have
Support your local
It's good that you're not saying that because
You run
Computers business
I think that's the only thing that unites all Americans except for the
The ones who work high up in Monsanto is that I think everybody's gotten high and yelled about Monsanto together at one point
Another of the practices they have
Disreputable and Roxanne
But I don't think it sent
Cibola to speculate that
They are making everyone sick it's so Bayer can
Cancel
Or whatever event for Alex to say
We have the documents that make it
So not specific
You don't need any concern
Xperia Z theories because of business trying to monopolize
Food is bad
Yeah give me before you go in at their entire existence is now based around trying to
Control food and everybody needs
I think ever
Making
Terminal C
You know that don't that
That's just so f******
Evil Creole downright
I'm not I'm not sure what you do to legislative company that would be interested in doing that I find
I understand why the profit motivation would lead you to that idea
But it's
That's no good
No absolutely
Much
I think that conspiracy to God is really stupid
But
He did
Contribute to what
Get behind that is probably given Ted Nugent covid
That is good
Not all heroes wear capes
And better than ever
You still Rambles a lot okay
I could
Oh my God just died
Toothpick
Sounds like
He always sounds like he's on coke
Quick talks all the time about how sober is annoying
A lot of this appearance on the
The show is about how
Excited Ted
That people celebrated him getting covid because
Validate
The people are against him
And I would say
Just because he's been a dick for a really long time and no one like
But some of my other musician friends from around the
Journalistic
Die
I feel the love I celebrate the love
But do you realize
As I think I am
I could
Wonderful human being
I hate
Celebrating my sickness and suffering
Is proof that they're scared
Makes me so happy
That's cute
No no one is scared
The death of you we were all just kind of hoping you'd finally go away
I do think there's something probably unhealthy
About people being happy
Singapore celebrating
Tragedy befall someone who is in the car
But I would be an idiot
Do not think that
The reason is because Ted
F****** idiot
He's ready to rock around the clock like Spock or whatever the f***
This is all your fault
That's all his
Personally like that
That's the thing it's
It's not necessarily Sade
Android so much as it is
When somebody spend so long telling you that this thing isn't even
King real
And all of this s***
Everybody celebrating because
F******
Do you get it
You get it now I don't know it won't so that's why the only thing you have left
To do as we like
Well I guess I
Just hope he dies or goes away to laugh you know you laugh at Ted Nugent getting covid after going to a
It is a hoax grocery store and having a hole
Long. Of time where you yelling about an hour it's not that bad it's all
Wow. It's in the same way that like you laugh when Ted Nugent
Bans guns it in France
Kind of like
Interesting it's a physical real world example of the you know me reaping verse
Versus Me sewing meme
You know like that
Interesting metaphor
Confused by I want to see if you can make
Consider myself a Schindler
And I already came
Is growing so
And they're all white
Hate
Everything I stand for
Viewers will understand
But some people will
Tubi
To be
So
I do think
He's right that some people will get that metaphor
Confuse
Even when he's trying to explain it
Yeah
That's what he's talking about and it the way you
Explaining that excuse
Oskar Schindler
Saving Jews who's on
What is T mean does he have a physical list of
People that
He's acting
Sing like Schindler about or is it just that
The brownshirts don't like him
Based on what
Describing like being productive
The only way that that really helps
Other people is by example I guess
Sure
I don't know I don't understand but now I don't understand that metaphor
Anyone
And I see him stealing the Valor of an actual hero in order to
You prop himself up
And boost his
Easy going
It was offensive
Various
So there's a solution to the problems in the world
And of course I've gone
But there's another solution
Ted Nugent
Atmore Alex
What do we do when the country's awake
But they stole the election
Call Alex
We need more out
You put there
Literally there
Metastasized into every orifice
Every every element of America the media our government
Hollywood
Academia
It's literally
Marxist
More often than not
They're little
Rock Solid in the skin
Calling if you look
What they're doing
That the economy is all artificial
Orange futures
Babies to produce
The most important thing is to support the Alex Jones
With all due respect
Wrong
Breath
So there's something
It stuck out to me when I was
Hearing that and it's just
He's angry
Yeah he's really really really angry
He's trying to come off with this laughing like I'm just
But he's f******
So mad
There is there is an affect
Rage
Underneath everything that he saying
That is really unsettling
Yeah yeah he's a he's a real psycho it's a real psychopath kind of thing to do feels
Feels
Scary Jon Ronson and see what he has
To say about the psychopath test
I just love
I just love to go from one
Clip where he died
Describes himself as Schindler
And then to the next clip where he describes
His political enemies the same way the Nazis
Describe the g
Boy it's not flaring
To do
Awkward weird word is not the word I would use
Oh nothing he's now one of describe themselves as the Jews
Despite the fact that they are still trying to exterminate
Weird
So
They have
They have some commonalities
Some less
Complementary than others
One of them is a little bit maybe neutral
Is an interest in the outdoors
In hunting
Alex believes that the most of
Effective way to can
Convert liberal
Over to their side
Ted Nugent says something
That I find
Problem
Getting back to honey I found with leftist and liberal to take a lot of Hollywood people out over the years
Mike Judge
They convert the shooting hunting instantly
Don't know why they were taught to hate it
Is if you can get a bunny or fishing
Where they've been brainwashed
Between
The brain-dead
The man in the woman
What
Thousands of people
Animal racing
It's called
Venison
I don't know if he actually has a camp for kids but if he does I'm going to guess he
She's not all that Hands-On I should hope
That should be illegal
But I think
Just from
From like a
Umbrella hangout from that clip
Believes that animals don't have right
Anything that is an animal is subject to
Man's domain / 3
He's a dominionist
I think that there's there's a
An interesting
Argument to be had that
Animals have more rights
Then we ascribed
Right
I think I cuz I have less agents
I am not
Fully
Conversant on some of the arguments
In favor of vegetarianism
Veganism
But I think that there are cement
Interesting things
They can't be discussed along those lines
Right and I just look at it as like I I
Live with a cat
Salinas
Like a friend
I believe that she has many right
Now
If I were Ted Nugent
I should only be mad if
You killed
Celine
Because she was my property
The only thing there is a property right that's been violated as opposed to
Something really f***** up you taking the like
Life of this
This
Companion Animal
That also mean
Oh is that you have the right to
Kill Ted Nugent
If he attacks
Text Selene in anyway
Because property rights
R a c
I'm interested in strange 22 imagine
Dude weight
He would distinguish
Humans and animals
In terms of where do rights
Begin
I think it's really troubling
REI
I think you could go too far with it maybe I would say that if you think
Animals have no rights
You are probably of the opinion that
Many people are also animals
2 don't have a ride
For cockroaches exactly
So I would not
Enjoy anybody who
Who's like
No rights
And I think typically it's best to err on
On the side of
The importance of sensitive to me
Stu
Two animals
Communicate
But they are clearly having a
Like a conscious experience
Absolutely there's no way that you can
I have
Not figured out that animals have personalities
By now
Pretty pretty messed up
Yeah
Yatted
There should be a restraining order keeping him away for
From any children if somebody writes his songs
That's an immediate restraining order away from jails choosing to believe that that was a metaphorical flourish like rock around the
Clock with a sock on my head
Future glockbox
Butter chicken
Anyway
Alex
Get some out of there
Band
Biggest news in the world
Which
I mean he's that time do that already decided to talk to Alfie Oakes and Ted
Ladies and gentlemen about to break
The most important news in my 27 years on air
This information is not
If it does not reverse the operations that they've launched
Then things are going to get a lot darker
Let me give you a
Alex is something like
If this doesn't bring down the globalists things are going to get dark fast
It's essentially saying
I can't make up anything more Sensational are antagonizing than this
Bike
The Next Step from this is me telling you to kill p
I can't make it more clear
I already know this
Sympatex
So you guys better clean my actual meaning from this
Because I'm making it very obvious
Emergency alerts ouchi project manager confesses
Tucker Carlson began to break this last night I told you on the war room we be bringing it today
He broke it
That's right
But he didn't
Get to the last part
Where he admits the project manager
Because legally they couldn't
Get to that box so I get the five irises if they combine them for a vaccine
Vaccine
Pathogen
That no one would ever make
Yeah it's not the end
So as I was really funny because he's talking about Tucker's
Segment
While he's talking Alex is kind of being a little wishy-washy about whether or not Tucker segments being censored
And I think it is this like
Alright
I'm posting
A 15 minute long video that's clearly owned by another media organization
You're coming with
A good reason why that okay
Something
Tucker Carlson
I come out the 14 minute report last night that
Expose this
Spencer Tucker Carlson report
Fauci
Why is there a criminal investigation
News
Headline
But it's not on YouTube
Fox News
Won't let you
Cruise great
I did
Say Sheena Central
Tucker Carlson Anthony fauci so just change that alarm please
Headline
This headline
Tucker Carlson
Why isn't there a criminal investigation
Listen to Country Inn in the sub-headline
You explained
That fox isn't posted this online
Cloudbabies
Alright 100%
Ends up talking a little bit about the story about the interview on
This week in virology
Haha it's just this
Is tragic
Cheater
Ecohealth Alliance starting in 14
Project Lead on 6th
We focus on the emergence of novel
Zoonotic
Coronavirus cases
Covid
Curology
I'm going to show you sit him saying
I was just stumbling over everything
Yeah that's not an hour-long interview
Is not good just everything is is just
It's by the rules of rounding up your going to Ford
But it's just covered in slime or something
No it is very much like
He doesn't understand
At all what he's talking about
And so they're just like
We don't have much else on the show today clearly all we could get it
Is f****** Alfie and
Disgusting Ted Nugent
So f*** it
Let's are Tucker stuff and I'll just kind of rip through it
I got like really oversell it
So you talked a little bit more about some details
It's and it's
Again not that
Accurate
3748000
$15
Is the head of
And we got all the doll that right here
Balancing reading some information here he doesn't really
The amount that he's talking about that 3 million plus dollars at Alliance has received
From the niaid for Coronavirus
Spurred on by the SARS and MERS outbreaks
And the need to prepare
What are the findings of his research was funded by the number of
Pornstars like Coronavirus
An interesting Lee they also found quote
Serological evidence of
Human exposure among people living nearby
This is something that ends in the direction of the natural origin
Jim theory for SARS coronavirus 2
People who researching naturally-occurring coronavirus is it found a number of them and discovered evidence of previous spillover
Viruses
Did it previously gone unnoticed
It's a particular virus have been different if any of those cases or
Something has gone slightly differently people had interacted differently
Those instances could have been the start of an outbreak
Alex's main piece of evidence he's resenting here these
These are grants in this study
It actually makes me think the opposite
What is conclusion is
I'm I'm Blown Away
Like this is this goes back to that hot
Possible that's goes back to the covid payments for Medicare where it's like
16 Grand Lake
I'm blown away that you think
You can make me worried about it
Conspiracy theory where it's like
It cost
The globalist
Send the devil 3 million
Kill
Everyone on Earth
If that's how much it cost to kill us why do I have to deal with all these f****** billionaire
Don't kill me with a few million
Yeah
Yeah yeah
It's
I don't know
It's that it's a part of your brain that just doesn't
You know $3000000 is a whole lot of money
Terms of a research grant that was over the course of 2014 to 24 years
That it's not that much research actually cost
Yeah absolutely I mean for a bit
Is if you want to say if you want to say that a conspiracy theory about this
Is a huge deal
Over 7 years
A business would probably be
Disappointed with revenues if they were only at that amount now
Scooby-Doo
Areas with revenues if you didn't get a 3 million in 5 years 7 years or whatever
Myself incredibly on inspired by
What is conspiracy
Inspired by
What you heard before
But I got to thinking about it a little more
I want you to help me write a new album
With songs like four horsemen
My car in Austin I said dude
This is very surreal day we've had dinner with Willie Nelson
Said
I said
I think that's up to you to write that
So
What a great story
Par with I was walking down on New York City Avenue and I saw
And I was like amen and he was like a
Dave Mustaine was really drunk around me one time
It's the same story
That sucks
I'm kind of disappointed because
It sounds kind of like Alex is trying to claim
That Dave Mustaine wanted him to help life so wrong
Text Alex Smith songwriter wanted to help write songs that would be on the album
Ourisman on it and that was Kill Em All
By Metallica
I wish that was what he was actually climbing
You to help me write songs are like that
Let's go to Burrito
Yeah I can imagine
I can't imagine anybody
I want you
In an enclosed space with me
Writing song
Songs to Galax allergy basically the Jim Steinman of your generation
I need you to bring this
Get get Taylor Swift's producers out here get those swedes
Get the Matrix
Dream would you need them for Alex's next album
So I think we've been talking a little bit along the way through this episode this just feels like Alex doesn't have anything to grab
50 feels really
Conspiracy
Two-and-a-half minutes of Alex saying nothing
Kind of
Dancing around but he doesn't know anything
Totally Tan today
This is
Hands down
Biggest
Trap of Awakened
The biggest haul of Truth
Moon do the globalist the biggest
Opportunity
Killer Joe
I mean
The Dominoes start falling in trials
I mean there's going to be
People getting hung
Sure
That's what happens
Did you get marked up there they pull the switch
And you like start kicking you take a
What
Killing people
How do I start a fight with murderers
But they start a fight with us
And
I'm just telling you like I said the first hour
Ouchie or Bill Gates
For the New World Order
Provision language
We want to see them up on Nuremberg to
Last weekend I had that weekend before last I had
The guys are hyenas still
What
Shopping because
I will not be at
Coward to say God
For your prayers listeners and I want to thank God for
By taking action
This is
Devastating
Devastator
There's no way to describe how much trouble they're in
And I can tell you this
They're never going to get out of this
One way or another
This is a political deathblow
Bolsonaro
Boris Johnson who's a follower
They want this too small economy
Working people
Global banks in big box or take over with big Tech
Anything to do with any of the bombshell stories it's just rambling and
Think about nothing
Assuming the conclusion is already been made
Time-filler
Yeah
That's brutal
That's brutal also if
Alex says Megalodon
He called somebody a megalomaniac
And doesn't say it takes one to know one
That it's disqualify
It doesn't count
If you do say takes one to know one
Maybe I'll listen to you because you are a
Absolutely one
Ham
But I think I think what's going on
Generally
Is it out he's already spent those
Rambling about you no lie
Like to talk to you will hang
And I always all proving it
Because I think what's really interesting to the audience isn't really the nitty gritty
Details or anything like that
It's an emotional experience
Announces giving them an emotional experience and that is it
This Is the End
Heels are bad whenever we want
There's no way they're going to get out of this
Is there in trouble
I don't know the Duke boys tent
Needed to get out of
Not the globalist
This is a big deal
That I have never felt so much fulfillment
The marbles reward Humanity
I've been around 47 years and I have never
Never felt so much satisfaction in my life
I was getting my ass absolutely
Dug down deep
Turn on the
Ben g h a
You know
But that guy's jaw it's all he's had it
Who won the fight
Feeling of dissatisfaction
Turn it on
Add
Risking my life you risking your life everything we've done together man this satisfaction right now
Retribution
Salix is basically like on this
Tipperary's like
Nuremberg trials will start in June
But planning them and getting like a twitch stream ready for the Nuremberg trials
Yeah this really does seem like a army building
It's giving the good news of the the victory
We have won the globalists are done now that this video from a year ago is Ben
Talked about
That doesn't sound
True to me
No it doesn't know that's the emotional experience that Alex is wishing to create because
You got nothing else
Yeah I've got nothing else doesn't really lend itself all that well to like
Be very scared
Yeah
It is interesting the felt like there is a ratio
Tween
Emotional manipulation
And actual details
Right-wing people
Because they made you can't just give them information that that that doesn't work
Do you have to have emotional manipulation
And you can't let information get in the way of that emotional manipulation
But you also can't have
Nothing
Like this is
It's a lot of nothing
Yeah
It's a it was
Infuriating to listen to in the in the sense that it was
Kind of like
I would describe it as being like eating a cinnamon twist
From Taco Bell but without any of the flavor
I was about to say empty
Tea calories
Exact no cinnamon sugar on it but it's
Texture of what you were supposed to eat but there's nothing
Nothing to it it's just music yeah yeah yeah
He does get
Excited
Middle-aged my studies to look into Whenever there is something like the sparse document tool
Look into
I find this to be a little bit
Unsatisfying personally
I don't think
That Alex is quarterly job evaluation is going
To go well
Just not just for my
Perspective having information about how the boss fee
Which is Springsteen of course
Q3 is going to be rough
Terrible
Don't have to get his numbers
If you want a sense of how real a piece of news is Dalek
I think one of the things you should take
Stock of is how much of the time of the shows actually spent
Talkin about that bombshell
Is this such a bombshell that you don't go away
And talk to alvie Oaks
Send Ted Nugent
Forever
Bombshells at you.
I don't know spend the end of your show just talking about nothing
And then
Cover this for a little while
Play short clips
Steve Bannon
Steve Bannon and Rodger Stone of a fights
Anybody
Smart guy
But he
Costco has
Meditating about Alex Jones
It's crazy
That's how it is
When you're headed
Your time
It's about people realizing that we don't make
The stuff up mostly research
And we have a wide spectrum understanding of the world
Say a thing
We really study how the globalist operate him and we know how they do things we know how to counter them
And we know how to beat them
Everything should be about the globalist
Because they're the ones that control of civilization
Take us to a very bad place
And so that's what I'm getting at here
But it is good to see it Trend yesterday Alex Jones Ford it on Twitter again
But I'll shows with ripe
And you can just
Sure so it's a little bit of Alex Jones
Media attention get some
Get some coverage here
Hi I just feel like he's such an insecure dick
It's so sad like
How many times has
Have we heard him talk about hating Steve Bannon he's a f****** world
He's gone to the global team
So pissed off when Steve Bannon neighborhood show
Attack on impulse
To take away all their real smart guy because it said something nice about me and let's spend a minute
About how someone said something about me
What an a******
Not hard
Today
You are a bad guy in Scream that everybody should kill him
He said I was the bad guy Zoe
He gets
Have you ever seen
Bill bars basically secret Tucker
Have you ever seen like
Breaking news story
Or a bombshell report
And then all the news organizations who normally have like live blogs and there's constant media coverage
Just kind of stopped and they're like
Can we just ramble around a little bit
We just got to have a little fun
You know bombshell story is fine but you know I'm just going to talk a little s*** with my buddy over here at Wolf Blitzer
Derails the show Situation Room
For a while because someone tweeted about it
Bright
Filters just Alvin like
Hey guys you know I'm at Willie Nelson
Yeah we went out for dinner one night you know he's like a
Pretty good songwriter
Brian stelter is like one time
Bob cowboy
Even closer analog
Imagine Brian stelter taking time to yell about Alex Jones is a.
Totally
So sad
Frat Alex's necklace
Is that great
Is this content that everybody
2 ninjas
So it's not been done
Alex
Doubles down on not doing it
All right folks
I'm at the tank call say I didn't
Launch coming up
I got a lot to hit before the show's over in 22 minutes
What gas is over
Let me do this because it's
No man's land first five
As our butt
This is really in a
Report
Playing a special report for the second time in this show
Replaying a special report
That's how little he cares about the story that he's cover
This is
This is kind of amazing
This is a
Complete abdication of
Annie
Even pretensive work
Yeah yeah yeah 33 every indication is like I don't know enough
Too competent
We even Riff on this
Yeah but I do want to cover it because covered it last night and I'll be way behind if I wait until tomorrow
This is the b******* that you get from a shity boss
Swear he's always any mistake you make like perhaps not being able to figure out how the phone system works
For twenty years
He's always screaming at you
But then whenever he comes to work with this b******* you don't get to yell back at him that he's waste
Thing everybody's f****** time
Somebody should have like a button where they get to scrape
Fair
Alex spends more time talking about the pipeline
I want to remind you that he's always right
Is very strong
95% chance
Watch out.
5% chance somebody got pissed they shut down Keystone inside
It's doing that Peshawar by the
What is my percentage of globalist
Percent chance that I'm wrong
It was done by people pissed off
Weather
Logical world you do that and then if you'll understand but no
Yeah so wait what
95% chance globalist false flag
5% chance false-flag carried out by people
Okay
So the channel false why
Look 0% chance it was hacker
The Logical it illogical world
Naturally somebody on the inside would be
Furious about people shutting down the Keystone Pipeline
So it only makes sense that they would then shut down a different pipeline isn't in order to the lesson
Be careful what you wish for that's exactly what we'll do.
That would be technically terrorism
Text structure
To spread fear
Yeah I think it I think it's interesting to see the way that Alex's brain kind of like
Comes up with possibility
Yeah he's just a terrorist
Anything that has to be fake every to ask to be traded kind of fake is it
Thirsty
So Alex is a ranting
Cuz I get just Valentine
The left want to be homeless
It's a happy thing
That's how all this crap works ladies and gentlemen
Or on and on and on
And on and on
And on from there I just hit my wireless headset audio off and I forget out at work
Oh my God
Somebody somebody
Acrophobia
Punch it up where it works thank you so much
Somebody screaming
It's right
What is a gentleman
We are here fighting the New World Order
It's hard
As we can
And and we can't do it without your support and I sell you things
But I know that you really really really really need
And so we all get the best portable food company with iPhones lowest price
We get it right
And
We bring you those products
Relationship a360 win an Oscar
Parasitic
Until
Tomorrow night
Great deal
And they told me the next two weeks or so
Because the whole thing shutting down
Because we're under braids
Wow
Deceived you see the transition generally from like scary narrative into ad but then
The ad leads into terrorizing the audio
And of course that's that's
Nice all this food for you at the prices good now but hey
Tomorrow prices going to go to regular and actually I know that in two weeks prices are going up even more
And also everything is going down because we're under attack at your food now or die listen
All I'm saying
Is that
I am going to
To take yuhas
Stage with fear and then you will give me money
And that's why you should be afraid
Yep. Very very afraid
I'm getting more for the office
I told my wife electable can good things that saved and some of the Gourmet Shawarma Foods well
Just get ready
And my parents about a trailer out
I've got
So learn all the stuff is gone
It's going to be like Road Warrior
If we don't turn this around
And there's not
Much
Time left
What's the shack
Infowarsstore.com
Funky Little Shack
Look I am sick of tired of Schrodinger's Bug out location. So sick of it
I don't care for this
Nonsense of I have a compound or maybe I should make one for the world so dangerous
The will-they-won't-they
Infuriating
Together with Rachel Ross come on buddy also here's the thing that I want to bring a tent
Abby and this episode Alex is talking
About how we do
Need to be really scared
I'll buy that food got a Bug out location and all this
Half an hour earlier he was laughing about how fulfilled he feels because the globalist are done for
Thanks this bombshell that he can't quite get himself to
Really cover it immediate absolutely
That is
Incongruent
And the reason is
Because
The emotional
Experience of
Defeating the globalist is something that he wants you to
Yeah keep people having fun
The money comes in
Makes money off defeating the globalist
It's terrorists
Yes
I would like
Some sort of
Man
You just get caught up in that
You know
It just rewires your your ability to process
If you're just so
Emotionally overstimulated
All the time with Nowak
Actual release
It just drives you insane
Like
It's it's insane
It's rate borderline solitary
You know
Yeah
Thoughtful
Yeah I think I think that's
Yeah I don't know what else
Disabled
It's kind of weird how you
You can sell stuff
Because that is not a weird aspect of biology is that somehow all the way along the line
Find Evolution has led to the people being like
Be afraid and bye-bye
I mean I think that's the American dream
Snake oil salesman and what-have-you there is a certain American aspect of you.
The way Alex is in a manipulating people in order to sell them bulshit
It's hard not to think if we ever did eradicate these type of snake oil salesman that we wouldn't
Also have
Like writers and and different people making nostalgic stories about snake oil
Man going from town to town
Regulate out of existence supposed to
This is not a this is not a cockroach this survive
10 Point of View Drive
Bentonville feel nostalgic
For the five-course
Cuz we're insane
Oh well
Anyway I look forward to going back to
The past because
I find myself
Incredibly frustrated by this a******
And I don't want to hear about
Another goddamn bombshell that's disappointing
I want to go back to
To the past when news was
Measured
Sometime guests wear combatives you are into everything was what it was
Not this overly dramatic nonsense
Every single
It's just a birthday
The candle is burned
Going to Bright Now at
It smells right.com
Eeyore bail Fund in your area
Did I help out
For sure how I'm Leo and bcx Clark I'm Daryl rundus
What the sex robots
Alex
Birthstone colors