Damn important
I have great respect for this knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Six around works with celine's alter
Indeed we are Dan how to smooth tips time I got it right in there
In there
You know what a lot of people meet
To see the
Process
Becoming definitely and I consider this part of my 10,000 hours towards getting ready production
Also part of your 10,000 hours towards telling Malcolm Gladwell he's a moron
Community service
Jordan
Hey Dan I have a
What's up
Maybe you should go first maybe I might be a little extended alright
Mine's just like
Emphasizes
Well
Shohei ohtani
Today just hit his 12th home run to win
Incredible
And here's a picture of the Cubs
No
Not know he's on the angels
Andy has an era around 2
She has several a I mean this dude and it hears why he was right
He's
Everything he's the only baseball player on this plan
That has ever lived
Yahoo can reliably throw 100 mile-an-hour fastball
And hit 450-foot dingers
On the regular
And I have thought about that if yours was my pricing is because unlike
So many other achievements
Right now
Is the only time in history that anyone has
Has ever done
What shohei ohtani is doing and maybe the only
He's the only person
Who is ever lived out of the 5th
Billion
People
He's the only one who can do this
For some of our international walks
Baseball
It's very rare for a picture to be able to hit well
It is rare for picture to Hitler
Well yeah it is
He's not rare for a picture
To hit
What is he's on Pace for over 40 home runs in a season that is crazy
Never happen anybody wants
Talk to me about Babe Ruth
Can shove it up their ass Babe Ruth hit home runs off of people who threw slower than I do
Babe Ruth
Is garbage
Garbage human being played against garbage
Understood
1/2
Major League Baseball as an organization doesn't make
How not good at hitting federally that there's a
The game was like these guys are
So bad it here in town
Yeah I was going to make a joke about Jeff suppan
I believe famously hit a homerun in the World Series Cardinals
Yeah the Cubs reliever I can't remember his name off the top of my head but he was one of the last people to hit
Home run in a playoff game as a relief
Hell yeah
Very rare
So he's he's
You get to see him
There's only one like
How
Insane
One person case for that
Sure that to me like I just imagine being in that position being in those shoes like I don't know how you would handle that pressure
You know I don't know
You grew up in the Japanese
Baseball leagues
If you've never liked in the Japanese baseball legs
If you're if you're eight
Playing for your team
You have the same amount of pressure as a major Leaguer the United
I don't know if you know anything about it at all
Okay
My bright spot is I made a little trip long-overdue trip down to the
The box mailbox
Some stuff to take out the bag Z Excellence
Something I realized I didn't mention this when it was my birthday because it also included
To get for your birthday
And I forgot what your birthday came around
You so much for that absolutely
And then
I went to mail back there some other stuff that was a bit birthday related
Cin-cin
Young at ginger ale which I don't know if that is Young gingers could be a rap name
Carl Jung specific I believe Beck sent a pink yukle
Lely which I'm a little confused but but I'm excited to try to learn
Time to learn a couple chords
Last night
If I was playing around with it
And my fingers are
The two fat
So I don't know if
It's going to work out but
They turned into a weird ukulele bad I don't know but I do some cover songs parodies absolutely also
You belong in the city is right for a ukulele parody
Also in this
Was the Sega Mega Drive classics
It's for the switch all right
Sand I've been used to seeing these kinds of
Collections of old games
Actually good games on it
But this is pretty solid you got dr. robotnik's mean bean machine
Classic got to have that Sonic
Sonic 2
Toejam & Earl
Are you reading the in chronological order
Comix Zone
I do remember comic Zone wow the past
Is far away the entire Streets of Rage Trilogy okay well that we haven't had in a long time
Whole lot of stuff on there and it's it's
It's very nice it's been a long time since I've moved
From left to right in
Things there are a couple games that are entirely that
I got another thing
I'm here
And this was a little bit weird Jordan I feel like I'm going to need your help because I think I might have actually been for you
You okay
So here I like this card the front look at the front
Okay there is a dog resting his while there's a puppy
Is very cute very lovable face on top of
Who is staring
Cute and lovable
What does it mean
We listen
And we have feelings too
Two, Jordan
Love,
Nothing else
Okay now
Okay to mugs
And this is one of them
Alright you shall know the truth that
The truth shall make you free all right
Central Intelligence
Agency sure
Sure
Map
There is a sticker gift shop
Either Becky I is trying to f*** with you and let you know Jordan
Fairfield
Either the CIA is very sensitive
Or it's already f****** Minnesota entirely shirt
Dot-dot-dot yeah we
But who's we
CIA man but I mean why would they send me a cute little puppy
Script address in Virginia
Oh well that would kind of make sense then wouldn't
I don't know if it's entirely possible but there tells me that it's someone f****** with you
But I still appreciate a mug mug admit how ironically
Would be for Alex
To constantly claim that they CIA at all important heads-of-state listen to him and yet we get very kind
Almost downright
Cute cards from
The CIA you are being too mean
CIA I guess wow wow Jordan is
Apology to the CIA
It does take both for all of our leftist listeners out there the really looking at Jordan is as kind of
Oh yeah he's on the edge man
You just apologize for the pink eye
I would be surprised Jordan a I would be surprised to know to what he left us
Is to a pod receiving a cute puppy or
Kitten card wouldn't be like
I mean it's Austin's me a little bit
Just to know the cute puppy
Jordans
You are talking about May 8th and 9th 2003
One of the things I wanted to try to do was I wanted to try to keep pace
Sure was 2000
13 I don't think we're going to be able to do that that's going to be tough with him
But here we are May 8th and 9th
Pink stuff to go over some
Weird parallels of present as per usual due to my witchcraft
Before we get into this will take a little moment to
Say hello
Ezpopsy
Next all hail the cult leader Saline
I'm a policy wonk
Good good muscle Nate thank you so much
Jordans
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
Should I do next
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
To give a little
Cap to sew mr.mac makinton thank you so much you are
Technocrat
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
Also before we get into this
The showbiz
Certainly not
We've never been
We have Mike's we're holding in our hands we are not in Show Business
I got a message from a
Character named Jeff
Just wanted to get a message out and that is apparently
They have a friend named Alex
Who's opposed to the spider leadership
If this is relevant cuz you're wearing the spider l
Artesia right now
Perfect so this is his friend of Jeff's is opposed to you
Also apparently Jeff's brother Evan
Justa got into the show so
What up kayak
Welcome to the wokery I have no idea this is just what we've become welcoming a new listeners
Another day
The god album
Here are a couple out-of-context drop
The first
Is a little it's actually a little game I want to play that is
Alex
Or Bill Clinton
Was that Alex or was that Bill Clinton
Here we go
Okay we can't do we can't do this is a stolen Newsradio B from 4
4 years prior to the show Eric's when Phil Hartman wet on his bill McNeill ended long in
Interviews with himself as Bill Clinton we can't say that it's that I will say that it's definitely nothing
Either
Sounding a lot like bill collector
Or Bill Clinton with Alex is going to break music playing in the background
Depression of dude smoking pot
Yeah
Good to know that
The Denver Airport will never die
Doing impression of himself
Little little sad
No backup back in his dad today
That's when people were smart
I really don't know if that's how anything works
Education or knowledge
College joke
We start here on the 8th and actually Begins the show with a story that is that
Mirror parallels to present day
You don't have
But the government
First things first
Alex
Stat that he cited there at The Little Owl
Outlandish
Not off on some of this stuff but the story that he's telling about this is missing some point
I was able to find a CBS News articles
From May 2003 which is
Discuss the proposed plan to vaccinate half-a-billion healthcare workers against smallpox
Of which on
Only 35,000
One of the targeted workers had been inoculated
There's not good evidence that I can find that anyone was refusing the vaccine
Just at the program they have only vaccinated about
7% of
The stated goal population
Refusing it but 1 and 7 is closer than I'm used to him being
93% of the targeted population that they meant
To get a smallpox vaccination
Did not get it
Sure Alex is making up but they all refused we don't know again
Not getting it
Doesn't like weed
No instead
7%
There's a real decent
That most of that was
Just due to structural problems out of the rollout of campaign
Most people
Not need to get vaccinated against smallpox now.
The reason is because thanks to vaccination efforts made by the people who came before us smallpox was declared eradicated in 1980
A 911 there was a concern about a terrorist group or hostile government using smallpox as a weapon
And that sucks the US government stockpile massive amount
The smallpox vaccine in order to be prepared for that kind of possibility
But typically speaking
Most people won't need that.
The people who do according to the CDC are typically lab workers who might be in contact with any viruses similar
Small popular
The booster vaccinated 2003 was based on fears that the
Potential Terror
First attack
And what was ultimately decided was that it wasn't worth
The risk and vaccines could still be effective after someone was
Exposed to the virus over wasn't
Much of Annie
The program was ended early and only a total of about 39000 people were ultimately vaccinated
Part of the resistance to this program was the people didn't buy that there was a real threat
Been pretty clear that there was no information of an imminent attack
And hospitals were reluctant to participate
In the end however through this program's failure Public Health preparedness was improved even
Critics of the smallpox campaign credit
With helping us be more ready for the later outbreak of SARS
David blue was a thirty-nine-year-old combat reporter working with NBC
He passed away on April 6th 2003 while on assignment
Reporting from a rock
It's pretty well understood that the cause of death of it was that bloom had developed a blood clot in his leg
From spending days on and crammed into an armored vehicle
And having deep vein thrombosis
Is clock made its way to with his lungs and caused a pulmonary embolism which
Resulted
Are the days after he passed away a doctor named Brian
Strong made a number of comments to the media about the possibility that blooms death
Was related to the smallpox vaccination he gotten several week
Week prior to his past
There's no direct evidence
Support this conclusion and making stuff up
And jumping to conclusions
That said no medication is fully without some risk in the smallpox vaccine is no
Exception
Compare to the smallpox
Fox come back though the risk is very minimal
Isn't it so f******
It's just so indicative of how stupid people are
That
The government was like
Okay
Now
Despite not having
Any idea whether or not they could have weaponized
Is polio
Smallpox
Would weaponize polio smallpox
Or
I even
I have some way of delivering it
We're just going to go out of our way and protect ourselves against the possibility of a smallpox
Despite the fact that
The overwhelming number of humans have died of diseases that have occurred regularly and at no point in time
Have they been like
Let's put a lot of effort into preemptive
It said
I mean they have any they have but not like
You know whatever you know what my point is it's not like the Bush Administration wasn't also
Getting tetanus shot
I don't know
I feel like you're just looking for a way to attack
Isaac
I think when you look at this it's like
It's a terrifying Prospect
Maybe there was some chatter of some sort I would believe
Possibly
This is something we should be concerned about you
Some
Body might have a sample of
Some Laboratory
It could really f*** things up
Maybe if you
If you ask late in your head
What the possible threat is
Then the idea of
The campaign of
Vaccinating
Healthcare workers
Who might be in the front line for
Or soldiers
A certain amount of sense
Looking back we obviously have the gift of hindsight knowing the
Didn't happen a lot more silly
But
Even back then you could probably make a pretty decent argument that it was
Excessive
We can understand where the thought process
It's just we had too many examples of this type of paranoia being the excuse
Action
When is paranoia vets
Inherently devalues the life of other people
As opposed to
The paranoias it's like
Hey
Diseases just come out of nowhere from
All of the time
Infinitely more important
Instead it's like
We've always got to be preparing for a war or or someone to try and get
Misunderstood
Your point
I think it was indicative of
A lot of
Like sort of public mentality
I also think that you can do both
Then that might be where
Might have misunderstood you were saying
At one or the other choice
But I think everybody was
Ideally
Heather pet on both
But it's not necessarily the best way to go about talking
I don't think you broke new ground
Start a revolution dad
This clip I thought was a really good instance to illustrate why you
You can't take vaccine-related stories seriously when they come from Alex
No matter what the reality of the story is Alex is always going to take
The story about the
Possibility of danger and he's going to report that is definitive
Exaggerated out it is like
It's been proven
They shown it
It's the same thing that he's does with covid-19 vaccine
Stories in the present day
This behavior is
Consistent
Cuz he is staunchly opposed
Do vaccines
Right not based on the science of it
And you can
You can argue
The problem with it is that the argument of like look
20 years ago
This a****** was saying the same lies
About different vaccine
And you can see that those didn't come true
So why would you believe him now and they are the argue
It will always be like
Yeah yeah but it's
The Black Swan
You know sure this one was a fake they want to make you come
Struble Road vaccine
Until they do it they want to lower you into
And you're like fine we will never
You can't you can't really be back by thinking
And I think if you do are able to get yourself to a point where you recognize that like he does
Do this over and over and over again
Regardless of the circle
You have to start to ask yourself why
What is it exactly that is
The opposition Tyvek
What is that about
I think you could probably come up with a couple of possibilities one is
A sort of inclination towards
Divine Science medical intervention
I believe that Alex is there
Because he
Like he's gotten surgery
No but it is it is that kind of like when it happens to someone else
Very much
What's the will of God
I'm going to happen
To you
The will of God is to save yourself
Themselves
Because it was their time it was their time to go damn you can't deny them that sure I'm saying that's slightly
The unsatisfying
Explanation for Alex
The other one that I come up with
This is the
Notion
I understanding that
Like vaccines
Have drastically improved the world the lives of poor people
Yeah people in developing countries around the world
And
I don't know a whole lot of Alex's policy positions
Seem to be
About not
Turn off foreign aid
Two things are are things with that
Seem to be
Kind of
I overlap of a lot of his beliefs
Yeah
I don't I don't know if that's where the opposition
In comes from but
It certainly makes more sense
Since then legitimate
Scientific when you think about
When typhoid spread through wealth
Neighborhood
There is far less like
Auntie medicine
Spread around about that s*** was very much
Everybody needs to clean their hands everybody needs
You know that kind
Anything
So Alex gives a little bit of a shoe
The beginning of this episode
You know hey man
Sometimes the world doesn't
Make sense
That's when you need a little bit of infowar
War
Your children
You'll find the answer right here
Is it the devil
Is it the devil devil
It's got to be something like that
I'm confused
I mean I understand
No I think we were all wondering that you know like those are correct wonders
Sure there's something
Yeah it's certainly there is there are there are confused
Militarization of police is confusing
What's going on
Why is this happening
I don't get answers from Infowars
He turns into a
I wonder if he's just not telling the audience at this point yeah but this is secretly just a big religious
Campaign
Is part of God's plan for him and
In fighting the devil to lie to these people early on in
His career
Like slowly trick them into being
The holy Warriors
Guide me right
Ass ain't isn't going
Bring these centers in
I kind of idea
Got it God was talking to Sullivan cell was like 9 or 10 in his dreams and he's like listen you got to lie to everybody
Right up until the good time
Yeah I don't know I don't know it's really straight
It's really strange to me it looks like I said it needs 2015
My ion is worthless ideas.
Does he think he's fighting the devil in 2003 you know if he does
Then that clip
Is busiek
If he doesn't
Then his world view doesn't make sense
Appreciative that clue
So Alex has got a headline that's not a headline
Federal lawsuit
This reading is not from a news story or any kind of journalistic source
It's actually the title of a press release
Was put out by the office of Lauren Regan
The lawyer representing the people who are the subject of this real
I can understand how this is still a source of information and it's entirely possible that the lawyers press release
Could have stuff with conveying
It seems like something that shouldn't be treated as the same as an article in an actual news
Outlet
Incidentally this case resulted in the City of Eugene paying one couple
$30,000 and another $92,000
To settle their cases
Which claimed unreasonable search and seizure excessive use
Assault and
Folsom Prison
The police consider contended that it was an instance of them having bad information
I believe in that they were raiding a drug house
Whereas the couple's believe that the police got a warrant by lion
Whatever the case it's not good policing
And even if the Intel had all been good
Directions would have been excessive for a drug raid
Here is that in terms of the big picture that this kind of police action is wrong
Alex and I are in complete agreement
Not hard
I still don't support how he pushes the message though however given that
You presenting
Biased information from the lawyers of people involved in the story present neutral headline
It's not
It's not necessarily the way you would want to go about
Framing your case even if your case is something that I agree
Yeah yeah yeah
I mean
It would be hard to be on the wrong side of
Strangers destroy your home
For no good reason
And face no punish
Like that
Seems obvious yeah and has a large portion
Of this episode talking about this
Couples
Houses that that were
We're search they were
You know how old
Does
Become hard
Take seriously
Wahkiakum I do care for these people who had this police intervention in their lives unnecessarily
And they were treated poorly
I just don't
I don't consider Alex a legitimate person some absolutely any more
Yeah anyway
Is that is also a really good
Question about the
I mean as far as
The fighting the devil in
The present goes
Another
Another like question that that raised
This is
Is this guy that guy
Or does he
You change into this guy
And what
What does that mean
You know like are there is
Is it possible
That Alex and I could have had a comp
Conversation in 2003
That wouldn't have wound up with me trying to throw something into his face
Probably I bet I bet it is I bet you what you might not really enjoy it all that much
Because he's lying to that because
He was a different person
Possibility that I could eventually change into this very monster
That's actually why we're doing this
That's really the thing that this is all about is like
Be like what do we have to be afraid of
Somebody get a whiteboard up with a cautionary thing yet
Alex starts to read this article and you bring up
This
The differences between presentation
Is this
Bring up this article and
You can see in this clip
Similarities and difference
Like okay one
What's big similarities
He starts reading and every
Nothing here EP editorialize Azar
A whole bunch of stuff it's not in the article
To the article
But a big
Difference
He says that this was written by a lawyer
He doesn't clarify that it's the lawyer of the people
Who were in the story Shore
He does he does
Give a clarification that I did
Didn't expect from him
Pre-dawn
You can hear the difference in his voice when he's editorializing
That's it
It's
Curry gets in a way you can you can
Feel him almost telling you when he
He's not
There is a slight
Bit of that
Still it's still like
To read this article myself constantly would suffice
Did I see we got you
It's slightly more responsible feeling
Because if you are at
Actively listening you can tell when it's like these are at the words of Alec right
This is his reading voice
And you know why that's a more compelling show than just reading the news because this is
This is very similar to how some a****** might be reading an article as he's reading at you no like
If I'm reading an article sometimes I'll read a sentence and be like
Delray the next sentence you know this is an engaging way of almost
Reading the news with your body
I don't I don't disagree
So Alex gets to talking about other places that have been rated
This is a case from early 2000 to wear a 27-month long invest
Navigation into an international gun and drugs
Smuggling operation
Culminated in arrest in a town called
Carthage
In Missouri
This is a real headline from an AP story but
The use of the words Town searched isn't meant to be taken completely literally
The multi-agency task force that was working on this extended operation set up some checkpoints to make sure the subject at their best
Navigation couldn't flee
Anime made the arrest
I'm not justifying
This policing us early I'm just saying that
Bee image that Alex wants
Creative cops kicking in every door in this town in Missouri
Looking for wrongdoing
The jam someone up
Like
Not accurate wants
To create and it's not real has elephants across the Rock
To get there
I felt like that might have been a terrible idea
But
Right I got it
I got it
I was trying to think of a way if there was a like
It's Corral do Jo Peckham Lane in the boat
It wasn't worth it
It was probably would have enjoyed it more if I wasn't trying to make a Fitz Corrado joke
And say what
We were working at cross-purposes
Sazon that rip yams
I apologize I should be there for you more that was on me
Alex is completely
Fudging
Find for him
His lawyer
I guess
If you put the pizza
This Together yourself you can
Kind of makes sense of
Text at this isn't the headline this is
Something
The press release word is never used
But you can put the pieces together that this is a lawyer representing
The people
A not unbiased actor in The Circle
Yeah you will
I think of this lawyer seems
Fairly straight up
I think she's distracted and
Maybe a little bit bemused by Alex's
Is constant
Said her name was Roberta Barnes gave me some pause
I felt more comfortable
Alex Alex knows how to arrest
You should know that
Go work
Go ahead
You can tell kind of air that she's trying to respond to staff
Is how I would characterize the interview
She has a point I don't know if she necessarily knows who he
Alex is
And Alex certainly isn't it as talks
Amantadine
2003's Ryan presents
You might not think twice about an invitation to come and talk about this
You're passionate about new want to get attention for
And you don't know going in that it is going to be a life-or-death struggle to
To finish ascent
You didn't know that
And you don't know that Alex is going to be constantly trying to drive the image of a naked woman being dragged out of her house
Yep
Because that's a visceral for them correct
Where is you maybe want to talk about
Infringement
Alright
Spell really
Interesting
Partially because
I mean
I agree with Alex
I don't agree with his tactics
I don't agree with him
Sensationalizing the story like I looked at the
The story in
Normal Outlet
And the conclusion of the police shouldn't have done this
Because we're in the future
That the police
And the City of Eugene did payout
Settlement
You take away whatever these people
Experience
You know something
Some figures are as restitution for the cops destroying your home
And your sense of safety
Be forever
There's there's going to be psychological things
Angel
There's a there's a modicum of Justice in that are in a settlement
Anyway the interview
And
Patrick says this
Rolled my eyes
1 800 25
He's setting himself up for failure
I'll give you plans to get 250 stories boss calls in one hour that's just not possible
If you factory commercials he's giving
Himself like 20 seconds birth story
That's not even enough to get through the head
You should be more realistic about what he can and can't cover in the time he has and then
Focus on what he has the time to cover sure make for better content
Sure it wouldn't be so dumb it does it does make it
I don't know what would I say
It does make it far more reasonable to just ignore that in the Press
You know it's like a long-running
Joke on a sitcom
It's been going on for 30 years
What are you going to complain now
If avallac'h says he's going to get to the stories
And you've listed
In 2000
You know damn well he's not going to listen to he's not going to get to the store too
Doctor house
Symptoms
Sprite
Play diagnostic game.
Coffee is not part of it
Alex has
Trouble with quotes
Extends far beyond time
So Alex
Perception is reality
That's interesting because that's quote most famously attributed to Republican strategist Lee Atwater
Notable prison tattoos of racism as a political tool
What did it what did name one big strategy
Also there is a associate with the Willie Horton
Pretty notable 1984 senior partner at Black manafort Stone and Kelly
The consulting firm run by Alex's Future Good Buddy Rogers
Wow something is real perception is reality
Jesus
1984 good ol Rodger Stone looking to his left seeing leatt water if they could I got a break
Futureadpro
Call Morgan
You really are going to get charged with crimes in 36 years boy
Definitely not laying the groundwork for all the crimes were going to do
This was addressed
Tumi
I'm going to stop saying it
This was weird
Sure okay
Alex
Hasn't intense news Blitz he needs to get for a full hour of news with I forgot about that
New World Order
Turn in the military
Waze
Everywhere
American
Revolution or I could say
We've had requests for the song wheel
Liberty
Alex plays the entire song of Billy Ray Cyrus's songs
I was worried it was going to be what I heard it being
Unhappy
I would give anything to go back to that moment in time
And tell Alex about Miley
Oh my God it's so weird
It's so weird
He plays a full song
As like a shout out to the Troops and he doesn't
He doesn't sing along with it or editorialized / Reeves
Now he couldn't eat a sandwich is easily back then
That's probably true
Yeah that was buzard this format is very strange
That makes me feel deeply uncomfortable
There's no what no
A lot of people have been wanting me to play Billy Ray Cyrus and I say to them know
Again
Everything I understand about Alex's format
Song requests
You can request songs
He doesn't play songs
What a weird strange
So the news Blitz doesn't really happen
What guy this guy is interesting
Hehehe seems to believe
That's spam
Yes
Messages
Oh right
Yes but not the food spam messages need
To be clearly delineate it as something with a commercial purpose
Cuz he got accused of stealing somebody
And he was just trying to harass them
Okay two things if I can get someone at the supremacy clause
Kakashi's veterans law
Legislation to make Spam
On the internet
To a Spanish commercial
Not
Not forcing
Compressor media to
See the pictures
Your email goes if somebody wrong you live in prison or white
I was accused of scamming people
How many times
After 9/11 Iraq War
They leave their email addresses in the newspaper articles
Is email address so he doesn't have to
Mystery
To the treason that's gone
Yeah it's open goes in
Find email addresses in newspapers in the
Yeah he's worried about a law against
Yeah
That's a fundamental misunderstanding of all of the problems with what you're doing
You back but it's fun
I believe you got the
That wrong
It's a phone call though because you can see the Dynamics that are going on and like
I don't know that sounds like an Alex Jones listen to me
Make
Making it illegal
For me to send chain emails to my family
And that
That's going to really get in the way of Mimi capping this reporter over here
So we got to stop this Cheney mailbox
Not spam
I
Email a journalist 100 times in a day until he's going to go to jail for today
I'm not a but I'm an ass-whole I suck every one of those messages by half the button
We're going to hear a little bit of
Talking about
Do you know you got the new money coming in
The new bill
Yeah yeah and a lot of people a lot of theories
About that
This caller believes
Will never have Harriet Tubman on the $20 bill
This color believes that there is like
Metal strip
Sure if you hold on to the money
Alright more than a month
It'll be able to time that
I like this money will know when it's changed hands this is a good conspiracy I like this and if you hold on to
To a too long
It'll Auto tax
What that man was talking about on
Money
Program the other day one of the things with the money with the strip
When you get it
If you don't answer
Turn on within a month
Cubeecraft
Starboard Virginia
A real person to have on with the Donald mcalvany intelligence
Visor
He's very well.
I have no idea however timer of a month would stars are
Love it
If I work if I were to buy something
With a bell like this is ridiculous
I don't I don't know anything about this. Old guy but look into it a little bit
Website is just a portal to a gold sales Outlet
So he's saying that maybe you shouldn't get paper said you should get gold
So then he of course
Sell gold
That's very strange how that work
Completely nutty
Conspiracy theories about paper money always said that sell gold
Super weird people who hate the fed and paper currency love
And also sell at Providence
Firstrade
So we go to
Okay
I didn't find that episode all that satisfying a lot of it was about
Is that lawyer
Just kind of spending
Wheels
I got in on the 9th
I found myself
Very excited
Is that the right word
Interesting
Will be joined by Geoff Moore
But
You heard on the
News
Would you say they got canceled if you will just misspoke there any tried to cover it by insinuating that the media
Got the story wrong but making you think that the two DJs got in trouble for playing Dixie Chicks
When maybe they got in trouble for
For criticizing
Only Alex can get to the bottom of it
How could you get speaks
Could you know
So these two guys works
Tkacs
102 FM in Colorado Springs
It's a station to Aveda put in place a boycott on playing Dixie Chick
Kick songs after Natalie Maines
I had some comments at a concert they were seen as being Auntie troop when she said
That you was a shame
The President Bush was from
State hazard in Texas
Good for the Dixie Chicks are being ahead of their time you know like now we're all the same to the United States but they really got there first
Obviously this was an instance of ever losing
Damn mind and Dixie Chicks but some of the details of the story
Particularly about this
Is DJ situation might not be what you remember
What's the ricin
Dueling Elvis impersonators
Actual to DJ's the story that I remembered was that they dare to play a couple songs from the Dixie Chicks and that was enough
Have to get them in trouble
An article from the
Times Herald-Record has some other details
Kctcs instituted a ban on the Dixie Chicks
Zoo at the time
Two songs on the charts
But to DJ's at the station Dave Moore and Jeff singer decided at 2 months
Was punishment enough
They broke the band
At 6:15 a.m. on Monday May 5th 2003 they lock themselves in the DJ booth
They started with long time gone and they didn't stop playing Dixie Chicks Tunes until noon
Was Adams
Taylor and Brittany
I didn't remember that was part of the story
Real life even though I agree with the point of what they're doing I totally understand that it's a brazen
Active insubordination
Listen you guys are here but we can't just not do anything what happened
The station manager Jerry Grant gave the to a choice
To either continue playing dicks
Dixie Chicks songs and get fired
Or stop
Unlock the studio to be suspended for a few days
And they chose
To end the occupation of the states
I have a huge problem with everything surrounding this story but I'm not sure I disagree with these two DJs getting a slap-on-the-wrist
Christopher essentially like you said living the movie area
AirHeads you just can't do it
It's like what the
The movie Airheads a good cause
You're sort of as we learn later but
What is dumb no matter what absolutely
I would want them to be punished too harshly but you can't lock yourself in a repeal booth
Pirate the transmission and expect nothing
Where is that
I think that is actually pretty restrained response
From the boss
Couple days suspension whatever overreacted everybody would have turned it in
Into a cause I would slap on the wrist is almost
Insulting to them like that protest was worth nothing more than take a day off
I found
It seems like
The guy was like
Yeah we were getting ready to start playing their music again anyway but
We wanted to do it on our terms you are a
I could see how
I could see how this
You know what
It's ultimately
The audience and the Pea it's been 2 months
Sure audience is kind of over it
Pretend This is
And these guys are
Yeah which is also interesting
And maybe probably for the best I bet they got a s*** ton of Free Press out of that they even suspended them
And then they came back and everybody was like
I don't know I don't know if you remember those dudes name
Dave Grohl
I mean it's a story that you kind of remember
Inasmuch as I do remember that there were
Some DJs who got in trouble for playing pics
I don't remember those details
I don't remember their names
I don't think that there
Kevin & Bean
To live echoing throughout history that's true
Angle of it worked out as well as you
They were going to be on I thought
Okay
Here we go this is this is nonsense exactly the kind of thing that I think is really fun
About going back to
Long-forgotten
Sort of
I want to call it trivial because what happened to the Dixie Chicks
So unfair
I'm not I'm not with minimize that at all
Of course
In terms of Alex's world
This is
Trivial
Yeah yeah yeah
It we're all going to die alright we're fighting the literal devil also these two guys got suspended for playing the Dixie
So there's a little bit of a disconnect and steak
If you will
These guys are probably not super political
But they don't know who Alex Jones is the other nationally syndicated
Eucalyptus beard intersection of things that would never happen nowadays
And I think
It's amazing
Anyway just to check in with the NRA
Alex doesn't like the NRA at all
She hates me
Don't like
I don't like going into the past
As much as you do because I find that his
Behavior
Is left
Egregious
And thus make
Makes me feel more like I'm saying stuff where I'm like
I mean yeah that's a good point
I don't like
Will like it cuz his behavior is still egregious just under the surface
Here's the thing that we need to really
Finally delineate
Yeah it's like yes
Opposition to the NRA is great
Opposition to Bush
He's great with those things great as sentences on a piece of paper correct
Why
Alex is against
Both of those things
It's different than what we thought holder
And so I actually think that you can be
What you're experiencing is exactly what lured a lot of people who wouldn't agree with Alex's radical politics
Into thinking
He was more in the center than he acts
Actually
Like the NRA
Maybe
He's one of these people whose kind of conservative but kind of gets it no
He's more
Extreme
It's so frustrating that
He could get away with
Conceived
We got away with really well for him at this
Decide this era
Yeah
And I think one of the things that is really good for him to is
This this Brandon
And you know we're talkin about this like
Attacking me Honore from the right
Because he is a
Extreme right-wing person
Extremely far to the right of bush
Because he's to the left reason the center
Impression
And Alex plays into that impression
Hair clip
He's talking about how people call him a commie
Because he's again
Bush
Call John Hardin
Oprah
American flag
Alex has this
Superficial
Defining himself by opposition
Yeah things
Dit-dit-dit actually does
Mulatto
People
I'm opposed to Bush and now it won't cost me a commie when I was against
When I was against Clinton they called me a hard right
Extreme you were and you still are
I don't care I don't know if I ever had anybody who
I heard
Say like
Alex is a communist
Bushnell
I just think of people thought he was more sensible than
You might think on 1st
And if you are an enemy of any part of the right-wing you will be called
Communist
Regardless of anything you may or may not have ever said or believed
Possibly by other people in the right wing
Michaelsavage.com
It's just wine
Yeah yeah
I think there is a pretty key problem there too though
They did something
That I notice about Alex
That is
The
Defining self
By opposition
Or by others
Response
When he talks all the time but knowing that he's right
Because people are attacking him and stuff is like
That's not a reliable metric
Back of
Yeah you know
I'm right cuz everybody hates me well
Yeah
Does that mean that Isis is right
No it's there
If he goes to therapy one time the first question is just going to be like
How do you define yourself and he's going to talk about everybody but himself in there but like
From the inside
And it's going to be 6
Years of concert
Did talkin digit even figure out where Easter
So these DJs
Come on
And I got to say
Is a little bit of a
Current style for Alex
The interview
Tough question
Chloe
Alright
Well we did it good journalism everybody let's go let's wrap it up and go home that's certainly better journalism but he normally
So how long has your management been evil it in the
The devil in the globalist
Think Alex's bedside manner leaves a little bit to be desired their attitude
S***
No follow-up question
The feel of like a
Maybe if I do
Just surprised them aggressively they'll be tricked into an
One of the thing
I think Alex has been presenting
People
Felt
Was that this was a prince
Multiple stand that these DJs are making
That it was they were opposed
The band
And they played this music
As a way of being like no totally believe in free speech
Pirate Radio
Vietnam War were doing it all over
If you listen to them it's
Very clear that that's not the case they did not agree with what Natalie said
They agreed with
They just thought I had to run its course
Because of what Natalie
Main said about our president over in London
So I'm that it was
Was starting to turn the other way like nu-start beat
Work for the president
Amendment 1
What you said absolutely not
Walmart
They were fine with this for two months
Superfly
I'd started the turn if you'd like
It has an expiration date of 2 months
I don't know I mean
I don't know I don't know how I feel about this from my likes
Station management
Perspective like
Do they have the right
To just say like
I don't want to play this person songs
They don't have a contract
But they have to play
Baby
Shity
Yeah if you're
No not playing some of the music
Because of a political reason
Yeah but like
Shapiro metal station you're not required to play reggae
Right I mean like
Unless
I don't know
Wyclef stacy says something anti-bush then you have
Have to play it
And so
Easy
Protesting
What if
This is like we're talkin
Mid late 90s
Sure he got an alternative station
But you hate
Peanut
The personal is personal do you have to have a 11
Like a personal problem
With Nick Hexum
Do you have to play 311
Don't think so
I don't know if it's
Weird and certainly I'm opposed to
Politically
Just saying like no I don't
Your politics are such
But I'm not going to play your songs but like
I mean
If I was going to be impressed by these DJ's having any interest in gas than their actions
Probably come on
No it is a little bit like a
I've decided that it is no longer popular for me to suppress this seat
We're not going to carry Jane Austen
We're just not doing it I remember her comments about bush
That's how we do carry no more than two months later that I will put you
New Jane Austen novels pretty hot people like it
See that this is pretty much exactly what they say there's like
Is that a joke
No no he said no
Seriously guys
That was not a joke
That wasn't even like one of those jokes where you laugh but you
You're hoping they'll be like we're totally going to
To do that you'll be like that was what I was trying to do I was just making
Can a joke it wasn't that it was like
Hey
What reality show was seriously
You made a lot of news suspension right now
Please block me
It is nice to know that
The cop chasing still strong back in 2003 early adopter
So Alex has
F****** clear
Evil doesn't really spell it out but if it
Really clear
He thinks that there's a
Conspiracy of
So here's the conspirator
Clear Channel
Alright about to radio station
That's right
To Clear Channel own about the radio station
And also about the concert venue
So what they have done
They have manufactured
A whole crisis
Where the Dixie Chicks
Picture of these stations that are owned by Clear Channel
And then
They go on tour
And they have sucked the sell out all their shows
At these venues
That are owned by Clear Channel
I would I would
Suggest that
The Dixie Chicks don't need to sell more tickets
No they were doing all right
They were huge
Yeah yeah yeah
What are the reasons that it was so nuts their orders
In the top
3 top 40 country music X
In the world
They were killed
That's why they had to be taken down cuz they had two large of a platform to criticize bush
So
Alex tries to lay out this can
Conspiracy to the DJs
Now through this conspiracy to make sense
There's two things that need to be true
Yes one
This needs to be clear channel station
True
The venue
Where the Dixie Chicks are playing needs to be owned by Clear Channel for this conspiracy to have any of
Effect on them
Okay
I don't know if they are the promoter behind the Dixie Chicks concerts or not I know they do
They have several venues across the country including a couple in Colorado
And I didn't know they have Clear Channel entertainment which are for both concert
Not sure if there are one of the promoters for the chicks or not
Jonathan Ross
Their venue in Colorado is fairly small bills
Center
Once I get all this attention oh I guess we won't know but you know
People do.
True
This this is falling apart
Usually it's more like
Verily this
Interview is fascinatingly falling apart
Because these DJs are not free speech Crusaders anyway that Alex
Maybe would have liked
Refuted
Weisinger in the span of about a minute correct pillars
If it's conspiracy that clear channel is trying to
Boost their life
Sales
For one of the most popular actor in the world
Let's talk where they get kicked off radio
Three of things that you hope to her true
At least one of those should have been true
Man
No that's not good and at the very least you're not a data point for the Clear Channel
So
Alex
Is recognizing some of the similar thing
Things that I am
Another this is falling apart
Besides
Retreat to attacking these guys supports Natalie Maines as bright
To say whatever she wants so
Coronavirus
Mayweather
Were there because I don't know
You know personally whether or not there are weapons of mass destruction
Weather Thursday
I'm not an expert on that part
Not
That's true
We're just country DJs and the end for us it's about the music mainland
Yeah
We are just country DJ's bases on the fair
I hate you
I like that.
Yeah
I would like to use that yeah okay so my position is that I support the troops and your reply
Bottles of that is making the own literally everything the government has ever done
Great
How about I tell you that I'm a country DJ the f*** alone
I'm not going to litigate every before the government has ever made
Great what a great comeback
Cuz what
Do you work
Picture of a country DJ
I'll tell you what
Complicated in
Clear-eyed views of global international politics
No
You're not with me even express
Phone or show we play music
We are going to we're not all that political
Certainly
This is coming on the show you certainly confused
Why did you say all those words
Did that is Alex just trying to take something
From the interview
Clear Channel conspiracy didn't work out
You guys aren't Heroes
They're kind of just morning Zoo dick
If your
Few have been
Slated Soca
Completely by these assholes
Then there's also that
Little bit of Alex's like
Resentment coming out of like you didn't give me what I want so I will
Take it from you that kind
Oh yeah
So I think
Codependency with the auto
This caller who calls in after the interview
Wants to make Alex feel better
And try and help him with that Clear Channel
Conspiracy
Name of the promotion promotion
Company is sfx
Payment
Counters
Go to website
Channel
It doesn't matter
Yeah
It does really does
Should
Does make me mad mex entertainment
And then got
Awesome
Into its own
Sing again
I don't know I couldn't
Go back in
Can figure out if
The Dixie Chicks
All of their events were
I'll run through Live Nation sure I don't know I don't think
It doesn't prove any conspiracy
I believe we are at this moment fighting
The little devil who is destroying all of Iraq
In order in service of
Destroying all of the United States
I'm so
What clear Channel's doing about the
The Dixie Chicks promotions make a few extra bucks on tickets
Whatever
Go for it Clear Channel I'd be willing
Stipulate
And not accept as true but I'll just go ahead and
I'm not even fighting
By virtue of
Live Nation
Is doing ticketing for all of
Of the Dixie Chicks
Sure why not
That still doesn't prove the conspiracy and Alex
No I won't put it past the recording industry
They pull up some b******* all the time that man so I saw Josie and the Pussycats movie was
I get it all
Conspiracy
So I called her called in another one
He's going to Siri
Sometimes
Alex's show
Is being blocked out
By waves
I think I'm tired
Because you need someone
I know frequencies
Continue with the same hours later
They can get you into
You can hear it but I don't know if they trying to block you out of work
The same thing too
I'm doing the day but at night time when people home
I want to listen to the radio
If the same block out they can't get you in
Appreciate
What a what a
I just wrote down
What do you mean they block us out like Alex said what do you mean they block us out not
Obviously they are always
Well I think
I think I'm going to realize there's not money in that probably
And the only action you might end up
Precipitating is harassment of
The stations that do play him that's true and you might end up
Cutting in
You might bite bite the hand that feeds
Convince people under attack with the affiliate
Restaurants
No good
Alex
Describing his enemies
Use
See if you hear The Devil in
Warburg
Rockefeller
That sounds astoundingly terrestrial that sounds like
Business interests
To have an idea of working
Together to create a worldwide dictatorship tyranny
Yeah it does not seem like
It's
People who are in the employ of the devil who has
Contacted them via trans
Dimensional demon
And offered them life
Suspension technology
They carry out an elaborate
A complicated plan
To slowly and orderly kill all Humanity
Should they fail to do that they have a back-up plan
They're just really super bioweapons real everybody off
It seems like this is a guy who wants to at least be taken seriously
As a knot science
Fiction writer
Yeah
His improvised storytelling is much more like
Grisham
At this point I propose to Phillips
Powerful lawyers taking over everything
Realty
No indeed exact it seems like his biggest problem is
Ultimately what the end result of capitalism always seems to be which is staggering wealth
Trinity quality leading to it
Aristocratic
I'd love for you to go back in time and talk to him about that
So that cooler
Who's talking about Alec
Speeding under attack through waves right
I thought he was
Terraplanter
The minds of military man
Scalar attack
Too much truth Play the song comes back from break and
Where in Texas in the satellites
In Minnesota that sometimes you know there's a problem
Just like that
It happens
Could be
And attacked because he's telling too much truth
Possible
Alex has an article in the LA Times
But he's been bringing up a little bit
To-do with
Ro boy Joseph McCarthy
Subway
Wednesday
Really why
Arone
Moral one
This article from the LA times as an opinion piece and Alex's actually lying about the main thrust of the article
The author John moroney is arguing that there was a point to opposing communism during the Cold War but the actions of people like Joseph
McCarthy gave that opposition a really bad name
Because McCarthy was an opportunist fraud and demagogue
Even in that sentence Alex reads the words
Quote the document shouldn't be allowed to undermine the importance storical Factor this
Soviet communism was a very real threat
Like those words
Don't make sure
Are these lizards curious why this article is arguing that documents
Possibly undermine that notion of his articles about McCarthy
The headline literally starts
Quote despite
McCarthy
Anyway
Things are in this headline everything because these documents that got released
2003 world record of Secrets
McCarthy held with Witnesses prior to them
In public appearances
And he was attempting to
Intimidate
Article about the documents from the BBC
Many had only tenuous connections of Comedy
Through family members are book clubs were marks was red
For unions with left-wing leader
The new documents paint a picture of a senator out-of-control summoning Witnesses at short notice and browbeating them with
The threat of imprisonment or public.
Disgrace
But it was noticeable that those
He could not intimidate and private were often not called
Then public session
How shity is our government press that they're like
These documents show Joseph McCarthy was unhinged
I don't know if you were alive when he was arrested to do it they reveal a new level of
Artifice
Some crap like
The articles that I was reading about this really laid out how different
He behaved
In the public
Earrings
And these private one
Sure and there was
Kind of
It did almost feels like
The feeling out process
That's like that last sentence there
Are the people that wouldn't
Back down to him quickly were called to the public why
Create the public
Looking
Grandstand
Sandwich
Also from the article quote
According to Senate historian David Ritchie the private hearings were more of an Inquisition
Using circumstantial evidence hearsay and intimidation to force people to acknowledge his point of view
Documents that came out in 2003 paint Joseph McCarthy as an out-of-control lunatic trying to run
Times editorial is an attempt to remind readers that just
Because McCarthy really suck
That doesn't mean that Soviet communism didn't exist
What do you say
If you were really someone who was opposed to Communism in you'd read this article
You couldn't come away from it honestly with the position that it
Vindicated
McCarthy
The article literally says quote
Many seem to have forgotten that the Communist party was dedicated to replacing our democratic form of government with a totalitarian state similar to
Listed in the Soviet Union
McCarthy and those who exploited his successes are largely to blame for that
According to Moroni McCarthy is a detriment
To the opposition of God
Essentially
The only two conclusions I can come to about Alex's coverage of this article or the following
He didn't read the article anything that actually says that
McCarthy was totally cool
And he's just making up with the body of a tie
Defending McCarthyism in the tactics of witch hunting is more important
The Alex and actually being opposed to Communism
Which makes us anti-communism essentially
Tactical as opposed to something
Play some Prince
Yeah I was going to make sure what I think
I was going to say you just read
Alex is also a detriment to and I
Defend
McCarthy as well
Yeah it seem it seems like
Nobody's like hey you know what's
Great the John Birch Society fighting,
I think they really did a great job I think they really got to the point
Really hammered at all
He is
You know like
Idealist
Sickly an ideologically opposed to Communism in all this
But
If you can't
Do it like McCarthy today
It doesn't want to do it
Defeat
Sex trafficking
With a daring sunlight raid
Then I don't want to deal with that I just want to make everybody else angry about
Yeah it is
I get
The science that he would not be so opposed
To Communism
Is his route to do it was to be
An economic
Professor researcher got no Fanfare and didn't get to do these
Public hearings like McCarthy which is a show
Out of it I don't know if your DS
As interested
This word is academic and more just s******* screaming we might have Alex on our side
It is basically what we're talking about here
Maybe there
Impossible
So
Neri so much.
So Alex picks another call and this guy has a terrible answer to it and that is why are we even talk
Talkin about the assault weapons
It doesn't even come up
Until next year
2004 is when it's up for re renewable or
Or I let it let it laugh
Sure sure
And so Alex hasn't
Interesting answer that I think is totally wrong
And
Reflected on on
24-hours
Circle B
Points
Dandapani
Administration
Dealing with the assault weapon
With so many concerns about
Warren so far
The blue so far
Start screen
Probably going to be a shooting at the second Matrix opening
Second Matrix movie
Disturbia trigger
And then
They're talking about the assault weapons ban stuff
So they can be right in advance
Ryder this thing that didn't happen
This like
Is the president
To the way he engages with gems
Yeah in the future like that
This is the pattern of thinking is there all along
That almost sounds like Norm pattis
The the color does not voice almost sounds like him
I'm not sure who the phone I can
Kind of hear it and I would love to
To find out that that was actually a young Norm noise like developing their way
Bishop for those early appearances
Is either
Like someone who legitimately doesn't really understand what Alex does or somebody who
Really really wants people to think he doesn't
I don't know it just sounds like we're in the word like it
TV show in our eighth season and we start doing all the flashbacks and it turns out our
Main characters
All coincidentally met twenty years ago in Netherland
Owen Shroyer
It's true what a weird world
So here Alex's
About things that will happen
In the future
Worse than
Borders
Empower
I'm really into
I know this getting repetitive and these two thousand three interested in what's
Going to happen
I went the bathroom.
Because
Keep hitting this note so cancel
He's bringing up
How the benefits are in charge
The government US government
It's
He's so insistent about something that we know for a fact to be 100% diamet
Strictly the opposite
And then he is going
To eventually run into that
Brick wall
Driving
It's 60 miles an hour
Interested to see you like
Does he
The brakes
The roadrunner
Ready go through you like
I hate I feel like that metaphorically is what he does a lot of the time
Tunnel drive-thru
So a caller calls and wants to know
Underground prisons
Better paying bill
I wanted to ask
Give you any information
Underground
Prison camps
Developing because
Underground
Because down here in Trinidad
Epic reading
Japanese
And it has all mine
It's that they're getting
I'm going to collect
Sure
Bro
Yeah it's very cool very strange to listen to Alex be like
The prison pipeline are the prison industrial complex is going to eventually become what it is like he's he's right on
What about the Prison Complex
To hear the crazier conspiracy theory from his collar like that weirds me out
We're living in a complete topsy-turvy world
Because normally nowadays he would come out with something
Let you know this at the devil's killing everybody in there like
Yeah but maybe the devil is just trying to raise the corporate tax rate like you know it's weird
The way that goes
It is true
Speaking of
Like an inversion of the present
This next call
Locked up
If you consider Alex in the present
I'm saying we need to
Increase
No demanding that they
Bring these people to Justice
The whole bush
Administrator
Nor'easter
Minions the bootleg
We need to get his puppet master
Everybody else
If it's good enough everybody else is probably
Good enough for now
Your
Call Omar
You're right your audio is cutting out
Sure
Exterminate their enemies
And the Puppet Masters of the globalist puppet
It's like bush
And Alex pretends that he didn't hear him
And goes to break
When he comes back from the break
He makes a point
To bring this back up
I heard what I heard from Target
From Michigan
Rent control
I know that Alex is like
Politically I want to kill you in the future or whatever service to the idea of
Was not violent
This is an instance where he
Clearly was caught off guard by The Scholar saying we need to exterminate these folks
And then went to break
And decided to come back
Re bring it up
Distress
Did violence
He's not the way to go
Haven't you heard the old adage
If you're not a liberal at
You have no heart and if you don't want to exterminate the
The port 40 you have no brain
At everybody everybody knows this
There's a real sense
What's the Tiger
Alex
Might be a little bit more
Keenly aware of how dangerous some of the people who are drawn to his worldview Maybe
Possible
I do I don't know though
Boring as hell maybe you just doesn't have the
I mean he's just more in a vulnerable position
You know he's still got boss
At this time he doesn't have
Complete
Autocratic
Yeah well that's fair
But I mean answer to some
There is still someone
Above
And now there is no one
While his dad is HR
I don't know if his dad is still alive I think this is a psycho situation where his dad is actually
In his attic
A skeleton
I just think it's very
Interesting
Then Alex
It's still like obviously is bracket still incredible
What you're doing
Weep
World of difference
Taking a step back
To calmly
I am in
Emphatically stress
No violence
Violence is no good it's not the answer
And Alex's
Long
Pornographic ramps
Sprite about slitting people's throats
I am talking about how all the globalist are already dead
And all they said that in the present-day I mean if you want
Bulshit argumentative Bedford
Cancel culture
Look at how people act
When there are possible consequences
Look at how people act whenever you just build available
Versus when you act
When there are absolutely none
To be done
Is there
This leaves Alex earlier
Cuz do
Wrestling episode
He gets into a bit of a hint
Space where are you
He's saying things that a lot of it sounds
Pretty good
I don't believe him
And obviously because I know where his Show Goes
Don't think that he means it.
But
Go after
Because
That's the reason
Yes
It's really interesting for our today that hate Camp our their their movement
Or whatever
Because I mean
I would say that that's one of the major problems with the right-wing as it exists
Today
Yeah
Because hate fuels their worldview
Allison 2003
Even as aware of it it's not as over
Or you just
Such a wide net
He doesn't even know the difference
It's between hate and not
You got this you got this headspace where you don't exterminate your enemies
No that would be bad
Wants them
Sure back off globe
I want to give you some really good advice
Has an interview
So much trouble Alex has good reviews and people coughing
Don't sign it worth
Is there time to argue with him I guess
Need to back off
Any other good news
I've got some advice
It's for Alex
Why Woody
Or something
If the
Is a globalist when they see week
Interstate acting when they see
Dominus they move forward
The preceding eight years after this
Keep it Alex
And all of his friends are dumb and weak
Yeah it's correct
Stop everything exactly what they prove
That's it
In two
3 turns out there's not many global
Wholesomeness
Also, I would describe his show in the present day
Wholesome wholesome
The buttercream gang
Alex
Harrison whites are the best Smith
I think of the buttercream gang
Yeah either this was just really weird
Cuz it was it's filling time
More last night about how like
We got to be peaceful we can't be hateful
Wilshire the globalist are in trouble cuz we're so popular
And you got to be strong and we believe in
Goodness
Seems to be in respond
Monster that caller bring up extermination of the enemy
It does seem like it's
Genuine to
I wonder if I mean
I wonder if it's also in part
Because Alex is probably pretty excited about getting these DJs on and it shouldn't go well sure I wonder if that really
Little bit
Since we know that
Generally speaking
The what comes out of his mouth is the result of how he's feeling
As opposed to what's going on
Wasn't something
To build on at all and he was going to pretend that interview never happened
Mulligan or whatever
Thunder
What are the things we discovered
. of time that we've looks
Through
At least the last
Few years you are going back into 2015 right even prior to Trump's candidacy
Alex loves poop
True and Russia
Love them
Big strong man I think the song I'm a horse without a shirt on
Yeah there's a little farther back
That was
Here's 2003
Figure that out
In the present day
Alex does not believe
Oh no absolute
Does not believe that Putin was behind the bombings they were blamed on the Chechen Rebels
Expedient
Truth
I think there is something interesting about this is
When was the LIE
Was he lying about there being a fact or is he lying now
Yeah
Or does he just
Not care
Yeah I mean I I think
To a certain extent like when you think about Ally you do think about somebody
With malicious intent or at the very least like
Desire to hide information or something like that
And to me what I'm seeing from all of this
Totality now is
The man who just doesn't give a
F*** if it's true or not or whatever
He's not
Lying he's just he just doesn't care
You know he's
He's he's just beyond lying or not lying
He's just making up his own reality that he exists in from a moment-to-moment
Point of view and there's some things that seem pretty consistently import
Like him being left alone
Christian
Supremacy whiteness
Spell rotten
And then he's figured out some
Routines that work
Pretty well-liked the vaccine live
Love you too see him doing
Consistently
Another caller
Jesus
I just keep this in because I think
Make sidewalk look like
I can't,
Yeah I know but
What
Wow that is that is pre-staging his televangelism right then
Your home sell your home to give it to me
Go to your neighbor to go get money to buy a second VCR so you can make copies of my
My movies which will Free Press
Wow
That's real.
Yeah I can't I can't imagine
The
The level of narcissistic you have
CB2
Have multiple follow-up
When someone's explaining why they can't Robbie your tapes
Sales
You know it that's at like
Bill
Back when I worked in telemarketing
You know if your calls were monitored
But you didn't trouble if you have two bottles
Exactly what Alex was doing there but
It's not it's not sales
Talking to a
Bulshit
31 West whip Year from May 9th
Alex
About his enemies
There's no mention of the day
Now that's newworldorder bankers
I mean
Multiple times at least 2 days
Clearly expresses who he feels he's up again
And it's all good rest real concerns if it's not an elaborate
Conspiracy of dimensions
It's not no it's not metaphysical dreams when he was 10 nothing
Oh no
And I mean like
This doesn't
Prove that he never talks about any of this stuff I like
A lot of the themes
That you would think
Might have been important
Yeah are not important if they normally come up
Now if you brings up something
Similar to these topic
There's always that personal element of like you know like none of that none of that
No talk about
Do you
Cabals secret no
Child Trading blood-drinking
Are you guys mentioned Bill Gates or what why
It isn't in there with The Rock
Child's in the Bilderberg
Mention of Bill Gates
Of course he's been relevant for a long time in Atlanta
I'll take that because it works
Counter to his political positions of
Doing everything
You can't hurt the developing world
Anyway
I thought you enjoyed a little bit of this
Inasmuch as
You know
The Dixie Chicks
Chickadee
I think the
Certainly
I don't even want to know what Alex is doing
In present day
Franklin
No-No No-No No-No No-No No-No No-No No-No No-No No-No No-No
No I know
Conflicted about whether or not
To cover present day
Anyway whatever whatever ends up happening will be back
Swervo on
We are on Twitter is that all just go to bed Jordan
Please find a local charity or Bethany ready to help out people doing God's work
Oh I'm Leo I'm dcx
Avatar cast
Secretly brought
Do you buy Clear Channel in an elaborate
Conspiracy to sell
Do
Alex Jones is live Cabaret review