Damn important I sweat it
I have great respect for its knowledge B. I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Need need money
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Jordan Jordan
Crushing a b after several weeks
The practicing attention to it perfectly
I don't appreciate positive
Fair enough, what do you appreciate that
Because my question is what is your bright spot this week
A good people about this and vibrate spot is
After four and a half years I've decided to take a vacation
The first time
In a very long time it's debatable if you days off here and there
I went to visit my parents
A holiday
Not quite vacation we went to Austin to do a live show
When you got to
Book and write it off on Earth
I don't really know how to relax
I'm not really good at that and but finally we've decided to take a vacation
And your partner actually going together Nightcore
I will be going to Hawaii
You for a week officially
Exactly
A big part of this is I've been meaning to take a trip back to my childhood home
Honolulu and Aulani Elementary School in
Go to Waikiki Beach
You know kick around to the spino the old deal with the hots
Oh yeah.
I have a lot of like sort of vague memories and snapshots in my head that I'd like
Like to experience hasn't
Adult
To try and fill in some of those gaps
I'm very excited
Take this trip and hope I don't freak out
From lack of working
Sometimes you're going to stay in your hotel late at night by yourself
Staring up at
The feeling
What if I were work
King right now
Better I don't doubt that will be the case
Also this is relevant because
The next three episodes we're going to have to
Preparing is a
Of taking off for vacation
Hopefully
The schedule of release won't be affected At All by
Notice
That they will be maybe
Hey what's up let's say something happens in the world we may not be aware of we may not know because we're in
Trump Mike raisbeck
Back to Powerade
Definitely will not know
I don't know I think of anything super crazy happen will probably break into a recording studio somewhere bill
Hey we got it
Guidon on vacation on Lake January 4th
BFF episodes coming out and we wouldn't be aware that the capital of thunderstorm
That's what I'm saying
View
Spore
Alibi you're doing with your breakfast at my partners as you know my partner is
The teacher at school to be unnamed
But
Basically
Their new principal started at the beginning of this
This school year
You're so
And she has proven herself to be a
Giant Reese's Pieces
Really bad thing about naming the school
To the point where all of the PPI bipoc staff and students have
Eventually just gone on f****** revolt
Wow
Unsustainable
And so today
These kids organized
The f****** sit-in
And then later on a walk out
And my partner sent me a little clip of it and
The
Bipoc students
Leading this s*** are
Absolutely astonishing
At a certain point all these kids are chanting protect our
Teachers protect our teachers
And I'm like
Weeping my balls off
Like these are
These kids are incredible
Great like truly incredible and that's my price but absolutely
Put on them
So Jordan
Today we have an interesting
Situations get into his eyes I mentioned
Yeah we're going to be pre-recording some episodes and that's going to make it more difficult to be
In the present-day keeping up with Alex so my plan to you no stay in the past in 2003 problem
For those episode
That's why I didn't want to do 2003 episode here
Today
And it so I was like alright present-day let's see what Alex is going at 2
Look
Alex has been on vacation
Why don't we coordinate
He needs to let us know we always have in the past
This is infuriating
I understand the situation israel-palestine
Ray's B big deal
I do understand that
I don't care what Owen Shroyer has to say about what I salute
I'm interested in the Infowars position and exactly how this is a false flag and
And what happened
I'm not going to listen to an hour and a half to get a sensitive really don't need to hear Owen say what amounts to
None of this is
Is real it's all Palestine actually attacking themselves and even if Israel was committing genocide
I support
I know that's what they would say I'm not I'm not into
Just didn't hear any of that nonsense from Owen
There is an update I need to give you about the present day
Psyop expert
It's been that subtly sneaking his way back onto the show
Big cannot quit him
Alex
Steve pieczenik is is creeping back
And he's just flattering the s*** out of oh and I watched Cory interview to that call you're the best
Horse
Goddamnit these idiots can be tricked in the same way all the time
Time I also noticed that
When I was watching
This this interview I noticed that Steve was reading a lot
Keep clearly looking down at something is rattling off a lot of these details and stuff
A lot of it
He's probably
Prepared
Yeah
I mean
Feel like
Somehow we're thinking of this
As a negative thing
But
Being a guest
Nbm by far more
Prepared than anything that your host is ever done
Seems like a positive ion disagree and I support preparation
I just think
Think that the wave it's Steve
Uses specific
And things like that is to
Create the impression of familiarity
Create the impression of familiarity with the staff of
You know various administration's it would be kind of not as impressive that he
Dino's people's names
If it's on a sheet of paper in front of that kind of preparation kind of trying to use
Who's his appearance
I ended the way you trying to present myself
And rattling off details gives him the appearance of
Having a recall that is
Astonishing
Yes how can
How can one man possibly
Play pull all of these things I'll give you making up all of
The exact
Puryear Steve wouldn't
The pier on video
You'd only be on the phone and there would be like a picture of him from when he was much younger
Sure
With weird mustache
Yeah but that was because back in those times he had like a bunch of files in front of him and he didn't want to be on
I wonder about that never really thought about things I never really watched
Too closely
But his eyes were
Definitely reading
I would also accept
It wasn't until the pandemic that he insisted that some child in his neighborhood go set up Zoom for him
So we can accurately I don't know details
If you do go to the YouTube channel you can see her pressing the start-and-stop button
That is
Very pretty
It is unfortunately humanizing of a real weirdo
But it's very cute
So I guess what that leaves us with is
Possibly
I mean I don't know I don't know
Can time for us to record anything in the present day.
Our trip
Right so we may be getting back to Alex in the present day when we get back of not really knowing
Exactly where to go for this episode luckily
I found something
We'll get to it
After
We say hello
Knives
Nicely done
So first Sheila be the garden
Queen package about your nail polish
Sheila
Give me from Seattle this is a shout out in a walk title going
I appreciate you getting all around the world into the show
Text Uncle patches CPA
Next
Thank you so much
Thank you very much
Down with the Tyrant King
Jared
Thank you very much
I'm a policy wonk
Mirror free advertising for God's Eternal wrath make as much when I was walking
Etc
Now don't we do a little bit of business
Sometimes
You know you got to take that
Punch as it comes naturally realize that you was messed up
Everybody has a plan until they get punched
In the mouth what is
A plan but God laughing
True or something
How's that work no man plans while God laughs
You got it
He's going to laugh at anybody for
For planning nobody it's like that
Oh oh I love this guy so much
Eternals
That's laughing at a homeless person God is laughing at a houseless person
F****** offense
I'm offended by God's God's house of April birthday
April birthdays
Happy birthday back April this from my husband
I wish you happy birthday I hope you had a great birthday
Although I f***** up this one
I talked to happy birthday back in April
Happy birthday Tanya
It's totally on me I need to do a better job of managing inboxes
Now you're doing
Now
Not all is trouble
Because we also have a present this is coming from Savannah
Savannah wanted me to give a shout out to their spouse
I wish I was there to Shawna a happy birthday so
Integrate one out there
Perfect
Jordan
What time do the pass
When do the present
We do the middle
I felt like that might be too confusing me out
Can't go back to that well
Project Camelot
I think she got kicked off YouTube
And now he's back to a membership model
I don't know about the ethics of using
I'm back to being an aunt
Shaky Ground
I told that leaves us in a bit of a panther
Okay right got to do something
Is there anything that I've been meaning to do review that
Bottle episode of Breaking Bad
I have some thoughts okay
Today
There is something
Constantly been like
Did you ever do that
And we had
Broadcast
Just coming up here
That's right
What are we doing
Feels so weird about the 2001 free 9/11
Noam Chomsky appeared on Infowars
Program
Noam Chomsky
The linguist
Not the very short shows up in your house in the middle of night makes cookies
Gnome with a G
No that is not is not
Good gnome chompski alright
It is the the noted intellectual
This actually is one of the more interesting interviews that I've ever heard on Infowars
He doesn't have the
The cachet of predicting 911 yet
I also think that he doesn't have
Nearly as much of the
Market share he doesn't have
As much notoriety I don't think that
People who might be invited to be on his show know much about him
And so
But you have you have that
I take it through what is not know that Alex is fighting the literal Deb
I don't know if Alex knows that
We haven't established that it was pointed the game aware that he was up against
You know I think everleigh is days in his career a lot of it was based around like
You know making big bubbles
Distance about trying to get the church
The Branch Davidians
3 belt
He had some notoriety on a regional basis
From that but if you look at the early part of his career really
February 7th
That's got to be all-around 9/11 conspiracy over this is the fourth
Also another thing that's really weird
Is the day agree about a lot
Of course
Do they actually know they have course they do Alex and Noms
I agree about a lot of
CertiFit surface-level of
But when you get down to sort of wet wet what their beliefs are based on
There's a little bit of difference
This interview
Could have been
Amazing
And it could have been
Great
It is not
It ends
Very poorly
I'll let you decide
Alright
So Alex
Reed's little bit of
Ibio
He's a professor of linguistics
6ya
And he's written books like Manufacturing
Video
I'm also called titled manufacture
They will have a supposed to bait on television
Participating exact implementation
But just a few degrees
There's really some
Difference
Supposedly
Either phony champ
That's how I put a Chomsky
Doesn't know it more sophisticated fashion
Manufacturing consent is about the media but it's not necessarily about staging events
Sir false flags are that kind of stuff away Alex's kind of
Leading in prison
The general thesis of chomsky's book
Largely co-written by Edward Herrmann is it the media engages in self-censoring of ideas that are opposed to the interests of the elite
Corporations
In such a way that encourages
Acceptance of the policies being put in place by the government
Switch support those enter
Often to the detriment of what's in the interest
List of normal people
It's more complicated than what I even what I'm presenting but that's a large part of what Chomsky and Herman called the pro
Propaganda model
It doesn't rely on coercion to operate rather get the product of just Market
Forces
There's a structural conflict of interest in how the media's organized that creates a disconnect between conveying all of the information that's rather
Move it to the interest of the upper upper classes
And those of everyone else
This is the general
Put to you
Media were capable of reporting correctly they would be reporting every single day that we should do
Do everything we can to destroy their billionaire owner
Otherwise their entire journalism is
Interesting
I don't think I'll be qualified to give a full breakdown of the idea than that text but I can tell you that I'm also certain
But Alex has not read it
The propaganda model includes five filters
Theorize is being determined
About whether certain news is represented in the larger media
The first Fallout 4 our ownership funding sources and flag
How to probably find agreement on those for but he absolutely could not accept the 5th
Which is anti-communist
Strikeout
Difficult
Communism was the preferred media fear Outlet in the time that the book was first
Published
During the Cold War the massacre went out of style but it is for some people during the Cold War
For the mass media wasn't going
Going to give a serious chance to an outlet that went at odds with the prevailing narrative which was to be afraid of
The commies
In more recent times chomsky's recontextualizing this filters updated
The time where the war on terror is more relevant as a media filter after 9/11 than a communist
Alex can probably agree the large portions of the media have the
The same opinion on big issues like a war on terror
And it possibly was meant to scare people into except
Open policies they wouldn't
Maybe otherwise
But he absolutely couldn't
Never accepted anti-communist fervor during the Cold War
Was it anyway part of that
Personality
Is built is
Crumbled
That's kind of interesting what happens is that Alex has
A predetermined
Set of beliefs
He's just decided the chops
Ski packs those up
Or at least enough of them that he
You can make it look like he supports all
Yes yes
Alex talks
Before getting into the actual interview
More about his
This is 2001 the similarities between the left and the right
Republic has always been very surface
It's like Republican
Conservative
The political left
Wear black uniforms
Police or black uniforms the ski mask around the world
They just have to
The police
In the middle of that system
More semantical deception
I think it's strange here is that like
I could hear somebody saying like the left and the right to say and they all wear black ski masks sure
And it being a metaphor
Malik I don't think it is
No it's absolutely Direct
Yeah yeah
If he does not believe that they actually have secret police
Then I don't know what anything is real anymore
I don't know what's true or what's false
Batman believes everyone has secret police and ski mask
Are you believe that like
Play foundational beliefs system
He believe he believes it
Small
Corporations that have SWAT teams and stuff at this point it's
I don't even want to know what army
He thinks AT&T has
How cute
I just
I I come away from
Clips like that with a feeling that
Like I don't
Know-how
In depth
Any of this
Assessment of
Like the similarities between left and right off
Cuz I do think you can make a decent argument that there are several are
Obviously there are
Entwined interest
There are
They're similar priorities
In some ways but they're also
Huge difference
Email
And I don't understand how Alex
Never really gives voice to those
Because they're ignores them
Because
What's the differences make it look like
They're the people that he actually supports our
Bad
Oh yeah that's right
It is it is hard to be like wow okay there's one difference between
Democrats do want people to eat food
I was kind of maybe being facetious when I say I don't know why
I realize that I didn't even know that I was being
Here Comes Chomsky
End of the debate
Sorry babe
Conversation
I do have some some agreement and this
This is a little bit longer clip That's goes Johnson speaks in full sentences
Oh yeah
Learned his lesson
Open right now
Okay
98% of people don't even know
The real parameters of power that surround them
Phony paradigms and systems of phony left ride
With all the roads leading towards a centralized highly controlled corporate
Bureaucracy
Think of it as a kind of a footnote
You're describing is quite purpose
I'm conscious self-conscious
The Country Fest
Pickling 20th century
There has been a
Very self-conscious
Speculative
L say so
Business Leaders
Electrostatic
Scientists know they say
Outer space
Important to
Public remains
Spectators
Participant
They're supposed
Directed to other concern
I'm not interfere with policy formation
Phenomenon
That's really
Find Century
And the reason was very clear
By the early 20th century it was becoming
Difficult
People
By other means
Branch of the voting franchise was extending
Labor unions for women were
Let me know
Ashley England the United States
Early on
Worser
Property or some other means you
That was used
That's what the US public relationship
Grows out of these experiences and
They develop put out their papers that I read
The Carnegie endowment others
Mind control
Haitian is much cheaper and much more effective
And it's the only thing you can do
Countries you can't control people with a gun
Something that I think is really key here is to notice like where there is
A salient
Agreement
Between
And also the way that those two things
Things are fully
Differently understood by the two-party about the same thing
No
I think it is
Do you know what what time can you bring two
To the table he's ideas about
Wanting to keep people disengage
From some
Publix
Discourse
Decisions
They could be detrimental to
Elite corporations
Centrist
I am in so much as that is in their interest then
You know
Not having all information
Polly disseminated Works to those goals
And I didn't invent
Muddying the water
I would like
Like propaganda especially the United States propaganda has been rocking that boat for a long time
Roots of advertising other than that what is social media in
Influencers
Ennard a what
Any kind of publicity
A lot of that stuff is
Is just perception management
There is a real conversation that can be had and I
It's
You know I obviously wouldn't necessarily take this tack but someone should say
But it literally everybody was
Engaged
In decision-making about every issue
He'll be impossible
For a society to function
And maybe
A limit
There is an argument that could be made for
You know people being disengaged
Is more
Is actually a better organizational model I'm not I'm not advocating that should I could see someone making that boy
And I can see tropski having an interesting conversation with that
On the other hand
His beliefs
We are so much into the vaccines are meant to make us dumb
They poison us in our food
In all this
Video
Even this point of agreement
Is a Point of Departure
For the two of them
I find that
Very
Weird looking
Yeah I mean it does sound like
Noam Chomsky is describing the phenomena of
Government
Destroying the ability of the electorate to honestly engage with their actions
And Alex responded
So obviously you're talking about mind control
And I think I think
Do you know I don't have a good enough glimpse of Alex a2001 Altuve
Based on
Dunno.
The present day
I would guess that he means like someone putting a pendulum
Zoology
Mind control
Look into my spinning
I think so but I think it's the way you know someone like
Is Castaway
Interactive that is taking that as metaphor
If Alex was like
So you're in agreement with me they're putting computer chips inside everybody's brain to make them do what they tell them to
To an old would have gone
That is
Not what I'm saying at all
But I don't know what
That's what Alex is saying back at this point
That's one of the parts
There is kind of challenging about this is
You can hear that
From Alex even as metaphor
As flourishes speaking
Right as opposed to it being like I have you under my control.
That does kind of
Point out
One big issue though
Is that
All too often
Can we just assume people are capable of
Well it's interesting that he's talking to a linguist
Borderline the Turing test
What's going on it's borderline Alex trying to fool
Computer addiction YouTube
Chomsky's is shockingly charitable with Alex
It's to his credit is my kind size
Alex talks about how bush in Clint
This is going to be have to be
Yeah I guess it would be
George W bush
Cuz he just got elected
Has been given the boot yeah and Alex
Facts about how
They're the same
Keystone of very specific
6 set of accent
Well take Bush and Clinton they have the exact same policies
On land grabbing selling-out sovereignty
The industrialization
The children
They have this
This
This cult like following of their parties and can't admit it's really the same
Can I call the same
Detroit to corporate
The New World Order
Maybe I'm naive
Publix in there
My feeling is that
The general public is rather well aware of
Public opinion study
Pretty trustworthy and various
20 years or so
Percent of the population
When they're asked
What do you think the country
The government or what it do
The answer that they pick out of a set of choices is
The government works for the fuel in the special interest
Coming at this with the perspective of like
Alright
A lot of people are aware
There's a different problem
It needs to be addressed
And that'll come up a little bit later in the interview
He's selected criteria upon which Clinton and Bush are the same
Is weird to me
It's
Very
Suspiciously specific
Unfairly articulated
They're both land Grabbers they both children
And then they move on and don't wait what hold on did you see me land-grabbing I assume is code for conservation
Either that or eminent domain
Yeah that could be at this point
It's huge on Alex's mine that could be could be
Oh and also I don't know if Bush's early record with EPA
Stanford necessarily always good
Drugging the children is the one that's like
Okay you're just talking
Sing about like
Psychiatric meds
Was a huge but it's not like bushes putting people up
No-bull shoe is
Cramming Ritalin down everybody's faces
I forgot the No Child Left Behind
Parentheses was
With Riddler
I mean obviously I think that there is
Over-prescription of
Matthew talked about that we're past
Sure
I just don't know exactly what
Expect Clinton or bush to Dubai
If you want to make it illegal
Ted 2 take
I thought he was for
Drug legalization
I see want more
Regulation on pharmaceutical Industries
Opposite Direct
If you're going to get your ADHD meds
You should go to the corner like everybody else does with their truck
I think that's what he's trying to say
If it's not on the corner it's not drugs buddy
Every
Every other night I go down and get a fifth of whiskey on the corner I know a guy
So well-stocked coat
Where else do you think I get my Lamictal
Yeah
It's it
Bizarre
The end again
I think that really illustrates the sort of surface-level and cherry pick
Way in which Alex
Describes the similarity between the
YouTube absolute
I think I
Largely agree with chomsky's analysis that
More
Groundbreak
King stuff
Did event
People
Have an alienation
From Power solutely
Random person on the street
You think it's the government or our corporate overlords
And they'll be like
Going to go with corporate overlords
Not surprising to anyone
There's a shift propaganda that Alex has been
Been feeling
Over the last few years
This is weird
To hear in 2001 because he says this
Timbuktu later years to
But there's been a shift recently
Over the last few years
Anything secret about the globalist
Throwing it in your face
And Chomsky is brought up the idea of hopeless
Hopelessness
Either response
But people can have to the idea that the government isn't necessarily serving their interests and that is a larger
That actually
Some of the other
Things that Alex
Bring up helplessness leads to Hope
I am so Alex is suggesting that this is this shift
Propaganda
From hiding the globalist
To throw it in your face
Is a way of facilitating the total
That does not go in for that
I've seen a shift in the propaganda the last three years from denying all of this
Just rolling it North Face
I am feeling is the roots go back
Really takes off
Screw on the basis of the
Sensible assumption that was
Free clearly articulated
Does not make
Democratic
Fraternities are available
And leaves us to run
And the way to do it was
Leaders are saying we have to
APU
We have two people to
Superficial things like fashionable consumption
Bread and circuses
Figure in the US
Elite media
He's the one who
And that is a phrase manufacturer
And he thought it was necessary
In order to
Make sure that we
Responsible men
I can run the Affairs of the world
And what they didn't say but what is
Personalize your
The people Beeb, responsible man if you're serving the interests
Concentrated price
He's talking about a position
And an idea
He's able to bring up
The people who are the proponents of the opposite of his idea
He's able to engage
With this
How much more thorough weigh
Even in the matter of a minute
Then then Alex is over ever able to
Strange to hear somebody talk on this show
And then be like
Wow
Really thought
Good work man
Good work
Yeah
I don't even know what to like what to respond with
It's just like about these issues but
Noam Chomsky
I feel like that's what I'm learning from all of this is that somehow
I'll see if people can harass him on Twitter
F****** Jones gets to talk to Noam Chomsky
And he doesn't get to listen to me s*** talk him
Wally's explaining the world today
Well
And that is a life is unfair sometimes
It is so I typed
This is this is one of the things that makes this
Kind of difficult
To really even engage with too deeply as
Contact
Jeremiah
And is that
I think
You can see why
Jobs be saying
Articulating positions
Yeah clearly I think we're buddy
You know there's some stuff that I maybe don't entirely agree with
B b b
It would be the matter of
Teasing
In-N-Out points
To really get to the bottom of like okay well
You know
Yes
There is an interest
In
Media in
Gavin people
Consumed with
Superficial
Short course
How much of that is
Intentional
Strategy driven by people who want people to be distracted
And how much of that is
Actively that is what people want their is a market
It for that
Do you know people are feeling that market
What is the balance by
Between the two
Yeah I mean it would be hard to argue that the best
Example of that very thing we
Would be Trump's tweet
Constantly covering Trump
They almost ensured he would at least
I have a run it happen
Rashad it become
President
At the same time
If the public weren't so consumed and so interested it with
With discovering more and more about his dumb
Wait yeah
Then they wouldn't be copper
You know
Mm2 to this question particularly
About what
But he's bringing up about the media and
Do you know what Alex yells bread and circuses with
He's
There's a supply component
Demands component
Ignore either
I think is
Is not the full picture
And I don't think the chomsky's ignoring
Picture of this conversation
That would be the kind of way I would approach this and I
The agency makes points
Are the points
Is he had a perfect opportunity
Opportunity
Cut into Noam Chomsky and be like
Actually I think it goes further back then
That
To roam red and circuses mr. Chow
Your phone now are you alright no could I tell you about that
Bavarian Illuminati
I'd like to tell you
Bucked up ideas I have about
About
The Illuminati
I think I think that
You know John's Keys able to make point
And so it
It's a foreign concept on Infowars
Aubrey brings up the difference of opinion
Between the
Sort of elite corporations
And the
Normal
Person who has a job perhaps in terms of
The free trade
Okay for the public
Are these International economic agreement
The trade deficit
40%
No I'm not
They're also big issues for the business world
Therefore the issues do not arrive
Political campaign
Agreement very little Water Country
Negotiate
Coming to the Americas meeting in
Anthony mansion
Negotiation for a couple years
Managers by trade ministers
Governments or basic
Potato
Things are still team to be going fairly well.
Between get on board with
Now maybe Alex would view this as
Is the consequence
An elaborate Shady can
Conspiracy
To put this trade deal in in order to enslave white man or something
Where is Chomsky would look at it more as the result of business interest
You know those filters that are brought up in the propaganda model things like
Ownership of a conglomerate
The sources of news the
Advertising revenues
Things like that create a market environment where
It's not in the best interest
You know people who made profit
From
One of these Arrangements
To cover it
Too much
If it if it's something that could
Be something that would be very unpopular with
Subnormal voting Pub
One thing I am absolutely seeing that is
Mitigating what I would
Think with so much
Disagreement
Is that Chomsky is elucidating the
Conspiracies that are real that we all know about
You know like
We all know that billionaires in the government's work
Work together to f*** us over
That's a normal conspiracy
That's what they do and it's not even like
It's not even like their fault they're just creations of the system that is
Chopping them up and then they
Continue to
They do that whole thing
But since he's framing it in that conspiratorial like
These
Business interests and the government are all working
Sing together
The fuk is over
That can
Viewed by Alex
In the same way that the metaphor could be viewed by
Right right
Oh you're absolutely right there is a conspiracy of
The Rothschild had the government to focus over with the
Yeah there's enough leeway to this
Was that that Alex
Can still find it
Useful
Maybe they want to read into it
It's the sort of Infowars
Narrative structure
Where is it does not necessarily and it's
But a lot more boring than the way that Alex would push
Batman you can
Absolutely see it like in 2001
That level of like
Because the government is so f******
Corrupt
Because Alex is an outright saying he's fighting the devil
You can go on in the Infowars Show & Save the government's f******
Kurupt kurupt and everybody goes
Incorruptible in 20 years later you're like
Let's overthrow the government and it's like
Because they're working for the devil
Real sweet spot pre 9/11 but
Post
2000 election
So much
Que hacen alienation in people
The results of the 2000 election
Turn was such
A
Awful
I mean he was literally stolen
It was a moment
Where scales fell from people's eyes
Waterways
Across the aisle
Perhaps even this is the way that our process is going through this
This doesn't feel right Ru telling me that process
Has been derailed by
Fake Republic by Republica
Can a fake dressing up as business people
What are we doing this our government is this how it works
Yeah
You had you had that.
Before 9/11 where people were all over the map
In terms of
Their beliefs
About
The administration
Totally people galvanized a lot after 9/11
Coming together
After a national tragedy
Forever
Dennis exist
In that space before that
Where there is
You know there's a lot of fertile ground for Alex to take advantage of
In political disillusioned
Yeah
And so I think
No
You know I'm Fortune
Smelly butt
I don't think he knows too much about Alex
And just thinks that he is kind of like an alternative news guy
Yeah and
He eat he says things like
You know Outlets like yours are in Port
Right I think that that is a perception that even
You know I certainly wish I had more of a feeling of
4 years ago
Cuz I you know there is there is a
There's a reality that
People who are outside of the
The structures of advertising
Those voices are important
And sometimes
There is value in somebody
Who's
You know
Maybe wrong sometimes but willing to take a chance
I think those voices are valuable in the broads
Spectrum of
Of
Media
Totally I mean
Chomsky's earlier point
Like if you recalled the media immediately following that stolen election
Like they
Quickly were like a you know what we need to do tonight around our President we need the country to come together
At no point in time where they like hey we can't have a stolen election
Can't
Be a thing
Yeah yeah and I guess that opens up another conversation of like
What would it look like
If the media had called out the Killer
Leaving that aside
I think the chompski has a similar tack
You know what I had
Perhaps before I knew as much about Alex's I do and I think a lot of people if they don't know all that much about him which is just like
Euro
Guy who's
It was on the outside your guy or are you bringing me and Grover whatever maybe I don't know
Free with you but there's value in you existing in the media Llano game
And I don't agree with that now that he's engaging with him
Radios can be very
Instrument
There can be
Involvement
Highly important educational instrument of their others I mean
Nothing that I mention
Newest Logan and say okay that's what I
That's essentially Alec
Responding
To know times you think you can't use sound bites
And catch phrases with
More less and a catchphrase yeah
Man
So you're telling me that
Noam Chomsky
Told Alex Jones that he's important
And Noam Chomsky won't even talk
That's just bulshit it just b******* it's unfair
Noam Chomsky I'm calling you out
But again again
If you don't know that much about Alex you don't actually list
Some to his show and I said I don't know too much about
Exactly what you would like
Making 2001
You see there's another area residents career to if you don't know all that much about him
You could get the sense that like
Yeah
You're not doing
You are getting into the issue is the value of radio I do agree with Chomsky on that
Not Alex
Get along pretty well they both seem to hate
Consumerism
$50
Nike tennis shoes that are so ugly I wouldn't
For free
My grandchildren
I went there
Subjected to is
Teaching them from infancy that the only thing in life
Getting those
Tennis shoes
Or whatever maybe
People winner in a variable
It's a hard struggle
Consumerism is a toxic influence
I don't know what what's the answer to it it's an individual process
It can't be like outlawing adver
Advertises know that probably won't work
I would say one solution would obviously be to scorched
The skies and have an AI keep us inside of
That would be
Lucian certainly
Although even then the AI has propaganda inside of its side
Me and you're never going to escape
No don't let the only way
This is productive as a conversation
Is addressing
It has an individualistic
Pursuit recognizing when
Those kind of advertising
Checks are being used
Right I don't actually want that as much as
I am saying I want it or maybe I do
Sure you know like advertising I think they'd sometimes
Is
Dumb
But I actually do want with being sold
I don't like Taco Bell commercials but I
I do want Taco Bell. All I want is
Like I'm so stoked when I find out something exists that I didn't know exist like commercials were just
Hey
You need to wash your clothes tide I'd be like all these yet I didn't know tide was out there
Yes you did that's not the point
That's not the point I mean that experience was exactly what I had at the beginning of April when I saw the commercial for Mortal Kombat
Dad will watch Mortal Kombat commercial is not going to convince me one way or another you're informing me that the
That's all I needed to know ya
But I think I think that people can do that be very capable of doing
And I think that that is what the message
The chomsky's bringing in many ways is thinking is
Is recognizing
And being able to work around these things
Can't really stop them
And the fact that you can't stop them
Is what feeds into helper
You can't
Get rid of advertising
You're not going to get rid of
Public relations firm
That isn't going
Going to happen
Because I'm even think about it just from a structural
Actual perspect
How would that happen
How could you do that
Legislate away
Those kinds of
It would be impossible.
Turn all the electricity
Sure then people would just make pants
Once again I couldn't do it without
Electricity to run their printer
No they just go back to the the old chunk
Get rid of it get rid of press
Get rid of ink get rid of ink
Wow you're good
I think the path away from
Helplessness
That I'm hearing
Is
Self-motivated self-driven
Ways that intellectuals and public speakers can be of help
Is helping people recognized
That is a path
This conundrum
As opposed to
Institution
Things you can do like perhaps
Breakup large media entities
Certainly there's
There's this organization and things you can do
On that front
But
The idea of
Getting rid of
Influence that is this negative consumerism
He's not like
No that's that is a yeah it's not going back in the box
Pandora
This makes Cooper's really weird
I don't understand exactly what Alex is saying but I have some
Some thoughts on
At 1
Crucial part of
Is to take
Circle service
I'm handing over to private
Power
Services are
People with
Health education
Water
A man unlike any other
Put into private hands unaccountable private hands
What's left for the public is
What is private
Take a lower Colorado River Authority here in Texas
CR record
That's right
I think they would Alex is talking about is the the lower Colorado River Authority
Is is like you know like damn
Yeah like
Lecture
Power plant
Regards
Around the area
Private security
But
What were Trump's key bringing up
Is privatization
Accentuate
And Alex has opposed to that but he also hates big government
Where is chomsky's answer to this is
Is public ownership
An hour to be staunchly opposed to the bat
He doesn't Publix Lyon Abyss
He doesn't have
A coherent answer to this
Because on the one hand
You have public
Business
This is our private business is
Should you allow private
Business
Referred necessities
Should you allow air to be privatized would you allow water to
To be privatized
Alex should be
Opposed to that but also opposed to the alternative
Alex has a clear way out of his b*******
Whenever cornered by
Noam Chomsky
So what you do is you awake
And Alex tries to bring up
The difference between a democracy and a republic
This is opal classic right wing
Between a democracy and a
Republic
Gnome
Can I read that
What's the name again
Noam Chomsky all that's who I would do it
I wouldn't know that other guy
It doesn't go well and I would say this is the turning point
Of the interview
This is where things go we're on thin ice
Republicans Democrats saying democracy that's a semantical.
Is horrible it's two wolves
Tennessee voting on what's for dinner
A republic
Bill of Rights
You can't violate
Democracy
50%
Take that far
Right there I mean
We hear this work democracy all the time but we're Republican there's a big difference
Actually I
Surreal
Elsewhere
Republic
Democracy
Not really
Founding fathers what they were concerned about James Madison
But he was concerned about Buddy wanted to have a
In which power would lie in the hands of
But he called the wealth of
The more capable
Because the goal of government
This phrase
Protect the minority of the opulent
To ensure
Cruel
I'm at the general public would be fragmented and marginalized
Middle class
Flourish
Spell that's
Now that's not coming
So Alex is having trouble now because gnome has pointed a finger at the
Founders
Yasso
Call Alex robots that a middle-class flourish
Tear
And
Because of right-wing policies
I have evidence of it is that
4% of the population of the world and we had half of the well
Yeah right
I think jobs he doesn't
Understand what he said
Cuz he's at 4% isn't the middle class
If he heard Alex and 4% of our population had half of the wealth
Then that would be the response
That would be given
Yeah I still think even if you'd accurately heard what Alex said
I still think it what are you saying is accurate
That the 4% that had all the wealth wasn't necessarily the middle class
May I ask they were very much nothing middle-class on account of there were only
4% of 3
4% is 4% of the world
World's population
Oh yeah yeah
So you leave the 4% beside
Even if we did have half the wealth it wasn't like evenly distributed
Among
The population
There may have been a fairly comfortable
Middle class
Yeah I would argue the slave
Population
Probably wasn't
And taken care of
Yeah
So this
Issue with the founding father
Is the
Beginning of
What is going to become a tear in the fabric of French
Sure
We have
This
Conversation
Italians are going to guns
Cuz of course
Almost immediately
Over the centuries
The options Republic
That's not what they meant
Second Amendment
Open contacts
Bear arms
We're living in a different world racing malicious
Are the question whether people should have arms is a
International Society
No did you just say
No
Neighbors
Gnome you have hit a very dangerous but me and you can't undo this now you have just told Alex
His interpretation of the Second Amendment is wrong new world
New world
Ono turns out
Noam Chomsky the shell
The United States has
Spectre movie
International Society
Do you think people are hopeful you helpful that folks going to wake up
People
Again
That what they feel is help
To be able to overcome that feeling as hell
People have organized they have struggle
David Chief rights we have all kinds of Rights
Exist
Not long ago
MSB cursive
Learn
Educate
Change the world
We're very privileged we live in a society where
Penalty for not controlled by force
Extremely important
Honestly and I really appreciate coming along to tell folks about some your Publications and let you get back to work
Right there it seemed like a groupthink
Mechanism
I think America the US has no author from
Get out of the main line
The rest of the world
As if I were little
Zoe's
Alex is trying to express this notion that
Are you trying to shame America about guns based on the
Notion that the rest of the world is
Is more civilized they don't have guns
Is
Out at this is just
Galaxy is decided that if you
Present that kind of position on his show
Your f****** s***
Alex throws out
Literally
A great degree of agreement
Oh yeah I know it's all gone
What could have led to a second interview probably could have led to
I mean eventually would fall apart
There wasn't hostility here there was someone who has a different
Perspective on some of the similar themes
That Alex talks about
No I I mean with the moments
Gnome said we live in a
Country where you can't
Control people by force
All I saw in my head was Alex
Pulling a gun and saying
You take that back
Guns are not about Force there by politeness
So
I even that
Groupthink
Even though
Trump is pretty generous in
And measured with his response
True but if you want my opinion
Took all the guns
Hickory high crime
It's been
Real difference between the United
So it seems like
Chomsky
Just ignoring
Alex's
Obviously misrepresented stats
No and he's framing
The conversation where he believes
Is it more important
Witches dance
Scott Gunn.
Which is
Out of pace
Swift other industrialized countries
Alex
The come at him with that b*******
Doesn't seem like Adele
He might be the first ones might be the first person who comes with this though
Country
Australia number one and two now
10 deaths by gun
Yes now they are
London is now more dangerous
4 years ago
It's now
Eyeworks in Washington d.c. sir
I have University
Salon
Infowars.com
Take a look
The reason is
That there has been an increased availability
Availability
You're right
Sir
A always have fun
In England
Even the police
We're not armed
The police didn't have guns the people have handguns
That's a different story
That is a we're done here
Your publication
If there's more availability of guns
I see I think that there's a really not
Not bizarre at all very
4 into Infowars situation
I'm going on where he's talking to a person
Who is is
Saying
That they were talking about glitches
Deaths by gun
Alex's fudging
Statistics
Making stuff up
You brought up a different issue I'm going to have to let you go
Monkeys doing
Is being overly charity
He's not saying Alex you're a f****** liar
Filmmaking
Stop up you think I would need to take a look at that
If that is
The case here is a potential explanation for why that could be the case
And then Alex is taking them
Pental explanation
The chompski has 4/8
Fictitious stats
Explanation for his fictitious I think I would have said something along the lines of if
Australia are one and two in gun deaths I will eat a bowl of my own s*** you idiot
I will take that back
He's doing the Firearms Amendment Act of 1997
Not in England with your past
In response to the dunblane massacre where a man in his forties carried out a mass shooting at a primary school
The strategy employed was not to confiscate guns but to ban future ownership of mos
Ghost guns
And let the valid licenses that were active laps and not be renewed
In response a ton of people voluntarily turned in their guns and Alex's pretending that's account
Station
It did make more guns illegal to own
It's a pretty strict rules about guns
In England predata
He's not far off
No it's it
Alex could get him on a technicality
If you saying that all guns
I've always been a legal right
Roller or whatever but spiritually he's he's not
He's not off
No
Now
That
Hasn't happened
Alex
Besides
I think I'm going to hang up on this day
Really appreciate you just say this one big part of controlling
Their system
Is having people out there
Propaganda
And frankly sir you need to get the information on the guns on the land grabbing all of it because I have it
Lightyear
And I respect your work
I just hear talk
Certainly is
How did Rockefeller for me
Wow
What a dick
Sweet dick
Now
I've bizarre and to this
Interview
Excuse me for about an hour but it turns out that you disagree with me on gun so
You work for David Rockefeller do you lying piece of s*** I hope you die I hope you die
Click that I think is really admirable is
A response to that like
Figure that out
I'm not getting gauge with your
Attempt to get you to fight with you or whatever
Exactly I like that
Excuse me Alex
You realize I'm gnome Trump
Didn't even go up at all
Nope
I think I figure controlled opposition in a real dick
Little Liar well I understand your point of view I think people will be smart enough
To look into it and
The difference here
And Noam Chomsky
You're wrong button
You're busted
So now that he's gone
Now we got to talk
Oh yeah oh yeah
Chomsky ladies and gentlemen and I read his books and now I'm more sure than ever
Inside down the other
Play motor Tinley
I mean how many
I mean you've seen the video
Problem cutting the guns and half over there, skating the handguns or rifles
Three years ago we've read the reports The Economist WorldNetDaily
Yasemin is just speak freely once he's gone
I've read his book
Now I know for sure
No idea to get him in there
And then find something to disagree with
And then declare him a shelf it has to have been because he has to like
If it is what I was saying is Trudy's read books
And suspected that he wasn't in wotl
I have to be like I'm just looking for a point of disagreement in order to make you an anime
That's not that's not cool
Suggested that when he was talking about one of the books that you supposed
Simply Red
Would be the time to say that
Hey I think
Yeah I don't like your position on Auntie, exactly
I love my favorite
People are the anti-communist as hell
Yeah
Dumb
I thought that this
Was really strange
Alex
I don't
I don't know what he was doing
I'm completely perplexed
There's so much Abreva
Yeah
Now I would have to give up a lot of the turtle more fun elements of his
Conspiratorial
Nonsense
If you were to
Continue engaging with John
Because that stuff would fall apart
A lot of it would in some of the
The more real
Sort of dynamic
Make the chop speaker bring to
To the table
Are not necessarily as
Exciting or lucrative
Maybe there isn't value
In it for Alex to be an ally of John Prine
No I'm making hard for me to imagine that he did this interview as a trap in order to create this moment at the end
Yeah
It just doesn't make sense now
It really doesn't
It also doesn't
Feel angry enough for it to be like a visceral
Response on Alex's part where you just like
F*** it I'm just mad at this guy
I mean it kind of feels like
If if I were running
Here would be my
Kind of game plan there which is
If
You and Noam Chomsky have an awesome interview
Then you get to say no Chomsky is a
Fan of yours
And that legitimate
Is you
To a lot of people it would help Alex's arguments of going to being above the left right but
If you get into a fight with Noam Chomsky
You got into a fight
With no f***
People will be like hell yeah
Who's in this scenario I do that I do think that
The
Extreme right
Elements
About this audio
Which is certainly
More of the
The Keystone of it
I'm sure then
Then anything
Would not like the idea of being
Friends with no job
Totally
I honestly I've listened to this interview a couple times and I don't really know exactly what happened
I'm not sure
It makes no sense to me
There's a decent chance that we saw there with him
Being like sir you know I believe that this is a group thinking you know I think that you're not being as honest
Maybe that's
2001 angry Alex
Could be
You know like maybe we're just judging it based on the bombastic performances of gas that maybe
Maybe that's how he wasn't angry dick back then
How many years did he been doing this not long
Mediocre at comedy for 7 years
So you can imagine it him being
You know right out the gate the bombastic
Disgusting human being that we expect today
Antabuse
Globalist and hot tubs of snowflake
Created
The character that is
Yeah I don't know anyway
Really
You're a new world order shell
Both arms tied behind my back
Make sense
It makes me want to puke
I might not have been the
Right thing for him to mock
Yeah they
Only human
So they definitely wanted to protect
Owning human
Yeah
I think that
If you take anything away from this date
It's Alex's
Contention
And that he has more brains with both hands tied behind his back
Banned completely meaningless Bragg
Really it really couldn't get
More obviously incongruous for someone to say look how smart I am
I'm going to use a cliche that could not less apply to the very thing that I'm saying I'm
Yeah I think that really kind of sums it up
Strategically it even
Thumbs up
What would I look at
There are very few times that I take
You know I look
Look at something that happened at Alex's past
And I'm just
Completely flummoxed
Staff and I really don't know
Why this happen
No
It's confusing
I don't know
I don't think I have any answers I would like
Text know how the booker got
Nope
Or people are more gettable than we think
That's probably
I think that a lot of folks that you might want to talk to
It would just be a matter of a couple email
Yeah I mean considering
How much free time I could make
At the drop of a hat in public intellectuals are in a very similar maybe a little bit the last for your time
The Paragon everytime Jordan
Yeah I think
I think about how it differently history could have gone if
Alex and no became Buddies
And instead of Steve pieczenik
You're not going to make it as many big swings from nowakowski
I believe you're just not do you came into the fold in 2000
This is 2,000 we got to get a new number
If the infinite universes is real
There is a universe is Multiverse Theory
Where is Steve pieczenik is played by
The Alex Jones Show
How does that go do you think Noam Chomsky gets crazier Alex
Gets less crazy
I mean if you go
Solely based on this interview
Sure I think I was
Skip less crazy
Because to be Trump deceived immovable
He's got a 120 over 80 all day
He does not see
Seem to care too much is willing
To loosen a position
And clarify things
Well just got some pics without
And I think
I think that that would
You disappear before he got crazy or be covered
I think Alec
Text believes that he is the wave
That could wear away The Rock
But instead in
Noam Chomsky
And to be honest I think Steve was crazy when he showed up
I think I was just making more crazy
Crazy when he was working
Probably
When he killed Aldo Moro
Thinks he killed although Mara
Keep did he kill Elsa
Extra
So anyway
We will be back
This is been a long overdue
Checking this box off
And I wish to bring to a but I honestly don't I think it's just an interesting Glen
Public intellectual interspec
Having a conversation with Alex
Text Babe
That it steps on a number of commonalities between
Where
Certain critical historical
Study overlaps with
Do you know
Pseudo conspiracy
Right you know and and where there is
Distinction where there's a Parcher
And I think you also get a really solid glimpse
Of even in 2001 Alex is so sensitive about gone totally the only things that really
Play means anything to him
Yeah
I mean
What is
Everybody danger to a certain extent
You know
Babe so many men treat guns as an extension of
Masculinity so
Maybe that's even more like at
At the deepest level it's just
Toxic Mass
Masculinity property rights
Could be a symbol of
The idea of
Personal private property
I'm sure I don't know
But it's it's it's strange
It's strange that he had to make a fight out of
Essentially
A decent point
Yep yep
Jordan
We are also on
We are go to bed
Drawer
World would you like to download the show please go to iTunes and if you could please
Find a local charity or bail Fund in your area
That'll help out people
Until then
And now here comes
What the sex robot
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color
I love you