Alexandra Thurston color
Quite a bit
You forced me into it I did watch a lot of
Seems like a stretch I need to bring you in
To the real world
Hot today Jordan you were brought in 1893 from the makers
Pepsi-Cola three all over again ladies and gentlemen
Blackcurrant
By the way I want to point out this is fair trade certified
They're definitely not lying to the faceless shadowy Corporation would
That is okay
I think it's a
It smelt air
Just okay
Hey is what I'm getting at
So here is the deal beyond the soda
Last weekend
We recorded our part our fifth installment of the investigation into what happened
Alex Jones
In 2015
That led him to support Trump
I would love to say that I listen
Unfortunately I didn't
Game show called
Here is the deal
Yeah
Supported by
Computer crashed
It's gone
For us
Dude Ryan remake the episode
Fake
Fake isn't Alex Jones
To make the same points
I feel so shity
So I don't want to do that
It would be fun though if my part was
Just played by a recording of be saying
That would be the nice wrinkle
So the next time I will be the Jordan feeling
Squawk Box
Pictures of very liberal Squawk Box is a little angry
Little
Batters I have been going to doctors all this week and I've been
Real busy
Yes so I've been just super busy trying to take care of that really preoccupied
Take me a little bit out of the game
On our way
Which is
Delightful I'm still betting on
Spider eggs
That's what that's my bet don't.
We pop
It's an urban legend.
Everything is okay with
There's no worry in the ass for me
Atropine
Yeah you shaved into a
Just f***
Fantastic. It's ridiculous
Old Prospector levels
It's the next level of don't talk to me
Number train
We'll be going over
The period of July 22nd
To August 10th
Which was the original time frame of
Are our fifth part of Art
Investigation
Much more heavily on August 10th cuz we didn't really cover that all that well in the original version
And there's a lot more to discuss there and it will actually be fresh
It only feels right that we actually
Hit some of the important point
From that time frame
So the first like half an hour
40 minutes of this episode
Might sound
False on our Park
Fair
Yeah
So we all go there
So we start on July 22nd
And one of the most important things
We want to remind everybody is that Alex
Still very fool
By the Planned Parenthood videos
The game out from the center
Upper medical progress
He is just
Hook Line & Sinker it feeds into his narrative he loves it
Unfortunately they are deemed frauds
Jail time is coming
Jail time
Everybody in Congress
It launched investigations
Found Planned Parenthood
But
As an excuse
6 M play a
Absolutely and now all the negative repercussions
Still coming
In fairness it's not like this video was the first thing ever to
Just me or Planned Parenthood for a long time
Yats guy
Taking over
Anemone
Was in the top smartest people in Texas High School
When he was 16
Until I was like four years old
Ubiquitous
Almost join this call
Told me about it
So Alex Jones is Dad almost became a globalist
Also you were screaming smartest person in Texas
I feel like this
Smartest person
In the world becoming a dentist
Especially
Is the the
F****** father of a mans
The creator of this
How hard Alex videos knowing what we know now
It's hilarious
My discernment to so right
I'm still on the ball about everything I can't lie even when I try
They will prove it
New Evansville come to life
Where is let's try and figure out some new evidence on those videos that might work
Okay
That's going to be tough
Is it like the five minutes of the Knicks
Sensor thing
The government
Oh oh no I see this is the
Exactly
Okay
Sapote
The Planned Parenthood Liars
Planned Parenthood
The globalist
Kenalog
So now what this is like
Videos
Center for Medical progress and there was the actual version came out
Planned Parenthood
Videos
Completely full of s***
To haggle for money
Even though all those committees
Exonerate
Planned Parenthood
Controlled opposition undoubtedly
Center for Medical progress
Alex Jones
Which
He has been
6 months
He will be proven correct
I like
Your confidence
I like the
Also part of the
Is it John Glenn isn't dead
Pets in during covid
Conspiracy theory
What about John Glenn
Number to walk on the moon dies first
Just got to go down
Strewth
We've got here the purpose of our investigation is of course
To figure out
Alex's
Mentality changed about drum
So it's important to every time
There comes up we got to discuss
Where his head was
About Trump
On our last episode
The mentality that
I don't trust
This guy
I'm going to
Stop talking s***
I'm going to stop talk about how he's mobbed-up
And all that
I'm going to let this man to the bigoted
Yeah
I love seeing my bigotry on a
National schedule but I don't trust him
He's probably lying about how much Haiti has
Big like movie over
That's really what it was
Yeah he wants his ideas put out like
Like if in the movie Armageddon
Instead of it being
The
Asteroid
It is the government's
And black people
Who made the
Sure
That's what he want
You know
You got to go mine or something I'm not sure
So in this next clip Alex lays out where his head is at about Trump
On July 22nd
It's pretty heroic
Really really smart
He said that because he was the leader
And Trump
Trump
Uncool
He's super smart he knows exactly what he's doing
And so just watch
On purpose
Knows all about
Trump
The he's talking about
Comments that Trump made about McCain
Because he knows he has to
Trying to ruin the Republic
Zach bush
Can get in there
You know
I think a lot of people were saying that then
I didn't go as pretty much I think
Was probably saying that back.
Just like fuk I need money
This is a great way to get
People to buy my shoe
A much attention
Impossible
Whatever everybody realizes
I'm a f******
Who is nuts
Who is
Who is Justin old bigot who watches too much Fox News
They'll be like
We can't have you
UB president
Can I get to go away
That's great
Literally everyone would have 1000 Alex is like I don't know
All these planes Maybe
I like titties on that tip
In the big picture
Small picture with monsters
Is getting pleasure women at the Hanoi Hilton
Another big lie about the wrong direction
McKay brings us to our next clip
He's trying to explain that Alex
John McCain
Is trying to make it illegal
Hi to sell vitamins without getting
Prescriptions were people
Because the end of this call is f****** hilarious
In order to buy a simple bottle of vitamins
He wants you to
Be required to get a doctor's prescription
To buy a simple bottle of vitamins
Yet you and I being adults can walk into any store in the country and buy a gun
Without a doctor's Blank gun
Dr. Kennedy
Was a correspondent
Yes
Shake Shack
You're the type of guy
Alex I'm old-school I'm 69 years old so I was one of those guys you grew up without the internet
But I have unlimited local and long-distance
So I can like so smart
So you've got to admit he has a house phone
Hilarious
I love your idea of of Alex actually sending out people to be like
Hey
We want you to go talk at the
This random things like dude I'm a f****** retired Old Man Without a landline
Smart
Fun facts on August 10th
Oh did you get hired
Nobody
Alex does not even seem to realize it's the same guy
New favorite character on the show
Those are credible dude from Wyoming
There's no denying
60 year old conspiracy theorist in the middle of Wyoming with the house phone
He's old-school that doesn't know about the internet
Well they don't actually have
I've been reading about the globalist in magazines
I don't have the internet
Why can't read blogs that are full of s***
I still open the yellow papers
So I would probably want you to
Get your information
From blogs
Have you he wants you to
Look into the globalist
Level
Stuck clip
He had some things to say about vax
I meant he misrepresents
Tucson knowledge base
A convulsion in the car
And then I never talked again that I warned you and it wasn't funny
I don't know what's going on but there was one
Eman one-in-five
And then one-in-three Honcho
Throwing feces up against the wall
And then no one's asking what's going on why is this happening
Written 40 years ago
41 years ago now in 1974
So I hear what you
What do you mean everyone was
Like that what's the ending to that plan
Everything okay
So damaged and destroyed by vaccine
Which
Yes
They are throwing feces at the wall but that is not diarrhea caused by polio
It's a mixed bag of frozen frozen come
They are
Absolutely
From the flu
But
Most of the population
Damn
So if you're ugly
The grocery store
The robots are coming
Oh that's a good point Terminator Okay
Globalist
Work with robot
I suppose though I mean
The idea
There I guess would have to be in a profound welfare states
Yeah that's what the global is really want they just want to take care of people
We want people who are incapable of beating themselves
I could be your items you might have cracked the code
Something really quick
These statistics about people who are diagnosed
Misleading
Because you know 34 years ago
People who would have been diagnosed
Nowadays as I would have been
Call the tard
Yeah we're whatever locked in a room
Boys weird evolved approach towards a lot of mental illness
Even
Then the sixties or seventies
Psychiatric medicine
The 1800 was just a guy going around f****** up your brain with a knife
Yeah
Basalt lobotomy
These would solve problem
Totally
But that was a lot longer than we think.
The idea
People who have autism
He's probably not true
The numbers might be going up slightly but
The numbers
Jim
Like massively higher if they even alright I don't know
Reliable statistics on it
But even if that is the case it is
Dropped an evolution in diagnosis
Not in the actual
You know a lot more
People are diagnosed
With
With tuberculosis
Now as opposed to back
When it was just go
Write the rise and diagnosis of tuberculosis
Yeah
Also
Feed the fun thing the reason why I desperately need to keep this clip-in is because I like to document every time
Alex Jones references one of his primary sources about global
Yes because it's important
All of those
Yeah because there's two
This one's Ehrlich right this one is John holdren
Annie
Alex Wolff
To give credit
She was the one who put
Also sprach
Zarathustra in front of
Ric Flair's entrance
Yeah
Paul Ehrlich
Annie erlich wrote a textbook
Call ecoscience
Population resources Environmental
Ideas
That the globalists are trying to put something in the water
To decreased population
It's 1,000 page
Buck
About
About resource manage
Populations
IND application
Everyone just
Miss quotes
Out of context
They are
Alex
Super guilty
Here is the
Here is the section that Alex takes his beliefs
About
Globalist want
To put things
In your food in order to make you
Infertile
I suppose
Quote
The third approach to population limitation is that of involuntary fertility
Control
Several courses proposal deserve discussion
Mainly because some country
Ultimately have to resort to them unless current trends and birth rates
Are rapidly reversed by other means
Adding a Sterilite to drinking water or staple food is a suggestion that seems to horrify
People more than most proposals for involuntary fertility
Control
This would pose a very difficult
Political legal and social question
Not to say anything of the text
Ankle problems
Exist today to be under develop
To be acceptable such a substance would have to meet some rather stiff require
Hey must be uniformly effective
Despite widely varying doses received by individual
And despite varying degrees of
Fertility and sensitivity
They must be free of dangerous or
And must have no effect on members of the opposite
Sex children old people
Or livestock
Fret
I don't need to be made of
And I don't believe that there would be something
Do like a uniform substance that would work on men and women
So you just have things that would make you
Like women infertile and then
Or vice versa
Easier to make every man
Yeah
Maybe
Forced sterilization
When would be the
Like if you are convicted of a violin
Crime
Virginia most racist thing that would ever happen
That would go, really
Suggested like that have been made and shot down for
Personal reasons
It is goes on again there's no sign of such an agent on the horizon
And the risk of serious unforeseen side-effects
Mitigate
Against the use of any such a gem
Even though this plan has the advantage of avoiding the need
A socio-economic
To discriminate against
Particular group
Or penalized children
Which is exactly what you were just talking to
Brett how in the past they have forced sterilization on
Criminals
As we all know
That's not a good way to do
So I guess I've never seen
They are making
Incredibly clear that this is not a good proposal there are logistical problems
There are moral problems
That it's not
It's not going to work
So they can cook
The globalist worry about putting
Something in the water
With climate
Caboodle
Turn on people when
Drink
You can just have your armored redoubt
On the top of the hill or something I don't know
Keep all your robots
Andy
People pay your poop thrown exactly
Most of the population control measures Beyond Family Planning
Disgusted
Summer is
Impossible in others are and probably will remain on acceptable to most Society
Although of course
Maybe great
So they can possibly be incredibly effective
But it's impossible
Would never be cool with it
It's not a reasonable suggestion
No that would be some serious Global s*** if you pulled that discussing it because it's a textbook
It covers all of it
For educational purposes
There's other techniques that are that are shown such as family
The
Even in this next
Paragraphs
Compulsory control of family sizes
Is an unpalatable idea
But the alternative may be much more horrifying
Has become clear to an increasing number of people in the 80s
They may begin demanding such
Control
A far better choice in our view
History expand the use of milder methods
Of influence
Family size preferences
While redoubling efforts to
I'm sure that the means of birth control
Including abortion
Sterilization
Are accessible to every human being on Earth
Within the shortest possible time
If effective action is taken properly against population growth
Involuntary or repressed
Measures can be averted in most come
I think the issue
She comes down to the fact
That
They're writing it
They're like it
Text
We're presenting this idea
And then we're shooting it down
To educate
So you know
Do that ID
Yeah
But they don't do that Riley like here is what we could do
Is why we shouldn't
Will do
Just put in there like
Here's what's going on
It's f****** stupid
Well on an assumption that your listeners are an idiot
And they assume the people are going to understand
When educational Tech
It should cover all angles
So you learn about the
Alex Jones
It would be possible to
I have compulsory abortions
Under the current constitution
Population growth
To get out of
Control
Be an actual crisis
Such a way that it would be legal
Would wind up being
The most racist thing that could
Could ever f***
To get rid of total desirable Congress whenever that was allowed
F***
We would lose generation
Not white
Statement of
This would theoretically be possible under our law
Forcing people to get abortion
Is not Africa
Like again
If they had like a little like
Hey
We should make a log
Perfect
Yeah come out and advocate
Paperhouse
Presented
In education
Which is a dumb idea
You know once people started spinning these
John holdren put out
Statement
Another book that describe different possible approach
Just a limited population
And then concluded that the author's own private
Prince was the employee non-coercive measures
Before the Environmental
And social aspects
Have overpopulation
Please do employee course at 1
Doctor Who
Has never been an advocate of
Compulsory abortion
Or other repressive means of population limit a
Further
Came out and said we have
At the serious mischaracterization of Art
And those of John
Based on a misreading of our jointly authored
1977 book
Textbook ecos
We are not then
Never have been
Of the Cronin measures
4 population limitation described but not recommended
In the books
60 + multi pages
How long is a full spec
Population policy
Have you ever been tried in some country or analyzed
But they're making
Clear right now
Make it clear way easier
Like a normal person
Fair enough
A f******
Course we don't think this is a good idea
Exactly
Statement come on assholes final like big
Suck on my balls you f****** idiots kind of
Havre de Grace
This is a problem
With us we're not
True
This is the new system
This is Matt
No nothing just besides
Put out the sides
Twitter is today it hasn't worked out well so far
Lot of hype man on the other side too
You know why
They speak
Sure
Argument
About
Bruzdzinski I have
What series problems with based on
And I'm not saying what Alex says
And now further
His argument that people are trying to put
Things in the water
To sterilize you
It's gone completely Shaky Ground that's not what this textbook
Was talking about at all
OmniSource
He's straight
Fuct
That is that is no good
So anytime you brings up that stuff just know that a lot of it
When pressed
To give a citation
This is what he do
And it doesn't say what he thinks he says
So
Great
I love it
How do I spell angry
Episode I know you're very bad
It doesn't feel weird to me
Listening to know Alex
Really surprised
We're going to get back this is the next
2 about an hour of the show is taken up by
Coming on the show chiropractor
I caught out that whole thing Alex Jones came out his
Trans-species
Cuz he's a dog
He wants to identify as a dog
Navigate to
You have trans argument
Endo
Can I retract my argument dog
And videotape
Making a transphobic argument
I wish I had.
I'll post it up there
Elementary
Preschool age
Daughters
Videotape in Macon
Video where he claims
Empty was identifying as a dog
And one of them dress up in a gorilla suit in studio further
Spell out the joke
Which is not a joke
It's just bigot
You made a child
That's Heavy
This is why
Dr. group
Did an hour
Body cleanse is going on in the group family of products
And
I don't give a f*** about listening to sell his product
Very important things came out about doctor groups
And Alex Jones's life
That the audience
Deserves to know about
First one
Is about dr. group
Their historic they usually live longer than I mean historically women live
Resilient
My mom actually was shot 6 times point-blank range in the head with a 22 rifle
And she survived
She survived that
That's bad radio
Tell me more about that
Going to the point where that sounds like
Fascinating
Mystic story
Well there's that but then also if Alex was to unpack that story
The most likely thing is his dad shot his six times
OSHA
If you use the technical analysis
He's making up for his evil father's crime
Yeah it's
Doctor group backstory
To toxic things
Veterans
Evils of his father
Yes absolutely
Instead of weather stuff it's
Chemical manipulation of human
B y group
Makes the cleanse
It could be whether it was
The dad that shot the mom
The story it's guns
Yeah and he doesn't want to talk
Those Second Amendment doesn't want to say it hear any stories
Ever that be great radio
It's not man. That goes against my gun narrative
You know what that could be
Could be
Should Alex Jones is brain damn
And this next clip
Is Alex Jones
Mites
They might not be well
And I had I think we already know that
I know but we're just building evidence up
I want to move on to
She just slowly
He's in the fog
I just need to clarify
You know what when we get this first time I forgot to do this second time forgot to clarify again
They just taking a call from a guy who was like a bug
Control person
Killer
How do you spell
Some chemicals on himself
I'm so doctor group is telling him to take
One time
The Army after 35 years
He's an older cousin
There were a few times where
Father cousin
And they were
Stop
I don't work with them
Topsail jobs
Experience
Remember going under houses with I'm spraying
How's it going
Hi at the Dairy Queen eating a hamburger
It was just so clear
Yes that's exactly what's happening and that's why we're here giving out solution
If you were a real doctor Yu-Gi-Oh
Oh my God
Children's brains are very serious damage by
Being stuck under a house with dangerous chemicals
I'm surprised that Alex Jone isn't isn't in a room somewhere throwing is on
Do you might just
Be competent for like 4 hours a day
Is a coiled spring and what
It could be
We've cut out a bunch of other stuff that we eat
Discussed on the first episode
That we lost
Doesn't really need to be discussed I'll break some of it down
Alex Jones has a bunch of racist
He whitewashes the history of Oklahoma City
This fast
Whitewash has Oklahoma City and Timothy McVeigh
And he cites as one of his sources
For the truth about Oklahoma City
Larry Nichols
Stevie Nicks
Like okay well that is not
Okay
You have invalidated your argument
Alex Jones revealed that what he lost for most in life
Is
Hollywood
Is that Bahama vacation
That we also
So using his millions and millions
Shipped on Friday July 24th
He spent two weeks in Europe
For two weeks
And I tried to throw
Alex
Reported that I was only able to find a few of them
And they were just him playing vacation videos on Infowars
It was hilarious him just being like
He's just out at some Grecian
Agora
And he's like
What's going on with the Greek economy
Get me some souvlaki
If Collins came from
I'm drunk
Dragon ouzo
These goblets columns
He claims that he's going
To Europe all over Europe
To get to the bottom of it he's going to go find out what's up
EXO
It's got to go find out why all the countries in Europe are failing
And like I said
He's reporting with his shirt off
Excuse not doing anything
Okay
There's just
No
There's just no
Equivalent to his elsewhere like now
Jackass
Maybe
Yeah
I guess so it is
Just wild
It's sort of hillbilly appeal
Don't care
Isn't lying
Well
Alex heard all of us
So he's on vacation to comes back to the studio on August
On August
The first Republican Presidential
Primary debate
This would be when
Yeah
Edith
You could at least
Pretend that we have
It's all right to left
Andaz
Invalidating the entire concept of this show
I feel like there's maybe a little more to the concept I think maybe People Like Us
I have never experienced
You're right but I just can't
Pierce the facade of affected
I mean I know people are listening but at the same time we're sitting at
Into each other
Hey Jordan shuttle know what's going to happen
You know I'm lying to you and I
Thingworx dad
You could be
This is your chance
Alright
Who knows what
Highbrow
Betrayed you immediately
You are no Daniel dad Lewis
Am I
Dwayne Johnson
The Rock
You're a better actress
Let's get to this next
August 10th
The first debate
Here is what he thinks about Trump
We are back
Thank you so much for joining us I will get the Donald Trump
Old MacDonald
Normally go
Malaysian Airline situation
He did
But also I just realized
He probably is using
Du jour
Some Europe
I did not get
Consider that I am considering it
No
Any really he really leaned into it to like a distraction
MLS
They were
Developments came out but the other medium
We covered it probably 1/100 of what they did
Because that was a pure distraction
What does it matter
The world
I told the media was running with nausea
Donald Trump
Because it's about the 2016 election
The future of this country and the rest of the world
And whether he's a shill whether he is for Real
The study example
Of how the media is handling this how they're spinning it
How people are responding tells you a lot
And I'll say this
Obviously falls on his sword
Ball on purpose
AR lowers is finished
How do you make
And there will be
Evans chickens come home to roost resuscitation
I don't believe that's true but I know you're using a metaphor Alex I'm going to let you outside
He said that
Alex
Sheetz
In court
Look at this.
Commit
Is being delish
You are so delusional that you think
Food
Is under the rule of law and
Look how about you
Do our ham sandwiches need to have less salt
Yes probably
This is a very Siri
That he knows him to be
You're wrong about everything
Mailed
You know like civil asset
Future and marijuana those two classic examples we have
There's a couple other things we started
Agreed with him in principle but disagreed with how he
He got to his
Conclusion
Always wrong
He's just
Almost always wrong
This is all the narratives that we seen
Coming out about Russia
A little bit later that you haven't heard that makes it all the more so I can
Scary
Cuz I think there is
Indication where he tips his hat
A little bit about knowing what the
The future holds
Have you ever discussed
Ghost
I think he has a premonition of what
Succumb
A little scary
Nailed it
Accident
He has more things he wants to say about you
Trump
What is he planning on the election
Wales
Donald Trump
Yirego
That Donald Trump was in conversations and consultation about
Republican
Something Bill Clinton and courage him to do
The clintons loving
You're so desperate
Somebody tell the truth about Pluto
Open borders
Ravens scores of other issues
Straight Talk
We're starving.
Swell
Immoral strong popular opposition
To social engineering
Viper s***
For sure we're going to find out about Donald Trump
Betrayed
Not that I don't like
Holyshit serious repercussions
The possible blackmail
And believe me
Donald Trump
So I just I just
It came to a realization almost simultaneous
Going by the proposition that he is correct
This one time
He's nailing it he's
All the sudden start speaking hard truth
Think of this
Already
We run is Republic
You and I
Huh
Okay and then we f****** turn on
We got two years where we can do all kinds of s***
True District
We can't wait
No we can't live in Illinois
Oh okay everybody
Correct in all things
We could definitely make a senate run but I don't think there's a vice
Probably better than strawberries I got a growth on my channel
Just for fun
But he's looking
Cuz he is assuming that the blackmail is coming from Hillary Clinton
And what he's not considering is that there might be other sources
Influence
Force between
So I'm not suggesting
Sara Lee the Trump
Has been blackmailed by Russians
Or the mob
But I am saying that
Alex
I think his assessment is pretty right on
Except he's not putting the
This together he knows that he's mob-connected
He knows that he works in
Casinos in his
The predator
Laundering
Russian money
He doesn't think that that is
That Clinton's
Know about
Can blackmail and because of that
As opposed to
To these mobsters
Bmike
We have our guy in the White House
We can
Run roughshod
Make so much money
Unequivocally
God
So I think Alex is right but he's blinded by his hatred of Hillary
And he's just
Dumbness
The globalist
And the idea that Democrats
Want to
For socialism to
To turn into communism to turn into totalitarianism
Just gone backwards
Skip the socialism
And just gone straight
From democracy
We thought it would be hard
I think Alex is missing the forest for
For the trees
I am anyways
Cuz he's so Focus
So focused on fake global
He doesn't see what's right in front of him
Could have been right
He could have been a hero
Alternate universe
Reveals the biggest story of all time
He knows about Trump
There would be nothing bigger than discovering
But you're
Has Infowars conspiracy theories website
That one conspiracy theory you at
Perfect
Conspiracy
Straight up
Play goddamn Alex Jones
Could go down in history
Woodward and Bernstein of racism
Make the caveat that that's not that great of a universe cuz then we have
Really arrogant
Okay
I mean he's never going to shut up about Sandy Hook now
Ivory
Great Scott's
As well
I want to check your calls on the Trump situation starting
I got some clips from the debates also have
That's true
Which of you judge Donald Trump
By most of his past activities
Supporter
And links it to autism
Something about Trump
So you know is this the how is that the wind
It's so weird that he's like all of these things like
He's he's bro
Is for abortion
Kids for immigration
But he's crazy about vaccines
Elective
Eat the bad thing is the thing that he looks
That's very bizarre
We should run as Republican
I think this recording might hurt us
And I still never find very very easy just
To take all of the dumb positions
Dunno resume
With Republicans
I am just run with them
I don't know
Who sings insane I think we would get killed
If we did that
If we ran on
Fringe positions that are
Just super crazy
Dyed-in-the-wool liberals lockup eyeballs
We still got some militia type would take
Yeah
Yet so Alex
How many supports Trump
They get to do it a little more easy
Dakota like
You know what I mean
I love Rand Paul
He says
Crazy things Trump says crazy things
I like making it okay to talk about
These crazy things
Even though
I know the
He loves the Clinton
Even though I know his history says that
Give
You know exactly what I would hate
Even though
Did my favorite politician Rand Paul says he's an a******
All of these
I got to give him a shot
Yeah
It's it's like recognizes like
Wants to be legislatively bigot
Trump wants
Yeah
That's why you get an hour
What do people do at the beginning
Alright
Be mostly about Trump
He doesn't have taking a bunch
Calls about Trump
But before he does he's got to get into pretty serious issue
That dovetails into a very racist
Proclamation
Black people are made of cheddar
So what do you think about Donald Trump
And then of course
I'm just going to say this everyday
Because now it's a season that folks actually care
I drove into
For twenty years
Also
This is the summer
He's about to happen does not mix
This is not weather related
It's not like a Christmas is coming up so we ought to bring up the culture War
What's what's going on
This is something I was informed on when I first got on air
Talkin all these experts hollykit
Your phone call
I've been focused on
Planning with brains and mice and pigs and cows and
Spiders
Jellyfishing
Probably earlier
Then they grow these humanoids
Artificial site
Okay
Stocks trading on this stuff
You're talking a bunch of kids
Give the public understands that they're selling baby parts
If they understand
Computer
Public to understand that's only the tip of the iceberg
It's admitted
The geoengineering
Iceberg
Everything
What else I don't know
Look
We promise
On the last episode
That we
On the Lost episode
Broken down
Some of these things so I want to run through some of it really quick
He talked about spider human
Yes is not real
That is based on a natural news.
About how there was a
Who realized
On a woman
Channeling out there
Great-great-aunt realized
That spider silk is incredibly
Strong and impenetrable
You could make a skin
Using fighter
She created a false
Skin
That
Might be possible to splice something
Things to make humans
Skin impenetrable
Bratz there's a theory she thought it was possible wasn't testing it
But
This blog naturalnews.com
That was
This is happening
And the interesting thing about that is naturalnews.com is run by Infowars employee Anthony
ERD
Naturalnews.com
Natural news
Nature
It seems like that's bad nature
Call
The only one
Zillow
Maybe
Armadillos are weird that I don't want to live in the desert I don't know the climates not good
How many bullets
I think I'm going to go
For my bulletproofing
Jellyfish
Absorb
They'll go right through me
I'll be fine and you in a bunch of friends
Could mold your bodies together and make a boat like jellyfish do
Sov
Don't know why that's funny but
Do it
Brains are not being put into mice
Unwraps that's important
If you look into it you can find articles about this there are some tasks
But have been done
Where in
Human stem cells
Into mice
In utero
Create some of the architecture of human brains within the mice
And the reason that they do this
Is because
Is there a lot of diseases Alzheimer's being one of them
Bitcamp
Be studied in humans while the brain
Give me the live
I just would be impossible
But with
Mice
You can do it right
And it's kind of f***** up its ass
But the important piece to take away from it is
It's research that's going towards getting rid of
Horrifying disease
And that's a plus
That's what these ethical medical people will do
That like
It's kind of weird or doing this
But at the end of the day if we can get rid of Alzheimer's
Humanity
But perhaps
Private conversation
Wildflower
10 vote that it's like
Your brain is going into mouth
And then you're going to see out of my size
It's not there still mice
I get that
There is there a hundred percent still mice
And their guidelines
Jensen place where any bikes that have
Human
Brain cells in them have to be killed Within
Like two weeks
Part of the park
I just now I
I really like
List
Some scientists
If you are list
They are
Just take out all the
Just just for me one time
Just take out all the mouse-brained
Just put in
Just put in a s*** ton
Fred's irs's Midnight Man
Because the
Truth is like who doesn't want mouth one time
I've read Flowers for Algernon I'm okay
Conversion I don't need a distraction so sad
It wouldn't have to
Maybe this time
Human story right there we'll get it right this time and we never do
But maybe the super intelligent
It might people
We'll get it right
Position about it being like actually
Human half mice
Is f****** absurd if you know anything about Sia
Further
The stuff about cows we went over on the last episode
Throat
The Pig stuff is all just a bad growing
Human organs within pigs
Not an exact science
Isn't
Practice at all
And it
Not
Pigs aren't parking
Further I was talking to my doctor buddy doctor gums
About this
Is
Saint for humoring me about
My dumbass question
What
Seems to be afraid of in some way
Is that we're putting these
Human brains into mice
And they're going to breathe
It's going to create races of
Super cute like
Super mice
I'm totally on board with
Impossible
As long as it's mine
It's fine I like your I like your stipulation there
It would not pass
To the children
In the same way that if you put like
Techno dude
Implant of a magnet in your scars
Hereditary
These animals don't reproduce
Finger
Alex is afraid of life
Is Planet of the Apes scenario
And it just is not at all what's being done
It's not possible
So Alex Jones
All this
Chimera stock
Is based on in the same way he doesn't
Understand what
Standees
Berating
And I know that
Because on his show when he's talking about these things
He flashes up the articles
Do you talk about
And I found them and read them
And what I mix
Is what they say
It's not that
Yeah but don't you love this Alex Jones I love the fear-mongering about chimeras Alex Jones
Don't give me Muslim hating give me a
Statues
Yes
I also a listener Madison
Treated at us
And that is
Alex might be talking about
Dulce base
Okay where's the Dulce base
I don't know how to tell you are a very boring
Much
I hate you
How to score 14 bel-ray
What is Jordan
I like the idea
Score
There's an arbitrary
This is like Whose Line Is It Anyways but for Alex Jones related podcast
Mexico I am looking into this a while back
I did a bunch of research into it
Basically there is an army base
9 floors Underground
The Reptilian
Alright
The reptilians are working with humans down under the
And there's all kinds of
Secret experimentation going on down there
It's I mean it's all
Basically
Space aliens working with people to create hybrids
And all this s*** under Smith
Doctor Who
And all of the bunch of bases that are connected by underground tunnels where the reptilian
I'm working
David Icke level nonsense
Yeah yeah yeah
Do it on the Bus videos
Adult
Score one for me
Suffice it to say
And if he is
That's crazy
If he's not
Still crazy
But he's also misrepresenting everything
Now I promised
But the script was going to end
Something weirdly racial
Did you promise
I turn my phone off I was sleeping
I woke up
Turns out I was driving
3030 5050
Maybe flying
2000 yd
Ice crystal forming behind it
Turn my phone on
Because we're flying on the same path just the other direction
Gone
I was watching the ice crystals
Disappear in front of me
Performing at high altitude
Watch her supposed to
It was dissipating
Within 30 seconds
Everything is incredible because you see the propaganda you see the manipulations he wonder what else is going on
Page Manor projects in projects
I've kept quasi Secret
Squared
I don't even know how you doing
Which is admittedly going on
All the specifics are classified
Underground
People again
F*** you
Because it's divide and conquer
So his version can't we all get along is what
So it isn't particularly angry homeowner
So it's a
70s Lily for taste that we are looking at what he said in 2015
But this is
On the heels of
It's like Ferguson happened not too long before
The Charleston shooting happened a month
Before they're so
So
Incredibly racist
Today's to wave it away
Right even if you even if you think it's not that big
A problem at least have some sort of empathy
Why people are angry
No because they're dumb because they don't know what they're spraying up there
Guys just got murdered by the cops
Can't you at least for one second be like
Bad that
Black people are getting murdered by the cops
You don't even say that
He's like you guys are just
Not this is a tragic event
And it's a
Distraction
This is bad and you fallen for this dumb old
What you know is
Perception of George Soros
Everyone who's mad about these
Or just tricked by George
The roast
Because if we came together would be able to find out
About fees
When is
Story about being on a plane
Not being chemtrail
So that's what really
Confused
Because I remember listen to this clip
And being like
What do you say in the jet was good or bad
But now I listen back to it and he saying like
All of this happened like it
Supposed to
Yeah
So what's your story
Where you going to get off your phone to take a picture of like
And here's
Things no
No I think his story is that like every other time it doesn't look like this
Maybe what he's getting at but it's
Cheerleader
And that's why they're boarding
Delray
Speaking of abortions Jordan
Next is where we begin
From the August 10th at the
He gets more into Trump
But in the next
You directly contradict
You said in the
The issues of Kim
Involved in them in the past
By myself I used to believe in
Come Along on those issues once you start
Learning more about it
I wasn't involved in that Sam was going on
Didn't do enough to stop it
That's a coward's way
It is almost more cowardly what I did
Blind dying it
Let me be clear
I was not good
The way I was when I was 18 20 years old
To repent for lying
Either that or the time
And I quote
I don't judge people until I paid for them
One of those
Paperboy
Clarify.
Oh that's true
He might not actually be even more of a coward's way out
Going on
We're all three of these are kind of like
It's a triangle
Yeah but be that as it may
It's like he's in a romance
Comedy with
Yeah
Meet cute with abortion back out he was 18
Bumped into this abortion and I was like oh my God
It is
Love at first
Can I play
A large part of this episode
We get to get a really good glimpse
What else would like
On August
About what who Donald Trump is
And what do you think
And
We're not
A real
Change
And we know for a fact
Because you know we live in 2017
Then in December
Has Donald Trump on the show
Right
And this is
4 months
Before that
Do something
Hamster really really pivot and we don't
Like you think you'd see it by now
And it's not especially with how intuitive is a median
The following
He's full-on like
Jesus
And I'm not saying like to the came on my show
Just be that good
From Trump and that was it if that's
Strfkr though
Yours is next clip where Alex again
Pretty right about Trump
Trump
Animal
He's the casino business that's his dirty business as they come
How can you be so right
I don't have a good gut feeling about Trump
I know
Him specifically I don't have a bad gut feeling
Just feels like a setup
Because what he's saying is true
Change crew
Send it
Because what he saying is true
What's the same time
I got some concern
So I mean
He's wrong that Trump is
Well Cienega
This is our cover
Running is Republican
We're being blackmailed
It's you can't
Look
We've said some very Progressive things
Sure
Maybe I've
Stetsom
Jailable thing
But
What what I'm saying now is
Give me the best of about Republicans
It's lost
As long as they have or at least libertarian
They feel like they're under attack or at least their ideas
Do support who's ever saying
And they always feel like outside
You know
Politician
B social progress
And people being equal is an attack
People on the conservator
Well if you've always been number one
The idea that everybody comes
Quota.
Steam's exactly
Play like you're falling
So if everybody goes up
That feels like
You're not as
As high as you used
So it's it's
Teams that you know
And also I
They're mad at problems that
Will not
Cannot be solved
Like the solutions they want our
As we talked about
Kohl's
Aren't coming back
We have f****** robot
That you're mad about that but you're losing to robot
Like that's not going to stop
They're mad about immigration
We haven't all giving me your weak you're tired
Like no matter how much you fight again
Against that the only way that that is
If Donald Trump becomes a literal dictator and start standing on our borders with me
Frankly
If that's the worst that he does I'm fine
Hell of a wall
Donald Trump
Kelowna Mendes
So one of the things that's kind of fun
Is it Alex
Pole
Around the around the studio he wants you want to check the temperature of the
Studio
Check temperature of his
Staff about what they think
Think about Donald Trump
So we got a guy in the
Control booth
Who I don't work there anymore
Famous cliff
When Alex
What do you think about Trump
Is John Wall
Overall on Donald Trump
Why does the country need a Meg
Maniacal narcissistic
To pull it out of the rut
That's just not what America is about
And help him
Pretty good on population control
I just
I can't believe
Trump
Jay Jay
You do not have a job for much longer
How to spell mad that everybody Compares Donald Trump to Hitler and Napoleon
These guys worked out
No he's joking
You can tell he's joking
I don't know
Comparing Trump to
Like dictators
Ama
What are you saying that like there was a guy in Germany was pretty confident
She's f****** route
Saying positive things about Hitler
In order to compare
So everybody it's fair game
Trump Hitler stuff is
That that would be a good choice for the country
Donald Trump
He's doing an impression of Alex in 2 years
But he's doing in future Alex
Compression
But that is true move over Anthony atamanuik
I just don't think that's the way we should be going
Dominated by the bull
Overall some people's responses they want somebody
The problem is
Charisma
Is Providence if he's for real
Taxi want to be president actually want to save the country
Who were Macho and arrogant who were not evil
Who were able to pull countries out of a run
Confidence and giving people the perception
The problem is horses
Yasser means
He is a little bit saying that
Hitler has
Some good quality
At the cost of
Millions of people's lives
These guys are right
Jodeci
But yeah
Lake Jennings
Everybody
Including idiotic Infowars people
We're right about Donald Trump the only people wrong about Donald Trump
We're 25% of the worst people on the planet
Disrespected even the people who were working for Trump to Rodger Stone
You want to know something
This next
Clip
Scary
This next clip
You predict
Almost
Exactly what's going to happen in the world
I can't be sure I told you he might be a soothsayer
I have this next clip
Cinefamily
Calista it's scary
And absolutely
Your leaders are
Leaders are compromised sold out to
And part of a plant
Maybe they're going to give us Trump
As a strong man during the collapse
Popular
But it can easily be twisted into a form of fascism and just like the Democrats
Cult of communist wannabes led by fascist
Knuckledraggin called
It were very good on many points
But the Republicans into something
Something big is about to happen
So I mean right there in that clip Alex
100% predicted the rise of Mike cernovich
He predicts the rise of Gavin begin
He predicted
He will become
And this to me tells me
But he's not
The same man
Even on August
If you will be
Probably at the end of 20
Does that but he predicts
Yeah
Set the tea party and the right-wing
Are completely susceptible to Fascism yes he has
A very amazing insight into his own group which he now completely lack
Daddy
That is bananas
I refuse I refuse to believe that
I meant this is the craziest part
Business before like Sarah kendzior and at all of those people
Before people are still talking about it
A mainstream
She was publishing stuff like over the summer
The territory where she was already issuing a warning
The point being
Nobody in the major is everybody was treating him as a joke Alex Jones
The only person who's like a Republican
He's not saying that he's staying that there's two
Susceptible to it
Which is
I mean it's predictive in some ways it's
Vicki knows that
Makes me really scared about that clip
That
In the same way that when I first
Discovered the Clipper he was talking about
Being mobbed up
And you
Change your mind
Means something
Bigfoot
You learn
Something
That preclude your knowledge
Mob ties
This clip
Whatever happened
Made him okay with becoming this
Thing that he's afraid of
Like you in this clipping saying that the the right-wing is
Susceptible to fascism
I there's acceptable to becoming this
The thighs ugly
Ugly thing
And yeah
Like you looked in a mirror news like
You know what I think I might be susceptible
He's aware of it and he lets it happen
Which
And not just let that happen
Openly
In the rise of the Winger's
Completely
People like
Mike cernovich
Rebel media
Sobiech type
Like he is
Use complicit in all of these things that he's
Ostensibly issuing a warning about
So
No
He knows what he's doing
On some level I
I think
That's scary
This is bananas
Yeah
Clip to me was very unsettled
Like okay
With Alex
Okay
Know if there's one thing I know about Allie
I don't think so
I would give up
Is future career prospects
Just for money
Cuz I think he has a good operation going swindling news
Is fam
But imagine he was promised a TV show where he gets
I do also believe him that people have offered him
I agree
The conversation came into being
He still
Couldn't do things on that panel he couldn't do on Fox
What you can do
Say whatever bulshit you want
But Fox would let him do that too
SEC regulation
I think that was added that was exactly the converse
Deer Fox
To like yes
We will let you spout Crazy Bowls
But only to a point
Trump was like
Dude I don't give a
Okay
I think that
Not enough
I think if you let him run Trump
Maybe
Gets his own
TV show Network
Kisses on network
Alright
Pull it back from Network
No cuz I don't think a show is enough for him
Okay you would Joe
30 million dollars
Turn the nursery light
D-mat worth is
Cuz otherwise
If you look at
It just the growth pattern
I mean I've been
20 years that he's been doing
First flight
10 work that great
Right or so
He's had a pretty
Steady rise in the past
If you were to look at his growth
And be like okay
This guy is trying to get me on board exam
I know
Is Mob connected
He might lead our people into fascism
I am
Going to need
Something that is out of the question
4 MI
Potential to gain
Going to mean like threat if enforced keeps growing at the current rate if we expanded the ways that I know I'm capable
Been doing
4 years
I need something I could never achieve on my own
On TV
I've already
You don't know that that's true we don't know that Morgan's career
All right you going to
24th at
I don't know it's interesting to speculate about
But what
I mean
What's most fun about speculating about a counterfactual
Because
He didn't lose
Didn't get what you need
Right
Which leads me to think there wasn't
Underage
But like that because then
Domino's
To be like okay I get their patrol
TV network
And not having
Contingency plan what do I get if you whip
It can't just be tons
There can't be
Okay
I don't know it
I can't believe that
Purely
I love how Trump
Hates muzzle
As much as I do
It's just out-and-out
Strfkr either way
It really is
He is the guy who's all about freedom and libertarian values and
Free market and blah blah blah
And he's worried about leaving us
Trump is leading us into fashion
Destroying the free market
Yeah it's so if Alex
Really understood the thing
He's concerned about
Stevie's
Please road marker
And be like I have gotten on the wrong
And he's not even
Close to that
Yeah but also the middle
Can get on the right
Be huge
I think that that would be
Be fine
Not for him
I think his list that means he would have to
D'usse
He was wrong
There's so what it's Alex
There's a way to do that powerfully we talked about it
He still can't say there's a way for him to do that that doesn't make
Emasculate
There's a way to prevent it
I was completely lied to
This
Supposition
The chance if you really wanted too late for that
Return
Amount
Right
He had was that when Trump announced
The globalist
I'm a nationalist and the globalist
Look guys
Rodger Stone
Fatality a lot of bulshit
All of his reporters perspectives
We got caught
It would be possible
He could do it
Think about his listeners
They would absolutely if they bought into him
They would try and kill
No it's well yeah baby baby they were totally try and kill Trump
Alex came out and was like
Red Alert truck just revealed he's a globe
His listeners who
Of which I would assume
90%
No I think he would have to I think you would loose up because a lot of people really love true
Okay I was telling you can call through a lot of his show
And most of them weren't worth it so I didn't cut them but one
Is coming up that you'll see
Add very indicative of all of the calls
And they're all just parroting his opinion back to
Okay they're all just
He says he's true things and I like him but I don't trust
Read all of his callers basically just have whatever
Perspective he tells them
So whenever
It's a very rare thing for
For someone to have a narrative it doesn't
Old man Wyoming
And says
And maybe some slight variations but with
The same
Narrative
Isaac licking it would be a pivot
Certainly
Funny people
The cult of personality already has
Documents
But he got the
The Trump was lying to him the whole time
Oh my God
Tweet Paul Joseph Watson
Believe believe
He's been snake bitten on that one so I don't think it's
He's not going to fall for that again
You know it
It's really f***** up we can
Speculate all night long but we got a few more Clips we got to get through
Is really f****** aware of
He's doing
In ways that we didn't realize
Before because
Spell their
Out
So in this next clip
Who is Michael Perry
Back to them
Earlier
Comparison about Hitler
Donald Trump
I agree with him on vaccines
Marjorie gross
Mobile tracker
What should happen to Trump political
A shell
Choo choo choo choo
He's a smart guy
He's even speculating
Gnostic
So he doesn't believe is a good guy
So are we
My pretties
Alright cuz a lot of his beliefs don't match up with Nasi
That's true
It's just weird
Cuz I cuz
You don't know.
In the
The Gospels
He's working with g
Jesus wants him to give him up to the Romans
And like imagine imagine is if there was a chance that Jesus didn't get
Killed
What was the religion
That's true
Like the whole thing has
How to be a setup it was a game
What is it called
Alex and Rodger Stone
Maybe they're in game
To sacrifice Trump
Much like Jesus
Holyshit
Cuz roll
Givenchy
And then
We get to watch
Southgate Publix
Crucified like an episode
I said it would be
I think your phone for good idea
Stipulation of a trial
Legal
And I've gone but I've been going back and reading a lot of scripture as a 33-year old man
How's it going
It's interesting
There's a lot of stuff that I I don't
I didn't remember
Angles
I don't want to get too into it right now I'm not prepared to give my thesis
This
I'm going to get myself
This next clip is
One of the most inappropriate things I've ever heard on the show but not in a lake
Horrifying way
Just in a
I'm not okay with this
I'm really not okay with this
Just a very uncool things
Okay
Christian in Texas are on the year of the Julia
Neighbor takes my call
About two years
What are friends
You know
People who are 18 adults have the
And it affects them
Text Amanda no
Custom
You know about Donald Trump
Noah seems like he is
Have a feeling
If he does become president
That
Obama you know you went out there instead of going to take your shot
Architecture semi-auto to look electronic do you
So here we have a 40
Ten-year-old calling in
Infowars
Who's been listening for 2 years
Since he was 12
Rights of a 6th grade
He's a little
Sing to this toxic garbage
Who let him listen to
So he
Ostensibly I would assume
Regularly
He calls
He just directly mirrors the opinions that Alex Jones expose RX bottles
So
You have a guy
Who's calling in
Who's not an adult
His brain is still for me
And it's clear
Found impact on
Absolutely doesn't understand the nuances of God
How do you say
You didn't do it
You didn't do any of that stuff there still
Obama is still in office
This is so inappropriate
If a fourteen-year-old
Like tweeted at me
They said they liked our show
Kodiak leave
Don't listen to the show
Is even though I agree with the things I'm saying
I don't have Ariel
I would be like
Alright you need to become a pilot
18 year olds
Because it's
Super Immortals
Culture
Yeah no absolutely Alex Jones
Response to the fourteen-year-old calling app
Should be something along the lines of
Hey dude
You can't drive
You can't see R-rated movies
You should not be listening to my show
There's a lot of content
And you know
I mean it's covered under free speech for the most part that everything he says
It's not illegal to say but it is
Their needs
To be parental discretion
Stop
If you can't have a kid
Listening to Chimera ship
Cuz that kid can't research that
He's not going to be able to figure out like the nuances of science
And what Alex
Was actually talking about
And it's evident by the fact that he's just
Mirror note
Alex
14 year old calls into
What you talk about
Good songs
Chimeras of the heart
I remember that
I called into
I told him that I have to attend to play The Mighty Mighty Bosstones
That's what I called in for
Y107
Come over with all the radio stations
We're back in Columbia
I2i this is my big first radio
But my break
I always had a fairly deep
Voice
And so I called in
Played the role of an adult
I told the guy I like
I'll give you my house
My wife
My car
Cuz I do if I said something like that he
And of course
I'm sitting here listen to the radio
It's not nothing
So he just recorded that music
Play the impression that I get
Hawking radiation
Yukon
No not really I just
No Lie
Because I never said I was just let him believe
Be that as it may
Connor's aren't like
Nevermind this is what fourteen-year-old
Not listening and I do not
Support 14 year olds
Listen to The Mighty Mighty Bosstones
Supportive
Mambo Number 5
Where is the kid does have a good point
Inasmuch as politics does effect
But what happened
Does Effexor
People who are too young to vote
That's a great point
Discussion
How much should be had around that
I don't know baby call Linda ellerbee
Instead
Host of Nick news
If you don't do something like that. There's more appropriate venues
Getting kids involved
In
Expressing themselves
Like Rock the vote
Right things with art
Anything
That's not it
Not done
I hear you and God bless your question
What perspective
It's really it's really opened up my eyes and
She was going on I mean I used to
You know I didn't care
Care for the news but I figured out that
Yeah all this stuff is
And that
ONN training schools Army going to school I mean I realize that
They're pretty much brainwashing that's ridiculous
Feeling
Good to hear from you appreciate your call Julia and Kentucky you're on the ear
Excusable it's f***** up
Should not be
Signing off on with a fourteen-year-old believe
Especially not like
Hey kid
Don't believe that school you go to
Do things that fill your brain with knowledge
Maybe you're going to learn about math
Maybe going to learn about maybe going to learn about literature
Nope
The doll
Amiable
Those things
Is are good
There are things that you shoot encouraging you
Critical thinking skills
Those are two things are absolutely good
What's good
Demonizing all authority figures
The thing that they're trying to brainwash you
That's not healthy
Because when you grow up super paranoid
Grow up with
Perception
Did anything that seems official
Be trusted even come Eddie Bravo
This is Young and brother
We're going to mellow out
Underlying pieces that Eddie Bravo in modern-day
17 years old
I don't know if I agree with
But yeah
That would be
Right
Bloodline all the time
And they would get callers who were fairly Young
And it was
Or they have
Concerns about
And stuff like that
And it's relevant to the show
Right
Adam Carolla did make a lot of jokes
They always
Tried to deal with people in a very sensitive
Dr. Drew did a lot of a puke until he put in a lot of effort
Into
Understanding
What your brain is like when your 14
And not trying to f*** with that brain
Right
Super weird the fourteen-year-olds were calling to adult men at midnight
It was super it was dealt with
In a healthy
And productive way
It's not this
This is
I think it maybe should be illegal
Sprouts to say those things to a fourteen-year-old
That is a good question
That is a really good question
Is getting
Like is it any media that you know
Like I think you should be allowed to watch
I know you're under the age of
At alive atino that it it does it does introduce
Shouldn't have brought up making it illegal or whatever setting
In a perfect world where there's good parenting
The kids should not be
The f****** world went
Crazy because they saw Janet Jackson
Set 42 second year old is allowed to listen to this s***
This is really demonstrative of what kids
Should not be list
Sport Clips
Ferguson
Cuz there is some police brutality
What the feds are globalist occupy
Run them into the arms of the globalist
George soros's finding
Tusker the shop and has really hard operators to do it
Anamosa cases that justifiable shootings the police were engaged
Police officers
Nope
Bigger than population in percent
6%
Disproportionate
Stop right there. Right there
Disease
And it's just me just doesn't even show up on the scale
Kids should not here
Angles like
They don't know how to parse the nuances that like that
And realize where the LIE is where's the manipulation
It's terrible that not human beings are not allowed to become human beings and it's terrible that old human beings are dying of
S*** old
People die of
But you know it's not that bad that
Young
Men with
Families
Are being murdered
Murdered and there are
Consequence
4-H
They are being indicted
So it's not
If this system in his head where it all works out
It doesn't it does not work out angry about
He's fully aware there again in the same way that it's a revelation that he's aware
That the Tea Party is susceptible to Fascism right he just said right there
Fully aware that statistically
Black men
Orbeez
Killed by the police
In
Very anomalous numbers still denied
Racism really exist
He's never seen white people being racist
How do you reconcile
I actually think his next clip actually help
I think we might be able to reconcile
It explains
Some of
His inability to think
Let me shoot video I shoot
For some reason
1 shots
Shooting 308 AR-15
Huge boxes
While I'm talking a couple of blow up
Center block flying around
One-armed headstand that's why I don't think I do.
He's walking brain damage
Yeah
Maybe that's why he has the inability to integrate information
He's
Gmate literally be brain-dead
You stuck under a house inhaling fumes as a child
He said that he got his head
Smashed around knocked in the
The concrete when he was young
When selling a story about
Shooting
Explosives
And a cinder block
I'm flying out of
Explosion
Serious
Shoot kill you
So we figured it out there's the above all of Alex Jones right here
Synthesized into one person
Who just is on
Able to really deal with what facts are
He doesn't know how to read
Probably get some of his brain damage
So he reads things he assumes the worst
He thinks his people are winking at him
Long article
Talking to ghost
It's a call this is
Is just a man like we have a grand unified field theory of Alex
Yeah
Futbin
Even if you have brain damage
Like there are moments
Lucidity
And maybe
These moments
Inside about Trump
And the inevitable slide into fascism
The vest
Images of his brain that works
And maybe
Baby
Taking all of these supplements
It killed the rest of the brain that worked at possible
Ironically be a Flowers for Algernon for 200,000
Mouse-brain
Clips
From August
Rights and like I said earlier we got the
Perspective of Jojo
The employee of Infowars
School
Things to say about Trump
Alex wants to ask
Naturalnews.com
Assignment
Infowars employee
Anthony gucciardi
Write these blogs on naturalnews.com
Did Alex reports on it
Clarify
Recycle it is a vicious propaganda
Confirmation
Absolute
Not even close
Sitting in
Studio is back in the control booth
Disrespected about Trump
At the same time it's like
Pain
He's going and being real
People white people
Even if he's not genuine the appearance of genuine
Miss King
Another
He screams now all the time about how I'm real
I don't know proceeding Foundation
This is such a this is such a weird twisting and turning investigation
It's bananas
Explain a whole lot
To the heart of it
Crowdsource
Compulsory
We like Alex Jones
We will get on auto-ship
If you submit to a brain scan
Will even buy one of each color of those t-shirts that never got made
That actually sounds like a fun chart if you get checked
Out
You won't do it though
No
I better yet
Yeah I bet he has memory loss I bet he's talking
You know
Weymouth
You are a reverse injected
Traumas to your head
When you're younger
It makes a
Impact
When you're older
As opposed to when you're like
20in get hit around the head a little bit it's not so bad
But he talks about these
Rites of Passage
Rinaldi's
Fights that he got in when he was like
Which is
Sweet spot
Concerned about people who play football
In like junior high or High School
For the rest of your life
I mean
Really looks like
That's what's going on with
Wow
August 10th
Yeah
Except we're not quite
How is this past
On August 10th
Alex teas for the next day
He's got an interview with
A huge
Astronaut
Is Eva
This astronaut got in touch with me
His name is a big deal
Okay that's right. InTouch
Alright
To break some big news here assuming it's one of the challenge
Do you like that either
You know it's just
To break the big news here on the show
We're going to have it done interviewing tomorrow
TuneIn it's going to be great
Teasing the f***
Turn on August 11th
Right
That's goddamn David
What's going on
Alex Jones going to be in later
Skip the interview
And we get
To his interview
StoryBots
Grave
If that is an astronaut
That name should be all over NASA
Is he a liar
He's legit
Okay I looked it up
He was involved with designing
Space Station
He's done a lot of missions in space
Super legit
How did it go
Well it's can't go well
I want to give you a couple of important
He's ninety if he's a day
He has been retired for 18 years
Alright Alex think
But he's calling in
To give him some big info on the secret space program
And s*** like that
The wonders of
Space
He does he does tell him like about how great spaces
You talked about how
Perception of the Earth
Changes when you're outside of Earth that I look down on it
Yeah that whole thing you hear from every astronaut their light
All of your troubles seem so small when you look at the Grand scale see the universe everything is
Is it
Is much bigger yeah we need to make sure we defund that
Otherwise people will get that kind of perspective
Alex is trying to
Trying to lead him down bro.
That would reveal
Conspiracies
Tip sort of talk about how great
His career
How how interesting space travel is and how
Wants to encourage people
To dream
And wants to tell his story
He's awesome
Fuckingawesome
Alex
The whole time
Hands like
No
He finally got a genuinely in
Aspiring message
F*** this the guy talks about how human monsters need inspiration
Story Musgrave is telling talkin about how like
When he was a boy he had to drop out of school to work
And he was like
Properly educated as a child
Went back to
Became a doctor
And then gotten
The space as I recall
He
Space Voyages of any
America
He's telling this super inspirational awesome story
But I did it's not the interview he thought it was
Most interesting thing that you can pause
Possibly run
Yeah I don't have clips of the actual interview cuz
It's really visual
Like Alex is this
Disappointment is supervision
But I want to play the beginning of the interview
And then the end of the interview but he does kind of rush out of it
Is
Gorgeous
Again this is Mike down situation
This cannot be the future via Skype
Musgrave thank you so much for coming on the broadcast weather
You're welcome sir now my biggest accomplishment is standing right here to talk to you and that's my daughter
Story Musgrave
Hi Alex
How you doing
She's nine years old
And now I'm going to let her go now she's going to go back to the Tractor so she drives track
After she got her own ATV
Auntie drive360 mowers and she does that kind of stuff she's getting the same kind of reason that I did so she'll
Chili ready for the Rocca world when the time's come
Bye-bye sweetie
Okay you weren't expecting that work
Worcestershire
What do I know I'm not sure what I know
Well it's good to have you on the broadcast programs are you mostly in Austin audience
I'm flattered that you reached out to us
F****** grades every part of that is gold it's so sweet
He has obviously his granddaughter granddaughter
That's all that's just adorable raising her the way she'll be ready for the
As if every part of that is awesome like
Not let anything other than like this girl
Great thanks
Amazing she's a Musgrave
Doing the whole thing
It's beautiful it's beautiful all right. We want to get back to the
Adventures I love the so what do you know about that
Never really watched
Listen to the show
That's where Alex Alex
Turn
This guy contacted us
He's going to teach us as a whistleblower I like that
And the reality is I bet there he was in Austin
Go on a TV show
But it is not
I wish we were a video show
Just so people could see the looking
His face when
Story Musgrave asked
Are you in Austin Bass
Your audience mostly in Austin is like Alex Ison
Balls cut off
Cuz he knows that he's getting emasculated in front of his own audience tonight I'm going to get Musgrave up
There's not much else about Trump in the 11
That Musgrave shed
Beautiful
Play plan I could listen to that all day
Is adorable
And get this
He asked them again
Worldwide server
He's adorable throughout the entire interview is great
That is
Well first off
When you say Alex Jones says he has a
Huge Astro
On the show
First thing I think is going to be a fact
I don't know why that happened that happened
This guy
Like he's just like wandering around
Thinking like he saw Good Will Hunting me by
Game is what exactly
Surely awesome
Who's accomplished
More than Alex Jones could ever
Dream
And the angle of Alex's lying about building
Everett
I actually wish I had more clips of it because they would be a really interests
In case study
Into how terrible an interviewer out
6 times at point-blank range
And she survived
He doesn't want to get to the details
In the same way you can see him being really frustrated
B story Musgrave doesn't want to give him any global
He wants to just talk about how great math is and how important
It's monstrous program but you could get a lot of really into
Stories out of him with your Theisen interviewer and Alex
This isn't there to play games
Disappointed
That would have been such a beautiful spot just like
Just nothing but
Racism
Globalist in all of the ship
And then for one brief Shining Moment
If the promise
Subspace
Sure beautiful
Could be
But
Only four dimensions
Yeah
The same thing with just the other day in 27
Antonio Sabato jr. on as a guest
Amazing
Subway
Hurry up there
We're
Watch that s*** is
The kid
Had a huge crush on
True damage
That's what Sonic Crush -2.5 friend
This girl
Well here's the thing it's actually really f***** up
So I have this like
Childish crush on the girl on Earth 2
I had these like sort of fantasies
Of us being
Friends and running around Earth two together and discovering stuff
That's the version of a crush
Pippi Longstocking
Corso
When I got older
I think it was in college
Iced I remembered
And it's been
Memory of a childish Crush
And then go back as an older person
Cheese up to now I wonder what
Attractive so you looked her up on Facebook I didn't look her up on Facebook
Expedia
And it turned out
She died at 24
Giving up
Become a teacher and then just
And diagnose one of the biggest bombers
That is a Superbowl
Define more sad stories about my life you can go to knowledge
Facts about Alex
Also you can follow us on Twitter if you'd like
At knowledge
Underscore iTunes leave a review people like that
Means more people
We are on Facebook
We have some people
Followed and given reviews appreciate it
Thank you very much if you want to donate to the show you can
There's a on the website
Support
The show
And you can get a little money become a policy wonk absolutely
A friend of ours Matt drop
I would like very much.
You added a Porsche
To the website
Wherein you list the novelty
God through put up a review section
Exactly
It's an exclusive Saddlery Saddlery
Coconut juice
?
Gag
It might be coming back
Future don't know what I'm talking about
I don't care
Something weirdly aggressive way to end
Mysterious
Paramount
Unfortunately my childhood Crush from Earth to is no longer with him
Is there is good news
Rapoport
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color