Air Jordan
I have great respect for Tenaya Lodge like I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
And also
Disguise Alex Jones
That wasn't me to bring attention to that tub
Pahrump
Jordan
What's up
I survived
An ordeal that would destroy
A lesser version
End of myself
I ordered some food
Delivery
And I went downstairs
To get it
And I luck
Myself out
Locked myself out of the house at about 9:30 in the evening
And I was too
Terrified
I do my landlord's not going to come over I don't even know who my landlord is out last night.
I can't
Break into my window cuz it
It's not on the bottom floor that I have that kind of Parkour ability
To scale the building
Which is never Gray
Are all dark
Everything is going to hit the buzzer in like week somebody off
That seems like too much
So I walked around the side of the building
And I saw someone's TV on
Exactly they both be at but I was so terrified there's like
I've got my food but now I guess I'll be out there
Are the eating and sleeping out on the in the alley tonight
It wasn't too bad yeah that's
It's true and that might have been part of the reason why I forgot my keys
Cuz it just looked like a
Sandals
How dare you I know you're not a another saying at those Clippers
Okay.
Vibrate spot dead is currently as we speak
Goes the Eurovision song contest
I know every year
What the f*** no you don't know I don't know I've never really even watched it before but this is the first time that I've really
We decided to dig in and watch some Eurovision
And it is
Just
Universally terrible music
The Patty Murray is amazing given an airplane Hangar to do whatever they want
And they create some
Ridiculous spectacle from what I understand I don't know too much about Eurovision but from what I understand it's pretty serious
Country against
Country
Most most everybody is
Doing like a
You know how Americans invented good music they're all doing that
But you know through there like her through their own lens
Tracker
But some countries
Their own s*** and it's really really good
Is garbage nobody has a good
Slide it's just
Tragic
There's like shows everywhere
So Jordan
Speaking of light shows I would like to let you look into my disco balls
It is actually a Time
Machine
We're going back in time
Beer where we up to today mr. Peabody
Today we are going to May 12th and 13th 2000
Continuing back in art
Exploration of Alex Jones
Primarily what he's all about
What are some similarities what are some differences where's the devil at
I mean
Definitely one of the biggest
Discretion
Does Alex Jones believe he's fighting the devil
In 2003
Steve Dennis dreams been a little bit muddled and a secondary element of that question is
Does Alex
Believe he's fighting the devil and actively try to hide that from his presentation
In order to be taken more seriously
At this point in his career
Start at the beginning of May 2003 we're now you're coming to the middle of the month
I think it's still an open
Question
And Bullard a little bit more today
Call Robert Verdugo
The first if I become policy won't do I get to see exclusive pictures of saline being excessively cute thank you so much right now if I was you
I'm a policy wonk very much I'm not sure but I will send a picture of Celine to Jordan seek
There are no exclusive snow
Cute picture you can put it on American Way
Thank you so much you're now probably want
I'm a policy wonk
Text the morning dew glistening on Steve pieczenik neon nips
I'm a policy wonk thank you very much
Terrifying nightmare that will never Escape my brain
Joe my neighbors might think I actually listen to Alex
Thank you so much
I'm a policy very much
This close to the joke not all heroes wear masks thank you so much you are now probably want
Ewok names that are
Really that one actually almost hits me in the gut a little bit
That one that's a little bit like I get off your high horse okay
Next
Very much
Scooter the Corgi thank you so much
Thanks good
Jordan in the past
I should say that something's happening in the present but not just
Wright's not just your visit
And that is this people have some birthday
In 2021 I should tell you this weekend was
Chock-a-block
With with policy wonk birthday
We got we got
Heather M
Happy birthday happy birthday Heather
Throwbacks
Happy birthday
Ethan
Mary sent a message wanted to wish you Happy Birthday over the weekend hope you hope you have a
Happy birthday
We start here on the 12th and it is a slug
It is a rough time
The beginning
Actual news
And that is where we will jump
I mean they're really
So just a quick reminder the LA Times editorial that Alex is talking about did not say that McCarthy was right it was infectious
Steven, condemnation of McCarthy and his tactics and a plea not to throw it all opposition
Communism
Just based on how big a piece
He's a s*** he was
So maybe journalistic Outlet Darkness
Pervious Houston
Presenting options based on headlines what you think
Things are then maybe
Sorry label to find this article that Alex is talking about in the LA Times about textbook
Hey by Diane ravitch an author whose work is almost
Exclusively about education related issues
The first thing to point out is that this much like the other article I'll excite is an editorial
Rabbit is writing in the
The first person
It's not a piece of straight
Reporting
Around this time in history rival should just released a book titled the language police how pressure groups were strict with students
The book was about half beer of the ignited controversy from both left and right wing pressure groups has led to text
To give students an incomplete View
Subjects like history and literature
In her article for the time she says quote
The textbooks go out of their way to sanitize the very practices and non-western cultures
That they rightly condemned in RC
Society
Branstad's every textbook acknowledges that the enslavement of Africans by the West
With a great crime
However went
Describing slavery in the Middle East or Africa many claim that is a path to Upward career Mobility or a chance
To join a new family
Slavery is wrong in any time and place
Contribute recognized as such
That's a fair enough point but I want to make sure that we illuminate had this criticism is different than that it's Lobby by someone
Unlike Alex
Alex doesn't want all cultures be represented accurately with proper historical
Contact
He would want the Middle Eastern or African
Slavery discuss
But he would also want the textbooks to ignore American slavery where they had to cover it
The focus should be on how America actually ended
Flavored know it was if it weren't for white people we never would have ended slavery everybody knows this
Ravages pointing out certain textbooks
That she's read that are lazy
Alex just doesn't want history to make
Can feel bad
It would make him sleep
Specific difference
Yeah yeah you know if you're if you're quoting Thomas Jefferson incorrectly all the time but it's like
Hey I'm Thomas Jefferson I love having slaves it make you free feel like maybe the founding fathers were very smart
Also I wouldn't like this paragraph in the Times article
The histories treatment of religion is scandalous
The origin stories of each religion or accounted as if they were documented history rather than religious myths
Many Publishers have Multicultural advisory boards to ensure the text
Books contain only positive facts about religion or ethnic
Snickers
Suspected Alexandria Duvall articles
Something definitely would not like
The suggestion that is religious beliefs are a myth
Also backflip that we listen to music
1/2 hour AIDS
The show it
A real it was walking through molasses
Yeah yeah that's not
Good it was to
Brick 88 bit started up
A half an hour
Really
Interesting stuff that
What about
But going back in time and look
These episodes
This is such a good example of like
Being able to go in different direction
Learning about enter
Interesting stuff
Like this
Murder
1 mi
Okay
Alright
What's going on here is that Alex's glossing over an amazing story
Just to make it valuable to his worldview when in fact it doesn't really work at all
The IRA member in question here is a double agent for British intelligence
Codename steak knife
He denies it
This is not as cool as you made it sound
No that sucks
Codenames
Nice
Cake
That's even worse I want to be upon whatever
She denies that any of this is true but is widely understood
And if his denial isn't the LIE his story is
Bananas
There's a great piece about this by James Harkin in GQ that I'm taking a lot of the background information
People check out that that are
Okay cool
Apparently in the late 1970s capodieci met an army Sergeant named Peter Jung
A guy who's so charismatic and his superiors quote
Allowed him to wear civilian clothes Dona beard and develop his own sources
Zoe was Sergeant Bilko
Somehow through the magic of Charmander
Who's even though Jones work for the British Army and scappaticci was in the ira
They forged a friendship that resulted in scappaticci becoming a mole
Wow this is a real Romeo and Juliet situation kind of
How do I get to bite this point the IRA to become a slightly smaller organizations
Mission which was where they were spies
Why is trying to infiltrate their ranks
Come snitches
That sucks they put together a counterintelligence
Which is meant to root out any potential spies
Harkins article
By the
1980s capodici was the deputy head of internal security and a trusted member of its
General headquarters stats
So many goddamn times
Why are you always putting charge their own investigation
Essentially through unconventional methods
The British government had cultivated a relationship with a double agent was placed internally in a position that it was almost
Comically strategic
Get the f*** out of here double agent was the guy in the ira who was in charge of finding double agent
Unrealistic
So as is the case with all these artists pie related stories everything is morally questionable
A lot of the story revolves around scappaticci killing or allowing people to be killed
You could compromise is
Position as a double agent
Or people who are they needed to protect
In order to pursue goals of like arresting higher-ups
Figure
It's messy business and no one's hands are clean but depending on Whose version
The store you believe
This is all made up
According scappaticci was responsible for helping disruptive
Multiple terrorist plots
I don't horrible cough
The accusation that pretty scappaticci with steak Knife came to light in 2000
I'm 30 and it's became a big story as
As well it should be
The important piece to recognize here though is that Alex is missing the forest
For the trees
Heater prices audience of learning about this fascinating piece of History
From learning about the history of the IRA and the troubles
Because the headline works
Different way for him
This is a story about a very well-placed double agent within the IRA but
Alex
This can prove the MI6
Was running the IRA all along
And the bombings in the attacks were all just
False flag
That's an outrageous misuse of the story and by reporting it this way I was actually doing something worse than just
Ignoring the story altogether
He's creating a fake version of it for Azadi
Easily convinced
Themselves they understand
He's like Aaron Sorkin
Even if all the allegations about scappaticci are correct
And accurate
He wasn't the top man in the IRA and he wasn't the one carrying out the bombing
Alex's embellishing that element of the story because it helps him construct the impression
That the world is off
And that everything you hear is a lie
It's a perversion
Of skepticism and curiosity
It is really a good day I mean as far as storytelling goes it when you
Reduce it down into this kind of b******* you miss out on a very human story where people are making difficult to
Visions in moral gray areas where they're struggling
Keep from being caught while at the same time
Struggling to shows that they're trying
The catch themselves
A really fascinating story
MI6 already running the IRA is a really boring story actually
It's much easier
It explain explanatory power over stuff
That would be so
I can take
Years of study Edward
You could be a historian
University
Yeah with tenure
AMC
Maybe not fully be able to explain it
Except over the course of a semester
Well I mean it goes back again to how boring it is
Said that your enemy is both
Everywhere running everything and it's also so incompetent that you can defeat them at any and all time
Of course that's a boring story I don't care if Superman can always win and I don't care
Sure I know it's boring I think
I think to like
What I was getting at is the like it's very unsatisfying if you are a demagogue
On the radio
To be like all right
Buckle down forever
It's going to require a lot of reading and research on your part
Instead be real became a huge it instead everybody just telling people like
It's all fake
The big Boogeyman is running everything who cares
These globalized
Cereal dude become a huge
I don't I don't know
Nevermind
Also I should tell you this
2018 Ford Escape
DG's homeless search
As part of an investigation into his role in the ira
Resulting any murder charges
Although he did plead guilty to having at least 329 images of animal p*** on his computer
According to an article in the Irish Times
Westminster magistrates Court heard scappaticci told police he was not sexually interested in animals
But preferred women with big breasts
He was ordered to pay a total of 185 lb including court costs
Man
Okay
This is why
Journalism has a huge hole
And that is
Very intended
I now need to know what they mean by a********* I can't not know
Pornography featuring animals I don't know what that means
The animal kingdom is large
You know what I'm saying is I know I know exactly what you're saying I just don't share your curiosity
I love you too curiosity.
Okay I'm sorry if we can get those Court files for you
I just want to know all those tickets
I would like
I do not want to see it
I'd like to apologize that
My research did not go deeper into this
PostScript on a story
I'm just saying decency rules keep us
Forgetting a full pic
Picture of the story and it shall continue
Alex's used this story about the IRA double agent
In order to justify that lie
Like everything is a false flag
All of the
Conflict
In Northern Ireland
Volkswagen
Let's do it all and
Volkswagen is a British trick although
It's been picked up by other
People that Alex might love in the present day
Putin
Moscow
Brittany
Petersburg
Turned out he was
3 years of a yelton's
I got elected with a large
Great
This is insane
Alex
2003 have a lot of reasons why he believes
Yeah we're very much in a mobbed-up
He's a front man for
Consortium is on the East Coast territory in terms of knowledge of crime
It's strange because
Cuz I don't think Alex is expressing like
I think he did it
No no no
These people were arrest
Did planting the bombs
To him
Definitive
And somehow that has changed
Or he's just decided
I don't care if someone
Swag
Exiled
Because
I like the way the
That there
Strong Manning
I mean I guess I guess it's if everybody else is false
False flagging then you know I might as well pick the guy who's doing it
They were doing it in in such a way Prince of my hopeful White
National perhaps he does truly believe that
It's like
It's a short
Jump from everything is fake
Do nothing matters very good boy
Everybody is false flagging everybody then
The ethical implications of pulling a false flag are really not that high
Yeah that's true you just what the results
Right I could see Alex ethically
Being okay with Volkswagen
In order to serve
Whatever interest
He's most ishua Airline
I don't know that to be the case but I could easily see that being
Something that he
Subconsciously
I would I would argue that there is zero possibility but
Alex's life is over
That he himself does not trying
And carry out some sort of false
Sure they're just going to like that's the narrative Arc
For him
Season of House
Etiquette ride motorcycles
I am just saying that
Everything is fake
World
And their price
Cabal
So that doesn't sound like the devil
No no
That's one thing that's straight-up global
Anna and secondarily
Alex seems to be convinced
Literally everything is
It does seem there are no real terrorist
The tax there is no real
That's
Dancing line
I don't know
Stand by that today but that makes
Yeah everything is
Lake
If you're if you start from the position of everything is fake
That leaves you with way more option
Chance to occasionally accept things
If you start with the position that some things are true for instance
Putin
Then eventually you're going to have to change your opinion whenever you change your opinion about
That's no good
Yeah and I say
Alex is so sneaky like
Lenny says like everything is fake there's so many different versions of
Fake videos
Okay well
Because they knew about the
The drugging in advance they would already prepared for Eid was on
This this clip actually
You got me into it interesting headspace
Power
That clip really help me put in
The context why it's
So much less
Painful to listen to Iowa to show in 2000
3 oz compared
The present day
Is there's a presentation of Hope
In 2003 most people Democrats
Tan Republic
Even people who work in the
Community or in the White House
Are good people
It's just a couple thousand villains who are secretly orchestrating literally every terrorist attack in the world and running all government
Financial system
Is Ludacris
But from the standpoint of gauging emotion
Channel States
There's a perspective of optimism that you can kind of feel in the program
Compare that to the modern-day where Alex's shows
F****** Doom
In this clip alone you have a reminder that most people are good people and
And a competent desertion that there's a
A good chance that the world can be saved
Both of these are completely foreign concept to Alec
What's today
Everyone who disagrees with him is a pedophile who works for Satan
And even if
The Patriots are successful the globalists are still going to kill almost every
With a super bio-weapon
Whatever he feels like ranting about that day
Part of the reason it's his show sucks so much in 2021
Is it actively depressed
Not just in the sense that it's depressing that someone would believe the nonsense
But the way the show is structured in the way information is
Conveyed is a f****** drag
I don't believe Alex
Fun facts about courage or honesty
But
I think that he might respect human life in 2003
Yeah
I mean
Here's what I would
Should last
Stronger than Satan
Cuz here's
This is what happened
Iron Man
You're just fighting Obadiah Stane
That's the first movie you're just fighting some other guy it's a real small self-contained story
20 years later
Half of the universe
Has disappeared just like The Simpsons
They're still there talkin about family
And then Ten Years Later is like The Simpsons are going to
The Moon is like because you're just
Can't keep going
The same level
Eventually you're going to have to say that everybody's going to die
If you start out with there's a few thousand people twenty years later everybody has to die
But it's just a yeah I think
I think that
You're right
When it's
I don't I don't know I don't know if it's Universal
So but narrative fiction does have that way of
I'm running into a problem of like what we told the story already what other story we can tell
Is narrative fiction oh that. I agree that that is the
The same problem that I was
What does running into how do you keep people excited
You can have other things like the MacNeil Lehrer our didn't
Do it.
I realized Carson was on the air for a while
There's other there's other forms of entertainment
Have the same escalatory problem
Vn2000 get out
So here is a nice example of the continuing threat of Alex being
Wrong in a way that he will soon learn
Is wrong
Amaya reporting Bass
Therapy
Myra
So we've got these really consist
Some things
Keep coming up on
On every show
Like Putin bomb the apartment buildings and they're putting the bath party CIAA
I empower
I know it sounds like I'm beating a dead horse
Is here but like
Constant
It did not like
He saying it every other minute
These beings are touched
They're both
Not at all
Well once
Just an accurate and then the other one is something that is
Exactly the opposite of what Alex will later believe
He doesn't know it but we don't know yet
De-baathification is beginning
Renault
So I believe I believe her another week or so off of when that conversation
I mean it
Clothes that I believe it's in May or roundabout
Two
This is one thing that is so frustrating about Alex
Is that on that day
That he does find out
I would like him to find out on air and I would like him to do
Deflate like a balloon you know somebody to pricum
And he just goes
Like that but he's not going to do that he's just going to included in some other part
They're doing it publicly to get rid of bath to make you forget
CIA people in there
This is this is this is wild I mean we're on May 12th. I just looked this up and the first
Coalition provisional Authority
Announcement
That
Started the process of two-bathroom Acacia
Suzuki 60
So we're four days away
From
From this as we look at Alex's
Absolutely Wild
I guess we'll know pretty soon
Episode will find out
I don't know
I'm a little bit older than you
Enzo 2003 hours a adult
Yeah I was not as a dignified
I remember the conversation
In about Freedom fries
Forget that one in Freedom tow
Yep
And I knew that was
Was f****** stupid
People
Particularly to members
Republicans in the house
I got mad about
French fries
French toast
Being served in the cafeteria
Because
Of course France had not agreed to join in with the
The Invasion
The Rock and they were cowards
Yeah
It's never not going to be
Surprising that we are governed by children
To Alex's credit he also thinks that whole freedom
Fry thing was stupid for him
Mexico
Old war
You know why they said no they
Cuz I didn't bother internal population
That's not
Great that's not cool I didn't even know there could be a racist reason
Been for that being
Stupid
Yeah it's stupid because
It doesn't mean anything
It's a Belgian waffle even if Belgium doesn't appreciate
It doesn't matter it's stupid on its face because chocolate empty meaningless
Pointless gesture
It's not somehow because of
Racism how is that possible
All things
I think I would rather deal with
Freedom fries on freedom toast
Then someone like Alex is perpetuating the idea that
Did France
Made this geopolitical decision to not get involved
In the Iraq War at that point
Because they were afraid of Muslim French people
Attacking
That's so deeply islamophobic
And terrifying
At the point in his career
When
He has the presentation of
Not being
Anti-muslim
He certainly not as
Aggressively
Things are there
Diving in Clear Lake
Definitely
That's that's the level of
Shyt where you like there's just no way you want
Take it back to racism
I'm just like you know I think
I think I need a new coffee maker
Well that's because of it I don't want to know why it's because of I just
Just because my other one broke
There's no other
There's no other reason
There's no people behind
The really old and coffee
There's no reason to be racist about this
So
I wish that I had musical ability
Cuz if I did
Long ago
Yeah I would have made a bumper kind of Sting
Sound
For the
Alex telling a story that totally happened
Sure sure
Totally happened
Cuz we get we get them all over the place throughout his career at any point you're going to hear stories
It definitely happened
Do me right before you play
Right now
Alix's true story
I have
Where the
Bigos
Incredible
Because we know this is
Steve Steve
Alix's true story crying
TaylorMade
Bushes and conservative weekend
Alex
Please free us from
Soviet Union we were raised
I saw your
Your eyes get a little
Confuse me was talking about his laundry and I was a little bit confused as well
Random thing to do
The time frame is really what was wearing
This didn't happen
So Alex takes a call
At this point
Michelle and
This was that this was interesting this introduces a large theme
That will run throughout the neck
Couple days
One more thing
Israel today that they're going to be doing about
15 minutes
Are you disposed
Take place for 5 days and raised the alert level
I'm told
The martial law
I will
This is a bad answer on Alex's bar but I kind of see what
Alex Methodist drill was apart of
Preparing the public
Look for martial law
What the color was asking was whether another drill would continue pass
Day 5 and 6
Sunday 7 and so on
What the drill be how Marshall all literally started
That was a question that was being a
Essentially telling this guy this drill was the beginning of enslavement
She's really bad
It's hard for me to imagine that Alex misunderstood the question
Except in the case that he wasn't listen
A Tallwood Drive
Totally possible
So I found the after-action report
For this drill by released by The Washing
Engine State Department of Health
This girl was called top off to
And it was meant to simulate a wmd attack simultaneously hitting multiple cities
It began with a bioterrorist attack in
In Chicago
And a dirty bomb going off in
In Seattle
In addition
These challenges quote
A cyber event
Affecting the state's communication infrastructure hit the week
Before
The further complicate the situation a hostile takeover of the washing
Hampton State ferry
And a hostage event
Did Pierce County south of Seattle where included
That probably seems like Overkill
But that's the
As the report
Explicitly says quote
In all the event was meant to overwhelm local state and federal agencies with a goal of finding ways to improve preparedness response
What's a recovery capabilities
The goal was to create a fix
Situation that was too much to handle
You can stress test in a fake situation
Instead of a real one
This buckets not done we're going to fill it full of water to find out where the f****** holes
This simulation taught the washing
Department of Health a bunch
Important
For instance they learned that their radiological monitoring and Assessment Center had no
Reason to be on site
Sunset quote
Became mired in the response organization
Which limited its ability to fully perform its work
An off-site areas
That's a pretty important lesson but probably less critical them learning that the infrastructure they hadn't placed a
Was insufficient to handle the needs they
Faced an
Maps and data tables that were critical to
Decision maker
We're not effectively transmitted given their existing set up which is a huge issue
That they were able to identify from this
Turns out
Turns out using the pony
Express is not going to do it ladies and gentlemen I apologize because up
Another thing that's important to understand is that this is just
The after-action report for the washer
Penn State Department of Health
They didn't run the simulation they were just one of the groups
Participating in it
Each entity that took play part they played different roles
Dissimulation in a face different challenges
Each came away with their own lesson
Their own gaps and planning
That they could resolve
I found the after-action summary for the entire exercise when the Department of Homeland
Security and the Washington Department of Health is just one
47 state or local agencies that took part in the drill
Along with 41 federal agencies
A21 agencies from Canada that got involved because that biotech it hit Chicago
Dammit Canada
I was reading over the summary and there's an amazing piece on page
8 where the exercise ended up teaching everyone who participated about the actual definition
Literally Stafford Act
Which covers have federal assistance
Floyd
It's an emergency
I know we were supposed to read it before it clarified
Definition cuz they hadn't roll places things
A terrorist bio attack
Quotes does not clearly fit the existing definition of a disaster by the app
This made it to the president couldn't issue a declaration of a disaster in the drill.
Instead the Secretary of HHS could only declare a pub
Public Health
They didn't
Realize this
Forecast
From the report quote
These two declaration
Illustrated some of the subtleties of the Stafford act that may not have been
Been fully appreciated before the X
Sure there's eight
Hannah value in art organizations preparing like this using fake disasters to learn how to respond better to real
This exercise was followed by top off three witches
Took place in two
5 in expanded to
Fully include exercises being run by the Canadian and UK government
In
And collaboration
In that scenario they came up with 50
Team scary terrorist ideas
Isn't chose 32 simulator
There was a terrorist release of anime
Plague in New Jersey
A mustard-gas IED attack
Connecticut
And then the events in the UK and Canada which this report.
Specify
And it really pissed me off because I want to know what games are there
This was followed by top-off for in 2010
And as of yet this series of scenario planning exercises has not resulted in martial law
You would think that if Alex's whole thing about other Global at Susie's exercise to launch their evil plans or something had any Merit
One of these would have resulted in something more nefarious than government employees learning
Fingers
Yeah
And honestly
I love
Reading these reports
It's because it's like
This would be my best day at work if I work if I worked
Areas like it would be so much
Totally it's today it's cool
It's my favorite day in school
There was this thing called
Casa in Missouri in Columbia is the Columbia aeronautics
Association
And so what they would do is they would have stood
,
And we would simulate running spacecraft one of the stations
Was
I'm at my memories of this are a little bit spotty
But one of the station's was made to look like
The actual shuttle
And so you're in there and it has no responsibility
Another one was
Command
Kobayashi Maru
Sure
Remember that being if that's a day that sticks out
To me and my head from
Like my entire
Elementary School career
Because of just the excitement of going in like role-playing this scenario of like
Trying to make sure that we
We're able to communicate
Between the email obviously there was
Some curve balls
What fun we had a we had a small like 6 ft tall in
Inflatable Planetarium
You could see the stars
Not quite as fun
No
Noah
So I don't know I I got I got really into
Furious that
The Canadian in
UK scenarios
Pretty document
I want to know what they were facing
I kind of want to see if we can orchestrate like a
Giant National role-playing game where we just play the exact same thing but where
People inside of the simulation
And we have to act
Like we're all dying
One thing that I found
But I actually kind of took a little bit of a shoe
Was Victor prior to this there was an exercise the original top
That one was unannounced
And so people didn't know it was happening
And I would say learn a lot of lust
It's from top off over the years other ones were announced ahead of time I don't know why they would do it on an hour
Like I mean everyone it was
Participating new
Yeah but I mean that happened with the f****** United States Army in Russia during the Cold War there like
Stimulate bombing Russian let's not tell Russia about it
Dumb people
It seems like
Not a wise
It seems like a possibility for
Alex gets another caller in this guy brings up a question about 9/11
And
I found this to be trouble
Holy Rollers
Commit suicide
This is a great indicator of how seriously Alex take the research into what's supposed to be his primary field of study
It's a regular talking point in 9/11
Conspiracy communities that somebody accused hijackers have been
And found alive
But anyone who looked into this of any depth
At all could tell you that this is a simple case of me
Mistaken identity
And the investigative process being judged in the middle eyes
As opposed to edits
Conclusion
One of the men listed as a suspected hijacker was Willie doll Shakira
Released a photo
Made a pretty big effort
Distressed
They have the wrong guy
He is a pilot in Saudi Arabia and had done flight training at the same school in Daytona Beach or the other
9/11 hijackers had
But he was definitely alive Georgia Morocco
Hi I did not fly that plane
On account of I am here
So what
This is a simple case of mistaken identity
One of the flight 11 hijackers was named will leave Muhammad Al Shakira
As the man who was alive
Protected is innocent
The BBC made an error in their initial coverage reporting
But a man listed as one of the hijackers was actually alive
Which route
Technically accurate gave a different impression from what was actually
We going on
If you just live and die by headlines and never look any deeper in
Two things you could easily think that the person the FBI claimed was on flight 11 was actually alive
But you'd be wrong
This is super easy thread to untangle if you
Want to know what happened
It certainly all of this information is fully available
There's a couple other people
People who are named as hijackers who initial reports claimed were alive
Actually we're alive
Like Abdul Aziz Al Omari
Hame Salim alfazema
These two men
I have something very specific in,
Which is that at some point in the not-too-distant past
They had their passports stolen
How has me buy a pickpocket in Cairo
And alomari in a burglary when he was living in Denver
Sure is Alex's of supposed anomalies like those are actually instances
Miscommunicated information that he never followed
Alex
Reporters worker Spiegel
We did look into somebody's coincidences to see what happen
He reached out to John Bradley
Levi managing editor of Arab News where much of the initial reporting originate
You told them quote
All of this is attributable to the chaos that prevailed during the
If your first two days following the attack
What we're dealing with are coincidentally identical
He also made it clear these articles were being written
After September 14th released a list of names
Disaffected hijacker
There's one area where Alex really needs to be sure he's covering
Basis it should be 911
Conspiracies
You can see here how sloppy is work is even on this trademarks subject
Even in 2003 even about 9/11
Can't go deeper than
Yeah
Yeah that
I can't imagine the
Terrible day you would have
If your passport had been
Stolen
And then you woke up the neck
Text Dale
And it was
Is flying into a
Good beats
A real bummer of a day for you
Men
Yeah and so there's this
There's like a combination of a number of different reasons for these mistaken identities there's like identity
Or at least very strongly suspected identity theft
Other
Memphis misreported
Similar names with the same name as a lot of people in the world some of them have the same name
Right
. of time between when the FBI release names and when they release
These photos
There was a great deal of can
Confusion and soda
The fog of
Of course
Unclarity as we see after every grape
Disaster
Yeah this one does not go well
At all
I'm sorry
Are you wearing
Of course I am
Has a
Recordings from the way back
But he has one thing about
Ubi
About
Even before the send it to the trash that it is now like
You would have 2090 spent all this time yelling about going back to man
Quickly became the gossip
A lot of people really like to listen to the gas station
He was looking more for that has call her and made Alex introspect
And
Besides
Well
The name William Cooper has been revoked on my show
I better lie about
Okay
William
Anybody
Here is the ears the issue Alex's totally write that Bill Cooper was in
Incredibly unstable
And I wasn't
He's lying about the appearance on the show that we didn't
An entire episode about how long William Cooper had been
Unstable for probably a bit longer
The last few years of his life fool boy is a lot longer
It's not I think you did get much worse than Advil
Yeah we we didn't episode The Covered Bill Cooper's appearance on Alex's show and
It does not match up at all with the way that I'll Express
Nope
Pretty rich for a guy to criticize somebody getting into aliens later on in life and
Then later on in life
Telling me the interdimensional beings are controlling
The global
No no
Oh no
I don't talk about psychic
You know
The universe was revealed
My prediction of 911
I have dreams that are prosthetic in the middle of nowhere
What a dick
What an assault call in this prison of prison labor
Sure
This is this is
Bizarre
Alex's opposition's prison
In labor might not come from the same place that you were yours or Mine by slave labor
And I somehow feel like Alex Wood
Disagree with me on
I think he agrees
But the reason why
Is what where we get into a little bit of
I saw him
Mark schauder
Thursday a week ago
Concerning
Prison Industries
Putting our small
They're working
For our military
I think
The opposition to prison labor
Be
Putting other people how to bathe
Yeah I would say that Alex is now a union man about 1845
Saying that slavery is great
But you're competing with our wages
It doesn't fly that this
Kind of thing would be okay
Worried not
To jeopardize the
Success of other business
Yeah and I think I don't agree with that the way to put it on an equal playing field
Is if they're competing with your business where you pay the people say $9 an hour
I would
You should do
Is convert them into slaves for you and then everybody's on an equal playing field that's Alex
Dissolution
I'm not sure if that is his solution think that's what he said but I find I find this to be a nun
Thought through
Position
At least a psychopathic self-involved and beneficial solution
It is if that is where his opposition to prison
Labor
A system that is in place if that is where it derives from
It's shallow
Yes it is
It has nothing to do with
The ACT
Making people in prison
For very low wages
Just not an industries that compete with American Business
I don't like this
She might like that anyways this caller is heard about a bill
Maybe possibly
Doesn't run with the belt but it did something
And maybe
Well I just I wanted to give you the
The number of
HR 1829
Did you know to tell you the truth I was waived
I didn't
At Mark Tauscher and now
They were trying to reach
Affected in some way
Admitted against it
They said
At their or ready to go
The government
Building new
New buildings
Expansion of the plan
Bright
So that color had sort of heard something about a bill but didn't know what it did or really anything about it
Someone
She'd heard talk about it kind of was
Maybe into it or maybe
I don't know what was going on there I appreciate
Is anybody calling into a political
We'll talk show describing their political views very similarly to my grandma
Drive the movie that you just saw a couple of days ago in it
Opposite of informal
Maybe
So HR 1829 in the 108th Congress was also known as the
Federal prison Industries competition in
Contracting Act
After 2003
Here's what that was
There's a government-owned corporation
Tim called federal prison in Des
Which is used to produce Goods using the labor of incarcerated persons
I'll redo here from the sea go cost
Assessment of implement
Misspell
Under current law federal agencies are required to purchase products from fpi if products are available to meet the
Agencies
Amazon
I would not exceed current market
Prices
Such products include office furniture textiles vehicle tags and fiber up
Under the proposed legislation this requirement would be reduced
Over the next several years
Have you shared the federal Market that fpi holds for the products and services
They provide to be limited to 20% and 5%
Respectively
If you understand that text properly what this bill would have done is actively reduced
The government uses
The products created with prison labor
The bill aims to divert some of this product
Capacity towards making good
That would be donated to nonprofit organizations
Instead of being sold
The government which honestly still suck
Additionally there were provisions
Thanks for funding of vocational training for incarcerated persons
And funding for programs
To test rehabilitative activities
They could be
Dip towards
Helping
This color is no idea what this bill is in
She's telling Alex about it as if it's something that
Expensive
Open system when in actuality
It was designed to limit the prophets that are Drive
From prison labor
And fold a fair amount of money towards efforts to help
People improve their lives
While incarcerated
In the house it's
Wheatley bizarre to see how split
The vote on this was and not on party lines
It got yay votes from
Steve King
Nancy Pelosi and Mike
Mike Pence
What they all love slave
Got me votes
From Maxine Waters
And Walter no french fries in my cafeteria Jones
Okay one of the guys who did the freedom fries
I am really struggling with the eye
DIA
Text somebody
Rode into a
Bill
Look before we've used
100% slave labor
For our stuff
But now
We want our slaves
To make things
To give to nonprofit organizations
Not 100% but I get what you're saying
Can you write that down and think of that as a
Not
Airparrot find psychopathy
That's why
What do you think Ron Paul voted
I'm going to go with Ron Paul voted
This would have restricted the amount that
The government could have bought from
Their slaves
Right yeah
So I'm going to go with Ron voted for it
Because he abstained promoters
Read cousin screwed with his brain
But he also wants
Private businesses
In the in the time of like polarisation
Now in the present-day it is really weird to look at this in like
Received it being pretty
Mixed in jazz of party at each side
The bill ended up passing the house 352 65 but it died immediately upon being received by the senate in
So
Government
Way to do your jobs yeah
So Alex ends up talking to this guy named Colonel Craig Roberts
The same person is Paul Walker
Craig Roberts
Is a weirdo
Guy who wrote
This dude is super
Conspiracies like JFK
Love's Oklahoma City
Gotta love the baby
The Finders
They're talking about likes
Some child ring
And stuff back in
Good he doesn't bring up Epstein so that's that's interesting so we didn't know about Epic
He might've
It's not proof that he does
It's not something that comes up
Immediately
Although Alex does save
In their interview
Come on
Your father
We know who that is
God dammit
Infuriating
Still could be a metaphor
It's very unsatisfied
That's dark
How dare he say that
Tippy-toeing around it
Dip your balls into Jesus
That's okay
Let's go for it talk about Jesus from time to time
I'm less interested in him being religious
Which does exist
His extremist
Andover
But
The present
But he
I'm I'm
I'm not interested in that
I'm interested in specifically
The
Literalness is Waging War against the devil
Where everything we're doing is
Is a fight against the literal Christ
Devil
Jodi Craig Robertson Alex
Have a conversation
Kind of like
Kind of conspiracy Shore topics
I am and it's
It's
Basis that we've had before interested in a lot of that minutiae
Because of stuff like that
Once they they put laws
You know that
These dudes are being
Super dishonor
About the subject recovering here
For one thing this episode is in 2000
Free over a year before the federal assault weapons
Openspan is set to hit at sunset.
Alex is saying that the band sunset provision had just been ignored which is a lie
And even if he was just saying that they were going to ignore the sunset provision in the future
You be wrong
The Patriot Act was not subject to a complete Sunset Clause but various sections of the bill were
However the Sunset date for that bill was December 31st 2000
5 more
The two years in the future from the point that Alex's speaker
Can gear
In terms of this one it's a little bit more of a complicated
Picture I'm not in favor of the Patriot Act
But I don't think that attacking it from the standpoint of sunset Clause is
Is particularly affect
Reproach
Durban multiple bills over the years that we examined and reauthorized various provisions and amended some of them as well
Is a common aspect
The bills that have Santa Claus's
No it's not like they have a self-destruct
Claws
The idea is to set a date
In the future to reassess whether or not the particular bill is worth continuing
You can take you see with the decision to reauthorize the Patriot Act by pretending it reauthorizing it is somehow
Cheating
Is a silly argument
Yeah that doesn't make a
Both of these examples that Alex uses to make
His point that the bills
Never go away
Their bills that haven't reached their Sunset date
Is it making this s*** up
Now the case of the Brady Bill is actually a little bit more into
The bill was first introduced in 1987 in Wisconsin
Set lien on starter
The Reagan Administration
A all that interested in it
Progress at a lot of trouble with getting it to a floor vote
10 to attempt to attach it
The larger crime bill
Which ended up being a losing strategy
All this changed when Bill Clinton was elected in 1992
And voiced support for the Brady Bill
And indicated that he was willing
Design it if it was Pat
Please change the landscape and Bill made its way through concur
Part of the negotiation to get the bill through Congress had to do with the mandatory waiting. The bill pudding
Place for gun purchase
With the technology available the time it could take awhile to run a background check
Jacksonville 5-day. Was included in the bill
However gun proponents wanted to strike a deal
Their long-standing argument was that provision
Should exist
That is waiting. We made Nolan void once the technology existed for an
Instant check
System
This made some sense given that the waiting. Is largely predicated on the tech
Logical inability to do that
Check quicker
Instead of this compromise What was decided was at the waiting. Provision the bill would have a sunset Clause that would kick in in 5 years
Whether or not there was an a
Check system
Dissatisfied both sides of the bill passed the House and Senate in November 1993
The Brady Bill
Itself didn't have a sunset clause
This provision of it
The larger bill was permanent
And putting plates requirement
For background checks for gun sales made by federally
Stone cellar
In 1998 the mics system was developed in that kind of made this whole question
Kamut
The sunset Clause came and went and now there is no federal waiting. Required for
Sing a gun
Each state has the right to make their own rules on that and according to a recent article from ABC News
10 states and the District of Columbia have waiting periods where it's most
Alex and Craig Roberts are covering the subject from
Completely dishonest person
How to just making stuff up
Craig is pretending that the entire Brady Bill was set to Sunset
What in fact it was just this
Provision which did in fact go away
I understand that their staunch opponent of any kind of gun regulation
Recovering the material this in accurately feels like it's
It's a disservice
Do sincere people who care about gun rights
And it leads me not to take
Stop they're saying all that seriously about any other issues
That's
That's very
I don't like it
I like it also I don't like that though waiting. Expired
Oh my God stupid
At the very least at the very least
Here's what we should have
No bad days waiting.
You can't have a bad day and then go buy a
You got to wait at least until your bad day is over
You know I'm saying like I do I
Understand that position
And I think of it
States
That decides
To pass those things are well within their rights of not having a federal mandated waiting
. doesn't seem that weird to
As long as the background check system is it does work
Effective
Not positive
It's fully operational
And does
Does a perfect job
Yeah I know I can I can see both sides of it
On a state level at
Static
It's fine for that to be where that little more sure I see that
Colton do breakfast of champions law
You can't have a sudden outbreak of a syphilitic breakdown
And buy a gun on the same
I think that's fine
Yeah it'll in a perfect world I would be all right with
Okay good we have come
Optimizer
It's time for you to play the theme song
M4r
Our new Sigma
Alright
Alix's true story
And I don't know
I don't believe Alex's
Version of the story or that it happen
But
Even if you take Alex at his word
M2003
You'd only been threatened watch
I just don't I just don't like that I know for a fact that they've been doing
TV interviews with voice modulators and everything
Alex
Only the government has that capability. No one else has a voice box
There was a f****** vocoder really high-tech stuff
Alright
Only the Fed
Have that
So he's talkin Oz
Craig Roberts
And
This this this clip
Really
Really was a big problem
Underground movement
Oh yeah here's the first real in
Indication that I've seen that maybe Alex
What does think he's up against the literal devil at this early stage in his career
It's still not nearly as overt as he is now but it
Kitten clothes
Being disturbed
Bijou that I run into is the baseball announcer saying he could very well thanks
He's fighting the minions of
The literal Christian devil
He could just think
50-state mr. idiot
It's doing dark pointless rituals to a nonexistent deity
So I regret to inform you that this is not conclusive enough for me to call this
This case closed
If I was interested in the idea that Chandra Levy Viet was involved in a satanic
Sex quotes
This was news to me so I decided
The Poke around
And see what Alex is talking about
This was not a story
The broken the mainstream news and the reason people stop talking
Much about Levy and Gary Condit was cuz 9/11 happen
It wasn't like a medium was worried that people would learn of a secret satanic sex cult so they bury the story
9/11 happen
I was well I mean that was
Look
That happened in the morning
Otherwise it was a slow news day
I'd I would imagine that not a lot of rank
After
Yeah I could see that
Confusing
On the website
A guy named techsmartt
This is upsetting for a number of reasons
Did one of them actually dovetails with this stupid
Conspiracy that I was Raising gear
This episode
Text Mars died in 2019
Credibly prolific
A conspiracy theorist
An extremist
Speaker
Perhaps one of the most
Distinctive traits
Of his though
Is a very clear
Very deep
And very consistent Auntie summer
Text still has a website running
And if you go there
You can purchase audio tapes
Or maybe they're preaching I don't know
Let me to read some of the titles
Oh no you can buy
But I'm not going to give this a****** or his estate
Who killed Jesus
How cowardly lukewarm Christians are abandoning the truth and ripping passages out of the Bible in a futile attempt to appease the
The Jews was that a sequel to who framed Rodger rabbit
Nope
Jewish Master race
I think that sounds weirdly positive Ana
Here's a little snippet of the description of that want Hellcat
Quote First the Romans asserted their superiority then came the Nazis and their exalted Aryan race
Now now it's
The Jews who claimed to be the master race exposes those would be Gods on Earth for what they are
Arrogant power grubbing people opposing God's truth
One click
Another one
Quote Obama tells Jews no more the president finally stands up to the world
Tormentors
What a weird
Staying to support Obama
This one was apparently about Rahm Emanuel even Meeting Street
One of them is called
Famous anti-semites admire
Interesting Lee Ron Paul
That ship BuzzFeed f*** you
Is that one guy called quote
Chimeras monsters pizzagate and the satanic Hoodwink of America in the world
That's that sounds like a
Pretty regular TED Talk
To be honest description includes quote
Jewish scientists are working on DNA that will be inserted into the mind of every person at Birth
Anti-Semitism forever in creating new races that will love Jews
That's almost a legitimate possible solution
For Jews I think they should try that one
One more is called quote should Christians burn the Jewish talmud
No
Now I don't want to order listen to this one but I'm guessing the answer text comes to his
Description end
If text Mars where did the Claret International burn the town mood day would you be there to help him toss these trashy devil volumes
To the bonfire
Also I should do the people burning holy books think they're the good guys
Text point out that his website also sell the bunch
Books about how the Holocaust didn't happen
Including one by a guy named Brian a Lewis Cheryl
That middle name probably a coincidence right probably
Things to do with it
Mars is a giant
Pile of s*** in one of the things those cost
Theme of his is the Judaism is synonymous
With satanism
It's something that constantly comes up in his lecture title
What is just called
Inventors of evil things how the Jews created Freemasonry illuminism communism Satanism witchcraft
Have a New Age movement and what they're up to now
The description of that tape includes this
Quote Jesus said of the Jews
You are the out your father the devil and he spoke
Absolute truth
Historical record is clear
Wow good work Bible
The earlier when Alex
Excused
You know you are out of your father
Little bit of
Making some crumbling parallels
Nothing to do with that or someone like text
Tomorrow is all roads lead back to Jewish people being behind the
Conspiracies that he promote
His brand is Auntie Summit
It's just impossible to engage with his material and not understand that so if Alex
Taking this
Chandra Levy being involved in satanic
Sex cults
Seriously
That's an indication of
Very serious
Towards a content on Alex
Cuz part
.
Text Road at least two columns about Chandra Levy's disappearance and murder and thankfully these are not behind a paywall so I can read
They're f****** ridiculous
Okay what attempts to make the argument that Levy was
A secret Mossad
Okay
An accumulation of evidence indicates that
The 24-year old Levy was a youthful recruit in the Israeli Mossad
That nation's Premier spy age
In that capacity she had served as an intern as the
Executive offices of California governor Gray Davis
An Illuminati initiate
Where maybe where she first met mister
Seconded also a little and Illuminati server
Falls just short of being
Is that a no
Accumulation of evidence
Sore just like
Yeah okay
Text Babe
Are literally no evidence other than his imagination decides that as a Mossad agent
Gary condit's life
Baby used him to get herself access to
Did the CIA headquarters
Bear she learned of The Illuminati's plan to use fake Islamic Islamic terrorists
To do 9/11
And that she had to be killed so she could
Don't Spill the Beans
Wow she's good
Text Butch
Bestway
As horrifying as a question maybe one must now come to
Complete the mind-numbing possibility that Chandra Levy very well may have been
Do a Darkly vicious satanic Force
My response
This is must one
I don't think one must contemplate a possibility
42 text
These Darkly vicious satanic forces are they work of quote
DCs
Exclusive satanic Brotherhood
Do what you claimed literally all members of Congress have
Be apart not that exclusive
When text Mars is discussing these satanic forces you have to be a Monumental idiot to not understand he's demonizing
Some Jewish people
It's really f****** obvious
If you know anything about his
You can just check out his lecture titled
Quote the Jews are preparing a grave for America
Which war
Powerful Jewish interest have a Stranglehold on America
Can government the economy in our culture
We are in grave danger about that
On the one hand
And it's kind of intriguing to have this first step towards
Alex take his feelings about the devil and Satanism
But on the other in much more serious and
And it's a real problem when you pull the thread of what he's talking about and it leads back to another Austin
Austin-based conspiracy theory who believe the Satanism is a
The plot of the Jews it would be hard to believe that
Living in Austin simultaneously
No one
Brought him up to Alex
No one brought this guy up so Alex has no idea this is and this is all coming from his old 390 the text
Has been on Alex's show before
I know that although I don't
I think that he plays as much of a role in later times
I know that the name was, but one of the problems
There's another guy
Who's the conspiracy theorist named Jim Marrs
So like
I know he was on Alex's show a lot
And I think the text Mars had a
Lesser
But definitely they still existing presence
Right
And they both
Created Eminem's together
Good joke
Sorry
I was jetty
I'm really
I'm really trying
I did not expect
51st
Like soda
Fuller Overture towards
Talkin about
Satanic
Forces and what have you
Would be in the context
Of a story that was widely disseminated primarily by text
It's Mars yeah who has a tendency
C towards
Satanism
And stop being coded ways for him to be after you submit
Yeah that leads me to be very worried
About
How much more in
These meticalica Shield may have been in
Yeah it does seem like that I need to when I'm looking at these
Past episodes
I need to be a little bit more
Cognizant of that
Cuz
The question
Could be raised like
With the global
Is he stealing
Obviously effective anti-semitic propaganda
In order to Rebrand it and use what is
A very effective way
To make his own money
Or is he anti-Semitic
And he's just
Camouflaging
That same
Propaganda
Under the terms
God bless
Yeah yo it's it's that kind of appropriation.
Never really been able to
To find definitive answers
But it still seemed like I
Because I don't believe
That anybody
Anybody
Could engage with the work
Architect Martha
Puts out and not be aware of the particular character of anti-semitism
280 Catholic
He's that you just ate a lot of pee
I don't think that you could
For Alex to
Do you know
Seem to take
Information from his wife
Seriously
It makes you worried about what other stuff you might
Yeah that's not good
We we now jump to the 13th
Because this sad that they have such a good time
Dragon Alex
That they just take calls
Chewy
Oregon
And overnight
There was a bomb
Megan Saudi Arabia there's a series of vomit
Sure
Give me the list of suspects
It really could be
So that keeps going
Again
It is a
Really great example of a false-flag effectively turning a man into a dictator
So there's that
You suspect
For this bombing
And
It's just based on
Like he has nothing
ITube demonstrate or prove
This was an anyway anything other than suicide bombing
Feels like maybe it's the CIA or Mossad
Feels like a cat
So one of the things we've heard Alex say in various.
The time is
Conditional
Acceptance
Of Wars of regime change
Patrolling our borders
But you know what can't really argue with
Again this
This is the same thing as
The thing about prison labor
Hits
It's somebody who has the same position as you being opposed
Go to prison labor being opposed to the war in Iraq
But the reason
Arnot
The same
And that's bad
Yep cuz I was conditionally fine with regime-change Wars is on the table just leave him alone
Arthritis bad
Sometime
That's not good to know because if you solve the wrong problem
Then the bigger problem is okay
We can't have a dictator in the
I don't mind as long as they leave me alone haha
I tell people how to live now I should tell
You I have studied everything about you
Probably the only person who really understands it it is a voice against all foreign
Cuz they cuz if you do my dictatorship you'll never have another dictator
Indicative
Of the shallowness of Alex's opposite
And the shallowness of his belief
At least around the issues
He presented himself as being
On the Marquee
Certain
It's really troubling me
Since I can't really get
Past is like
How obvious it is
Listening to this
The even if you
You didn't know that Alex turned into the biggest piece of s*** in the world
If I heard him say that
Back then I'll be like wait
Wait a second you would be fine with this war if you didn't have your guns
Hypothetically meeting to be registered
I don't know
You know that's one of those and I think what it is not so much
That is as it is like I think about going back and watching a movie from the 90s now
And stuff pops up in your leg
I remember this movie is being one thing and now I saw this and I'm like no
That's definitely true. You're going to win
End up missing early like
Skipping over in your brain
Just stuff and be like
He wasn't really thinking about that
He's on the radio he's just talking
You know like that kind
I guess I guess that's true you can also you can account
For like
How differently you engage with things
Based on the time
Can I watch some of Eli
Like Attitude Era wrestling
Not too long ago couple years back and I was watching it
Horrified
Wow did not realize
You go back in here like
Jesus
Yeah so Alex has been
The story the story of the episode is
The bomb
Saudi Arabia
Not there is no
Real actual.
Discussion of it
There's no
I mean there's discussion of it but there's no information that he provides there's nothing
Did you discuss that at the false-flag every information that you get
False information Dan so you just got a
Speculum
Right there's a lot of speculation and then also this
This is what I think is the most
Important thing
Moron
I have to save is a pretty desperate attempt to grasp
Put straws on Alex's Park
In order for his theories to make any sense
Terrorist attacks have to match up with a drill
And you can see here because he's already covered the top off Grill
You accept any event as connect
Regardless of how weak the Arkham
I want to believe about the whole drill thing is that the globalist use Grill so they can have
Plausible deniability
In case one of their plans goes wrong or you know someone involved in the attack
Gets caught
Princeton spell Runner bombing grow when they plan to carry out a bombing because that way they can plan out the details of
The bombing
You can say it's for the
They're also ideas but have the globalist temp
To tell you what they're doing before they do it according to some dumb intergalactic
Contract law
But generally speaking this concept
The drills are used as cover
Precentral to why the
The connection between drilling event means any
Alex's theories about the London 77 bombing rely on a misunderstanding about news reports about
Consultant giving a brainstorming presentation
Do business executives
Where he had a scenario plan
The closely mirrored the actual events
The bombing
That's a thin connection to draw but at least
Is the subject matter of the scenario and the attack were similar enough
They could see what Alex is trying
In this instance
There were a number of suicide bombings in residential compound in Riyadh that were generally known to be
Occupied by foreigners
Particularly West
Meanwhile in
Chicago in Seattle there was an inter-agency exercise going on that simulated
A simultaneous biological attack in one city in a dirty bomb
Another
These two situations lack the primary piece of the hole drill
Conspiracy puzzle
Which is that they're abused
The plan the attacks
This is sloppy s*** and I'm kind of shocked that out to his listeners wouldn't realize this
I can kind of understand buying a hole drilled
Conspiracy when there's overlap
Between the drill in the ocean
And even pretty when you accept this nonsense like now Alex expect
Like you to believe like a
This extends this far
Like these
Completely unrelated and not even
Thematically connected
Scenarios
Seattle and Chicago are somehow
Related
Bombings in Riyadh
Like when
Like I'd very unpopular War
Yeah happening
Yeah in the rock
That is that is probably one of the benefits
It's for him of having
Constant Global News
Is at all times because something is always
Something else that he
You know this is
This is so it's weak s***
It is weak tea
It's
It's always off
I wouldn't if I were Alex I wouldn't even try this
He's a young guy. He's an experienced he's really given you got to find your boundaries
The only way to find your boundaries
Is to Step Beyond
Implied
Alex talked about this a little bit more and my only note on this is that this is unreal
So now the bombings themselves arment
To give credibility to the exercises that are being run in Seattle and
What the f***
No I'm very tired
That exhaust
You cannot eat your own tail at me
Yeah yeah
It's not it's not fair it's not fair either these exercises are used to
To provide cover and
I'm planning for the globalist
Sprite
Or they're part of contract law
Or
There
Not actually what time's the terrorist attack is actually about the exercise it's actually reverse
Twisted around so now that the
Now the terrorist attack
Is providing
Cover for the drills
It said of the drills I mean
I guess the reality is they when anything is fake
It doesn't matter
And if you believe
Like your editorial line for these narratives is
They all this stuff is fake
It's no longer disrespectful to take something like this because
Okay. Position is just Expedia
Whatever is
I don't know if anybody is ever really truly made a career out of taking the path of least resistance
Quite like Alex
It's just like
I'm just
You know he's almost Reach This Then position of just flowing through the river
Bulshit comes out of his mouth
Ride along it behind his self-sustaining
I have become one with the wind
Alex pics
Calls
And he gets a call from a guy who
It's pretty religious with him sure
And it's interesting how
On the scalp
But I also spend my life
Also in description
And what's amazing to me
Tokens
Belly B Tires
Yourself that there's a few others like
You out there
Description
Call Dante
Like you're in the Bible
IMO calling
To say that you're a prophet
Listen I don't have that kind of stuff on my show cut up to
Play 2 Chainz
God damn that is fast
So Alex
Altima 2003 one of his primary
Positions
I am free
Strategies
Birthdays anti-police
Brutality and anti-police
Easy way to look
Above the left-right paradigm
Infowars.com right now
Parking ticket
Obviously this is not something I'm okay with
We should never behave this way and I think we can all agree on the
I just find it interesting that Alex ends up taking almost an entire segment on the show to rant about this story which is
Honestly tragic
But definitely doesn't seem like something that needs to be front-and-center of the show's news that day
Just makes me really sad to see him spending like 10 minutes
Decrying the evils of the police
Killing two dogs
20 Ms later career he rationalized that
Sometimes police are right when they shoot unarmed black people
Personally I'm opposed to all active police violence but I don't
Think like a story like this actually ranks is important news for a number of reasons
The first is that even from Alex's headline you can tell that the city council person is
Upset about this event
To take appropriate steps to address
The issue
Instant you
Can see on acceptable behavior from the police
But you can also
Almost be certain that the victim is going to win a civil suit and have some kind of rest
Katusha
And that's exactly what
Did end up happening
When they settle the claim against
The cops who shot their dogs for $320,000
Monica never make up for the loss of a love Pat but
Me what can you do after the fact
Hold people responsible and
Pay the victor
Even the story that came out in
In the morning call
About this shooting
Prior to this episode that Alex's recording
Quote another cop Who quote
Said he wanted the family to know the constables carry up to $500,000 in liability insurance
Quote we're walking cash cows for a good lawyer he said
Even other cops in the department where they hang
That they needed to do what needs to be done to make things right
Cop reminds me so much of that Kyle Kinane bed
Where is like you know you meet somebody you meet enough you live in interesting enough life you made it plenty of cops
What should your day and every now and again you find what and who's just like
For the grace of God go I was like I could have been working at a gas station or I can hang out being a cop
Play Starbucks better
So
Oh man that's great that cop just being like a man stupid s*** out of it
A lot of insurance
So we have one last clip
Hear it it's another story that Alec
It's a sort of touching on
Really know the details
Quarterback
Orders
What they're talking about
I don't know how
How you doing
Seems like if it's this kind of story is probably should have
So what happened here is that there
Look into taking control of the Texas legislature in the most recent election
And I did include it harsh spending cuts
Andre District
How funny is it that we no longer live in a world where I can assume after you say the tech
Texas Republic
Control of the legislature
That it would end in
In an Alexa
The Quorum of at least 100 of their members actually meet
Vote on things
So 58 of the Democrats in office decided
Just an option
That's a boy copy agenda that they were essentially powerless to stop in a vote
This is something that
And in response the house Speaker has the authority to send
The Texas Rangers out to find them
And bring them into vote
It's basically hide-and-seek
But with the government
52 the lawmakers decided to
Get out of the state
In order to avoid being arrested so the speaker
Acid help from other states
To get them back into chamber
An Associated Press article includes an amazingly did she respond
That's from New Mexico attorney general Patricia Madrid
Who said that she had quote
No authority to arrest lawmakers who show up there
But went on to say
Nevertheless I have put out an all-points bulletin for law enforcement to be on the lookout for politicians in favor of healthcare for the needy
And against tax cuts for the wealthy
Goddamn
Roast battle
Goddamn return to the time had elapsed
For the Bell but it didn't
Matter Governor Rick Perry held repeated
Special session
To push through the redistricting plan
Eventually got a pass
Thereby gerrymandering the hell out of the State House districts and giving a very strong
Republicans
To remain in power
How to pretending that this is an instance of power-mad folks having their political opponents arrested
Sent to the hole
But the reality is it
Part of political maneuvering it's on
Common
But it's not really outside of the
The standard rules set forth by the time
Texas house
It's power-mad politicians so corrupt that they're willing to destroy their entire stay in order
Ensure
That right-wing politics rules the day but it has nothing to do with putting your political enemies
The gerrymandering and the redistricting stuff is the real issue conversation
Texas Rangers
Put people back to vote
Is a silly portion of
The rules of
Assertive government
Procedure
Yeah there's it there is that like I understand that we have those rules but
Like how you have to say like a good shrub New Hampshire
I don't need this b*******
How we reach the end of this boring episode 13th
I got to say
Talk about that bombing
Not a lot of
Actual information
But I think that we
We stumbled upon something
Fairly import
Here and this is living underneath
DC swallowing
The blood of our children
The way that this is
Is characterized
The way
Disorder
I have a little bit of a clue
Leading back to text Mars
Is a b
Troubling
And I'm worried about what we're actually going
Find
Through this fanciful
And seemingly
Fun investigation that you when Alex started
This to
All rooted in
Appropriated or
Exploited
Cosmetic ideas
It's not what I would have liked does feel a lot like that day
Kerry Cassidy
Kind of an anti-semite
Crumbled down and you like f*** all fun things
Just wind up with anti
Semitism
The bottom
Brutal
Does
Seems that this might be another into
Another example of a
We will see we will check back in
And you know what
IPad news
It shows up his act together
3 days of there's a break
Future ahead of them 18 years later he will be on are threatening to eat his neighbor
Goes well
Best lateral cuz he's richer electrician
That's true
Subway
Girls on Twitter
Please find a local charity or bail Fund in your air
Omniome Leo mdzs Cork and Barrel run Desai
I need to think that steak Knife is a fine coat
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work