Damn important I sweat it
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
We are the bad guy
Stripe.com
Everybody welcome back to fight knowledge Jordan
This is the podcast where Selene worships at the altar of freezing
Anybody but Alex Jones
Collaborative worship
Relationship
Mutual
Every well
Today is
Oh s*** that sounds like it's a
The other show that we do you are the dungeon
Master slightly competent does it poster
What do we know about dungeon master
It was a couple of weeks ago I recorded it was a lot of fun
Hang out with with all of the with Marti & Liz
Sarah and you it's just so much fun to hang out
Social things that we don't get enough of these days and
We could have been doing
Stuff like it
Google
I admire
Your effort that you put into that
You know like it with your s*** on your bed but
It wouldn't work if you didn't have a story
No that's true for it that is true and it's just so much fun if you like it you like it that's great but I like
Like it so everybody else can go to hell
You're a you're right but actually kind of leaves into buying a little bit
Do that
Dungeons & Dragons
Ish
Role-playing game
How many got away from me a little bit
And I started I had a few drinks
The white rapper show on VH1
Bro long time it was not available anywhere I couldn't find the actual episodes
And I started watching some of it on YouTube
It's not available on YouTube
Thank God for internet archivist or just like yeah I guess it was a show in 2003 we're going to find it at
Going to be out there
Finale
Brown is
Great
John Brown
John Brown King of The Burbs
And king of murdering slave owners of John Browning
What I say about murdering slave owners
Hallelujah holla back
Well well Dan for today's episode episode number 6 of Jordans xol five-point
Miss to make sure that doesn't disappear I did notice that
Today we are going to be talking about
Nazis in Alien
Stan my God
I will say I will say this I went through you told me that you'd have something that was really exciting and really
You're staying
I didn't know what to
Expect and you telling me that it's not season aliens
That is
As good as
It could have been as a reveal
We will be talking about 1 maybe or maybe not Doctor Joseph
Pharrell
But I think before we do that we're going to need to say thank you to some people
Would you do that that's a say what's up to peaches are nasty plumser Supreme you are now
I totally agree with that to plums
Underrated
Next Ceramics wagons with her thank you so much and I apologize
Thank you very much cervix wagons exact from Texas
Thank you so much you're now policy walk
I'm a policy wonk
Exact
This one is supposed to walk and also it and added shout out
Shout out to basic
And this is the name a few miles I wrote that wave like a dick you're now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much to all
Text Sarah cat thinks about you and I'll probably walk
All one word here
Haha
Tacos burritos and chimichangas thank you so much you and I was who I
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
It is actually a combo
Girl with a u
Girl
And even warble Napoleon mohel
You're now
Money off that heroin
So good
Freakishly large
Napoleon oil
To the both of you
Indeed we are
I kind of lied to
11th Hour
Yeah what happened
See here's the thing
Oh my God have you been dead this whole time
I saw a ghost home in Hawaii
I knew it was too good to be true Dan Friesen is been dead for 17 years with this is
I know II
It seems like just a random vacation psychos overdue
Let's take some time and have
Some fun
The reality is that I'm celebrating a couple of walks birthdays
Wishing happy birthday to Just Another Day
I feel like it everyday and should not feel like they're just
Another Day Another Day special
No
Dennis hastert
Stop Dan Schneider and Dennis hastert in my head okay
Also newt
I got to
Fantastic lovely emails
From newts and dead like to wish nude
Happy birthday
Although you could go with a Gingrich on this one but you should
No actually
That's my grandfather's
Is that right it is his name to me
Is it his birth name I believe it is not I believe his name is Noble
Oh okay somehow they just started calling him I guess
At a certain point in time newt
Was short for Noble
I'm so that's how he goes
Wow how about that I don't dislike it
And also while we're in Hawaii
Come down
Ton of lizards and newts
Chose
So iguana I might come back with a bunch of iguanas
Them holes in it and you're just gonna have a bag of lizards that you're wandering around with
Think that that was one of the most important parts of my childhood
Hawaii was a little lizard was reclaim a little bit
The Plains of central Midwest
The Jordan I hear I hear that we have a conversation about Nazis and Haley
Indeed we do today we will be talking about an interview that Joseph Ferrell gave with
Richard Serra
Who does the conspiracy show with Richard syrett he's also a regular guest host on
Coast to Coast
Kind of the junior varsity guys are just keep track of those guys unfortunately
He's pretty
I don't know we'll see how how much you liked him but
Pharrell
Is
Call
Has from what his
Bio says
A doctorate of
Patristics
From Oxford University
Which is basically a theology
That kind of thing
If you go by what
Many people who have interviewing have given him credit
It's for he has a doctorate of physics
If you go by Ryan
He has a doctorate of
What was it not patristic see that philosophy
Sticky hats
I kind of don't think that he went to Oxford
Mainly because
He has one story about his time at Oxford
And I can find no evidence that
Vista
Saforelle went to Oxford
Harbor there's another Joseph Burrell with a doctorate of Economics remote
Okay
That's possible in his story from Oxford his years there is he was at 8
Debate
At the Oxford Union society that lasted for 8 days
Oh my God for the Ethiopia
Food relief right around Live Aid all of that stuff
And endurance debase
Here's the thing
If this is true
Then Boris
F****** Johnson was there
Was running the union debate society and so we should know
About where they on opposite sides of the issue or they don't know
But what I'm saying is he doesn't mention Boris Johnson
At all
It seems like it would be a headline seems like you would know if 8-day debate with the
The future f****** prime minister of the United
The debate went so long that I had to
Brake pencils and make a little fire in order to keep food warm yeah like Wade Boggs
Absolutely
He also according to himself
Grew up in South Dakota
And what fun story he tells is that when he was growing up he was around six or seven years old
And his best friends
There were more than one of them
Who had
Fathers
Who fought
For the Germans in WWII
He grew up around
Here is the really want to keep
Closer that I don't want to tell people
Tosses it up like
Yeah it's weird enough of that like
Yeah we we do shower Alex
Talks about like being Confederate Royals
I would I would think that like
I know people and I hung out
So we're not doing nothing
Still no big deal
But he is however a scholar I think the fact that he grew up around Nazis
Will explain a lot of his later on his later life
However he is definitely a scholar he's got at least a master's degree that I can
Confirm and he has written a total of maybe
4045 book
Too many books way too many
Here's the strangest part
Okay his first books
Are all about
He translated the mystagogy of the Holy Spirit by patriarch photios
From the Greek and apparently it's a really good translation and he's excited
Writing the forward in in Chris
Holy cow
They also
This is foreign to our show
He wrote Free Will in St Maximus the Confessor which is
Him trying to deal with Calvinism
He does not do well
Bye-bye and then the disc
Mutation of parrots
As well as
What was the other one
God history and dialectic
Which is his final religious
Now
That was published
In 1997
In 2002 he published
His neck
Book which would begin the
The future of his career
Would you like to guess what
The title of that book might be
Well I mean you've already sort of tilted some of these cars
I think there's aliens involved from play
So I would have I would say
That
Likely
It had something to do with space Raptors
Being
Involved with the Holocaust
If you thought that the pyramids were just
Tombs Yuri
Idiot turtles that pyramid is a Death Star
Exact
Really like the one from Star Wars I would like to bring up the
They were
Storing grain guy told me that
He went on an absolute tear that continues to this day
He keeps crying
Checking out books
Some of which
The titles can be
Like that
Grid of the Gods the aftermath of the cosmic war in the physics of the pyramid
Peoples
Not a bad title
Right the black Sun Nazi secret weapons in the Cold War Allied Legend
Hellboy
What's a financial vipers in Venice
Alchemical money magical physics and banking in the Middle Ages and Renaissance
Of all of his titles
There is
Four of them in his early life that are like
I am a good Christian I read the ology I'm focused on this and he's a good historian
And then something happens and he's just
Off the map
Yeah like completely off the
The map
Wind up on the splc's hate watch
List
Because
He is a y
You know that's something that I have been struggling
Because I think if you'll listen to him
As we go along
He's not enough
What I think he is
Is a Nazi femboy
That's
Can be as bad
It is
Weird really weird strange
Big distinction it no one in that I don't think he wants the Nazis to win
But I do think
He's amazed at how good the Nazis were at finding alien technology
Which is a very strong
A subset of anti-Semitism sure but it's there
It's definitely
Well I mean it's so
So he's he's another of the he talks about globalists
Makes the makes a bunch of puns about them he's he fancies himself a bit of a Dennis Miller type
Sure
But yeah I don't know we'll see we'll see how that go
Then
There are another thing there another few things that are
Incredibly annoying about
For instance
He always wears a hat
And it is always
It is either a Indiana Jones hat
Classic English bowler
A little bit well
War I wore a bowler for a little while in high school
People you went to Oxford know it was a
Desperate affectation
Here's one that's even worse
He chain-smoked
Chain smokes
With a Cruella Deville cigarette holder on my God I love this
And he does not inhale
Chainsmokers
And you just pups
The Smoke Out
The whole time
So it's so infuriating to watch this bad
I'm just screaming at him like
I quit
Stop doing that cuz it's so intentional it's not in the picture
No it couldn't be more pathetic
Or or
Use life is art
And this is a piece of the
What will all of
Wolfie
But he if he was Perry dating
The type of
If
He got Kaufman
So say that what happened
After his religion
Just Books and did
Is he was like oh s*** actually religion might be stupid
Create this carrot
Pull-off
A decades-long scam
To show people just how easy and how similar religion
And gizadeathstar really are Andy Kaufman
Do his wrestling toys
Serta stretch
And he's like
I could do this but with religion
Aldi's translating game
Yeah he came across attack
Didn't tell anybody about it translated it upright Ono
Oh no
Satirized nobody else is stepping up to the plate
He's he's a he's a real life
Professor type
But the kind who kind of creepily
Talks to
Antique box with acrylic nail thing but doesn't inhale
So on and so forth
Almost at the end of
Everything he says
It is the most
He's just an annoying
He's just such an annoying
You know what the I mean I say be that as it may
Totally
Interesting like you can't fault somebody necessarily for their
Ticks
Those that you know cliches and no no no problem but after every sentence
But people just have ways of speaking
And so on and so forth
That's fair
That's fair and so forth
So on
Wego
What is going to happen I've listen to probably like
15 hours
This guy talk
And none of it was it all remotely usable little behind the scenes
George Steele you were telling me how interesting this person isn't how much you wanted to talk about him
Dude watch
Hours and hours and stuff
Nothing here
And then
And then last night
Hugo's on rich
Surat show
Surprisingly enough and there is a lot of interesting stuff up there
Also
In this particular interview
Joseph morel
Is
Looking into the webcam on his computer
And he is holding an old-time phone up to his ear like a big old timey phone like
Peach
Which ones that you could really slam with a wire cord the ones that had like that yet to put your finger in and
Then go around the Rotary
It is
It is so ridiculous to watch a man in a webcam holding a
Phone up to his ear I like that
Open house phone that's tacky you should have just done audio
Intel on this
He has a hamburger phone
What is the hamburger yes
And upgrade
Oh yeah
We are going to begin this interview and you are going to hear Richard surrett
Give you some whiplash
If we get there doing the Canada open up they say in face
So the first phase if
60% of the population is vaccinated
Will give you a little bit of your normal
If then in face
Is too if 70%
You'll get a little sliver of your normal life back and then finally face three we need 80
Percent
Evax
I don't want to argue the efficacy or the safety of vaccines
People want to have the vaccine that certainly their business and those
The don't that's their business but
This disk
Level of course
Are we forgotten about
The Nuremberg code and
How can people
Have such short memories
That's a mean that's that's
Very in line with Infowars
What's fun about the I find it so interesting that he is
Reasonable all the way like
You know what if you want to get the vaccine I'm not going to be huge and it's killing you
And if you don't want to get the vaccine I'm not to be like I'll kill you if you don't
You know like that
I don't want to argue the knot
I'm on board I don't want it
I don't want to deal
But like the Nuremberg
Code
Kind of argument is is very
Present
Infowars World by Francis Boyle
Brings that up a lot
It's annoying
It's just them saying hey
This is how
Science and math works
If we have this level of protection then you can do this number of thing the argument that I would
Make back to this I think
Would be like all right let's imagine a scenario where this isn't all fake
For whatever
Season actual
Panda
How does what's going on now look different than what would be the best thing to do
What is
Do you do you do you accepted this
Vaccination quota quota quota or quotient
Is
Appropriate in the case of a real outbreak
Yeah so
That's that's what I would I would like to see a
Can you plan a better
We open the interview and of course we're going to talk about
Covet denialism in the light
We brought up Nuremberg and I have to do is not
So I assume
You got it Joseph Ferrell has some things he would like
Like to say is he happy
Sorry
Pharrell joke
If these
Vaccine
We're so safe
Why
Why are they resorting
Such Draconian measures
Push people
Into receiving
They're not
Exactly
And the answer to that even if they were is
Because of assholes like you were telling everybody not to get them
I feel like they're being like people are being
Pretty
Aware that like
It's important
But like
I don't know I don't think I've ever
Seen anything that would indicate to me like coercion
Jackson
I think that most of the people who I am
In Social Circles with
Have been
Chomping at the bit
Mnf hunted down Vexy we almost drove 5 hours to get you a vaccine
In-N-Out
Vino the CDC had that that recommendation that people can stop wearing masks
In public that
If they've been vaccinated
And that is just a
Measure of
Trust
That's not like everyone must wear a special shirt
Did they only
Only get from vaccination centers and they cannot wear mask right
Or whatever like
There's no course and no
What Draconian policies are you talkin about
Recommendation
Go to sleep
You're totally right
It's always
It doesn't matter it doesn't matter
Especially with this guy
Anyting
That you say
Confidently
You are either right about but
Here's what you're missing
You are completely wrong about and I have a completely different idea
So
Here is
Let's
Going play this is a long clip because I want everybody to get an idea of what this dude talks like
And how
So just see if he answers this question
Richard is going to ask him
How much of this
Is preparing us for a world without
Here is Havana
Well I think a lot of
It is at least in there
But I'll tell you something Richard there's something very peculiar going on
In in Railroad
People that know me know where I'm
Going to go with us
Because my dad
Does a railroad
Engineering
Voloco
Engineer
Text attraction
When I was very very young
And
He got me fasting
T-Mobile
And
Effusive
I've been following
Been happening
With Railroad
This country
Union Pacific
Railroad has been restoring
Steam locomotives
A breathtaking rate
Master restoration
Articulate
Big boys.
Steam locomotive
You know Hall Freight
And so on and so forth
Now
The interesting thing is Union Pacific isn't
Investing all this money to basically
Who created local
Imodium works
Cheyenne Wyoming
Enhance railroad heritage
There's something else going on
And my sis
Station is
That would be
Increasing reliance
Samsung
Will technology
Digital system
Suddenly realized
The favorite
Bozeman
Call Xander
They're precious
Systems
A little thing called electromagnet
Call Thor
For that matter
Kayaking
Colonial pipeline
So I think
Afterglow bologna is also kind of
Hoist by his
Picard
They're trying to put in digital
Systems
Particular
Current is
So what you're seeing
Has pushed back at least here in the states
Be prepared
Canadian province
But in
In several States in this
Country we've seen some pushback
Very unusual nature against
This idea
Digital currency
South Carolina pass
Measure recently
To acknowledge
As legal tender for all transactions
And interest
That legislation
Did not stay
Point had to be to nominate
It in dollars
Texas open
Downstate bully
Depository
And so on and so forth
So you're seeing
I'm very honey
Unusual push
That towels
Made at somebody
At least in
Some of these days
Knows what
Is an
Their act
Accordingly
Secure some sort
Basis for currency should they try to roll out at
System
With her helicopter money
Nothing jobs
Universal basic
Look
Did he answer the question
The yeah
No I forgot what the question
I was going along with what he was saying
About Railroad
Railroads
I think he was
Speculating that
Steven Jen locomotives could get hacked
And I don't know what was going on with that and that wasn't
First and I was I was thrilled to find out about
Stephen Hawking
Converted to digital currency
I don't know what's going on anymore
So the quest
How much of this whole lockdown
It's preparing us
For a world without job
His answer was the railroads a lot of it is at least the way that they say it
And then he goes on for two full minutes about something
Completely unrelated
Completely unrelated I resent this because I'm not a
Cryptocurrency nonsense but I am
Justin the locomotive would you like to know about the local markets like
I definitely would like to hear him talk about about hacking training
Hear it well his his thought and Auntie said that anybody who knows me knows this oh yeah
Maybe it's a big thing of it's a big thing
Hat is a huge thing of his
You know what you know it's very hackable
Cole
He's saying that Union Pacific
Is restoring old
Steam engine trains
Because they know that eventually all the electromagnetic
Trains
Are going to be disabled by an EMP
Oh yeah that actually makes more sense
Slick as a
Coherent thought that I thought it was cuz I thought you was speculating
Lake Steam would be happy
It makes sense that it's like all these trains are digital
Then we have to have these of the backup
These theme
Etsy steampunk
Yeah and then of course futuristic giant mechanical robot spider
Steam engines Olive Back to the Future 3
So would you like to know what's going on with Union Pacific rebuilders
This is from Justin Franz of Atlas
What's Gareth I'll just go ahead and read you the headline real quick
One of the world's largest steam locomotives is about to make a triumphant return
Hold onto your engineer caps
Railroad history lovers
Choo choos that sounds like
This very very simple
6 days
After six decades after the last big boy was taken off the rails
The Union Pacific is rebuilding one of the famous locomotives in honor of the up
Coming sesquicentennial celebration
Transcontinental
That's kind of like a
Tourist
Celebrate
As far as the digital currencies go
What he's talking about is
States having repositories for gold bullion and
You know like certain
State saying
You have to
To take gold if somebody gives it
Sitting right right
And I don't know why
He's bothering about that because you'll notice what states
Specifically he's referencing
They are states that
1 are filled with people who say
Would rather have the state have a gold bullion depository then sending a large amount of money
Do Ted Anderson that would be that would be smart
Sure and then of course with South Carolina and the like
There
Filled with people who are like the
Money is the dollar is going to explode so they
All these laws all the
It's just random ask
I would really love for you to
Sit me down
Weather map of the United States and tell me state-by-state
It's full of
But I know it's
Potato my version of the Animaniacs song
Africa Panama
That is
That is kind of the way that he talks
Oxxo
Pass that I've tried to kind of edit it down for clarity
Yeah as you will
I'm like a guy who is boring as hell
But also
Teasingly
Slightly interesting thoughts
Anyway that's
It's frustrating realize why I was like I got to talk about this guy but he
Yeah
This is this next clip is basically another in very similar stray
So
You mentioned
The colonial pipeline
And the other
The yes cybercriminals
Effectively shut that down
And it caused
Long line up Cynthia the gas stations and so forth in end up really
And about I think a warning shot of things to come
And then Colonial admits that they ended up paying $5000000 in Ransom in crypto
Do currency
I think
We're probably not getting the full story
Hear what what are you hearing
What really happened
What's this really just an isolated
You know what incident
Some
Gang of cybercriminals
Decided you know to roll the dice and see what would happen
Long behold yeah they paid up I mean
What are you hearing a
Okay so
That is the question
Very simple also
Every show that I think I've seen him doing interview on is at least 3 hours long
Thankfully only an hour and 51 minutes I'll save it like a lot of the stuff that I listen
In conspiracy
That that that sort of
Sweeter
I will at least these guys be
Precise
It's
It's not good or all that like
I don't know if we're going to get any truth
Asking a specific question
For that kind of I I like that Richard Surratt is doing a
Casey Kasem impression
We're going to talk about the
You were down south going to the left
Billion dollars and ramp silhouette about you and also
Here
303 really don't know where did that one come from
I don't know man
Trying to think of bad music enter the first thing with you
You could have done worse man
Simple question what do you think is what are you hearing what's going on
Do you have the deer feelers out
Well I've heard they see
The same thing but
I'm like you I don't think
We've heard all of this
Story
And one of the interesting things
What about the colonial thing that
I don't know what house
Was recorded up
Bear butt
The media down here
Fighting
Government official
I'm saying
Affected
This is are there will be more of though
So you
He's citing government officials saying that there will be more of this and all he's really responding to him with his
I think you're about right there
And then he goes off
On a different
You didn't know about
Like that kind of every time you
Introduce something or ask a direct question
It is
Immediate like
Spell maybe
And then going off into whatever it is he really wants to talk
Everybody just listens to him like that's fine
I've watched him talk for almost
10 minutes uninterrupted
And people are rats
By this and it's
Blowing Me Away by people you mean to you the interview
This is not a small thing neither
People like constantly doing all those things that people aren't riding him off
Like 3 minutes in your answer you should absolutely be doing that
So the answer is yes
It'll probably happen again
Obviously
That mean like what he's doing is playing that game of like
The the government is is
Beers like
Hey
This is a new threat
This is something that we can expect might happen again
No need to prepare strategies
To deal with this
Iqra
Business
Like the colonial pipeline
That has like maybe infrastructure-related
Necessity in your operation
Be aware
Presenting that is like the government being like
I do this about happening all the time
Again I would I would ask
If like
This is real
There are these hackers doing this
How is that
Statement from a government any different than
The best-case scenario harvesting potatoes
As a war
What is the differentiation between
Well they never do that
I assumed you would think a that answer is over you've answered the question
Yes probably in a probably false
He is not done
He's not help he keeps going
About a week after that
Story broke there was a
The story about the
The interstate Bridge
Interstate 40
From
See
The bridge was shut
Because they had
Discovered a crime
In one of the tile
I'm at Bridge
Crack
The crack is
Is a perfect straight line now the effect
Bridge shut down
Was that
Barge traffic
Mississippi River
South
Ignored
Of Memphis
Came to an abscess
Standstill
Somebody
He appears to me to be
Working off
Hard
To take down
Infrastructure of
The United States
These kinds
Creative ways
So I think Colonial pipeline
Is kind of a tip
That they're getting
Ready to
Nothing major
Alright
Get it
Yeah
See what happened was
Has the colonial pipeline was hacked
Now what all so happy
And was surprisingly enough very near to where he lives
There is a crack in the bridge
Right
But I mean that the government gave for repairing it was
Pesky barges need to get in and out because it's a massive
Actually
Do you realize
For the last like
The globalist have been planting stories in the media about how bad our bridges are
Subtly warning right
You have to you have to tell everyone you have to give them
How's make a choice
There have been these op-eds about have more resources should be funneled toward
A sneaky
The real story behind the heck is actually really really fast
And if they had bothered to look
Intuit
Now the bridge is not in traffic
Text maintenance just maintaining the bridge I had a hunch
You can turn anything you want into a conspiracy
Theory if you just go
Well they hacked the pipeline and there's a crack in my bridge
The government's working against if you just if you if you play the insinuation game
You can
You can make a lot of mileage
But the real story
It's not obviously they didn't mention any names of the p
People were hacking they were like is it a one-off event or anything like that
This is a hacking group called Darkside
You've done this
They are ransomware master
They have been taken s*** ton of money and then they disbanded immediately following the colonial pipeline
Smart from what people are saying is after they got paid 6 million
The small Collective
The hackers
Disbanded and then just took all the money
The way that they normally work is almost 70% of the money goes to all of these like
Subsidiary hackers who do all of the the grunt work
And and then they take their cut at the end
Not so this time
So what happened
Lights out 2
Yeah brutal right
Nobody
Not too surprising
So this story actually begins before the Colonial pipeline hack
Whatsoever so from technology review by Renee Dudley and Daniel golden
On January 11th antivirus company bitdefender said it was happy
Happy to announce
A startling breakthrough
It had found a flaw in the ransomware that a gang known as Darkseid was using
Antifreeze computer networks of dozens of businesses
In the US and Europe
Companies facing demands from Darkseid could download a free tool from bitdefender and
Boy paying millions of dollars in Ransom
That's a great thing right it's a good idea now damn
What should you do when you find a
Flaw in a hackers
Kroger
Wait who am I am I a hacker your job is to protect people from
So you find a flaw use your brother trying to patch
They did that
They fix it up
Okay
Here's the problem
They released it
As a
Public relations
And within
12 hours
Darkseid
Was like oh they found a hole in our software another hole it was over with
Bitdefender has
Basically and this is happening over and over and over
Constant back-and-forth
Well and here's the thing though
People who are good at
Don't tell any
And all of these antivirus scammers
I basically announced the moment publicly like hey
We fix this that hackers can no longer get to us
And then 5 hours later
It's all
Write all of these antivirus
Company
Are trying to get
The positive
You know like look at how great we are aggressive we fix this to their goals
You got it
Continue to go on
There's a bunch of really kind of
Interesting little details here are intent left a Chicago cybersecurity attorney
He is he consulted with
10 companies
Attacked by sharks
He said that
Darkseid's representatives were shrewd bargainer
If a victim said it couldn't afford the ransom because of the pandemic
Darkseid was ready with data showing that the company's Revenue was up
Like they had all of this already
Hackers
I'd like to refer you to the accounting wing of our hacker Collective
And not only that but they have this like
A half way we're only
Attacking corporations that we know can Robinhood contact
And yeah they even came up with like
Actually we do know how much covered it has impacted your bottom line and we have adjusted our Ransom
Accordingly
Even if you don't want to pay the rent if it's like God damn it they make a lot of sense listen we're not heartless
Cracker
So what wound up happening
It is
Darkside just
Blue ever blue them
Away because bitdefender is
Very very stupid
And they're going to continue doing
It's just
How it goes
And all this bear talkin about
Like always
Conspiracy are these Rogue actors or anyting
If you look into it you'll see that this is a
Hugely sophisticated operation with people who are incredibly successful at all of this and it's kind of
An inevitability of
Like digital progression
A girl like
As there is more stuff that is
Is is online and digital there will be the The Highwayman
The online space
It's just
It's exactly what you would
Expect to grow more sophisticated as
People who would Rob
Stagecoaches
Turned into a mafia
Get more
Skated more organized it makes sense that the inevitability would be something
Been like that
And instead they just
Say they're so boring
It's so much more boring there bad can
Conspiracy theories then
What is a real conspiracy
Yeah I feel like this is the exact same thing that we talked about with like that guy in the ira
You know like it's
Did the reality of it is fascinating and it is a really
Interesting piece of how
Like history and
Like human interaction works
You're turning this into
A conspiracy there's actually more boring
Then the actual
Otherworld
You're trying to fit into your large conspiracy theory
Where it doesn't belong
No just be interested just be curious
It's just not hard you don't have to distrust everything
Exactly
So real soon we're going to get into space
Despite this one I just have to
Saint Michael
Joseph what about the
Halo
Bobby wants to add to go a secret space program I guess here or something related to
Eleanor Landing hoax
Joseph
What about the
The Apollo 12 Ascent stage
Experiment
Crashing into the lunar surface
And it rang
Like a bell for a long. Of time while I don't know that it raining
See
I accidentally cut it off just a little bit early but he is saying
He's got a question from the audience Michael
Saint Michael
He's asking Joseph
Hey how is this pause
And as Richard is answer is asking the question is like they say it rang like a bell
Well let sound
Silly thought I didn't
So would you like to answer the question that I have
Negate
And here is the answer
Thoughts on the
Apollo 12
Ascent stage
Experiment
Crashing into the lunar
Individualism
Actually siding
The languages
The scientist
Reported on that
Experiments that would
There were
Hello I'm a scientist
It rang like a bell excuse me mister cigarette
It did ring like a goddamn Bell okay
Immediate immediate responses just now
It read like a ring like a bell
That's literally verbatim
From the saint
Literature it despite being
Physically impossible in the world we inhabit
Event Event in space in the universe we inhabit apologize
Then
We have introduced space
And this
What is the conspiracy
To hear that
The Moon is hollow about to find out is that is that the thrust of it ringing like a bell
Because they were Beach sound vibration
Sprite is it was Halo
But then I have to have an opening
So
It's Earth hollow Earth but the Moon
So the Moon is a base
Okay I'm putting pieces together
Okay here I'm going to spit ball
The Nazis are inside the Moon
Okay
You're not far off
In fact you're terrifyingly close
Go ahead and this is basically that movie Iron Sky
I think of the early seventies I don't
Remember exact
That was
Magazines
Soviet
Periodic
Probably stay
Set of articles
Bison
Soviet scientist
Actually
Have the feast
Let the Moon
A big huge artificial spaceship
Explain the physics
How it got there doing what
Doing
On any of the natural bottles
4 or 2
Consistency
Capture model
Armored model
I'm so far
So I
Credence to those
The story isn't even to that
Barry because he
It's like
Isaac Newton
Decide about the Moon the Moon
Gives me a headache
Have a good way of
Explaining how it got there doing what is
Doing
I mean the guy quoted splooting
Magazine from the 70's or 80's some Russian scientists speculate
Maybe the Moon is a spaceship
50 years later Joseph p4l thinks that that's probably true
It is it is that
That's the type of thing that we're dealing with absolutely right
There are not
Nazis up there
I mean I feel like
You know in the 70s
To the late 70s
Smite have been after
Particular deathstarr showed up in movies
Looks sort of like the Moon
It's a space station
Biting their time with like doing anything with it
So yeah
The second death star was like
Under construction
Makes sense for like a why it wasn't doing much
They they would have blown up a planet by now or something like the idea that instead
Whatever in Star Wars Aayla
It's fully operational and said they like listen
We're going to have to hang out here for about 56 years and then we'll get to him I swear to God
Right there
F****** move unnoticed
Don't leave the Moon
Not just that but you always need to have like MREs to like a dude have so much food and such
But not just said
You have to then say that the moon has
Always been a space station
Right because everybody is
And there needs to be like some
I'm kind of
Like
A biome
Inside
It has like
Something there is no light source so you can
Like planetary photosynthesis
I don't know how you keep animals alive
That seems like it would be prohibitive
I guess you could have like an elaborate fungus kind of
Economy is true
It could be like a like a lost world scenario where you going
The moon and it turns out that there's actually brush and beautiful burden tropical isle
I think you would still need something to
To give
Like energy to that
That's flora and fauna
Atlantis and Magic
Citizen play
Thank God we're at the midpoint they just started talking about space
And now I'm just I love this clip I just love this
Hey thanks for inviting me into your home
Long Haul
RV camper
Taxi
Your parents
Well-appointed wreck
With a simulated wood paneling
Electric fireplace in the painting of dogs
Playing poker
Your loft beds
Greasy spoon just off the interstate
And your cabin in the woods
Hello to everyone listening in and our
Flagship station AM 740 96
6.7 FM Zoomer radio
Here in Toronto and
I added those of you tuning
I just love it
It just reminds me so much of Casey Kasem here just so much case let me describe a Norman.
Rockwell.
Give a shout out to the only station I'm on
There's something about that that just reminds me of literally a road trip in the middle of the night
Listening to some terrible radio station that you hear that and you like a that's what radio is about
Go to be like junior varsity guys on Coast to Coast smells like that
The reason that I wanted to do space
Aliens are obviously in the news these days
And we don't get enough of it these are these days on the podcast
Now how am I using
That
One question that I was
Interested in
Especially is
Everybody normal now everybody who is not a
Space weirdo before
Is now like holyshit
Government saying there's aliens or something going on here
How is the UFO Community take
Taking this
Impulse life and the fact that the government stole UFO from them and changed it out of
Nowhere just because they didn't want them to look so
It's fate
Siletz
Okay
We have this Tech
And maybe
You know that might explain
These
Tic-tac-toe
UFO videos
Even though the
The Pentagon is saying they're not ours
They're not ours
Well maybe that
Underwater
Well
The Tic Tac videos
You know I'm in all of this stuff
You know you can go look up patent
Online
For triangular shape
Vehicles
Let's use some form of few
Propulsion
What bothers me about
All of this
This is not so much
Too bad
The technology apparent
What bothers me is
The constant rush to attributed
To e.t.
And
Well
I mean that's a thought
Yeah
The guy
Who just
Told us that the moon was a f****** spaceship Pyramid of Giza
Death Star
Everywhere cloning people all Vista
He's telling you
People are rushing to judgment on this e.t. stuff
Yeah
You don't that you can
Sure
He's being real dismissive
And I will admit
If this is one of those situations
To where I've looked into it
And
Z's the
Original UFO folks
Arnaud's
Debunking
The government's videos
Cuz it doesn't work for the stories that they
The folklore of
In this situation
They're doing a good job
The government's videos
Very easily be explained
And it's kind of disappointing whenever you look into the Simplicity of their explanation
Oh s***
What a surprise
Human error in machine error
That's never happened in the military before yeah yeah like a lot of like headlines
Bike
Excitement
Can get ahead of yourself a little bit
That's something that I actually think is really fascinating is that like a lot of these communities are capable
Of decent critical thinking just misdirected attacking their bulshit
Apply very rigorous and solid critical thinking
Skills do your b*******
They can
Yeah
It's just not usually
Exactly
Never done
So that's why I want to hear that Clippers like okay. People are
Really
Eager to attribute this to aliens inside
Yes they are I don't disagree with that statement
Exactly exact
And he is
He is getting he's getting a little bit salty
These days don't know what is UFO information
The idea that the
This was a vehicle
Reconstruct
On the basis
What they had
They had
Recovered from
Crashed
Recovered UF vehicle
UFO vehicles
That
Could be a cover
Story for what they really are
Another is that this might be holy
When product I don't know
Alright I'm increasing
Skeptical Richard
About
Bet Naruto
Particularly from Ghana
Could have been willing
To lie to our faces
About you no mask
Vaccines
Self
Yeah he thinks everybody
Job
What if it's an actual
What if it's just
Buzz Marketing
Put pictures up and they got bomb threats
What attacks been biding their time
Shorehaven up their address America
There's a secret program
To give Tic Tac
The power to create extraterrestrial vehicle I believe it
Terribly wrong
Everything that you think
Is wrong everything that they think
Is wrong and if you know something
You're wrong about it and here's why
Oh and
No
He's starting to get
A little bit
Possessive as well
Are you thinking that the the technology
Exists and it that these are
Made in the good old USA or
Did this technology find its way into
The hands of our adversaries
Russian China
Well I see
Take a lot of it
I go back to
To what I've been writing about him right now to series of books I wrote a book
A few years ago
Ufology
She loves to ignore
Call Roswell
I pray that I never do anything
That the UFO Community loves to ignore
I pray I pray
That that is not a face that I have my career where I'm pissed off
Community ignores my book
It's very strange that the UFO Community is not also willing to toss the Nazis in with the
Roswell Circle
Some of them do though that's true I feel like this guy is being a little bit
I don't know
Salty
Like you said I'm in like
There are that is a
Before it's not something that's like
Verboten
And conspiracy in space
Communities
I have read a little bit of his book though and movie called
The novelization of
The movie Iron
No it's
It's just
Nobody reads my book
Yeah I know
I have professional
Misgivings
About
More people could listen in or
No
No no
You would prefer generally like anybody who creates things
Like we could have a wider audience
I feel like that's what you saying
Yeah but he's more saying they don't
Respect me
So on and so forth
I just love if this is this is kind of fun for me
Just because
Everything is Everything is obviously false
He's obviously had ET
Giza Pyramid is a Death Star
All of this stuff is
True simultaneously
But
Somehow
These guys
Don't take it to a meme place
Like it even for all their covid denialism which is inherently mean and cruel
It's not like they're they're not the type of person that I'm used to hearing sock about this
Where they almost relish
Like that the inflicting of Cruelty or the expression
Great Lakes for someone like Alex
It's less about the point
It's more about getting to yell at somebody
About how they're wearing a mask
He's kind of
Feature of a lot of stuff
Louis c.k.
It's not malicious
He strikes me more as almost a hoarder of
Nazi U-boat
Leica instead of somebody collecting Beanie Babies
He's collected lore
And he's just hoarded
And so
I don't know how much of it is anything about how he
Feels or thinks or even has like
Prescriptions or what we
Do I don't think he takes any of his like here's what we should do
Seriously
All he's really interested in
Is hoarding all of this in
Information
None of it is true
But he's so hoarded it over there you know it's just like he did with
When he was a theologian
He hoarded all of this biblical knowledge all of this history and integrity wants to be the dungeon
Master of
Nazi space
Exactly he wants everybody to Kiss the Ring because he
He's hoarded the most now
That's the way that he operates
And so yeah in this situation it's just
Just ridiculous
Alright let
Let's see oh you betcha
You betcha asks
Joseph how do you compare covid vaccine
Sports compared to the long-standing requirement to have your kids get a vaccine to go to school
Or vaccines for yellow fever to travel
Which is an interesting point
So getting another words why we getting all upset about in work
Stuff about
Vaccine pass
Passports
Right that's a good question
That's a really good question I got excited when I heard that question because
That would be a moment's if that shows up on Infowars where Alex is like
And hang up real quick cuz it's a very solid
Yeah I honestly was listening to it
Got lost
Because it
Boardman
Alright
This is great
Because it's a reasonable question so the only way out of it is you got to take a big swing you know I got really a
I simply don't buy the universality of
Vaccines I grew up
As many people in
States that
Interstate where this
Is not a
Exactly only back
Singing I've ever had
My wife
Polio vaccine
Saving vaccine
I was very young
I've not had
Antivirus
Clean ever since
So it's not
An entirely universe
Experience
Nope no big swing it all he just says I grew up and I didn't have to get vaccine
Except
Now why are we not talking about how the polio vaccine is also evil let's not worry about it he's already had it
Sure that
Does big the question are some vaccine
Good
Right but
We're not going to be
Is that a real I was so disappointed
I was so disappointed because his answers just basically like
Well maybe if I had grown up in that culture I would understand what you're saying but since I didn't I don't care
I wanted I wanted Nazis to be behind
Yeah yeah yeah it is a little bit of
A swing-and-a-miss that's a real bummer
It's a real bummer
Interview with
Conspiracy theorist
Equivalent of stepping on a banana peel
Somebody should have thrown a pie in his face immediately following that
Put a little comedy in
So now we get to some of the things that Pharrell is right
So he also has a Blog
Any post stuff all the way all there
Did you know if you looked at his blog
Driver ed a lot of it does he have any post about have no one ever really dies
Don't think he has post about how no one ever really dies
But
Any Rd
Victor B Pharrell was in all my God
Sorry
Sorry killing me I'm trying to do this I'm not great at running a show and dealing
With references this is what I
After I put up with the from you fly regularly
Screw
They talked about one of the things that's
Joseph has written
Oue posted a Blog
I'm not sure how long ago was too long goat
Discussing some
Rather interesting formations
But you've spotted
Fauna on March 1st
There was some discussion about
Some ice
Top formations on the planet
And that led you to look a little further in and what did you spy
You buried the lede
You didn't tell me this guy maybe has a telescope he does
Because that's enough
Unfortunately he does not have a tail
Talking about pictures posted from 2001 by the Mars Odyssey spacecraft
Charanda
Richard
Set this up
As though this is a very important article
And Joseph is response we're not going to listen to because
It's eight minutes long
And all you really saying is nothing he saying stuff like it looks like it could be
Let me let me read you the
So the pictures that Richard is talking
Saying this article is very good
Let me read you the captions on these two
Quote
When I look at this with my Layman's eyes I'm not seeing much about
Ice floes
And a whole lot of weird stuff that borders on things that look like nearly perfect circular whatchamacallit
Huh
Good you think that's
Good stuff
Yeah okay
The scientists said that the moon rang like a bell
The doodads it what's it called
Quotes
And then there are lots of odd little
Be things
Obstinately arranged in rectangles triangles and so on
And then finally we have lot at someone's lots and lots
Rectilinear and structural looking
Thanks I somebody who'd spend a fair amount of time
Reading
Things in journals
I'm used to things being described as bumpy Little Things
Whatchamacallit
To cut your chest open
And perform some surgery on your you who's it
And then we'll take the WhatsApp and put it in your hole
You fell off
This high place in the problem is that really hard thing inside your arm
Got a headache
I got a crick in your heart sexy all I all I hear is
And unfamiliarity with scholarly writing on your part unfamiliarity with a
Research
Wow that me not to let that does that doesn't
Not sound very soon sound like
Somebody should bring it up in an interview and be like
Now you just wrote this interesting thing and I mean that you have an uphill battle whenever you're starting an interview of being like you wrote
Roblox
Is that alone is
Telcel
Whatchamacallit
Whatchamacallit starts not great
Now I'm assuming you're asking it how is it that they can
Can pay for these whatchamacallits
And structural looking
King things
Okay mister mister Global annoyed as I think he likes her instead of saying Global as he likes to Dennis Miller
Clear it up with mister Global innovator when I got to avoid the global annoyed
There we go that one I got
So yeah so now we're going to talk about
How everybody paid
We were talking about Mars and
And I will be about the secret space program you mentioned Catherine Austin
If it's earlier and that the missing trivia
Something like
21 trillion dollars missing from
The US government
So is it
Your belief that
That much of his money is
Is being funneled into
The secret space
The secret space program for 1
What the construction of deep space
Platforms and so forth
I know Catherine off
Austin Fitts
Block personalized like cheese
She comes up in
Various places
So
She's a former HUD official in the W in ministration
And then when she left
She created a brokerage
Search firm and she started business doing business
You guessed it BH
Now
What was going on is while she was doing the accounting
For these contracts with the HUD and the Pentagon and not
Captain look
It didn't look right at all things are going wrong
And so Joseph is going to tell us
That's what it is she fell
So if we go back
To let's say the Baylor
Enormous amount of money
End of the system
Or did they
I like that
For the bailout
Yeah
We're for like upgrades to the Moon
Siri I guess
Is that if the bailouts happen than inflation
You should have Skyrock
Which
Okay
That doesn't exactly work
But that's fine
What
He is
Completely ignoring
Is that
The 21 trillion that we're talking
Sing about it's not missing in the sense that it's like
It was taken away and now it we could be anywhere right
It's missing in the sense that the pay
Pentagon
By Design
Does not
Keep track of where it spends money
It doesn't keep track of it it doesn't
That you can't audit it you can't
Nothing happens they tried to have
So many accountants go in and just
Give it a shot
Right and you can't do it by Design
Because if you know exactly how much money you're spending you might get less
Well there's that and then also I would assume that there's probably some
Some kind of like
National security reasons why you wouldn't want that information being somewhere where people could
Possibly get a hold of it sure that I would assume that maybe there's some of that
Even then you would have a budget
Right they just have money and then they spend it
So even whenever they're talking about passing a military budget
It's just
It's just better
And they spend money and if they spend more than that budget
The government still going
Nobody cares
Right right
Missing money is is the the same kind of
Single people talk about with like
There's this unfunded
Social Security until
Future exact
People paying into it will pay for it in the future
You know like it's the same sort of
Semantical trick
The people used to Tryon
Argue against
Any kind of government spend
Exactly
Maybe there's more to it that everybody who is looked into it everybody who has looked into the Pentagon budget
Has
Immediately
Like they they open their computer they look at one line and they raised a red flag up into the f****** sky and shoot Flair
This is not good
It's a misunderstanding
Based on like the waves being
Describe
This is a problem for a different reason
Yeah you got it now Joseph has a different Theory than
So I've actually speculated
That somehow
This money may actually be
We going off world
How I do
No sure
I'm in
I just love that
I just love that he does not go on this is the one time that he really doesn't go on further
Cool here's his response
Well I think it's probably off-world
And I don't know how it got there
Now I should say for the mechanical this
I got no idea
Write a gas but I will say
That I'm just
Literally just saying
I might be in that empty Moon up there I would love to be the guy doing this interview
Cuz my response would be like oh you speculate
Google
Oru
Interesting I'm speculating that money stayed on world
Now what
We have reached an impasse
Just agree to disagree
Yeah I mean it's just
It's just that so often
So what he always has money in space
Moon rocks
No no no it doesn't mean anything
No Intergalactic treaties recognize money
All right otherwise how could we do business with bet if they don't recognize our currency would suggest we don't
Please go on
Yeah and so that's it
Exactly
What Joseph does
A with ever
Specular
Yes the only difference between that clip and what he normally does
Is the trick
He uses of being like
I'm going to flood you with names I'm going to flood you with information because he's an incredibly knowledgeable guide
Right
Hits you with so much references
All the time
That's people skip over the fact that most of his response
Questions
Are essentially
I'm speculating here
I don't know anyting
I might be making this up
Totally
I need stitches just mind-boggling how
Popular
This guy really is
It's not cuz he's boring and he doesn't have anything to say
It doesn't seem like it
And then this
I believe this is the last clip because I just couldn't do this after
Do
One of your blogs recent blog
Books on Giza Death Star, this it's entitled how to get that
Precognition
And
As you point out it's a it's a wild article
I guess someone
Shared with
If you want it it has to do with the scientist
Has to have discovered
The heart and brain
Can respond
To future events obviously beef
For they
Appen
Tell me more
Well I find that very
Because
The present of physiologic
Okay slip
The structure in the brain in the heart
You have a very very
Somehow
Represent or
Mirror
The fabric of
The universe
And the reason I find that very interesting is you can go online
Pictures
Galactic
Clusters
And what they say
Tank RV
Plasma
Nostrand
Connect them and then
Compare those
Actual neural
Mapping of
Neurons in the brain
Have a remarkably
That's that's what I was I was listening that just going
Supposedly
I'm supposed
To take you as an authority on this
And you're telling me your response to precognition possibility
It's to say
Look at the pictures of the stars and people similar
Yeah maybe we are little
Little bugs
Is inside a brain is like their Universe G another person
Fine man but come on
Come on you're supposed to be the expert in this s*** and you cannot come at me with
You know they look alike
Sure it's so disappointing to me and I just can't handle it I couldn't handle it past that point I was like I've heard too many times you
You just go do it looks like a whatchamacallit
And then be done with your with your evidence my head up I see the Whatchamacallit and it looks like a doodad
Is probably true or not or whatever
It doesn't mean anything no
Keeps
Getting listen to as though he's Authority wearing his
Indiana Jones hat
Cruella Deville cigarette
That is naughty
I feel like you shouldn't be mad at the hat in the affectation
Those are kind of
The Charming
Do you think that's why you keep get invited
Probably talk to him
I might be true
No he's he's
Not interesting enough to trick you
Don't think you'll need to worry too much about that
How so
The Camelot
He was interviewed by not Carrie
Oh by Bill Ryan
Okay member seeing that okay
I was going to
Talk about that was less fun
Boombox
That was
Not good it was done in a weird hotel room that like a Motel 6 yeah those there early aesthetic
Yeah yeah
Soap that is Joseph p4l
The possible doctor definite shitbag and mediocre writer
Nazis did not factor into this as much as I expected
The problem with the Nazis is that that is his like
I guess
Mid. Work
Haha like now he's more into
Pixar killing everybody okay and
It was about 10-15 years ago
That he was
All into Nazis all talking Nazis all the time before the era of podcast
Lot of available audio
Sorry.
Tease but I do know what
Whenever
We never need more.
Next to nothing so we could probably ask them sure
I bet they've got a lot of mouth
Oxycontin
Well this is interesting Jordan I thought it was fairly interesting I thought he was an interesting guy and I thought we should talk
Thanks for bringing this to my attention
I hate you will
I guess I think we will but until then I'm pretty sure we have website
Knowledge freight.com thought we might have been on Twitter at one point
I think if you wanted to
You got it
Bye-bye and as always I am neither Neo
Leo
Dzx Clark
Ordered a reason at all
And now here comes
What the sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color