Damn important swetik
Pray I have great respect for this knowledge B B I'm sick of them posing as if
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Lean and talk a little bit about
Alex Jones
Jordans
Uforia what's up
My bright spot today honest
Leslie is a little bit of getting back
To it yeah like
Getting back from we went on a vacation to get back to Selene getting back to
Work getting back into a little bit of
I think I think one of the things we took one of the undervalued or under respect
Thought about elements of vacations are how much it makes you like
I don't know my day-to-day life is better than nothing
I think it is reading Terry Pratchett while we were on vacation and he had a really great quote that
I was like
You've never really been anywhere until you get
You know until we got back I was like that's kind of
The silly thing to say and I kind of get it
I've been on vacation it's been a long time
Experience over and over again
Everytime you go on a vacation to your life is probably in a different circumstantial or was the last time we're sure it was nice
22 come back
And
Take a break
Now I really want to get back to work I think there's some things but we're dangling
Threads
Do not run into any lizards
Having perception in my head that there were lizards everywhere when I was okay to maybe it's because I was a couple feet shorter and closer to the
Grandma I can just see them everywhere
I did not catch any Wizards
Got blisters on my feet the first day we were there so I didn't clean up any Kohl's
My childhood home has been torn down and turned into an apartment complex
It like that
At least it wasn't a convenience store
Lovely time
I'm sure you know I have a hard time finding anything similarly
To you you know it
I feel like the vacation was great
But my bright spot was
When we got back
My dogs were still staying with my partners mother
Hey and they got back today
Send it.
First time I saw they went so ridiculously called
How did I ever leave these beautiful things
Pittsburgh PA
That's love bajor gone for a week
This is what it's all about me
Yeah
It's fairly similar with a lot more yelling
He's yelling at me quite a bit
I got some snuggles and some aggressive headbutt
Eventually
But as I was coming up the stairs with the luck
Has to teach you a lesson before they can be as hell but it wouldn't have it any other way
River difficulty ahead of us and that is kind of like we missed a bit of time
And so also
Some stuff happened
Right when we got back
And it's very relevant to our our our business
I didn't really know exactly what the strategy was going to be in terms of
You know do we go back and listen to all of last week's
It's a little challenging at
Spoiler alert to email
Yeah I mean
Buckwild on this
Since the time we've been back
I haven't had enough time to read all of
It's like 3,000 pages
Jesus
It's okay it's their boring emails
Doing this I'm not reading business evals you know I thought that to myself a whole bunch of time
Because
Most of what I read so far is
Talk to you forwarding something to another person
Nonsensical email to him and him not responded
Stop the time I'm looking around like
I've been next email is going to be like we're going to need to refill the toilet paper in the lobby
How do I clear my cache
So I haven't I haven't gotten the full enough
View in and just like everybody else I think it would be almost impossible I don't I don't know
Unless you had a team reading them making chunks or whatever
To get through all three thousand pages in
In the time it would take the
Multiple Outlets working on that priority but at the same time
To be able to do some like really current stuff for Monday
Through a narrow with a dartboard
Started the arrow board whatever
And May 27th
Thursday of last week came up Thursday and Friday
Thursday ended up to silly and Friday's off the tables
Yeah here we go we're going to do May 27th 2021 budget
This is going to do is going to be at
Alex is very sick
Let's not overburden ourselves with like
Something that's going to be
All day
Nobody wants to come back to the office the first day and really deal with that stack of paper that built-up you know
Pupae has to be taken care of
Sure but not today
So let's take a moment to say hello to one walk and then introduced
A new develop
So I think it's much better but his National discourse thanks to Alex
Most of Germany
So Jordan
Yes sir I have decided that look Lee's birthday things
They never go anywhere
So
I have
A new drop
Okay alright
By the introduced
Birthday tie
Someone wife is giving someone death
You can say that
Time to get some Happy Birthday shout-outs to poke Sarah
You never fail to impress me you never fail to impress me
The first ever got touch with us wanted to wish you Happy Birthday
Also like to say happy birthday Sean Stalin Stritch Maher start his bring glory to the emperor and justice
Okay I'm back at it
I had a 30th birthday
Basil
Send me your bagels not very sure I think that I have been told how to pronounce it and I refused
I think when people tell me how to pronounce things
I-88 like 8
Death
Dueto America is it's our god-given right to ignore British
Pronunciation
Congratulations
Upcoming nuptials
Cindy Bob thrilled for you
And then finally coming up
On the 5th I guess that's this weekend
The Saturday sure Frank Adams got a birthday
Almost over for happy birthday Frank the close of the happy birthday shout out
Giving someone life is giving someone death
You can say that
Life is death
Felix
That's going to go down in the rake affect Hall of Fame
Two episodes from now we're both going to be like Addison
Adorable 85 episodes from now on
Continue losing my s*** every tough we will see
Alright
Alex's
Some strange mood to give you a little bit of a
Oh my god did I get hired now cuz that was fake
That is fake
I do kind of feel personally offended by that last that was Pillsbury Alex
So this is where I actually got on the hook
Sometimes it takes me a little while when I start up an episode 42 be like
I'm blessed that you are
I got on the hook immediately
All eyes I have been brainstorming lot of it
Thank me to do this
For a lot of it you're not going over
I really just think it's important I cut
Right to the chase
Watch out yours coming up
Today
Get to it all
Soap for my ears I hear this is Alex saying let's go through the b*******
Outlook
Shoot Straight
Finally time
Some of this stuff I've said before some of it I have not but it will all be
My hands to God's ears
Call will be revealed in the fullness
Yeah you're saying that like he's been on air
420 years ago
That's not actually true
Sounds like it might live before I just got hit
Weather
Extreme Clarity of what I was doing
Knowledge information we have interest
Vision but the brilliance
Computer program
That's been working on a problem working on the problem
And then suddenly it's completed the problem
With the computer
But completion of the buildings
I mean answer come sliding out
It was just a whole nother level
Exactly what they're going to do
How they're going to do it
Hauser operating
Okay so again Alex has had a Moment of clarity
Every single day this is the first time in a long time that we have taken some time off
Alex has it
Part of me is like
I wonder what he would fix this like I got free rein now I don't have to worry about you
Parents aren't home
Jordan are listening to speak freely
Countries of Asia
I wouldn't think that was what was on his mind
Sure
It sure was
Hit by now at 27 years he's realized it recordings
Yeah it's just I can't stand this a****** every single day having a vision
Oh my God
It was like finally all the pieces connected to play so you can't do this everyday like I do like that the computer
Thinks it's going to be over sooner at but unfortunately the computer took a little bit longer than it was expect
Hey man I mean you're joking around about that but I have
Has been in a situation where let's say I am downloading the game PlayStation Network
And then what
Check back in 40 minutes
Computer think all of these computers
Tell you
What they're thinking and it turns out what they're thinking is
It's it's terrible you know.
Do robots dream of
Being late
For work that's what I was
Yep yep
Do robots dream of
Excuses for tardiness
Here's the deal
I think this is what Alex's Vision or his new bit of
The clarity is about
To do with the globalist
And their new plan
My town for this cuz it's on
It's absurd
What I wrote
Right after I
Is
On screen
Send it transmission
The scientific
Dictatorship control
Toolbox the great lie
The greatest of Lies
That is too obscure
The great truth
That is
And that is our human psyche
Piercing the Veil
And
Connecting in an even stronger way with God
And basic
Telekinesis
Application trying to suppress
Okay
Alright
Figured something
Write in order to distract from the fact that we've connected with God and now we should move objects with her mind
That's correct
Here's my problem
Here's my problem alright we live in the future
So I know that this is fight
Him saying that the real goal
Is mass telekinesis
The next day you can be like fauci release
Females
Hirelevel
If you've got mascot telekinesis on the way
I want to be clear about something to because I'm not an idiot I know that he means telepathy
Of course humans like a connection
Speak without
Speaking so right right
He means but he could have
That's like I can pick like Isaac Asimov like all the sudden our brains just grow a little bit bigger in the right spot
Course we can move chat with our minds and I know that it is but it's
Already have mass telekinesis everybody knows it
And
It's not just telling
Kinesis with each other
Obviously obviously this is getting a lot stronger
Course reason
Genetic
Development
Fox's the environment what whatever it is
The globalist know this they want to control it
I want to keep
The public from understanding
Alright
Can't get over him saying telekinesis at 7
Obviously women have it stronger that's just so good
If you take him just literally at his word.
You're not giving the generosity understanding like amines telepathy
Like it's telekinesis but not
Just with each other like we can only lift each other
Of course
Bug
So I think what Alex is going to get
2 I think
The point he's trying to make is that humans have this telepathic
The connection because of
Connection with God and
The globalists don't like that
They want to control it in order to control it they're going to come up with a big lie
And I think the big lie that he's going to say
Is alien
Therapy to be review
Because he says this
Send
I mean this is just childhood's end
This is really good
Just the book
The difference lies that they're going to launch is going to be
Alien Transmissions first
Chileans are going to be communicating
Alien
We already had contact and they gave us technology
That's really where all this came from
All the upheaval in the popol endorse it and say that's our God
This is our group that is what they want us to do
You just got to accept and do the entities one
That's just the plot of childhood's end
We come down say that we can't reveal ourselves for 50 years until you're used to us being
Look like
Harkins option of the email
No the only person who can break through the illusion is obviously Rowdy Roddy Piper
You know naturally that's the way it's got to go Our Generations Rowdy Roddy Piper
So the aliens are going to come down
They're going to give the pope all these
Messages
I'm not going to reveal themselves because they didn't in the book
Still in jail in this scenario
Flummoxed
To be fair I don't know if Alex is talking
Deceive
That's not a problem for him at
Also the plan is then once
The pope is doing all this stuff and telling people to have to listen to the aliens
In order to get this technology
Or something
Then
Leader
Who is able to talk to them and if you do what he says
Everything's going to be okay
Will learn
That this is one of the scenarios
Different ones at different times are all at once
Aliens coming and we got to do some certain things
To stop them
So there's this bad alien
A f******
Non Pleiades I'm not f****** around with just a lien anymore
Kind of animal do they look like
What are we talkin about need some specificity in order for this to be any fun
Do this better
I thought the plan
Was Plan B and they're just going to give us a bio-weapon
In order to kill everyone off why do they need to do that
Theater dad about patch
Give people to show its bread and
Circus man
Everything you blow about
The globalists have a plan that was direct
Do them by the devil that involve the super bioweapon release little kill off the population
Why do they need
Bacon alien landing to get people to do things
Precor living in at Galax
Sick Make-a-Wish scenario we're all about to die so aliens are trying to give us a good run before
It makes as much sense as anything I was just saying
I don't know it doesn't does not make sense
So I guess
That's the
Big Revelation that Alex Adkins
Restarts the first
Yep
I need some other really big news that he under sales
This is huge.
Frankenstein mad scientist chopping different pieces of human running
How high powered electricity through it
Reanimating a corpse
Well now they're actually able to do things very very similar to that in the real world so many times
What humans envisioned
Hundreds even thousands of years ago
We are now able to Bill
On a mass scale
Comes with all of that
Sure yeah death
Well only a little bit see what has to happen if you have to play music and then the body will be kind
Ambulatory in a kennel little Dancy way
Towards the source of that music
Sure there's a Weekend at Bernie's 2 scenario okay pass that it's a Weekend at Bernie's
This is really kind of like the evolution of human technology
Well I mean
Dread alexina
Maybe
Seems a little bit like it yesu Frankenstein is real
Cool
I don't know where the bottom is in Turkey
Like they're just think what I can say is a joke that she thing
Actually he actually is suggesting the universal monster
Kind of
Area you know he's already got Dracula's right
He's just trying to
To create the monster
He's just trying to convince people that that graveyard smash is real
It's the Monster Mash
Gunby
Everyone dies
That's the month
Monster swim
Was the second one
Ticketmaster Tuesday is called the monster stock market
Crash stock by God damn it I blew I blew it
There is a certain to get a follow-up cuz monster swim
That's true and then
Years later he had the
Climate match
None of them worked out except for the Monster Mash Cisco had done just like various colors
The Thong Song like black songs about dog that just released one next month or something about a negligee
Beautiful
I could see him doing that but I watched that making of the song video on YouTube there's a there's a
The documentary series
About these these
Squeeze hits
I like how they came to be and I saw the part about Cisco's the thugs
Erudite
I could see him making the series of songs about different undergarments everything else
Does it work to give it a go
Silences little bit
Stem cells
Paint by numbers
Art stores like five bucks and it's got a little
I just been here on a 27 years researching
What you got to White River levels
Stem cell
Spell means a
150-lb humanoid
Human
Chimpanzee clone that doesn't sound true
But I could be wrong I just don't think so
Nope he doesn't paint-by-the-numbers and get the green unicorn
Pretty numbers are wrong picture
Look like
Brown
Yeah but numbers is ostensibly creative
Because there
Do you want the extra there's numbers
Didn't know in the abstract it exists
Without you
You can just imagine that those colors are already there you're supposed to
Adult you can usually tell what the picture is even without color
Open there before
Sunnyway chimpanzee humans
150 lb in a kg
And this is important
Because there was just that bill
The way through Congress
Rules on stem cells
And some cells are defined as
Tissue
About stem cell
We're talking about is growing human or humanoid
The definition
Better
Video this
Here's the article
48 + 49
Defeat Braun
Bubble Indiana
Certain types of human animal
Sixty votes were needed
But it didn't pass
So did you hear that is legal right now
Human-animal hybrids
Against human
There's two things that are going on that I was just kind of playing with
Conflating
There's one is the bill that got defeated in the Senate
That was an attempt by the GOP to criminalize genetic research that involved creating embryos that work of Merit
And from what I understand good thing that did not pass
It seems like
It was a little bit of a trojan horse
Something about a boar
I know it always goes back to that
He's complaining this with is a recent movie that was made by the international Society
84cm cell research
They loosened their rules about how long a human embryo can
Can be used in
Experiments
Previously that a standard policy that studies the Wimpy on 40
Some days would absolutely not
Be done
Isn't technology they say that these experiments
Could possibly done
The quotes that moves quote
Only if
Lots of conditions are met
We're not going to suddenly have horse people drawing our cars around that's we're going to be fine
The house is freaking out about these
Chimeras
And what have you
And that leads him to go to break
Extreme
Pretty extreme
They're figuring out how locked out of
So they can kill everybody
Everybody stay in your houses
Well that happened
What combat robots go up and down the streets and so
This isn't
Something that they are
Just thinking about doing this is all set up very very soon
You and your family will be killed
2 years 50
But if we don't hold him back everyone listening is dead
Okay
They're going to kill you they're going to kill me
Kill Everybody
The bad
But you a certain extent you know
We live in kind of a fairly mundane world
When we go from that to like
Oh there's robots in the streets and chimeras in my home I think that would be at least a little bit more
Exciting four days ago I was having a fun hot dog and on San Souci Beach
I come back and I got to hear Alex saying that I was dead
Dead
It's a jarring
I do see your neck Juliet a 45-degree angle right now so that
That might be trouble yeah it's it's
Some
You know what this there's that that standard think about like we know if you just keep moving
It's not hard
To keep moving. Then you start moving again
Object at rest
Obviously
Bullshittin everything
Troy
It's a little bit after a week was not listening to him to come back in here like
You and your family everybody listen to the show will be dead within five years if we don't stop my enemy.
It's comically over
What I take time off
I start to doubt myself these like
Alex isn't as crazy as I think
Cannot be real not like you says within two to five years everyone listening will be dead
No it makes you realize how many like
I totally get
When you're when you've been doing this non-stop for a long
You know you forget how real people react
To do this kind of stuff
You're the one who's a conspiracy theorist there's no way that anyone would get away with that
I'm Atkins
Spirit appears this can't be real
This can't be real
So
Hurry hurry
Discuss this neck
Let's see
The globalists
Sprite
They plan
Heard it
At least two
Super bioweapon kill off
Maybe that's
Plan A and B plan C involves aliens coming down and not revealing themselves
Telling us that there is bad aliens are coming we got to do something in order to stop about aliens
It'll be counterproductive
Give.
Yeah I heard that there's a plan d
What humans can envision
We can end up building
What we've gotten to this point
Is
Free energy
Active life extension
Supercomputers way more powerful than what you're currently even aware
Exist
And the decisions have been made
To basically go ahead and go operational
When a system that will make us obsolete
Obsolete in their works
Computer won't recognize Beauty
Is computers won't have our ancient history
These computers didn't create the computers like we did
Okay
Force pushing this and in my life
The whole show up and I just made this very
Very simple
And that's
Alex's talking about robot
When I hear somebody
The politics but Alex has
Worrying about
We are going to be replaced
Kind of
You know it exists in a certain linguist
Space
Yeah you know
The way he's talking is like a person in like the early eighties who is like
Computers at the Devil
You know the computers are going to have a safe trip
But we don't live there he uses computers all the time
He lives in a world where
Computers are perfectly fine and people are evil
You know
Keep the people he wants to tell you are evil letters are ethically neutral
Yeah
I don't know I just get I just get a little worried
Fears of replacement are generally not
They're not good opening
Well you know what it what comes after that is usually bad
It's a little bit like a little bit like the space races and we deal with where it's like they're evil cat being
But you like it that's code for something else
The great replacement Theory you can't just be like
No no no it's
Computers that were worried about I'd not have a be like
Is this juice again I feel like this is using
I know that doesn't really care that much about workers right so it couldn't really be a conversation about like automation
Tune in the workplace
We need more gross
I don't know it's just
It's a word that I don't like hearing
Zoey 101 more thing here about the global
Okay
If you don't resist this
Under survival of the fittest
And social Darwinism
You
Deserve
So it's all about humans being a commodity
Mass smuggling of children
For sex abuse
For slave labor
But really
It's about
Committing crimes in God's eyes
Having you do nothing
Spiritual hedge
A protection can be removed for mice
Everyone can be a
And so this is very sophisticated
Interdimensional du Lac
Warfare
Hellboy
Tough tough to wrestle with
Isn't snow it's not be so confident I feel like I need to ask
That's part of the trick
That is true
Yeah so the first thought that he has there is a globalist believe you don't fight you deserve what happens to you if you are
That's essentially just so many crib from
Quiet Wars
The first chapter and Bill Cooper's book Behold a Pale Horse
Leave your meat on the
Play Future
Meant to be
And then the second part is just that like if you don't
Defend
God's law
Then you make us all susceptible
God's punishment
Which the only thing that could
Really lead towards
There's a fiacre
I mean
Yeah yeah absolutely entirely around it
Too strict religious rules
You do
It's not the ones that are the religious rules are really great when they're in power and allowed to kind of go under
Everybody knows that from history
Are you just cured nonsense
Gary
Interdimensional Collective
Play that's true
That's the closest to Lake
I'll let it slide
It's arguably hyperbole
I mean I know you
Not speak metaphorically
You could hear that and be like okay whatever
Contextually weird
I don't
If Alex believes
That doing things that are against
His religious rules
Make everybody
Susceptible to God's Wrath because God removes the hedge of protection
Then the only way to keep everyone safe
Is to make sure that everyone is forcibly adhering to God's rules true according to his version of God
And to me
I find that to be an incredibly f*****-up way to
To conceive of how
Society should be organized
I mean V ironic part about it I think is
Something similar
In practice
Is what we all try
To-do defeated disease
To certain extent do you know what I mean like we have to
We have to allow a certain amount of like
Oh we are locking down in order to keep but you know
Everybody if people don't act
In everybody's interested in the steps to SEPTA ability of that disease is spread
Throughout
So he's fine with that
I think I did what I'm saying
Think your thought is interesting in it
I said I do see a little bit of a parallel
Yeah it and I think what I think is most interesting about Alex's conception is the Divine Wrath
As opposed to the actual
Causally
Determined
Yeah I don't know
I don't
I don't feel like it
It's possible for Alex
Contain this kind of
Stinking
And this this idea set
And also actually believe in the First Amendment
That's how could you possibly believe in freedom of religion
If
You believe that
Breaking God's rules
Makes
What is the hedge of protection
Can go away one of The Commandments is you should have no other God than me
But if you follow another religion or you don't follow a religion
I mean how could you follow or how could you believe in freedom of speech if the government has to
I guess murder you for taking the lord's name in vain
You know what I'm saying like
Penalty for sin is death obviously it would be it would be a challenge
Certainly
To believe in a republic
I think we're seeing a little bit of
Some flaws
And I just think this is hilarious we're not going to talk about him at all
I think it's really hilarious that this dude is showing up after the beginning of this
Bulshit
Alright we are butterflies ladies and gentleman and Ethan just get in the studio
But please don't forget that
Listeners and viewers like you
Broadcast News
We bring out is just critical to all of our futures in the future of our species
A special to honor of the veterans
Posted to serve
So yeah we got coming up
Would you like to talk about how Frank
Consign is real
Do you actually your real serious reporter let's talk about
Telekinesis undercover sting operation inside of Frankenstein's Castle actually you know what's ironic
He could actually do an amazing sting operation on Alex
Really good if you just brought a hidden camera into a regular conversation without you
God dammit somebody you've said he can beat
Turned right you can return from the federal body
Jones's career I don't care
God I wish I would have
We got to get a billionaire on our side to just throw money at
People further irony though is that if he did Sting Alex
I don't think I would believe
I couldn't trust it cuz it still
Dangers of lost credibility
I don't care James O'Keefe has a
I guess another Facebook story I don't care
Whatever
I don't care
Interesting story to tell
Solvang
And white papers and textbooks and
You're very low circulation books
Easier
You like Klaus Schwab
Past
Jon B holdren
Real quick
Jumpy Holdren's book ecoscience wasn't a low circulation book it was a text
Was it a mass-market paperback
Fail
Barnes & Noble tried to push poles
Rockefeller
Club around documents secret documents
A whole bunch of heart I've secret documents on the Bilderberg Group
Out of the Senate archives
Hold up a motorcycle in Virginia without cover millerberg there and just said here have this
That was all
How are the 60s
To cover the u.s. Union
For the deed for the industrialization project
Probably cuz you got them from a random guy on a motorcycle random guy on a motorcycle handed me papers
Reason people don't believe me
It's basically deepthroat isn't it
You mean the park
Open garage random dude on a motorcycle drives up to
No big deal
I think this is probably just like John Birch Society esca literature and ideas
Cuz it's talking about
Just like infiltrating the Union's obviously
Do the best workers
Kind of ideas of unionization or something that are antithetical to the Patriot movie
So you might as well say that there's no point in you needed in cuddalore
Not only infiltrative
The plot in order to destroy America
So I just love the idea of Alex in there's a guy on a motorcycle comes up
I got all the archives of the secret
Virginia cuz I remember when
What's the weather
A lot of videos that is in
One of his documentaries I think
I'm not sure I've definitely seen the video of him
Chantilli I don't remember a guy on a motorcycle coming up and giving him
An archive of secret globalist
Bilderberg documents
I don't remember him going back to his hotel room in freaking out that some guy on a motorcycle gave him an archive
Okay okay
Now we're both imagining this
What it how is he
He holding these
Document says he have a briefcase that's
Like handcuffed to his wrist and he has to go through a process
To give it to him
If you just wearing a messenger bag and he's like I here you go
Is it is it like in the ocean
12 or whatever where the you know I'm guessing it was Daniel
Motorcycle in the new just gave him his stupid book
There's big news on the way to Paramus
The night is that Alex has found
A triangle
Socially unacceptable
Boston in the ATL
This particular one is from Maryland and Virginia
And it says
Fathers are a form of
Parental parental
I'm going to cover that later
So what do you got is a triangle and it has like at the top there is a line
So that the smaller triangle and then the bottom of the triangle
Motorcycle is the unaccept
Audible white supremacy
It's things like
The Klan lynchings
Shut up like that and that underneath is the more
Subtle metaphor
Supremacy
Fathers are one of them
However I watch the video cuz I can't find anywhere else, I got to go find him
And I looked at it and know how to read
Parental it says
Paternalism
Okay
Merriam-Webster defines paternalism as quota system under which an authority undertakes to supply needs or regulate conduct of
Those under its control in matters affecting them as individuals as well in their relations with authority
Into each other
Paternalism is essentially believing that you can restrict another person or a group's actions
Because you understand their own good better than them
Alex has no idea about the word let alone concert
Discovery
A piece of paper that claims that paternalistic attitude
Contributed covert white supremacy
The way he reported is that the sblc unity as having Fathers as whites
That is a bit of a jump
But I honestly don't
Think he knows
But it doesn't
Safe for rent
That would be most likely I would
It it feels like you misread that got mad about it and whether or not he's realized he's wrong
It's too good for him not to be mad about it
Cuz he'll never read it
It's not like he was like wait I got to double-check this
That's never happened
True
Yeah
Parental ISM whatever that is under attack sure
It sounds crazy
Rena Phillips
Ilysm
My parental ism is it just you
You can't keep that father
You can't eat today
You can't keep saying it
Is believing in the nuclear family
You can Adventure
Racist I'm not
Sure the parental ism is a widespread concept
I was thinking that he could have misspoken
But still understood the word you do like telekinesis or when it was like yeah using the wrong word he means telepathy
And then he went
Further the prince was whose parents so we know
Bohr effect
He does
Does not understand what was being said nobody
Still think it could be an instance of him this reading the word and then never
Checking again
Sure sure but you know what it's embarrassing
Pretty funny different than the other misuse of the word
Like
Like the telekinesis thing is just funny
It's okay I get you meme
Telepathy is creating parental is another thing to be mad about
That may or may not be an actual word
I mean I could find some uses of it online but it's
It's definitely not like
A word people use of snow it's not you don't
Find it cited in Psychiatry paper Hoover
Yeah it's ritualistic attitudes
I mean
Oh no I did the Alex paternalistic
My eyes went wide what's going to happen I know Alex got into my head
Most of the
Middle of the show middle to end of the show
Is about Alex
About Alex
Talking about
Joe Biden
President
Apparently he's blaming
The victims of the Tuskegee
Experiments
Black vaccine hesitancy
He's blaming the
Victim
Okay I have a hard time believing that but let's continue talking about it and then clip of bye
Matthew's to rationalize
Give me the speech today Joe Biden Wayne's black
Hesitancy on Tuskegee Airmen
The first black sister Civil War allowed in combat who did an excellent job
So you blamed black man
Until
Port Orchard
Billions were allowed to be infected overall by the tens of thousands were ejected
Android now blames them the victims
Poor
What happened
Well he's an old man
So I hear he is blaming
The very black
Alabama
Who were victimized with a secret government experiment tell him it was a vaccine
The polio when it was syphilis
Now blaming them for what they did to him
Just lie so much you can't stop
I asked one person to do nothing but deal with
Equity
To make sure that
We were reaching out
Enderman Rd communities
Which by the way
And many of the older members of that Community had memories of
Experimentation on Black America
That we're not
Told about
Like what happened
The in all the Tuskegee Airmen
For sure Flatirons you killed him huh
Happened
And I misspoke and he said to
Tuskegee Airmen which were the group of black fighter pilots in World War II
Experiments
It's unfortunate gas in about this point here was that by
Doesn't know that they
Difference between the two uses of the word Tuskegee I'd say that's probably a stretch but whatever
I don't really
Using this clip to argue that biting his
Blaming the victims of the experiment for vaccine hesitancy do that
Absurd
That's
Mom said I was listening to this
It's really
It doesn't say anything
Close to what Alex
They were biting the saying is that the memory
Free of this
It is this staying on on American history
This the shame is what would Kant
Tribute to people
Being hesitant to
To trust
I'll rollouts of large vaccine
Program
That thought is
Makes sense
No it's Alex is not missing the point he is like cutting the points Achilles tendons and then bearing Italy
Live in the backyard like this is this is
A way out of
Control
Also a little bit later Alex makes the exact same mistake by Shore
Call my wife this rap group that Dudley pro-vaccine should have believed those
Run DMC
I got a new one weird shows Tuskegee Airmen
Gigi folks and says
Yeah we injected yeah but we don't do that anymore we don't do experiments anymore experiment
I'm in Alex City exact same slip that dividing did
It's an easy mistake to make
People in one circumstance in if you do it like oh no
Steak
Yeah it's just a
Stupid game
Yeah so
Rand Paul
He's he's made some
Disparaging comments about fauci at this point
Your answer Alex believe that he's going head-to-head
But the enemy
And maybe that means
But he should be present
To support
Who's winning Paul deserves a lot of support on
He's going directly at the enemy flies getting death threats
I've been physically attacked twice
Broken Islam
I'm sure was a lawn are given
I need a good heart very presidential
Material
Mexican president
Schmick's
Black women like those guys
One second
White male
Who else who else is there
Kielbasa mauro's wife's fine order on a saying
For him
Discussion about
You do digress
That is true can't believe that we have that conversation
Yeah
You're the one who brought it up
Yeah I certainly didn't I wasn't like
I wonder if bolsonaro's White knighting
I did that was not on the top of my mind also my first response that I would have
Did the idea of a Rand Paul DeSantis ticket
To Whitefish
Policy is that I would be really offended by
First
Here is Alex Van Dyke
Baby Come Back
That's all
It's
Go to rant
Yeah
Mayonnaise
Haven't gone through that
Disenchantment. With Rand Paul
At the 2016 election
Pretty funny to hear him say so
Stuff like that cuz he knows
You blew it
Yeah I know
There's there's just
Stihl dealer
Paul boat
I wish I could
Stop
Being at least a little bit surprised
Howell crane
You know
No matter
How Craven I see them
I'm still like
Your dad Craven
Man
Just pull in a week he's going to pretend that he didn't say that there's a fake Alien Invasion that's coming and they're going to not be able to
Themselves and then
They're not tell us eventually bad aliens are coming
He expect you to not remember that a week ago he had a big Revelation right before he got on air
He's got a lot of Revelation
I think you just expect him to have the radio show it
Ridiculous
Tell me a fun with that being more fun radio show to listen to
Certainly
He said a lot of extreme stuff on this episode
Some of it not as hateful as usual so we're just kind of
Dumb
But you should know this
We discredit these guys we send the prison but I kill everybody
Missouri weather
It means everything
Of course
Of course earlier in the show Alex it said that it's going to be open
Open phones in the third and fourth hour is getting really pumped for it
Yes I'd love that
I was I was really I was really going out on a limb going more than zero I kind of expect
0 but I'm really hoping
I feel like whenever you take that bet it should be zero or if the field
The over-under is 1.5
Yes he takes none
Couldn't do take
Open phones
The 4th hour cuz he initially he had Matt Bracken schedule today's the 4th
Thursday's $4
A bunch of things I'm working on.
Very important behind-the-scenes I'mma leave it at that
Had to go to Family Court
Chad this is the night I believe
That his ex-wife
Was trying to live
Stream a court
Appearance
On YouTube
Open hearing
And people should know what's going on
Answer I
I would assume that that's more was on outside that a big story
Yeah it was
Possibly going to be live stream
Terrifying for him
Even at
This point machote that's in the future
We have to worry about
Cuz now
Undercover news
I got a bunch of other huge Governors as well
And it's a really scary stuff
Really mad and also
The Abomination stuff all this cloning
When the universe
Agadmator
We're a musical instrument
The best way to describe it
Energetically
Through the dimensions
What it is
Census
Read write and talk when she couldn't hear and couldn't see but
Figure it out
Times were there
Well spoken
Person through communication
Wild
Only you know
But it was there and so
Trying to describe this in
Let's just say
Trying to describe what
You know what's weird if you'd like
I just
Don't know how it is
He could
Really somehow be defensive towards
Helen Keller like
Helen Keller didn't
Do any work
It's that the people broke
Through her
Defenses
In order to get to what was already there inside
Oh oh oh yeah yeah
Somehow I don't
Know where your friends
Helen Keller
It is a little
It seems like a
Stray thoughts
A little bit
I would guess that the people who worked with
Helen Keller
Wouldn't say like
It's lucky the ark
Archetypes were there
I'm guessing that that would be the way that they would describe it
So yeah the universe
Yeah
Musical
I know that when I was
It doesn't fourth grade my parents
Made me learn a musical instrument. But they said I couldn't play like drums or guitars didn't want to be in a rock band
I took up the tree
I didn't know where that was going did you got me
Our bodies are musical instruments in reverse
What's the best way to describe
Look in the third dimension it's horrid limiting
To talk about these things which I don't know what these things are
I don't know what's going on I thought we were going to get to covid news
I don't know what that
I do I do like the scientist approved it
Didn't everything's kind of like that
Yeah The Music of the Spheres
So what I've done now is I have just
Made
Cots
This is one long steaks
Okay is it a weird place
Thought we were getting to the news you're talking about our bodies being musical instruments the third dimension
Look dude
This is a mess
This is a very primitive level of
God's creation
Azteca videos
This
Havasu Creek
Matter
Sure
Dimensions very very sad
In the lower Dimensions witch
It's even more
More empty
In the lower dementia
Human term
The lower
Is up and down in ounces
The game of thing
No
Yes
Like it or not this is happening
This is how we come back from vacation
This Dimension is.
I don't know what you're talkin about this dimension
Olga creational level
What does that mean
Look in the third dimension
It's third-dimensional words are limited
Just saying s***
Space below
Snapchat
More empty
Is it is it that mean it's thinner
He thinks that the human term
But I mean lizard place on that level
We're talkin all the difference
Between the levels of Dimension is Riley
Measurable by thin or thick
How many communities whenever they they talk about like these higher vibrations
It's often referred to as a higher density or maybe Alex is taking that as like
Alright actual dense I really I think
You can
Float easier in the fourth dimension I would have said you can the third dimension know I would I would assume if you have
Have a lower density float more right
Don't know cuz you're not talking about the environment is denser yeah yeah I had it backwards
Alright
Yeah look
We're engaging with too much
Creation Ali
He brings up his a good thought
Maybe if you're high
Interested in your in college
Alright
And that thought is this
We always imagine
That like
Is aliens were to come down and contact us
Baby so much more advanced
That's the nice man
I think we leave
Experience this in the Aqua Teen Hunger Force Shore
Who's experienced this
Plenty of
Bias towards
Anything that would contact us would have to be far more advanced than us
That's not the case I mean if we can't contact them but they
Can contact us that would suggest that at least on some level they have an ability for me
Right
The contacting across
But I know for sure so weird theoretically
Opening the possibility to a Intergalactic spacefaring race
Anything in this great big marble little world
Okay anyways
Thought
I'm going out of my way to give some credibility or Credence here cuz the rest of the Saudis stupid okay
Interfacing with other things and like oh it must be advanced
No
Interface with us without our free will
Is low
Wow then
Lucifer
Who does come from one dimension higher
With all the other dark energy
Falling in the human world
Right right right
Right
So
Is Step Up
I mean maybe maybe what he's trying to say is that Satan isn't really a bad guy but
He just needs
Debris thinner air
I mean
No I don't think so
Kind of
Attractive some of the other ideas he has
No I ain't seen this one level higher
And he's a lying with the stuff
Who knows why I'm not I'm not messing with that right I'm not messing with the Y on this one
Certainly not
Yeah
I got nothing
Let's just move on
What
Road signs
That's not
We have to create our own terms
Even understand interface with the cosmos
Which itself again is just an expression of God
I'm not saying troglodyte
Preachers that aren't really Christians they think they are
What is
That I worship the creation no no no
Made all this
And if I create a piece of art that is an expression of who I am
That is a very primitive
Form of
Making something that has consciousness
And Free Will Will
Guess what God gives you a little taste of that Acquire
Quite a few times were made me image of God
Poor little G
What do you take away from that
What do I take away from well
Blasphemy
Well
Make a call
Well the idea of
Comparing yourself to
Did God by simply little bit
Size of
The G would still technically really beat
Construed as
Calling yourself somewhat equal to God
Which I think
Now I don't know if I've read the Bible enough
X
Pretty big on the door
Do scale
Yeah
I mean
What is made in the image of really mean
Telekinesis
Total
A million percent
Yeah I was looking for a thesis
I'm not finding
I think that was your mistake
That was
Attitude
Lesson I refused to learn
So here you have an interesting perspective that you think
The capitalization on God doesn't mean all that much
Think I'll expensive.
Also he thinks he's
Got the
Personal connection to God that gives him Visions all the time
But he's not God capital
Fluttershy
Satan
Okay
He comes down
From is an address which is
How you doing
Your God that you are God
In the fourth dimension and a lowercase s in the third dimension
I never thought about it I always
Consider to be a proper noun
Me too
Fungible
Poor little G
Okay
2001 Space Odyssey
Go through this process should come back as a
Starchild
Reincarnate
Implant the egg that is Earth and create
The new Lucifer
Well that's that's just a tan
Papi chocolate
Satanic poppycock
I thought it was maybe a little bit
Long but I didn't necessarily
Construe it as satanic
Well it's fair you are not the most reliable
Cinematic reveal
Over I miss that and Ebert's review but I supposed it was all unspoken
Bright
All about the Titanic poppycock
Nism
Cavalry
Do you know the stuff in 2000's
Might be just as real
As Frankenstein
Well that's that's just satanic Papi chocolate
I am
What God is actually create
2001 Space Odyssey
He's very
Close to actually
What's going on
And I'll just leave it at that
Don't know what's news
Acura rudimentary special effects
So special that I got to get back to the news on a certain level
Please do not
Are you say something like that
What's in the news
Boo
So 50 is it so
50 years ago special effects were very similar to
What they had
Then
So would you say that special effects of
Gotten better enough
They are what they have now
Or is it like
Proportional
Are are special effects true to what they were to what reality was 50 years ago and now it's 50 years
Ahead of what we have
I don't have to be right that's the only thing that makes plantar if the
Evil globalist are implanting secret messages and they control all those cinemedia
It's not like they would
Give access to like Secret
Technologies for
Special effects
Right so Andy Serkis only has a career because of a lie
I think that's what I'm hearing I don't know about that whether or not.
Cinema world
Is privy to those those futuristic
Technology
Congress is Godzilla's real
So back to the news that's where it is
The cervix
Excursion into lunacy
That weirded me out so much
Like I said I was
Like what
Trying to
Express
This is
It seems like just kind of
Bit of standard
S*** hedary's from like
New Age space
Conspiracy communities
Dumb nonsense Rogan
I could see
Somebody who wouldn't get invited on Rogan but really want almost starting at all
I want that one tier below
I don't see a lot of depth
Here
I just see Killing Time
And then Alex
Angry about his not sure
Life is only an experience
A free-will that God created
Is the only thing God can create
Separate from God is all-knowing all Powerball controlling
Omnipotent omnipresent Beyond quilt
Is creatures with free will that create other creature
Free world
We have been made
Ball
It doesn't want to be alone
And so
Put us on this planet
Away from other things so we don't kill everything
Wall-E
Run around inside our Nursery
And what does God put in the nursery
Majestic creation
Puts a lot of nasty
Stop
That's weird
What are weird God
What a weird guy on the radio
You know what I was thinking when he was listening to this I was like
This
Alex
Turned into like the like I remember when I was growing up there was the small town Church
15 to 20 people in it a sort of the revivalist preachers
I don't want to know what goes on there
It's none of our business and we just stay out of
It's loud
There's something going on but we just
What you taste like a black hole in this small town wherever it is kind of avoid that out of
Instinct I think I might have gone to a couple of those churches and I think I know what you mean there was one moment in his thing
Thing that really hit home like in that way for me
That Matt is the like when he's yelling about
Like we were created by an all-powerful being
And there's a pause and the
Who doesn't want to be alone
It's the anger the pause
Does MMS off delivery of this ideas
Created us to keep him
Or whatever you can hear it I got it
That's just
Evangelist
Church where there were snakes before I've heard this
Rhythm in Cadence's is
Is very
Temperature kind of
Everything that I thought about when I heard that clip was
About like it did naming of his website is prisonplanet
Really interesting to me the way that like
If you think
He's just this guy who's into Political
Conspiracies and like
Hey if a One World Government comes into play
Yes and they turn into a tyrannical dictatorship
We are on a prison planet you can't get off
If there's nowhere to run
If there's a One World Government doesn't
Control of everywhere on Earth
Is a Prison Planet
What are you looking at the way he's kind of
Talking now
It's more like
You know
The Earth nursery idea it's
It's kind of like he's saying that like
You know I'm in a crib
Crib
And this weird guy threw a scorpion in here
Yeah you know I got pushed into the deep end when I was five and you swim or you die
That kind of thing
Yeah and it also implies that there's a bunch of other alien
Things on other planets
On other planets through whatever we're going through
I mean if God's lonely
It seems to reason that
Maybe he's lonely enough to make more
You know and so he's just running this shell game
Suggest that maybe
How is it possible that
The whole thing
I've gotten lonely
Pisces still lonely
Escalation you know you what you get what you want and you find out you just want more
God's not immune to that kind of thing
Seems like
Is a lot of people who've lived
If you need some company there's plenty of options
If he's so lonely
You know why not just make some people and keep them around a party
To get be in the nursery sure
Got a deal with the Scorpion
And then get out of crib
It's a really babyish idea
Well I mean really it's simulator
More similar I would say to the wheel of reincarnation then anything else
You know that idea of like
You're constantly being tested through throughout time until you become a full beard
And then you would send me under
Yeah but I don't know I don't know how Alex is ideas about reincarnation work
Exactly
I know that he thinks that you're literally Rancid
Tronos Petra
But I don't have that works with ancestors that are
Concurrently alive that's fair
I don't I don't I don't really understand any of that
In between
You doesn't really articulate a lot of that stuff
I don't know if it is
Like
A situation where where he believes in
The reincarnated
Casino that kind of
Yeah it's weird yeah that is weird
Anyway
Is dumb
So there is some news
Alex has been building up to this news but I didn't realize it
I have such a hard time remembering that this is got a news
I didn't feel like you've been building this up for an hour
I felt like he got distracted but bulshit
I know teasing Alex
That we've experienced that over and over again on the show.
I'm going to cover this
Go stand over the highway with a
Understudy
University of Louisville
Gun show
Any signs or any evidence that they help.
Define
A review study
Came out
Is there's people asked questions about methodology of it
And even under ideal circumstances
Assuming that you know it goes through. View and stands up
The scrutiny
Still isn't saying that masks art
Effective it was looking
Larger populations make
Estimates based on whether or not mask mandates
Had an effect
On a larger population individual level whether or not masks
Had any effect
In terms of actual train
Plenty of studies that have actually looked at the question.
2 pretending to study answers
Ima
Routinely
I assume that they do
They are
Yeah it maybe not 100% effective
But they are effective in as much as
It's something you can do right
Right right
As opposed to nothing
This is about something different than what he is
Saying it is
And then
Secondarily
Too early
To really take it as solid
Like a bed Rocco's of of a
Sloppy
That means and you if he says study say I
I always hear you say
He's referencing an on. Study like that
Then that's that's something that
It's weird
You know like
He says the study it's a non-peer-reviewed saying that
It's on like a preprint
Or something
Maybe we'll get
Peer-reviewed or maybe won't
And then you'll just forget about it you'll never know where it ends up
The same thing with bills like if you look back at like these pastimes on his show he actually
Talked about
News more he would have these bills that he complained about and they are always things that ended up dying and committee
They're always bills that are like
Can you believe someone's doing X wires either died
I can
I also know that that
Is never going to even get a
Yeah
It's kind of the same thing
He's preemptively
Making
Everything a huge deal
That's one of the reasons why I can't do
The coverage of the police state three that I wanted to do
It's almost entirely about doesn't happen
It's
Yesterday's say
Next sentence
Not a review
Hb20 33 next sentence died in committee
Yeah
So we won't last quip here
And this is
Example of why
Everything in Alex's world is
Quarters u.s. Intel to analyze information
Impossible Rihanna tablet
I need cover it up
Stooges
I ordered by The Kill
Doesn't
Investigate the theory that there was
A lab origin
Ted coronavirus Shoreline it's a cover-up and if he does
Do an investigation of it it's a cover-up
Doesn't matter the reality and what happens don't matter
This pendant is intact no matter what
The only way Alex would allow for something to be real
Would be if Trump
Himself
Was running
This Commission
And the only conclusion that they even make
Accepted from the beginning
Is that not only
Was this a bio-weapon released
McKay matters at lab
But she
Cool Hand salute
Chile is a
Pizza is
Is it
Special kind of virus
Directly if you look at the molecules that spells out communists
On the virus unit like that level of b*******
That's why
Get off
The whole lot of this stuff is just
Seriously inasmuch as like there's dangerous consequences of it and it was straight
Of
Bad thought patterns
Certainly
But like when you hear stuff like that like you should
You should recognize that like
This is how he preached
Every yeah yeah everything is okay
Yep
Doesn't matter
B b to do X
Spider do why
Either way the decision tree for what Alex is going to say about it is
Yeah it's like
Preparing for a disaster
You hate
You say that
Preparing for the disaster
Makes it happen
If it does happen
Or if it doesn't happen you say that by revealing that the preparation
For the disaster would make it happen
Excuse
Aurora talking about these bills that died in committee
Total eclipse
It's just a trap
Yeah you you create a universe where you always win
And then you never have to feel bad about yourself so why would you go back to the real Universe you know
Sounds fun
Jordan
This is Ben
We're back it's great to be back down you know what we had such a good time
Play the birthday what it gets here that would still tickle
Just wait till next time
Jordan on Monday and I hope to it's gotten a little bit more
How to emails by then a little more time
But tell them we website
Knowledge underscore
We are going to be like the Dallas Zoo could please find a local charity or Bellefontaine area to help out people doing
But until then I'm Niro I'm Leo I'm dzx Clark
Barrel run
I live next door to
This evening
Dimension
I'm not sure what above are
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color