Knowledge party.com great respect for knowledge B
Chicken
Knowledge fight
Fight.com
About the altar of Celine
Jordan
Question what's up
Speaking of Celine
It's a Saleen oriented right spot
So one of the things that I
Enjoyed
Over the course of my time living
With this animal
Is that she finds new places that she likes to hang out
China periodically on the couch for a while that was like where I always find her
Basic
Of course totally basic normal
Lately he's found a new spot that you love so she's going next
Every single time I go to the bathroom she's laying in the tub
That's how you elevate the form of laying in a weird podcast now
Gratifying
Is commonality that we have is gone
You're both people
His much water if adding
Drive stick not think nothing would be would be the best
It's like to share things with a cohabitant
Sure
What is the chance to break into Robert Evans
And steel is it raining strippers
Unreleased currently as a podcast or Oregon
Episodic thing and I got to read the whole thing and it
Very very good I mean I'm sure it'll probably be the final version that everybody else here is unless
She takes my advice in
Rewrite it to be about motto shark rampant
Represent
I guess you're still writing but I don't know why all art must contain shark Rapids
No it's it's
Very very good and there are few things he does
You know
Not glorify the violence that is just so is so great
Call After the revolution in
Is really really good
I recommend people read it
Coming out to like you said is like chapters in audio format and also in imprint
Twitter
Today we have an episode to go over as promised and episode
Okay so I wanted to check out the day after the fauci emails got really
Because to me this
Seems like the biggest bread making opportunity of Alex's recent Curry
Females you can say whatever the f*** you wanted something
So I checked in on June 2nd 2020
Now all I'm doing is just screaming Blackjack whatever I realize I'm not going to catch up
Vocalizations
The shot
Doesn't work that way
Find
I kind of felt like one of the first was
When the initial release came out
Like the second
By then he's had the evening to come up with whatever bulshit he wants
To say I'm excited to see
How he responds
Does he fail even at this
We will see
Thank you
There's a real name apparently and I feel for this person
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much sir
I'm opposed to the sequel to The King and I I'm writing in my brain
Post-tribulation Rapture thank you so much
I like that one too
First Erica Indian
A loyal servant of Queen saline May long she reign
Yub
Freakishly large
Thank you so much
I like how people are going to boil servant of saline
I feel like we could
Spiral this out into a cult a lot
Faster than I would have it
But like you know how the buttercream what the buttercream gang is do regular gangs
We would create two regular
Do you know what I'm saying this is already taking over my tub
Oh man I wonder what her first commandment
Stay out of my tub probably
Do Jordan now it is come time to check-in
Some birthday shout out
Bored
Is the condition that leads to death
Life is a disease that ends in death
If you're different
But Alex has been hitting lately
Happy birthday
Touching wanted us to give you a shout out
This is back in May I believe Steve
Happy birthday
Belatedly
But again life is data
Born
Is the condition that leads to death
Life is a disease that ends in death
Happy birthday happy birthday
Jordan
I told you
This is the day that I would be responding to the emails
And
Here's
Restart
This is after he played a little bit of like
Goofy meme video about like a Scooby-Doo
They take the bags off of the ghost Ted's Italian Bill Gates
A lot of fun he's promoting that
The wheels and completely come off
Covid-19
The globalist are in deep trouble
We put out
Dark comedy peace
You just saw
They're TV Oregon just heard of your realtor
Spoof on Scooby-Doo
Where
Calcium
Operation
Prison for
And we put that out of here yo
It was banned on Twitter and Facebook
Was obviously aperitif
Based on
Real things they die
Boy here later
Meaning
When we first
Put it out
Scooby-Doo just saw the covid-19 mystery
Got 200
1000 views video
I think it needs a lot more than that.
What's the featured video
Video
This is important stuff
I was I was a little
I am very saddened by the SI I was a little underwhelmed
Not least of which
Because Scooby-Doo right there right there year old memes booth
Is it what we need to really push
Need to get that.
Assertive wrestled with
Exactly what it is about Alex's show that I think is
Is bad
And I mean obviously they're dancers
But a lot of them
But one of the things that he sort of central that makes it bad is actually what he articulates
It's in this next
Because it's radio / TV transmission is not just your regular entertainment it's not just your regular news program
Participation sport
I think that's censored report
Video needs to get share don't you
The Scooby-Doo
But this is a participation sport
That's
Kind of bad bad way of looking at this stuff when you
You know I mean
Underoath
I'm just talking about my feelings
Right I don't know about sources I don't know about
Have to act you have to listen to the whole thing
What he's free and he's on air
Please this is this is not news
This isn't entertainment this is a participation sport
I'm trying to incite you to do something
Nothing. Lisa Wolf
But that implies that information is
A win-or-lose situation not
Things are real or not
You can win with information that's not real
You know
It's a participation sport it's not about
Finding what's real or what's true or what exists
It's about winning
Don't challenge your notion
Come up with things that you can miss represent in the real world that real
Enforce your predetermined
Conclusion
And play like hell out on the field
Take make sure everyone else is forced to accept those things too if you change your mind you're just giving up
You are you can't get you can't give up you can't be a quitter
The challenge t.j. Lavin doesn't like quitters
Hate squid
Throw in the towel
So finally Alex does end up getting to the Apache emails and cover them that much
Gmail
Ichiro
Not effective in keeping out virus
I need a publicly said it's about respect
Living in fear
Openshot
Tool
Boobs
In the emails he did say that there wasn't good reason for everyone to wear
Because at the
Unaware of a number of variable
But existed with covid
In an interview with CNN
David email got released fauci was asked
Quote a lot of transpired since then
If you had to go back and do it all over again would you tell her something different do you regret that
Here's his answer would I think it's gray
Quote
Let's get real here
If you look at scientific information as it accumulates what's going on in January and February what you know is a fact
Does data guides you
Hi guys what you tell people and your policy
If March April May occur
You accumulate a lot more information and you modify and adjust your opinion and your recommendation based on the current science
Concurrent data
Of course
If we knew back then that a substantial amount of transmission was asymptomatic people
If we knew that the data show that masked outside of a hospital setting actually do work when we didn't know it then
If we realize all those things back then
Of course
You're asking a question would you do something different if you knew what you knew now
Course people would have done that
It's so obvious
God's great answer that is losing the participation sport
No wonder we never win because he is learning and growing and then regretting actions from before
What he should be saying is no
I'm so stoked all those people died because of stuff I didn't know that I told them
That's what I wanted
I just think there's something to delineate there though that it's not I don't think it's regret
Necessarily
Maybe a hope that more awareness head or more information had been known at a certain time
But based on the information that was available that's
Solidus recommendation
Mmsd
The thing about psychological
Hot stuff that Alex brings up short
Best I can tell like that was something that was going on early on I remember this this is what they were talking about like
When there wasn't an awareness of the asymptomatic spread
There was
Discussion of if you're sick you should wear a mask if you're not sick
You don't really need to
But
That puts
The stigma on anybody wearing a mask you got it because now if you wear a mask everyone's going to assume you're sick
Could lead to people
Being disincentivize to wear masks when they should wear my
No I mean leper colonies worked well everybody with Leprosy was like I'm definitely going to go right to this leper colony
I don't want to hide it and key
Keep people from knowing that I'm a leper because
You know I'm treated so well in leper colony
The psychological benefit of widespread mask uses that you kind of make it easier for people
Hoodoo
Higher reason
According to the understanding
At that time right to follow Public Health
Advice
Everyone
No it works out better for everyone
If you need stigmatize these things
I make it so everyone
I don't know
I have not read all of the voucher emails I've read all of the ones
That like
Get pointed out as like a haha
I-Ready
Bunch of the ones that no one pointing out
IC
A nothing
And I think Alex does to because here's what he does immediately instead of going more into these
Easy maokai
By the way let me let me let me get back in always
Tell the news
Let me just tell you some of the other stuff coming out today
And then I'll go into each
Area
Went over my parents on Memorial Day
My dad grilled ham
Markers
Delicious
Which one they're swimming pool
I solved my children and family
Wife
Is a great story
She came over the house
Friendswood
More details
Add
What he tells your story
It's accurate
And I know her daughter very well
I guess I'm not the old old enough now or no
A seven-years-old a granddaughter
Her sister Dash
Lottery
This is f****** annoying
I can't adopt it I can't listen
I can't keep track of all the variables
This is not the Bible's I don't care who begat
Well
You're going to wish for more set up when he finally gets to the actual story
We need casing together week
The other best friend
Live in Rockwall
Are there Evangelical Christians are very nice people
I don't care
Add
One of the daughters the granddaughter was arguing
We had
About
Issues
But the mother said hey
Why don't you go to your school counselor and ask them
About some of your
Boyfriend
I'm going to go pay for you to go to something else
High School freshman
But I went
For the first two years of high school
Awesome
I was 16
Jessie goes into the school in Rockwall and it's a male
Counselor
Conversation
Nice repeat it to her
Acceptable
Don't you think your problem is you're really
Amman
Oh boy
So that this is B
This is where the story
I would like more Preamble please he exactly would definitely like more preamp
It's clearly not to restore
Think about
This is made of b*******
Beckett simonon
How is it that you can think it's a
The great idea
To give that much of a preamble to a story where all you want to be at
Transphobic in meme
Demonized
Sir population
In order to do that
You got
Izzat
Third-hand story maybe maybe a fan of you have something on the family tree that's
Long Branch away from you that's for damn sure
Yeah
I would
Believe that there's a possibility that somebody was in a school counseling position
Could
You know if someone weird
Come to them with
Gender issues or something could be
Emprise
But I don't believe
This
You're having problems with this boyfriend
Are stool
Because you're really sexually confused
Are you joking or snow
We have put your child sleep outside
You really need this right now
Puma shirt for girl
This is a f******
This is that same meme we're like that
This is a joke meme where the soldiers in the other professors like Liberals are good in the soldiers like I killed everybody
America's the best thing ever in the liberal professor
Correct all the time this is a made-up nonsense story
Conservative tell themselves
This is a boogeyman story this is
I mean
Frankly
If this happened to Alex's describing it she should own that
That's cool
Malfeasance
Go to school
Very easy to to get to the bottom of
What a Libras
Oh God
Imagine
Not trouble Charles boyfriend
When you're starting you don't so much talk to your mom
You know who's the right-wing you know Christian
But she's conservative
You don't even expect in Rockwall Texas a suburb of Dallas
Pushing on you
You are a man
You are a m
What are the odds
Men women are like
This outrageous
The only real question that I have is
How much is this is the story that someone told him at a cookout
And how much is
Alex Azar
I'm going to punch to the shopping list Gallagher on man
This isn't it's either that or like he's half remembering Austin Powers isn't it
You're a man baby that could be you might have taken some sizzurp
And I watch some movies
Ever
Imagine his audience
It's over Taylor story
They had a big assembly the principal
Scream whatever the prince
Isabel tells into as we all know children do
Jesus
Changed
Literally entirely since I was in school but I do remember the counselors
And every school that I went to
Being the sort of folks who just listen and roll their eyes
I don't kind of believe you honestly the counselors are not really actively engaged
They mean well for the most part and I like
Was positioned to be a school counselor
Yeah I don't remember them being all that much like
Working across purposes trying to make conclusions for you
Find it weird
When I was in third grade and they school counselor put all of us under the Sorting Hat
And I
Determine whether we were man or woman
That was a that was an interesting day but
I guess that's part of the counselors job now
This story let me first of all
100% absolutely not true
But it leads me to believe that Alex doesn't really want to talk about
A little bit weak
Well he read some of that you meant well he didn't read him his actual grandfather's nephew he knew him
Come back when they go hunting know it's something to you don't even want to know about it
My son that guy got
With his
Diddler in the Sheep on the other side of that sad if
We don't need to talk about that this story is about my great grandfather's nephew
And how he had a son
And his son was married to this woman that was
His first marriage
Marriage that was a disaster but
What is first marriage they got married again it's like Grover Cleveland non-consecutive marriages
Just kind of thinking right
Really letting me you're leaving me out to dry I was kinda hoping you would get into how the second marriage
Importing exporting business
Antique and Relic
40 countries that were stolen
Errands I'll be in traffic
Cousin who was rewrite that to the Tri-Rail right
The story about again email great story
So also not to do in such as emails but Alex has a new shirt
That's really popular
I was going to plug this and I keep it like this shirt is popular with
A designer shirt
And I think it's one of my better design
Looks like
The concept team
Robert dollars over there
It's just incredible
Regular lights
We got a black shirt
The frogs infowars.com and on the front of the shirt
The same little symbol over
Your car
And I'm telling you
For almost a month
As soon as I wore this out
John the boom operator
My son
Yesterday
He works up here
It's because I am 4 years
XXL
Not important storage
Hey you go to the warehouse down the road you get one
You don't steal my shirt
I'm telling you this shirt so popular
Why so popular with
My employee and my son
Is not a good Market sailboat
Got the brand new market research work for me like this shirt work for me or I Cry
Created
Listen we can't keep them in stock they're stealing them from us you guys done
Including the people who work for me only and I only the people who work for me just love these show
Amazing
It's God to frog
Dand
So I think that this was just also a nice way for Alex to weave into talking
Think about some more of this you know like
The frogs
Harvest Bread and Butter with everybody loves to
He's trying to do a little bit more
They were cloning animals and humans before I was born
What are the way twice as much that are similar part insect
Asparagus
Hello
Asparagus salmon
I try that so Alex is talking about a new genetically modified salmon that's being bred by a company called aquabounty
Actually not really new in 2015 they got approval to
Like create these genetically modified salmon
Came to Market but like almost nobody is buying
Puffer upper
Pufferfish
Set
I'm not sure that I'm okay with what's going on here for ethical reasons but Alex is still way off on the
The fish don't grow to twice their normal weight they grow to their normal weight twice as fast
Who's the chief by splicing into Atlantic salmon tagine from Pacific
Chinook salmon that make it so the fish produced
Growth hormone all year and shutter part of
Sure
Gene from another fish the ocean
That essentially actor the stabilizing
Mistaken for the hormone
I've not been able to determine if a salmon is partes para guess but I do know that
But if you look into it
But you can find some interesting recipes where salmon is paired
Alright done that
Cook-Out is a good weekend
But butter and asparagus
Put some salt and pepper on their maybe maybe braizat even then
I'm not sure I'm comfortable with this stuff
Entirely I'm not sure I'd have to think about it a little bit more maybe have a conversation with somebody about it
Apparently most food retailers in the United States agree and they aren't selling
This may be like one of those funny
Instances where I
Kind of agree with
The conclusion that Alex has it like maybe maybe this isn't cool
But I think that the way that he reaches his conclusion is childish stupid and a disservice to
Anyone taking these issues seriously
Ridiculous I mean like part of my immediate reaction to that is
As the sign
It's fiction fan I was when I was 8 years old was like
Yeah fukin
Can splice everything together let's see what happen
And now that I'm an adult I can realize that maybe that
Kids shouldn't be in charge
Gene editing research
So maybe we have to hold off on it
Concerned about obviously and I don't I don't know whenever I try to look into this a little bit but I don't know if I could even find a
Clear answer
How much
Does that growing twice as fast
Like effect
The life experience of the second
You know cuz that seems like a
Could be hellish
Yeah and I-80
Think that I don't know what you're not
I don't know when you unpack that you open it up to the whole leg while you're going to eat them anyway
She and then you get into I don't want to wait into it with us
Hardtack
So Alex talks about the salmon and then he jumps into another story about
In Japan
And I did not actually pulled
This clip I regret to
What am I
What am I bungle
But I want to talk about it a little bit because it is also fairly interests
Sing but again the thing that Alex is
Is talking about his nonsense
Is this like the Nigerian email scam he got catfished by somebody in Japan
No he's found an article in Japanese about a Japanese science
Research
Project to make
Catfish
Female
Essentially using
Something that they derive from soil
Already
Amateur
Catfish are turned into females or in the embryo no matter what it will be
Female cat
It is
I don't know if it's fully adults
But but they are actual caption
So this is another story about people try to find ways to make fish bigger quicker
Female catfish grow at much faster rate
Rates then males and in farming situations often males are
Just thrown out
Raising them to the point where they could be used for marketable product
What cost more than would be brought in
Researchers in Japan recently found that if they
They kept the fish in a tank that way
Was full of water weigh
What's different things dissolved in it
Create a more female dense population
The use of actual female hormones is not allowed for animals being raised
Consumption
So the researchers at
Explored isoflavones
Badger the chemical that's found in
Beans
They isolated a compound called genistein
And that it is derived from from isoflow gonchar
And they found that if you had a tank of water with 400 micrograms
A leader
This resulted in a tank of
Catfish that were a
Hundred percent female
Wow
This is interesting and it's obviously of concern to people who raise fish for a living
Pretending there's a one-to-one parallel between humans and catfish is a little bit soft
Which is what Alex is due
Even if
Biologically similar to
To the point where at
Relevant
This would still seem to suggest that humans would need to swim around in and breathe water full of isoflavones
This kind of effect
This is all too often the case
It's just an attempt by Alex
Text to take a headline misrepresented and use it as a weapon
Against trans people are trying to make
The fact of
Trans people
Existence into some kind of a conspiracy
Because
This is what they're doing with
I don't know about that
That's why don't I don't want to
I want I want a big no on that one
Yeah and interesting research
From what I was able to find
Applies to
But I want to try to get a little bit
Closer
By taking another silly relate
Story
About monkeys
I also texted this on monkey three different species and found
But they make the same weird smiling face
They're aggressive and hateful loaners
Very unsuccessful
Female
Long-term story consumption makes monkeys aggressive loners
Shocking study
Responsible human applications
Lar
Not surprisingly Alex a zombie tails on the study wrong it was also the studies from 2004
The headline he's reading Israel website called
Herculean strength.com okay well I'm already out
Siri where he's pulling this from
I'm sorry of men's rights activists name is it is kicking me out it's their tagline is become a demigod
Diesel bodybuilding site
The variant to testosterone
Interesting Lee they also part of posted an article about that catfish studies
Just hangs out on bodybuilding sites
Texas Health news actually does make sense
But this is actually an interesting
Comparative
Study but here's some of the things Alex
One there wasn't three species of monkeys
There were three groups to experimental and one control group but they were all male macaque
Marketsharp
To all the stuff about the weird faces is made up
I think Alex has you're taking it from pictures of the macaques
But they were on the build-up bodybuilding website
Put random pictures about pictures from
Of course
I was probably just thinks that monkeys look like demons
Getty Images yet
I have no idea how Alex is gauging whether or not these monkeys were successful regardless of
I don't know what the standard for that is
For I don't see anything in there about killing
Females
The study itself did find that there appeared to be behavioral changes in macaques based on the amount of Swords tarot reading
In the diet
I don't suppose focusing on the aggressive tendon
These but the study actually found that
The opposite was more often
McKay's
There's a 67%
Increase in aggressive behaviors but a 200
3% increase in something
This is an element of the study that Alex is choosing to ignore because he's just going to
Different directions
Increase solitary Behavior does match up with some of the stuff sounded
The study like approximately there was a 30%
Increase in time spent alone
For the group that had to hire soy
Intake diet sure
One important point to bring up here though is that there was almost no difference found between the control group and Below eye
Asoph Logan diet group
Control group in the low group word
Almost
Not
Tell the difference
In order for human
Dominica levels of isoflavones
Consumption of the high diver group that they were getting
For 15 months straight it would be next to Impossible
For humans to do
Maybe the equivalent of human swimming around in isoflavones
Unsaturated water and breathing it in our little Gil
You're not going to be able to get a diet that dense that
That controlled
Did you get any of the
Be kind of
Marginal effects that were interesting though still whatever whatever they're looking at I don't happen
Inclusive it isn't art certainly don't know if it applies to human I mean to certain extent
That does also have the flavor of a study that's like
Non-consensual changing diet of animals
What causes different behaviors you know like I know I get it but I do
Okay
Shirk
Yeah I don't know I found a really interesting did instead of really getting into the veggie stuff Alex instead goes on all these
Weird sort of
Animal
Genetics
News items that summer current
It's in summer old and
They're all bulshit mean aside from the transphobia that that's more fun
Yeah I suppose
Gmail emails out a talking about emails are still boring and where are they
We're still
Like rolling from Hillary's outside bar with Hillary's emails
Think I don't think you're going to find anything you're not going to be able to podesta this
Not going to be able to pizzagate if you need a pizza gate if you want email to be exciting and there's no
Pizzagate here there's just like
I think maybe we don't need masks
The conspiracy theorist
Community I think is burned out the pleasure centers of their brains come from this
Hard on people gate
Oh well
What is things that we know from listening to various periods of Alex's career is that
What's the summer for
Rage
Owl
Or into this
They got a good chance of doing it
We are stopping
Oh boy
For the
May 7th
This summer
Coming to
Do every city
Near you
Summer of Rage wasn't always a race war though and now that's true there was just like Financial collapse or like
The race war
Laugh like five or six Broadway Alban race war related
Get my butt
Yeah used to used to be just kind of like could be a number of different things as one note
Yeah
Anyway Alex gets to talking about fauci but not Apple TV
Instead he talked about
The factories going to get home
I think
What I was listening to this
I feel like this clip is really a good
Isolation of
Why people live
Listen to this show
This satisfies some emotional needs that these listeners have
If you're trying to get evicted
Stop to The Gallows Pole
Coming
I told you to come
The snowball too big
You killed 20 people
You will pay
I see it in the Stars
I see it in the card
I seen him at Ely
I see it in the bone
In the room with my dear
Your fault
You are distraught
Justice is right
Just commenting
I think people just
Have some sort of the gratification of hearing someone say that violence
Who's coming to the people that they've
I've been trying not to like yeah it seems like
That's
That's very televangelist televangelists
2A
Realty
Also no false
Yeah
Yeah yeah
At least at least sinner in the hands of an Angry God with felt genuine you know
Doesn't have to try
So one of the things that I think is always
Talk to suss out
Like who's on what side
We've had a lot of changes over the years
Yeah so I regret to inform you on the on the side of
Secret Patriot
I don't talk about
Celebs
GOP
Now we know
But I'll explain to the literal devil is behind his enemy
Yes
So
That must mean
That all of the people who are on one team
There with the Devil
Conceivably with God
Yeah they trying to avoid moral gray areas very
And that way we did have the UK
I was looking good when brexit was going through but apparently Boris Johnson is a traitor
You think they're up in the air
Yeah yeah unclear where the UK's going to fly
Should not forget
At the queen hits
The dictator button I forgot about that
Spinning plates
These days
So many spinning the queen is a secret Patriot and forgot about that would like to I would like to know if the pope is
It's still in jail
I need to know did he
You know or has is
Cuz this is the pope hasn't
Did said like new things that are bored
Conservative than they were before
Fake Pope even like
At an actual clone who's just unable to break the programming
The same old Pope
I need to know
I don't know if we'd have to ask Steve
Anyway here are the
Okay we have it we will lay out of
Who's who's good
It's not surprised
Islamic
What time is China the EU
Hollywood the blue City Blue States
The UN
All again
America
Wow
And the Brazilian people
We got Brazil in their check.
Did Russia United States did Brazil vs everybody
A lot of people inside the United
Country at least get more above the left-right Paradigm the
That's about the most
Here's what we got going on okay we've got we've got everybody
And then we've got
Russia United States in Brazil
Definitely not
The new axis of Evil
That would be a crazy thing for someone to say
That these countries are very similar right now
To Italy
Germany
Okay
Yeah I find it interesting
We not not the sort of other countries that Alex feel kinship with me at all
Like his guys
Bolsonaro
But
I find it interesting the way he
The rest of this is so stateless
It has to do with the blue CDs the blue States in Hollywood
So much of it is like
Half of this country's going to have to go down
If
You know we're going to be able to
Make this
America
Make it America
Yeah I mean it
Honestly
Siri's Quest
That I mean obviously
If MBS
Send Alex like a letter that was like
Hey I'm a Seeker
Christian
We're not going to
Not persecute Christians in Saudi Arabia anymore
That's not right
Yes he loves what NBA
Does
Defendant killing khashoggi
I think
Even if MBS didn't go that far
I I think that he's made an overture inside you're right about the club
I will have my guy will not join your religion but I will follow you again
Demonic
Pretty cool
I know what I heard a lot of stuff about
About them in the past and turns out that was all lies
Is it good Christian tried like I might have been a long time coming by every day of
I've never taken back any of those comments suggested that what I said was not true
I don't care
Alex spends an entire segment
Talking about
China
And
Exhausting
Because it's all kind of stuff that we've gone over in the past
Like his grievances about Chiang Kai-shek
8 PSI unloader valve course
China has
Double cross
The globalist
Across the globalist
On multiple fronts they're not doing the one child policy
Military system
Add enough
How to say we won't build Miro battery
Only buy from China
Shut off the main pipe
Wife to the Midwest
We are under
Horses running
Tulsa car years ago
Killed each other
Obvious is this
Please don't forget
She's 9/4 +
Yeah so apparently
Alex's
Pretty mad about Biden
Going to Tulsa
To celebrate pay respects
Do the anniversary of
The Tulsa Massacre
Weird
Yeah I'm surprised that Alex would not want to to have that talk
Talked about even mentioned
Recognize or even have any
Exist within the record
But you know what
Weird
Last year Trump schedule the campaign rally in Tulsa
June 19th
Which understandably seemed a little not great
Oh yeah because
June 19th is Juneteenth
Is the celebration of the ending of slavery in Texas was the last state where we still taking place
Tulsa is the site
Of the Tulsa Massacre
Which occurred on May 31st and June 1st in 1921
When mobs of people destroyed the Greenwood disc
Street in Tulsa they largest concentration of black wealth in the United States
Obviously
The combination of trump going to Tulsa
Seems like a little bit
I'm not just not just moms of white people organized mobs of white people with the
F****** military on right
Side so yeah rescheduling that event
I'm very understandable backlash
He did say in a subsequent interview
Quote
I did something good
I made Juneteenth very famous
Actually an important event in important time
But nobody had ever heard of
Wow
Oh man
Problem with any of that but for Biden to visit the Greenwood District to pay Allman
How much do the Tulsa Massacre
That's a huge problem apparently because
I guess
I don't know
I think one of the main reasons that it is such a huge problem
For conservatives
And why they absolutely do not want
Discuss it whatsoever
Is because
Is it is the marriage
He's that they love the most
At cross-purposes
Switches white people
And wealth
And they can't say that it's okay for the wealth to be wiped out
Without saying that it's
There
Ifucking races
And I can't say that it's not okay for white people to murderer on masks
Because they're giant f****** race
So they're just trapped in the space of like
You can't earn your way out of racism in America
That's what they're saying
And that's their message is always yet know you can pull yourself up by your bootstraps
The real messages
If you do that
You will be murdered and slap
Down again because that's what they need
What are the other things to not to not to totally jump-off subbed
You was talkin about these pipelines in
And stuff
Politics be that states
Can opt out of my flight
Biden saying that
What states
Not participate
I don't know it's just there's just nothing
Nothing that would be like exactly what he would like if Trump did that he be like
Power in the states
So there's a big news breaking in the middle of the
China made a comment
So when you see the comment of shinies come out in their official publication State can you investigate the lab we're going to Nuke
What a list of cribs for you
When we come back who the traitors are
I definitely don't like the idea of someone tearing a list
Do Traders on their show specially Alex someone who has a participation sport
Philosophy towards historically listing Traders is usually good idea
This story about China paying for articles and some Western Outlets
Not news
That's an old story about an english-language China Daily
They paid to have articles place than Outlets but all those would have had to have an alert before informing
Readers it is
The paid content
I don't like it but it's definitely not.
I'm gone in like huge deal that Alex is making it out today
I asked for the nuclear war thing Alex's line
True that there's a Newsweek headline with those quote
China's State media says country must prepare for nuclear war with us after Biden asks
For covid probe
But that's not a statement that's meant to convey a causal relationship between the two things
Which is what Alex has reported
He's saying that the Chinese government has said that they
If we investigate the lab
But that's not what this article as saying at all in this article is his primary source
The article is about comments made by who
The editor of the global times
The commons had to do with how there was growing tensions and us China relation
And the quote China sees bunch of America
Cuz actions and comments
Encroachment on itself
Who wrote an op-ed that essentially boiled down to the
Quote
The number of China's nuclear warheads must reach the
The quantity
That makes
U.s. Elite shiver
Or should they entertained the idea of engaging in a military confrontation
Vagina
The comments were an escalation in an arms race kind of thing that I think sucks
But they also want
If we investigate the lab Theory
That's nonsense
It's right in line with Alex's narratives that he's been building
So that's going to take precedence over the reality of the situation that
Honestly we should
Not be thrilled about
I mean
Wild
Wild to have the headline be
Chinese man says Reagan had a point
You know like
I don't I don't understand yeah of course
Historically you should have more nuclear weapons to keep the United States from invading you
I don't want people to have any. I don't want nuclear weapons at all no absolutely not
Absolutely not
Yeah it does make sense
For a power in the contacts
Text of
Heightening tensions
I feel like we should make it so no one will attack us because it looks like
Summit
Everybody's everybody's pumping out Iraq war propaganda about the understand that
I would prefer we take another Direction with it and deescalate thing
Onana on a larger
I get that thinking and that's thinking that is
Behind that
That comment not that if you look into the lab will nuke you
Take that again
Kissinger was like we got to have this
Why like listening to Alex's kind of a dead end
It's because there is a reality that you should be aware of this Newsweek story you know that is
These kinds of
Conversations are happy
Or making comments
It will be an official Outlets are in iPads that are like
We should bulk up our defenses to ensure that no one attacks up that's f***** up
It doesn't necessarily reflect the government policy
But it is something that is worthwhile
If you listen to Alex
The weight of the story is going to be presented
Do you is
The Chinese are so afraid of us investigating the Wuhan lab
Ryan
Is a Jetta
Because what what do you do with that information it's not true
Nope
If it's it's ridiculous now it's just
You saying see they're so overreacting to it it's obvious
That's all he's he's not asking a question
Not saying anything
What he's really doing is
They would
Hey they wouldn't act like this
If they weren't the cause of the Wuhan lab leak
Beyond
You know basically
So this episode Alex is really obsessed with her interview the Judge Joe Brown
No no no you cannot see the only point of it is that Judge Joe Brown think
That
The stand
Larry Joe Brown
I used to watch Joe Brown a lot because it was on during the day
Me and my friends would sit around
Get high
What's judge
I love you just got up from a nap
So annoyed by everybody in the courtroom
But you mean to tell me
I liked his demeanor quite a bit
But here's my okay so just Brown says the bidens erase
If judge
Judy comes out and says bye
It's not a racist what we got to go to judge Mills Lane
How beautiful
Yeah I mean look no disrespect
To Judge Joe Brown
You're the judge and all but
I think
When it comes to
With your real treasure is easy don't think you can be on those shows and I'll be a real judge
I think you have to be a judge
I don't know if that's
True that might not be true
Definitely.
She is a judge
Maybe Judge Joe Brown's a realtor I think he is
You get to be a judge and then get on TV
We should explore this more but you don't
It sounds really f***** up to me now that I think about it so they've been
Practicing judges food on the bench for a long time and then they get a TV show that seems wrong
It did seem strange but it also is a good
Good career path you're not wrong okay
Joe Brown
Is he
Joe Brown real judge
Judge Joe Brown is a former American lawyer and television personality
He is a former Shelby County Tennessee Criminal Court judge
Former Arbiter of the arbitration based reality show judge.
He was formerly a judge in Tennessee
Okay yeah I would imagine that if you're ever on one of those shows
You're not an ass
That's where I got confused
Like what I filled out my Chicago ballot and I was voting for judges of
Then another that connected to my mind was obviously I was voting for a Judge Mathis
No I didn't
Yeah I think it's a good sort of late-career moves your someone
Charisma and
Can.
Court hearings fun
Absolutely
We will meet again
To settle this next to issue okay
And now it's going to happen in
That's not good
Fauci and Bill Gates are being destroyed as we speak
I told you months ago they will be politically
Someday I believe will watch them both hung in public
What kind of China
It's not communist China just read the new customer
Read message
See
See how that information ends up being used
That's silly
Dude
Does everybody know that
That like now in
In the modern world
When when they see like public hangings in a
The TV show
The movie or
In real life
Those are the bad guys
The good guys are never doing public hangings
Yeah it seems rare
What's up
Yeah I mean book
I struggle with this
Because
On the one hand
If anything that Alex was saying we're true
These people are enemies of humanity you're not wrong you're not wrong
That's true I mean if they are wiping out millions of people that is Drew I do think that you should
Probably
I think so
I think that there's a narrow area where death penalties might be
Maybe we go ahead and genocidaires can get the death
I'm fine with that I feel like that's an arguable
As a as a relatively Fair solution
Spectacle part I do I I certainly don't think that would be healthy
If you
If you didn't do that everyone becomes
B receives about how it didn't really happen
Traffic reports still alive
Negotiate
We don't have to we don't have to
Indicated that he's okay with a lesser pain
Okay good
You have to say it I don't want any harm
Bill Gates and fauci
I want them arrested
I want their record brought I want
Public trial
I want a jury Define
Them guilty because he has overwhelming
They are incredible villains
I don't think execution
Let them spend the rest of their miserable lives
Publix
Play
Animals in a cage
There we go again
Joe Biden
Alright man
I'm okay
That was all right what a gracious guy though is offering life in prison
It is nice to to say a lick
Look
This requires a public hanging
The Mandarin
We will keep you in a dog
For the rest of your life
And that people walk by
This is what happens when you release plagues we put you in a box
Yeah that's about right
Alex has Behati
Sequins on
Who are a couple of twins
As their name suggests
Yeah
They are conservatives
And
Jon Huntsman
Best joke
He used to be
Hodgetwins
Today is somebody penny
Said about Chris
The climbers you don't want to
Celebrate that why y'all want to
Celebrate something that happened
100 years ago
The talking about the
Don't reason why they want to celebrate these things
Ambisome anything
Joe Biden in the den
Democrats in people after sex
Just going to give them reparations a restitution
You're not going to see any in it
Any of that
Till this day black
White folks
Black labels and Vulcan
Umbrellas with these people
But doing today
Yeah using them mentally enslave them
The only reason why Joe Biden's they're actually asked him
Preparation for what happened
Like to survive
Somebody's doing All-American shutdown pipeline
Last year
It's horseshit that Alex is saying like yeah of course
Why why
Why Alex
Why
You don't believe that for a second
You're saying that because you know that like
Saying
Don't
Yeah absolutely
Mel
A baseball should go whizzing right by his head
Just as I like warning shot do it again man
Claim that you're fine with doing some people reparation
Break through the air
That one of the reasons
That's the Tulsa
Masquerade
Particular is
Something that is brought up in the conversation about reparation he's because it wasn't
Justin attack on people losing attack on black
Exactly
Do you know one of the reasons
That's
Some of these issues have rippled through our country's history so
Resident please
Because
Of the exclusion
Of non-white people
From participation in the mark
And generational wealth
Exactly
That was a giant attack on exactly that
And I think
Pretending that you don't understand that is a little bit silly
Yeah I think if you're a commentator than
You're going to come around and say that
People only remember that event
Because they want
Thought something
Yeah they want
How to Gilt biting into giving them some
I think you're a piece of s*** I think I think that's a shity opinion
That like
Idea of Alec
Sexy even being like well you know there's two survivors so yeah they the government should help them out or something
Sing like that
That's absolutely missing
The point of wiping out generational wealth
You did there not
Two survivors of that Massacre there are
Countless survivors of that Massacre
That's the point
Apologies
He's a
Voiding specifically and kind of like
Detracting
Is what I was
While at the same time confusingly saying that it's okay to give something
Take to those two people
Again I would just ask
If I were anyways H it in a position
Hodgetwins
Please say why that's okay and it's not okay another absolutely
So these people had something
Right right
So they deserve recompense and some for correct
Okay
Take this a step further I don't understand there are more steps
It's not
So there's been a lot of talk about Heather's coming in Dyckman
Trump going down July
Rodger Stone
Alex has been
Warning people that he's going down on the 4th of July
No I thought he was going to be reinstated no no no
Maybe who knows maybe they'll indict him and magically like
Like a Phoenix Rising
From the Ashes who will become president
That could be
Maybe
Maybe the Democrats just want a third go in a
You know like a f***** up the first two real bad
However The Hodgetwins
They do not think that this is
Is real
Distraction
I don't I don't
Getting indictment
Vetted president
Everybody's investigate this man they have found nothing
I'll be shocked if
Doing anything
That exists just to destroy
Doing the artists in Arizona in the
That's what they really don't it's just a distraction what Bonds doing in Tulsa
I mean
Everybody on Main
Mainstream media on the left
Just lost their minds.
Talking about
Woman they started
Ashley aadatan de Brazil
I'm like I don't understand why they will be so UPS
Unless they tryna
If you're so sure
Did Biden won that election
Why don't you let
Everybody go in
The result
This show
Entail
Everybody that's on the right
How stupid and naive
You show everybody
In America
Hello
What's going to be on car
That mean that's just a dumb argument
Take the exact idea and
Just place it wherever you want with the story that you written for yourself
Good example of this or whether or not there's any truth to it is
Why won't Trump release all this financial information if he
Has to be afraid of
And that's a story that you can write for yourself it may be more likely than
This whole election was
Metal rod for whatever but
Pretending that you know what would be found if someone looked at something
I'm at why they're not look
Looking at it is just a dishonest
Kind of game
Yeah I mean
The thing about that though is its
Eminently reasonable from what we
We dunno
Is that if you really went through just about any billionaires know any billionaires finances sooner or later you
Find some
I'm crying like not like maybe not a big crime maybe not nothing but you'd be like
There's no way that you can
Get to be a billionaire without something along the way being f*****
I understand that and I think
That you could make
An argument
For what you might
Expect to find but I don't think that you could argue definitively in the way that they're arguing China deflate this is what you would
The Trump won the election from history about elections
Especially this one it is really hard to cheat
The entire country
Yeah really tough maybe impossible
Also
This
Same
Pattern of
Why won't you let every everyone invest
Instigate this you must be afraid of what's underneath
You were just to apply that
The Trump baby like no no he can't have it because that's why
It'll be a hundred reasons why
This is not the same thing
Yeah your b******* argument of like
They have a real opportunity to make conservatives look stupid.
Now get the f*** out of here that's Pro
The f****** you dick
Speaking of trolling
Wouldn't Alan West Betty Wright governor of Texas
Hell yeah
Just after this episode
It's probably at least partially due to Fallout permit and attending and speaking at the qanon conference last week where am I
Flynn said there's no reason that what happened in Myanmar shouldn't happen here
You didn't serve for Cherries long for a long time
Time in his time and in that position
You changed the GOP of Texas's slogan to We Are The Storm
Which is about his over to reference
Wow
I would West is a terrible terrible choice for a leader but given Alex's Embrace of Marjorie Taylor Greene lately
He's kind of seeing the political utility of seeing these folks is like a new Tea Party
I think that you might tell you might
Expect to see more of that
50/50 shot Cornel West
Could become governor of Texas by
Like that is honestly they don't
Don't know
They don't know
So Alex wants Trump to get back on
Social media
Something to respond to good
Set a time
Talking about
Everything was better for us when people were constantly talking about Trump same argument that they make
About the media saying like Trump is going to get indicted
Trump is driving ratings he's good for ratings of the doc about Trump
You know you're doing the same thing right
You know yeah
They wanted to get back on social media and The Hodgetwins
Interesting Theory as to why that hasn't happened
Social media
Billion followers on cab
If you join Gab
Tomorrow get 10 million the site works good they've got the bugs out
We need to get a message to Trump
Hundred thousand followers
Interested
On these other platforms he needs to be on he needs to be out there instead of
Right now in Big Jake
Banned from every
Social media
Communicate
American yeah maybe he's
I thought he had some time
China social media platform in the works
Maybe that's what he's waiting to
Lady body seed and not somebody else's
He wants his own
Fine so Trump is going to roll out his own social media site which ultimately turned out to be a Blog on his website those
So roundly mocked
But it was taken down permanently less than a month after lunch
It was so poorly done the Trump staff had to climb but there's a
Prince social media think he's working on
And it actually wasn't
Embarrassment After All In
Is wow
It was the blog version of the four c's
Brimstone
This is it for the episode
Unlike
Honestly he just interviews The Hodgetwins for the rest of the
Is it his time and then
Gerald Celente takes over
This wasn't about
I would say
But his emails ethics I can I mean
Wow
Dropping the ball
I suppose that's about a stirring an admission of
The emails being a giant nothing as you can
Could possibly go
Like
Because they don't it doesn't even need to be true it's never needed to be true
That's the way you can lie about any of it and they're still just like
I don't think this one has legs
I feel like that's what people are coming to the conclusion right now
Feel
Like
A big whale
And you know what here's the thing to like
The way that it feels like a big wave
From
Everything that I've been able to tell the thing
Alex's responds to Yorkshire
That's a real problem
Cuz
There should be something in there
That's really damning is any of the stuff that Alex was saying is
True
There should be
Something that is
Bucked up
There should be like a message between him and his Chinese handlers
Totally
Cuz then what you're saying is like the okay okay
So
You got
All of his private emails now
Man you got all this information
This is the
Proof that you are looking
4 and none of it
Backs up what you're saying
So you then have to say like
No no secret email
The point of ever leaking anything if it doesn't prove what
Like you're just going to say the secret
It goes back to
Being like you got a real opportunity to prove
Conservatives are idiots right here
Doing it for us
Yeah if you have this giant to crotch
Is it weird that Alex loves
To use the great work emails that have come out
That
Banquet beef
Something that you could use to
Builder
Narratives that you've been building forever
You think that this would give you some kind of an insight into what was going on and instead
So much of the emails that I've read are very indicative of
Learning along the way and like
The changing awareness is
Like
Beginning
People did not know a whole lot
In
I don't know it kind of
Weirdly
Reinforces reality
I mean from
From what I understand it is really like
Reinforced my I suppose
Confidence in the people who are doing
Because
At every point in time you know
Obviously looking back
You would say obviously
If we knew everything we would have done it differently hoping they handled it better duh
But the way that you see the
Progression there is
Exactly how you would want
People to do it as we
We get more data where
Finding out whether or not this data is useful or non useful we're taking the data that we can use
And we're using it to refine our process
We're taking that refine process putting it back into the system
Getting useful and unusual data and then refining it a little further
And it's like that
Exactly how I want
People to work
That's all I want
Like science did you hear anybody
You just making these giant guesses
No point in time in the emails was it like
Hey we don't know anything about Hydrochloric win or how it works just yet but
What you go ahead and say is great
You know like it didn't happen like that and the fact that it happened for other people like that should give you giant
A realization that there
Dumb
But that won't happen
Probably not cuz it would be
Hard you have to think
Yep
It was kind of a bummer cuz I was hoping for a little bit more stuff to dig into as opposed to
New salmon that you read all those emails
On your gun for a werewolf it ain't clear
Profile of a metaphor
But I also like I didn't read all of them
But I read enough to get a very general sense
What a lot of these are
Mnn
The people are talking about
In the conspiracy sites
And Alex's
Just doing nothing here
On the 2nd
Bummer
Yep maybe maybe later or maybe maybe
Leo zagami will come up
Confirm to work with
Let's hope I need a big swing out of these emails cuz yeah
Is so distant this isn't even a check swing
This is a whip
Yeah and you know this is this is also you know still a little bit like on the shorter side of an episode
Still like
Getting back adjusted after vacation
I've been on vacation for a very long time and I did not realize some of the
Sleep disturbance oh man of the challenges and appreciates folks
Giving us a little bit of
Hour and 15
We're getting it on Friday
We're going to get there come on now for that but until then
Website.com
Twitter
We are at record that now just not go to bed Jordan we're also on Facebook
Please find a local charity or Bell found in your area to help out people
Doing God's work
Omniome Leo on dzx Clark Antero Ruckus I am part of
Asparagus
Alex
Birthstone colors