Damn important
I have great respect for knowledge b b
Flashlight.com
Sit around to drink novelty beverages to words without their sweet and talk a little bit about Alex
Oh indeed we are Dan had a little thing we were going to just
Old habits die hard
I don't know
What's your B
I mentioned this to you I decided I was going to give
Ohio another
And then I just go to Lost
Pinterest
And not make it very far into it
You were telling me that there's this at the New Ireland.
And so I decided I'll go
Give this a shot
You buried the lede
Holyshit
I went to Ireland almost immediately instead of horse you now can ride a giant cataract
The white bright spot is now I'm riding around
Discover it on your own cuz I knew you're going to go
It's the best
Horse
And I could be happy
Now the game is back in my good graces
And I'll probably finish it because I have
Cap-friendly
Striped throw as many pets at you in the
That is nice
Yeah
My bright spot via as you made no
Or probably don't the French Open is going on right now
Good chance that Rafa and Djokovic are meeting for there roughly
Play 600 time
Djokovic head by one win
Closer the Kevin Owens
Destined destined to fight forever ever and ever and ever they're the two best that ever lived
Along with forever
And that's just going to be great tomorrow
Today or whatever you're listening to us
I imagine
Rob is going to wind up winning cuz Djokovic has looked a little bit shaky.
Is when the French Open 13ty
Feel like the French Open is happening like a week or two ago
Just keep happening
Is every every year so I feel like there's some tennis thing that I just always assumed as a
The French Open The Tabernacle
Team French Open
True
So Jordan today we have an episode
From the past
Things are better Jordan shoes
In the present day
And
What are the things that was like alright I definitely don't have to
What about the past was that
I kept seeing people posting that picture of Alex at Astor
Strip club
And I just lost my patience
With a depressive
I don't understand how being like
A viral tweet on Twitter
Like I don't I don't
Who cares instant reaction a lot of people were telling me about it and I was like that's
Okay
He's a monster
Good for him he can go to a strip club
It doesn't it doesn't really it doesn't really make anything he doesn't make any
Larger Point other than like
I think there's something weird about going to a strip
I mean I suppose
You could
Probably try and make the argument that it's hypocritical for him to be
God blast it all day every day you met me at a strip club to talk your way around that
I'm a man
How are you could say
I went there cuz I had a business meeting and the people I was with one of those you don't understand what it's like to be in the higher echelons of business
The run-around business I'm totally
Yeah there's there's a hundred ways you could
To get around the quote-unquote hypocrisies of it
I don't I don't know I didn't look into it too much but it looks like he was in a bathroom
Look I hate I do
I hate Alex Jones
I will say that if someone was taking a picture of him the bathroom I think I was a violation
Of someone's right
Pics of privacy.
I don't I don't think
It's cool to take pictures of people in a bathroom
I don't know I imagine maybe he has a rebuttal to that but I don't want to
Talk about it I just don't care
2/20 blackjack
Damn it that's the wrong one again
This is. That I've been looking forward
The covering because as we know the debate
Application begin
Yes around this time
He's been screaming about how they're going to let the Bass party run every
Everything
After taking over
Bushes in the globalist plan for
They're going
To be in charge of Iraq
Cuz they're basically CIA exactly
See how that would be affected
Goodbye
You know how Alex is rhetoric
This is an over the weekend
What's goes to Kansas City to do that local radio station
We have a couple of dangling thread either going to come together in this episode
And I'm excited to get to it first
Let's say hello to some new walks
The first possibly Pluto thank you so much you're not about to walk
Thank you very much too or flooded
Next
I like that one too
I would go to a CPA
I would go to that if it was a cold war theme Blazer Tag Place
Totally awesome
Next Liam we know your favorite food is pickles
I'm a policy wonk
Omar ChaCha
I'm a policy wonk wonk
Us to give it as a policy
Pennsylvania
APA is a bunny charity like a rescue animal charity
Trying to expand and you can go to their website and donate if you want to help
Hell yeah
I was very close to trying to adopt one account
There are you can't now.
I'm a policy wonk
Lego robots
Jordan
Just listen to Jordan stand-up on YouTube and really enjoyed it
And Derek's brother Connor your now technocrat cake graduation
Engaged
Recently
I hope you and Mallory have a great time with your life
I don't know how to say words
I'm a policy wonk
How's your 401k
What's the business
Money off that heroin
Usually large
Thank you very much
Especially Tammy for donating to our show just to make sure everybody knows that I might have a stand-up
Video on YouTube
We're going to get into this here but first
Steer is Nautica
Is a good thing
Holyshit I nailed it I did some of the things
Bethany felt like really Alex Jones
I do I do appreciate that
You got to love yourself
You know
So we start here on the 15th
It is a Thursday and
Is still covering the bombing
In Riyadh
Didn't happen
I recently interviewed
You recall it was a residential complex
Compounds kind of area where a lot of westerners were known to live
In the intervening time since then some more information has come out about the
Particular West
Turner's that we're living in these compounds that appear to be the target
Write that into this is what the Direction the Story is going to
Local Company
Where I said
Group is going to be involved
Well guess what
Guess who owned the company
Are wild
So the company in question that were apparently the targets of this 2003 bombing in Riyadh was the vanilla Corporation
It's a construction business that was founded in 1931
Has a deep history of international contracts
Are you at Center
Princeton Street Vietnam War Vino was Tas
Asked with maintaining power plant
Over there overseas
They're actually pretty well-known for this because in 1967 approximately 2,000 Korean workers at a vanilla plant in
Cameron Cameron Bay
Or dissatisfied enough with their conditions
They rioted
From Shelby standard the book the rise and fall of an American Army us ground forces in Vietnam 19th
65 to 1973
The primary cause appears to have been dissatisfaction with
The food served
Particularly the shortage of rice
The Koreans refuse to eat their Saturday meal on November 18th
Then went to the vanilla mess hall
Where they turned over tables and attacked several American
Before Steve Marriott
Can project manager to eat some of their food to show them how bad it was
Vanilla Corporation civilian took out his gun and shot three Korean
He was that Mama been severely injured
A Korean shot another American
4 days
I like you say company that does
Stuff for American government
Since 1931
Not since 1931 do they were founded in 1931
Government contracts in what are probably War zones or a lot of the time yes
Yeah a government contract began during the
The Chinese Civil War when they were hired to ship supplies meaning
Weapons
Duchesne Kai-shek
No weapons to Shanghai shek
I'm sweating again tomorrow
Point there
What's really most notable about this company however is that in 1975 they landed a very lucrative contract to train.
Saudi Arabian National Guard
This is almost certain
This is almost certainly why they're building was a target for that attack
In Riyadh not some obscure connection
Can people Alex
Insisting on connecting ever 12
Back in 2000
Impact their headquarter
In Saudi Arabia been baumbach in 1995
Something
Attic people
No to do yeah I mean your
So
This happen
I think that the people who would be trying to attack
The Saudi Arabian government
Maybe some
Rebel types or
Terrorist
Wouldn't know enough
To be like well
Let's not just
The tactic of helping with materials.
Here's the connection between Vino and Carlisle
A 1992 vento Corporation was Bob ibdm International Incorporated
Which in turn is owned by the Carlyle
However in 1997 BBM was purchased by TRW Incorporated
Which represented the end of their association with
The Carlyle Group
According to an article in the washer
The poster 1997 about the
The deal Carlyle had agreed to sell its entire stake and shares in the company to TRW in the acquisition
So there isn't even some minority ownership remaining to Alex
Pretend
Then in 2002
TRW was bought by Northrop Grumman
So the time Alex is recording this episode
And he wants to talk about this company in the context of the military-industrial complex is this would be the angle to take that we
Seems really simple to which is why you can't do it
By pointing fingers at the Carlyle Group Alex is making this piece of information fishes pre-written narratives about Bush but he's depriving the
The audience of access to any real contact
For the subject that he's cover
At the point Alex's on are here the Carlyle Group was six years removed
From selling videos parent company
And even if they were owners of vanilla's parent company
Still at work
Prove
Yeah man
I mean
To a certain extent
I think
Once once you're talking
Talking about a company that been bought like
Three times in 6 years
I don't even know if any of these people have any idea what it is they're buying or selling at that highest level you know what I'm saying
What do you mean George W bush knows what's going on or anything like that he's got people who are just
We will do all that stuff is bumbling around like a fool I don't know
They don't know what they're doing if they're buying those kinds of companies and then selling them a year later for what I understand
For reading some of these articles
It was a period of time where there was rampant
Consolidation and murdering going on in terms of these
Is international conch
Contractor rights
Let you know that's that's kind of explains a little bit of easy moving around right right
I don't know if
It just doesn't it's not compelling
Because you see the name Carlyle Group in the
Past of this company
I just
I don't know it's
It soft
Northrop Grumman is probably a
An easier name to just pull and be like problem
Doesn't come up at all
At all
The name Northrop Grumman doesn't come up at all in Alex's conversation steak indoors or come and see me
Can do it then anybody can do it Alex owns part of Northrop Grumman so it's all a conspiracy that he's trying to get people.
If anybody has founded
They're also apparently this operation is also apparently a
A front for the CIA
And the venelles one-time owners.
Crib
Articles
Right now
One of the things that I've learned to be very careful about when dealing with speculative information
Claims that people are groups are fronts
Does an accusation that's really difficult to work with because generally speaking at the claimants
Constantly without proof
People who make the claim often seem to think that the burden of proof is on you to show that some group isn't
The front
Which is a trap
If you read any John Birch Society text or book
From the anti-communist
Crusaders that Alex loves
One of the first things you'll notice is that every single thing is asserted to be a Communist front
And none of it is ever so
Substantiated
Gary Allan's book Communist Revolution in the streets
Accuses literally every civil rights organization every student activism group
And most bookstores are being communist
I'm not in the sense that like
Some communist my gravitate to these things like
You claiming with these exist exist
Explicitly
Crops oh yeah the Communist Party
Barnes & Noble
If you
My point is that one of the rhetorical tricks that I have the least interest in
It is like an unsupported allegation that so
Someone is a fraud
I was nonsense
So the question I just wrote down is like
After all these years what does Alex think the cia's portfolio actually looks like like if there was a
All of their fronts
Jesus
So in the case of an article in the London Times about how they were formerly owned by the Carlyle Group
The Carlyle Group had a history of contract
Thing with intelligence
Who's the headline that I was stalking
The thing
I would never come to you and say that vanilla
Absolutely hasn't done some work with groups like the CIA that's almost certainly
Considering their long-standing contract the train to Saudi National Guard
Allegations have been made
From a 2003 article in the LA Times
Quote
In a memoir former CIA operative Wilbert crane Evelyn describe using his title is
Female vice president
As a cover
While working
Africa and the Middle East in the early nineteen
It's definitely conceivable to imagine that a * people who work for the CIA if used fake employment at
Vanilla as cover
But that alone doesn't demonstrate the entire company itself is a
The front operation
I'm going out of my way to provide explanations for a while
Could be right and I still don't think his argument stanza
Up to scrutiny
No I mean
Here's here's what I get
From all of the Evan
Something Shady could be going on here
Here's what I give him Alex
F****** globulus inside exactly it's like I'm Batman I'm not saying nothing is going on
But I'm not saying nothing not going on
Initially after the bombing it was suspected that the attacks were on a housing area known to be used by westerners living in Riyadh
As more details came out of
Kenmoreclear this is likely target attack aimed at
What may
Makes a lot of sense
From the standpoint of people who might attack the Saudi government like we were talking about like the assistant
In training do you National Guard
Saudi Arabia
Do you mind
My profile Target
Combatant
Target
The CIA could outright a run vinyl or they could just be a company that had close ties to the government and allowed CIA
Do use our businesses named as part of the cover
Either way I'm not sure really matters because the thing they're doing sucks
There's a much larger problem here with the
Entire state of private armies in war contractors
What's the jingle around Keys liquor
CIA in Carlyle Group
Because distracting is easier than wrestling with difficult information and looking at
Looking at the reality
That's that's what he's doing
And it's yeah
The wild
Is it again to a certain extent it's hard not to look back in the context of like
When he has Trump
He's fine with so much of this s***
You know he likes Blackwater now he loves all this stuff so
You know
Maybe part isn't real differences a hero
Part of the reason may be that he is he's doing all of these
Is jangling Keys kinds of things is because he wants
The fundamental problems to stay the same
He just wants to be in
Control of those fundamental problems
And how we react to that we know he wants to have a private Army
So why would he complain about
People who have private Army
Unless it's within the context
Pics of jangling keys over here certainly
You know libertarianism is not
Averse
Oh no no
Most Libertarian thinkers Seafood
Yeah
Alex receives about this
Today in Saudi
Turns out
So you sing the 50 of the 70 employees advento we're gone on a training Mission but what he's doing is he's trying to create
False impression
In the listeners had
Whenever there's an attack you'll always here claims at some select group was warned not to be there or been removed from the area beforehand be
Because claims like this
Simply really strong indications of foreknowledge
Probably
I don't want you to think
50 of the seven employees there weren't at work that day which is suspicious but that's
The buildings that were bombed were a residential compound where 70 American employees live
I'm not sure where I was getting the 50 number from but nine employees died
15 raspa2
Is not counting many who are merely treated for minor injuries
Also people who worked at vigneaux weren't at home
They almost by definition will be on a training Mission since
The reason they're in Saudi Arabia is a
Training mission
The words Alex's saying actually mean nothing
But they're meant to create a denser air of Suspicion around the bombing
Which is unearned
By the information that he's acting
Representing
It does seem like he's
Even presenting at the exact opposite
Weigh-in this far as
They were just at work
You know he's like they're on a training Mission meeting they're not at work but in this circumstance
It's there at work
They're not at home
You yeah he's mending it to be like
They were told they were short
They were sent
UAE
Right right right now he's trying to sell it like if the Pentagon exploded tomorrow but all the top generals Escape
Miraculously the day before you're like
Full episode
He literally does a couple times like
The janitor's world
No but I don't know about this
Sophos topic
And he reads a bit of an op-ed by Joseph Farah
The guy runs WorldNetDaily sure
And that is great one of the things that I think is really fascinating about this
Is that Alex doesn't seem to like WorldNetDaily in 2003
Hi Mom just soak
Use he don't consider them a light
This is going to start with him reading from
Expounding a little bit
What is feelings
Call people
Most people agree you have
What
Republic
Uno
So weird
Yeah Alex loves WorldNetDaily now
Overlarge
Stretches his group seems to think that they're neocon
Yeah at this
Yeah yeah but Joseph Farrow Road
An indication that they're coming around or something
I'm less interested in that bed that I am and Alex
Discussion about the
Specifics
About his belief that the right left Paradigm is is an illusion
I'm a big fan of how he confuses economic systems government system
I need number of differ
Listening to mostly more current episodes of Alex's show from the past five or six years
That idea had something to do with political parties
Even at the end of the clip he's making reference to the left and the right having something to do with giving you the illusion of having a choice
You look he's talking about voting and political parties
Yeah
Please 2003 episodes the concept is sort of taking a different shape
Little bit more about what he actually means back then
And I have to say that
I think it's actually way stupider than I thought it was
Seems like a political philosophy the
It's TaylorMade
To be defined by opposition
Which goes a long way toward helping
Make sense about the shows
Nonsensical
In the Trump era end
Now
What Alex is discussing the illusion of the left-right paradigm
I believe you have to just completely get ideas of liberal or conservative
Out of your head
I think Alex is operating on a completely different Acts
This government is bad
It's a pretty childish thing to express as your fundamental political beliefs
Especially if you don't have the
The courage to just come out and be a full-on Anarchy
If you're against big government than I'd like to remind you that
Small government
Is f****** huge
Compared to November
Leaving that aside
I want to discuss for a second why are Alex's conception of this being the only relevant access in politics is woefully dumb
But not the way to
Look at the world
The sole Factor Alex considers in terms of ideology is whether or not something is a system that includes government
Control of the
Command and control
Aspect
On the one side of the spectrum he puts communism socialism and fascism is systems with
Hi government
Control
Is an idealized version of a constitutional republic
Like which I guess it's supposed to have minimal government
Termite Control
Outside
If that's the only factor that matters
Then there should be no difference
Stalex between anarcho-capitalism
And libertarian
Both advocate for the elimination of the centralized state which would result
The system with even less governmental
Control over the public
Can exist in a republic
Both are conceived around people existing in a stateless world
Characterized by voluntarily construct
But obviously these two ideologies have a stark difference
Probably the biggest is their stance on private
Property
Anarcho-capitalist believe the right to private property is essentially the Bedrock of
Society whereas libertarian socialist to interview
Accumulation of
Into the same oppression one might face from the
What state does being carried out by a private Corporation
It's very obvious if you look at these two systems that Alex isn't really being honest about his political
Princess
If there's two schools of thought which
Both issues centralized governmental control
There are still political preferences that Alex has
The door on the left right
Spectrum
Private property is a matter of the left rights
Well it's true that most center-left
Concentra right people tend to agree to private property ownership
Chip is good that's not true when you go to the other end
Spectrum
Further left ideologies tends to favor
Communal ownership of private property or democratize workplaces
Conversely further right ideologies tend to believe that private property rights are inalienable human rights
No problem with exploitative workplaces because employment
Is a voluntary relation
Alex presents himself as being above left-right Paradigm because he wants you to think that he's talking about democrat-republican two party system
Stuff that exist in the United
It states
He wants you to think that because most people are disenfranchised with that two-party system and its
Easy thing to find agreement
Most people would be like
You know these aren't
Fully they don't fully encapsulated by
By ideology
Yeah if you look at it as like a lime
Between the two parties
Yes that is an illusion
That's what he wants you to think
But that's not what he's talkin
It's important to recognize that and and know that
You recognize that he's a liar
When he says he's about the left-right Paradigm what he's actually saying is that he hates
It's government
But he lacks the political depth to coherently advocate
Anarchy that he would prefer
And so just pretend
That Daddy answers
Republic
Yeah I mean I would also add into that level of
You know the type of person who wants
Capitalism
But you know
They're not going to be the people ground underneath the boot of cap
Capitalism
Listen
Beto
Saturday
PayPal shouldn't have all this money I mean I should have all of the
Obvious
People shouldn't have all this
Are you know so
Again you want to preserve so much of the system that gives you
You power over everybody
Instead of being like
I don't want any government wowowo then people might
Steal my expensive
Could fix that kind of feel like if you created his kind of left-right paradigm
World within there
There'd still be f****** cops
To protect his ship
So he doesn't have to
Like
What kind of a narco bulshit easy pedal
Cell
F*** off
Yeah I mean it would I would need from him is okay so if
The question is commanding
Control nonsense
Sound like what what
Vermont the government
Controls the population right
You can judge pop
That's it
If that's the case
Then you need to explain to me why a constitutional republic has more
Preferable than an anarchist
Because that would be the complete elimination of this thing that you think is right
You have to argue I guess if you're Alex that
A certain amount is a horse
And then
Okay why is it well because I like
I liked
Kontrolfreek
Numa Mikey this isn't even get into it like
Differentiation between personal and private property
And how many left ideology
Do you still believe in person
No property and the right does try to
To muddle those things a little bit it's easy
Yeah even getting into the differentiation
Between political
More economic models
And how Alex
Playing fast and loose
Between all of them you can have a fascist communist safe
Government and an economic model there
It's not a
Fascist
That's not how it works
Yeah and
I just think when you hear stuff like this it really it really
What does it helps me understand a little bit more about these
Assertive
Elements of Alex's costume
That he wears
To try and trick people into thing
Thanking Jesus you sent
Being above left-right Paradigm looks sensible
Because
You know you could say
You know
Republicans and Democrats are all the same there Bolton to corporate interests you are special interest groups
Sonia not like
You say that
I think you can get a lot of people to be like
Yeah you know what
Make some sense
That's not what I was talking about
No it's it's just a little bit of Disguise
Yeah I mean you can call yourself above the left-right paradigm
Fairly easily because
A winning strategy for both Republicans and Democrats
Is d'usse
Listen
The Republicans and the Democrats f****** suck
Electricity to be one of those Republicans or debit
Winning strategies
Yeah
It does it helps
It helps
Pathetic world
Yes
If your goal is to Enlighten an audience or help them better understand the world around them in the political conversations at their hearing
Exactly the opposite
What you should do
Communism and Fascism do definitely meme sound
They are just words that describe Imperial strongman differ
Colored hats
And convincing audiences that that's the case
Wixom entirely unprepared to deal with challenging political issues
Also if you take Alex's word than the Hallmarks of the sort of government that he hates Andy
Does not want to exist
Is one that's run by a strong man or Thug which is an Empire
I know apocracy means nothing
Standards Donald Trump
Precisely the candidate 2003 Alex Jones
Strongly opposed
In 2015 Alex no-trump was connected to the Mob and presented an image of a strongman as a facade he put on this
Is M8 here's a fake
Yeah
Drop made signals
To being open to Empire and Alex even defended Trump's desire to buy Greenland and claims
Space in the name of the United States when you want space
Truck Sales Alex's imaginary test
It's allegedly above the left-right paradigm
Alex still supports him
He actually passes Alex's real
Miss test
Is heavily
Dependent on the left-right paradigm
That's important to keep in mind
Important to remember that
That's really what motivates
It's such a bummer that
Like these Concepts like
Communism and fascism in all of that stuff
Things that really do take a
Book
Or multiple books or many many books to understand clearly
Let alone try and implement
And
Then you've got people who are just like
Communism is this
It'll short sentence
That's going to muddy the water
Nobody wants
To read many many books
I think you have you have that same problem
On the Riverside
Automotive
Certain ideologies or systems
Doing it over lease
Simplistically I think into two similar issues of
Watering down meaning
Confusing
Sitting here pretending I understand
Intricate
Absolutely it becomes you know
Why did you why did
Mark's right dust capital is so big he should have written a one-page ad in the New York Times and we all
Still would have gotten it right
That sounds simple theory is capitalism I got two words for you
And I'm done
Sansa goes on to another headline that I guess it's big news
Batman
Don't care anymore
This is a sad headline
I'm not sure there is any place being part of the news Roundup of a national radio show
I don't know
Sprinkle person hurt in accident
On shows like Alex's
You'll hear coverage like this alot
Because it serves a couple of important emotional purposes for the audio
The first is that a straw man is created of the heartless people who just exercise while the person next to them was dead
The Listener gets to imagine how horrible these people are Infield morally Superior
These imaginary people
The second is to demoralize the audience about the state of the world
Call the neuro their believe in their fellow person
The goal is to present a situation where the audio
Here's this headline and they imagine that these people in the gym
Continue to workout
Fully aware that this person was dead
Because that's shity of that
If they didn't know the person was dead and thought possibly he was
Just resting
You can't really think this is a story that highlights
The moral degradation of the broader culture it's really more just a situation where people mind their own business at the gym as a tragic
Coincidence bothering stranger
It's sad and unfortunate but it's not like
This is not a new story that like illustrates
How bad people are
It's like he's trying to admit he's trying to do a sequel to Boondock
Saints
But it's about people at the gym or just like minded their own business I've been to the gym
Many time
People could have
There are people who I've seen laying like
Your favorite word supine never going to let me live that
Go to playing there and obviously
You know if you want to go poke
But also
Every time I have been around
They eventually get up
Cuz they've just been tired cuz they're working out
Imagine how many years someone does that if if you're listening to Alex Jones
The 2003
Right and you're like
Taking this one story to Heart you've missed everything else he's ever said but you got this one story
How many years are you poking people at
The gym before maybe you find a
Did that guy
You know you're just poking people out you're not
Alex has Craig Roberts back on
2003 Alex Jones of the story where people wants everybody died and I just not going to let it happen
The only way to be a good person with the Pope everybody
So Alex has Craig Roberts
Tobacco
Who is this
Conspiracy theorist
Type
Partially because he's going to be at in Kansas City with Alec
Venice Beach
You know there's a war going on in the world
Sure if this is obviously just a distraction am the financial collapse Court happening
Tomorrow
Gold
And then we hit a
Common theme
Rocket League
Blowing up
Everyday
Putin and the apartment building
Every
Single
That in the stretch
Everyday
I have I've been keeping track not a
Single episode has gone by that it hasn't come up multiple times
Cornerstone of his sort of report
You can just
Whatever you want
You certainly can
Lesson of America if you're a psycho you can do whatever
Ever the f*** you want
Alex
I'm kind of short and I don't really care
But what is interests
Is it Alex's and has an interview
With his water filter
No no
That's basically the
Destroy all the way through the car
We're going to get hit blah blah blah
Pick up the phone
Only product
That is Without Shame
The definition of Shameless
Scare people
They want to scare you with all these terrorist attacks let me tell you something people the economies collapsing so you need water
Filters I'm not trying to scare you with terror attack
You know I think we've talked about this a little bit in the past
A really long time
I think there is a way to do what Alex is doing in a responsible way
There are dangers in
I am
You know let's say if you have
It would be good to have a little bit of food
Storage in case of a natural disaster or something
When I was growing up there was a worry about tornadoes in Missouri
My parents had some canned food and water in the basement
Just as a like we never ended up needing it but just in case it's there
I always have an extra big bag of cat food on hand
Because
I have a cat and I don't want to run into a situation where something could happen and I'm not able
To take care of this thanks
I think that there is like a
It's not this
I'm playing on people's fears
Yeah there's a there's a version of this that is like
Looking at life responsibly and trying to be like well
You may need this
Right
It's not a terrible idea just in case
The other side of it is this
You're stupid if you don't
Get the water filters cuz of every terrorist attack in the economy going to collapse
Yeah it is
It is unfortunate that that's
Likes that combination of
When
Commerce and capital Mets
Psychology and turned it into advertising in there like we can get more stuff if we emotionally manipulate people than if we provide
Irrational argument self
We're going to emotionally my life
Do you filter sponsor just got some
Big news
From a major sign
Scientist but how great is filters are
Alex tries to set this up
Play virus
Be the filter sponsor doesn't have time to talk about this
Listen to Alex's appointment
Really
Well Alex
The trip
It if I can
Okay
Who is the famous scientist
Is that a famous scientist
Say the name
Then give the address
It has been approved by Marriott
Absolutely
Watson and Crick
Jonas Salk approves of my water filters now we have a special running
Naturally
How's the weather Gaston
Something that he's been promoting
Ring all day
He's so excited
He is a Canadian journalist named Barry's wicker
Guyot and
He does not like 911
Pics 9/11 was an inside job and have you
Has like the biggest deal
Like a huge Canadian Journal is one of the most important in the world
And berries introduction
Proceedings
Placements are real pleasure Alex
For the first time
Called aftermath kiddo
Question
Answered questions from 9/11
Francisco
For people to wake up
Tavares Wickers an interesting fellow
Everything I can tell he was a pretty standard and accomplished
Canadian Journal
He'd worked for mainstream outlets and then 9/11 happened in every
Things seems to evolve
Liquor decided
Except I don't think that's workers Gone full hard right
Or the Dennis Miller was ever funny
I don't know if this occurs when I get there
He decided that the mainstream media story about the attack wasn't real but
He did have a bit of a different angle on it than Alex
According to what he told reporter Terry glavin in a 2006 interview the end goal of the attack carried out by the White House
Worcester creative war against us
Okay
That was The Conspirator
In 2004 he would go on to make his own 911 film titled the Greek
Conspiracy the 9/11 News special you never saw
It's just as good and just as bad as every other 911documentary and has a title that Bears all the Hallmarks
The early days of Internet clickbait
4 people really got good
It turned into an art form into itself
Over the years he's continued to be a 9-11 truther and generally the sort of person you can count on to college
Just about anything or false
I got a recent interview he did with the Global Research NewsHour where he was
Discussing how the storming of the Capitol on January 6th with a bullet
I kind of expected to hear him doing some Alex stick
If you could
Do you think that the event was a false flag inspired or directed by Trump
Which honestly makes no sense
No I love it
The term false flag comes from the idea of a ship attacking someone while flying a different countries flags of that country
It's Brian
If Trump at a bunch of people storm in the capital of wearing Trump hats that's another false flag
It's just a straight-up correct
It does seem like that unless you are in
Implying that
Because it's so
So he's saying the Trump was also in on the setup
Of his owns
Supporters yeah but he does look a little Volkswagen order to discredit his own I don't ideology
Write could Trump be in on a false-flag if that's what I'm saying
Make sense
It's tough for me to say but listening is that interviewed kind of feels like zwicker is like an Alex Jones but with opposite politics
He's making wildly unfounded assertions and claims it don't make sense but he's also staunchly opposed to Trump and recognizes that like
Systemic racism exists cure
So
Yeah real moment that was possible in 2003
Probably not much later than that
They felt like they were in agreement as far as 9/11
Conspiracies were concerned but they actually didn't agree on anything
Because they're dreadfully far apart on the left-right paradigm
Paradigm is fairly important in reality
If you judge everything based on something position in terms of the right
Left Spectrum sure
Maybe that's a little bit reductive it's out there multiple axies upon which the judge
Pretending that that one doesn't exist is a
Rio's limitation
Barry
Oh boy
Banff
Barry says something in this interview
That if it were present day
Alex would lose his
Okay I'm on here at
Bertrand Russell
And he's Ten Commandments
First commandment is never
Yourself
And I think that is the first
So that's a huge tell for me that Alex doesn't believe his own bulshit
According to Infowars lower Bertrand Russell's writing outright admits that the globalist planted drugs
Kill off most of the population
Russell is one of the old school global
According to Alex was instrumental in coming up with and publicizing their evil plans
I can understand wanting to have a polite interview and I do think their times just to agree to disagree about
Thanks
Princeton
Did Barry thought that the 9/11 planes were remote-controlled and Alex out they were piloted by the hijackers
They could go ahead and agree to disagree without having a gigantic problem sitting on the table
We have a disagreement but not a fundamental contradiction
Not a deal-breaker
Barry isn't just saying that he kind of likes Bertrand Russell
Russell is his hero
Are you guys work for major papers and he taught college courses so it stands to reason that if he says that Bertrand Russell is his hero
He's probably read as much or more of his writing than Alex
This is why to me this cannot be an agree to disagree mom
In order for Alex
To maintain all the narratives he has in play he has to be agreeing to dis
Agree about his gas
Sakura worshipping a guy who's who he has red
Discussing the plans
Insta kill off most of the human population
There's no other reasonable conclusion
Do with the information provided
Other than that berries an enthusiastic
Globalist
Conspiracies
You love them
Yeah Alex should want to fight him
It does seem like Alex is like okay okay
I get it we agree that 9/11 was an inside job
So I'm going to
To gloss over the fact that your hero
Is
The architect of
Killing everybody
So we can really get to the bottom of this 911
Lego you might be missing the forest for the
Fallen trees if you weigh
Alex knows that there's nothing he can do and he can't really fight him on this cuz he knows the berries red Bertrand Russell open
Probably way more conversant on the subject that Alex is embarrassed
The issue is s*** about Russell's made up
But he also knows that he can't just let us stay tonight like
That's stand
Unless you end up with this Middle Ground as spineless agreeing to disagree about one of the top thinkers of the gigantic demonic
Conspiracy
But Alex has made his entire career
It's
Yeah yeah cuz
If you're saying that you're above the left-right Paradigm you should be more unhappy with
Plan instead of a like on the left there's Lovelace on the right what are you going to do
Loosen up Stuck In The Middle With very late
I think of it I think
Obviously this is major surgery
Spitballing and coming up with that what I think is the most likely explanation
I went to The Branding at this point is so dependent on him being able to pretend
This left-right Paradigm thing is an illusion. So for him to have someone who's ostensibly 911
Conspiracy theorist
Stew's on the left right left
Quality
Texture
I don't think he wants to fight with that guy
I think it's really important
For them to have some kind of an appearance of an alliance right
Especially with the way that Alex has been building them up as a reporter in like
Super important person in in Canada
And so I think
I think that's
Takes precedence over
This guy's hero is one of your main villain skaff
I think the berry isn't aware of
He can't think that he hasn't read
The same things that I
Well I mean
Because Alex is
Taking advantage of
The enemy of my enemy is not my friend
And and you can prove that because Alex is taking advantage of people thinking that the enemy of my enemy is my friend
Fairly simple
Open and shut
Elspeth Berry
This guy really really
You creep me out this guy so creepy
Bill in Alaska
I just had to call in I got
I got an enemy that hasn't been mentioned
And no
People want to know why this is why
This
In the mirror
Jim Jones
Case in point
I don't believe he was a
As people that phone
K
Wow wow you're going to need to sell me a lot more on that one
Not a lot more
Salesmanship on that take
I will tell you delivery a
Confident both
Creepy as hell
I don't like avakin
Bit player from Bonanza from Alaska telling me that Jim Jones was a good leader
Suicide cult don't hate the player hate the game
Here's the problem
People followed Jim Jones actually wasn't their fault
Their fault
Okay
Alright
Alaska
Cowboys
Tell you about this
The rest of the clothes are kind of
Blastoise
Kind of
Abhorrent
Sure
The interview takes
A turn
Hard
South
When Barry starts talking about his new DVD that has been developed
We're having incredible
Looks like it looks like we're moving toward
Population of u.s.a.
On your own and you write for newspapers in you
Papa John's
Awful
Like Alex straight-up laughing
Yeah that was not a I'm laughing with you
Uncontrollable
What's to like
Oh no
And there's also the problem of like alright even the rule of 10
Piezo 5000
Still not
For what Alex has the illusion that Alex
Has created about this guy
Throughout the report
Journalist in Canada and he can get the 500
Well upwards of 499 people to really get these
UCF
The Hertz the facade
You can tell there is a total change
And Alex
After this
Specific number has been given good like
I can't I know now you're nothing to
Pretend that he is like Rush Limbaugh
If he's only moving those many units like my audience
Just think there's just
I can't deny that now
Yeah
You know it is what it is
And it doesn't it doesn't go much longer but Alex does
Finish up this episode
Fairly standard
Alex brings up the boot
Bombings in
At least
Four times in this episode like it's really excessive
And then he says this about the Russian
I find this fascinating because in the present-day when he's trying to defend food and Alex will say that Russia isn't a globalist
Country is a system of crony capitalism
The positive thing now
Or at least it's not as bad as global
Bernie capitalism isn't a negative Commander
Control system in the present-day to Alex
I could speculate about what the reason for this change is
But honestly
Just be guessing
It's a glaring
It's pretty weird
To the 16th
Is
It's Friday
Analysis on route
Kansas City is going to speak at the local radio station
And he's not in studio
What's that a six-hour drive
From Austin
I have no idea
Probably
9 hours I don't know if he's actually
Driving cuz I
Think he said you flew back
I don't know I don't
The point is he take Friday off
Sunday
A show at this point
Do comes back on Monday
And
Here we go
Completely different sup
There now Maine
Control trigger
Control
Is there
Now
Wonder how
4 years ago
And I will be
Little bit later
Okay
Quincy
But the doubt it
This is this is not
I got to tell you
What the first hour of the show is basically just Alex saying over and over again that the new treasury secretary has been bad
Mouthing the dollar
Annette and this is leading
Do it collapsing in
Relation to the euro fine
This is the only thing that likes
Seed actually even in
In it within about the
The first hour
It is a
Desert wow
Wow
90 equals 8/2 what
It's
It's so great whenever people are like
Do this split Matrix is
Control and then your leg okay well 20 years ago
The Manchurian Candidate was telling us that the mind control is happening and then twenty years before that
I just
I just don't care what you think about movies
I just don't care
I would say the probably The Matrix
Has some ideas their explored maybe not as
Eloquently as they could have been
Confuses some people were
Further it has a aesthetic
That
A lot of people adopt
And maybe you could
Trace those things to some of these shooters
I don't know I also think I overthink
But generally speaking
When you have somebody
I can't
A couple stories that Alex brings up and its people who
Shot somebody and then
Said they're trying
Believe Matrix
Sure
You are
I'm not positive
Necessarily how these cases shook out
And how much of that was just a defense
Right
Right you know what I'm saying
Seems like something that could have been a popular defense
What am I going to be either plead guilty
Cuz everybody saw me do it
Or I'm going to shoot my shot
You know you do your shot sometimes you don't make a you miss 100% of the shots you don't take them
I was excited at least
To hear about Alex's thoughts about the Matrix
Sure
He doesn't get into one
Ether reel
It's a real desert I was walking around
Reloaded hadn't even come out yet
How much does say like
I'm going to DeRango's in Baker
Tonight is out in theaters
Actually I was going back through it cuz I was looking over the plots of those movies I
I'm not sure I saw the
The third one
This plot seems
Borod look you could watch it again and you'd be like this. I don't think this is and then you would forget it
Tomorrow I definitely saw the second one cuz I remember the Arctic
Yeah
Vocabulary
Instead of writing
Sure I saw the third one because I know if I saw the first two I would want to finish it
Call the third one I do not remember and then you move on
I was reading the puddle
How do I say okay let me see if I can receive the final fight scene
YouTube video or something like that but I
Remember that
How much do you remember from
The plot that you read
I'm going to see if I can't pop the Dome
The 3rd
Matrix
It's all right I remembered Broad
Strokes
Okay so you can give it a try
Neo just passed out cuz I'm the second one he turns out he can use electric power out in the real world
Up and he's actually in The Matrix he's not plugged in the Sick Bay or whatever
So then eventually wakes up and blah blah blah baby did The Matrix come out
He and what's her face
Staples go on Trinity they both go on a suicide mission into the evil place right
They fly up over in the sky and I like in the meantime
At the Zion
The final attack is going on
Spell ababababa on for a while but I understand so far so good
They got these weird Mech suits and then there's some heroic action cuz it's a war and I'll be moving you got to do that
Then Neo and Trinity they make it through Neo and the way I are both like
Hey man this agent Smith dude is f****** out of control
Right that says though
AI plug
Neo into the AI and they're like you better solve this f****** problem
Signs of being absorbed by
Orange
Smith Smith
After a massive
Useless
Pointless fight
And then the AI is like blowing them all up and they start over and everybody finally breaks the cycle and everything
School for awhile
I think that's me
Basically at
I'm out of breath
At all
Neo negotiating with the robot
About
Face comes out and it's all like dude and the robots mad do I don't cover that I don't remember that at all
Is weird the robot a I did a lot of roaring
Which seems like a weird thing for the AI to be into but is the a I would know what would intimidate a human
Yeah buddy
It seems like hey I don't know
He doesn't have eyes anymore so why would you
He conceived
Excited for the 4th what that's all I
I may have to go watch the third one
And see if I
Seems like
I can't believe that was the
Always bad
I don't know real bad
It sounded bags on paper
Buchheit's
Execution execution
I do wonder if the
I don't think
I mean I'll defend slightly Reloaded
Like I said that to not as bad
Maybe some people have said
I mean there is some fun things the Twins were cool
Sure
They turned invisible for a while and then they showed up that's fun
I got to watch that third one
The Matrix
What Revelations
See if I actually saw it but I was
Younger
Anyway Alex doesn't get into talking
Much but he does
I have some other news fresh from the
Bureau desk
It's in his imagination
What is reporting that basically that yeah yeah
Saddam got an amnesty deal
Yeah
I don't know who negotiated that one I think they left a few people out of bed to go she Asians if he got an amnesty
CDL with himself
I think that might have been the case app
Another familiar theme
Vladimir
Rebuild a blown up
Why would
No
Time in Moscow
Paramilitary forces
Alex talks about these
Ideas areas where Putin
Is not talking about this
That guy's bad talking about things that are
Create event
He knows to be true
Mount for him to change his position on this
He needs to show his work
He needs to explain
Why is that no longer trip
Right were you wrong here
Or did these events
Give a new explanation for all of this
He doesn't ever do that either service switch
And it's and it's not
Tumi
To go back and listen to this
And see just how consist
Simply it is just like a
F****** puta
These false wagon around
Yeah you know it would be ironic
If
What seems to be one of those like the main pillars of his
Everything is a false flag thing because these are
Documented events
Swear you're like
So his
Main evidence that you can follow up on
Is now
Not at all mentioned
And wiped away despite the fact
Then he still claims that everything is a false flag
Just not that
It's strange it would be ironic if you weren't aware that he
He's just a psycho that none of this matters
And he's going to use whatever he feels like using however he feels like you
Yeah so it's it's
Completely within his care
And this also seems a bit more like what you would expect from somebody who's like this anti-communist
Best Crusader type
If you're not like
Russia and China are evil at supposed to like
China's
I don't know it's
It's
I want to learn more about
I like how they keep those women from
I'm talking in churches
Feel good I want to learn more about
But I don't really know
Much more
Then Alex will not stop talking about Putin
Blowing up the apartment building
In 2003
A lot more
Detail to it but I'm keeping my eyes open and I'll let you know if I
Comes up
Has he already been on Artesia bunchers this is like in a very short period of time he will go on RT of
I'm not sure when he started appearing on that I know he
I would imagine
After
Hair like that let's see what Alex has to say
I guess not
So Alex is another guest at this point he's it's Dennis Cuddy
He's another
Conspiracy New World Order guy I love his kids music
Basically
Kid Cudi
I like a
His wife doctor Cuddy
From house and beat
Now you're playing the game
He's on for like the rest of the show and it's just
Rambling about
Basic ass New World Order
Conspiracy talking points
It's a lot of the same stuff we covered in the endgame documentary
Aboard the hell out of me
That's said it's a far cry from the content that Alex producer
These days
This is at very least a show that
Striving to be about an alleged
Conspiracy
It goes off track pretty regularly
It provides horrible info
Formation ignore stories in favor of headlines
But huge chunks of time
Are devoted
Unsourced accusation
About like a Bilderberg Group and Bohemian Grove
So when I go
Talk too much about this interview
But there is one
Very important moment
They use facilitators to through various delft
My techniques
We need a business
I must lead the people am I not their service
Here's what you
You say you want
Alex rovira
I've not heard them 2003 please can
Has clearly eating their butt
Most of all the content
Yeah that he's
It's okay it's kind of funny that I already brought up advertising in Psychology and then 20 minutes later he's like
And also
The businessman Levi look away from
Navigate to be horrified
So the caller calls Indian Cudi
You take calls
And when I was listening to
Cutty is old
It's cool like with his new world order
He has
The all the Talking Point
Points that you expect
Hiiraan old-time New World Order
Receive
Shows or
I bet he knows Bill Cooper
As I was looking through the hour of the time archives and he's
Spit on a respected 96 Amazon
How are the time like that checks out
Wow
He does her day job
I think he writes book
Probably goes on speaking
Things
I don't know
How do I get caller calls in
Has reported that Saddam Hussein
And this caller
Says that
One of our old friends
Joel skousen
Is reporting on something
A little bit different
Reported by Joel skousen
Yes
Blue the first reference of someone bring up skousen
Which is interesting
It's taken
Can okra 19 days into the month of
Let me know where we beginning
Such a familiar face in other. The time and the first reference to him
And
He thinks that saddam's in the United
Midstates Russia
They're both wrong
These guys
These guys and also that ending of just leaving it open for that now there could also be a double cross you never know
No they could anything could be true right now the evidence of which I have none I is all pointing towards this place
But I just made up so there we go
Do you have Cuddy
Who's been on in the month of
May 2003 already
And you also had Colonel Craig Roberts
Who was on who's been on before
She have some familiar faces
Starting to like
Appear to be there sure are faces that we know
Rack you know there's
I haven't seen any mention of Steve pieczenik I haven't heard anything about Girl Scout
Paul Craig Roberts you know couple of other folks who were like
Webster Tarpley
Sure these
Jerome corsi
These folks
Arnot figures in Alex's world
At this point or at least have not made themselves known
There's another person
Who also has not made himself known yet
I found it very
Confusing but this is the first mention
I seen of him
But I was wondering if either one of you
No
What
So I run a very curious that Alex takes this tone on this color brings up Bob Chapman
Haven't heard the episodes cover another. Time Bob Chapman is one of Alex's most regular gas
First track of years leading up to his death in two
Adam-12
He's an alleged precious metals expert who Alex used as a scene partner when doing extended commercials for Midas resources
The gold sales company that syndicated Alex
Also Bob claims to have been invited to a screening of a film of Ronald Reagan getting
True
For years Bob was on Alta show every Friday
Outside of people who host the fourth hour it's tough for me to think of
Give anyone else who had what amounts to basically a standing engagement on Alex's schedule
Do your Alex and he doesn't know what's up with him
He doesn't want
Talk about it in 2003 is really weird
Things get even weirder when you consult issues of his newsletter
The international forecast
From back in 2003
They're not all available online but there are two that I could find from 2,000
Free
Even back then Bob clearly had a working relationship with Midas resource
Special offer
You may also order it and sooner
Prince to the book The Beast from Jekyll Island
By calling - resources Incorporated
Midas resources will give you a silver dollar from the early 1900's
$12 value
For purchasing the book at its normal price
Of 1995
It seems clear to me that this business relationship with Midas is intact
At this point even prior yeah who this episode they were listening
So whatever weird energy Alex is giving off its
Seems like it's probably person
I ran over Bob's newsletters
To see if I can find any reasons that Alex might not want to associate with him at this point
I'm not sure if I see anything
In one of his January issues he predicts an imminent Return of the gold standard in the United
States because of the war in the middle
What a surprise
That he would want or predict
That the war is going to put pressure on economy
Fairly standard
Kind of stuff you know
Cialix
Disagree with that
He does say quote
Do Muslims believe they can destroy capitalism by force and gold to the Forefront and we agree that this could and probably will
Be successful
Which is a little weird but it does not seem like it's outside of Alex's wheelhouse didn't seem like you'd burn a bridge over that what a wild thing
Thing to think / even Wilder to say
Some of the next issues that I could
Could find were from July 2003 and honestly just kind of sounds like a transcript
Do something Alex
Might say it's his life
Quotes
All we can say is buy gold and silver coins and shares as fast as possible
The ship is sinking and there's no sense in drowning with the rest of the idiots
Incidentally exercise your constitutional rights and legally armed yourself in your families to the
This isn't going to be nice
The only thing I can find in there that I can see how it's being pissed off about is that Bob advises readers to buy gold
Inselverbot
If they have to invest
Austin currency that they are going to hide
They should favor the Euro or Swiss franc to the US dollar
I could be Alex thinking this was bad-mouthing the dollar like the treasury secretary
I don't know but
That's the only thing that stuck out to me as like
Alex would not like that
You should always favor the dollar if you're going to favor currency
Yeah
Could you like what happened to Bob
What they're suggesting is like
Bob went off the rails somewhere and
Saying that the dollar isn't the single greatest thing in the world
Probably
Currencies are evil
Reserve currency status of the dollar
Nothing had happened there was some
Problem
I can't get any sense of like what that's in
Yeah
Because Bob can't get out of pocket
You know like Bob is expendable
Maybe now
Hi Mary.
Video of a pagan
Incidentally Bob Chapman's in his letter is definitely
Play without a doubt written by Bob Chapman
Here's a lot of these folks who have these newsletters that are like
Bob cannot reclaim
He calls people who don't
Take his financial advice eighty-eights and he's basically just f****** with his readers
Don't forget as interest rates go back up to say 7 or 8% you will lose money on the value of
Unless you buy a par and hold to maturity
Most of you may be dead by then
We don't have all the answers but this is the way we see it we've been making these kinds of decisions for 43 years so we guess this qualifies us
The Voice our opinion
Power Rangers stuff
Considering this is like it's supposed to be Financial advice newsletter out of
You're all going to die
Ariat
Yeah whatever it's life-or-death
Barry some Swiss Francs at get a gun is this good financially
Yeah I have no idea what happened to the two of them but it's an open question that I'm excited to learn more about as we
We see him later on yeah I know and see him in 2009 Atlanta you know. Definitely
So I know that there is some sort of it coming back together
I'm going to guarantee that that no point do they discuss what their differences were
If I'll be able to learn more like another caller calls in
Specifics or something
How do I keep my eye open
Turn on this one
So what are the other things that I'm tracking
Very closely
Understand is whether or not Alex Jones believes he's fighting the literal devil
In 2003
We know what the present day he believes that the devil is the head of the globalist conspiracy everybody's
Speaking to him
Extra-dimensional Eeyore being possessed by demons true
I'm not entirely sure if that is
The case in 2003 so every time there's some kind of an in
Indication of something
I like to bring it to the Forefront
And I don't know if it says anything about Alex
Cody definitely believes in literal biblical prophecy
Google regulations as
Has the United
And when Rudolph Giuliani
Stated on cpanel
Capital of the world
New York City with a capital of the world and quote he was
Correct
And that is found at
City of Pharr
Chapter 111
Caldwell
You know revelation
18 +
Airport City
New York
The World Trade Center
Because when you get
Candlewood
Endomorph
Symbolic of the Statue of
Okay
Open baby coming up
Thank you very much
Alex doesn't necessarily
Jump in with him in the lips
Decode
Endtime relation
But he's also like that's amazing information that
He's he's encouraging of it in
The guest book
He's not engaging in it himself
I find that interest
It does seem like he's
I mean it from what we've seen he's allowed
Other people you platform in a hell of a lot of things he's always been
To jump in on his own
And and really give people a full-throated
Hell yeah revelation
The 18 is how we're going to get through this you know he does he does seem to be walked
Nightline a little bit
I'm so cut
He takes off
After a very long interview
And Alex
So you haven't seen the movie yet
Oh my God
What is Hindu / Buddhism up or whatever
But also
Maybe
Designed to make people
Nautical
Farm
A series of murders
Mine
We know they have the technology
Tonight
I don't like to speculate
All I'm doing is
I pull out my white glove
That would be like me saying
I don't like to check into things Alexei
I seem to do it a lot, I'm honestly a very quiet person
Can people live Rekha
He denies that for a long time I don't like to do that I don't like
To be loud
So I missed 19th
Is May 19th episode we one last clip and this is literally the only mention of the bath party
I bet I heard at all
And I should say that we are now past
The point where the policy of the pacification has been
Openly announced
In other people who are coming out and speaking about getting rid of
All party members within within government
And in such an today
Online
Well done
Walk outside
That train is coming
Hit me excuse me step aside
Don't
Yeah
She's a
Isn't going to work
Prolong
I guess it's fine
Now it on the 19th
Yeah forever
Framing like a day by Z sometime
Yeah this is not going to be the way that
This is this is this is
Isn't going to pass the smell test for very long
Thousands of people are removed from their posts
They're still in there
I think we're going to get more
In-depth into this stuff
In the coming days of
I think
Alex is going to have to try and wiggle a bit
And I'm interested to see how that plays out
There was actually like
You know a couple of
Really compelling threads that I'm starting to see in 2003 that I really want to learn more about
What is the anti-putin stuff Shore
2 is the DeMatha vacation
3 is
Alex and Bob Chapman
Find me a new condition
Expand that out to like
Side characters
Well it's like you're playing a sequel to a video game or a prequel
I like the main characters the same but maybe they're in a different
Place
Different NPC character
I wondering where the old friends are and where do these new people
I enjoyed I'm enjoying this a bit more
Continuous enjoying learning and discovering new things like you always have and now that you're
In the present Where We Are
Rarely learning anyting and often discovering the same things
Daily
This is new and exciting there's at least interesting context it
Ethics of disgust where is present day
Episodes
I do end up going
Could just be like
He didn't read this
Do we get to the 20th
Justin Alex I was hoping he'd seen the Mayfair
Because you know I love a movie review
He did not go see The Matrix
Yeah probably
So
But you can talk about it later
Control
Lank
Idiot
Correcting the record
Connecticut people slander me in
How silly
Silly for someone to think that the Matrix has
Crime like
I would never
They control mine
Does Amaya
Cheese's
Now the trigger makes
Please
I'm telling you
Stay out of my business
Gaston
I'm sure this is a wild guess
For Alex to have on for a number of reasons
This could never have happened in any other. Of time
And it does
Doesn't go super well but this guy named Noah shachtman
Who has an article in wired that it
Just come out about a DARPA program
Talk about it a little bit more
Alex distorts
Some of the ideas around sir
Surveillance
And such in order to introduce Noah
Corruption
Going in the grocery store
Noah on
The weather
I'm going to guess that you if you were
Find Noah shachtman and today and asked what do you think
Thinks about haven't been a Gaston Oz Show
You might not get an answer
In 2003
But now
In 2021
He's currently the editor-in-chief of The Daily Beast
Been out with that Alex screams about quite often
A very cruel coverage of the stupid things
He says I'm.
Wow
That is
A career path
That is a career path
He's on the show because he wrote an article and wired about early possible plans from DARPA to create a project
Called LifeLock
Compile all available data on individuals to be able to tell the
The story of their life
It was outrageously fun
F***** up as an idea in a
It did not end up coming to pass for a number of reasons
What was probably public backlash but another was probably the unfeasibly of creating a system that would be able to do this in any
The meaning for usable
Yeah now the NSA just grabs our metadata
Duh
This is beyond
Conception of what this life
The primary sourcing on the program was a solicitation from DARPA for people to make proposals on
How to create this program that they had the name for
In an idea what they wanted to do but not much else
This is to say that there wasn't a program they were testing they were request
People to put in bids
Create a program to do some
Pretty overly ambitious
Overly f*****-up thing
America the Pentagon deserves your money
As I understand it from Woodway Noah.
Describes at the way they were hoping to start some of this research
What the heck researchers
Themselves
How to do like mock
Trips
Places
This program
Good logger there like physical movements scatter transactions
Things and stuff like that
They did it did it did not work out
Wow I can understand that is
I can understand how someone
Might look
Like
I'll be really helpful in
Criminal investigation
And I don't get to do it probably wouldn't
Has a lot of other ramifications that I don't think
That would be
The problem on the Seesaw I would say that if you're looking at that program is a positive UA
Wearing rose-tinted glasses at the at the very
What is one of the
I suspected he accepted this booking because it
In 2003 no one really knew how not serious Alex is
And how else will taking me opportunity to use Noah's credibility to advance nonsense exaggeration
Of his underlying
Reporting
And that's all that's going on here
And I was polite
I will say that
Trying to read pillow
Digital
That's more polite than I would have been when he's like you know there's already RFID in the money I've been like
Play f*** you
And they're going to do
If you don't put it in the bank
Call but how would that work
Waterpik hundred-dollar bill that I have to take a zero off of it
It's like $97 cuz I've had a
How does this work
You're just renting money by the hour
Is it is it possible that would the system would be is that if
Too many people have too many hundred dollar bills out
Then all hundred dollar bills will be devalued
Play shitted like if there's too much of something it's like 88-82 goes
And then
Dilutes the don't over the RFID chips
To be necessary for that would be extraneous
Anyway he's very polite
And the Alex starts talking about the finger scanning at the grocery
Tree store
To do
It's like oh it's the extension of self checkout Lanes
And of course as I was always does when you talk about this like
Not really a problem
But
It seems like he
He's not happy about it now man to a little bit of a disagreement
That would be a low level 10
I do see it
That might pull out all the Restylane
Cheese's
So funny
That's so funny he's coming here to talk about
The plan that DARPA has to try and log every aspect of a human life
Play about to every human on the planet
And Alex comes back with
I'm going to have to back my own groceries man
I'm not positive actually even
From reading that
I bet
Wired article
That's lit station forbid
I'm not even
Positive necessarily that the plan was ever to make it
For every wash
Cleveland
Opossum
I think it I think it was
Something big
Could be abused
Exist
Absolutely
Yeah
The article V Noah
Noah shachtman wrote wired is
I just got Shania of this
A discussion of the moral implications
The people even within the
So technological community
Worried
Natural article
Talk about it this is what
Imma have to beg my own groceries
Diamond serious person
Bottom right on the groceries I got to go and then it's going to unlock them
And that's how you have to get groceries now and I have to put my own bags
Another thing that is a concern of both serious people and Alex
Maxis drone
And
Another is also
Relevant
Conversations around that don't involve Infowars stuff
And Noah brings up drone
Are the Browns going to bring my groceries to
Did that
That's not that's not the context
That of this okay
This is how the interview went
Beautiful girls
The chain
Noah
I just want more I want more of that on my regular news
I want more of like
At the end of a very serious interview with a f******
General or some b******* then
Halo real quick
Play Live recently I've got a pretty good movie.
I think it I think
It's a lot of fun
And I wish Alex has one harder and been like
Did you know there's a major
Pictures of Mind Control trigger
What do for it once you open a can of soda I want you to get to Matrix my control
Mother Gaston after this
Has a talk show host
Out of Rhode Island
I believe Alex has been welcomed on his show
So now the river is repaid
Keep referring to this station Wala
As I think it's like a 50 megawatt blowtorch
Somebody gave him that and he went crazy
The credibility is up
Matbuot
Yes
The years
When I was in college
Generations later or decades later I mean
College
Exactly what you just said
Apologize
You with a nut
I was
I didn't believe
Because I didn't want
Want to believe whatever
We think you said was going to happen
Did in fact have until you're right Alex
Conservative talk show hosts
Stein Rhode Island Oyster how wide is indication was but
He just seems like a kind of like a John Birch Society dude sounds like
I don't know I don't I don't find
Damn all that
However what is interesting is that mentality that there
Expressing
Kind of like a mantra
A propaganda stink
Conspiracy theory
I heard Alex say exactly the same sort
Nothing in the present
I've heard him say it five years
He says this all the time
Dislike our credibility is through the roof cuz everything we've said his come true
The reason this rhetoric is used is because
It's not about credibility or track records are predict
None of these concepts are even real in the game that's being played on
Funny shows
The goal is to tap into the audience's feelings and provide them with psychological comfort
They all have memory of someone think
Taking that they were crazy for their conspiracy beliefs
And it makes people feel better to have their supposed
Expert hero give voice to those
Viewing
Importantly to put them in the past
You're right to believe me all along we're on the other side of it now
Story about Rick's Ranch
From college apologizing
For doubting him
That didn't happen
That story's constructed to give the audience hope that if they hold strong to their Fringe as nonsense
Eventually they to while everyone in their lives apologizing
A big too afraid to accept the truth
You see this really consistently in these sorts of communities like
With rampant
Qanon
Yeah I conversation
That you see you like
Fantasizing about the day that everyone will admit that they were right
Yeah
Weird
Miami can't possibly be like the like
Everyone thought we were wrong but we're keeping right and so our credibility is through the roof
It can't be right in 2000
3 + 20
Like I can't
Be bright at Bow Tie
It also can't be right in those intervening years when I've heard
Right
Do people just constantly forget about her credible you are I mean it seems like he's creating a like sine wave of cred
Credibility that just goes up and down depending on the the year or the day or whatever you know like
Today our credibility throw the rope and then tomorrow I credibility is way way down you know like what are you talk
Terrifying
Yeah Rick
I was wondering about now
I am.
You know he's very much in line with Alex
His beliefs are simpatico
I was wondering
Hey does this dude think he's fighting demons
Well I have to go back to a bib
People but I have to
Say it because I'm not a
Unlike yourself I tell it like it is
We're dealing with.
Horses
Evil in this world today
Thunder
Again
Hours
Qualities of evil
Now I want to say Alex doesn't not respond to that comment at all
Platforming somebody who has like
Assertive Fundamentalist
Believe
The Christian belief in
The war that they're fighting that is
Presumably political in nature it or actually again
Principalities of evil
Demons
A Furrow my brow at you.
Why
Because I want Alex
The f****** way in and I'm sick of this teasing Bowl
I know I'm I'm a little nap I'm a little bit frustrated with the tooth
But again it's another interesting
Thread that exist
In this. Of time
We now
Have the ability to learn more about in unravel and I find that really
Compelling
So weird
When y
Why was it
Not acceptable then
I mean I guess it must have been a strategy
For him then and maybe at the conclusion you could jump to and I'm rightly sure if it's
Going on like it has to be
Something is going on but
Frustrates me because it sounds like I'm making a conspiracy theory
About something going on but that's why we need to learn more and gather more information and evidence
Course
Stuff that some of these other folks are saying
Isn't too far from what Alex
Says in the current Alex Galvez more and talk more
Grossly in
And and graphically about stuff
But it's not too far off in terms of the we're fighting demons
Snow
But Alex stays away from it himself for the most
Right
Which that's why it seems like a strategic
Decision
I guess you still booking these people that yeah
He knows who Rick Adams is he probably knows
This element of his
Is belief
He's comfortable with him expressing it
He's just not
Talkin to wake he would
In the present day
Cute crayon are in the present
No and I mean with this
You know with those types of people you've always got a time to Bible reference
So it's not like he's been
Talking to this dude outside off air for
Open a weeks and they just have never had the Bible,
Like these people have
Okay if you are talkin to me
Within a 30-minute stretch you're going to hear about the
They're real good chance and it doesn't matter what
We're talking about
Sports
It's going to be the Bible
It doesn't matter
Uno
So we have a couple of clips left from the
And the text
Him and I
Rick
And
I guess this is the other thing to that was really wild
Like
Cutty is on for almost 2 hours
Hours
Rick is on
Look for a really long time
And
I thought
This is long
For an Alex.
Yeah
Just like right on the same page in terms of those
New World Order Bass
6 a conspiracy
He cannot just have them co-host with you while you take phone calls.
Another thing that feels more like well this is what this radio shows
Is trying to be
Also
I did not get into whether or not demons or what we're fighting with Shaq
That would be that would be a twist
That would be a nice little twist for us
So like in the maitre
Negotiate with a robot
I would stick to this call
Is this
Is
Awesome
I don't even know how to set it up
Okay this is awesome
What happened with your deal when
Do your license and they asked you to
Team Masters of
Terror
Last week we picked that up
Use it at her church in
No
Gottman
They will not give
Bright
So f****** funny
This is one of Alex's biggest early publicity stunts and you could argue that it's
The closing segment be like
The big p
Peace in his documentary America destroyed by Design
Alex brings in a bunch
The cameras when he goes to the Austin
Dmv2go get a new driver
Where's license snowing
The process requires a finger
He brings along a
8 forms of identification and it's 50 shouldn't have
Provide fingerprint to it
The people at the DMV say you do
I don't start yelling about how Bill Clinton wants his blood in urine neck
Stan asking if the DMV workers are going to stick a needle in
It's a petulant display and it's a real sign of the sort of
Publicity stunts that would come to characterize his career move
Forward
It's so hilarious
That at the end of the story he just went back without the cameras and gave the fingerprint
To get his driver's license
I know he has a driver's license
She got a DUI few months back
Driving without a license.
So
Infuriating exactly like Alex
It's it's so it's
Is Alex to a T
I need a new I need a new ID so I guess I'll go get I'll give you my thumb Pride
I will go and I will take this sand and yell while there's cameras running and get attention and
An Insight people into a frenzy about these
Supposed political
I believe something's like I am
Standing up for all the people
Yuno anime
I need a drive
Dayan this hell two days later I'm real sorry about that that's my bad
He's like yeah you can't get around it but like
I don't know
The radio I can't do people going to do
Hire a lawyer to do it for me while I work no I have to do all of my own lawsuit what am I supposed to do
The hard work of having a printer
Pretend to have a principled stand do you have time to have principles, I don't care what
What you don't have a job fine
I'll have principles outside
Crazy
Alex
A call from an H-E-B manager
It is this has to do
With more of his
Thought ideas
About waivers and what-have-you Asher
This manager is bringing up
That
Her place of work
They are now talking about bringing in a scanner like a fingerprint
Scanner
For the time clock
Different
Then the idea of a checkout lane that's connected to your credit card this is the beginning of
Bring it
Anyway the manager wants
To ask Alex about ways that she
She can fight back
And not
Use this system
And Alex's advice
He's so Alex
That it's almost laughable
Here's my thing
I need to know what is my
Give them my fingerprint
You're not going to be
Okay and is there a
Any place you can recommend
On the web or
Certain spot in the library that I should look
Research
Stopping what my rifle are at
But I can use as a dependent
I can't think about your home
I really do Billy I got
He's not
I forgot he has plenty of you take more calls
Yeah there's no advice
There is nothing
There is no specific references he can give her to help her better
Navigate list
Struggle that he wants her to engage in
And to his advice is essentially
Make up a religious exemption
Use use religion as a prop
Yep
Yeah there's no part there's no part of like
Here is what
That is violated all this religious belief here is the reason
Like dietary restrictions
You know
Make sense
Religious exemption
In various settings
Whatever you want
That
Make sense
And there are other things
Opposition to war
Being conscientious objector
Absolutely makes total sense
This I don't know I mean I guess what he would do say mark of the beast
Easter something like that
I guess that would be the direction that it would go
I don't know if
I don't know if that relieved
Wood standoff
Describe Nick's
Amen
It's
Tumi
Indicative of how Alex engages with a lock
It's use it to your advantage elderly the things you don't want to do
The things yet absolutely
No I will not
Tell you where to look into this I mean how could you possibly expect somebody to win a
You religious exemption lawsuit
If there's a clip of you saying
Make up a religious exemption for this
I just want to be totally cleared that's
My language
Did I do or make it up
He's not saying make it up
That's how it is
He is saying make it up you know he's saying find something in your religion that you 99% of the time either
Don't think about or don't actually believe
Ubrite
To convince somebody that it's the most important thing to you now suddenly despite again never having
Thought about it in your entire life
Have these arguments very loudly on camera and then go back and eat
Sorry about that my bad
What how is he
Man it takes so much
It must be so exhausting
Convince yourself that Alex
Susanna giant useless
Piece of s***
Like you just heard that clip wouldn't you be like
Oh
Well then you're
Your entire life is meant
To be fighting at
The tip of the spear
And you are giving me advice that is nothing
You are the person who has more knowledge
And more resources than we do
Individual info Warriors out there in the field
And you had a perfect
Situation where you had a lot of people supporting you they had your back
You could have been the one to do this lawsuit totally in order to make sure that all of us
Good guitar waivers
And not have to give
Fingerprints to get a DMV
We got our licenses on the radio
So
Guess I guess it's going to have to be the H-E-B manager with very little money no note IR
No cult of personality around back
Responsibility
It's a little bit do you know
I mean it's not new but it is
Is just a gross
Denial of
The self-appointed role
This is a Grassroots movement where is
Exploit the Grassroots
Okay
You can water the grass
Or you can suck all of the life out of it
For every single Cent that you can steal
Yep
Manos a good show
Nikes
We come to the end of this
I really feel
Like there are threads
I'm fascinated by
My in two
I think a lot of stuff is is is
Is coming up that I really really want to know
Where are these things go
So I hope to have you say I'm not going to lose track of the present-day or ignored
Entirely but this is
This is
This is getting me
Get my juices
Just so uncanny you know like
I recognize this guy and yet everytime I hear and talk
Who the f*** is this guy
You know like it's so close to Alex but it's
Even weirder
Yeah we're even taking for granted like almost
How
Nutty it is
The position on Putin
Night and day
Agates
Outrage
I can't believe how jaded we are that that
Completely is like almost pass a to a certain you know like
Oh yeah
Of course he believes this bed and doesn't believe that
Now that that's just boring
Foundation or there's a lot of major stuff that is is going to have to get
And I want to know where like
Wear these
People are
Where are the experts
Where are the
G Edward Griffin Where's that dude
Well I know
Some of them were editor-in-chief of The Daily Beast
Why isn't Alex
Like obviously talking about gold a little bit
Midas resources is selling gold at this point
He's not pushing gold as hard as he doesn't
Like years after that yeah
I don't know it's answers
It's confusing to learn more
And we shall in the sea
But until then Jordan we have website
Yep worlds alarm
We are
Local charity or belt under your area to help out people doing God's
But until then I'm Neo and Leo
I'm dzx Clark I'm Daryl rundus
And now here comes
What the sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work