Air Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
MoneyGram
Fight.com
Acknowledge
About Alex Jones
Jordan
What's up
What about today
Well I mean obviously there's only one bright spot for me
Possible bride
Snow delay mean
The experience of watching
It was only it was fairly long
Significantly longer
Matches that are going over 2 days
Yeah but
Rafa and Djokovic played the
Going in my mind through the greatest
Mismatches in all of tennis history and
Djokovic and Rafael played
The greatest clay-court match
In the history of jazz
Without question the third set lasted
An hour and 40 minutes
That is the length of most Rafa on Clay match
And that was just a Thursday and it was just
Spectacular shot medication for it was impossible shots
Left and right
Truly incredible and Djokovic one unfortunately
B i
I mean there's no
There's no shame there 33 points Go a different way and Rafa win 6-3 6-3
Blues
Totally there's nothing to be said for like
You are able to go that
You were able to go that hard enough French Open
Pens for people to think
He's pretty good on
He's one of
Whew that's what I've heard
Alright on play for solo for so long but well it was just
It was incredible to watch
Well I'm happy for you
But you got to watch that
6. I'm not joking I got that from your Tech
Indignant
Hence emotional experience
My bright spot is actually kind of a athletic thing as well
Recently the switch
At the Nintendo switch
Updated it start the game so you cannot play Mario parties with people
In other places
Yeah and so I've started playing some Mario Party
With folks who live in other states
Some friends of mine and
I am
Essentially
Beat It
I accept and I understand
I understand all these things
But yeah I've been
I've been killing it
In the Mario Party game
I don't think there's anything wrong with getting confirmation as a
An adult that you could
Defeat children at something
Yeah you know Life's good sometimes you see kids do stuff in your like there's no chance I have
Competing with that makes you feel bad cuz you're an adult
Really beat the s*** out of kids
You can sometimes be well maybe that's too far
But really beating him can feel good one of the one of the fun things to about this this Mario Party
This iteration
Another game is
It's a tablespaces where you can
Can get a friend
So you'll just have like I always plays Waluigi
My friend follow me
Fun
Anyway I Jordan today we have an episode to go over will be back in
The present today a little bit
It is weird
2821 B
Maybe maybe that's
So
It's a Monumental day in a lot of ways it is also a day of
Walking through
Knee deep mud
Yeah
Alex
This content
Yeah
Things like whether or not we're all going to die
Is dealt with quite
At length I mean that seems pretty important
I must be answers know in which case
It's not very important at all is it
You put that on the back burner ablation
So we're going to get that a business let's say hello
So first Doctor David strange or how I signed up for the
I only got two because everything is uploaded as a video
Thinking about your nail polish
I'm a policy wonk
Should be clear to Doctor Strange
Stream everybody else there's nothing that is behind very hard
Maybe we could do a better job of putting those videos as audio but
Onyx from my brother Ben
I'm a policy wonk
Very much Matt W
Brother I freeze that
Text Emily Finch
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
Lil Wayne
First Stevi B's most dirty dossier thank you so much you are now if I was you want
I am brouhaha Chicago's drinking pod thank you so much
Juvenile technocrat
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
Thank you very much not to not to correct tube
But to clarify I believe cbp's dirty dossiers also
Correct yes
You accidentally said policy
Oh I'm sorry I didn't want anybody to Twitter messages
Man I appreciate you checking me before we started recording I barely got any sleep last night
I appreciate the the the subtle
Shove
Jordan we have to do a little signal before we getting
Today's episode
Is taking the World by storm
Giving someone life is giving someone death
You can say that
Life is death
You can
That's true.
Who is the best cat uncle and snail dead
Write a birthday on the 6th happy birthday good night also
Is it this is a this is a weird one
So Sarah sent me a message
It said her friend Joe has a birthday in June here
Happy birthday Joe
Sarah also told me
The Joe will not say when his birthday is
I like this a great deal
I am conflicted
One level I enjoy people retaining some mystery in their life
Course but on the other hand just tell your friend when their birthday is
If you're not on Facebook they might not remember anyway
Reminder birthday
If somebody doesn't want to tell you their birthday then you have to
To surreptitiously Discover it in anyway but follow them to the DMV one right
And then be in the corner just with a little pair of magnifying glasses
Eyeglasses if you well something along those
Yeah you have to do something
Tell Sarah what day your birthday is the parents
There their they're ready and waiting to give you
Also this is not a birthday congratulation of Camry
Graduating from the University of Ottawa getting engineering degree
Realizes now just spiraling completely out of control operated place to completely this is this is our new
Shoe Show basically I don't even know if we do Alex Jones related content that he bore
This fella Eric
Send a message to Reed
Baby
Jordan just shook his head
Eric love you
That's big
Happy 22nd Birthday Alexandra
You're the happily-ever-after in my story and I hope you have a wonderful day
Remember to work for Progress not Perfection and keep sight of what's on the other side
Alright well
Because we are getting dangerously close to territory that I am deeply uncomfortable
Alexandra hope you have a great birthday
Boy born
Is the condition that leads to death
Life is a disease that ends in death
Happy life is death Day to all of you
Absolutely
Jordan we got to do June 10th to go over and he was not a contact dropped
Pleasure
Bowser testicles or Superstar
Like in testicle related
Fumes or or like
Celebrity is an influencer situation here 17 rebounds
Last season
Show and describe it is
Bad weird mood
If you were anybody but himself
Sure since he is himself
Is regular more I would describe it as a pretty normal Personnel at the gym
I've been saying this a lot before the shows just because all I do is tell you how I feel
That's a really great wave
Now this is really
Starting to set in on me
Around around
And I was already ready to date
To come on air
All members of the
Preston is amounts of young people
I have a heart attack
From the so-called covid vaccine
And then
I was sent a
A big Twitter feed
My good friend of mine a national talk show host
The Twitter feed
Medical documents
And
Ashley got dizzy almost passed out
Alex almost passed out cuz you read a Twitter thread
Yeah it's
It's a little much
It's kind of amazing how accidentally self-aware that first bit I do is get on the radio and tell you how I
I feel such a great like yeah man you got it but identified the problem
Nailed it all YouTube people
Yeah I did
It's somehow we really cathartic to people who are really angry
Oh God no that's me isn't it
Yeah I am
Interested in what was going on here what was up with this Twitter thread I wasn't so interested in his like
I'm so angry I can't do the show and
Body hurt
Happens all the time
Time
The present day is like
So boring with something that's so interesting like anybody else
Doing this
Would be
Good ground break
Anybody got a boss acting like oh my God
Fire this is how TV shows start
And then they get worse from what the first episode you like
Alex Alex talked a little bit more about
Do you have that effect
Women
When you're overwhelmed by something and
Just passed out
And that's really the point
Nothing
Rolling forward I was reading
About 100,000 people getting sick from the shots that are young
Are children
It just pisses me off it's on my brain says
Go out and you know do you know what people are doing this
What is overwhelming
I looked up the most recent information on the cdc's website
And there have been reports of 5208 deaths of people who have gotten
The covid-19 vaccine
Alright
This is Alice 302 million doses administered which represents 8.00 17 death rate
Even if you assume the ridiculous absolute worst-case scenario that all of the dancer even related or linked
To the vaccines at all it would be a p0017
I thought Africa too dangerous for a vaccine Dan and the truth of the matter is that they are not all
So so it's too dangerous to even hear about the vaccine I guess so
It's also there is something that's been happening lately there been some more more reports of younger people
Having some inflammation
They could be connect
To do vaccinations
And it's something that needs more study there have been 623 reports of myocarditis or
Pericarditis in persons aged
30 or under post-vaccination
These are primarily males and I'm through review of medical records
The CDC was able to
Looking for a 200
68 of these
None of these cases have resulted in deaths in only 50
Teen ended up hospitalized
With 41 of them experiencing ongoing unspecified symptoms
This is not good obviously
And it's something to CDC is investigating in one they have Morgan
Information will know a bit more about it
Dealing with the story is
Is just sensational
The point of
Being dangerous
Makes me want to do you know what
Yeah I thought about killing
It is it is amazing he's he's exemplary he's he's doing part of the trolley
Ethical question where he's like you know
We can't
Hurt one person
With a vaccine
To save five other people's lives
What we need to do
Is throw that person in front of the
The train
And then having the train run over the five people after that and then I live happily ever after
Throw in front of the train as a doctor
Exactly
I'm going to get all of these people killed and then I'm going to jump on top of the train and fly
Yeah
So the first hour I would say is
Meandering
It's a bit me every
Because as we as we learned in this
Play squip
Alex is so much news
So big
Like its balls
He's getting chills
Years ago out of 100
Article her seller might be one really big one
I have more than 50 devastating reports
Better confirm
Send chills up my spine
Lightning round
Real realization of how screwed
I walked outside
Oh my gosh
That happened a thousand years ago
I think I like that
Because
Something in motion that is the plan organize total collapse
A civilization in math
But I was in a bad mood
There's something happening we're all dead
Definitely doesn't seem to be much wiggle room.
For all of us are we we didn't few minutes the plant explosion into a red giant Earth is still gone man
Yeah yeah and that the way you speaking about this is obviously meant
To be like there's nothing he could do or I'll f***
I mean
It's certainly not inspiring
Over-the-hill man
Charge
That you necessarily want
I know that Patton but he was giving me some of his sort of famous
Speech is generally black
We are f****** bedworth screwed
Rachel fight them on the beaches
It won't matter you're all f****** dead
I thought that's all you blow up
So I think the sun blow up metaphorically one of the things you might want to do is run away to a bunker
You know
I mean if it's the sun I would just lay down and be like let's do this man there's no hope at this point that's why I said
Metaphorically
Metaphorically might want to run to the Hills
It's the end of civilization
Selfishness but my very cell
Get out of Austin get your family out
I know the most remote area and dig and now
Go
But if we do that the globalist went
They're going to accelerate their collapse and finally dig us out of our holes later
Every movie every show is not coming out with dystopic
Planetary extermination robots killing us
Conditioning everyone to accept that
The video games the movies
What about movies from like the 60s about robot
No no
Battlestar Galactica never happened every movie is now
No that's true and it's so funny that we're also in the past
And he's like
I'm pretty sure that Saddam is in the United States did Russia or Australia and then he's like they're going to come
What's up out of our holes and I'm like why you don't even know man OU's in the past don't even know
Some people get Dugout a-holes buddy
Yes Alex is pretty pretty doomed heavy
Here even actually kind of more so than usual
Like I think a lot of the time he doesn't descend
This deeply
Into that Abyss
It was a medium
You got to ease me into that it was a media have two going over commercial breaks to like
Person when he come back he was still doing this alright alright
So we're in the word full on the the guy in The Watchmen shouting for the end of the world territory
That's what was what's going on
Here's the situation
What do you have been like let's say
I don't know convicted of a horrible crime in your put in front of
Squad
They'll put a little
Blindfold over you
Alex is doing the opposite
Aiden is next clip
Do wonders
If maybe he shouldn't
Do the opposite maybe he should allow people to just have a blindfold
This is not a deer in the
Watch moment
It's almost obscene
To even tell everybody does it is kind of like
They put a blindfold on somebody who's in a firing squad
Watch themselves because
And I got to give you a cigarette
Maybe a little
Brandy
Before
Also polite
So you know what
We kill our babies
So I guess
I just guessed prepared everything collapsed
And
Destroy
Guess that's just really yet
Prepare to die
Seems to be Alex's message
That's what day was
The 10th was Thursday right before the weekend
Port Arthur Dent he just never got the hang of Thursday's
What's up you know it's like everybody's working
Can for the weekend
It's just rough
Yeah Loverboy was also pissed off as hell about Thursday
So there might be an answer
Maybe
I'm listening to the B2 I don't know if
This is exactly the message you're going to take away from it
Maybe
The answer is blindly accepting whatever Alex wants
You to do
And not questioning anything
And just do it
Wow to be what you think
Will solve all the problems
In the world Visa V the global estate starting a religion
Maybe
Because this mad scientist evil
Posthumanist evil
Has figured out all the angles
The only way you beat it is recognized
Full spectrum salt and then do the exact opposite
But instead the public likes to debate and argue Annex Ilion
At the low-level
And if you do that we have zero chance
And we just woke up
God said to do
This evil just evaporate
Everybody can feel it
Everybody can see it
That's just what it comes down to
So here's what I'm going to do
Make sure we stay on here
Make sure that that's dealt with at your own house is in order
And then I'm going to come back and I'm going to head on the stairs
It's best I can I'm just going to cover it then that's going to yet
What
Maybe next two segments you can't put stuff on screen because
People in New York
Saying we want to wear masks forever
We don't want to take them off we like them there are blank
Painful to look at
Right on the edge of just
Plus
It becomes a distraction
From what I'm already covering what I'm doing
And the proof of your other shows or something
I'm going to go back to reading articles and sub remote because
Because I can't look
Look at the mascot
We already did what's going on
Okay so if I understand correctly here is how the show is going so far
Also that clip is
Very indicative of how the show is going so so
Please
If I had to say correctly
We're all dead
Call already
We need to prepare to die
Bye crew put up a picture of Joe Biden and people supporting him so I am going to throw a
I'm going to go off the air
Viet
I don't even think it's going to go off the air it's that I'm going to I'm going to threaten to just do radio now cuz I'm too distracted
Directed by images
That's banana
That is unprofessional
To a level of like
I think technology the wrong problem
I was too distracted by pictures to do my job
And therefore get rid of the pictures
If somebody Jangles plastic keys in the room I can no longer function as a human being
Just get rid of all plastic he's everywhere Dan it makes perfect
That does make sense unless jangling plastic keys are a major
Where is that that is a problem I do work at a jangling keys FAQ
There are a lot of decisions that you might have to learn
How to
Focus your attention
Better
You could change you
That was possible I'm just passing that up
Yeah yeah
Think that that also
The idea of like
If you just saw all the Angles and all of this
We would just be able to defeat the New World Order
That's just your code for like
Is everybody good
Thought the exact same way I did
Oh yeah
If we all just did what God told us to do
Who's telling me what God is telling me to do I only asked you that question
That's a really important question
That sounds right
So the vaccine side effects
There's something that Alex's
Greatly exaggerating
And not dealing with
Seriously
And
You need any more evidence
That
You're the worst
Ranalli Federal documents
Now they know
By Design
Shots now they're going to mess up
Rivers in brain
Alarm for life which is not to be very long
I knew this while they're doing it
I just thought killing you
It's a sacrifice of the uterus and that pleases our God
And also it's going to lay down and hurt their families and cost
English and their families
Cuz you're supposed to bury your
Now you see you see
These vaccines
BBB side effects that some people might experience
Are a sacrament to Satan
Right
I just
Can't disagree with any of that
It's just airtight you're not supposed to bury your parents
I mean the other way around
I've heard that said ye had supposed to bury the trash
And then if that makes sense
I assume that all the preceding arguments have to make sense as well
The problem for Alex
Because his whole thing is about like
Dealing with people who aren't in a trance
But as he was arguing earlier maybe just let people stay in the Tramadol blindfold
Icing
Alex's essentially admitting failure
Because
His self-appointed role is that guy who yells and wakes people up out of there
Exactly so if he's primary complaint is a people are too much
That means that you are ineffective at the job you have given yourself
So
I don't know but I don't know if I'll be proud of this Nextbook if I were out okay
See the public mesmerised
Into a trance watching their Sports
Video games
And I can't join the global is because that
That's evil and I don't want
And then most Republican
He says predatory Layton
I guess we're just here to tell the truth
But people make a decision for themselves
Don't work out God's plan
I don't know what it is I'm supposed to do
Everything I'm doing
Your job
Or something we're supposed to do right now the way.
Guilt
You should know that. Feel a lot of guilt
I have stacks of government documents
Richter scale
Just some person nearby just needs to be like
Alex just
Do your job
Just shut up
Do your job talk about how well you could do your job
Don't talk about how is everybody else's fault you can't do your job little annoying
I would argue that it actually is
Calculator
Good thing that Alex is doing
And not necessarily because he decided
To get on there and act like a weirdo
It's Vicky didn't prepare
It was not to get ready to do his show
At all if we have to fill time rambling about nothing
You can't just come out and say sorry I have to burn an hour cuz I've only got two
I have too much news
To get over
I have to talk about all of this
I'm going to kill a third of the show saying
Complete horseshit nothing
Got to do that
I got to do that to really get into the news
I don't know what else he has to do
Predict things
Will be sitting here in a year or two
Weather
110k to raise money
Cuz you know all the neurological problems
Don't have movie stars up there
Together
Poster signing on to volunteer to be euthanized
Is another too much of a weight on society
Extra money and it's
That's the plan
This playing
We got a lot of plans. Lot of lives up in the air all the time
I don't know I don't know if I can handle this many plans I don't seem like complimentary plan
Yeah so then
Two years celebrities will be doing
5K charity thing
I would assume that's true not necessarily
For people who
Like we're hurt by a vaccine side effects
From covid-19
You know there are certainly
Experiences of people have had about long
Covid you know there is our like there are things that we will learn
Moving forward they were not aware of now or we're
Starting to become aware of now
I could see
Celebrities doing fundraising
A some sort of a charity
In that line
10 years from now
I would believe there will be so many people
Who have been hurt by the
Covid vaccine
Right there will be
Euthanasia drives going on where you get to party
Haha
Have you
So that's a little bit like Looper
Is that kind of what we're dealing with here we're dealing with you sign a contract for about 10 years and then you get killed like I did
Like suicide bombers but without the bomb
Predictions that Alex is going to forget
Who's going to run the 5K 10 years from now when are we've got all these euthanasia Drive
I've going all the runners will be dead
Who made the first to go
So when you were worried about like who's going to be
Interpreting the words of God
And I told you was a lie
Yeah I tend to be worried about that too
I believe that Alex primarily because
He seems to think
The churches are all full of
Betrayers
So this is
The Day stuff
I just want to have a good time
Lot like churches on
Stop
Satanic
The real betrayers weather to make sure
There would be at church.
So I'm sorry folks
I'm real sorry
We're being judged
But this is going to be
My church
Whatever silver
F****** parties at my church
All the time
GameStop party we did have it our church weren't fun
No we didn't even have communion wine we run out from so many f****** party
Sweetheart youth group we had like every ever
Is every Sunday
Do you have evening Sunday evening
Just youth group
Services or whatever
Afterwards it get to Papa John's Pizza
Right
Yeah but you had to pay first one
That's not fun
Let's have a party
In the church yeah man you realize Jesus would have run in there and started throwing Pizza Oliver
Around the place
Flipping a pepperoncini box
It was not fun
Jesus and I don't like Allah
Episode
Is just
Amass
Like the whole first hour is
Is this
These outrageous like
It's even worse once I would start trying to explain why he's feeling the way he is
Just such b*******
But it's crystallized
And then
Because the forces they told me not to
Michael Allosaurus
Information can't get out
If you got any other
Before they start to work they're doing but
The major Counter-Strike to all this in the works right now
My job
It's been confirmed the documents have been seen
But this is a killed man
Accuplacer
Okay
Alright
So yeah I went to the source
Buddy can't give up
Speaking
Because the source
It'll blow their cover too high
Still working under Undercover
I guess
Alex talking to Steve again agent situation is this somebody in the government whose
Viewing the kill plan documents
Anybody who actually has access to anything would never talk to a dick like this
You thought I already talked about how we're all going to die for an hour to get to go fishing
I really call a Alex
I've got to get your brain in on this
See this is why I just can't be allowed to be part of the government because I swear to God I would crank call
Call Alex at least once a week and be like I've got some documents for you I'd send him pictures of bulshit it would
Never not be hilarious to be for them to show up the neck
Text Dave yeah just never not be fun I'm not certain that you have to work in the government
To do that
Get yourself a protonmail address
You could probably a plant some story
Lieutenant colonel
Bolesse hit
Protonmail.com
My grandpa service
Under you and which one did your grandpa serve in the North or the South which one was it
Okay okay okay I got you
I guess Alex
Was sent into a tailspin
Before the show
Because of some secret information that he got from the source
Orator
Twitter threads that almost made him pass out
Norwich
It is but maybe it secret source is this Twitter thread
I don't know
I mean I understand being thrown off by what would be relatively Petty things like one thing that threw me off during that
Clip with literally going like
Why don't I remember the theme song
Talespin
And then I realized it because every time I think about the theme song to tailspin I go
Did it tailspin
I think I did the exact
Same thing that you did at night
I think that it might not have had lyrics I remember having
Loud drum Sagittarius theme song didn't have clear
I think it was just
Interest I'm not sure but I did do the DuckTales.
So we got to kill plan on her hands not entirely sure
Exactly how this is going
Going to play out
Who do you think is
Person-organization
What's the organization
So if you're asking me it can't be the UN that seems too obvious I'm asking you because we've been listening to this show
For all the times
The covid has a
Existed
And
You should
No
By now
Who's running all day
Oh if there's a kill plan sure
Who's running
The devil look
No.
China
No
B no
Spelter
No no
Bfr
Brazil
Official government plan
Haha
CIA
Major foundations
Oh
CIA run by the Carnegie endowment
Determination plant I mean
Final Solution World dead
Wow
You guys are really evil
I know they were evil but
It's bad enough Wonder Wipeout 3
They don't have jobs futures
Any of that I'm not sign on to kill him
Whoa that got weird at the end there
That is such a bad writing
That's just bad writing to all of a sudden come up with a brand new villain at the very end to swoop in and got
The end of Scooby-Doo episode they took the mask off and they're like
Terry from three towns down the street what are you doing here to go just do this time certain that Alex has never been
Big on
The Carnegie endowment
That was not some organization that's come up as
One of our even in the mix players
Johns Hopkins is constantly a villain
Icfr obviously the Rockefeller
Foundation
Yeah I don't know I
I mean The Rock
Child's are always in the myth
The Rothschilds in the Carnegie endowment
Boo
You do what you have to do to destroy the world
Actress practice practice
Also f*** Alex were saying that stuff about people in the developing World they have no future
I'm so Alex has the source
Instead of told him about the kill plan
He doesn't just
Believe these source
Until you
He does just
Believe the compactor
I see I just got stuff like that going on
I don't just believe people that have seen the documents
I can see the document
Everything I was told
Individual to stop this playing
Event 201
The planets
The plan is all there
But but specifically they reached the point now
Recruiting
Level deep in the government corporations
Operational now
So they're even telling people the plan to get them onboard hey like you know
You and your family are going to live
500 million that live
Georgia Guidestones
You better get on board right now
Space your fam
During the collapse
Deeper
This is what these individuals
It's exactly what they
Call Vista
They believe all humans must be gotten rid of and
Above that there's not much knowledge but everybody including top pentagon
Four Star General
Small group
Everybody's dead
I mean
It's true
Yes there's nothing really we can do right I mean if you make a deal with aliens
That's out of my that's above my pay grade
Four star generals
Then we got to get new generals
Yeah that would be good
Via
Deal with it
Atlas only to be 500 million last we made a deal with aliens it's a real bummer
What is the aliens other deal was like
We kill everybody
That's good deal
Compared to
Yeah compared to the human extinction we live in a scenario where there is
Kill everyone or kill all but 100 people
Obviously KB 100 people is a preferable option to make everybody dying
Yeah I mean it's all made up
Opso
Trolley problem just feeling bad
Ferris 7.7 billion people
In front of a train we've got 100 we can save I think it makes perfect
So you got this get right with God
Cuz everybody's going to die
He's giving very little hope
At all
In this first hour sure get right with God
Do the aliens know God
It's debatable whether they're actually aliens they might be demons
You're right so you got to get right with God and Alex introduces a guess
Rusty's going to have
My town for this cuz he honestly sounds a little bit pissed that you going to be interviewed
And the Dominos are falling
EDD program has already started
The countdown is here
I don't know what to do I just get right with God that's all I can say
Instead we'll talk to my pillow guy
Kevin Hart
Wow
Get right with God instead of my pillow guy here the assignment
Talk to the f****** my pillow really know I heard it I heard the f****** that was not spoken to
So this is the episode of Mike Lindell from my pillow comes on for his first appearance on Infowars
That's like that it's his first appearance
Save-A-Lot
To go from
Limerick
Soap man to s*** talking the my pillow guy
I'm just saying maybe you're getting above your britches
Is there buddy
Thinking about like what the Dynamics are here
B b b
Like
Not super happy about this
I think why Mike wooden
Be super happy about the
Is either
Is is because
Neither of this is neither of their fur
First choice
Alex probably don't want to talk to him cuz he's not
He sounds
The potential to drag Alex into litigation
With 1000 slanderous
He thrown around like water
You know you could you could end up getting
Dragged into court
For having
Too Close of association with
Particularly in this sort of asset
Interviewing them and allowing them to broadcast
Slanderous claims
About
Various things
It does seem like Mike Liddell comes along with the same
Producer is like a prank show
We're after you talk to Mike Lindell some lawyer just runs up to you real quick and he's like
Okay I just need to give you a quick interview you're going to need to sign this statement
And I also think
Mike can't be super happy about this either because
Cuban
In the Trump orbit in one of these
These people for
A while now
If you wanted to be on Infowars he would have been on there long ago long ago
He would have been on there when Rodger was on it when the good days were going yet and the reason that he didn't
Is because obviously no one wants to be on Infowars
The Last Resort
Griffin for the my pillow Guy this is slumming it
Mike Lindell is doing this
Because he's not allowed on those other channels anymore
Because he's being sued by smartmatic and Dominion
And those claims are all he wants
To talk about
And this those networks just won't let him
Spread that s***
So yummy
Infowars
The TV networks are better lawyers than Mike lindell's
Lawyers
Because they're the only people who were like
No wheat
Can't have you talking about your case on air
We're going to learn the Mike actually just lost
His lawyer
A little bit later this interview
So Alex before he gets into the actual interview with Michael
Glendale
He's going to accept talk a little bit about how the last hour with
And it was
Pretty wild up last hour got to submit heavy issues I'm just telling you where the globalist want to take us give they succeed
They're going to fail
Please remember where listener-supported I think you all your amazing
The picture support we're still on air and still more effective
Mega immune support supplement
If you add Mega Euro you've already admitted you're done you know the moment you like this is our Mega health
Supplement
You're making bulshit up
Very much so
Interesting to me they were all dead everybody's dead
F*** it we're going to die
It doesn't matter
We're all dead
He's sort of tries to walk it back there was like
I'm just talkin about what the globalist want to do if they win their going to lose
Like as if to undo
Already did in the last hour
That could have been
Anything else then
Anything else
It was meaningless
Completely
I'm just a guy
Trying to get
People scared
M and hopeless
I mean
Okay
So
What he did was spend an hour telling us that we're all going to die
And then his way of
Apology is like only if they win and they're going to lose
Now that
First hour be valuable if you were giving me steps
On how to make them blue
Because you you're giving me
I need to buy those Mega supplements
The destiny that we were on
Tired
Have a long walk
He works a lot
Migrate to
Sincere
You're a busy guy working twenty hours a day wow
I've been going all around this country trying to go
The selection full down and we will get a
Working 20-hour days trying to overturn the elect what are you doing
That's a really good question
I don't know what good why what am I to work there is to be done on this front
I guess writing letters
Could be
Traveling to another place and then writing letters because there's no lifetime limit on talkingshit
That's true
Brother is doing
It doesn't qualify as work
If no one's around to hear you talk
Is that our new like if a tree falls in the forest Mike Lindell is telling you about the stolen election and no one's around
If you're Your Own Boss
You can count that is on the clock hours
Got this argument about overturning elect
Action right
Some arguments
Maybe
They're three of a kind
Maybe there a full house haha
Not Mike's argument
Royal flush
Pretty amazing because it's like
You're sitting here with a royal flush in a poker game
And we're just straightened
Play it
We're going to
They don't forget to bring it to the Supreme
Stream Court in July
Every every person is country
Getting it out there so the Supreme
Courthouse pressure
To accept
Not a f***
Can chance Supreme Court
Has pressure to accept
This case
Not a f******
King chant
This seems to be the theme of what he's trying to get to his like
We need to get everybody on board with this so the Supreme Court can't reject it
I think he
Probably isn't stupid enough
To think of that
Really how things
Woodwork
I think he knows that by the time people realize that the Supreme Courts are not going to take this case up we still will have
Pretends to be the case it it does seem like you are always moving the date where we're going to get that royal flush
I know you're never you're never pushing it back you're never like
You're always liked and now neck
Month will get there
And you know what
Real fat
Things are going great I've been be happier the way things are going in Ark
Country right now
Really
Quarterbacking the resistance and
I believe in you and I know you've been behind-the-scenes about all the folks you been working when I leave it at that
President Trump a real president
And now in his second term what's with the agent
This weekend as you know
House on the White House
Sooner than you think
He is really excited in
He believes there's a strategy
Tell us about that
Boy
Trump going to be president again in August
Is a lot sooner than I was expecting
That was sooner than I planned for
Specifically
This is such a
God damn roller coaster
It's like the first hour is we're all going to die and then Mike Lindell comes in as I
No Trump will be president again within a few months
Yeah
Yeah the globalists plan seems very
Easy to sightsee
How how are you supposed to feel if you're on the secret to this show it's not
Your dad in a year
President-trump
This is just how you go through this broadcasting Constance
Stream of look I'm bipolar and this is f****** with Maya if if I took any of this
Let all
Based in reality I would have a very difficult time
Emotionally surfing these waves
Yeah I know one of the big things that I try and do to cope is is like
Lower the amount of intense emotional stimuli that I receive I believe if I listen to one of these broadcast
I would be running through the street that's green that's why the delegation of Labor is the way it is
Only way this can work
So what's the Supreme Court
In July
Get a hold of this
They're going to rule
You understand me
Unanimous
Really think the best you're going for it 3:55 there
Roberts is going to side with you guys I am zero
When that when is supreme
It's not subject
So it's going to be 90
Navigate to 1722
It has to be 90 cuz this is
Subjective evidence
So they're going to
Oldest Stone
And now and now but everybody needs to know there's a cup
Juanita's
There were many.
Down tickets to that were flipped
Senators in Georgia
Jason Lewis from Minnesota
Many Congressmen mini gummy
This wasn't just at the fair
Presidential level
And in our country I want everybody to know this
There's no there's no statute of limitations
Call Mama
Well let me tell you some
In-N-Out
Every election in the United States history
Committed
I've got the other person one in anyway let's say it was just a mistake
Backyard office
And if there was a crime
Anyone else
Hundreds of times probably thousand times the smaller cases
Were you find out the other team
A cheetah
The other
Team cheated
Hey then forfeit and then it's given to who they actually shoot again
Do you notice how Alex used a sports metaphor instead of 8
Example from the world of jalapenos seem like a sports metaphor has more opportunities
Like if you're in a boxing match and it later comes out that your opponent was on the juice
Or something like that
You might you know that you might end up having the other person for fifth yes that's true
I'm hard-pressed to come up with examples from
The history of our court
Close races
After a recount
You know you'd a had slipped to winner
Something like that
I don't know if I can think of any example of what
Their talk
Talking about
Balance the top of my head
I would I would say the thing that
Most surprising to me about this whole conversation
Is the idea that Mike Lindell was talk
Talking to somebody
About this was like
We've got an open and shut case
It's all done and that person responded with
No it's out of the statute of limitation Glendale says there's no statute of limitations
This person goes on
Yeah
In that case
I'm going to re-litigate
So like that 68
To the beginning
I don't think TJ one that elect
That's what I'm going to go out there right now I think he stole you undo one of those pasta
Everything at the chaos cuz what if it was a two-term president
The whole country
Custom reset from the beginning
We dig up George Washington and we get them back in there
Yeah
I honestly think of that might be a better solution
Do this
Fanciful nonsense
Like this isn't a better solution of Georgia
Exactly
Metaphorically
Mike Lindell
Let me be clear really clear
None of us is going to have
If you were to have incontrovertible evidence
That doesn't like it was stolen by foreign powers or whatever
Are you get to the Supreme Court they voted 9-0
July
I think the answer is it put drop back in office it's right in Yukon
Institution
Capri's failed
Complaints figure something better out frankly we should already be starting
The new Khan
Institution process as we speak
You know but
Let's just take this country like an Etch A Sketch
Totally
Hold on to some of the goods
Stuff for the protections and rights
Anyway Mike Lindell
Wingsuit fly
I would even go so far as to rewrite that 13th Amendment to include prisoners
And not you know just be like
Slaves are bad unless they committed a crime one time
Mike lindell's being sued by Dominion
Smartmatic
Over
Raclaims
About there
Computers and their technology being used
Intentionally to
Yeah that's a bit that's a big one
Vicky's being super it's in the billion
Yep I think punitive damages with
Suggest that the good idea
Now there's something you may not have her
Mike Lindell is also suing them
I have not heard that yet
You got to watch his documentary
I can't do that
I'm sorry
We'll talk about it anyway
Another minor setback and that his lawyer
Quit
Apparently
Apparently Georgia this is cancel culture
Thursday
This is really cute
And smartmatic
Through them in there too because they're all in cahoots together
Billion dollar
Didn't hear about that probably in the news
Lawyers
Conspirators
Are lawyers
Either lawsuits
Writing letters to over 200 people in this country
And at news outlets including Fox and whoever
Everybody lives in fear
I'm being sued
But when I did that last Thursday
Counseling Minnesota I got so many lawyers I don't even know their name
But I got a logo
Minnesota Minneapolis
They were attack
On Thursday night
Controls
Email Anna left
Oshawott
Turn on Friday
Expired
Lawyers
Mike lindell's keys
Reminder the attack
It's just more can
Cancel culture
Cancel culture man
Cowboy
Adjust
Just seems like maybe they the law firm was more like
I don't think the billable hours is worth this
Yes
This is going to really be a drag we thought we could go under the radar
I just
Bill Mike Lindell for money at Mike Lindell book
Bizarrely Rich for someone who has a pillow company
But
Not that rich
We can let him go
You got this new documentary
I guess like things to be documentaries event like absolute proof
Absolute collusion sure
And now this new one is called absolute 90
Everybody needs to watch this
Video
It's absolutely 90
This is the Cyber profile
It shows China attacking our country
I like to give everyone a fair chance
Text to be heard
Sure I went ahead and I watch the
Misspelled
I was not
Convince
I think your standards of evidence are a little bit higher than the Supreme Court
There's nothing persuasive in the film and it's honestly mostly just Mike talking into his phone
Airpods are in
He's talking to an alleged
Cyber expert whose face and voice are distorted wearing automatic Personnel who knows
What the f*** he is
So we boil down to the mic is claiming that he has what's called
Packet capture
Azure the raw information from these computers that proves that votes are being chained
Amazon Alexa
He shows these long
Scrolls of numbers
Over and over again in the documentary
Is it to insist that even though you can't read this code
It's so definitive
Trump is going to be president again in no time
Mike does a multiple times that these girls are numbers are actually the package
It captures that they're working from
The Washington Post among others pointed out that these Scrolls of numbers are not packet captures and they're not even in the right
Format that information would be found in
This sort of data transmitted over the Internet is generally in binary where is this is all hexadecimal code
So it doesn't even make sense
What are the claims
That are being made for him to jump at the Supreme Court
He's got this kind of proof I don't know the post took a look at some of the code and translated into readable
Letters is a piece of s***
It appears to be the Pennsylvania voter roll which is publicly available information
Okay might be a safe assumption to believe that this growth of numbers is it dumb propagandist
Pixelated cyber expert is someone doing so
Fun role playing
This is just
The bunch of b******* sounds like
Man
Inverse relationship between confidence in a set of numbers that a pillow person
Cannot read and Troost
Behind
So Alex I don't know what it was like I think
Mike Lindell was a little delayed
He was like my pillow guy
It might have been a situation where it's like
He's late
Shore for the interview in till like maybe that was it was frustrating
Cuz I want to sing a number of positive thing
He's being he's being pretty polite and positive and putting up with
Clearly nonsensical things
He's doing is he's chasing
The contract at sonaca
It's a little too late
The cash cow for Mike Lindell getting some of his money is a little bit
In the past
Like a lot of those like oan or right side broadcasting
They could get out any money they wanted from him I'm sure
We saw all those those rallies
There were just like the coverage for these Networks
Entirely sponsored by ELO
I think that Alex
Maybe would want some of that
I mean I would if I were him
Easy money
Yeah I think
Billions of dollars
When it comes to principles versus gaining money I think Alex is going to go for
For gaining money every single time
But that money just won't
Be there for long
Yeah I think it's too late use
Fishing in a dry well
But he does say some nice things about my
And accidentally a my pillow commercial breaks out
Alistair still on Trump album from
But
Do you know Michael and death
Because it's an example
People want action
They want somebody to stand up and I don't Trump
Lick his wounds get ready totally cut off a few months to
Exercise lose weight from
I'm not criticizing Trump when I hold up Mike Liddell
I'm saying he's being example
I'm putting it on the line
Why do you bring this up now
How do people
Support
The globalist
How do people support the work you're doing and how your supper for my pillow
With your earplug election but
How do people do that so they can
By the pillows and then Finance what you're doing
I thought you were my pillow was separate from the political selfies orbited finances
Suspicious
Track my employees to be lost RV tarso people
Really stepped up
Pachuca
UK dealership
Promo code Mike
Today just use mic
And you can save up to 66% on all our products
Disco's on awhile to
This visit this ad is not sure
Mike is created a new bed
Yep
I want
I need to sue for something for Alex I need to sue for like
Extreme gaslighting
For Alex insisting to me that Trump
Lick his wounds by exercise
Are there needs to be punitive damages for that
Something
Because you can't do that
Carpe donktum is going to put out a
Population of Lake
Boxing meat hanging
In a locker
Show me example of him working out
More masculine hero worship
That's so disgusting
So I think it's his next clip is one of the weirder things that I
Heard happened on the
Michelle ever
There's things that are bizarre ideas that are bizarre Shore and then their thing
It just happened that I'm like
How did that happen
That's weird
And this is one of those weird idea I just don't know how this happened
Irwindale stay there
Stay there
I was almost never does that
He runs into the brakes all the time
Whether it's like
Skip this break that used to do that multiple times on this episode he's just in the middle of a sentence intercoastal
That's so great
Why would he interrupts Mike Lindell in the middle of the big announcement
That's the best time to interrupt
Right now
You break in the flow a little bit I do understand
It is a presentation standpoint you would want it to
Be clean
The full announcement will be back at break
That makes sense
Alex
Pharrell
No and I would
I would assume that most professionals would know that Abby
Big announcement was about to happen on their show
If you
Also
I mean just from a professional standpoint as it is an interviewee if you're going to make a big announcement you should know
It's going to be broken up
Damn boy
You ready let's do it
We were going to break that a big announcement
What is the big announcement
Are the plan
A big announcement is
All the Cyber evidence I have
Everybody
Absolutely 90
I got over the United States
Schreiber
White hat hacker
Passing Bitcoin
Sometime in July
I'm going to get a dollar I don't care if it's USB
Stadium
Cyber
And I wanted televised
All of them
Be there
And I don't care if there's a hundred of these companies there
On GB and everywhere
Oh there it is hundred percent there it is there it is
It's like showing a royal flush in a poker game everyone
An election
I'm not going to hold my breath
On this event happen
Yeah
How do I get less like
Showing people of royal flush while you're playing a game of poker and more like
Instead of having cards you throw a dead horse on the T
Lexi
Well technically he would have something
To show them I guess would be more like
He's got a two
The death card from a Tarot deck
Nolan Ryan's rookie baseball card and a piece of naan
Royal Flush Baby by the looks like cards
I don't know I I would love
For this to happen
No I do think it would be
Be chaotic
It would rival the the
Phil Landscaping
Four Seasons
Yeah that would be pretty delightful I was just thinking like I wonder if even if a ransomware company it if he would even
Notice if his
Computers were locked and he can't get into his busy
This offer I love you paid 10 million Bitcoin he be like
Oh no
Edmund just
Record on his phone but it wouldn't even
Care
Yeah yeah for a would-be cancel culture
And this is where I
And I was kind of
Getting a little bit worried that maybe Mike is a bit of a
Christian zealot
Everybody needs
Michael Dell
Everything he's doing
Thinking I think everybody
For your prayers and I believe
I do believe that were in the greatest Revival ever people aren't looking for
Open Nest
We got through this it won't be once again one day when nation under God
Biggest Revival
Everybody right
And we are out
Prayers are answered
Can you imagine if this would have been
December
You might have had a
Temperature
And whether you're democrat or republican it's going to be a laundry and it always your message. We win
So I don't know I don't know if you quite grasp the saying at the end
If Trump has been put back in
Like right after the election or whatever
Democrats would have been really mad but now Democrats all know the election was
It was a scam
So we will
We will carry the Supreme Court Justices out of Chambers on our shoulders
Chanting
A cheering for three and a half more years of trump three-and-a-half
4 years
I think he gets time served
I disagree I have to take that up with Mike
I'll take it to the Supreme Court
So Mike Lindell takes off
Another guess
For the last hour
It's a Halloween out
Homeboy
Mary prankster alright alright this bastard
Rodger Stone has back
And do you want
Let's talk about the good old days
Those were the days that he would like
To talk about I assume yeah
Governing philosophy
Finances
This is no longer the case
Now we went to overthrow to micro
America first party
Under Donald Trump
What abundant
Pardeeville
Harry Truman
Character
They don't connect considered generally
Hey it wasn't like radical Islam.
Defeats Truman is the headline he was holding up
You know by Dewey
Yeah I think
I don't know I lose patience
It's for people who
Make these two arguments together they like there was a time
When both parties loves
The country show at now we have all coalesced around a charismatic leader with a America first
Slogan
Any other people
Everybody else I co-opted by the copy
No middle ground
But although I miss the days when everyone is love
Nixon the main thing
Reaching out to the others Isle that's what we did
Definitely what I was working with Reagan
We reached out across the aisle to destroy those Union
That was our plan
Describe Rodger as a belief
And that is the Trump is
Is the greatest president
Since Lincoln
What do we do then
We're just sitting here watching the country destroyed
Civil War
What do we do then
You can go to Rodger stones to save america.com
That's a little
Get a Bentley or something
Don't have a website that Rick
Requires upon apostrophe that's what I thought
It's too confusing through people you're trying to Target
Especially for those
Please check out my website ww.w. Rogers
Just got to get back on track..
God I went to this website
Just one of these
Awesome
Things that you just the people on the right to this all the time they're so good at this
That is just a
The donation landing page
And
I have a plan that will save America
Put in your email address and I'll send it to you just to get back on his Hospital
Cheesy app to transition back into being a
Direct Market to people
Jennifer Greenwald
Working on that subject that might be that might be a good wife
Priscilla to go Greenwald & Stone
Manafort went down so greenwalls the next song
If you got a you got a consulting firm of Greenwald would know how shity
He's become if I really told him that he and Rodger Stone
Equal now
That be bad
You might have some ideas about Greenwald
Rogers got some ideas
About fauci
You will be remembered
As Hitler
Adolf Hitler
Joseph Stalin and Chairman Mao is one of the Great
Murderer
And those you say already talkin about
Millions of people have taken this vaccination it had no reaction
Well I have been roundly outsmarted Rodger Stone
I didn't think of
Was that
That's certainly not an argument paper
Can be made about everything
No no
Know that one
How about how about we just apply that to literally any and all arguments with Rodger Stone from now on
Not yet
Not yet so now you've been defeated
So what are the big things about Mike lindell's interview was the turnip is going to be
President again
Imminently
You going
To be put right back in that office
Maybe a little bit later
A couple months Maybe
Maybe I'm a little bit off you never know how long is going to take with argument
Casino
There's literally no
Protocol
No I don't think we've ever done that one before
So I would
Think that there might be conversations it would last quite a while about that
Anyway after Harding
They were like
Listen
I mean this is too soon we're just going to redo it
So that's Mike's big thing
My Rodger
Amazon right after
He's not a doing okay context for this this next
The eclipse
Rodger is wife parently has
Just recently been diagnosed with cancer
That's awful. I hope the best for her
Recovery
Sucks however
Alex
Take that information
And prized
Turn Rodgers wife's diagnosis
Into a vaccine talk
Pinpoint wow I were Rodger I would be
Furious
Respect for Mike Lindell
Who's doing extraordinary job
How do you say
Is money where his mouth is
I would never do that
Even then turning over the election will be very difficult
I really hope
I hope Mike window is right
I hope the president's instinct
Is correct
At the moment I've got to be honest with you
Cancer treatments
Tsunami
And the millions and millions of
Phds and doctors
Homeopathic Healers
It is heartwarming
It really is but it's also
Overwhelming
That's what all these scientists are saying
Florida out of Palm Beach Post where you live
You're not you didn't take the vaccine but did anybody
El Cenote
Take vaccine
Well
My wife
Disgusting
Was absolutely disgusting
No but I can tell you that you're a disgusting monster
Cancer diagnosis in
Into a prop your own b******* and normally I'm
Fine with that wife were talking about
You a******
Yeah I mean he's brought up on this interview a couple times like I wouldn't pull clips of it
The two discussed
Private life in
And that's very difficult
Have have a medical condition like that
And he's brought up a couple times but it seems like something that is
You know kind of scary and
Something that is difficult
What's the deal with four even four
Slimy fuc
I would rather
Make fun of his terrible position
Legitimate
Tragedy and pain that he's going through
So he brought it up a number of time
End
Alex to now
Do that
Is so insulting
It is so
Exploitative
Is Alex's listening to him he has to recognize it like
This isn't
Like Rogers polonium poisoning
Here's the other hand I have for that which is just
Rodger and Alex have both done this to so many people in the past where they be
Exploited their personal s*** for their propaganda that it's like
Hey you live by the sword you die by the sword of course this was going to happen
I guess you know you care
Rodger camp
Feeling salty
Without
Wrestling with his own behavior
I guess you know so I can feel itself it on his behalf because I haven't taken
His wife nor my taking anybody's cancer and uses of broad
It's just low you know like it slowed
It's a real bummer
It's a it's a it's a it's a real real bummer
I hate both of these people
But Alex is really edging out in terms of who I hate more in this interaction
I can't I can't imagine what it would feel like to do that
The way Alex is doing my to like
Hey this
This article is from
Close to where you live
Did anybody you know who maybe just got cancer yep
That day was your wife
Please use your use your wife
This condition is a is a way
To make my narratives work better for me to make money off
You're around cancer people now you go to the treatments all the time so you got to know a bunch of people with cancer tell me which ones to the back
And then let's go
Turn that pain into profit man
Not yours
Cuz nobody's going to get to your dumb URL you idiot
Going to put that apostrophe ahead and get lost
Sorry one last clip here and I really do think that this
Is so indicative of like
Present-day Alex and why it's
It's just a bad person doing a bad
Job
Cuz you know it
The beginnings of our of them just talk about how everyone's dad
It just doesn't matter
And here's what he says
At the end of the show
Sometimes I start the show The Best of moods in a bad mood that's robbed
You'll make it a better world so I appreciate you all going through this
Just like I'm doing it
So many days
Powerful stuff we had
I haven't hit yet
Because
Got me pissed
Man the news gotten pissed
Wake me up to cover the news can't
Convey the information that is the information part of the information War
But he can
Take his feelings
And project them onto the audience and lash out like a little baby
In a way that
Reduce releases endorphins
Courgettes
Feeling better
The one you was yelling about I had a migraine and then he called the pope this
The devil and he felt better
It's just that but with the audience
He just needs to get his emotions out yeah
Bike
This is I think any good
Therapist or psychologist
Would be able to correctly diagnosed
Their relationship Alex has with his listeners as
Incredibly abuse
Parasitic
Feel like
What he just did and what we listen to of him telling me that everybody's going to die and then him feeling better at the
The end of it and me being left alone with his feeling
That is domestic violence
If I feel abused
F****** b*******
It's obviously it's not
That bad
Because you and I at least know that he's full of
Sure
Affect
That's in any way that we're taking what he says
Seriously
But like if you did
You would be
Being taken for a ride
Alex would be
Trying to make you feel his emotions
And leave you holding the bag
Toad of the bad emotions
Let's just not cool
I am getting my bad out emotions out of me and
I'm giving them to you because you deal with that and
That last clip gave me
Little bit of a hint
Maybe he's a little bit
Subconsciously aware that that's what he does a little bit
And it could be that Rob
Who has told him
Specific
And maybe that conversation was robbed was him trying to be like Alex
You did it again
Yelp
Wow
I want a fuckedupshit
Cheese's
I wasn't this episode
There's something that's kind of like well that's a
10th psychodrama
It's going on
Obviously
And it's monumental
That Mike lindell's my pillow guy is on
On the show that's not happened
Before is a meeting of the minds
And
Trump could be president again after a week
We will see
What yet
Yet
Looking at this in especially in Jacksonville station with a 2000
3 stuff
Like
8 dozen
Feel like Alex
Does taking his moods out in 2000
It does not feel like he's just having a kind of
Lashing out at a microphone
And that's kind of why it's
Better
You can't I mean there's just no way to view
Our time with Alex's anything other than watching a man descend into madness
That's right
Like we're doing a
Apparently lucrative Madness 27-year Heart of Darkness situation
That's what we're doing yeah maybe
To Kurtz
He dead
Alex's
Just a mess
This is a been our adventure
Matt Jordan
Waze website
Twitter we are on Twitter it's knowledge underscore fighting at go to bed Jordans
We are they looking with that
If you could please find a local charity or belfon near your area to help out
People doing God's work
I'm going to take
Alex