Damn important
I have great respect for knowledge B
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Fight.com
Alex Jones
What's up
Give us to discuss all right
I
I was a fan of the tick
Growing up
I love it later mouse come on man
Loved it
Not everything about it was just
I have always been a little bit hesitant to give other interpretations of the
The tick a chance
Yeah I tried to watching the the newer one
Which one the Patrick Warburton no Peter serafinowicz
Outstanding
I have a few
Episodes
Exactly
What I would have wanted
From a live-action version of The Tick
Spectacular
There's so many little subtle things
I would never have guessed
The characters
Griffin Newman
Please think the First episodes are really hinging around him and like
Disorder backstory of him as as a superhero
Exactly the way to tell the story that's really good
I am so pumped
I'm
Bump that I think
Canceled
Sucks that there's a limited amount of that but I'm I'm excited to have something to watch
That I really enjoy
Yeah that was that was one of my favorite they like I'll never forget
Deflatermouse
Just because I saw the cartoon when I was like 8 or something so young and it was it was like
20 years later that I was like
Oh that's a reference to a f****** Opera
What kind of egg rolls are we like
What a great pun
What was the mad bomber who bombs at midnight upon
Do you like the mad bomber bombs at midnight
Do the weather's nice out and we only live a couple miles away from each other so I've started walking to to do the show
It's about a 40-minute walk with the perfect length of time to start going back through old albums and actually live
Listen to the full thing oh yeah the ninja Tunes label here recently okay
Lemon Jelly 64 through 95
And the final track on that is called go
And it is so good
Because they use William Shatner's sample there and so it's just
Like they finally do something
I'm good with William Shatner it's been so long
They finally did something
Good with William Shatner around 20 years ago
Is raw
Really not or not
Books about it but
Yeah yeah
Good
That's as good as I have
Hey look we're going to put this on a date we're going to lower the lights a little bit and
You should listen to anime couples
Marty Stuart
Yes sir I'm glad you're enjoying this album
Today we have an album
To discuss
I look at those as album
Okay yeah alright he's prolific
We're going over May 20
21st 2003
No
I'll go back to the past
This is because we have
A little bit of a
Cliffhanger
On the last episode Alex is complaining a whole bunch about the Matrix
Are you saying he was going to go see it and you're satisfied
To give some sort of closure to this guy was in The Matrix
By this point
We're going to get one of those rare
Gentleman movie reviews
We're going to get a gem of a movie review I found
Get through this
Hello
What's out there
Lego from
I'm a policy wonk wren
What's your name
I'm a policy wonk
First middle-aged mice
Technocrat
And Perry from Norway thinking about you and I would like
Money off that heroin
So good
Is freakishly large
Midol
And unfortunately rest in peace middle-aged apology
Father doubt so to speak is going to be fun
If you will
Giving someone life is giving someone death
You can say that
Ben got in touch with us and dad on the 17th coming up this week
Thursday would be Thursday
Also
It's Matt's
Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy birthday
Universe and everything
No it's 42
Right
Isn't it
12 in 32 first
Okay
Thought you were f****** with me
Vets
The universe
This is trying to answer
Is what is 6 * 7
If anybody got
The question in the answer right at the same time the universe would be destroyed
And be replaced by something even weird
Okay
Happy birthday Alex
Kind wishes for
Born
Is the condition that leads to death
You said life is a disease that ends in death
Jordan today where Alex
21st this is a rare instance where I decided like
I have not watched
Steve's movies in
Forever I might need to refresh my memory
Actually watched
The Matrix Reloaded
Has a
It's a sort of refresher course cuz I was like what is he talkin about it comes to movie reviews
Dan's going to look into it
And research things and take down your opinion well I was curious
I was curious I remember enjoying
The movie
I have a lot of things I'm going to read some of my my notes
Just sort of raw
Go over some my thoughts are you doing a live tweeting and I basically did on a notebook
Book page
I enjoyed it
I'm sick of these long like explanations of the plot and the history of the movie or the shots Angela
What that means for interpretation now
Alright really picked up after the highway scene
The beginning
Ticket but
No everybody wants to watch the dancing scene for at least another 6 minutes use
But I don't begrudge that too much it wasn't it wasn't insurmountable in terms of enjoying the movie
Like I said
So does that
Alex
Last night I went and saw
Shrimp
From Illuminati origin
It is a deeply Illuminati s***
But when Alex said
I'm going to give you about a 5-minute review Dan just went
Shook his head no
All of that was robbed
Alex had seen the
The first major
First movie
Illuminati s***
I don't know
Yes
Definitely Illuminati s***
You like that the concerns have been put to bed put them to bed
What the concerns to bet
Because the answer is yes which is somehow less
Concerning
Well I mean it's a
It's no longer an open question
Now you know that this is just evil
I mean I suppose certainty is a comfort in Subway's ripe
So I guess at this point I would say that
If you're convinced that this movie has Illuminati Origins
Maybe you shouldn't
Do that old redtail thing
Like we shouldn't take that metaphor
So so what you're saying is
Perhaps these stupid thoughts
Are b******* that they're feeling in the moment and then later on they'll be like
A truly great movie and let's use the metaphor
Get the sense of that
Shouldn't see this movie
Humans
But if you're going to see it
Eaz whatever
Just don't show it to kid
And
If you want
New World Order
Battery
Barry
Very dark
About Matrix Reloaded
Culver's
He does go over a little bit of it
I will save it
From
Like I listen to Alex's review first
Got confused and then I watch the movie like
What is Allah he doesn't cover
You. Have a very good sense of the movie
It's a big movie
Me too much in it
But
He starts off
His conversation about the Matrix
Expire talking about the first movie
Don't know if I agree with his
Overall
No problem
I take issue with that mean like maybe there is some new aging is to it certainly
Believe in yourself and you can change the parameters of reality
That's most everybody in that movie who also believed in themselves right next to Mio
We murdered within the first 45 minutes
Yeah Neo didn't have the ability to change things
Because he believed in himself because he was created in Born inside the Matrix
You're trying to say that we're all the chosen one
But that's not what them if you're going to bring that to the film that's on you
Coming in for fucksake sand one movie later after this one
Neo is literally in a christ-like position to show you this making the sacrifice
Spoilers
To get to that
I can't wait
Yeah I think his interpretation of
The first movie is a little bit slot
Based on everything about the
Yes the End of Watch
But he know he watched this this
The first film
Like I said he was confused
This Illuminati
Because you don't know if it's Illuminati or not
Maybe the wachowskis are putting out some things that is heroic sure anti-illuminati
Or maybe
What's illuminati
New age
But overall
Not sure if
What
So I was pretty excited to hear about like
Why
Pure C
What seal the deal
What was it about this film that was like
God not dead to rights this is physical ability need to know
Did you just watch the credits in the executive producers were the Illuminati
I was not prepared for
How this review would get going
Okay I was like okay he's going to misinterpret something or
I couldn't have
Possibly imagine that this was the start of it
Outrageous
And there is a
Behind
With
Talking about
Alex is mad about a Powerade commercial
It I was I was I was out
When he said
Before we even get to the movie we got to deal with the
The trailers
No no no I don't even know why would the Illuminati trailer this isn't even 2 trailer
I thought he was misinterpreting a commercial for Men in Black 2 or something like Rip Torn
Hi Dad.
It's not it's not we'll get into it but he's really mad about
Power
Great your
Do as you are ordered
It's not it's a commercial
If you watch it like now if you
So this wasn't an authority figure in the commercial it was one of the agent
From the movie
Subliminal flickering lights
The commercial was just setting the interrogate interrogation room where they took Neo in the first movie
Tell me the stuff that Alex is saying is from the commercial but some is also his own embellishment but
Obviously just a way to like sell Powerade using the character from the movie
I spent a lot of time thinking about it and honestly this is the only way you could
Could do a commercial like this with a
Italian
To The Matrix
But if you use any of the main characters
It's going to really
Team goofy ass s*** all.
The engine would be great
They're perfect for this because
They don't have a personality except for agent Smith
Essentially this blank slate
One of them selling Powerade doesn't negatively affect your impression of the agents because
The cat
They aren't individual right
That said
I wouldn't watch this commercial
Canon problem with a commercial
Play a little clip hear from that commercial and then we'll discuss the other issue
Consider this
Somebody heat pure precious life giving me energy
Fortunate you are collective puny little Minds couldn't figure out a way to harness this energy put it to good use
Somehow but that's beside the point
Energy your body needs to be replenished so
Powerade
Quotas to meet that's obviously supposed to be like deadpan comedy the problem is that this agent
Trying to sell Powerade to people who are inside the maitre
Activities inside the Matrix shouldn't affect the amount of energy that gets produced by the person's physical body outside of the paper
People's actual bodies are in
Pots they have no need for power
There's some stuff going into a to believe that they are suspended in
Google of some sort them out. Couldn't rube if so
This commercials underselling
Given what we know about the machines in the movies
Is physical activity
Booty in the Matrix translated to greater energy production in the real world
Then everyone in the Matrix would be suspiciously into exercising
Billion batteries any could boost the productivity by 30% of their avatar The Matrix works out
That's an amount of energy production that would not be ignored by
Generally they are well known for
How do you think is on the table but it's like the idea that there's somebody somewhere
Man
Nobody is using these gym membership
This is unreal
Anyway
Bottom line here is that
Commercial just got a dub
It's got to be so fun
Powerade commercial the play before the movie
Top part of the film and it's not meant to shame people for being dumb
Diversion of ergot
It's like sorry guys
Nobody's working out so you can't turn your AC on this this week
Yeah I like I like those that Alex is sitting there in the theater watching this Powerade commercial and he's like
I am personally insulted by this character
I have been shamed by this power
Wow you just can't
Find a single moment not
To be mad about
Yeah mad about a Powerade commercial what what why even bother with the movie you're already done yeah what's it like
How do you take in any media
If you're shamed by a Powerade
So the actual movie start
Here's where Alex is at
Man launches in to
World of the Matrix that is the real
Call Laurel
The underground
Zarion
Get it
And
You
The
Haha
Okay
World or the maker
Both of these are
If there's one thing that I took away from the message of the Matrix movies be even before I went re-watched it
It's kind of the Opera
Opposite of perception
Funny movie is it something's that
Feel like reality might not be
But there is a definite reality
Which is worth fighting for
If perception was truly reality that I wouldn't matter if Neo ever perceived The Matrix to be the actual world or Andalusia
If you accept the Matrix has reality than it would at
Actually be that
The movies do actually deal with this quiet
Eloquently
Perception can shape reality to an extent
Like if you're in the Matrix and you want that to be a reality it's possible to live your entire life in that state and not run into any
Joey pants
His character in Cars movie he wants to be reinserted into the Matrix and not be aware of the fight against the robots because it's more come
Walkable to him
And it's implied but that's something that can be done
He's subjective
Experience and perception
You can create is subjective reality
But that isn't real
The movie is very clear there's an entirely different
Actual realities exist
Regardless of your subjective beliefs about reality
Nothing you do in The Matrix effects that fact
As the what is reality
Robots have turned humans into batteries
Doesn't show you the desert of the real real
Not the desert of the we perceive this to be dark
Really interesting to me that this is this is where Alex is that because he's getting caught up in a pretty Elementary philosophical question
Perception and reality that movie actually
Cuz One Step Beyond
In terms of the even just the starting point is path
That's what we're really dealing with here
It's like when you're when you're watching
Explaining the movie to my grandma
Do you know of just like
Things that aren't really part of the movie but she's going to like it a lot more than if you tell her like there's a car chase
So Trinity jumps on a motorcycle Alpha
Okay
Wearing black spandex Italy
Looks great
Zion takes issue with
Like weird things
Specifically about like naming conventions
But when I went back and I watched
Take issue with everything
Everything has a f****** name that means of the reference to every
Another one
Overtone
With
Leader
Absolutely not
Call the Merovingian
Illuminati
With the Merovingian
He's not a good guy
Nope
We are we all recognize that he
That's why he's got Batman yeah
High-end villain he's accusing tagonist of this planet
Side quest
Yeah I guess it's
Zion and we are vengeance
You take some picture with those portable like
Nebuchadnezzar
Is the name of their ship
Yeah yeah
Trinity
No don't worry about it
No
Morpheus absolutely no reference there then
It's it's interesting The Selective
Was outraged or selective like pointing this out as well
Mean something without
Without incorporating all of the things
It just fits
Pikachu I mean
If you name something Zion in a
Piece of popular culture someone's going to be
Scooby Alex in 2003
Yes that's going to happen but if you're mad about that you can't
You can't let that get in the way of being mad about all the other religious references in the movie no
That's the problem here he needs to be a more holistic
Decatur
The movie
It's evil
I mean really the bottom line
Oh my God
F****** Illuminati or back at it
Why is it
The first thing that you bring the fact that it's mind-twisting at evil
Urges
Very weird to me
Very strange
Even for Alex that's weird
Yeah
There's homosexual and lesbians
Seeing yeah yeah 2003 was was different though he like
For gay people were even allowed to
Mary so I think there was a lot more open and vicious
I mean now there's so much open and vicious hatred
The world sucks
Yep
So this is all just trying to make
Implants
Fashionable
Body Mod
Yeah yeah
It's in the back your head living in the future now
That's been bored out we all have jacks
In the back of her head
The video games
There was
All over your body
Like Okay so
Matrix was popular
Alex is trying to make this argument
To condition you to get jacks on the back of your head to plug into
The computers or something sure
But like
If your argument is just that that's popular and there's like spin-off properties like
What are the Ninja Turtles
Oh yeah
They were
Huge
What about that
What were the what were the globalists
String to Main Line
That really trying to turn us all into people who will
Going to Google that I had and this I remember specifically I had a Raffaele
Action figure and what you do is you would push Rafael's
Head down
And it would
Attached to a spring and then you
And the head
Like he was head-butting you up right that I learned that the Illuminati want me to head butt
The s*** out of
Wait a second
Raphael
Was a Ninja Turtle true what weapon does neo grab when he's fighting the mirror vinje in the goons in
That staircase
Was it was it size
Oh wow Neo is Rafael this is blowing the whole thing wide open for me
Ninja Turtles were preparing us for the Matrix comparing us to take
Jackson baccalaureate
What's another point of pride in the movie though how many people were born naturally who didn't have
The Jackson were like
I'm pretty sure that that was I believe so
I'm also the scene that I was just talking about like with the machines are good or whatever it's just that scene or the
Who takes Neo down to the engineering level
Zion and he's like well
You know
Cheat suck
But also
We got to use it
Yeah we wouldn't be able to breathe without here so it's like a win some lose some situations
Is a little heavy-handed
The dialogue play
Whatever I guess if I would want to take that
As
Oh that's right whatever the old guy pulls them standing on the ledge with all the
It's behind them and no one can see them or whatever the middle-of-the-night Via wakes up
Thing I loved about that scene is like this
F****** apartment complex if you want to call it that easy
Gigantic
That counselor or whatever had to been waiting forever on the off-chance that need
So you could walk up and be like
Do you need some cocaine do you want to hang out
I would love to
That's either we just behave like
He doesn't even have like a cellphone to like play a game
B16a twiddling his thumbs
You got the new futuristic version of Angry Birds and he's just throwing plushies off of off the
Should I hope Neal has a bad dream and wakes up
How to make this look like I'm randomly pass
He's hiding around
The corner.
So
You know the big set-piece at the end of the movie is Neo meet
What's with the architect
Who created all of
The previous matrix's
Write to Neo that he is a
Aberration
Yeah bakerix
He's supposed to go to the source and that everything will reboot reset all over again it was built into the code etcetera
Etcetera little bit
Employed
Obi-Wan Kenobi
No
Te bote
There
That's correct
Surprised he understood
But with an allergy
God
That clip was fascinating to me because he's kind of getting it
But he also doesn't seem to understand that it's a
Piece of fiction
No he doesn't get that the characters
In The Matrix that like Neo runs into are supposed to be Pro
He doesn't get like the ID
No no
Explicitly say things that are like oh that's what you are
You're all like a guy who fights Neo before he goes to talk to the oracle
Is like
He's basically like a password screen
Totally whatever they go through all those doors like it's the back door in a program I think talk about this
Pretty explicit
Constantly you're like wait
When is he going to fight Microsoft Word Greek god
Going to show up
Would you like some help with that
God yeah I don't understand I don't understand how you can like it half of it I guess and not
The the the bigger picture
Yeah the Oracle herself
Itself is a program and not a person or an actual Oracle at Delphi
So I have now my note
Probably charge reload
You remember the movie right that your handwriting
Is much larger than mine
That was just sort of looks like a
Scribble
Haphazardly take note
To hear I'm just going to read the notes as they appear on the page
Michael from Lost! True
I forgot that Michael for lost
Really great I love that guy. He's really good and roll 2
I don't want him to get hurt
This is just a little note what are the fun things about the Matrix is how important NADA Neo characters are
What route you know what is it is like he's the chosen one and all this
None of it would be possible like what he's doing if it weren't for other things
Like Morpheus is doing
Is doing like everyone else has like
Parts that they need to play
In order for
Him to be able to live up
To his one that totally whatever
What characters are from a diverse set of backgrounds with a bunch of different possibilities within my next note
Willie Jones jr.
Videos of the night also forgot the Rogers juniors in that onesie
Oh man one of the one of the great albums one of the greatest rap album
Around 1 the album
Roy Jones jr.
Weird who won the kid knocked out
Who won the fight Roy Jones who won
Oh yes
Weird yep
Okay
There's that scene
The stupid note
There's a skeeter
Agent Smith turns another person into an agent Smith actor
2 kiss
Totally
Felt like they were going to
Alright
What would you do if you met you Dad
I probably would have died.
XO probably try and beat myself up
So I thought that it was a little bit tacky that the Beast
Between Morpheus in
The commander was about niobe was about a woman
Easy especially when we're dealing with
The good character choice because despite the fact that we're dealing with such an end-of-the-world level threat
People are still going to have those dumb little personal
You know I'm saying I get that it's a little bit convenient little simple
I f****** love Harry lennix
22 plays the commander he is great he is really really good
Man f****** hard-ass for
No reason half the time but also
This is my next.
He's not wrong to doubt Morpheus
Out-of-pocket
He's ignoring the chain-of-command understand
Yeah
The other the other thing too that I was thinking about is like
You know you
You forget
I guess if you haven't seen these movies in awhile you kind of forget that everybody
She hates Neo
Morpheus basically
They're not the heroes
Was to the powers that
In the human world of Zion like they are not
Like
They are out
But you said they're out of pocket
Totally
You forget that
It's there their they're
Basically populist leaders Alex should love it
Yeah to a certain to a certain interpretation to you can view that as like
It is a positive thing bed
These people will
Just completely ignore orders and completely ignore the
The current power structure in order to fight what they believe is is true and correct
But also what if they were wrong
They just killed all of humanity
So there's that
Yeah you know
Next note I love Hakeem died on sex
I do love a cave
I just didn't
Care for the aesthetic of
Tell you about the cave we when I watch that movie with my best friend and his dad
I can't remember how old we were at the
The time but it wasn't like
Cool for us to go
Because
My parents heard
That there was a tit
In the dancing my friend
Oh I didn't you have spotted it unless somebody told you way in advance as if there's a lot of people on earth
That was enough for my family to be like
There might be at it
Not being able to see that leads me to my next note is that is this cave is way too big
There are their moment app.
Tribal beats and The Rave
Tubac the acoustics
We're great in that cave big
Next note Fishburne
Not good I don't think he was carrying his wife
First movie he did so much he was allowed
Just kind of be in the back
You know I was just not
That I was not that into him
Is Neo a virgin
Look when he and Trinity or hook it was sure his first time I mean in the real world that has
I would think so
That's interesting
What's not very
But a little bit interested
What kind of what kind of Dick Powell's could you have if you've only done it in the imaginary world
I don't know I mean maybe
Hey if you coming in The Matrix you coming real life is that true
I think so if you die in The Matrix then yeah
Everybody Google is gross
Next
Keanu is not enough of a blank slate
Like when you were sitting there talking
To the the oracle
He's supposed to be
Like a black fly
That's
Kind of
Do you have
You is too much agency before the role that he's in
I think I'm okay
All right I might be wrong
But I would need to watch the movie again and then we could really get into it
I got a little bit bored
There's cuz it dry a little bit
This note is
This movie is
Just a video game everything is affect request constantly over and over again
Yeah yeah you have to
To go get
Key-maker the key-maker takes you to a door
You know it's over going over again like
You have to go to a and then once you get there also know you got to go to be
It's getting a little bit clunky but
Like I said
Get to the
Like
Highway chase
Gcn
Things pick up bismuth
This business picks up a little bit of like
They're just going around doing a
Statquest a little bit more
It was
A drag
Later on borderline a heist film in that way of like
A problem arises we have to
To go somewhere and get the
Like a like Ocean's 11 we got to go get the
EMP from some other place cuz I was broke or whatever it is
Like that kind of thing
Hugo weaving is a monster
He's killing it
He's good he is good good act and he's good at
And I have a different interpretation of the elrond but that's fine
Crushing
Also I didn't
Really have as much of a memory
Of who the bad guy is
Like obviously in the first movie the bad guy is
The Matrix
It's
I kind of thought that was true in the second movie to and then agent Smith
Becomes the villain in the third
I didn't realize that it was really clear
Early
In the second movie
The machines are no longer really like their independence
Maybe
Hassle
I have clearly agents
It's a virus
Yeah
Also
This is this is just a little bit of a nip pic thing
Neo stops bullets
You know why is he ever punched
Sometimes
He has telekinesis
I don't understand why nobody threw up
Bottle of Powerade at him that he can also start with Drake
Well he's stopping power 80 could scold Alex's
It will give you power
I hope to see Gan fight scenes look amazing
Being made in 2003
They hold up
I'd sometimes like a little bit of it's a little bit cartoon you can tell its digital but like
Considering that this is
18 years old
There was a point in the agent Smith fight where you so clearly see it Go from
People trying to actually
Do choreography to
I like
Complete CGI stuff for you like okay well this might be a little bit on The Uncanny Valley but
But it's not like
It wasn't so much that it took me out of the experience of watching
Expense digital or whatever but it's not distracting
Everyone is right
All of the humans are right
Reality is complicated
Everwood disagrees everyone is right
I thought that was a little bit weird
I do I like that
I like that a lot I like that everybody's right but everybody is also
Disagreeing about maybe they have a cross-purposes kind of being elected Maybe
Do you have the same goal
And the way that you think
We're going to get to that goal is
Correct
Right but it might be sort of contradictory
Next note
Two exclamation points on this one correction
Cornel West
I forgot Cornell what does forgot that he plays one of the members of the Tribunal
Get the f*** out of here
Speaker.
It is
Although probably the first time I saw it I had no idea who Cornel West was why would I go why would I be a
12 year old that's like a huge Cornell whiskey
It's possible that you just had no idea but it's it's outrageous he's one of the people who's on the board or whatever
Whatever they're talking about sending two more captains to help out with an epic another
And then there's the old lady and then it's Cornel West
There's a couple other people but yeah those are the three that I have speaking roles
So this is from the Merovingian seen him cry
I forgot that that woman orgasm from eating the cake that he sent her
That's true
Becky
That was really weird
Because
Is because the only thing that you can think of while that's going on
Is somebody right next to her going
I'll have with cheese have
Nothing like that's literally WhatsApp
The Matrix
Code goes in between her legs and then there's an
Explosion has like this
I would have
I would have taken another path
Totally not in line with the rest
Genitals give you an orgasm
Bright
Okay alright
Monica Bellucci
Thought this was really funny
This computer program really wants to get kid
I don't know why I'm like that
I thought I was watching them go in and out of doors
It made me think of The Adjustment Bureau
I have nothing else to add to that I just thought of you
Bureau
They were the hats
I'd like to the twins
The dreadlocks albino twins this is aggressive I don't know why you're pointing at me because I remember not liking them the first
First time I saw the movie has a little bit
Or whatever
Their powers are really well.
Defined
And well done in the movie
They can choose when to have physical form accentuate
So they can be in danger
From a knife or a gun or whatever
Breakaway is they go in and out of cars
If you're the only thing I didn't like is that like they apparently dian-anic
Explosion
They could have just gone off Memorial
Also
Miosha just a toilet
Trinity that you saw her death
If not Matrix
Really cut down on time
It certainly would have been more
I don't know if
They have what's presented as a good relation
They seem to really care about each other
It does not make sense that he wouldn't
Trust her with that kind of information
Bear in a post
Apocalypto
Hellscape world
Let's be on the level with each other
Yeah
Honesty is the best policy whenever everything is collapsing
Three exclamation points again
Suburbia clear Stakes
Everything is very clearly like a flashback to the Joey pants situation
Wait are there more sticky
I think that the stakes were a lot clearer than
I expected them to be
A lot of sense
Amanda the last thing
It was
From the architect
He says that you can go to the source
And then you choose people to repopulate Scion like we've done the last five times
Sure
Who was the last one
Who did that and create a desire
Who was the
I don't know
I know oh okay you're you're telling me I mean was it the exact same meal was and it can't be the same Bo
Because later on we find out who made a different choice is it the same deal who's learned from his previous
I don't know but it's a pattern code
It's it's
Whoever the last
I'11
Is not a good Cara
Yeah I mean that's
That is that kind of like
Really dangerous choice
Theoretically
He could
Just wind up wiping out the human race entirely
If that new and I don't know why were
Using a gender
Pronoun for this could be anybody
But
Spay
He's bit of the person is faced with the choice of like
Is everybody going to die or am I going to reboot this perhaps infinitely but
If I reboot it at least we got another go
Ralph so
There's that moral quandary there
I hated the architect because
Freudian
No Obi-Wan Kenobi
No yeah I mean you can't replace big words for actually
Making sense
So there's a lot of that where I'm like
You're just using that word because you know people are going to look up the definition
Enough sense
They're like
Did it serve
Actually you get it but from a fine granular kind of
Septum Crossing out $5 words left and right
Yeah yeah that might be a good note but also I did enjoy how like you know that obviously the movie is building towards like
The climax
Like somebody is going to maybe be like action-oriented
That is fun
There's some subversion
Inappropriate
Anyway my review overall not bad
No I don't like movies that much but I enjoyed at least
Half of it
Like I think it was really slow start
Yeah like when they're in Zion
And
All that
It's it was tough.
Yeah I was like I'm going to turn this off
Like 15 minutes and I was like
I can't sit here and watch this
Push through and I enjoyed it once it got cooking
Yeah I recall there being a lot of
Vitriol towards Reloaded
And and then even more towards
Revolution
I think that also might be because we were coming off the back of
The Phantom Menace and attack of the Clones at the same time so everybody
Furious at every
And I think
What is the first Matrix
Almost
And impossible challenge
To follow up
Talk like
I think that was that was something
Caught on so huge
And
Blue Mind
Like I don't even know what you would
Do if you like
We're trying to make another one
Especially with a massive budget
That you're expected to show in the film
You know like the original Matrix was so well
Written and so tight
Because of those
You know
Challenges
Actually not of course
It's because of them
Yeah but that
That kind of we got to figure out a way to do this that's cheap is
A lot of times they really
Interesting and
Fanta created
Necessity is the mother of invention
William the architect
So Alex gets to talking about how like in 25 years
That's true Machines man
What are warning you of the Takeover
Global
Government control
See that's kind of fun
Because Alex
Could take that clip
Look at Facebook
I was right
He's talking about the Matrix and talking about that being with you
In your in your house that you're plugged into or whatever like
It's not it's not a metaphorical
Oh my God social media is going to take off
No and there were people already at the
The time going like
Social media might not be a good idea to have it take off and they were people who had studied
Real life
Technology
In real life Trend swords that they weren't like
It's going to be exactly like the Matrix dog eyes
The movies evil
That's all this is there like this whole movie Everything Is
Preparing you
Jordan
Go into the Matrix
Pairing you
Your journey into the real Matrix
The elite
And you were going to be
Word
Wired article in case you did not listen to our last episode was about a research
Proposal the DARPA had for Bergen called life log
I was didn't end up having
We're not in
We're not
Or are we no exhaust
I feel exhausted by those sorts of question
Hungry like 1 maybe we are what is real
Fun Alex fine
The painful
To watch movie
Like the mate
Who's painful
But
Supervisor coffee
Larry
Pairing
My money buddy
I just
I am just blown away by that statement out of a human
After what he's
Yeah I mean like these things are the Illuminati yelled at in 42 hours
And part of that was a Powerade commercial
What's the Powerade commercial on the original DVD or do you have to get the director's cut
Theaters invited on YouTube by Tommy
Gripping
Appositive
The review word right
Remind
Control mean it's hard to keep people entertained
For 2 hours
There were
Who's there really good then
When you're conscious
Curiosity killed the cat
It was about but I'm going to buy a boat
Experience
I don't know if you
Could do a better commercial
For the Matrix movie to Alex's audience than
Yeah like that is catnip
To the theater to like
Like
Oh my God
I was able to resist the mind control
No it's like one of those
It's like one of those marketing strategies where they try and piss off
Christian's because then they know real people will watch it and be like I get it you know this is fun
I'm doing this to make
Whiny old church ladies angry at me
So this makes what Pisgah
Confuse me
Lunar eclipse
Really offense
No
So
I guess according to Alex like which doctors are Illuminati
Man
I will tell you this right now
I think the thing that scares him more than the Matrix Reloaded
More than Oblivion
That's weekend at Bernie
Me too cuz if you recall
I think we all know what happened to Bernie in that situation or the clip he was brought back to life
And ambulatory by what we
We would have called it
The time of Woodstock
Yeah I know that I've heard these sorts of ideas from Alex
Come from like
Weird
Colonial era literature
About the like a horrible to picture
Shenzhen
I know that I've heard these thoughts but I didn't know that
His idea of like shaman
Being part of a guild
An ancestral gilled shark
I didn't know that part of it which I think is really funny
I think it's hilarious
To imagine that he think
That all of these these shamans are whatever they were somehow Linked UP
The best hotspot
I just that's what the scam was
What a
F******
Ignorance and racist
Thing to think
Without
Blurting anything about it at all
The question weather like
He got this
From some other very misguided Source or if you wrote it himself
And I'm not sure
So
You like Alex
Is kind of
As it relates to the Matrix
Really caught up and it being a little gay
Diversion
Overall
Illuminati term
Brings up way more than once
But there is like there are things
Is that are homosexual in nature
That's a real sticking point for him
So what he saying is that the Elites in the middle of a crumbling Empire
Will
Do their best to distract you with superstition
And gladiatorial combats
Extort
ISO
That is why Alex
Is
Giving us the Christian point of view of a movie
It makes sense
Turn off so I thought
Man
What fun
We got a movie review Alex's
Off-base on a lot of stuff
Do for the rest of the show
Yeah I feel like there's
There's really nowhere else to go after you
There's no game to the reload is one place to go
I'll expect a call and this guy is he's a disabled person
He wants to know what the global
Worcester going to do with him
Golden
Mark
And
Haywire
I was blessed I was cut out with a rock
Aziz murati
Pretty much all my life
Can hardly read
Anna
Browser real bad wreck
I had to go on cold days
Spell DMS my neck and Mom sign up
Disabled
Nu-Way Whitney
They are going to
And you will live in a small one-room
Cameras everywhere
Curb weight
What the fuk was that
That is so f****** cruel that dude is
Clearly struggling in the whole super f***** up
He's really just
Man
And then Alex just
Without a f******
Thought just makes up some b******* about this guy's going to be torture
The death in a small apartment under watch of the SWAT teams
Luda hydrator
Is that what that guy was calling and looking
I don't think it's
Maybe he couldn't possibly have been looking for
No
No maybe he was looking for something
To justify his
His belief and Alex
This is where the whores that they're going to inflict
Upon someone dystopian future
Yes that I must fight
And this caller actually does you know I guess he does get what he was looking for and he hopes that he can Fight 2
To the death
Against these people who would
Seek to dehydrate
Where are you
God gives me today
Still got two boys 124
What
I mean honor thy father and mother of course commandment more important than all
Sure
Also no
Huge no
That seemed that seemed a little bit out of place for what I know of Alex
Got to take care of yours are going to hell
Very strange man what is strange man to react like this to
Guys clearly babe I feel like these are into
Interesting glimpses into things that you know he would say or
Support
Really necessarily come up if it weren't
There's a lot more callers
In the past also
Yeah I do like finding out hit more and more little tiny details of his a weird cosmology like well obviously if
If you don't stay with your parents and take care of them until their death
You go to hell.
Bat signal
Must be must be
He's been he's big into re-litigate in the Civil War
Here's a couple boy
Soldiers from the Union
Lincoln ended up with AJ
I mean
Translator on a president
Lincoln was like
Appreciate the call
I got to go
Lincoln shows up on a episode where he hates homosexual
Reality so much
So we can
Break me comes back and gets another call and this guy is just watched
TV show about Hitler
And
You want to make some comparisons
The George Bush
The phrasing that Hitler used
Bag
After the Reich
UPS.
Enabling Act
Gave him
I didn't but I certainly hope
Somebody does
You would love it
Geisinger
Brazing
If Hitler used
And arguing for the enabling Act is the same as the phrasing the George Bush
Is using
He didn't take this he has no idea Alex hasn't seen that it's just a conversation.
You catch that thing on TV
Wild
Whatever
I have a theory that I've been working on for a long time waiting is that
Part of why we are where we are now
Is
So many people
I have been so obsessed with watching documentaries about
Hitler and the rise of the Nazis
That
Over time it's turned into a sort of admiration
For a lot of people
Which is why we see all of these conversations and comparisons
Hitler
From the far-right
About everybody else
Despite them
Adopting those
Tactics almost whole cloth you know what I'm saying I think I sit there like it was a
I think you can learn the wrong last
Alexandra's Colorado talking about Hitler and his speech
That has mirroring
George W bush
They get into a little bit of a hey
Let's recast
The Bush Administration
What was there to do
Their analog
In the Hiller Hitler Administration
Don Estridge
Homeland 30
Patriot Act
American hangman
Well I just got a behind-the-scenes
Belew drugs
Nebraska
John Ashcroft was the attorney general for Bush This is not analogous to Himmler who is the right
If your SS if you want to be overly generous
You could say that he was
Metaphorically the
Head of the joint
Chiefs baby
Something like that
Colin Powell
Tom Ridge is the Secretary of Homeland Security
Hermann Goering was the head of the luftwaffe and then he wasn't
Control the reichstag sewing
Speaker of the house or maybe
Vice presidents into the president of the Senate
Fairly Rumsfeld is gerbils which is f****** nuts
Karl Rove is garbled
Yeah anyone who knows how to book a fantasy Nazi team knows that it's a disgrace that Alex's Macomb throw
It's grown out of
No there's only Grove and girdles like it's those two
Very very simple so gabbles
He had some ideas about the big lie
That is so much like how
Devils
Get my ideas about the big lie right enough live people will believe it
Big lie
Harder it is for people to get it whatever
The big lie
What Joseph
Was Hitler's minister
Make it big
I don't know I seem to remember from
Play I quoted it
That may well be wrong
So some people think I was taken out of
Is there anything more American than two old white guys talking about Nazis but they haven't bothered
To read
Gerbils took the concept of the big lie actually from another
Source
From mine comp
Hitler's book
The passage in question had to do with Hitler blaming everything that went wrong on the Jews
The Jews that committed a big lie about what did God down
What Alex says Victor Bose points out that their enemies use a big lie when he's failing to point out of the actual contact with a quote
Is Nazi propaganda against
What's Jews
The big lie what was the LIE
About Jews being the proper
That was the Big Lot
Yeah the big light wasn't
The Jews lying about their involvement the big light was telling people that it
Great job putting the history of the contact
Extra
The great this is the guy said that Hitler and Stalin
Complete badass
Cheese bread
So many books about WWII
Millions
So Alex gets another call this is my
Kind of cat
He wants to know
A very specific question
From Alex
And that is
What Bible do you read man
And this is a loaded question
Because this means something to this call
Obviously he think
Max B some
Versions of the Bible
Are not a cure
Yeah it seems like a like a newer version
The King James of the NIV or whatever it is you like books that are added
BECU somebody who's into some non canonical book
Books maybe who knows
I love this kind of question cuz
Very specific and there's a specific answer that
That you should go
If you're religious person you should have an opinion
Even if that opinion is I think a lot of different translations
You are okay you should have an answer
Outwits
Let's talk
Jordan
First-timer
Nothing
I just want to know
What Bible
Church
Work with the government
No no no Alex doesn't go to church does he goes to text Mars
Noted anti-semite
Yeah yeah yeah
I don't answer leave him believe that I think I was just grasping at straws and I was the only thing that could come into his mind of like
This is a crazy right wing
Extremist
Church I can
Signal to
Yeah then the caller is just like he wants an answer of like King James
All the way baby
And Alex instead of like I only go to insane semites Church
I don't go to church
Where you worship the government couldn't be more of an import
Question either because the simple fact is if you want to believe the Bible you also have to believe that it was
Divinely-inspired
So if there's a difference
It's between two different versions of the Bible
That would suggest that
People got involved somewhere along the line
At least in one of the versions
If there is a discrepancy
So other Scholars into Jesus should be enough for our
Call Ryan Lewis
Just leaving the old time religion
The Lord Jesus
You know when going out
Personal Soul winning in
What
So apparently
Alex's prerequisite
For church
To actually be a church
Is they have to have his political inclination
And preached about the New World Order
It's not enough
No they are aggressively and confrontational e into saving Souls 4D
That's weird
That's pretty weird
Yeah you know if there's anything I've always thought about religion it said it should be in politics
Non-Stop
Yep
Another caller and this guy is kind of into Hitler I believe
The New Yorker on the here go ahead
Oh no
Hughes
Navigating
Well duh
The devil
So I guess you saying that the Jews are
So
Wait so the Antichrist
Toll said that Hitler
No the Antichrist doesn't reveal the aunt
Christ plan
Good thing to reveal the Antichrist plant
Hitler talked about how the Jews were to blame for everything in World War 1
Like pointing the finger at nationalist leaders that is
Hitler revealing the Antichrist
Plans which was
I mean if you look at it
Is very clearly saying that the Jews are
Basically what he
Yes that's why I'm
Concerned
Right
It's an issue
There is a problem especially after you know
Alex's said that he goes
Text Mars's Church
Yikes like this is just this is deeply a smell
Yeah but everything that's going on here
Yeah
I don't
You could just get away with a lot of s***
Oh yes how man and then it gets even worse
Speakers
A name gets dropped
And Alex
Although he should be denouncing this person
Will not
I forgot his name to eat from
WhatsApp
The name David
He was saying you know it's a new world order and is not much that we can do about it cuz you know it's in the Bible
Thinking of anything less than the Bible in
Exactly
The world
So David J Smith is doing the same thing that all of these evil churches are they open
Paid off to do it
He's saying there's no use
I'm fighting the new world order or whatever
What he's doing it for
If you don't recall David J Smith is
The creature whose Super8 to British is realism much a white-eyed
Proponent
Are the true Jews are white
So now we have
Two examples within like 10 minutes of Alex's show
To very
Anti-Semitic
The preachers
That Alex is a fan of
Speak ill of
That's bad man
That's that's really bad
Yeah yeah and especially because
One of the things that we
Thought for so long as they went under the radar with his anti-semitism
By just renaming it globalism
That he's just openly anti-semitic here it's kind of
Mind-boggling
Like
Does he
Hyatt Lake
Isaac
He probably doesn't experience all of this stuff is being as anti-semitic as address
So let's let's take a load off let's get a little bit lighter this been in
Put some heavy stuff with these calls
This is just a good fun it's one of the things that I think is is
Is Google
What are the Delights
I'm going back to the
The past
Theme
Keeps going on throughout the show
And that is the people
From the Republic of Texas
Keep calling
A warning
To like
Get Alex's take on things
Sovereign citizens
Alex Beyond bored cuz he wants
What's the seceded what have you
But he hates these people
Appreciate
Not Dewayne but why
And checking to see if you have gotten my letter
And I think you'll recognize it
Because it had the two
Flag on the envelope
Fax number from you not over-the-air
My fax
Well sir I don't know
You know I barely have time to read
I understand
What's on your mind
Received a letter
From the
Republican National
Committee
Only mine
I answered your question error and then
What are my opinions
Yes
What are your opinions
Well my opinions are
Set
The only way we're going to beat this Subs
Start small
Start the process for success
And then
Republic of Texas people
Not a big tent
M414 president
Yes I got your letter.
That is the best yeah I got your letter
Malaysian of
But I got your letter familiarity of like I know exactly who I'm talking
Yep this is happening
This is going to happen
The president of Texas call again I have to I have to let you talk a little bit because I know so many of
My listeners are you
There isn't really
All that much
Arab
Between us
There's not there's not a real substantiv difference between what we believe I just hate you I just hate you
Because you won't shut up about it
I want to talk
About the Matrix Reloaded
Yeah
And take aggressively antisymmetric calls
And now I have to be like
Do the government to lie
Rap-up
Alex's is taken
Some calls he has it he has a guest
Who talks to for a bit and
The 3rd hour
Who's someone who ran a
Iea Union
In New Mexico
Because I had a war
Yeah and
Something that takes probably
Bi-Lo
Canal point out or whatever else would do that in the present-day but also I don't know
I'm really that interested in this because like obviously it personally I agree they shouldn't have been evicted
But I understand
Having a demonstration
Could have been a breach of their league
So I understand and I don't understand why Alex would be against
The landlord's
Write 2
Evict someone for Happy Valley
I don't talk for a bit
One way I am like you know part of protest is that there are going to be concert
You can't protest in think that
It's not a protest if no one is going to fight back
You know that's just
Advice
Much like
But you like The Matrix 2
Need to be state
Absolutely
And then on the other hand
F*** you
Evicting that fair enough
Microban
Do you know how strong he is
He kept you kept your mind control he's going to buy the movie Jessie
Test himself against
Mind control
ORD and it's good practice
Ordan perhaps all of the mind-control that he was concerned about is not the Mind Control they were thinking about maybe they were mine
And controlling him
Into buying the DVD he also has a fridge full of power and it doesn't know why
Is chugging Powerade in buying tricks don't work on me
Only way to get rid of powerades to drink at all that's what's going to happen I'm going to drink the whole business dry
Our rate is a finite resource
Eventually I'll get to the end of it
Run out of power and I'll give them all my money
So I guess
In terms of this
Obviously you needed to get
To the point where you actually sees the movie
Preparation for an episode list
Concluded me watching
The movie so you know that's a nice little
Derivation from the norm
Will be back
Next episode where Alex will not be reviewing
The Matrix hopefully hopefully
Website
Jordan
We are visible music down the show iTunes could please find a local charity or bail fund interior to help out people
Will doing God's work
Emilio Emilio I'm dzx
Clark I'm Daryl run disarm the American Indian
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work