Damn important
I have great respect for its knowledge B B I'm sick of them
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Around
What about Alex Jones
Indeed we are.
Jordan Jordan
Unprecedented
Did Jordan my breakbot in the same thing it was last episode
But I finished it
OU finished and I had her back in the cartoon again
No I I watched all the Amazon original series cuz I couldn't stop
Everybody
Is just great and it all the characters are great
John Hodgman
In the second season
Freight
Yeah that was rhyme
Going to be a small roller
I know that there's a lot of other things we need to complain about Amazon and Bezos about
Obviously
This doesn't rank really high
The terms of other complaints
You know
I did unionization squashing you're sure it's a lot of problems of Amazon
Maybe not having a secret
Is right up there maybe 48 it's like how Alex
Complaints about the robots of the grocery store is I can
It's the bag of your own groceries of media consumption
I make sense
What about you
I will announce this now
Very excited I will be making a return to Stand-Up post covid
Whoa that's true I was for my first stand-up
During the time that covid was like really
You do look pretty vaccinations coming around I didn't want to do it and I couldn't
People in that City I thought that was a really responsible choice on your part
Now it is in October
And it was booked by friend of the show Matt drift
Play there a lot of people in the higher Q rating than to get through
I'm excited to announce that here
I feel like there was some open questions about whether or not you even were going to continue pursuing
People being interested in by requesting
Basically South before the pandemic
Nazi if I want to give it another shot if you still connected with
The bad kind of expression
See if I still get the feeling so it's always fun to do one of the shows the draft ebooks to
Although
You probably have to go to the Burger will probably have to go to the bank
Yep I'll come with you I will be there as well
Not performing that I will I will be there
Nice to see you
Baby nice to take over the entire show and
And then the rest of the comics are like I don't understand what's happening right now
None of these people know
That sucks
Take over anyting
Jordan today we have
A present day episode of The Alex Jones Show just got
I'm trying to shoot for something a little bit
Different
I'm trying to
Take an analytical perspective of even myself and how I engage with the material that we're covering all right and I think
One of the main problems that I have with the present day
He's sometimes I try to bite off more than I can
Can chew that I mean cover in more than one day at a time
I think that the really hard in the present day because Alex is mood is never the same days in a row
You expect him to cover one piece of news
Yeah but he was really big on a Monday
He probably is going to forget about it by Tuesday
We're all going to be dead on Tuesday Wednesday we're winning
Cheapest just
Incoherent to the point where
Painful for me to try and make it
Palatable to an audience
And it's frustrating to me to try and talk
To you about it
Well why is he in a better but I don't know
Could be anything
It's like he used to do is serialized show and now he's doing a monster the day kind of feeling
Yeah everything's a bottle episode
F****** weird
Think that maybe a better approach to it would be to just look at a day at a
Right
So
I sped into the bike that cuz I know you're trying to lull me into a false sense of security
There is there is a metagame currently going on between us
On June 13th is the as the kids say
Okay
Is wildin out
He is on fleek
I disagree with your use of fleek
But we shall see
Not sure what it means
Business on this before we do let's say hello
Oh that's great
So why first
Rev Dr Robert EO Speedwagon
Call Alisha Adventure saw there's a character
Call Robert
Speedway
Whoa
Could be alright
Next Jim no relation to a certain World War
Thank you thank you thank you for surviving so long with that Dave next child
I'm a policy wonk
Seized
First mr. and mrs. makeshift hamster thank you so much you're now technocrat
Sister scream thank you so much you are now.
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
It's time to get deep
Giving someone life is giving someone death
You can say that
Life is good
You good
I'd like to say happy birthday
Leonardo
Congratulations on the graduation to Madison Ave
Okay
Also I should say that this happened in May
Congratulations
And happy birthday to you may have missed a message
I think they just sent it now
Oops we forgot to give him a birthday shout-out let's get on it
Happy belated birthday congratulations on the graduation
Is giving life is giving death
Is giving graduation just
Signing up for school
Look I've got to I've got to leave you hanging out that way it's fair
One other thing was that Erica send a message
Special drop played
Why not I think the people are itching
Temprid SC
Is going up to you Erica
I got baby shark.
Mama shark beat beat beat beat beat
I'll be right back
Always good to hear some daddy shark
So are we talking about June 13th but here is not a caltex dropped
Today Show
You know I would never say if I got killed
Start a civil war
Good
Well one
You would already be dead so you wouldn't have the opportunity beforehand
Deadman switch for a civil war
Austin the meaning is the
Opposite of the meaning kind of thing I would never say
The planet when I die I would never say that the only reason you would mean
If you want that to be true
Almost nobody would say that
Except for maybe Mandela
So Alex has got a piece of news
Is here on the 30
Papism Sunday show on the 13th you've gotten
The news that's a this gentleman by the name Christopher sign
It passed away
He was a reporter Auntie was the person who is credited with breaking the
Story
The president and former President Bill Clinton meeting with Loretta Lynch
Right arm at CarMax
And of course
That means this was annexed
What is the next thing to come in a season like this
What is the next move always
And the movie been tearing all over the world
Well it's this right here
That's what it is
Forty-five-year-old
Christopher
Sign
Award-winning
TV
We just had a
I was super happy
Well he got executed inside of his house
And his body wasn't even cold
Blood related before they said it was a suicide
Just like Breitbart
Suicidal
Breitbart
Suicide is a heart attack
They said he did a lot of Coke
The situation with his is the reporting on it is
Treated as a
Respective
People reporting
Signs of Foul Play
But generally would lead investigators to initially give a
It looks like a murder
From the inside like everything I don't know all of the Pacific
All the details
You know this is the same thing that Alex does all the time
It's like they're saying that it's suicide in order to make sure that there's a cover-up as opposed to
There's reporting that it preliminary indications appear to be
That this
Was the case of
The cover-up because they're reporting that it's
Not a cover-up
See
Make sense
Yeah so one of the things to keep a real sharp focus on here is how definitive
Reporting this as an ex
Funeral Home
Funny how that just
Flies over me.
That guy was executed with no evidence or thought or anything like that and I'm like well of course he's just
Can I claim that
He's the crying that the media is definitively saying that it's suicide when in fact
The articles that I could find about those were saying that
It's being handled the investigation
Is presumed to suicide
Intel other!
And Alex's doing
The exact same thing just the office
He's claiming the media is doing it
That is jumping to the conclusion of
Knock Lovelace execution for sure because they
It's almost as if he forgets that there are real people involved in the story
He doesn't care
So he also was treating this like a real departure
Trump
The way things were
Let's say yes
Suicide threats
Clinton
Because he's supposed
They have the judge Department in the FBI all Alabama corrupt
Partially
Well
Been waiting for a green light time
To go offensive
His execution is a message everybody
Check to see a lot of these killings that he was definitely murdered in my view
So
This is this is pretty
Definite
But also there's a number of things that he doesn't ever substantiate anyway
On the show which
Just me the problem
The first is he doesn't
Show or give any evidence
Of him saying I will never kill myself
That's just something that he says
Quesadilla tries to make Muddy
And then the other thing is he's taking
Can things completely out of context there is an interview that you did on Fox News this Christopher sign
Were you saying that when he did this reporting he was getting
Threat store
But
He does not say that they are from the Clinton
There's a hundred different explanation for where these threats could have come from
I mean I guess if you want to jump to a conclusion that like
Bill got on the phone
I guess you could use that first person I've had a kid
I guess you if Alex wants to just make that conclusion job and and take
The only evidence that he plays or
Is it always this Fox news interview
Proof that the clintons worth retina
I guess
You can but he can't prove that what has the Fox news interview
It was within the last few years
Okay wasn't recent okay so the interview where he's getting
Threats is from a few years ago
Also he's saying that it was when the reporting happened and that was 2016 5 years ago
Fairly certain people that had to have Let It Go
No they just let you forget about it
I don't know president
That's true
Because you was partially destroyed by this reporter partially taken down
So Alex jumps around a little bit
Just throw a few darts
Surround there's one of them
Heading out now Mainline doctors sweetly to Mexico
People are seriously magnetic
And then we find a literature about its design
To grow magnetic
Prions in the body
See apparently Alex is on the magnet tip
Magnetic primer
In the body
Iron in the blood
Do they inject you first and then they like
Is it like an embryo that grows with inside you and then you give birth to a magnet baby
I don't know
I don't know cuz I would doesn't explain and I don't really
Is a little bit
Viral videos of Schubert
Sure
I got you into it
To talk more about this it's just a throwaway things I guess
Active baby I need more information about that
I was like how small his geography is
Like if this is the
Biggest world in the world from Italy to Mexico
Chirp
So
The clintons
Rick Heller
Time is it the beginning of
Because they were waiting
For the green light or something
Do go ahead and take out people who know
They're dirt
A couple hundred here a couple hundred there's no wait awhile
You'll see the top of group it is
Arkansas Savings and Loan
People that know about their corruption in euros
The Africa scams and deals
But this is how I believe the first Salvo and I've been predicting this is coming
What about Larry Nichols
We don't talk about her that's it pass
That was just bring up Larry Nichols at all here like he passed away within the last year
I swear I
I think we're the only people who notice
I really I really do kind of feel sad about that we talked about it when he died but it is a bummer
Alex doesn't even bring up
If this is if you're doing Clinton conspiracies
You gotta bring up the the Larry nickel
You got to say like a convenient
Now we back up their killings Larry Nichols is no longer with us in waves
Is the oracle
Hot man
Why would they kill in Waze
Doesn't that make
Lesson
Now you got two ear to kill it
And then
The tide go out
Chenab
And then come back I feel like I
Connected killings in a short. Of time and then along
Series
Length of quiet time would
More suggests that it was
You know it's a sensation instead of like
And isolated event
Well if you're not on their Trail
Because I think I've got it
So we got another straight Dart here off of the assassination
Narrative
Very bad development
On that front a federal judge has ruled
That
Employers can order you
Protective vaccine
In experimental testing they won
To have the job
Well I guess they commanded you got to inject cyanide
My Free Will you can kill yourself
The point
How would you get a job
Hospital employees who refused covid-19 vaccine
According to Alex's politics he should not be opposed to employers having the right to make these sorts of Demands
Employees
Right-wing libertarian based on that believes that he should the employer the right to make whatever requirements
They want and the employees should have the right to
Accept them as a condition of employment or find a job elsewhere
Vaccine requirement is something that hurts a business's ability to attract potential employees
The free market will sort that out according to libertarian ideology
Come on be unfair for everybody else libertarianism is about fairness for me
Call those people
117 employees out of the 26000
Houston Methodist Hospital System refused to get vaccinated
How are suspended from their positions
So they sued the judge recently dismissed
What are the reasons that they're kasecamp
Possibly win in court is
Because they're in Texas
And in that state
Every week protections for employees in cases of wrongful termination
Bedard in the judge
Decision they spell this out
Quote Texas law only protect employees from being terminated for refusing to commit an act carrying criminal penalties
To the worker
Based on that standard refusing to get a vaccine can't possibly meet the criteria needed to satisfy their charge
But interesting Lee
Alex is example of injecting yourself with cyanide
I was hit that standard for wrongful termination because that would be a criminal act that would be the only example
Chile Jesus so anyway this is crazy huh
I mean they have
Sort of these that he's weak Protections in place
And warriors
Can make
These
Sorted
Conditions of employment center Alex
Thrilled with that until he's not for everybody
This fits my policies and telefono
So now back to the vein
Varsity storyline which is
Dot-com
Boating information
What is the headline for today
Emergency broadcast
Like the emergency
Reporter who exposed Clinton control of
FBI
Executed inside his home
Very very professionally
The problem here is that Alex can't prove any of this
Recycle the scene play out over and over again and conspiracy culture
By Alex reporting this as a defendant of execution
You feel like he's just creating a thriller plot around a tragic
But ultimately there's a lot more going on
Because Alex is so sure that this was a professional X
Execution he's giving the audience permission to be just as certain
And this leads to problems they encounter people who don't share their certainty
People like victims family members are government officials or media figures
Who don't comport with the conspiracy version of this death are now
Is being participants
Or engaged in the cover-up
These people often get hurt or harassed
Sometimes in these conspiracy campaign
Alex don't give a s***
About them or their well-being
There's nothing wrong with holding some skepticism or asking questions about events that happen
The appropriate thing to do then however
Is to explore the questions privately by reading or interviewing people
We're doing some other kind of investigative technique
I'm trying to find some actual information
This is not what Alex does
He doesn't ask
He makes decisions about how to write other people's stories so they fit the narrative that he
To make a profit off of
And it's to the detriment of the people who are involved
The word
The worst part is just
Like
Putting that per
Professional in there yet
Okay so we do look into it we find out that it's absolutely a suicide
Right well that's how you know it was a professional right only a professor
Evidence of
The conclusion that Alex is already read
You can't
Applicants and overwhelming evidence is even more evidence that the conspiracies true
To be just a little bit of evidence in that sweet spot
And this is bad because I mean obviously I think anyone listening to our show can understand why this is
Is bad
Even more than we've already discussed and that's because Alex is presenting this as like
A real escalation
Same things from the globalist assassinating reporters in order to cover up
They're dirty and there's going to be a lot more of the crossing of the Rubicon
Padma hold other Rubicon
It's because the globalist are so incredible
Everything they're doing
Willing to kill
Hundreds of millions of people attended vaccines
They're willing to do any
I just don't understand how anybody could hear this show
And not think
He's telling you to
Kill people yeah that's the only
Like they've gone offense
Assassinating the people who are putting their business in the streets
And Reporting the truth quote on quote about things
Sprite right so
What what
How how does
I don't understand how he can present like
Do do anything violent
You literally cannot use the metaphor of Crossing
In the Rubicon because the point of the metaphor of Crossing the Rubicon is that once this happens
You cannot be unhappy
Yeah
The line the language that he's using it and the way he's presenting the stories very specifically about like
The game has changed
And now the Rules of Engagement are differ
Right
I don't understand how he
Can pretend that that's not what he's doing
I don't understand how this could be the inciting incident if
We're already confirmed that
The people who have the vaccine are going to
He kills or already dead or whatever it is
This seems like a d escalation about if anything's
Thank God they're only killing individual people instead of murdering the entire country
The stakes are weird
They're not quite as in order as the Matrix related
The hundreds of thousands of people are billions of people live in packs
Well it's the way that Alex needs to tell the story
That's
Stroke
That's just passive murder
This is active but this is when the Cold War goes hot
So this clip is 4 minutes long
And I think it's a ride
Journey
It's
Starts
With Alex
Enthralling
Clip of Sia
Christmas I'm talking on Fox News
That clip does not get
Okay then said it will be a ride
Alex Rambles about how big of a threat
He's under us about himself cuz of course he does
For the course
Admitted ends in a way that will take your breath away
Doritos from the grave
Talking about all the death threats and courage
Is that all these big lawsuits filed against us
Job
Party groups
A lot of stuff that
Disbelieve me
What
I know it's rather big National talk show host
Take the threats and bass
Stop
Back off
Sure for me it's about
I feel close to God
Composite right there just to
Is Macho
In his conception I think that is the same
Endorphin rush or whatever that someone would get from posturing as a macho person
It's just putting the
Context in language of Godly
Or whatever
I think the only time that I am close to God is when I am acting violence
That's not good
This even entertain selling out
Alone and
Why the service of humanity
I'm just a very blessed person
It's not going to be a failure
It's going to be a real success
Is a reckless enough to kill me
Put me in prison
VIP Automotive
Locations of cooking up
Fine I understand
That's not me bro
Throw
Amazon pro
Another
Even after I'm dead
That sucks but whatever
Easier
But I will not have them kill me
I didn't say
That
How they operate
What they've done really good manatee plasm
You know it is a come when you're there with your wife and kid
I'm just going to be completely honest about this
Tough guy turn levels
But I have to really think about everything operates at and then the way things really are
And so I mistaken the Spy
But I do need 24-hour day security for my children
I'm really most the time but I need to have real security I mean guys on the road
All the time
Because you know
That was a big
Just a reminder two-and-a-half minutes ago Alex was introducing a clip
Guy talking about yeah yeah from the grave
Hahaha anyways before I get to that I'm going to need to build a moat around my house
I'm going to have to have snipers on the roof 7th Ave
Chain link fences and razor wire I'm going to do the whole thing need to find more people who used to work for Blackwater
Because of imaginary enemies
Right
Next few days next few weeks
Message to threatened everybody to shut up
Tomorrow
Unpause
Car bomb goes off
This is a very good chance to return
They're little armies Busan
They'll kill Tucker
Wait till kids are in college over visiting or something
Call miss out on me right now
We have to go into war mode now it's gone
Criminal terrorist attorney Oklahoma City
They like
Killing people
Guess what
I'm going to be a soft target for these people
I'm not going to let him tie me up or they blow my wife and children's heads off
Sure
For the real security I need I'm leaving at that I've got done
The time
What is happening
All the time
My family
Target
Selling products
Opera
Show me ladies and gentlemen you know what to do you know who did it
Thrilled to have your ad play George Noory
The fuk just happened to me I told you was alright just f****** happened to me it was right
Is he selling products based
Getting people to pay for security for a family
Okay
Alright
Basically he's saying that if you don't buy more of his pills
His family will be murdered in front of
Wow
I just thought I thought it was pretty shocking
That it ran into money
At the end I shouldn't be shot it was going it was so intense
It's like so off track from where the eclipse started in what he was
Trying to do
We just cover this story and he's not talk about himself like I don't want him to kill my family
I need more security
Okay here's a paranoid spiral
Whatever I can go well I get it
I think that's in the Alex Jones wheelhouse
Then when it turned into like
Using that paranoid
Spiral
To be like I need more money for the security detail
That's what I like
This is crap
He saw that they were coming up on the commercial
He knew that he was about to go to break
He's like
Oh my God
At
Perfect
I can't afford security I need you all to pay for my security Rudolph
Absolutely brutal
I don't know what world
I don't know what the rest of the world would look like if one day I woke up in the headline was
Tucker Carlson dies in carbs
Like
What
The IRA is back like what are we
The IRA limit in New York
I think
If like
Selected people like Ron and Rand Paul and Alex Jones at Tucker Carlson all died in a short. Of time
Ivan
Even I as somebody who'd the space of being full
Disinformation
And bulshit
I like those problem
Well f*** there is a problem this is an issue there
They're probably still wrong
But you know hey maybe there is some kind of a fringe left-wing terrorist
That we have not been aware of
Or something would be a shock if we discovered a strange
Paramed paramilitary leftist organization
I would I would start having
Some questions if there was a convenient series
All of these people.
Even if it was
Justin Tucker Carlson a car bomb
Holyshit something's not right
Yeah
What is happening in this world
I mean all of this
Predicted didn't happen there was not
You know this
This wave.
The 13th right okay we're recording this on the seven
That's correct okay
Tucker is still technically alive from what I understand you
So is Ron Paul
You just can't kill rampal with the car bomb
He's to craft
He smelled it out so
But again
Seems like Larry Nichols would be exactly who Alex would want to throw into the mix on there
Patel Brother
Not bring him up at all
They just forgot about him
In this next clip Alex salute
That's the short sets for sign
And then of course makes it about himself
Grotto
Brave died
Hellboy
The coward Taste of death
Okay
I'll tell you
Again they are bringing us
Free books to read about it
Grandpa about it when they were alive
And a certain point you're just like well
Alright
Sleeves up here
Nobody should be offensive rebound against you
Used
Neutral coming for long time.
They're going to start
I don't understand what offensive Lee Violet even means anymore on his show
Keep your eyes peeled for people to attack you saying that we wore mode
These people like to blow up the Waco Branch Davidian course
OKC is their fault not ours
I don't understand I don't understand
These terms even mean in the way he's using them
Because I have a definition of offensively Violet night don't think
April 2nd
Is the way he's using the term does not seem the same
Silence talks about Karma
Oh he should not what goes around comes around my biggest want to find out
There's a large Bleach
Face.
Call it karma what goes around comes around going to reboot yourself
In my life
I never even wanted you bad stuff every time I did
Great life.com would because I really been pretty good person
And I really want
Weak or stupid
And you think you're going to get away get away with it
Caught my attention
To the wild
So here's here's what was missing from the broadcast
I treat people like I want to be treated
And what I don't do that I'm guilty
Okay I'll try to make it
Weak or stupid know what's weak and s******* all over people's you f****** piece of s*** New Order
And you think you're going to get away with it forever you're not going to get away with it
Damn he still bad it's just really bad at using swear
You know what else do you like
Clippers at in the video
And there's a look on his face it's like
Did it again
I don't think he's that good of a performer to be able to give that subtle look of like
Yeah
I slept in
Screamed obscenities again
Weird
Play childish
Bums me out
I feel like people should learn how to swear
For someone like myself where the potty mouth
I accept that
Yeah it's still the way I would squares is a little childish
It's a little bit
Yeah AB dub
Teach children swears but I am saying as a child you should learn them
So Alex needs to get his family
Security
But he also in a sex with his talking about them as if they're just like collateral damage
And by that I mean he literally says that their collateral.
My family so much
There's no future
If you don't make me swallow so I've taken out of my mind
The opposite of sociopath
Just my
Collateral damage
It's not like I asked for this
My family
Government make me stop what I'm doing
But I will not leave on the chessboard
The chance of them having their victory
Where they kill me
And my family and then blame me for it
So I got to have people cuz I don't
I don't have a computer
Working working working working for comes out always
Security I was already
Calling my security police agencies we done and then I saw this story on Infowars
2 hours reading all about the angles of it at all
Anytime I'm with
Really sounds Speedy to me
Yeah this is really f****** on accept
Audible
They're tossing around here he's connecting thoughts on the way there
Very scattered
I'm it's a little bored
I assume this is all because of the few articles that were like
Alex was coordinating with Trump for the 6th
Thrive
Maybe he does
Mention that a little bit
Show me pulling Eclipse it was disconnected from these other
This other story
Totally dismissive about that
To be dismissive
Yeah yeah we're going to the Capitol
That is that is true
100%
I don't I don't think that it's related
Right
But he's just
Going so hard with
Personal Chittenden the factor
Like the moment you go from
Like we need to protect our family to like
Acknowledge that your family's already dead
Is is when you turn people into a holy Army and there's just no
I mean. He's in some ways Crossing the Rubicon if you will
That's f***** up I don't disagree with you but I also have heard him say stuff
Like this in the past
Things have gotten like fairly intense
For him he will he will
Talk about like I give my family up to God
Before it just seems like
And it's rare and feels
Worse it's it definitely well in our current context
Today feels
Pretentious
More than it would have been like
The late nineties you know you didn't get the sense that everybody was kind of itching for a holy war in the late 90s
Battle over f****** say
Satanism or whatever it is you know
Yam
So Alex is spam
All of the show
Rambling about his own
Need for security and how
They story
About this Sir Christopher sign is really a warning to people like him
And you are really real narcissistic s***
Quick fix
Quick thought
Thought
Art snipers on the roof more to keep people in then
Keep people out
I'm not sure but Alex has many time starts better yet snipers on the roof of Infowars
To keep people in
I don't know
You see people in the back of your sniping on top of a roof
So that's why I've always seen it
Interesting
Anyway Alex is not covered really anything
But he has a lot of
All this incredible news to cover tonight so much
I'd so much preparation for the show today
And I haven't gotten a lot of that.
Want a message to reporter
You do not
Report
On
Clinton with the Attorney General on the tarmac
What
You do not report on this thing
That will literally never happen again and was widely reported
Every Outlet
Alright
All the New York Times journalist
Dad Washington Post
Dad
It seems like he's very desperate to excuse him not doing his job
That's what it feels like
So I was like okay well at least he's getting interest
Everybody's got more time on the show
He can get into these stories that he's failed to cover because he got caught up in this
Next
What domination in Conquest in war with us because
I'm not against nerds I don't even get into what you want
Alpha
They're not
Ugly
That's like they're covered
Anybody that they would call
In modern parlance a Chad or someone is
The enemy
Will show chin modern parlor
Crazy little scientist
What's algae
I don't I don't know if
How I feel about Alex
Talking about Chad's
Sometimes nerves bully meeting with their brains and I'm supposed to believe them with my bronze
I don't like it
I don't I don't I don't know what this is
Useful
Kuwait has spent time
On the show
I mean saying
Inferiority complexes is
Something vetted maybe Alex
What's on the phone
Channel
Wait wait for you mister pop the problem is I like some of these wimps
Pretend that they're constantly under attack in order to escalate the things that they're talking about to make themselves more interesting
He's door Kendall constantly talk about how they're so tough
Deep down inside there.
Bello super into Star Wars but they tell you that they weren't super into Star Wars
You think they rendered right
So Alex is another clip that he wants to play too but up to this guy Frank
Figliozzi
Is a former FBI
Agent
Guy in the FBI that does have a name of an F-350 gliozzi
Never heard what I was saying that he wants Congress arrested
It's not quite
Not quite
But Alex
Also wants
Congress arrested
Watch them to have trials
Okay that's import that's very nice of him now they already know the outcome
Without trial with arrest members of Congress I would stash we off the air
Everybody
The water's edge
McDonald's
What they've done yes
I would want without a trial cuz that's something I kept my kid
Rules
Jerks they always get rid of chivalry
That was get rid of the rules
One step ahead
Then there
Just in my wheelhouse that point
My wheelhouse people like me
I don't want
More
I don't want that
Like a pig in slop on start
Bhuban like asleep
Am I really feel sorry for the staff
Because I looked at every possible exit from this
It does not end well for them
I don't know I don't know the difference between this and being like
We have cells in every city
Totally
Basically how a terrorist makes threat of a terrorist with a f****** mask on going
We will Grill your soldiers.
F*** off with your trial b*******
How dare you tell me that you just upload files
Come was anything other than the one that I have for rent
But the trial is important
Silly
Also I love the idea that he's like Mitch McConnell should go to prison
Except when he's acting in line with what Trump wants
As long as he's doing that I was aboard him staying in office when I will
Defend him
Also deserve to go to prison
You know what really shocked me they had a Mitch McConnell story I recently they had the gall
To ask Mitch
McConnell if he would see the Supreme Court just
By biting intro yeah I saw that
Do you think McConnell
I said
Yes
A nice cuz I did see this story and I thought it was like
What a waste of everyone's time
What a waste
List of everyone
Outrageous course he wasn't going to do that in 2024
Frank figliozzi
I think his interpretation of it is a little bit off
This is such a criminal statement
I publicly on the hill that what happened on January 6th as domestic Terror
What have we learned
From our experience with International terrorism
In order to add nothing
Resting
Operatives is merely a speedball
Not a roadblock
In order to grow really tackle terrorism in this line.
You've got to attack and dismantle
The command-and-control element of a terrorist group
And on football
Take it back to the beginning
I know this is painful
We've got to attack
Let me chill
Shutdown
The Brain Trust if the Republicans
Pedophile seats for kids are open the borders and
Philosophical
I don't
Know if that's the one I would I would have taken away from the
But I have some problems with what I figure they were saying
Just from a different angle
Certainly the way that we have carried out a war on terror around the world is a good model
How we would approach the best
Flawed I can't think of anybody I want dealing with domestic
State terrorism less than everyone who has dealt with every type of terrorism
Concept is not busy
I think there's a lot of dangers when you start
Trying to apply
The way that we have as a country
Behave
These RV International terrorism
I am trying to apply that to domestic
Issues of terrorism
I think they'd tell you run into a lot of issues and I hope I would hope that we
Choose a different way.
Brooks if there's anything that we know happened it's that whenever our soldiers trying to deal with International terrorism
To those places they viewed everybody as a possible combat and then that's what I want them to bring back home right possibilities
Everyone you live with is a combat
It's not good and I would argue with
Figliozzi on that on that tack
I would also
I would also say that there is something to be said for the other point
But he's making though
You're disconnected from
That's why it is that everybody who got into the capitol on the 6th
Isn't necessarily going
Cause the
Kind of changed that you would hope to write
Prosecutorial Eeyore from disruption of
What causes
That's not be approached
That you want to take there's a broader Spectrum
Of love and end
And things that you would want to do
Yeah
I do agree with that
I just don't agree with
His
His comparison between International terrorism
Domestic terrorism
And I also agree with you that what lessons have we learned nothing
Nothing also Frank figliozzi has not been in the FBI's enter 2012
He does not speak for any organization in any official capacity
That is what I was looking
Looking for
So
I just
I think that Alex is interpretation that this is silly
It's just the same thing that sadist hypersensitivity that you see in the right
You know like when Biden says that
The main Terror threat in the United
Midstates comes in the form of white supremacist groups
The metallics and all of his friends reported Biden said that white people are the bigger
Just threaten the country
It's just the same game being played here
Hummingbird
To act like that
That obviously if there's anything that we've learned from the way that the right is
Behaved whenever there's even the slightest
Threat to
Their ability to act with a
Computer date
It's to go ape
And clearly that's the best strategy cuz nobody's been able to do anything about it
Yeah it is
It does gum up the works really does
Like you said he has a lot of big news to cover
What a big stuff
Sure got this clip of Frank figliozzi
The fix yours is
Problem
And this is
Just
I have no idea
I have no idea why this
You please a video of someone coming out as a trans
Man oh boy
People clap
Yeah
And I don't know why he's mad at
Play crate all the people who were working in their life
Brainwashed by leftist
Behavior
Manipulation
Squeal and squawk and scream
Because this person is declared themselves something else instead
Celebration of transhumanism
And there's a weird social worker in the Press like
It just goes on and on here it is
So these are the Lost helpless people
The system is now in total control off
I don't understand
What Alex is going off of
Other than
There's a person speak
Looking to a group who support them then
Affirm and validate them
I don't get how he can
Take this and be like hahaha this person has been
Been tricked into doing
Or whatever it is
The only way he can do that is by
Complete invalidation of
The existing
That's really the only way you arrived at that conclusion is that everybody
It is being
No I I was kind of Blown Away by
You know like I stay away from
From that world so much but
My
Family is
Like
Told me about some
Super Christian literature written by pastors and s*** that are like
Here's why
People think they're boys
Zora
Not like
This is Eva
Possible
Blanket rejection of the
The possibility
And
Your like Society has failed
So I mean
I had no idea really how deep that
Believe what I thought they'd at least we're like
Oh they're human
You know like it's it's just
Mind-boggling
The sorts of things that Alex is taking his time with
And Manny gets to the end of the
It's towards the end of the show and realizes
Haven't done my job
The great Owen Shroyer coming to hook two hours of live radio / TV and I'm in
I got the time
Reporter that exposed
Call FEI being under control the Deep state
Yeah yeah
I kind of wasted the first hour of the show so
I'm going to do the actual job on another show and maybe probably won't
Yeah I am supposed to do
And interrupt him and
Keep him from doing that very same what I'm going to be soft
Sandwich
A all-time little respect for this
I understand that I was like who cares I'm still on air
This is your show
This is your two-hour block
You can't just
Co-op someone else's show
Have you liked all that we're going to do the real stuff
I'm just kind of felt I'm yelling about bulshit here
I tried to get you to pay for my family's Blackwater guards
Power Rangers
It is
Just dumb
It is very out I would like to get mad at him when he's doing his job
Get mad at him when it seems like he's
He's on his
Olden time
Yeah yeah
I do prefer
Feeling like we are actually responding to something
Deserve a mutual professionalism
So Alex
Racist
Forget to hear at the end of the show
Can't close without it
Nope
So
I don't even know how to set this up
It's just outrageous
Barry group killing black people and
Dumping them down a drug dealer neighborhood
Gangster rap
Tells you all day how much they love black people and how they're just so sweet
Are you drive down the road almost all the Billboards are black people for every corporation
And all the big TV ads are black
The global of corporations are
Putting a black
Face
On everything they do
Is it all black people
You got to be nice to them
Camouflage
Can't have people paying you got to be.
You are going to then
Your operations and say black people are doing this
Anderson conscious level
If you hate the government you hate
Corporation
The UN
You hate all this
What are you do
Oh God holy
Shitz racism as always
Is everybody else's fault
I was blown away by
DeSoto
Articulation of how Alex sees the world
Yeah wow BLM gave us NWA 40 years ago
I would guess that Alex is using some sort of selection bias about all the Billboards are black people
Babies could be
Maybe you getting mad cuz he sees some black people there in
Because that's different to me I notice it's so now I assume that it is going to 100% the opposite direction
You're all of the instances of the things that don't make me mad
Because seeing black people in ads makes me mad
I am a child I am a child I think like a child and I have no higher order thinking
Skills whatsoever
Yeah
And misses
Is a bit much
So again
Why does racism happened Dan
It's because the government and corporations put a black face on things nothing to do with I don't know
Several hundred years or f******
Let's be honest
Several thousand years
Of massive races of nope nope nope nope
It's cuz the corporations in the government
Now
That's why
That's why white people are so racist
Commercial everybody knows it everybody knows it
Commercial kiss commercial
It's because one time I saw a black person eat McDonald's with a smile on TV and now I'm
I don't tell you I'm not loving it
This is this is a bit of a leader
Two story about this recent shooting
In Austin
There was a concert
And there was a shooting there and
Alex
Have some stuff to say about it
We love God or we love Satan
Are we a dumbass says you're the one exist
PS4 God of your dumbass
And of course
Ha
There's a great example of this
Most I would like an example
Are pain relief
So
Hispanic Hispanic
Black on black
I want to do
It's white on white
Who the Hell's Angels in the
And the
Good they were fighting
California
The Mongols
So
That's how it works so when I hear about nightclub shot up
In Miami no say what was about so I looked it up it's a black
Nightclub
I bet
Sure enough it was two rival gang
But about what color they work it's the reality of
I hear some
Right-wing square dance going on in the middle of Alabama had a shooting at Uncle that must be some
White
Here's what I'm getting at
Story is so huge
Because it's not about
Protecting black
It's about the media the control Corp
Romania
Being able to set the precedent
That whenever they want
Hi.
Austin
Star Wars
Pacific Democrats got way worse now
They'll be a serious
Divorce
I could get a house that a real place
2nd Street all that area
Call and 12th
No it didn't
It happened on 2nd Colorado Cuz I saw it
I heard the gunshots
So that's why this is so dangerous
So you got a
Hip-hop concert
Going on
Who do you think's going to be at that
Water people
Wild
Mass shooting in Austin
Texas leave 13 wounded
Can you imagine
That shot into a crowd of mixed
People
Yes I can't matter why you did it then say it was white supremacy
Well I guess what he's saying that at the end is like if circumstances were different people would cover it differently
Sure
Okay
Sub argument
White supremacist never kill anybody
That's out
Main argument that he is burying
Yeah this is this is weird
This is weird I don't know how Alex
Has evidence of crimes that were committed
Being placed elsewhere in the city
I don't know what like I'm
I love to imagine Alex just in like
You know a duster
Old-timey
Detective from Noir going out there on
On the 2nd and Colorado
I know they're going to say this is at least off that I know it
There's a guy wearing a press badge in is it in his hat just walking around
The only thing Alex has in common with like those sort of Noir detective is a pension
A booze
The only thing yes,
And yeah
I think
I think that this is also
A bit scattered
In terms of
Thinking there's a lot of stuff going all over the place
When he was in an apartment he knew the two crimes happened to differ
Some places than they said they were
Also all these various shooting
What's going on here is that he believes that the media is trying to cover up
The
Notion that the shooter in this Austin
Suitcase was a black
He's going to talk about this year
Disagree with his point entirely
Amy Fox Carey that press conference every other channel didn't
The Austin american-statesman
One further
They said
Firestone police have only released a vague description
The suspect shooter
As of Saturday morning
Gothenburg State including the option
By the way
Smart
In perpetrating stereotypes
Released
We will update
Airport
Picked up my check today hour ago
Why is that so important
Why is that so
Because
Color somebody yes
But they're driving what they're dressed like
To stop them and find them
So does editor's note that Alex is reading from the Statesman
I found it and it's in the article about the shooter's arrest
At the point of the article's publication to Vegas
Description of the shooter is no longer really that important for pup the public safety angle that Alex is talking about
The newspaper does not have identifying information released to them because the suspect is a juvenile
Just really simple explanations for you know all of this stuff that Alex is
Claiming is so confusing
And it comes from the very Source material that Alex is going off of
But it's more important
Constraints do quite Sapphira
Couldn't agree
Yeah I was going to say it's
It's
Very I don't know if I've ever heard of white dude describe why what
What he's doing is not racist without being incredibly racist about
That is a phenomenon that Alex falls victim
Yeah
Cuz it seems like if you heard it you know like the best deal white person can probably do is be like Hey listen
I was raised racist in a racist ass country
I got blind spots I'm doing my best
Please tell me when I'm being racist cuz I'm sure I will be
My bad I'll learn
Not Alex
No
No no different approach to it
That's why I don't I don't know why I feel like this
This whole display at the end of the show is Real gross
Hey
Why didn't you get to the news
That's a good question or was that a big
Story or what
At the end of the show right is he going out to
Throwing it to Owen
Gets to one of the big headlines that he didn't
This is huge
News if true
Which I don't think
Elusive defense
Department admits major Defector has been there for over a year provide evidence of Chinese military
Orchestrated the creation of the covid-19
Analyse the bio-weapon an important day is so cute
Do you not want you to know this
You don't want people to know it
Theoretically confirmation of everything he's ever said it's theoretically biggest news ever
The Chinese military's released a bioweapon that is
Killed millions of people
Okay
You have two hours
Astoria
Me about me for the first two hours
So
So that's how he answers and
I think I think you're all I ever get all does does MASH with like
Who he is as a
Self
Totally
It's intense
It's trying to incite people towards violence or sex transphobic it's races
Its side
Stupid
It's a yeah it's a real Murderers Row
Constantly
Self-critical of
I haven't got to the stuff that
Haven't done any
But it's about
Now
It is it is like a
Perpetual
Child
Who has not done the
The book report
It is a weight is a show that is entirely around what if
You just gave that kid
3 hours today
To try and distract himself away from revealing
He didn't do the work
Yeah it's almost a really interesting bluffing
Improv exercise
Getaway it kind of is
If it wasn't so destructive and dangerous it might be the greatest 27-year login Harold
It's just a nonce
Stop Alex does sing sometimes it could be a Herald
Bananas
Anyway
Jordan bookbag
Indira
But until then we have website
Brother on Facebook
Are your bail funded within your area about people
People doing
But until then I'm new I'm Leo and bcx Clark I'm Daryl rundus
Robots