Damn important swetik
I have great respect for its knowledge B
Knowledge fight
Fight.com
The altar of Selene and Doug little bit about
Alex Jones
Jordan
What's up
Today is
Thanks to some folks
I'd like
Are we just over the weekend we recorded a little guest appearance of God awful movies
And also I forgot to mention this
At the end of last week episode that I recorded
The podcast called your music saved us came out
Listing for having me on
Words come out we talked about Five Iron Frenzy peep that I really really like
So when I was younger and I still really like
That's a lot of people should go check that out there on iTunes or what have you
Little bit of fun
Alex Jones related
Could be good from time
Appetite announcement
Type news
We will be doing you leave
Finale
Episode 8 of the six-episode series gadzia blizzard
I will be doing it live at 9 p.m. at the Lincoln Lodge in Chicago
That's where we'll be doing it it's going on
It's all coming together and a very short. Of time and hopefully I will finish writing it by the time
Hopefully there'll be people can get tickets put out or something
Whatever it's okay it's available fun although I am a little bit
Weary
We'll see
The first time being out in public
I forgot
A little bit in public but not like a
Live performance
That's a little bit
A little bit weird
You can get back to it man
Baby we'll see we'll see
Effect of this announcement is that there isn't going to
To be new episodes of your goddamn wizard
July 1st we will not be doing any more episodes of that so
Look for juvenile to eat out the link and we'll put it up and you can catch up on the old episode
Hoorah
Some people have asked just to make
It's clear more public like one
Why all of it's done
You are going to release it as an audio video now
I finished up and didn't
To be edited nystrom's everybody needs
To get me their individual audio which some have been very very good with the private conversation
Today we're going to be talking about
About
An emergency broadcast
But Alex did on Saturday June 19th 2020
Emergency episode
That Alex did
And
I was glad that he did an emergency episode because
I was struggling I was riding water if you were thinking about
Covering his present a nonsense
And then is emergency broadcast happen
And something about you mental went down okay
Something that we have been waiting for for a while haven't
Some b*******
Night some b*******
I thought it was something I've been excited about happen
Before you drive me to take a little moment to say thank you and welcome in
Congratulations on the birth of his first child
This is Santa
By Ryan
We're just a Riley is a policy wonk
But you're much Ryan and on behalf of Riley
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
Cool disco George
Thank you so much
VSCO George
I'm a policy wonk
Lake very much DJ's house mouse a little bit of a shorter policy
Because
Jimmy someone life is giving someone death
You can say that
Life is death
You could
Joel had a birthday thing out to someone is also shouting something into Subway and
Giving life exact
Last week
Tammy reached out wanted to wish happy birthday happy birthday happy birthday
How you doing out there hope you have a happy birthday
Something will hit me up and I wanted us to wish you Happy Birthday
Was named Anita is that right yeah yeah
Great trivia
Text John Heather birthday
Teresa says hey happy birthday Teresa
Dusty. Dusty Springfield
Jesse Rhodes
No he's passed okay
Still alive as evidenced by their birthday
I was reached out and wanted us to wish you Happy Birthday
Happy birthday.
Very special from from Michael
This is a happy birthday
Technocrat shout-out
Combo
Situation
Not Borat
Bora Bora
Ali G AKA spills with a z
Happy birthday and you are at
Money off that heroin
Is freakishly large
Giving life is giving death happy birthday to all
Jordan we're going to start this thing off
Against
Alex's goes for an unconventional approach
On this emergency
It's an emergency broadcast yeah and he's going to open it with something other than screaming
This is an emerging
Yeah okay
And I'm interested if I was gauging
From the title of this video
Emergency is that
The January 6th
Storming of the capital was a false flag
That does not sound like much of an emergency
I don't know
Qualifies as an emergency that requires another broadcast in an emergency
You should be aware of something really fast
And this is standard Infowars lower at this point
Really just like
Listening
Aquino
Or is in on it now cuz I was really thinking about is
It seems really weird on first glance that Alex is doing that
Broadcast about like
6 being falsely
Makes some sense I mean if you really think about it
Publicly available information
Alex seems like he's on pretty solid footing legal
Lee speaking
Next to the storming of the capitol
It seems like something is getting him a lot of attention
Rightly is trending on Twitter because people are like
They found this video of him being like
Drop told me to lead a March I'll manno in like
I think it's probably something really good to lean into for him
Attention there's a lot of possibility for
Claiming the people are misrepresenting him totally
I think it's probably
As long as he doesn't end up
Defaming anybody
In the process like
Probably a good thing to do
There is a dog outside this attention he knows that he needs to
Rihanna
Trial of that crew
And I love the boom operator The Spinners 7 days
How's your beer tomorrow for Sunday show
Want to thank them
And I'm going to hit this big news
Now I'm going to go right to these gas button
Doing is afoot Dorothy and I'm going to do it right now
Because I've got
A bunch of reporters
And I got
Operation
Cuz I want to watch it I got things I want to do
And I can't do without your support so
This coming Monday morning
This big sale
High quality
Organic
Vitamin D3
Jay starts off with a very explicit blog
Start
The emergency broadcast
With an ad
Overworked
Which seems like a hem problem shua seems like you can probably hire more staff
Apitherapy cutback Orcutt
Right right
But because these people are working
Seven-days-a-week needs to hire more people and therefore you need be to Alvord
To work
Whatever
Seidel soundtrue
Write it sometime
Georgia laughing
Sometimes
Short when you're a person with a lot of energy
People think you're on cocaine
And then we've got the three new products by new
The new ones
It finally came in with a supply chain breakdown
That were discounted your habituated discounts and I get it
And I made it that way it's my fault
But now we have yes
On sale
Going to sell out
Cuz you don't buy horses on sale
And then stuff sold out for 6-8 months that's okay
Are you complaining to me about you three back and stock the tryout of your immune system your body your energy or let me know
Everything
Stock 60% off
Andre Shepard Elementary point
Open krill oil 40% off
And of course about her selenium for the muscle
All infowarsstore.com right there
That's lightning in a bottle
That's how we fund
This operation
Add
You've always that's why you got so much energy
Totally down exhausted
10 hours
I went the bathroom ticket
The passion I walked out
Security guard
The song
What drugs
Are you on cocaine I said I would
I said I'm in a war
How'd you go from looking completely exhausted
Play ready to kill somebody for their bathroom
Google Play
About out of bed
Okay
That's what I'm on
It's a lot for
Call John
John Paul Jones
I really appreciate
For keeping us in the fight
And I need you to take
Now
Now I'll give you everything I've got
Because it submit to these people death
I need a word of mouth
And your prayers and your support
Please just give me money at 9 I will fake
Mood swing that was
That was pathetic
That was really pathetic
Yeah
That was really bad is
How artificial that like mood
Swearing is
And if it's not about
To see a doctor
The 2nd
What he's talkin about not being on cocaine
He describes going
Going to a bathroom
Almost entirely yeah
You know what was crazy all those
Stories about Studio 50
T4 back in the day you know people would always go into the bathroom and they just scream into the mirror they were like
I'm not somebody who's done a lot of cocaine in my life
But I'm not going to say that I never had
But I will say that I don't think I've ever done it outside a bathroom
I think we can include laundry room
Hard to say
Or just at
I don't know this is just everything is so fake about
The passionate
Yeah that's
What's that is really that's really bad acting
But you'll continue doing that
As Faithfully as long as you pay
Please give him some
Yeah I don't like being chastised
For taking advantage of his discounts and then him being like
Sell it at full price anymore
Like what what you do tell me
Don't tell me that
I put things on sale too much and now people are used to it and they know that I just put everything on sale in a week if it's not on sale now
Never buy anything out of real but normal price so I have to
By the Gods
F*** you
Is Reese's cups on f****** 2 for $3 if you're not going to buy a model 141 99 day
Employee at Walgreens
Like after Easter like a day after
Easter their jobs just up to everybody
Oh now you want a drag
So Alex gets to some of the news
Alright let me show you these articles are going these yet
The big revolver article
Global Aquatics
That's a good thing and weed
Literally for Sade
And pushed it together
3 weeks ago
Enemy
Freedom
White House unveils new strategy to counter the message
Laser focus on violin
The same thing Brennan
The Economist perverts
What
Why doesn't Bill strategy to combat domestic extremism it's everywhere it's their whole operation
So first of all this article isn't on Revolver
Revolver isn't so much a new site as much as it is an attempt to make a new Drudge Report now that the Trump campaign
Is turned on drugs
It's just a bunch of Link
Gangsta clickbait headlines
For the most part
The actual article that Alex is talking about here in this clip
On the hill
The Articles not some kind of a bombshell that has the globalist
Running Scared
Discussion about how the plans that have been floated by Biden
Administration
Possibly good ideas but also there's some serious blinds
Princeton's here's a quote that's included in that art
Administration is rightly focused on addressing white supremacy
Violence but its strategy includes none of the Civil Rights
Liberty safeguards
The rights groups and
Communities of color have long sought
That's a criticism of the bidens plan that was put out in a statement
By the ACLU
A group that Alex believes is high-level global
It seems like it's the ACLU shouldn't be
You getting in the mix trying to sow doubt about the globalist plans
If they're on board of the globalist plans but look man I'm not a 30 Dimension chess player whatever the f***
Yeah if I was a 30 dementia
Open chess player I would say that Alex is opposition to this
This makes more sense
Or no nevermind
It doesn't make any sense
Whatsoever
See that new plan dividing put out as a realtor
What are the pillars
The plan is to quote
Confront long-term contributors to domestic Terror
In that section they say quote
The US government will also work to find ways to counter the polarisation office
Fueled by disinformation misinformation it dangerous
Conspiracy theories online
Supporting an information environment that Fosters
Healthy democratic
I'm not sure that I believe they're capable of achieving that goal but if I were Alex
I would recognize that this
Looks like a situation where
You might not get to fly completely under the radar movie
Home forward
Not be good for him
Fighting some qualms with the plan but it's
Not really a specific
General
And critiquing the general plan is good for
For conversation and for fostering better ideas
Show me the best ideas possible but
So I don't think it's where the actual
Fights are going to happen
Yeah I mean I think the only thing about any of those plans is always got to
Boiled down to
Hey guys
Guys
Tell me honestly
When there's a Republican president or even
This President will this be primarily used to hurt leftist Act
And the answer is ninety-nine percent of the time
So let's let's calm down on our
Plans real
So I asked
False flag
And you know what other people have false flag before
Now we know from listening to 2003
Line
Conversation will come up
It'll be Alex will use every day in 2003
Slightly different in the pretzel
Distance the old Soros
Onstage.
I just at the old KGB would do it a Hitler launch WWII
I'm about to Stage attacks
And some of the corrupt
Declining systems do huh
Strangers phrasing is a little little different
Collapsing countries that did this
You know like it seems weird that they would be one very obvious
18 years
Changes to
So Alec
Let's gets to what he's planning to do for the beginning of this virgin
The report
I'm going to have this over
Interview idea
On Friday
One of the main lawyers
Depending people
Arrest of the capitol
This is a memory from Friday and then I've got interview that some wife
Not enough
Security Menlo from set
From
January 6th
When he witnessed what he saw what
Ended up telling the story
Little while after it unfolded
Family vacation Utah but
Demi logos through
Exactly what really
What happened
So
Play like 20 seconds of like a lawyer death
How to make
Details of it
I'm at a very long conversation he had with his
Security guard
Easier to get
Get him on a family vacation
He interviewed his
Security
Also Rob do is there a man
Went to his food supplier the my Patriot Supply Warehouse
Family vacation with the security guard going to your
Disaster Foods
Supplier
Kind of but suck
That's just a business trip that's not even to work
Kaisha Norway I'm not having a great time
Utah I mean Salt Lake City
He's nice sure
We don't need to listen to anything of the security guard cuz it's honestly just
Exactly what they've said
Pretty much all along
You know hey we were asked
Ask to leave this
March to the Capitol because there was another
Stage
I'm going to be set up there there was going to be another rally
And as far as I can tell
That makes sense it seems like everyone
Action
Make sense
It's based on that
Trump was onstage saying that he was going to March down with them they're going to have another rally to give strength to the
Spying needing Republican yep
Sure
Is that I don't know
Incredibly boring
Contradict any of the things that I think are actually the problem
It's just kind of
It's on the side
Defense
Is
I mean 88 Rings true just because it's the only party
The story that they have told
Exactly the same way
Over and over and over again you know like every other part of it that's a false flag in there all that stuff
In the first week after it happen
Andrew the story of like we were
Instigating we were walk
Always the same always the same the video of Alex
Very clearly being like don't do this
Yeah
It checks out and it does follow his behavior
What I was watching
The live coverage on the day
The way that Harrison
Smith was celebrating it
And I realized it was going down
Yeah everything change
Recovery John Infowars
Because
Alex was in the field he didn't have
Control over what Harrison was doing
Subscript and realized
And Alex
There's also video of a one of his employees
Police to let Alex
Get on like a megaphone tool
Play calm the crowd down
First of all the other cop absolutely.
And even best-case scenario he gets up there like I everybody stop and then they don't
It's a no-win situation but
They have of their actions
The near behavior on that day
Unless somebody can provide actual evidence
Of them
Doing that
Is cover for what they're doing behind the scenes right unless that can be demonstrated then
I just
I don't know I don't think the story
Have Alex's actual actions that day are as important
As the app
The story
A conversation about
How these narrative
Propelled
Ibiza
I think the thing that bothers me most about
People
Being like this s***
Is that
Ultimately York
Giving Alex
Too much
Credit
Yeah you're amazing like Darth Vader
He is too much of a
Howard
To ever even come close to doing something like that
Whenever you give him that kind of like
I'm sure part of the reason that he wants
To do this is just so we can be like seed looking how
Look at how strong people think I am much people think I could be running everything
If only I weren't so much of a giant f****** cow
Coward
I mean just a stumblebum
The courage
Do something
Like that would be surprised
Speaking of the business though
Alex toys playing at
I think it was after the security guard interview
And I just thought this was really fun
The globalist want all of us to be
Refrigerator
What's the price today
So yeah Alex's family has a ritual of making juice
Powder
Man
I just think it's fun to lie call it a ritual
Carrabba's
Achilles all off it so in order to fight back my family
To swim at Kool-Aid pretty regularly
Sunny D commercials were like no sunny day we're going to make our own stuff
I just think that's fun
Appraising is fun
Start having some gas
That's no fun
What a crazy thing to be involved with Nick
Nowell and it's really gotten
Breaking new report here from
Revolver I think
It's blown the lid
Wide open on the
Fire situation and hopefully given some clarity about what really went on on that
They write the baby baby big
And I kind of miss poker earlier
Revolver is primarily just a link aggregator like drudge but they do actually post some of their own blog
I think what happened earlier is
Is that Alex reference the link they posted
To this whole article
Pinpoint for the day was supposed to be about this
His blog
BigNik brings up gotcha
Gotcha this is just a really overwritten
Plea for people to insist that the only relevant variable in
What terms of January 6th
Is whether or not law
Enforcement head moles
Inside the keepers
I'm a 3%
That's the only thing that matters Aunt if law enforcement did
Then the whole
Thing has to be a sham
One paragraph really stood out to me as dumb
If it turns out
The federal government
FBI army counterintelligence or similar agency
Undercover agents are confidential informants embedded in any of the groups
Involved in January 6th
The federal intelligence agencies failing to warn of the potential for violence
Looks less like an innocent mistake
And more like something
Sinister
This is part of a discussion
About how the
Excuse that has been used to explain the storming
That there was an intelligence failure
But if that's what was used but if there were any informal
Pedro
And that's
Suspicious
Thing that they're using that excuse now
Sure
Any idea how these types
The groups operate knows that this sentiment is
Just so dumb
Groups like The Oath Keepers specifically follow it leaderless resistance
Since models
The confidential informants
Can cause
One group inside the organization might have no idea what another group is up to and its best
If it stays that way
There are Central figures in these organizations like Stewart Road
For The Oath Keepers are Enrique tarrio for
For the proud boys
Know what each other Splinter groups is up
They set up their group
Like a disconnect
Good franchises
Because then it's
It's harder to disrupt
There's a classic strategy that the extreme right-wing
Has been using for a long time
Specifically songs tonight
Call terrorist conversations
Right-wing circle's out
Being there there model
495 mean they wanted to create an insurgent
Attitude and they have 100% done
Even Alex's show operates kind of this way
Like when Millie Weaver put out Shadow gay
It was pretty clear that Alex had no idea what she was doing with her time
Use pain
Sing for the documentary book
She didn't know what her point was who she was
Was talking to he know anything
She as is the case with most of his employees
Are tasked with
Knowing what they're supposed
To do an operating in Waze where Alex has
Plausible deniability to not be personally implicated if something they do is a f******
Renovations would definitively prove that the government at all the information about the group
Plant is just dumb
And I refuse to believe that whoever wrote this piece doesn't know that
This is just sort of like a dip
It's argument it's not even a real
It's kind of ridiculous
I tried to read this piece and it basically just boils down to how there are people who are left anonymous
In charging documents
For The Oath Keepers
The Oath Keepers who were indicted in
In the storming there's names that are not listed
Person-to-person three
Answer like as one of these to be forever.
It's full of like
Enticing speculation but if
Literally proved
It's just
States
Did the very long
Article 2 prove
So then it's not even they're not even
Making the argument that it's
The false flag so much is it entrapment
Yeah yeah but it means liking me whatever you want now
Words have no meaning in this world not anymore
So
The idea is that these FBI agents inside these groups
Who are now these are
Name people in the
The charging document
RS
They're all FBI agent I guess what
Alex knows who they are
We'll just leave it at that
We know the names of the FBI agents Direction in the building
Dodgers informant
What are they going to do Nick
In the next few weeks and months when that's all Rollies
Tommy said yeah we were in there
Again
Watch this space
For Alex to announce
Vanilla wow
I can't do this not to happen
His parade if you just started Maven FBI
Show me princesses
Incredibly annoying
I find him
Insufferable
He's not talking about being banned from
I'm flying at this point
But he is talking about have this
January
Unravel
When did unravel
Everything
Comes with it
It's like that sweater song
Weezer
Izakaya
Don't know if you want to destroy my sweater
I do not know this thread as I walk away
I don't really love them that much either but
I know references
If you want to destroy the globalist
Sweater you pull the thread of January 6th while they walk away
Unravel it all of this
Is the myth of January
Travel the myth
The 20
20 election the b in Lansing
That will unravel the mess up
Call Bad Waitress
The pretext to use the mail in ballots
How to rig the election
It's going on travel all the event
Sabine tire patch
All of this was commentating in the overthrow of Donald Trump by the Deep state
It was all just a big colorevolution in this
This is one of those things that is going to
If this comes apart
Will unravel a
Series
Huge mass
Supplies
So Nick Fuentes has a unified conspiracy about everything that's happened over the last
Year-and-a-half or so
Cool
Yeah
So when this goes nowhere
F****** b******* back to complain about the airline
I just
Can't stand it said I don't know he'll just Retreat to like demographic
Birth rate
Nonsense
He tried really yelling into his face
Another
But just like
No
I know her and over and over and over again Banshee like power with your yelling
I think that the smug prick like
Resume
Throughout his
High School
Career and
Years he's been out of high school
I'm getting a lot of people
Why so easy to hate
Only gets
Easier
Global temperature going to organize group
Into thinking it's okay to literally
Can override
Marshall Plan I can do it according
Glasurit according to race they admit that
They doing and you're right that's what's happening in South Africa that is what hap
Happened in WoW iblade formerly Rhodesia
This is what's happening all across the
The world
Little people are just going to have to make a really tough
Decision which is
What are we willing to
To do to save our Western Civilization we were given this great inheritance
Okay okay
So I love
When someone like a Nick Fuentes is like I'm not racist at all
And then he starts talking about Western Heritage
And great
Inheritance and how it was squandered
And the two examples that he has of the squandering of it or South Africa and f******
What are those things have in common
Ikea
Bastard
Believe
That white people were forced
To endure the Injustice of
Continuing 20 90% of South Africa
I feel I feel like those
Sort of moments are real indications that like
He is trolling
Like whenever he's like I'm not racist
Hi this is just I just care about America like he
He's nosy
He's talking with you
It's not right
Rhodesia memes white nationalist
The end just being like
Hey here's how Rhodesia should have gone we keep it is
White nationalist
I mean there's no other way of putting it
We believe we should be able to go into a country
Take all of their land by force and violence and then
And force them to work for us
For nothing
Yeah yeah
Nick Fuentes
Nick Fuentes on the show until I get some of this
Priorities
I got kind of tired of Nick
They weren't really talking about much
Just about how like
The extreme-right is so strong
Overthrow the
And capital all of this
But they're going to pull that
Fred and all is going to collapse
Systems.
The right
Is going to win that doesn't sound
Untrue Alex also has his lawyer bar
I can listen to any of that
Does who gives a s*** at work
Nope
Jealous
Bored meme
Try stand-up also talks to Pete Santilli
Who's the guy we heard a couple times on the show
Zeii heard this
And I was like well you are disqualified sir
My dad when I got out of the Marine Corps
He gave me a sit-down he was telling me how powerful
The Nazi
You know a socialist movement was
And he in fact and my dad is not a white supremacist
It was so powerful
Voted for Hitler was the people
Allowed Hitler to rise to power
Because of the trinkets that they offer out you know
Of course free please for everyone
Going for everyone
He said it was so powerful
But it was the people that actually
Are propelled
Hitler to power
Firstly Hitler was very specifically not
Favor of universal programs are advocating for free
Forever for Ariens but not forever one baby later
This is an absolute fabrication and lie about how Hitler came to power
It doesn't matter that this has nothing to do with reality this story doesn't exist
To convey history and help people understand the world better
The reason the story exists
Siddhivinayak social welfare programs
Pure and simple
Hitler did
Become Chancellor because he and the Nazis offered everyone trinca
Peter run for president against Hindenburg in 1932 and he got 36.8% of the vote
And afterwards he was appointed Chancellor as part of an attempt to create a coalition government
The Nazi movement
I'm getting Outta control but more importantly
Make sure that the
Communist state
Far away from Power
By the time by the time of the reichstag fire in the enabling act the only people in government or opposing Hitler with a left-leaning
Social Democrats
And probably Communists would have but they weren't in the Race Tech anymore
Nope Pizza instantly tells the story because he wants everyone listening to think that if you have a politician talking about expanding Medicare social
Security the next thing they're going to do a set of concentration
Caps
It's total b******* he's just against
Public spending that
Like it it's just
The desperate attempt to
Toyota make that argument
Based on nothing
Dan just wanted to subtlest things in it is that 99%
What number I'm just like
It is
Easy
And it is right
To demonize
Everyone
That disagrees with
99% of them will be
Be taken in by
Freak it
They're not even people smart enough to wake up but can't
Blankets are all they need so it's fine too
Obliterate them
The app the app
And this emergency report
Really
Was about 1
Sing for me
I don't care about Alex's ideas
Babe
Texas V
I don't care about no
Nicoletta
I don't care about Barnes and I don't care about Pete Santilli
I care about one thing
Mike down
Well he's one of our most popular guest and he is back
Vitamin doctor
Steve pieczenik
A best-selling author
You're which you are as you were saying last week we were talking over the show you're like man I've been me
Missing Steve I've been needing a big Swig but I also was the same. Like I feel Steve coming back
Like it's just
It's around the corner
Even when Alex and him had the falling out
About his
Diculous prediction
Yeah around the election
I still was like alright he's on time-out he'll be back
He'll be back
Be VIs
Use back so
As far as the bat
You made the soft Landing into Owens
He started coming back on the War Room a little bit and then that was the way to get there the toe in the water
But the thing that I find really interesting about that clip is that Alex is like
By popular demand
Steve pieczenik is
And they let him go on over and show is like a Hey listen you can prove you can stay on
On Target
On the show
Then we'll give you that if it's not to humiliate
Call Mary
Kid gloves
He's too popular to get rid of completely but I hate him so much
I need I got to say that is their word guess
That we had like we had gas
There's guess we had it was really really popular but also with
The complete dick
Yeah I was using us
And lying to everybody
I wouldn't care how popular they were I did not beyond my show ever
No
And if we had people being like now you got to have a bag on the show be like
We will not be having him back on the show end of conversation you should stop listening
Goodbye
What integrity
He's just one of the heroes of our time tip of the
The sphere undoubtedly
So Alex let's do you speak
Cosby sand
This to me is Steve
Declaring
Victory over April Wars
That's always a pleasure italics to always remember you and I are the
The focus of the rage
The last
Particularly when you have what we call
Liberal sashes
This is what you
You beginning to see with
50 Biden Administration with Susan Rice with Obama
Fightnews
Running any
He had three aneurysms he's cognitively
Impaired
They at there's a demand for you
That's the real issue
Stay at
We are in the midst of the millet
Bateriku
I said it to you year-and-a-half ago we
We know exactly who's corrupt we know where the Corruptions
Is it touring with
What you saying
Is the federal government
Trying to hold on
So not by popular demand
Alex has to have Steve back on its
Steve is a budget underwater Martinelli
He lost
The bat
Still going for it he's going to mold reality in such a way as to win
What an a******
What a
Better that mean I can totally understand why Alex hates him
Like on a deep level
Because that is
A narcissistic psychopath
Fighting a narcissistic psychopath
And losing your reality to his that's brutal
Like its
It's to narcissist
6 Psychopaths
But one is way better
Manipulate
He's a pro
He's a real Pro
You might have
Some doubts about Watermark valid
Plenty of Fish
Is it bad out to go to bed
Weimar
Computers we Marquita
Ink Engraving
And it was a
Fisticated Engraving
This was a sting operation run by many of our military intelligence civilian intelligence
Key select
Good. People who knew that we were having
Corrupt government and they would
Tired of War
And we went on your show to Bass
Pronounce that
And make that an ounce
Completed American public
Because you be
Came
The OneSource
That was reliable valid
And
Portent
To our institutions
I am going to stay a bunch of s*** directly to your face
That you know is not true at that told me about truth and then I'm going to
Compliment you for it at the end
Compliment as a way of buttering up compliment as the knife deep into your gut
And then twisted around
Because in order to stand up for your dignity
Disagreeing
Bulshit I'm saying you would have to disagree with
The compliment
So evil the evil
That's just so good so Steve's got another predict
Dictionary
Said I don't think this is a good one
Basically saying that the Democrats want
Exist Within
A few months
That'll be, what you're saying is
Be a ruption
Parties that will no longer exist within the
A few more months
A sound
If they going to be
Successful
But they're not at all
So give them
Steve I'll give him till the end of the year
By the beginning of 2022
Yeah
Well once again
Be encouraged
I mean Allstate I would say I have to
I'll stop it about
Halfway through the campaign
You know what I'm saying whenever the Democratic Congressman or is still are going back
For their next House of Representatives
Senators are up for
Pasta Pasta few months
I'm trying to be as generous as possible
Given 6 months is pretty generous
You know you got at least see if the Democrats campaign before their eradicated
Completely
I don't know what that dissolve Super Bowls
So Alex has this big talk
Hats that Trump has come out and he said we're going to win back Congress and
Were you expecting you know like
No that's probably true
Well Alex ask Steve
Did Trump say that
And I
What about the amazing statement
Buy Trump two weeks ago where he said we're going to win the house we're going to win the Senate
We're gonna win the presidency a lot sooner than you think
Play something Joe Biden would be gone and now you see prestigious
Democrat doctor saying he needs to step down
Election fraud
And the proof coming out
What in the body language
Garland and of others
They look like deer-in-the-headlights so can you
Layout for Russ what you thought was going to happen
On January 6th versus WhatsApp
What's then now unfolding right now and what
What do you think Trump script
Open statement
What trumps date
That was simply to say that
Shein
The fact that we in the military
Alien intelligence
Community
Select
At certain number of people
Go to be involved in what we call the sting operation where we put
Put watermarks
Encrypted
Code on the machines
The voting machines and all the
The ballots
So Trump is it on
That is so good
That is so good Alex gave him that subtle like
What youth
Haha
Tell us what you think
No
As though they were going to be different
Nope same b*******
Giving some signal to like
Hey you know that it turns out you
Maybe we're right about all that stuff maybe I was wrong
The submittal
Yep
Yep Alex got tricked by Daddy Again
What is it one of the things that might come into your mind is like okay
Is there a big sting
Obviously do the guilty party
Somebody's got to be in prison
Secret indictments
Wildin what we call the sting operation where we
We put water marks
Encrypted
Code on the machines
The voting machines and all the ballot
In the process we understood that they would be a lot of people implicated
Indicted
Convicted
And sent not to
The prisons in America but you are prisons
Guantanamo
We built a whole new
Facility a year ago using new wiring not in the old Wantagh nobody in the mountains
Guantanamo
Many of these people have
I've been sent down without any notice
Say anybody else
What secretly
Guantanamo now so this is just you and I
There's a bunch of white-collar bureaucrats
They forced to go to a mountain stronghold prison in Guantanamo probably the Pope
Probably the real Pope yeah
That's probably true
Oh man Beth
I don't want to go to that prison
No terrible
Steve gets talking about January
6in essentially what it is is a Pelosi Merrick Garland
False flag or something
It's not
But what's more important
Listen to Steve spin his wheels while trying to describe Merrick Garland
I really want you to pay attention to this
Cuz it's it's
Outrageous
And this is once again Nancy Pelosi
Thea green
They have this
Best type of false flag
Using another one of our wash
Washington-based
Quote attorney generals
Garlin
It's a full of Garland went to
To a school called Andover
He was a little prep
At school for
Wasp family
In New York then went to Yale
And then went to
Prestigious Law Firm where he only earned a $9000000
Alex in1
Case and is worth it
Between about
16 million
224 million
Never having served our country
Never having built a business
Navigate having
Take a rest like you and I
Show Dave Chappelle Garland I'm sorry it's
The Jewish guy
It's the other guy
No
The Jewish guy who also went ironically the Harvard
Also went to Harvard undergraduate Harvard.
Law School
Steve got the memorized bio for Merrick Garland wrong
I was going to say that doesn't
Sound right at all
He's just he's like a little bit too little information that he's memorized about drugs
What's the throw up
But you also noticed that like the things that he's her hinges on her like he's a wasp
He's a Jewish guy
Weird yep yep you got to know what people are before you can
Build an opinion about
That makes perfect sense
Interview with Steve Nash
Boy
And scary like if he actually believes things that he saying
He is
Gyorgy
With butterfly Nets
You should be in a Hannibal Lecter mask
100%
Talking about how the Democrats are done
What was the GOP
Does Trump has now created a new better party
His reasoning for this is strange
What you're seeing is the end of Apple
Political
Party the so-called Democrats
Turn we will end the Republican
Party as we know it
Has Trump came in
As a
Black Sheep
In the Dynamics
Politics
He was
So far out
We the people understood that we needed a businessman to
Come in and no longer politician
Has Vladimir Putin
Open set it correctly when he saw a Biden or
He did she buy
Fighting is nothing more than a political hack
Spin around
43 years
What I need is a man who has character personality
And is able to take the risk
Flu Putin
Taken before in running Russia
So yeah apparently
Fighting the bad president cuz Putin doesn't like
You know it's
Really weird
In
2021 to listen to Just out-and-out fascist
Talk
Fascist lie you know where you're like
I don't remember people being so openly fascist back in the day
Maybe I just wasn't paying attention but as a kid I don't remember like
Just hearing all these fascist talk all the fascist time I do feel like this is more over than even I remember
Yeah I mean
This even on
I'm putting that aside think about how old
Wake this conversation about
An ongoing military coup to overthrow the
The government is
Steven
Almost there like gleefully just
Discussing like
This point we're basically
Cleaning out what I call
The lavage
21 this is a
Political lavage
Of America both Republicans
And dammit
Live in France
A political advisor
I'm using a
Turn that I created
To make ohmygosh the American people understand swear basically cleaning out
The system
An alternative term for that was a
Cool or regime change
When I came on your show and I explained that I had the right
Just say publicly
That we were in the middle
Beginning of a military coup which was
Sting operation
I wasn't
Coming to the Forefront in saying something that I wasn't allowed to
Can say he's got a lavage going on
Or at least you don't know what
What Steve's
Speed up political term is a coup
I was going to say cool but I said a different word to make everybody think that I'm super smart but instead I
Just made up a term
Which makes me look like a complete ass
Yeah I mean
You know he's got an ongoing military coup on his handle that seems like a lot
That seems like a lot
But
Steve's team
Very deep
They're everywhere
It does seem like that
Dude
This is a big revelation
If true which is not
This is a huge deal
We in the minute we outside the administrator
Patient some of them are famous
Generals
He's head of the
Bored
But the reason we
Jumped over Amazon
Which we wanted a cloud of Civilian clown the large
Intern we placed in a 4-star General nakasone third-generation Eastside
France he was in cyber command
We put it into
The White House so what we did
To take over this Administration
And allow it
To play out
In a car in the wrong
Corruption
And they are on
Miscreant
Away
Because we knew that everything they were about
Would be either ignorant corrupt
I am dangerous
United
States
GG
Won't even talk to buy there any ministration they won't even talk to him like
They're scared like they know it's a trap
Steve has a little team and they've taken over Amazon
The government
It's amazing
This is
That's a big swing that's a big swing you know you come to see you for a big swing and
We overthrew Amazon first not the swing I was
Expecting
The cloud that biggest company in the world thing we stole it
We commandeered it
Bezos
Get out of here
If Alex
Took that seriously for a f******
He would have to conceive
Fix all that s*** that I complain about Amazon all the time
Weren't you guys doing anything right
Your military-owned now or whatever nonsense
Weather things
Steve wants you to know though is like
Okay so like
There's there appear to be some Frosty
Between Biden
Doesn't seem like things are
Maybe as amicable
Not great
But what
Spine
Because Steve talk
The China
Key Point here was the GG
Ping understood that
Biden was not in control
I have sent him a message
Approval of my people a year-and-a-half ago
That this was not relevant
Shine at we would remain remain
Friends of China
The same time we sent
A message
The Modi of India
To say we are your friends
As well
Wow I feel like Steve is born volved now than he was in the past
Oh yeah I feel like now Steve has gone from being like I'm part of an operation
Intubated
I'm running this s***
I think I think it's an escalation that comes with knowing that you're untouchable challenge
F*** with you at all so why not go ahead and create yourself as like
This Arch supervillains
Perspective
And he's using we and you think he's
He's talking about his team but part of me is like we're at the Royal we level of him describing himself I know
At this point you can get away with whatever you want you got Alex basically
Dead to rights
On everything
You can just
He's not going to put up a fight about anything you know where David Knight
If you want to show for a few months and now he's
Forced to have you back
You get away with whatever you want why not just Legend build
Yeah
Jesus this is so big I control all the levers of power in the world
I told
Call China
Put up with Biden it's cool I like there's that big lie. That he's operating on with Alex
It's too big
This is just too big
Notice there that he
Key pronounce digipen
Yes that makes me think of that's why I look
Probably from talking
Steve too much
Anybody whoever speaks to Steve toxic
Sure
He was talking about how like they've taken over Amazon
They also took over the government
They took over the Biden Administration essentially in order to let it
Play out its corrupt way
And this is because they wanted to show the world that this is all Coronavirus
Bright
Yeah let it happen
If Trump had one
Right
Do you know maybe get a little bit done
What if Trump loses
It shows how corrupt everything is
Even bored. You can write
I know you think you're playing the long game but there's a bad
8 brilliant
Alright well we'll see and that's all Trump is trying to do man
Trump was just trying to show the world that things weren't good that doesn't sound
What happens if
You answer cell
Destruction
And that's what
Washington was all about
And that's what Trump was trying to show the
People and those of us who've worked
In Washington but no longer live there
Trying to show the America
People how incompetent
Disgrace
People politicians were the Mitt Romney
A Mormon
From Utah
Governor of Massachusetts
Here's what I'm asking you
Is
It wasn't
A blind hog
Integra twice-a-day broken clock is right twice a day
I love hearing all this confidence it's wonderful Freddie Okie
They're now saying
There a secret
Watermarks
3D holograms on the ballots and now I see certified expert
Alex
Oh my are you loser don't you dare tell me that Alex could help over
Throw the f***
Can capital
Turn into a little baby dog
Could actually help
Afaik
Overthrow the government
Yeah. In the War of the Worlds radio play
Yeah this is
This is a little silly
Susie wants you to know that the
This is really actually a good thing
What's going on
Community it's all getting cleanse
He's all worried for his own safety it's
Qliq
This is far more of a
Cleansing
Then anybody realize
UB harm
No
Are they dangerous
Could be
Will they hurt you
No
Wheeling Obama
Imma come back and write another
Not sensible
The book yes
That's what they
I gave them
A dying in
What happened in the
Is Hollywood went under
I mean I guess he does own Amazon Prime
My show 18 years ago still haven't got to find those interviews for vacuuming dead right so I get what you're saying
I got to find those
BookFinder
I would like you to find those at
I love that self-interview of like
Are they going to hurt you know
Are they dangerous Maybe
Brother got hurt you know
Is Obama going to write another dumb book
You bet
Wow
What and infuriating way of talk
Talking to me
You a******
Az88 put it out on Netflix a dying answer
Doing all right
Or not I don't care why does that happen
Look
You think that's an annoying way for someone to speak
Do I
Is it going to continue
Probably
Am I worried
I would say that you need to show some
Goddamn respect
Cuz this man
Single-handedly
They took down the Soviet Union
Years ago on your show and maybe the
Before I was on you
I was involved
In the takedown of the Soviet
Not me just
Groupon
Involve both CIA Miller
We took it down
Without any
Are kinetic action
What happened
Is we made a little mistake
Instead of picking up
We decided in that was my
They have somebody who is rational open-minded
And we
Gorbachev
What Barbershop is on me guys
I cannot believe how magnanimous he is being with admitting guilt for
Nothing he could not have been less involved in
Look in the physical Universe we inhabit anything that he is ever done that has Zero Effect
Me and my boys we took down the Soviet Union
And then.
We put in gorbachov and
Should have gone with a dictator right from the start
V for something that you absolutely did not do disarmament
Try that it work the next time whenever they're like hey
You have been doing it at listen I'm really sorry I I thought it would be a good idea to overthrow the key
Human resources
Is department and I installed the current head and that's on me that's on me right now they're like what
Do you have a part of the hiring process what's happening
Little do you know
I've been pulling the strings on all capitalist Enterprises since the beginning of time
Have you ever seen Undercover Boss and then
You take your beard off
I invented the chair
My God
Do you know before I came along there wasn't
Photosynthesis
Can't
Steve pieczenik man
That dude
There's there's a disease there but I don't
Don't know which what
Or how bad it is but it's bad
What is it like
I feel this way about Alex to is it there will never be another
No will be another Alex
Because he came along at this
QuickTime why in the in the era of Public Access TV
Right-wing radio becoming ascendant
Career was taking a taking a upward
And then he had this established career
The point when numidia was really becoming pricing and social media and so he had some
Credibility
That other people lack
When when information
Became so
Easily disseminate
Assure
Steve pieczenik
Is a guy who's nuts
He is
One of the most fun Liars
I think I've ever heard
But he also
Did work
It's a state park
Wild
He was involved in Aldo Morrow's death
These are things
Like they're just real they did happen
All these other like dicks
To come around people are unlike Project Camelot just making up every
Beat making up a lot
Oh yeah
He also has that
Veneer of credibility that comes from what he was doing in the 70s
Play like
Nothing will ever be able to replicate
If you want to put
Together good credibility in this space you need one
Tiny acorn
Truth about you
And that will unlock your you're okay
Tree of b*******
Yeah but you got to have the acorn and then if you want to be like Steve you've got to be
Naturally gifted
It's spinning these Yarns
Glamorizing
In fact
Or have a rare delusional disorder that allows you to think of these things as though they weren't rude
Emeryville confidently
Steve Wynn
Be able to work without a light
Like
I've heard him on other shows like he was on Costa
Coast a couple times
It's not the same
Like you mean that gimme that Alex straight man that you can just
Steamroller
Yeah you need to be able to flatter someone into giving you so much Anakin leash that
Eventually have gone
Until it is gone
Whitlock
Doctor Steve can go out-of-pocket we're going to keep them close
We're going to keep him on the leash and then all the sudden Alex is wearing that dog collar like I don't know what
That is exactly what happened
So
Back-to-back to the narrative
Steve took down the Soviet Union
Accidentally put in Barbershop
Decision
I think ultimately he should be you should still be proud of that decision Putin wasn't ready
Batman that's the real
Probably true if you hadn't revealed the corruption in the system
You never would have gotten Putin in the first place see
Playing out all over again history Rhymes Dan
Interesting Lee
Steve is the kind of guy who likes
It's clean up his own mess
Gorbachev wasn't good idea
Gorbachev
It's not strong enough
Control
Time zones
What time the Soviet Union was 14 times
So we pick
Re-cook
Eureka
Instructed
Mistake and I
I picked the man
Warfarin drop of the head of the KGB named Vladimir
Putin
Putin knows he was big
He was
Specifically picked
Because he was East German intelligence
Bespoke English she spoke
Germany spoke Russian
Steve handpick
Vladimir Putin
To take over for Gorbachev
The fixes mistake
Curb after you overthrew the Soviet Union
And Putin knows
Vet Steve
Britannic was the one who is behind
His rising to power
Homeboy
Hey
Alex
Just so you know
Inositol than me
Call me
Everything
Inside your entire career stats me
Guide international relations by sending a message to China or India
Everybody just waiting on my
Beckon call
Listen
If you fuc
With me there's nowhere I can't find
Find you in the North
I can find you in this cell
I can find you around the world
Time zone that's how many time zones
I can find you in
Steve never that animation
I know but it'd be more fun my character I think his is a little bit of a nice addition
I guess I mean I feel like cut wow
Steve
Steve's Menace
Is far more dry
You know like what the hurricane and he was
He was more terrifying that he didn't yell at him he was
Just like
Wow Budgetel my neighbors houses are underwater right now in
That's scary
Yeah yeah he does have that cool level-headed malevolent
What about him yeah
That's a that's a big
So what are the eclipse that we found early on
In our time doing the show was something that we kind of
Shock.
I believe it was it was the Clipper Alex talks about going on RT
And
Evening gets debrief
By Russian intelligence
Yeah
And
That was a bizarre
Clip and it's not something that we've heard a ton more
From Alex about
We're going to have to find those Steve pieczenik
From 18 years
When Alex
Talked about that
Clip about that experience
The first time we heard it
It was the story of the Russians being like you know so much
Yeah right about Alex
The story's a little different now it tells it again
Kind of different Focus
The last time I was on Russian TV
This is probably about 10 years ago
89 years ago they go listen to We got this group wants to talk to you it's just Russian men
We want you on
So I'm sitting on Skype
Big Board around there's all these guys with beards
Zaba crtv
And it's like all the big brain bugs are intelligent eggs when they're all
Lego
Tell us about pechenik
How do you know pieczenik
What do you know about pieczenik what do you think of Putin and pechenik
And they were like I'm not an intelligence operative I'm a talk show host
But definitely
They've been sent by Putin asked about you that
I just said I don't use a bathroom at him on
DeTour for us intelligence agencies
That's a true story
Something like it's a border like
15 dude
Did you see on TV these like the brain bugs you know like the
Like totally
Starship Trooper
That actually have
100% actually at
Just because that's all
Apple X doesn't mean it didn't totally happen What would happen if pieczenik
Why is
Single-handedly responsible for
USSR Russian history
Over the last
Yeah it does seem like if he was the one who both overthrew the Soviet Union
Installed multiple prime ministers
And so on and so forth
I don't even think that the party guys unless it was a splinter group it would have to be that's the only reason they would be
We asking about Steve right right
It wouldn't because she would get the phone call liquid
To find out
Dirt on Steve so they can take him out
Because he's too powerful
Where did that
That would also be likely
Alex got interviewed on Russian
TV and like
He was asking
The question that sounded weird
Baby cam
Or
He went on a show
That did a pre-interview
Steve pieczenik
Easy right
So
Steve
The bidens going to be gone
Soon
Although the way he talks
Facts about it
A little bit
Biden will no longer be
Lincoln will not
The Secretary of
Estate you will not have all these American Jewish guys never serve
Country 25 of them remain in
Power
At the same time Trump will have to have a whole new
Backups is
The people he had
Jared Kushner
Has to go
The Trump has two
It seems
The real strange
I mean not strange at all but no that's
Vicious anti-semitism
He seems very strongly focused on defining people by
Their religion or heritage
Not good
They're very easy visual ways to disqualify people as humans in C4 Jetix world
Yikes knock
So
Steve
Are interviews about to come to an end
Got to ask
You seen the bidens going to go down
Give me a time for
Give me a time frame Steve make me another bet
Closing to come back again soon
Temperature in Kampala
Waitressing work there
Enclosing know what is the time frame on Biden
I will not
Was not active
Let's just say in time
With patience
You will see this Evolution that way
With talking about evolution
Okay
Alright Ali
Convince yourself alright I admit I got the math wrong the end
The world is not on December 21st 2021 it's going to be
December 21st
So it'll be there this is so awesome
And so frustrating
And so funny
I can't I can't imagine how a little dignity
One must have
To allow Steve back on
It's a date
Embarrassing to level that I would have thought Alex would be above
He is such a
He go to
Steve
That was like
The around the election that was
Acceptable
No way
I let him back on the show
It's going to look so bad
Doesn't care
ATV back
He's backing out is making excuses why he's actually right
I mean I heard it in his voice
I heard that
There is a certain day
Respondents in his voice that I felt like was was definitely there a little bit of disappoint
Maybe a little bit of like
Just a small
Smid of what have I become
I feel I felt a small like when he was like
Yeah that's what they're talkin about I feel small
Describing and I'm not sure they relate to this at artificial world of
Bulshit you are so right
You're so right
I'm trying to be a human
I even thinks
Strategically from the world
The b******* this
Is a bad decision
Because all you're going to do is anybody who like
Alex
And thought he was onto something
Is going to look at him as
Somebody who is kowtowing
To this guy who was
Definitively wrong
Beta bad about it
The Pope's been arrested
Scrape so that's just going to hurt Alex is Imogen the audio
Fantasize
The best you're going to do is you're going
Attract
Use fans to you
AeroCare
Steve cell supplements to it's not like you're going to get his business wow
Yeah this is sad
And for somebody who's
Self-images so
Ifucking matcha
To really go into this interview and just
Take a little
Kiss on the chin
A little pat on the head and I'll see you next time
Is brutal
Yeah that's brutal so
Flipside
I'm happy
Because I am too I like being Alex
Who won the show
It's true
Guy is just like
If he comes up with
The baddest chick
Yeah now there's a f****** big head cutout of Steve directly
Behind Alex that you look up at every time you see Steve's face in his little tendrils yet his presence is back on the show
Appreciate it
Hopefully this
Make me more interested in
Seeing
The fun
Thriller novel that
Steve's writing goes what
The next chapter
How do you escalated from
I am the reason
Who owns Russia
I know
Play politics
Yeah he's going to have to ask you later till offworld omigod imagine disclosure happy
Sprite
The government is like we've been in contact with aliens
Steve's going to have to up his game totally
He knows all these alien is the one who negotiated the original treaties with the alien
Have to go down.
I would love it
I want the scores for the happen now just
Because of that.
Come on government we need
Steve's work here
Alright
So yours is
Ikenberry your b******* about hiding secrets
Secondary to what bulshit Steve's going to make up
Yeah you are a roadblock in terms of our
Interesting improvisational storytelling that we need to Steve tape agency
Santa's here
So that was the emergency report
I don't think
Watching it I got convinced
What's that
There was an emergency
Or that's
January 6th
The false flag
I was convinced the things I already knew 1 Alex's a spineless worm
Agreed
A Great Hero
Is an anti-semitic a lunatic
Nick
Fuentes is a racist assholes
Alex's nothing else
To do on Saturday
Come in and maybe try and sell a few pills
The kids that weekend
Got to move a little product
But until then
We have website website
It's not right.
We are in front of that knowledge go to bed Jordan
Please find a local charity or Bellefonte in your area to help out people doing God's work
Dzx Clark
I installed
I can't remember what the name of the king from Skyrim was
I put that guy on Tower
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work