Important
I have great respect for its knowledge B
Knowledge fight
What's fight.com
Looks around
Put solder of sleep
Heard it I was going to let it go
You know now that you brought it up
What is your
Brightspot
For today
I've been meaning to get to for wild there been
Difficulties
I'll just code for my printer hasn't
Don't work too hard
I've been wanting
To do this again we did it
Gave her some
The folks sent them out
I wanted to do another run of these eating some new design themed around the cult of saline
I would like
Text to announce officially that we're going to be doing another run
Of these buttons
For Folk
Books and
Here's how it's going to work cuz I got
Completely screwed up all of my inbox and I am not interested in that
New email address that is specifically for this
You do not have to be someone who gives to the show you do not have to be anything it just anybody if you would send your email
Career dress
I will
That is the one limitation on
And you have to send me an address
Send button to
And then I
Take care of everything else and you will have a button sent to you
The email address is
KS
Business
At gmail.com
And that's spelled KS
Viz
Mess
Kaff business
At gmail.com
If you send an address to that be a little bit of
Alright I'm going to obviously
Got to make these up
Could be a little bit of a delay but we will get this into work
Get some envelopes
It's with your addresses automatic
Get these button sent that to a very excited I really I know the last time we did this
One of the things that I discovered as I was really really enjoying
The process of making meditation up button
Stick to the crafting of it's in the the sort of
The repetitive
Sure sure
Go to junk
Zen and the Art of button-maker I feel like
Replace now to there's a lot of
Precautions that we took the last time around true with
Wearing gloves while making the butt feels a little bit
Chill out a little bit about a nice gift
Steps are very excited about that and if you all want to
Send it to my address is with husband
His gloves
Will be on and they will be coated with anthrax
So it's a little bit of a different problem at an Elvis impersonator and then he had some ideas
What are you doing with your Xbox
It's in the early stages
It's not a super bright spot but after a year of writing nothing but
Mean things
To Taylor Swift and stories about wizard
I've started a new project
It's much larger hopefully it'll be about the size of the book I put out last year
You're so that sucks
People will definitely not
Here's the inspiration excited
Absolutely
I wish you the best
That's meat
So Jordan today we have an episode to go over there it's a little bit of a challenge
It was it was
It was a tough challenge for me and here's what happen
Sojourn
Studio at the beginning of this
He was in New York
I mean I think you're in New York
Maybe ya should have people on the border sea I think that a lot
Two people probably
That's the first thing their mind would go to
Is that you probably going to deal with some sort of illegal issue with the Attorney General of New York
Juliet threatens on are multiple times and of course he had the season 2
First of the product that he was selling
And I think
There is
A possibility that that's the case
Suspiciously went to Connecticut
Recently if I got why'd you go there
It's possible but also he was going there to do a POC
He went on that flagrant-2 podcast he was drunk last time
Well yeah he was so drunk last time that I don't even care to cover it
Maybe he's going there for some legal issue but then also maybe he's just doing this podcast
And so that was a possibility
Maybe we cover that apple
Simultaneously
Kill Tony
Play podcast
Had Alex as a guest
Tony hinch
Which Cliff noted Asian slur purveyor
Taking that towards his career
Yes actually
Tony's career
I mean I don't think it'll matter cuz the cult of
Rogan Enterprises
Has he
Ensconced
Under their umbrella
Tony Hinchcliffe is a writer guy
Comedian
Who he probably wrote for the w.w.
Suction
He's want to Rogan's buddies he's one of the ones who decided to go to Austin
Because
Their bread is buttered
In a very specific
Any more people don't like me
This is where I'm welcome
My career revolves around Joe Rogan Joe Rogan's going to Texas I am too
That's her like that
No it's not I think it's people understanding where their cottages
History about the specifics of my career revolves around Joe Rogan
You can do worse
So
Kill Tony is a podcast that he does
That grew out of this open mic
Restore was called potluck night
Or something something like that I just decided like let's find a way to monetize this
Ties that open mic
Of the business decisions for an open mic that was probably the best I've ever heard sure
Listen to a number of episodes of it cuz it was a morbid Curiosity on my part
I always back not just
Just recently put
Builder the show is basically
Yeah yeah Tony
You got
Is producer Brian Redban
And then you got to guess
A celebrity comedian gas
And they just act like hot shyt while he does a minute of
Material
Which is
Impossible to tell
That's all you need
That's all you need to know if you've
Got it around school and generally
Baby
Overly encouraging of some
Things and overly mean to anybody who doesn't fit in
They're like
They're box
Just dumb
I wanted to cover it kind of
Because I felt like
Alright
This could be fun
This could be a fun thing to do in episode about
But it's so much of the episode is like
About other people stand upset or an open mic stand upset I don't want to cover that
She wasn't doing a minute
Yes
He would
Until like I guess I have this drop
I want some of that Joe Rogan weed
So there's that okay alright
What
Beautiful vagina
Have a nice night
I guess we will the part where where Alex
Smell some girls feet
Who was in the audience School her up on stage cuz one of the
Open my cruise has a foot fetish and then they get somebody with a foot to smiling
I don't I don't know
Yeah that's not an episode
Great I'm loving
Every part of this
Right up my alley I'm sure Alex had some insight
Full criticisms for the comedians
There's one guy who heads
Alex is like
I drugged but that was a very cerebral set
Okay
There is some insightful.
I can actually
Surprisingly at least at the beginning
He was a little boy
Bit more thoughtful
Red Band
Contempt if you
It's very difficult for me because
Ditto
Critiquing some of the stuff within the comedy
Free space
Is always going
Going to be
Walking in Vallejo
There's not like
People will just hide behind be like it's comedy I'm just joking
Whatever
Verstappen
I don't know it is
I was listening to the kill Tony
And I thought
Iowa lot of complaints
About this
But who cares
Yeah I kind of
Feel like maybe
Listening and criticizing a podcast
That's about listening and criticizing comedian
Isabella
Comedian
Everyone's
Yeah it is
It felt felt like challenging
They
Possible
To make it worth listening
Well maybe we'll do a little bit of
About that
Episode of flagrant 2
Why not
This is a little bit longer this is a conversational piece
Alex
Was so drunk on the first time that I've
Just didn't want to cover it was a little bit better
But I
Panda listening to it it's
So annoying
And
I think that the
Actually make a couple of pretty decent joke
Oh okay
I can see a little bit of life
That's what you like that's
If you like bro Eng
Comedy show or whatever people are talking
Talking about
Hey I had a threesome last week or whatever like what
You know
This being up your alley
It was insufferable for my
Purposes
Alex takes his shirt off at one point
Early
Call early
Early what are the hosts
What is the
Jimmy Seibert
Kreischer on kill Tony one of the host calls him Bert Kreischer okay well there we go and then the other
Weather host
It makes the joke
Did you say Burke crisis
Actor
Which is not bad
It's not bad word play
It's not bad words like
Funny
Because Alex ruined a bunch of people's lives
These guys are just jokes
To Alex
Know whenever you leave awake of misery and destruction what you should
Do with that is like
Make it a funny little bit that you can
Pawn off of Tulare
I can't believe you pulled it off
Like look
It's obviously only funny because you're talking about something monstrous that the person next to you did
Right all right but that said fine word play
Anyway I
I really struggled
HW Bush
Alright let's all have a fun time making a friendly conversation with George W bush
Exactly very funny
You are let me that your pictures are dumb
So we have a couple things that I'm going to talk about towards the end of the epi
Episode from the flagrant podcast
Because I think there were
It'll look as much as
These guys are just bullshiting and having
Fun and
Whatever I don't care
I don't I don't care
But there are a couple of salient points that I think
Could be brought up
And
Whatever we'll talk about that the other day episode
Thankfully
Something happened
Breaking news
And I Alex had to weigh in on it
About today
Special report that Alex put out
Last night
Recording this Wednesday
Evening all right
So this is a a lie
Is it an emergency report on something that was reported roughly a year ago that we're finally talking about now.
Actually breaking news
We're going to get to this before we do lunch
Oh that's a good idea
Chavez Chavez thank you so much
Next
Thank you Alex has been Alias your sweet sweet music
Ewok
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks Chris
Next dimer this is Paul give dancing money thank you so much you are not a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
I don't ignore that message
Paul
Okay
Going out to
I don't know how to say this may be dicey
Tycho brahe
Dieco Bross Bros
Freakishly large
Thank you so much thank you very much
Now Jordan yes sir
Can't upload it
Jimmy someone life is giving someone death
You can say that
Life is death
You could
The first stuff you don't got a birthday this week so happy birthday Tiana
Laura and Lisa reach that wanted to wish Ron a happy birthday happy birthday happy birthday
Yeah
Cooper
Got a birthday coming up Julie
Liam says happy birthday happy birthday
They also would like to wish a happy 21st anniversary
Me to Heather and fill up also known as Captain
An awesome
Okay
Together
Also I checked into this
Do you know they have the Hallmark recommend
Yearly anniversary gift
Sure sure they got the
The paper anniversary
21st
I checked into this just to be sure
Brass or something is it one of those
It's brass but it's
It specifically like
Ketubah
It's that kind of blessed recommends 21st tuba anniversary
4th anniversary is woodwind
I know it's
Steamed gift surrounding the idea of
Fire
So okay that's enough
Interesting
So let's go with I mean I have a tattoo of a firebenders symbol so we
We've got that you can get yourself some
Firebending tattoos
Rooster I think that's a great idea talk to Zuko
Get that out so you know what I'm saying
Black dragon Queen Christi
Our old friend Christy
Happy birthday coming up this weekend
And also
In the last month
End of the end of May
Christy
Robin Monty celebrated their 30th anniversary
What in God's name did you get like a pair of timpani for that quick what kind of are we just doing orchestral
30th anniversary is office
Sword desk decor
That's a lie that's actually the 41st
Anniversary
The 41st
So you're telling me that I'm somewhere at
Conservatively in my 7
And you're getting me some office
Equipment
So in the evening Hallmarks world you work till
Absolutely tirement
No
Office equipment
41st anniversary
30th is apparently Pearl
From what this is saying I would rather have
End your marriage at 30
Why would you make it all the way to the office equipment
Laughter
Well then everyday I celebrate by 39th anniversary
53rd anniversary
Long time
Marriage
40th anniversary is Ruby
Right
Okay three what is this of the Decades are precious
Intervening years
Is is
I guess
At random
Pulled out of a hat
3/50 is gold
60th is diamond
60th is Diamond 40th is Ruby what
What's 53
I got to go with
Marine creature
Plastic
Classic
So you telling me that I'm at 90 years old and I'm getting Saran wrap for my anniversary if you're lucky
Alright
If someone's following the Hallmark recommendation
Happy anniversary Christian happy birthday
Also Alex would like to remind everyone that we were born dead
Life
Is
So Jordan
The big news
Is that was breaking yesterday is that
The John McAfee is no more
18 he was found deceased
In a prison cell in Spain
I'm sure or do you have just
The gotten word that he would be
Extradited to the United States
Two-Face
No charges
Yeah I think if I were being extradited from Spanish prison to United States prison I be like nah
I'm out it's it's hard to say but
It's not here Alex
John McAfee did not
Kill himself
Public statements Amazon Twitter
Is early as just last week
He said I will never
Suicide in prison
I have been murdered by the US government
I'm going to listen to a man I knew and respected
Suicide
With no corners or no inquest
This thing stinks to high heaven
That's a that's a good cool to open
Special report that he put out
Even if we
Take as absolute gospel fact that McAfee said he would never kill himself
He was the definition of an unhinged
Drugged-out lunatic who said complete
Bulshit
Essentially for a living never imagined that a man so respected is John McAfee would perhaps
Send out a dumb idea very quickly before we thought it through
A couple of my favorite things that he said there were complete nonsense he said that he had nothing to do with his name
Neighbor in Belize is murder
Or that time that he said that if Bitcoin wasn't trading at
Get $500,000 within 3 years from July 7th
2017 he would quote
Eat his own dick on National Television
Never do that
Too late now
Some of his more recent work includes that time that he tried to create a
Publicity stunt hoax
Were you pretended to have been arrested for refusing
Don't wear a mask
Wearing a lace thong on his face instead
He's brilliant McAfee and his wife publicly claimed he'd been arrested in Norway but the picture
Posted as evidence of this were from
The Augsburg Airport
Witches in Germany
The Oxford police told the media quote there has never been an arrest
Explain that McAfee tried to enter Germany but decided not to when he was told that he would have to quarantine
And he's created a bunch of bulshit on social media right
Thanks for the libertarian nomination
For the presidential race or
The very overt and transparent history of involvement in pump
Dump cryptocurrency scam sure
That was one of the cases that McAfee was facing
Along with tax evasion twitch
But the US was looking
Extradited back to
Spain
He was found at a Court ruled that he could be extra
Aphroditus denied
Midstates
Actually really
MattyB was 75 years old news facing essentially the rest of his life in prison for his fraud and tax crimes
Which absolutely would be convicted for
Since there's a video that he released of himself where he can
Confesses
Might be tough to refuse
Don't pay taxes for a year or so
I have not filed
Every right tell the IRS
Define
That's going to be tough
You know what bums me out
What bums me out
So much
Is that
We know for a fact
That if you are rich you literally can get away with not paying taxes
You know what I'm saying like we just
Scott a New York Times
Report sure
About how you don't have to pay taxes if you're rich
And the only way that you can f****** if your riches if you're just an
A****** like this
It's the only way
One way
Some people are too defiant
William loopholes we've created for rich people do not have to do that
Principle of the thing then fine you're going to die in a Spanish prison so I don't know what to tell you
This is on you
It's basically like the the ceiling metaphorically with his taxes is coming down
There's an open door
It's like you want to go through that door
Open it's over
But there's nothing on the other side
There's no punishment Sonata perhaps you'll just go out to the loophole
I will not
I will be crushed by this roof okay
Alright man if he died
From suicide but if that does end up being with determination that experts end up making I'm not going to be
I wanted to get a sense of how the media was covering
That's so I sampled some of the largest Outlet
It's that that you have work we're covering
The story
The headline and CNN was John McAfee found dead in Spanish prison after his ex
Extradition to the United
What states was approved
The article doesn't say that there's a known cause of death at all
McAfee was found dead in his cell in a prison near Barcelona on Wednesday around 1 p.m. Easter and Annabelle
Medical examiner is on the scene
A spokeswoman for the
Superior Court
Catalonia
Told CNN
She said the cause of death is under investigation
A statement from the Catalonia Regional government just
This department which manages prison
They're said to prison medical personnel and guards attempted
Perform life-saving
Procedures after fighting McAfee but we're
Successful
The statement said quote everything indicates
Unquote that McAfee
Could have died by Suicide
That article is eminently responsible
It doesn't jump to any
Wildly so
The BBC headline was quoted John McAfee Antivirus Creator found dead in prison
Incel
The article also doesn't provide a cause of death but does mention that same press release
Quotes
The cattle and justice department said prison Medics tried to resuscitate him but we're not
Unsuccessful
It said in a statement that quote everything indicates on quote mag
Took his own life
The New York Times story of the headline quote
John McAfee software Pioneer turn in Spanish prison
They mention the primary source statement
Quotes
The justice department for the Catalan region in Spain said that pending an investigation it was treating his death as a probable suicide
The NPR story doesn't even talk about the Catalonia Justice
Department combat
Instead just reporting quote authorities are investigating the cause of death
This article even goes out of
It's way too soft in McAfee's image
Then turn them into some kind of a
Prankster type outlaw
McAfee took pride in outwitting authorities
He once boasted about eluding police by dressing as a driven Taurus
Speedo
Another time is an angry homeless man
It's like the MPR version of this is really like
I mean these things are true Maxi did dude
Did enjoy
Creating This Outlaw On The Run image of himself
Outsmarting the police right
You know it's not wrong for mpr2
To be the the angle that they're take
I would have included more of his
Bombast
Psychotic criminal acts but
I suppose if you would have paid him but as a
Modern-day
World traveling
Catch me if you can type
Con artist
Raiders had this headline
Larger-than-life software Mogul John McAfee dies in
I'm staying by Suicide
Lawyer says
This is because this story isn't about the actual death
It's about McAfee lawyer making a statement that McAfee died by Suicide
Quote McAfee lawyer Xavier
Villa Elba
Set the anti-virus software Pioneer died by hanging as his nine-month prison brought him
Even so even though this article as saying this
The article does not say that this in fact
What was the cause of death
Only that McAfee lawyer head
Said that it was
None of these Outlets are reporting anything to fit it
Given the information that they have to go on is directly from primary source state
One from the Catalonia justice department in 14 McAfee Zone lawyer
This is responsible reporting
The facts I can't find examples of these folks rushing
And jumping the gun
The called is a suit
No I can hear every
Free editor of every major Outlet screaming we're not doing an eps
Steam this time
Alright no f*** ups
No Epstein conspiracy theory
Here's why this
Looking at the coverages
Alex is trying to rush in jump the gun on the conclusion that his death was not a
Suicide
And in order to do that he needs to make the circle
Circumstances around the coverage
Z
As suspicious as poss
Oz reporting
A fiction which is at the media's immediately and without cause declared Maccabees death a suicide
Because they're trying to cover something up
Because that
Colonel suspicion is necessary for Alex
Use the story for his own purposes
Alex is an opportunist by Nature
Any needs to use everything you can
Oregon's largest Ben
Just last week I was recovering that reporter Christopher signs death is it
Definitive
Professional X
Accusing
And his big prediction was the globalists are going to start killing people like him
Himself and Tucker
This situation with McAfee isn't there
Perfect fit but it's good enough for Alex to use
The claim that you was right
So this absolutely cannot be a suicide
Yan Infowars world
Yeah it's almost like it really doesn't matter how response
Possible the reporting of mainstream Outlets
What is Alex
This is just going to make it up on his own regard
Absolutely
There's a real danger to this kind of behavior and it's in how Alex is rhetoric has been shaped over the course of the past
Gear and even further back honest
The covid-19 Claire the globalist
The big move and something that they can't undo
This is the end game coming into reality
Which means that there's no going back
How to set that over and over in so many different construct
Victory or death
No Going Back they've crossed the Rubicon over and over and over again
Different ways and goes no going home again
Also I'm very very sorry Hamdi I apologize
But listen
My bad
The rhetoric surrounding how this is like the end the game and you know this is this is the big move
That's dangerous enough on its own
And if Alex is now going to start reporting stuff like people like McAfee dying is the globalist killing off Brave
Patriot l
What's the logical leap he's expecting his audience
To make
He constantly talks about how everyone
Is to keep list of globalist in their town and be ready
Take them out with things
Jump off
How is killing off Patriot leaders not the most
Explicit evidence that things have jumped off
So you could imagine
Weather remains to do this or not is kind of irrelevant
It's just part of the message that is audience is going to take from that
As far as I can tell all week
Can really do is hope that
The people who get that message
Aren't the type of listeners that he has would like
To take action
Yeah cuz the only message you can get is
Once they're done with all of these people they're coming
Sing for you
So you might as well stop them now before they
I'm talking about like
Steam as a murder a Hillary murder
Or whatever
The little bit different
Even because that's like
All right they're trying
To cover up their tracks right or whatever dassault
On
The Patriot
Folks
He's not like a McAfee a Libertarian anti-tax where do we actually would go on
Infowars really would
Is there ads
Is it really going to move the needle though I feel like McAfee is just going to be a blip and then everybody's going to be like yeah I'm fine
Alex needed to justify the
Previous coverage of his predictions of patriot leaders being killed
So it's very important
For that piece true he's got to sell it hard
But I don't think that at this point Alex is aware that mac and cheese
Instagram posted a big
Q right after he died which is going to complicate that's going to make it a little week
Looking to make a little bit dicey
So Alex talked a little bit about how he
He got to know
Rob McAvoy
I got a chance to get
Get to know
2012 right after his Escape
Belize and Guatemala
Larger than Life
Several times
A guy
Most definitely
American success
Antivirus
So American
Success story
5 magazine was born
England
The BBC quote I feel as much British as I do American
Wow
He founded the McAfee Associates but he also sold that 1994 and since then
It's not what I would call a glowing
Success
You know more like a cautionary Tale
Or just perhaps
An evil motherfuker wandering around
Setting weirdo I'll take that one
Sounds as a comparison
Historical comparison
30 mics
That what it what a shock
It has to do with booze
They certainly try to go retire down abolition live like a
Captain Henry Morgan was a big old pile of s***
I don't know if it's the person you want to be compared to
His later career he was employed by Jamaica
Privateers
Pirates away
From the area surrounding the island they used to call him the jamocha from Jamaica
Instead
Compliments
Jamocha
Jamoke
Never
Okay
Instead what he did is he decided to just demand money from Pirates to allow them
To come on
You got to pay me title running a protection racket
Outrageous drunk and he declared martial law twice in a two-year span because of fears of a friendship
Invasion
I wish you to be pointed out
He was accused
Collaborating
After all that
Until his death Morgantown
Free slave plantation
Chance in Spanish
Bunch of his time trying to enslave more black Jamaican
He sucked yeah yeah but you know now we venerate him for his booze
I guess that's good I would imagine that Alex knows him as a pirate on a bottle of rum
True story of Captain Morgan is high on anybody's listed
I would guess it if Alex knew some of these things could be like
Even more into heaven
Be cool man
And I would like to run my own Island
Fortress and collaborate with the French
Since the overthrow my own
I'm f****** home L Ledger
Yes it's unclear
So
Alex
Tarnish his name Alex's big
Piece of evidence that he has really too
To go on
About McAfee
And how the
Could not possibly
This got to be a murderer it's the one time he tweeted out that I would never commit suicide and if I die in a prison it's because the United States government
Sweet Talk app
Here's another one from October of last year
I am continuing
I have friends
The food is good all is well
Know that I hang myself
It will be no fault
I will not commit suicide
It's a setup
That's the first instance that I heard in this report of Alex
I don't know why you saying this is the second time I think it's probably an editing
Screw up
This queen is probably the strongest Avenue
Alex has that Max he didn't kill it
Since he said he wouldn't do that in October
I accept this as something that makes sense on its face but I also don't think a
Approve anything
John McAfee was where the most unhinged unstable people in the public eye and it isn't necessarily wise.
To take most of the things he says without a
Giant brain
Consultant
I can believe it in October he may have felt that he would never come
Commit suicide
But that was also eight months
I can change to person's mental state over the course of eight months
Particularly if they're in a foreign prison and maybe without
The drugs that they generally do
It could change your
Poinsett McAfee
History of being arrested in foreign countries
Sorby wanted in foreign countries
I'm getting away and going on the Run
When he was a person of interest in his neighbors murder in Belize he fled the country ain't got away with
More notably in 2019 he was arrested and released when you docked
Is boat in the Dominican
Who's on the run from the United
Midstates for that old text thing
Are you taking to living on his yacht I guess an international waters like some
I'm goddamn Andy Daly character
Fun
The kill time on the boat McAfee post
Did some pictures of himself with a bunch of big old gun
Is Drew the attention
The Dominican Republic authorities when he tried to Doc so he was arrested and held for four days and then
You know what I think about going on the Run
If I was running from the law
I would try also very hard
To not be
Noticed
See that would be part of my strategy of like if I had the opportunity to tweet out something
I would be like maybe people will notice this
Yes and I don't think I should do that when you're on the run it's kind of like you're in the No Flex Zone
I might even change my name
At the very least get a new Twitter handle
I'm trying to get rid of that blue checkmark doesn't serve your interests of being on the Run
To like really publicize a bunch of
Yeah I'm living out of this
No one will ever catch me pressing my Instagram followers but might be working across
Purposes of my trying to see on the Run
Maybe
John McAfee of the history of getting in trouble and then the consequences just disappear
We are so in October just after he been arrested in Spain
If you're him there's no way you think you're going to be in jail for the next
Months let alone
End of extradited to the United
Totally I'm posting that tweet
Can see that kind of a shitpost
This will be him saying like
I'll probably find a way to escape in a week
Until some actual evidence could be presented to the contrary
I see no reason to think
The simplest explanation
I'm here
Impossible
Like John Maccabees luck had run out
He's going to be returned to be 9
Midstates and he was likely going to be in prison for
4 years
He was a vagabond the world traveler a guy who flees countries and lives on boats
The prospect of long-term incarceration
Seems like exactly the thing that he would find intolerable
Yeah f*** that
There's a lot of
Remain to be answered but make
Teen murder I think
Going to be a really uphill battle for Alex
Especially if the thing is leading with his
The tweet
8 months ago
I don't know
I mean
Cuz cuz then you just get back to life
Really
Why
Why would they send it
Hit team
Yeah
You could but I mean you know
Also
Look for Mcafee McAfee has very publicly
On Twitter
Painter shoes
Said that he has a dead man switch
Yeah
Okay yes
Okay fine
That that's like okay anybody who would want to kill him
Presumably because he has some kind of information that they want covered up maybe like oh wait
If he
Ends up getting
Killed that his wife is just going to release all of these
Sure
Whatever
Yeah it's it's not
That's is all just a spy novel
Magic One
I think
I I mean
Certain extent you could just describe it as those
Destruction of one man's mind
Coincidence
I don't think it was quick
Wow this is been going on while his mind was destroyed
So not only did he tweet once
Tweeted another tie
In November of 2019 so
Before
The one in 2020 and I quote I like f****** whales
We're coming
We're going to kill yourself
We're going to Arc
Kill yourself
I am suicide myself
I didn't
I was
Check out my right arm
And there
Is again
Tattoo
With the money there in the Y
Sty
Those streets are real but also John mcatee was a delusional paranoid drug addict to promise
Adidas own dick on TV as a way to promote cryptocurrency
Probably as part of a pump-and-dump activity
This isn't compelling evidence of anything
Like these tweets
Send them getting a tattoo that says
Dollar sign
It's not
Since to Me of anything other than McAfee was unwell
And maybe those weren't turns
The phrase so much as typos and poor
Grammar
Yeah could have some I might not be so much though well done
Author Lee talents
McAfee
I would love Alex did also try to go through Mac
Hippies
Twitter
Go for it let's
Let's all start talking about whale f*****
That's what needs to be in the public eye
So Alex needed to jump in front of this really
Rite Aid to get a narrative out
Can't let the cement dry on the
This one no no no
We're told
Kitchen
Breitbart it was a heart attack before his body was even cold
Contamination
Corn
Assassination is a very real thing in America around the world
The outlets that Alex thinks are in on this
Conspiracy did not report that it was
The suicide within minute
There was very matter-of-fact coverage of the catalonian statement and then eventually Reuters reported the statement that was made by Mac
Duffy's lawyer
I strongly suspected I was just laying there within minutes it was called the
The suicide is based on random
Tweetsie saw that Sanchez most likely
We did a whole episode about the day after Andrew Breitbart died and nothing Alex is saying is real about that case either
The media didn't immediately call it a heart attack in the initial reporting that it was suspected
Had to be a heart attack
The place that came from
Linda Direct
Line that everyone was quoting
Was a press release put out by breitbart's own website
There's no
Conspiracy there
As for the coroner thing that was just a conspiracy narrative
It's based on nothing
This was about the death of Michael Cormier
A person who worked at the coroner's office
The problem is that he had nothing to do with breitbart's autopsy and the amount of arsenic had an assistant
Was so large
The one of the detectives on the case said
It'd be impossible to poison
Even some of that much arsenic without the
I'm noticing
And people were pretty
Confused by that
Backpage
Yeah
Alex can't prove the cormier's death
For the poisoning
Intentional boys
Didn't die from a heart attack
All he can do is pull it string
Real or imagined
Turn order to create a sensational story line
Fitz's purpose
What are most important aspects of this is the narrative that the media immediately caused these deaths suicides or in
Breitbart
Because that implies that there's a cover-up
If there's a cover-up
That means that there's something to cover up
And that means
But it's murder
In breitbart's case Albertsons just making up with the immediate the media immediately call the doctor
This case is doing the same thing with Mike if he's death
It's a pattern of behavior that exists not because he's responding
Real reporting
But because he's operating from a pre-existing script
Regardless of what any media Outlet published about Maccabees dad
As soon as Alex heard that he was dead he knew the angle was
That the media immediately called it a suicide told him that
The rest of this video is
Is kind of
But I mean here
Alex's is defending himself
This is known as
Corky talking about himself
He told his wife
For the cryptocurrency
His work will live on promoting libertarian ideas
What
Like
The cryptocurrency
They just want his money
He doesn't have that
Much money might have a bunch of Bitcoin or something I have no idea
The people were talking about
Multi-millionaires McAfee wasn't a multi-billion
What is the globalist to kill him for his money that's silly
Second I don't know it's not like you can
Can kill someone and then automatically you just get their Bitcoins
Bailando
If you cut off somebody's head
Immediately it's the quickening it's a big name
It's basically like
In Assassin's Creed when you have Auto loot
For you
Perfect
The evidence is overwhelming and
Listen to this
Tyceno ever
I see a couple of tweets
I see the most reasonable course of action being the explanation for events
It's the one that makes the most sense to me
Yeah I mean if I'm 75
I'm a globe traveling Rich dude who's escaped over and over and over again
Outrageously lucky
You've lived
Probably one of the most insane lives
Imaginable in foreign countries
Dodging
Totally
Boxing above your weight class
Forever and what it what are you going to do
What are you going to get your going to get another 10 years of life in an American prison that's
What's the awful
You don't want to do that so f****** Audrey yourself it makes sense
I made that that's tragic
As much as I want to minimize
Ghetto people who
Are struggling with suicidal ideation
It is Imagine
Cinebowl to put yourself in back
Cappy's position
And be like the indignity of
The trial
Yep the damage that
The trial would do
The things that he has made the most
Important parts of his life like cryptocurrency
You can see taking the outdoor
I don't know it I think
I'm not
Making any assumptions
I'll let the information
Guide me to whatever conclusion
Is there
Based on the statement from the catalonian just
This department
Based on the statement from his lawyer
That they are saying this isn't a parent
Suicide
I don't
See a reason to doubt that
The only reasons to doubt that our
Nutty tweets
From somebody who tweeted nutty s*** all the time
I'm not going to take that and I
That's not going to stand up in any kind of Court even the court of my mind this lying liar
Add something I guess I must believe it
Yeah
Adhere
Further anime be larger problem for me is
I just don't care
I just don't
Don't care that McAfee
I'd like
He's just not
Important he's like a sideshow it's like a it's like a
Carnival Barker
It's like
See I just don't see the power that Alex is
Thinking that you can wield
Through this year
I get what you're saying and I'm not super interested
In the case itself
As much as I am
The behavior
I think that the important thing to take away from this
Really understanding that Alex put out this report that night
What we talked about that concrete idea the idea that
When concrete is wet
A leaf that falls on a
I could leave a permanent impression
You got it
The information space is fairly similar
And
When a story when the details aren't out when there isn't
Like solidified information
Surrounding
Stuff you can make
Indentation in that conch
A lot of people are going to say
Subway has never used
Tuna in their sandwiches before it's already happened it's too late now
With this
Alex is trying to put
Into his audiences mind
Before there's any solid
Information
The media immediately reported
Did it was a suicide and that's
Suspicious
Because McAfee tweeted so crazy
That's
You know that it is a consist
Behavior
It's it's
One of the most
Kind of worrying and disgusting things
Is that
The conservative media
Has so insulated their listeners and viewers in the like
That they can make claims about any other media
Because they know you're not going to go check
You didn't listen
You don't read the the papers
What what person who is reading Infowars articles is then going to be like
And now I'll switch over to the Reuters article
That's not happening
So you can just make any f****** claim that you want about what the media said
Because they'll be
Believe anything you say about what the meat
You own the mainstream media
If you are in the
Conservative
Puppet that you can wield
And even if you are like an Alex Jones listener and you go check the writer store you'll see the headline larger the
Van life software Mogul John McAfee dies in Spain by Suicide lawyer say
Lawyer says why would you be like
Are reporting that he died actor
Yeah it is
It's a
And its profits used intention
Because
The false version
Of the story or the presumptive
Version of this story
Sulfur Alex
No it's one of their most powerful weapons controlling the narrative that they're telling you is the narrative they're selling
That's just
That's that's complete control over information
You know that's just
It's just Ironclad
You can't escape
So it's a real bummer
Play Pick A lot of people probably were reflecting on some things when Max
Skippy the news broke
Certainly
I was taking
Got woke up
And I had to tax
My friend
Telling me about the
Snooze my immediate response was well I bet Hillary did this
Baby
Okay alright
Jerry still out on
Yeah I think some people
Had some fun
Remembering a time you said that he was going to eat his dick
But slightly different
Print I respond
A lot of our interviews
With him over the years were on YouTube
Dozens of them got banded knocked off we never re-uploaded them
Banned. Video
This reminder
John mackovic
Archive page
Will post all the interviews we've done with him
Interviews on the tail end of this
Right now we're going shooting with him
My first interview with him in 2012
Archives
Juice this thing
She has told me that says Instagram posted a q
Exploit this
You need a new page
We need to get
Call Steve pieczenik and tell him to pretend he was on the
Alright
I'm waiting to find out
Did Stevie peas is the one who Ark
Orchestrated the assassination of McAfee
Getting out of pocket
Now my people in Catalonia
Alright then
So I like you already sort of
Respected
Anyone would
Alex does have to make
Take us about himself
And
You know it makes sense
He's in a Big Sur
Season right now about
How queues under
Sam Global if they're going to come for him and they're going to like kill his family and set him up for it or whatever we heard this like a week
To go on his show
He can't not take this up
Opportunity to
Reese press that thing
Closing
We we got a lot of threats a lot of attacks
They're making a movie
Journalist
Clear to Infiniti
I will never
Suicide
I will never kill myself
Anything like that
It is the Deep state
Held accountable
If anything happens to me
Look at Bill Gates
Hillary Clinton
The Deep state
They are the enemies of America Embassy vanity
And they're the ones
Longer
Asurion
Thunderbolt The Godfather says
So
Maybe this'll
Copy copy
I would I would prefer if every time he was like
If they find me with a needle in my arm if he just got really specific into what kind of drugs and alcohol
If they find me in a hotel surrounded by three empty bottles of Jack Daniels you know they killed me
What is their fault 100%
Kalama Jameson map
The only actual content analysis that Alex
Put out and it's his boilerplate as you can
There's more information that's got to come out and Alex knows that one side information
Available his job next to Impossible
The only time to act
What is immediately
So you get this
Arrest formulaic
Meaningless insistence
The Maccabee didn't kill himself based on a couple of years old
Does doesn't
Matter
This
Episode I think
Is
Is it still
Salient maybe it's important to do because it's important to recognize
Bees trick
Yeah they cizik
Hockey trick that Alex uses
One thing that I find
F****** excited
And I haven't in a week
During the day on Thursday at the end of the week shows
I want to know how he incorporates that Q on it
That's going to be tough
Yeah cuz already said the qanon is a globalist intelligence operation
Either ignored or or
Maybe it's the globalist
Taunting people on McAfee zenput could
It could be that they put it on there to claim responsibility for his murder that way
They put the Q on there so Alex
It's knows that it's
The globalist
Who are doing
You could be
Could be an option for him
Adjusting needle to see him thread
I'm excited too
I'm not really all that excited but I think I'll be interesting
Maybe maybe actually we're just finally figuring out the real spelling of
A John Malkovich
Mqa Fe
Maybe Indiana
How to change it for the soft
Maybe it's him admitting that he's cute
I don't think
So
That's that's it for the McAfee
Coverage
Sort of
Exactly what you did
Expect ya little underwhelming
Yeah
Whatever it would be nice if there was 18 you know
When the when the cement is this soft
And you can really just pull off whatever you want I want one big
Big swing you got to give us at least one big
Swing of like
A perpetrator or a group of people or or something other than just like
The globalist
Bill Gates and they wanted is crypto
Story behind it that you've got
You know you can't just be like all the media is lying
You have to give me a better story adversely when you're lying about what the media says
Barebones media coverage in order to justify your made-up
Give me give me something give me like
Did you know that Brian stelter was in Spain last
PetSmart then then and then we're like I hide now I've got it yeah yeah
Something like that
Somebody was in Spain
Around that
Time is what you got to give me
Yeah we good
But no one was in Spain
However I was in New York
Okay
This is flagra
To podcast
I don't know we're going to zap giant podcast
But at the same time it's still like
Joe Rogan
Junior varsity
You can't get on Rogan
At least
Not regular or not enough
Right I'm so
Yeah he can get on kill Tony I sure I can move the needle enough
Service publicity tour
Goes all the way to New York presumably either to do this podcast over to do this podcast and
And something else
Maybe at a deposition or something
But yeah
I just
I don't know it
It's really hard
For me to cover these sorts of appearances that Alex does because it's like
Alright
I get that this is an attempted
Right
I don't think it's funny
I think the subject matter sucks
Yeah probably
Somewhere on the bigoted Spectrum
Yeah
Whatever
I oppose I oppose this joke I oppose the message
The underlying this joke
But
I don't know like where where is the line of free speech
It's a speech to me but
You know YouTube should be able to
Decide whether they wanted on the platform or not
In terms of
Our conversation to become
Becomes a total mess when you're trying to
To criticize
Failed or
If he attempts
Sick humor
Yeah I mean it's it's what
We don't
Cover shows that are just Bros talk
All too often
You know it doesn't sound interesting
Really that
That like newsworthy I suppose the exception is like when Alex is on Rogan
And that's just kind of like
Because it's event
Level of
Hand
And because Alex really goes for it
He does
MN Dental like I was listening to this and I was like well okay we do cover
Alex when he's on Rogan and or maybe this is something that we should
He is
Cast on this show
If he's got something to say then I want to hear it
If he doesn't have anything to say then he doesn't have much to say
I want to play like the beginning this is how it starts
Alex
Spoiler alert comes out wearing tinfoil
Around his arms like Brazzers
Funny
What's up everybody
Two-player to iron
We have a major
Major
Probably
I come
I realize how we figured
Women's empowerment
Woman in the
B a i mean
Incredibly
Excited
Everybody right now good morning
Forgot
Everybody Wonder Woman Wonder Woman and we have Wonder Woman
Yeah
Transphobic
Joke
It's a it's a load of nonsense
I get
This
Sing
Imagine right before they started recording
Alex is like yours or no deal I'll put on a wig
Tin foil Emma pretend
Be wonderful
That's an idea he had
And then these guys were like
Cuz that'll be great got to do that
And you know what we're going to sell it
Yasso a boy
You can take that
Icees
Moments like this that just like really highlight to me how much of like a duplicitous game everyone is
Play Alex's there to try to launder his extremist beliefs to a gullible audience
He's also trying to bring more customers into his web
Simultaneously these dudes know that if you get Alex
To do some sational things that leads to
Increase the tension in traffic
You get him to run around without his shirt on you might end up going viral on Twitter
Could be a me but I can do something that is a long-lasting reaction gif
If meme or whatever
That's better advertising than you could ever pay for
Totally game
Both of them are playing that is
Promotional it in
Are not in nature and
It's just like okay I guess you're trading the possibility of having these moments
Willingly or unknowingly
Selling your audience
Cool
I just can't believe that people would want to listen to the same social
Show Dynamic that one would see you at a
F****** Elementary School
Alex might as well be eating
It's the same f****** thing Alex's there
To be humiliated for them to
And then they laugh at him
Stila Armenian
So no great no no
Even more integrated cuz I was about to talk about his dick
Nice Packer but I have a large
It looks like a grub worm with hair
Do you like
Really big
Surprise them later on
Yeah yeah
Yeah
This is not good riffic and it's
Unbecoming
Someone and Alex's
Position to act like this
Yeah
Imagine this juxtaposed with him
F****** praying on air
I got a trick dick
I mean it's so much like
I immediately get
Flashbacks to
Like early on doing
Stand up working with a
Established
Clean comic headliner
And it's me and Young
Female Comics you she and I are at about the same level of talent
Then he starts telling
Creepy ass f****** jokes right to her face
That is so
F***** up an inappropriate in your life
This is not okay that is what I'm hearing Alex do right now that creepy as s***
Himself
One place as beating
A pious
God-fearing man and then
When there's a
Social situation where you can f***
Can take advantage
This goddamn is positioning in the pirate gates to f*** around as people and I hate it
I think I think there's some of that and then there's some of it is just wanting
To have people
Think that you're in
Interesting by kind of like oversharing
I think that early on in my time doing stand-up I kind of was
Susceptible to that and I certainly
Would say more stuff on
Stage then I would become
Super Bowl with now extraversion of like
Let it all out there man. That was partially because
OU
Idiocy
Not taking myself
Seriously enough
To know that this wasn't
Appropriate
Alex's
47 years old
Doing this
As a human
Investigative truth-teller reporter for 27-year yes he thinks he's fighting the literal devil
Government want to kill him
Yep and you still like
Acts like I did
When I was in early dude, you're so stressed out you need an outlet
And that outlet is telling to weird Bros
While they mock you to your face that you've got a weird penis
Perfect set
I guess
I mean it should I guess
I guess if you know people want to
Look at him as a
I don't know
Good thing that I
They kept
Flashing to
Was
These people
Like these
These hosts
Flagrant
And
I would say even Rogan
Probably is this way
Tony Hinchcliffe
They have an image of Alex as
The drunk guy who talks about his dick
Or yells about aliens
Or like
Tells them some weird subsection they've never heard of
Okay I talked to
I talked to the weather weapon guy you know like that
BMX that they have of him
And that's what they think his show is
They haven't listened to his
Actual show
Probably not know
They don't know
And when Alex comes on
These types of
New shows
Crying about fighting the devil right
He's not like
Yelling
All his racist s***
He's he's not doing what he does on his show
If these people
Actually listen to Alex's show they would either be bored
Out of their mind
Or they like wait a
I'm not sure I want to be associated with this
You know I don't know exist
Years long
Trojan horse quest
Nice to get people to give their life to Jesus
Yeah people like these hosts
I want to be a part of this
Bringing people to God I mean here's what I could see this I could see them all in their mind
Because they are all that mean
What were the names of the people that were dealing with are all traffickers in toxic masculinity
Betrayed
So I could definitely see them being like
Oh you know is where we just played up on our show Alex just plays it up on his show and then real life easy
This guy so it's okay for us to be cool with them
Despite not realizing all of the f******
Destruction that his show does
Just because it's easier o'carrick Terron the show means it's okay
For them to be like you know what we'll have them on our Sophie the real guy
Except the reverse
Yeah I was going to say
Please do not reply.
To make that argument
That's what I'm what I'm saying I'm saying these people are worse
Then you give them credit
Argument is that it's a character and this is the real Alex if we're hanging out with bro
Went down with about our deck
Okay
Then that person that you're broiling down with his a psycho
Yes
Friends AR
To mean you could absolutely see them saying something like you know the
The Joker the crisis actor Joker
Itsfunneh
Because it's not Alex's fault it's people taking Alex to seriously
Who went too far with all that Sandy Hooks up
Alex is an Entertainer man
If people take it too seriously it's not Alex's fault just like when people take
Our stuff too seriously and it's like no we're making a joke
Sure I talked I made a quote-unquote joke about raping a woman
But that was a joke I don't know why people are taking it to f****** seriously
They even do I know
Touch on that a little bit everybody takes me out of contacts at 10
Boring argument
Cuz I've listened
Hundreds of hours of Alex
The show
I think I got a pretty good sense of what's an aquifer
Position in WhatsApp
I'm f****** around
And I don't take things that he's f****** around about all that
But seriously
I think that argument is
No I I would say it's self-serving and delusional argument that helps
See you go to sleep at night
Because what you're actually doing is
Exposing people to a f****** month
Yeah you're helping make it easier for people to
To accept it
The bad arguments and the awful things that Alex
Does believe yep
Presenting him in a way that's
Positive
Sociable that is like
And allowing him to
Perpetuate things
Explicitly
True
Winfield how to
F****** podcast
Please put Dracula
But there's just things that like you allow him
Perpetuate that aren't true
They're talking about Colbert and like white Colbert isn't
Funny anymore
New York
That's in the news that's almost unbelievable
Who's that they get calls
From Democrats
My cousin
And those guys know that corporate
They are job their cons
Pursuant to a
New York senator
F*** you man
Okay Heather Schumer said I'm supposed
Your summer joke
Old baggage
I control that
This is entirely about Jimmy Kimmel discussing on are having spoken with Chuck Schumer about the afford
Care Act
Would you mind recall was a super important thing
Jimmy because his son lives
Congenital
He was discussing on air
About how the coverage
Pre-existing condition
The really matters
In a very concrete weigh
Campbell was taking issue with
The Graham Cassidy bill was shot
To get rid of parts at some of the provisions of the ACA any preparation he got some assist
From Chuck Schumer's office about the bills.
I want to take an external from
2017 and embellished it now to the point where he's telling these dudes that Schumer is basically the booker and head writer
For all late night shows
This isn't joking around inside even in the territory of embellishment for a fat
This is just a lie that Alex's specifically.
Deploying to convince
These people's audience
That says going to all known crazy entertainment is just Secret
Globalist program
They're reacting to it with like
Galloway
That's almost unbelievable and you're like
Why wouldn't you stop for one second and go
That is unbelievable
No I mean Alex even gave you an example for you to be like I know people in comedy
Of course they too would say
F*** you Chuck Schumer you're not funny. These show the show the two dudes Who are the
The main host of it one of them used to be on MTV's Guy Code
And the other one was on wild and out
Comedians
Yeah you know people in the industry
Yes all of whom would do that regardless of whatever political affiliation you have a very very
Aggressive about you shutting the f****** some exposure to some of the things that Alex
Is being completely developed for this about
It's just not worth it to have an actual conversation
About it I don't think
If you've been on
Geico door wildin out or that kind of stuff there's no way you haven't interacted with
People who literally work
At SNL or Colbert or the like
Like that
There their they're
They're everywhere yeah I mean that's
And that means you know Chuck Schumer
That means they're taking orders from Chuck Schumer
Great I found largely listening to this to be like I have already said intolerable
I found it
So boring
Just
JustBats
That's the kind of noise
You put that for two and a half hours for about an hour
But they're worth
One really important
Something
They came up
A couple times
Who's in the first hour
And this is
Alex trying to formulate
A way to
To justify some of his
I found this
Really I really interesting we go
Call Renaissance
All the old
We throw it out
Nothing to do with rainbow Flags
Just literally sitting there
Total Renaissance
To overthrow
Entire thing
How everybody
Nothing let's get rid of
Play some black people
Mascot it
The front
Get rich
I really like black
Yeah do what I say I like black people
Flags
People are using rainbow flags and black people
What's the contract
Rainbow flag
You're like dude
That's not
You're killing people but you using
Good intentions
Listen to countless hours of Alex's show and I honestly don't think that that's an idea that I've ever heard him
You late like that really haven't either
Attract
Dewpoint and honestly I don't actually
The disagree that much with how he's framing at now I think he's
Well I mean you to see Nancy Pelosi in the like in f****** yeah businesses
Pay lip service
Vista communities in meaningless ways in order to Garner Goodwill
Directions might not be as supportive as those words
Imply
Rainbow flags and donations
Insta Trump do not go together and yet somehow I think it happens a lot and it's a part of the shallowness of the nature of corporate
Ouija corporations like people and all of a sudden they have a brand in a Persona to call today
And part of that is trite social-media gesture
And I think a lot of pee
People see through that
My framing Alex's opposition to things like a black pea
People and rainbow flag this way
I was just trying to hook the Audience by appealing to something that they could easily believe
This could possibly be the belief that Alex has that everyone says races
You know all those times Alex gets called a racist
He's got to be because people are misrepresenting its stance against corporate use of black lives matter and rainbow flag Christ got2b
Actually erases right
That's what Alex wants the audience to think
Because the reality is that Alex has a gigantic race
And if the audience knows that going in
They won't ever make it to the Infowars
Store
Trust me
The difference in how Alex
Response to a murder when the victim is black
Or when the victim is white has nothing to do with corporate signal indo-aryans explicitly races
Homophobe
Baked it's transphobic
He has those things right
He's being allowed to launder this
In a way that's a
Do you want to not only the house
But the audio
And gives them away to be like
Oh yeah everyone says Alex's races it's just
He doesn't like
If he doesn't like this
Corporate
It's saying we put a rainbow flag up during
Pride month
When you're a big
Right are you doing or
It's a valid criticism B
Trying to be used as a
The Shield
Bigotry
I mean that's the feedback
That's the feedback loop of
Conspiracy theorist
And
Shity politicians is that
When the system is so
Corrupt and so transparent bulge
It is easy for you to take a potshot like this
And get
People towards
More conspiratorial Aiden bulshit
Because obviously
Nancy Pelosi is f****** lying
That's not
Hard to jump to it don't the miniature version of how Alex's
Opposition to the Iraq War
Can trick you into thinking they key is an ally
And then you probably logically on the same pages and then corrupt
Shallow assholes
Use that conspiracy theory to get elected
When they corrupt
To the government and make
One less functional than it was before then York
Conspiracy theories get even stronger
Because the government is so obviously corrupt
Antique reset feedback loop of Destruction
It were possible mean I have said this so many times but the greatest weapon that the Democrats have against the
Republican Party
A governing effect
Ugly and I cannot do
They simply cannot
And that's why we get into these situations
I think that even if
The Democrats wanted to or had
A unified Wheels
The governor in WoW
I don't think it's possible that probably true it's probably too late now
Probably way too late now
Everyone can just do their best
Man they really had a they really had a shot 2008 to 2010 if they
Get together
It so much
Everybody had a
Right-wing terrorism problem
I wasn't going to stop
I just
I grow weary
View
Laundering
Attempt to Valley
And I just
I don't I don't think people don't have the right
To do it
Sure I don't think people are
You know
Should be
Band
I don't know I mean it's the platform
Choice they can do whatever the
F*** they want sure
I don't I don't
Think of it
And I don't think they should be arrested or
Anything for this
But
I wish people would consider a little bit more what they're doing
I wish
Fit like
If
These guys
Want to have Alex Jones
On their show
I would like them to ask about the devil
I would like to ask
About Lake
Valid criticism
About him as opposed to allowing him
To present his
Very
Very clear racism has opposite
Corporate signal
Right I would like it if they
You know this is a rare opportunity where you have Alex
Is there a UK
Can ask him
Digging question
Instead
Just allow him to
To poke your audience
There's there's really only
At this point
The bar itself
So there's only two things that happen if you have Alex
Jones on it's obviously you're right
You have
Either the option to
F****** eviscerate him
And then you will not be
On his level you will be over the bar
You do this
In which case you are under the bar right now
Next to Alex
I have no sympathy
4 people
Uutern flagrant-2 into Infowars in my mind like I have no
Continue is people
You should f****** stop
And if you don't get that if you don't make a change towards at
Then f*** off forever
You're just Infowars
Yeah I think I think we have
Probably
A very unique
Perspective
And I don't mean unique in
Like necessarily an overly positive way but
A perspective that other people don't have because we folks
It's so much on Alec
Text Joshua
I think that we have enough of an awareness of what this dude does
And what he's up to
His history
The way he lies
That position
SimCity actually has
People who
Would choose to associate with him
It's your right to
Sure but we know
Is it that you are him
I don't give a fuk
About Joe Rogan or Tim Dillon or these fox or any of these people
Alex Jones forever Dior at the rally
I get maybe you feel like you're not but if you stay at that rally
Get Susan.
A second time
I mean I guess
It's probably boost a probably boost numbers
It probably helps
With traffic and these guys have a bunch of heads on their show hope their sponsors don't dislike
Alex being on
It's okay if you destroy the world if your listeners go up
It's fine
Now it's the trade-off
I just
Don't understand
Being this your response
Ansible with
Present
Yeah that's that's really what it
It really comes down to like a part of you just
Breaks down
Discount like
Do you guys just not care
Like is that really it you just don't give a s***
I mean it feels like that's got to be the most
Simple a
Explanation about your show you don't care about the people who listen and you don't care about what happens because
That's what you're telling me
When you have Alex Jones on
Like I mean like
Here we have
A completely
Dissonant
Presentation
A week ago on his show
Alex is talking about how we're all dead
Yes you are getting old lady he's talking about they're going to kill everybody
I got to stand and fight against
I promise you I will take everything in my my ability or fake crying
The week is a New York wearing a wig
Great
What are you doing what are
Any of us
Brutal
What's comes back
And tries to present Mac
Cathy's death is a
Murder which can only
Only serve to incite his audience
Nonsensical
That's just so f***** up
It's so it's so f***** up how easy it is to
Jangle the keys of like
A f****** performer
In front of these idiots and then they'll just be like let's talk about dick
6 / 2 hours
Baby game baby I do I watched most of the first one
And it was not
In-depth or interesting
I watch the first hour of this one
Before I turned it off
Yeah I am the only thing I found interesting really
Was this presentation of Alex's racism as being opposed to
Corporate
Yeah
I don't know I guess I
I could have listened to the rest of it
Yeah I mean it can't if it weren't so
Reasonable to assume that they are
Corrupt lying piece
Pieces of s***
I think it would be harder to launder
You are a racism behind see look at those corrupt line pieces of s***
I wouldn't you know I would like it if this was actually a long game
It's not
But they were trying to Lowell Alex
Send you a false sense of security
You been in the last half-hour where they
Just f****** nailed it
Anyway anyway
Somewhat excited to see how Alex tries to incorporate that Q from John mcatee zinsser
Instagram
Will check in on that on Monday I believe
But
Until then
Website.com
We are 100
We are Facebook and establish a laxative could please find a local charity or bail fund to help out people
Until then
Text Clark I'm Daryl Rhonda
What the sex robot
Alex
Kirsten color with huge fan I love your work