Holding
Alexandra First Time coloring with huge fan I love your work
We're couple of dudes you like to sit around and talk a little bit
Emerick Jones
And today you have brought
Filbert's
Old time
Quality lime
The rhyming aspect
Perfection part of why this is my choice
It's a clear bottle of nothing but
Green neon green
Yeah
Here's the thing the other day
I woke up in a cold sweat at about 3 in the morning the other day
The one thought that wow is that bad
The worst thing I've ever tasted really invalidates the middle of
I've not tasted this but I realize like
Lime is a great flavor
I was laying awake in bed like
Man lime underutilized
Let me see if I agree with you
Do you think it's under
That's not bad
You're still wrong
A lot stronger
Based on your response
We have some strong opinions about
And we will get to them here in a moment but first
The show with
Contacts drop from Alex Jones
TV show
So bad
That's so coarse as a reference to Ted Nugent song
Hell yeah
That's just a nice example of hat like what we're missing out on
His back his his singing in and out of brakes
Astounding
This one was in the middle of the show so they kept it in
Jordan
Oh my investigation
What happened to Alex Jones
In 2015 to get him on board
Wrecks today
There will also be incredibly f***** up
Stuff to happen
Yeah before we get to all that
Give a shout out to a new donator
We got another person to donate
So I
And like to give a shout out to you number one
Rated podcast
Amongst
Yep
Thank you very much
You speculated that it may be Chase Bank I wanted to
You spell any of these rumors
Do we have taken up sponsorship with the globalist controlled Bank
Alex
He hears about a good love people who need to donate to the show obviously
Obviously it's donations
Call Alex in my head
Jordan will be going over the time span of August 12th to August 16th
In 2015
Pink eye
It's a wide range
. there's a whole lot of stuff that goes on
Others
Really no good way for me to distill
Symphysis
Of the events that we are about to
I will I will say
That we start
Lucy
Trends that alarm me a little bit
And this first clip is is part and parcel
There is a mark
Rise in
Tamagotchi
All these people want to turn off their Tamagotchis
Global
Is a divide-and-conquer strategy
Starting
You say a lot of positive things about repressive regime
No that's good there is a bit of really trope
Sentiment
To come through
And also this first clip
What
To complain about Jeb Bush
I am doing so
White washes
And completely tweaks
The history of the Syrian Civil War into a very pro-assad
Newpointe
But here it is
45 years until 3000 of them
Military
With Russian backing has been really fighting
No
And now the answer is to bomb
So he is essentially what he does end up saying about Putin and a later date
What about all those people that have gas
What about all this
Fake news
For speaking out against
What about invent murdered after
Okay
What about what about it
His car is he has a lot of
That's not fake news
You got a Hellcat
Americana the whole thing in
Syria is
Such as
F***** up
Future Revolution revelation of
Climate change
That's what
That's why I
People are like all of them
100 years
Ignore the fact
People are going to move
Mean s*** is going to happen
Just look at how rough
These work Netflix
Syrian children are
Just Meats
Somewhere to go somewhere
Tubi
Survived by their own government
You
Child
Terrorist you girl you very small
You are a dumb libtard cock it's not actually a small girl it's an adult
Passport that says he's a little girl
Okay
If we're willing to entertain that possibility
Counterparts
Two very small searing
You know you got to blend in
Yeah if your kid no one like at the country you're going to his refugees going to give you any credibility
You know you got to get nut wrench code on your friend shoulders and put on a fake beard
Play calyxes
Misinterpretation of what is happening in Syria
Abacus
15 is
Is calamitous
It's a literal Jen
And he's super willing to side with Assad
Like side with
The side because they love money
Alex
Because he's not getting
People
That's kind of where he's at probably right
Documented it pretty serious trend of trump
Seeming to really admired
Dictators and hating
A Cooperative bodies
That's kind of
Is very similar with Ally
It seems like you
Yes respect
For men
In the people who are like strong men
Like I mean he's talked about like
In the Philippines
Declared open season on his soldiers raping women in hostile territory
Say what you want he gets it done right so I mean he has
Friends but you obviously
And I think the
I'm not going to say that that doesn't play a small part in why he ends up eventually liking Trump
We're starting to
Be more of it in this August
So
Gross misunderstanding
All of the people who are fighting again
Asad Ric
And the al-Qaeda is the same thing as
That's crazy
Because Al-Qaeda
With the Syrian rebels
Who are also fighting
The Syrian
The people who are screwed the most
In Syria are
Please stop
Killing us
Yeah
Those are the people who got f***** over
And because of xenophobia and because of unwillingness to wrestle with the
The nuances
Susan complexities of it
We
Seem to have a position that Dean's Alvez
Screwed
You're probably a bad
Yeah
That's really bad
Propaganda on
Play the part of
Opera
The narrative
That
Equal
There's no
Like the Syrian rebels
Didn't want
Or don't want some
I'm kind of
Modern
Civilization the one that they were
Not just not getting but they were
Starving to
And all they tried to do
Do is modernize this
And become a
Free
Free her Society
One that does
So we should be on their side right America story
F***
Our bloodline
The third man
Finlay cassatt's been in power for
Pretty long time and his dad was in power before it's not like
Good
Hey we're going to do 70
2.0
Here's what we do
Okay we go all-in on
No More Kings
We're not declaring
Declaring independence
For us
We're declaring in the
Independence for the world service
Another globalist Bankers behind the scenes
I'm fine with that
Let's just go get rid of them but if you kill the king of the global is Bankers will just install new people who will be a problem
The problem not the King Park
I don't know
And we've already spun backwards into
So this next clip
Alex Jones shows
And his
Is Providence
Is discernment sharp as ever
He's back on his
Everything online
And he's into the collapse
Narrative that goes through the next couple days
This said is predictions pretty specific
12 signs and eminent Global Financial crash
Michaels.com
Did you see what just happened
This caused
Other Global currencies
World of the US dollar the price of oil
The Dow fell 212
On Tuesday.
Appointment
As we hurtled towards the absolutely critical month of September
And October
Organized hoarder
Christmas Christmas
Naked Joker
The police are heads of their bunkers right now
But we shouldn't fear monger
Do really well with the global crisis Alex
I wish I wasn't right
Congratulations you're not right in October
A+
Fakeness
Adidas
Globalist would be
Concerned with still having a Christmas
What if
Are there other famous they want 95% of the world population
But everybody
Tell you that the globalist have a warrant
Concerned with when they pull the trigger on this globe because they've got to make all the money off of selling breakfast
Narrative
Field day on making money more than they make it JCPenney's for Christmas sales
Yeah
Stupid stupid
Weird Alyssa
Send to him
Real numbers
12.6
Your Alex
But that's also real numbers as reported
Contextualize by an article on infowars.com
Massage Envy
But my point is there they're just
Spice it up a little bit
The other thing though that I want to punch you
How to be one Yuan
Child
Commodity currencies
This is not
Fiat currency cuz it's resource
Right back onto the Willy Wonka
Go get on those little
Chocolate coins
Christmas
It's really f***** up is that like
He really laid out in that last clip one of the games he plays that is really
If airtight
It's basically a skits
The phrenic game
And that is that like
Everyone's making fun of me now and then when it's not so bad later because we've exposed this thing
Because of the work that the Patriots have done getting the word out
Don't make fun of how I made a big deal out of it
But
Secret hero of
Every single time that I complain about something doesn't happen
It's because we have made it not
Fair game to play
That is literal insanity
His audience
Expose this stuff
Game
There's just
There's just never any pie
Communication
Alex the
Economy didn't
You predicted it you're welcome
That did not occur to me
So you're saying that the economy didn't collapse because of
The View
Well
How about
The last time it didn't collapse
It was that you had a flu
I tried to stop
I was too busy focusing on the globalist other attacks or something like that
Antenna
It's perfect
It's fighting anime
I really respected him one level because
It's clearly super profitable respected in terms of reality
You'll notice this is
Like our investigation in 2015 is
Specifically about the Trump campaign
He doesn't really get into much
Trump stopping
A little bit down the line
But if you have not listened to last episode
Get you up to speed
He thinks
Trump is a predator and a weasel
But he works
Casinos cuz he thinks their predatory
Hugh loves Trump is a vaccination
And is playing crazy
Because it makes it okay for people who don't support
Paul to say those things public
Is it
Big fan of Rand now because
I mean
He's not saying though
No.
A friend would say that
It really feels like if I can be
A little bit dramatic
It feels like it's a relationship that he has with Rand Paul
That's been going on for a long time
And then a new hot kid comes into school you know what new Joey Alpha dude
Shows up
Grandpa
You guys had a good thing going you philosophically matched up on a lot of stuff
But this guy who just showed up
I am loving this analogy hijinks are getting you f****** wet
Spitballs and what-have-yous calling
Calling people racist names
Feel like oh my God this guy is
He is a rebel
So you're just your p**** just gets going
You just want it ever say that word like that ever again soda
Grossest thing I've ever heard in my entire life and then
You feel yourself
Pulled away from Ron Paul
But at the same time you know you loved him for that shared history and shared philosophy but you wish you would be more like this bully
Any wallpaper
Because that's not him
I think that's where Alex is in August the 20th
In a breakup
Relationship
Force the person
So you got
You're going to have to f*** the Reb
In some ways
This stretch of time that we've been in
Uno
Trump announces candidacy on was a June 16th
The 2015
And now here we are on August
August 12th is left
Two months of kind of been a holding pattern
A little bit of like
You know you're going to
It's kind of weird
It's super weird 22c
Am I beautiful
Really good really good
Is very good
Gross
This is an adult show
Not a family show
Like I've climbed up ass
Is really weird
Rallying the troops
Letting you know the war is going on whether you know it or not
Right
With
School
Right wing
Mirror why
Father will deal with on the other side
I wish I wasn't
We don't mix
Cottonwood
And the wood lights on fire never been sued for libel or slander
So you can sue our source if you want another publication
We're just going off
25% what we cover is open source intelligence
Analysis of where I think it's going
And the Patriots worldwide
Operating
We've been trying to stop all this
Old Forge
Do you claim with fireballs
I've looked a bit of looking into Margaret Sanger because Alex is really mad at her
You gave women rights
The reality is
Racism
Stuff all of that is super out of
Context
Popular, let me see if I can pull up
This quote here exactly
You know who started Planned Parenthood
She was
Yeah well
Started Planned Parenthood in black neighborhoods
In order to
Get rid of blacks
That's one of the big claims with
People make the reality is that the first Planned Parent
The clinic that was opened in 19
Italian
And Irish neighborhood in New York
Talk about it
From a letter that she
She wrote that says
We don't want word to go out
That we want to exterminate the negro population
And the minister is the man who can
Can straighten that out
Straighten out that idea if it ever occurs
Sounds
Terrible know what it sounds like it's her saying
Oh I know what these people are going to say about
Now you're smart
That was so easy to pick up
Hey we don't want people
We'll just save this dumb s***
This is the guy who's going to get out in
In front of that.
And apparently
You should have gotten a way better
You take that
Quote from her letter within the context of the letter that is what
He saying if you are someone who is violently anti
You hear the words we don't want word to go out that we want
Exterminate the negro population
And what you hear is
We don't want that s*** to be
Republic
Of course so which
Again
You got to be more
Precise in your language
If you're writing a letter
To anyone
Most of the time people don't expect publicly
She
Margaret Sanger
I don't know if I kept the clip because he yells about Margaret
Hair like
Within this this stretch of episodes
But one of the things he talks about
She is responsible with Planned Parenthood
Funded the Kaiser Wilhelm Institute and Nazi Germany
All the Nazis are just an offshoot of Planned Parenthood
Oh I that when I
Have not heard but it's a good one
I like that that's not true the funding
Funding stuff you can find for like the Kaiser Wilhelm Institute came from
Like
The Rockefeller Foundation
The Kaiser Wilhelm
A society the Nazi scientific organization its roots in a Nazi
See.
It was founded in 1911
Exist
Before Planned Parenthood first
Kaiser Wilhelm
National Socialist Party didn't get going until I come with 1920
Give or take a little bit longer after that
Late 20's
And then
Form into the party
Beat the thing is is that they wasn't
Ended up
Maybe in some
Some dicey territory later
Want to get into it but they did not have
Some funding scheme
Where in Isaiah
Then I paid
The Kaiser Wilhelm in
Shoot to kill minorities are in
Anything like that
Is pointing to is that they both
In the Eugenics movement
That happened
Look it's f***** up the word Eugenics is a really f***** up word
Because of racial eugenic
Of course but the rich as I've already
The Pasto
I support it
Because I want to see somebody hit 100 home runs in one season
Figure this s*** out
Get them all together
Let him fall
And then we'll go from there
That's kind of the Olympics
The problem with water balloons
I don't have time to do a full book report on eugenics
But a lot of it was bad and it wasn't
There we go
Nazi stuff is the really bad and if you wouldn't
And Planned Parenthood
While it had its roots
Install
Eugenics
It wasn't like
Get rid of black people you done
No it was
Be deliberative about our reproduction
I'm not from a like
Government or organizations telling you what to do but you take
In control of your own reproductive choice
Because women were f*****
Economically because they couldn't chew
Structure
That's the real reason
All of the Planned Parenthood
Because they want to make sure that
Women aren't allowed to be
Barefoot and pregnant
And that's it
The economic and social power of men
When women are equal and when they have their own
Strongly disagree
I mean
Text
It still
Frustrating whenever
Their aim is obvious
And their lies
Is our
Yam
But the reason that we have planned parenthood make
Perfect sense
To everybody
If you if you have
No
If you're coming into it with no bias
Whatsoever
And somebody says okay well
You know
You should be able to control how many kids you have
And how many you can
That way
None of them starve
Yeah you can take good care of them
And they can be raised properly to become
Better people than you work
You go oh yeah that makes perfect
Beyond
If that's just one angle reproductive take away all the
Screening is an STD STI stuff
Because of those fake videos that were put out by the Center for Medical progress
Alex is still trick by them
The detox
A bunch about how Margaret Sanger was
She was
Deeply involved with the KKK
Okay well he's throwing a lot of darts
Around
Study about
Nazi Kaiser Wilhelm
Text k.k.
Your pic of one you think you're angry about
And then you're on board with olive
Margaret Sanger KKK bleeding exactly one time in her life
Alright how did it go this is taken from Margaret Sanger and autobiography
Which she wrote herself
I would hope
Which was published in 90
1838 otherwise
This was excerpted on PolitiFact
It's a work Advocate birth control
In her autobiography
Free across the United States
Exercises are willingness to talk to virtually anyone
Quote from her autobiography
Always to me any aroused group with a good girl
I therefore I accepted an invitation to talk to the women's branch of the Ku Klux Klan
It's Silver Lake New Jersey
One of the weirdest experiences I had in Lex
Singers account suggest
She did not hold the group in the highest esteem
After Rising
A complicated process that involves driving to a secret location
It was time for her to speak
Quote
Never before had I looked
Into a Sea of Faces like this
I was sure that if I order
One word such as abortion
Outside the usual vocabulary of these women
They would go off into Hysteria
I'm so my address that night had to be in the most Elementary of terms
As I was trying to make children
Sochi
Do not seem like she has very positive feelings about these
To the
The women's
Yeah I'm trying to educate
Hate them
About
Two rights in general
Help
Taking care of themselves
And then those b******
Stupid and crazy
Concise summary of her thought so you can even see within that quote the idea of like women going off in
Paternalistic idea from the time
Absolutely not a member of the clan
And based on the fact that she hired
Black doctors
At that time
Free clinics
And stuff like that
It really is a strong indication that she was way ahead of the Curve
In terms of racial understanding
Horseshoe
And then further
Personal philosophy
Was
That having access to abortion
Not even if it wasn't even legal no but having access to birth
Controlling making your own choices with a way of empowering women
It was a way of giving them control
I'm so if that is her premise
The idea of giving that to minority communities
That's not an attack
That's the absolute
Yeah
Established clinics in minority neighborhoods
Means that she is actively trying to help those
Of course that was too long
Why
I mean I know I know why but
Why are you doing this
Idiot it's a good thing
How do you
It's a good thing
They know it
And that's why they have to put up this propaganda
The Republic
Looking f****** new
That the Affordable Care Act was
Was a good thing
Clearly
So
Why would you
You constantly spread all these f****** lies about it
The only reason
Because control
Try and
Like minorities especially African-Americans
Hispanic
I have a long history of voting
Swing communities as a whole
Demographic Lee those are
Blocks that liberals
In order to maintain
Any
Representation in government
Among
These minority communities
They hate secretly they're trying to kill you right
Secretly they hate you almost
As much as we
How much we don't like it they secretly hated
Friends don't actually like you
That's true of the broker
Coalition
That the Democrats rely on
Withdraw support
Make them less likely to vote
Absolutely the whole thing is
Make sure that is few
People of color can vote it's boiled down to minority and Warman
Bruce Owens
Calculus
They really should
Has anybody thought about that
Like let's just have women and people of color
Just f****** murder all white men
I bet you guys would
Well I don't like you I don't like even so
Suggesting as a joke
Just because of what's going to end up happen
Episode I feel like is are we going to commit genocide on this episode
You suggesting these things were a dumb dumb to ever to listen to the show and want to attack us
They would use that as a like these guys advocate
Quote about hate
Like these people are going to try and smear us don't let them smires as
See it's evidence that there sweetheart there's no winner
Is that mean that means if you're just coming through everything I've ever said line by line by line
Something out of context
That makes me sound like a f******
Dear Lord
Lunatic like
Now it's not Whitwell Jordan
Be careful with your language now
After r600 hour of knowledge bike
Woohoo
That way
604 after this episode
Clip we finish up
The matters at hand for August
In this clip Alex is talking about
Severe the situation is
How the global is really want to take out people like him
And also want to take out people
Like this other guy
He's a representative his first name is also a representative
And he apparently has
The 28 pages from the 9/11 report that proved that Saudi Arabia was behind it
What's criminal forces in our government that Alex
Cell
And then also he wants to get John Boehner out of the
Chair
Position he wants to get him out
We all
Imagine going back to those times
John Boehner out with R&B
Probably
Could sort of read the tea leaves as it were and see the John Boehner was about done
Movement where he has
And they talked about how we got to get her out of there
Set the groundwork for a victory
But they already know is going to happen with or without any action on their part
Amazon
They are going to f***
Can kill this guy
Because he
He's coming out and saying all this
S*** and it relates to Alex
Atlantic
Exaggerate
Nth Degree
Lunacy
I'll guarantee
Killing killing killing me
Killing killing
Believe in the criminal Council
I know it'll blow up in their face
But
A nuke goes off in a major city and then it's just a footnote a bunch of people
They're going all
To kill him and in order
Alex Jones
This is
Possibly delusions of grandeur that is that is the biggest
The building went up in a fire at but there was one guy
Killed by a bullet
Sting
Storyline of Columbo
Mr. president
Alex Jones and strychnine in his body but it says he was killed by a nuke
That's crazy
Insane
Another city
I thought it was going to be like they murder him
Then drop the nuclear bomb on it to cover it up and meanwhile in Austin Alex
Kick the bucket
But also
You started to notice
You keep saying katie-bar-the-door
Yeah and that's another like steal your hand Kennewick
What the f*** is he saying
You never heard
Malik
And I know
Contacts that meme
But never heard that one either
Trouble's Brewing
You know I get that
Context clues
I looked it up really
Skewers Scottish thing
I didn't know that I've never heard that
Alex says it all the time
He's Welsh
Itsfunneh
It has a good ring to it doesn't Rhythm Katy Bar the Door
Shady Bar the Door
The Scotts
We know
Where help
We're literally Hill piccata
Okay
Alright well I mean
Yeah sound off on Facebook our new Facebook page
If you ever heard of the door
Genealogy
Your understanding of colloquialism
Those two things are important for us to gauge
Also on the August 12th show
Good segments with Anthony gucciardi
Where they sit around and talk about how great their pills are
Now pretty good
They just had one
Guys
I f***** up
I thought it was good look at this f****** rash this is brutal
We're going to get to a really weird
Testimonial about his pills
In a little bit
Yeah yeah weird but we got to start August 13th here and
Presidential hopefuls
Now most of his shows by talking about how
Bush
Is one of the big bows
Of the drug-running organizations
Is a drug lord basically
It's always the quiet one
Cocaine I'm bringing into the country
So Alex is
I think it might be a little bit off base on that
We're not here to defend
Jeb Bush
But
Don't give a fuk
Alex goes on to say some other interesting things about other hopefuls
And we ever push it out me open at Planned Parenthood
Nope
Push it out in the open
Geyserville home Institute
Can't recover the National Socialist Workers Party
If we're ever able to push out the organ harvesting of babies
Republican
100 blacks
And part of the Nazi operation
Does using
Chopped up
So did he hears what I think he
PCS when
You
Say abortion
Egg scrambler
Red
Winning around
Pull it right back out
You got little chunks
What's a baby right there
Probably fairly I got a baby
The bucket nonsense is if you really really hate abortion
Then you really really philosophically need to
Support
Contraception
And you need to
Support the morning-after pill
And if you don't know
Then you did not about aboard
About something else
It's about women being punished for having
Ben Carson
Is not a good candidate
For the job
He's doing now really a good brain surgeon
Qualify
He's not classically qualified to be in charge of Hud
Certainly he's not qualified don't there's no class
Play to qualify
Do anything
He certainly not qualified to teach about the Antiquity ancient history
Green green silos pyramid
What have you
In our government
It's dubious.
Also if Alex Jones
Says there's a real black president
That I've ever heard where I'm like
No run
You don't want that Monica Legacy that's going to be you're going to be used as a race
Strop
You run to use as a prop to do
Barack Obama
Some sort of
Book
Can't remember what it's
Oh I got you
So it's interesting to me though.
We've got a situation where he's super into RAM Paul he's indicated that he trusts
Ted Cruz 95%
And now he's saying Ben Carson would be a great president
Convoluted
His beliefs are and he claims he's not a Republican
Meanwhile he's fine with
List of the mall in Rand Paul
Republican news
Christian conservative a******
Crazy Ben Carson a lunatic
A complete Republican lunatic
And the thing that combines all of them is
Severe distress
A Planned Parenthood
All liberal ideas
He's not really even
Heathens
Yeah they are in the guns but it's not
I think that Alex Jones one of the things I'm starting to realize
Is that he doesn't Define himself as a positively
His beliefs are positive obligations there negative
Against
As opposed to being forth
Well exactly
Well that's the entire as much as he is against
What what is
Like
That's what they've been that's what the GOP in response
4-H
So they immediately got rid of any idea of well as
As well
What fox say said
McConnell
It's our job to make sure that
He doesn't get any
He's hot
Our only job
Is to make sure he's the one
Govern
Not represent
Your people but just
Delay
Distract
Avoid
Didn't I do all of this stuff
So now all they have left
Is we're against
There's no like an egg
Putting so much of their capital on being against
Obama care as opposed to
Creating something productive
What what is what is the age to be a butt
Cutting out all the good parts of Obamacare and leaving Obama
I'm taking money
Exactly Peter Pan
It's not something
It's not helping anybody it's not a positive thing it's not like you're introducing
Vhpa you're just taking Obamacare
Cutting out all of its inside
Pulling them out and then drink
The blood for yourself using rhetoric
About why you're doing it with legs
Suggestions of freedom
And that sort of stuff
You're going to be
Is there any
Positive
Legislation
That the GOP why
I don't think
I don't know here's what we want to make
Here's something that we want
As opposed to
Here's all the stuff that we want
That we don't want
I'm sure that there are if you get down to some lower level I bet there are
Maybe in state legislatures and stuff like that because
If it's anything like
Kansas they're going to have all go to
F****** s*** anyways it's hard to get away from this feeling but I don't fully accept
The idea that there is no moderate Republicans anymore
And I think it's I think that it appears that way certainly on a national scale but I'm positive that there are
Within
Within States within local bodies
And stuff like that
Are we getting
Into trouble the trouble there is
Is very simple
To make
It is
The same thing with police
I know
There are a lot of good
Yam
But
If you are fine
With
The bad police murdering people
I don't really think you're good
That's true
Qualifying
Look I get it you don't
Think you're racist
And maybe you're not
You think that it's all about tax
But you're fine with those f**** right over there
Yeah there's a boy
Oh you get a
You get a different star
Yeah
You know it's either you are
Going to break
No
They're not Republican
They're not conservatives they're just
Walking racist being part of a group does not preclude your responsibilities of the
So we know now
About
These people
Alex support
Love them but we haven't heard anything
Luckily Alex
FrontRunner for a year
Really now in the middle of the pack
Because of the Donald Trump
Extravaganza
I think I like the fact he's aggressive he doesn't apologize that's the fresh
He's confident knowledge
Bloomy wants president
Mesa Flea Market
And pull the world out of a depression
And a single-family home and
Australia
CV global
I don't see Donald Trump
I smell a big snake
That's not alright
Yeah
Okay
So he's giving
Okay we're still right there on that I love all the Stuffies
I love how
He's not but I like she's got a big ass I love to slap it
Like
But Alex's if I don't think he really believes
Alex is a fake smart version of those people who we all
No I'm baby I was guilty of this for a very short. Of time
Where is a
Hey man
It would be fun
Freezing like it would be like we have chocolate Sunday
Is a holiday or whatever you fill in the blank
Whatever lunacy
What happened
I'd like we'd be a circus
I think that Alex is
Country we are very much
Dark carnival
Actually I'll be much more comfortable with my brothers out there my apps
Seems like
What's the weather
Shaggy 2 Dope
Blaze Ya Dead Homie
Oship Miracles guitar Supreme Court
I've never gone down to Georgia
Commercials
Amazing Grace So Good
I just don't need that
I'm trying to get press passes go to the Gathering
Play but I always f*** it up
Anyway I'd love to go
Do you want to go get me press passes to go to the Gathering
In
To cover the Alex Jones Goes to the Gathering
They would eat him
They would be
Funny smart for Alex
I think there's probably an overlapping audience
But I don't think it would be
Cuz I think
She would also hate
Probably thinks they're getting into
Some kind of satanic cult
Opinions
But
Discovered his position
Still thinks he's untrustworthy
Here's in this next clip Alex gets into his feelings about the Russian
The show but here's here's where he's at with them
Infowars.com
Combat Russian media
As I prepared
Colorado Lucien inside Russia
Talk about stirring up the Russians
This is what Obama's
Directions work
Okay
Village from a cartoon or something
That's a bad way to look at the world
All of it is just George Soros launching color revolutions around
Spring
The purple Rebellion the orange Revolution
So just
Attached to them would your favorite
Green is lime soda is a revolution
Not bad limes a great flavor
Glad I had that moment
I couldn't sleep
Thought about what
Myself
Please send them there while you were yelling he says Russia did nothing wrong
Russia
To do a lot of Rock
In the future from there
Not granted a lot of stuff about the hacking and a lot of stuff about the interfering in our election
Wasn't really publicly known at this point
They had just
Started their campaign apparently
But the FBI has said that it started in the summer of 2015
To go on there I'll give Alex
Credit for not knowing about that
Anything to us
So
What where we at
I don't know I think it was the way that we
The way that we talked about
A few episodes
Citgo was
They know that something happened
They're just trying to
To figure out the best way to hand
We don't have to
Fight a World War
Right
So
It's hard
What's happening now with
Like the more and more
Coming out very very
Slowly it's like
S***
Vital War it's been coming out is really really strong indications
Was personally involved
And Racine
Evidence
Starting to come out
That that pretty strong indications that voter rolls were at least which could have
Disenfranchised voters made them ineligible to vote cancelled out their vote
There's a lot of strong indications
People are saying
3 States
17 Somerset
At very least it was like 20
Which is very much like
That's inactive
The war that's a literal Act
The stuff that we've
I mean there is that to unpack but it's too difficult
Item
I'm not Charmed
By the argument hey it's okay they did it to us cuz we do it two people
I didn't say that was a donut
Position to have
But it's very serious they did it to us and we should stop doing it to other people
Yeah I think
Right I think those are two positions that are compatible
These sorts of things
Very very very serious
Reno in 2015
They're not doing anything to us so we shouldn't
Be mad we now restarting
Proceed there's pretty good evidence
You should be mad
Wellington
Craziest like did you read the the
Washington Post
Obama article the one thing that
Boggled my mind
It's coming off like
Because the headline basic
Obama didn't do enough
Regret that
And it's like
Every time he went
Regio Pee-wee
Any of them
From
A state
From anywhere
Didn't want to
8 years of we hate you built
So anything's
Any alarm he's trying to sound is not going to be listened to
So
So yeah and
You could you could take that as like that
You know is that evidence
Of collusion
Some people but
Your your reaction to it is
Is way better which
These guys
Hated Obama so much
They were willing to let the country
It could be a mixed bag it's certainly possible that both of those things are slightly true
Alex is literally talking about in this case is
Setting up Outpost
To fight Russian propaganda
Yeah go Russians
Whether they are our big bad guy or not there's arguments you could see on both sides at least until
Stage of 2015
They are notorious for propaganda
Really good at Cold War that's been a really big piece of their Warfare tactics
They had to their weight
They're amazing
And so I don't really see anything to evil or nefarious but the idea of setting up
An outpost in Lithuania and work against
The Insidious influence
End
Destabilizing influences Russia
Just be like
Dan friesenhaus for this
Began to show called knowledge fight
That's what it is it's just it's just hey
They're lying
Let's stream
People how to know when there
Being lied to
Do you know if your birthday or is it propaganda
The thing is it's there is a fine line between
We live in such a f*****-up time.
For everybody lies all the time
Becomes a thing where if you're really just trying to poke holes and propaganda the other side isn't real IQ propaganda
It's just
Exactly what happened with the fake news idea like the fake news is supposed to be about
Propaganda
President Bush
Yeah
We live we live on the global playground
That's the idea that I had during the
Ramp up to
To the election
Just scared the s*** out of me
In the primary
Raise even
That was
There are no adults
Right this isn't going like
You always
Kind of get the cents growing up
That like
When you're a kid
Straighten this out
The idea during the primaries
You know it's crazy now but someone
This isn't going to work
You can't you can't do this
You're having fun
Bitstop kind of there where it's like
Okay
Miller
He's going to just
Step in and there's going to be like
Guys
We f***** up
We're going to put them in jail and we'll do this all over again
But now everybody
I think it's a self-defense
Homecoming is incredibly scary
But the once you make sense of the fact that help isn't coming you can be
Become the help
That you wanted
And I think that the reason
He is a director
Revelate
Response to the revolution
No one's going to take out Alex
Come out necessarily
But no one's going to work against him and I'm uniquely situated to do so
So
On a very small scale
I'm here to help
That's what that's all week
That's the best we can do
We've been served document
Alex Jones
And his relationship with his own path
As it relates to abortion right
It's really weird about
I do not judge
I started to psychology
That makes no sense
Especially if it was early on whatever
Realize you were fooled you were deceived
So Alex is talking about himself
Projecting like crazy
Into the abortion game
Because they're guilty about their past is him talking about how guilty
Which is why
Jesus pooping
That people were trying to
To use his
Guilt
To make him think that abortion is okay
When we all just in his own head
8th psalm
It's all entire episode the function of
Are those that streams
Videos telling a caller
Is
Him sayings
I felt that guilt and they tried to get
But I Rose above
I Rose above it I'm one of the rare ones
Who's able to not get Waldo down and guilt
Which is insane
Clearly he's wallet
Guilt about it
And
That whole f****** idea of whatever it was in my heart is all that matters
Clutch
Escapist Christian idea
It's so like alright I beat that guy's ass but I meant well
Preacher
And I was like
Abortion
But
Confessed in front of God and man
Yep never have to worry about again
Slandering Planned Parenthood in Margaret are all over the place
Pay for an abortion
He says he's paid for multiple ones in that past web
I don't know
I feel like it's irresponsible for us
Speculate
We know nothing about
Alex is f****** dumb
Dallas
Racist black people
Does that mean
Incredible culture
Manny
More racist black people have seen white people
Which would be
Imposter
I think so
That would literally would be impossible
Well the reason possible is if you
Don't think the races
Things are rapists
Like he's gone on his show and talked about how blacks
Gavin McInnes
To come on and say that most
The Black Faces Reverend
Well it's I mean it's just take that as a microcosm argument make sense
In his mind
Because nothing he does is racist
So the only racist things that happen
Are done by people who aren't
Exactly like him which is a racist racist
Further you allows the rationalizations in the b******* that
Would say about their action
Of course
As legitimate
Like so dismissive
Whereas he would not get the same
He's just
You f****** raped
Yeah you know so
And also
I want to know what black leaders
You talk to Khalid Muhammad
Carte blanche to say whatever the
The f*** you want
Anyway
So
Later on the show he has an interview with his newly-hired invest
Navigate of reporter Wayne Madsen
Oh how long did Wayne stick around
Around 42 episode so far
Clinton
Cook was murdered
And this is the key to everything
Hillary Clinton cook was murdered
Was found
With a note on him
Contact Larry Nichols
Which
Something is not right
That's a real thing
No that's what he said
There's no way
So anyway apparently this cook
He was the White House chef
On 911 something about
Now I'm
Just thinking about how much fun it would be
Just wandered around and
Every time we
We found a dead body we
We just put a note on there
Call Larry Nichols
We have his number
We can do that
We should call Larry Nicholson ask about that cook
That's a good maybe we'll get back to that
This time
We have to let him know that we were record
Webster's
Jeb Bush
The reporting that he gets into
I don't really care it's not
It's not good
But it does say that Trump
Is a pause
Mind you
Show Donald Trump is like a millionaire Archie Bunker
Poop
I got the point of Archie Bunker
Archetype of an old race
Yep so I went back and I watched
Some clips from All in the Family
It's way worse than you remember he says like
F****** he calls black people Coons all the time he claims that all Europeans are facts
Like it's insane right because I started looking around today
There is a sizable YouTube Community
That believes
That Archie Bunker was at like a warning
Of the truth
There's a different number of people who put out videos about how like
This was this was like
Subtle warning that we all just
Finding the truth in All in the Family
Yep
Dude
Open a open a book
Just one
The other thing too is that like those videos about how Archie Bunker was like a prophet
I'd like 400,000 views
Me
Bums me out
Archie Bunker was a prophet
No
Got it all
So
They also another thing is being I like vehicle at
Narrative
Spinning along as as it does
He's mentioning that you need to buy gold
September
You know you're putting you putting these time frames on
Things I want you to hold off on that
Because before he gets into another interview
You got to do a little sale
I want to tell you that you know all these other places like
TBS
Cuz your taxes go to them
MSNBC
They get tons of taxpayer money
Just to give f****** Rachel Maddow raised
But not him
He's based on free will
MSNBC
Forum
So Mister dent
Is on who is this
Yes
I know it his name is first name
Play I don't know he's on the bed
Peter dent
Harry Dent is on his Anaconda
Yeah it's like a butthole my butthole is hurt
Economist
He's on a bit
He's in the Peter Schiff League
Of Alex Jones
Terms of these sort of out there
Economist
The come on
I want to deal with the premise that Alex is making that he's based on free will
Are you getting a gun to your head saying you got a pack
Now
Maybe true
But
All of his premise
Are based on
The globalists are doing things to you by the water that you drink
Rattling the foods you man I'm so because I'm scaring you
You are not going to be a complete healthy
The person unless you take the
Which is kind of a gun to the Head
Creating a problem
That
I will insist his life
Providing the solution
Which is life
Yeah it's a problem reaction
Pollution
Essentially I am threatening
Until you
Take
It's like you have a gun to your head
And even worst we've already discussed
About the
Disaster narrative the economy is about to collapse only to have 10% of my resources as a guest
Here's the answer
$50,000 an ounce
So now on Alex's show here on this on this 13th day of August
He's saying
It's about Free Will I don't do no I'm not trying to
I just you know if you like the stuff we do
Like having Harry dance on your money
On the show
China is the greatest problem history it is finally coming unravel
That's why I'm confidence
Of the global bubble bursting against China was the first thing actually before that and Mark
German
The leading Market
In Europe look like a dirty to me and then send in the China crash in late May
And in the end of July and now I think the US markets are going to start heading down early stuff to
Number probably peeking in the next week or two so
I think this is happening
Bill come back up
Yeah
It's within week
So then weeks
Is
So irresponsible
Like even eat like economy shows like
Like Financial shows
Shouldn't be saying s*** like that
Like
Factors
And like really credentialed people
Shouldn't be saying stuff
Ignorant audience
People will believe them
Wework
Economic
Is
Also a belief system
Before with runs on the back
Destroyed
There is a shared
Concept that
The economy is going to go well
Cuz we're all parts
And if you think it's going
To fall apart
You're going
You can sabotage
So the Aviv like constant
Fear meta-narrative
The economy is
Always
Collapse
Is
It is basically saying all of society's always
Yeah because it is
Shared ID
In one
Economy
Totally agree
The whole thing
He's coming down
Coming down
Yeah but not in the same way
Feelings
For sure
Water in your house
Some Ramen
Something like that a bad thing
But it wasn't because of like
Collapse or disasters is because we lived in Missouri there tornadoes destroyed
By a tornado
The basement would be safe and we could be down
There anything
100 reasons why
If they have and put a blanket in your car
Fill the rest of the base
You hear me
Are you crazy
You build the basement out of gold
Gold
Deflect
Tornadoes everyone knows that
That's why that's why Bill Gates is trying to get all the gold cuz he's got weather manipulation
Then you can't deflect the tornadoes all right
It's f****** basic
Supply and demand
Alright well then you're right
Guys I'm quoting
Tornado
Quotient
I want them
Coverage of the
And as we see his position has not changed
It's really on Trump at all
The 14th
Is incredibly f*****
No s***
Snow
Necessarily
But
The show itself
Is not really
That gray
There's not much going on on the show let me let me consult my notes
Here are two
To get to
I want to take care of the important
Pieces before we start playing clips
Same Old Pro Rochester
About how
It's just a roast trying to start a color Revel
Revolution
Also
Hillary's emails are now starting to
And play
The FBI had taken her server
Right at this point
Turn off all that much that was
It was basically the Planned Parenthood
They have a Straight Outta Compton review
Done by KISS Daniel
Such a car is still around at this point
The review is the CIA created rap music
That's a
Definition
Trusting review
Peter Schiff who comes on to stress the disaster narrative the financial collapse
Narrative
And in this one they start talking about Peter Schiff
Shift dab
A bunch
The political prisoner
He's in prison
Should not be
It's and they say that it's because you wrote a book
Called Federal Mafia
About how you don't have to pay your taxes
They don't really talk about that
Political prisoner
About how the things that he was charged with
Were
He didn't pay billions of dollars attacked early 80s
Epsom salt
I mean
How long
Has he been in jail for
He is like a couple months after this point
October
How long did they say for like 10 years
Oh boy
B b Hardware
30 years of
And
The other thing is
Because he was this guy was writing this book
Where you don't have to pay taxes all of these people ended up going
He screwed over a lot of people with
Very inaccurate information
It was about self-enrichment
Toupee
Was fake
And so they ended up
Defrauding the government of over
Things like 70 million dollars
Just people who are directly associated with it
And most of them got shorter prison sentences in him
Because they didn't write a book
Text
Contempt of court charge
Because he
Who acted up in court
In some ways I'm not sure
Yeah
They all they do on the show is talk about how
Because he wrote This Book
And they allow people to sell the book
But you can't sell the book
And the reason that is
Is because he can't
Prophet off the
The crime
It would be like
Illegal
According to the First Amendment
To be out there it would be adequate
They're like if I didn't pay tax
Here's how I would
Took the book can exist but he can't make money off of
Ended up just giving away for free online
Stephen Curry
He did time
Yeah and here's the f***** up
And when he was first getting charged
He taught him and his lawyer tried to use essentially in insanity
Defend that a mental disorder caused him to have these beliefs
He shouldn't be held responsible
Okay now was it then what
Well here you just let him keep telling the butt
Here
Here's the thing
That is him trying
But
His ankle on it was
No no no
I did that because I wanted to
Get in front of a jury
They would have just had a judge decided
If I hadn't have tried to do
Like I don't
Is I mean God Rest his soul
Whatever
I don't care
He was in prison for million-dollar
No
Easy bucking libertarian
Who thinks
The taxes are a crime against
Write the taxation is violence
I just I just wanted to show these people the world
Did they think they want to live in
Because it's f****** insane yeah absolutely
You know what
If you want to be a Libertarian and that way you can do it
Go to a f******
Forest
Builder
Your cabin and hunt
That you don't have to pay taxes on
Yeah as long as it's long as nobody's
He's there and nobody knows than fine live your libertarian idea
But just know you won't have electricity you won't have f****** roads
Your kids won't go to school all of this is because of taxes
And if you are a libertarian
Take your f******
Kid out of school
Throw your phone in the garbage get rid of all of this s***
Because you don't get it
Quite frankly that's because we've already had the conversation
Society has decided decided that collectively we can create a much better
Place to live
Then killing things in the woods
With no electricity and no Netflix
If you're a libertarian
You're not allowed to watch that
You can watch Hulu
19 +
Some crazy s***
But the stuff I want to talk about more
Is a narrative
There is a
Every now and again
Alex Jones
His show has a beginning middle and end
But logically make sense
I'm there was a storyline that goes throughout it
That he did not intend
And this episode
I'm going
To lay out
The exact narrative
And it's way more f***** up than you can possibly imagine
So here's the first clip
Or he's talking about Rita's reading review
From the internet of his product brain for
Wash from
Call City California
What's what's happening
I cannot stress enough
Missing screws or loose screws miad
Great concentration and focus
Galaxy force
And that's what's so amazing about a bottle
Quan
Gross
My brain Force
Don't waste your time
That are prescription in Europe prescription Europe
He took a pill
Are you not cape
Bilal
Love seeing how
If you don't take it
Can't you feel it
That's not the same thing as taking it makes me feel good
If I don't
4 after
Having smoked
10 years old
I feel it
You know I'm nervous I'm
That's called addiction
He's describing essentially withdrawals
So is that review
And Alex
Pop the pill
On the show
Is the beginning of the narrative
Cuz we get to watch
To somebody who takes brainforce
Yes something actually happened
Oh yeah
It's unclear
It's all probably it's probably like a homeopathy
We'll see what the I don't think
I don't think there's anything
Let me be perfectly clear
It does not do what is on label
But it's
It's really crazy
Cuz about half an hour after he takes a pill
Keychain
Exactly what happened
You've got to make some other b******* claim
What if it was just
Don't think so either but
Next thing is
Just absolutely insane
Constitutionalist haven't done anything to anybody
83 cops a year
Clap shofar
For the
That's what the lowest crime rates of any group out there
What Constitution was a self-fulfilling prophecy
Let's Talk About Us haven't done anything to end
For Colored Girls 45 cops
But that's
Here's some headlines from this week
Just about this
Judge sentences Sovereign Citizen 12 years in prison for Oakridge Rampage
That story is about a guy
Was convicted of one count
Of Reckless homicide and aggravated assault
He drove in Reverse through a crowd of about 200 people during the 4th of July 2015
Firework show
Airpark
That Sovereign citizen who did that
Another one
Computers taking too long to load up
Sovereign citizens with my Wi-Fi
Oakridge
Monday
Two stories about sting
My bad
Add a Fourth of July that's Americana was it,
No that's fine
Also if you don't if you don't know about Sovereign citizen
All of you out there listening I highly encourage
Look it up on YouTube
Cuz
They're f******
Hilarious
If you take out all of the like they do kill people stuff
Watching them argue in court
So funny
There's a argue in court
But they don't believe that they are sovereign
They don't believe in the Integrity or the right of the Court
They believe that America was established on like admiralty law maritime law
AmVet
So here's everybody was just
Forgotten
It's a secret
The secret behind the scenes knows the truth
But they don't tell you
You know on your government documents
Your name is in capital letters
Yes you do you know that me
The capital letters
That's not you as a
Person
That's you as a financial entity
Right you are just created in order to get
Debt put into your name under the
Capital letters version of your name
No you
A lowercase ordain as a human flashing
Blood that's your Sovereign it
But the capital letters
That's the tax identity
So every time you go to court
If you go to court
There
Quarter all these capital letters
That's not you as a person
They're trying
Tax identity
Starts crying weight
As a financial entity
And never speak again
Argument is on
Capitalization of letters
That's a big part of it
Authority
Awesome stuff
Are some of the judges
A really they try
They try to treat them
Okay well let's see what is
What are you trying
Could you make sense
Crazy person
But there was a there's one where an old man is in court
Eventually just gets
Really fed up and so she goes to Chambers
Left
All the charges are dropped she has left the court
And so he leaves
It gets in the car and that there is an addendum
You got arrested that I say
Are contempt of court charges
These people are they are really
It's really funny
To see these videos on YouTube
But the dangerous ramifications of it is
If you don't believe in any of the authority thing
You do think that any cop who pulls you over is a grasping upon
Alright also another part of sovereignty
Citizen identity is
In order to be
Your whole
Lowercase
Lettered
Soul version of yourself
The human version
You have to renounce
The capital letter version of yourself
And to do so you have to write a letter
And send your ID
And like your identification documents
Back to the government and tell them that you
Give them a notice
Of your rejection
Of the text
Entity
Version of yourself
You now if you were ever driving
You don't have an ID
So if you get pulled over by a cop your automatically going to at least get a ticket
Maybe arrest
So every time a sovereign citizen runs into a cop
It's basically a situation where they're going to get arrested
So it really is a powder keg
In a lot of weight
See the thing
I just
It sounds to me like the world's shittiest religion
It basically is because
Like the idea
Yes
Okay
Sure
The government and the laws have been around for 300 years or whatever
But
Have you can
Considered that maybe
They made it type
Maritime law
None of it applies to
What what
It's not it's not like
It's not like Cinderella where it's like always if you don't sign this by midnight
Ignominy
It's not it's not a heck
Magic
No
It is an extreme version of distrust
Of the government
It's an extreme version of libertarian
Pieces of
Their belief is
The government
Shouldn't have any
Supposed to have any
Control over traveling
Vacancy
Steve of like driving as traveling
And so like
Instatravel
You're not traveling
You're driving
I did a lot of looking into them a while back
And it's f****** fast
But
If you're not an idiot and you look at it you realize that this is a real short walk
From real serious problems
Beams
Don't get arrested a bunch
People. Respect
Police means you're going to get arrested a bunch
Beans
You're going to
To feel like
They don't have any
Authority to arrest
And you're already
And you're not going to be threatened in the same way
Nissan systematic oppression over
You're going to
The fuel
Threatened
A real Philly maritime law based
Admiralty thing
Delusion
Watch some of these YouTube videos when they're amazing
So Alex gets down that road
Break the prison station.
For rent for the ride starts
And swirled around in that in them guts
Alex gets on a little bit of a rant
Orgeat
You start by talking about how honest
Pistachios
Then
A bit about his girlfriend
I am it just goes from
Of course
The sheriff says we're Liars
I remember the articles
Around about last year when all this bro
Infowars or Liars
Stop there
Chinese files from Pluto
I agree
I want to be the truth
Truthful
Girlfriend stuff with ask me
Does this dress look good I tell you no
What is this s*** on the end of my nose look bad looks bad
That's why they always attack cuz I got my phone
This is where it gets real
Yeah I'm about to
I'm about to see this go
Wild
So this is just jumps off
A mysterious way
You can see a change
Fascinating
Always been involved
Call fight Jaron
14 years old
I'm at a party
His brothers getting drugs for cheerleaders
Brother
I wouldn't bother
Cheerleader
And he said yeah yeah
I see cops
The cop was just freaked out.
You want me to kill you don't know what you doing
I understood that stuff
And Texas monthly didn't believe me so they went investigated
Police Department
Prostitutes
Drugs Olive
I wasn't involved
Golf Course upper-middle-class neighborhood
For myself
I want to stipulate a f*****-up story I want to stipulate that this one might be true
The sheriff of Rockwall
Did get busted for drug charges
I can't find independent confirmation
Call here's the thing
Alex is a liar
That story
About the Rockwall stress
Came out in 2009
There is an entire possibility that he built
Fictitious passed for himself
Based on the knowledge
That story had broken
You think it's possible that
Keystone
Roach like
Like like
The false recovered memories
Yeah kind of
It's like
He saw that in your ghost
Oh I remember when I was
The part of that
Although also
The only reason that I think this
Story sounds
True
Is
When he said
They're getting drugs for
Cheerleaders
I thought it was better that he wasn't
See I wouldn't take the drug
We are giving them to Young impressionable women time
Well
Drugging
That's what he's
Witnesses buddies drug women
Also I mean
Sure there is the Cosby aspect to it but you got to also consider this was like mid-80s at the time you know
Another one some Rave culture that was going on it. It's not necessarily that they were drugging people as much as maybe they were
For supplying
These cheerleaders that he's referencing
Did want recreational drugs
To me if if you go to a
Join the party
Don't go to a party like that if you're 12
Party party
Well that's a crime
But the guy's a drug dealer
Atlanta cop threatened to kill him
I think some of the Talisman obvious
Obviously
Very bizarre couple years after his
Termite poison
Exposure I found pretty good evidence
That
An acute exposure
Just like an hour even
Call serious metal.
Wow they've done studies
As it relates to this story
There's one possibility that he's not
Lying
Or like you said false recovered memories
Hearing the story from
But he's not done with Israel
These experiences and I'm not going to be signed onto it
I feel guilty enough
Call.
I feel guilty for all this stuff
Okay
Hispanic stores
You sonsabitches I'm sorry that talk like that
Florida
Running roughshod on people
That's a normal male response
No boy
Don't shoot your advancement
Your punk
I don't watch them cops either
And follow-up gangsters
4shared
You shouldn't admit that
If you are
There comes a point
The New World Order
I put my, why my family
For sure I'll Never Compromise
Never Say Never
I'll Never Back Down
Very ironic considering how much of a cheerleader
Keep conceptualizes more ironic
Considering he's had to back down from multiple stories
The ID
Everything is about the globalists in the New World Order
Allows him to
Do you know he's going to take out right now
The Cowardly sound like
No he's not done yet
Federal
Wannabe gangster
Makes me want to throw up
Disgaea
Gross
Once an hour
Yeah but even though
He had to find something to do as I got. Might as well plug
Bring force is a roller
Furious and then just the law
Yeah
The deflated after screaming yeah that's weird
Obviously it's a combination of rainforest and his own
Michelle wins
August 4th
But he does overdrive
Which means that it's not on the regular radio
Right
Some stations that decide to cover it
And on the internet
Wards.com
Fret
Still on the brain
Oh yeah
Haha
I think
He is pretty glad that this isn't on the radio
Once it starts
I'm going to play you exactly where overdrive start
And it will pick up probably the next hour
Of Our Lives
That is the most problematic thing
I think I've ever heard on his show
North Carolina thank you for calling thank you for holding your on the Year Frank welcome
Give me a moment I promise tomorrow
I heard you making some disparaging remarks the other day and praying that he was one of the most
Where I'm coming from
The whole system is lined up against white straight
Traditional no
At is the winning team
Call Villa Capri
Be on the winning team
So
Alex
A white supremacist collar
Yep
Clearly on the consciously
Or very much
So
I can't wait
I mean he does
We're in overdrive we have plenty of time as long as you want now
I think
Right before we get into this cuz it's rough
What I think Alex Jones
Think
That his response to this
Out
And out white supremacist
I'm saying that knowing what you going to say
I'm not miss aligning this color
Right
Respond
He thinks
That he is
But he's not
Waters
His response
Did the caller is
Weird and because he's on the rainforest
He mixes up a whole lot of other issues into it
It's like I said
Problematically
Super f***** up
You're probably wondering
Who is that call or talk enough
About Frank in North Carolina
Find out
I think he's among the most voices of Reason out there today
Well I'll be honest with you
Organization
And then they run all this race war garbage
Dominate
Basically
Fra-dor or cover-up for Israel and all this bull
I don't blame Jews for it
Some good Chinese
Because
ATL connection
Be in the prison complex divide-and-conquer where everyone is
Unifying idea of a basic human Liberty
I don't care what color you are I don't want you
I don't want to speak cuz I have read as much
I probably was radio shows 10-15 times
I've seen
About you
Even listen to it
All I know is
Is it people want to feel like they're better than me
Because they can say
Alex Jones
Work for the Vatican
I'm a real person
For the ideas of basic freedom is best.com
So
His response
To this caller saying
What's your beef
David Duke
2bc are is a direct answer I believe I don't know much about him
Yeah that's kind of makes answer about this idea of what
Of course there's a war on
There's also a war black
You're getting there buddy has deflection from the very real issues
Of race
Racism
Right it's this made-up Boogeyman that I have in my head you guys aren't
You're stupid
And I don't like
That you guys are folks
On
I don't like that you guys are focusing on this
Race narrative
That's what he say
Someone
Like someone
Yeah you're your District you're part of the globalist
Plan to distract
Against
What they're doing
And calling David Duke
Or at least an agent
Of the globalist subway
You guys like get it
You're just not right enough
Right leg is everybody it's not just
Which is good
It's not guilty all lives matter
Best Vet him all lives matter in white
More or less the other thing is
Alex Johnson
Realize
How people hear him
He doesn't realize
How much
White supremacist to love him
He thinks how can he
Well there's a small group that are very vocal that do things
But he's a Zionist chill
Stuff like that
Like there are people who obviously sound off in his comments sections on
His YouTube videos
Better like you dumb
You work for Israel
These
Small subsection
Of the white supremacist
Commenters
That that respond to him as being like
Not realizing that the narratives and the way he
Culver's race differently
Throughout the show
Let you know the difference
Potato white gunman in a black gun
Or the way he's so Auntie Islam
Doesn't realize our Manna From Heaven
Two white
So he doesn't realize that
This caller is essentially in his demographic
Squarely in his demographic
He's been listening for an hour
Isn't saying Alex
You're wrong I hate you you work for Israel and I don't like
Get along
If I can't come on
Synthesized your philosophies together into my personal philosophy
Yeah well obviously they are
And there are much like the situation with the police in Rockwall
There's two possible for situation
What is the totally oblivious
Of the fact that he's a racist
Which ICS
Very unlikely
Man
You got it
You got to know your
Surprised by
White supremacist loving him
Estranged
His his defense
To be that he says
I don't care
He says we all bleed red
But
You do care
Clearly
Because
Of what you say
End
All of your ex
Actions are racist
You don't get to say
So you know
It his entire life is
But yeah
Like that
I don't care if you're white or black
We have races on both sides
There a lot of people on both sides but black people beat me up
Your black butt
Muslims have little girls allowed to go to pool shop and Starbucks
Freak me out
So you're
Fairly right but let's get through this call cuz there's other
You would never do
Saying that never do that with someone who's Maybe
Supporting like
Ferguson
You get them off the phone
Out of the general white supremacy
Do I take them
More than I hate the blacks
Manipulation
A lot about
You know how to block and that's legitimate points
Call Kendall
Barry engineered
Genocide of the white race
Basically
Advocate
Corporate
So how do you miss
How do you misunderstand at that back
You're scared of everything
Like that
How is it
That you
Like you being cool with other people
Is to you
The government saying we can't have it
Well I look at
Like this
So I am
From a white Caucasian
What's a hamburger
Florida
Forget I go through my life a little bit further and I
Encounter Hispanic culture
Now I've been validated my own white culture
Because their culture is superior
In terms of burrito versus hamburger
Okay little bit further and then I run into like stir fry
But I run into a Thai Cuisine
Burritos
That eventually becomes
I think that's as dumb as what he saying
Nike okay I was saying was very dumb
She does make
But no it doesn't make sense
In the way there
You mean it but
As an explanation for how they say
That does make
The first step
This one
That one of them has to be better
Yeah
Like it's not
Like you and I both know
Some days I want to hand
Sure
So
If you
Always live in this like
How to be the best
So if so is better
UCare
Because that would as you said that would invalidate your
Culture veneers Alex Azar
Look you guys are being distracted by hamburger vs. burrito when the reality is there is a bunch of globalist elite
You want us all to eat bush
That's sort of his
If you want to use a food metaphors
He's getting a burrito fight against becoming bush
Kind of makes
Absolutely.
I wish I could find an episode where Alex Jones finds out that like that guy was developing Soylent
Like a food replacement
Oh yeah I would love to hear your take on that
Keeps
Get more into this
Which
Batumi
Kind of a little calculated
Early
Something that he got
Which is that
I get
To have it both ways
I get to let this white supremacist
Stay the stuff
That my listeners love
And I get to
Like I am against
Somewhat yeah
This version
I look like a hero
Sort of provide like the idea of eating myself
Like I said there's a lot of call last
Let's Dive In
This one I just left I didn't really cut out all that much
I cut out a couple things workout repetitive or
I would have you just a couple of minutes of the
Of the call this one start with h
Coming back from break
You lies about how he calls out all sorts of race
No matter where it is
False equivalence
Organized and persecute
Tribalism a private property
The power of the family
And yes whites are under attack yes they have free slaps for whites Berkeley
Yes they're telling
Bad and Evil
Break right there tell you a little bit about my childhood
I grew up in Hawaii for a little bit when I was
And they call
White people howling
In Hawaii
The translates to no soul
White people don't have souls
There is a fairly Rich tradition of distrust of white people in Hawaii
God still not enough
The reasons only they have gotten it at
Overthrowing of their government
Taking of their land dance
Complete destruction of
There is a reason for that
Even despite
When I was growing up a lot of my friends were Hawaiian
They were Native
A lot of Polynesians
It's where my friends growing
There wasn't racism against
Mia
Although
The calling people
Was intrinsically racist
Right
So
What I'm trying to get at is
If I wanted to
I could get up on a soapbox and talk about how racist everyone was to music
I could do that
I could say everyone called me and no Soul Heaven
White guy
Broaden
Right
In the same way that Alex drive to get all kinds of white victimhood narratives out of nothing
Get blood out of a stone
I could do that same thing if I wanted
With it with my childhood in Hawaii
But the reality of it is
I did get beat up once but I had to come in
I was being a dick head to somebody and I could frame it as this big
Reality is I would with a smartass kid and I was making fun of him
I could reframe it if I want it
I can leave out those details that no one would be able to find
No one except maybe my brother you might be aware of it
It's it's
It's silly it's pointless
I don't think
I don't think the Texas could possibly be
A more anti-white environment than Hawaii
Like
Hawaii has
Hawaii has a very
Morepro white that maybe
Maybe Frank in North Carolina
Dragon North Carolina's houses
The very Pro white space
But what I'm saying is this
I think
Hawaii has AIDS
Cultural reason to be against
It's very simple
The cultural reasons
You're there
Do you know how you got there
Not good
You stole it
You stole shed
No
YouTube
At no point in history should anybody's trust white people
No like the biggest change in his
Three would be if you just sent one guy back ever
Every time to be like a
Don't don't say hi to the white people
No I don't think there's a way to go back in time
There's not but if there was a way to go back in time I think there's a way to still allow people in
And be like don't trust their intention
Like
BB more hard-line negotiator about stuff
Do not have souls don't give the benefit of the doubt
I don't know if it's necessary
For me to make this
The first thing that he said
In the clip is
When right when white people are racist
Listen to all this s***
We call it out
If they're you know if they're being set up
If we're covered with we're going to call
People are racist
We will condemn it
But every time we've seen wipe
People be racist
It's a false
Yep
They're set up to
Distinct
Between
Frank
Really dumb
White supremacy
And Alex is
Cloaked white supremacy under the guise of globalist
For the life of me cuz I've never spoke
I don't really know if it's
Intentional or not
Like I don't know if Alex really deeply has white supremacist beliefs
Or if it's just a byproduct
Nick
With underlying racism
His kind of subconscious I don't know and I don't think we can though
But this phone call is really
This is going on
This is unfolding
But then
The basically pigeonhole
And go after
Black people look at Gardasil
Which is known to cause reproductive problems and all sorts of other
Major major issues
That's being targeted against basically American countries
Mexico is
HP4 monster
When you look at what larraza means it means the rice
It's okay
4S Ranch
Manipulative it's all bad
No it's not and you're lying
What is
The reality behind
Bourassa translates to the people
It doesn't Translate
Version It's a false cognates
It is like
Erase
Based organization
Silly it's mostly cultural base
Pictures is itself
Just an advocacy group for Hispanic
Right it's a group
Equalize
Healthcare
Education
They seek to do good which means I have to
Destroyed in the same way that like the n-double-acp will step in
First civil rights
Complaints
Black people
La Raza is there interim
Hispanic
Malbec
Is a youth
Organization
The college organization
It started back in
It has a little bit more of a revolutionary bent to it
I bought it
Not at all
Like
The clan
They do have their ways of the catchphrase
Not sure if it's their official slogan
Where are Delarosa nada
Which means for the people everything
For those against the people nothing
It is
Atake
On the phrase that was popular during the Cuban Revolution
Which was por la revolucion Toto
Guerra de la revolucion de nada
Good
Against it
Essentially
KK is stupid
Because
Even
Even matchup
Which does have a little bit more of a problematic history because
It's mostly made up of
For college students
And sometimes they do dumb f***
Can things
So there is a little bit worse than history to that but
Not on
Not on the scale of
Okkk
They just have
Maybe said some bad stuff about Jews
In the back
No answer but I really like their restraint
In there not murdering
And killing a bunch
Not targeting huge fan of the violin
Didn't murder a bunch
Two people for no other
Add LaRosa is itself like I said
The organization
I do not
Against
Anybody as much as
You help people rent
That's the thing that that's saying that n-double-acp
Is the
Black cuckoo
Right
This might be me giving Alex too much credit but there are some
Streetgangs
Something
La Raza
He's trying to make that false equivalence
The reality is to
It's so much more of a complicated conversation to have about the reason why organizations like the n-double-acp
Hanna rosin
Exist
Something like
Partly because of the f****** ku-klux yeah it's something like a white version of that
Doesn't really need to exist
Because if we got the Ku Klux Klan
And and a lot of our interest
We don't
White interest
Are protected by.
Default
And Society
That is
The standard of every
And the reason why these groups needs to exist is sometime
The priorities of people that just automatically get fulfilled
I'd step on the toes of the
Culturally disenfranchised group
That is definitely more fair
Pretend
Cultural Matrix of power doesn't spray
Is absolutely insane
But
Why don't we have a history
Because all all hit all of all of them
So just shut up
If we had a white history
No one would care
Shut up
So Alex wants to make another time to explain
Like his idea about the divide-and-conquer strategy
Using against us by race
The other way to explain it.
Pictures of prisms
In divide and conquer
They organized it around race
Eugenics
I was a guest on the radio show one time
I'm invited, for our discussion
A few weeks ago
And have a serious discussion about world events
How does the square eugenics
All these programs are going on
It was just a conspiracy against white people
Light
In the Gardasil
I know it's giving it to the Alder Lake
Mystics about
Gardasil statistics about the incidence of side effects from Gardasil
There is a database
Negative
Reactions
The people have had behind
To Gardasil like everybody gets
What do you mean
So everybody
So there's a hundred percent
Murder rate
Call them
You get all of them every time in the database
Investigated the claims
These incidents
You know you just get rid of fever
And stuff like that
Fevers headache
Stuff like that
9 to 1/200
Landscape
You get to serious side effects
And people went through Port over
20000 incidents
Negative side effects of people who got these
Vaccine
Right
Conclusion
Is
That could analyze
There is nothing that suggests that there's causation
From the Gardasil vaccine at all
The numbers were
Statistically
On
Interesting
When a 2d just population
The deaths that have happened because of Gardasil
Are not things that could be attributed to Gardasil
The side effects
Correlation causes
Beside effect that are very serious
Are things that like I said are just
Statistically on par with a population
So they did a little further Deep dive into side effects of vaccines
I want thing
That was really interesting but this guy
Was that if you take
These five specific vaccine
And the other ones
The incident
Reported of cervical dysplasia
In people who have had these vaccines
You look at it
The people who had the vaccine
Two people
Had cervical
Dysplasia
Three of them
0 one of them had one
Those numbers are
Stanford we lower
Then the main population as a whole
Now maybe they also cure
Well you can't make that claim either
Correlation not causation
Interesting
Statistically and
Saying that the flu vaccine cure cervical dysplasia
Have the same amount of scientific credibility
Did Alex
So the idea that like fluoride isn't nearly
Negative is Alex
It's I don't think
It's great put anything in the water
It's not some sort of brain chemical
That part is a huge man
Further is other example
That they're forcing Gardasil on people and no one's mad about it
Tens of thousands of women die every year globally because of cervical cancer
If you look at this
Statistical rate
Negative side effects
Deaths caused by Wichita
At least
Not negligible number Medical Science
But compared to the tens of thousands
Not to mention anal cancers
Not to mention there's like four or five other cancers that takes care of
Hbv causes
Bunch of cancers
You can just get rid of it
It's insane that he's against it and thinks it's a
Some sort of a scam
Because it's
For women
Liberty also knows that
80% of his listeners are food
Who cares
Do the other thing I wanted to point out what about that clip was
His premise of
Prisons are run by separating people by race
Warden
Control the
Play them off against each other
Games based on race
Documentaries about prison
No one's doing that to them everyone does that to themselves
People separate based on race
In prison because
It's a desperate situation
There are a lot of criminals in
Yeah there's a lot of it
Exploiters in there
There's a lot of people who have created a system
If you're weak
They will rape you
They will take all of your food
Your week
They will get you
To have your parents
Send money
There's so much methods of exploitation the people use in prison
Not to mention right so the fish
Is
The system
The inmates
Have been able to figure out which is
Definitely flawed
A big part of that might be
Little lot of these criminals
A lot of gangs on the outside
Translate
Who is Emily of the global
Weston acai
In this metaphor
The fight then we'll have total control over the prison
With those games
So stupid
His metaphor doesn't work
It's a dumb metaphor
Yasso
It's a little bit weird about people
Thinking he's Jewish
There's something bigger here
It's much worse
Limited
Is there Jewish
Absolutely
What does it mean
Individual Jews themselves were very diverse people
It's more complex laws in Israel
Is that a yes
Why does this real promote
Rachel stabbed over here but that doesn't live by there
Greenville Walmart
They are back
About me
Orders from Israel
You complained
Really seem to be mostly about
The problem with the KKK
Sometimes they're mad at me
Everything else
And then we'll find some legal officer Corporation
Lawyers
Alcohol
And so I must work.
Liquor license for liquor store
Losing something that isn't there
Shroud
Persons issue
I don't like the way you say
From Wales
Alex Jones's are walking around
You think you gained some point on me
Okay
By yourself
Sakura whales
Wow
F***** up I tried I listen to that like three times and I really tried to parse
Exactly what he's saying
About being called a Jew
Put a nail in it I don't know I have no idea what he saying
I don't know what he's mad about
I think
Chill
Either line
Frank didn't say
He's responding
Criticism of David
I am
You know things that people put on his message boards comments but he gets the
Heat
Frank is calling to talk about Alex
Mischaracterizing David Duke
And the two of them seem to have cinnamon
Of course
Alex
Some people in the white supremacist movement
Called him a Jew
Now
Consider
Consider that brainforce is sold as a focus
And attention supplement
This is a this is a commercial against rainforest
But also I don't like you were saying that you don't like how he says and I agree
Not a good way then also the thing is
No matter what he's saying about people trying to score points on him by accusing him of being Jewish
Playing into the game of being called a Jew is negative
True
That's not exactly
I I didn't
Because I assumed that like it's so ridiculous
Being called a Jew would matter
So of course that doesn't even cross my brain
In his world though
That is
They are
It's very very weird
Not because they're
Because
Oh man
Very weird
The call is not done
Back on the line
And what he does
He had sides to hip Alex up on a little bit of new lingo
Oh that's going on
Is the Galaxy ever hear about this
B the beginning of some of the the seeds of the alt-right rise that we have seen
Two things
Nixon in that context
He was like
Ally
But then also
But then the other thing is
You like these black racist
White racist
Has been stolen from them
U-Haul
Body of products that you sell is based on the globalist
Feeling Your vitality
You are the worst
If the problem is it's right
It's not global
The globalist of taking our sovereignty they've taken our Vitality through the water
Take me to Waverly
Angle of attack
Is incredibly silly
Like that is complained about races
Anyway
There's my rent on that subject
Frank
He's better than you friend maybe I should get some of the
Worship
Cuz she wasn't that
Because there's a bus in Canada
Culture overwritten in before
That's your right arm stand review
The globalist want to tear each other's throats and we don't need that on the
Yeah I think that's a really good idea to have to think it would make for great radio if nothing else
I don't think he's a white supremacist
There's a lot of people out there that probably did 30-40 years ago or maybe after
Not at all
Either way
Stand up for themselves and then stopped
Directions
Just a reality white men or have to stand up for themselves
Yeah this is this is dark
Alex is not repudiating really any of the things
Not with everything other than the
Stand up for themselves
But against the global
God
If you say race-traitor
Yeah
Gazette
Again that implies B race
Is a
No don't reply
It does
White people are all in this
Together
Instead of people
Countries
Cupboard
Cuz I was born with this skin color
Means that
I have to follow along with
Like Bandits the best
Skin color
Yeah how arbitrary is that for bigotry
It's Billy to take a step back and look at it like f****** stupid
It's mind-boggling
To really to really like
Get into your head and just think
You know what
I bet it's skin color
I bet that's what does it
Well the problem with modern racism is that there's such a deep history of debunked
Scientific theories around
That a lot of people who don't really want very smart
Might have
Some beliefs that date back to like phrenology like that and I think it's really smart versions of
Not all black IQs are way lower
And stuff like that smaller brains
S*** like that
So
If somebody says a problem
From people just deal with the reality that it is
This is based on Aesthetics
Yeah
You hate you hate people who look
Just say that
Your tribal fuc
No you see it's fast
Muscle fiber
That's why black people are better at basketball
Likenow f*** you
You're an
Yeesh one more clip in this call and then we will move on to greener pastures for a minute
White supremacist proud just says the same stuff over and over again
I understand what you're saying
It's just that
I'm not a traitor to life
And the globalist conquer
And control
And I think somebody should expose the masterplan
Does it mean
Did you grow up
Can you get attacked as a white person told your bad physically attacked
Doesn't mean you don't want to go
Black people
They're so close to each other
But you jealous
What
Shoe Show close
When it comes to
Appreciate your call
Appreciate your call talk about
Beating or something it's not
Explosion
Rainforest
Frustrated
Is over
But Alex is not done
Could never have guessed that
The next
Clip here is his aftermath from this call
He thinks
These above racism
I don't really know what his point is in this
Doesn't sound good
So many white supremacists comments on Infowars
Would you really take a one-year-old black.
No
How do you hate Khalid Muhammad kill all the white babies
Soul recoils from
I don't need to read it the book or no it it'll actually know I do
Can you get that done
And even worse
I will not sit here and feel good about myself
It's disgusting
Racist blacks
Guns
Bunch of big black guy
Because you're white
Oh yeah
You mean yesterday
Tomorrow
Suggest
That says
It doesn't happen
No it doesn't have it it's gone the other direction
Black people are oppressing white people
Well but if you wants to just literally talked about
Dunno black
Folk you know we just have to do Castillo video come out
It's a horrifying
To know that that s***
Carter
If you look at just if you want to extrapolate further cuz I know that he doesn't like Muslims either
There was that young girl who got kidnapped outside a mosque
Beaten to death just recently just like last week or so
They're saying it's not a hate crime it was a road rage
Which is great
Killed a fort
13 year old Muslim girl road rage
Wind up with you beating a
A fourteen-year-old girl
I don't know
I don't know I don't know
I don't know what kind of a f******
Monster would burn down the other day
The guy just got charged with it
Somebody's went in wanted to find out if they're Mach with heavily-armed
Bowers try and find guns
Cuz they were convinced
Fart
Military centers and what have you
In an arson
Are cockamamie their nonsense
Is really offensive racist in that last
If you're racist are you willing to beat a 1 year old black baby to death
Cuz that's what we're talking about that's not what we're talkin
What about you don't have to do that to be one of the worst races possible all you have to do is deny that racism
You have to live your life
In such a
In such a way as to deny the
The validity of people who are expressing their reality
PlayStation app
Dawn
Mary love them
Like fantasy
White dude fantasy
I get to be
Justified
And killing somebody
That's what they really want really want to be that guy with the gun they want to kill somebody
That's what they
That literally the
Gold when I was like
It was I wanted to be in a righteous fight like I wanted to get into a fight like standing up for somebody
Like I wanted to be in a place where I could just unload I was doing it because the other person was the
And Alex has grown out of that
Sorry that took up a lot of time but it is important
The overdrive is done
He takes another call from somebody who explained to him that he's fulfilling biblical prophecy
Which is not
Alex
Caller says that Alex
Will really help out his f****** Jesus
The complex music play almost like looking like he's going to cry
Because Alex Jones has sources backing him up and he's not a liar like everyone else
I would ask that guy to look at Alex's sources
Oh that's I got to read the Bible to get back on his meds
You get the call or towards the end
What is overdrive
On August 14th
In the fourth hour of his three-hour show
Call Lemon Grove
Yeah Alex I'll try to be as quick as I can I just want to throw out some point so you can put a timer on me or whatever 2 minutes or whatever but
Throw out some stuff for you
Pilar country
Has the
X to the last
Replace my best on rainfall
Versus
On the roulette wheel
Play some 101 bet on Trump trump has any character
Okay and
Spend our time and money on Races that we can win you know I mean in like you're saying other time but
They say I think
She's an outsider that's why people feel he's an outsider he's out of career politician
Actually I feel he's an Insider he's actually an inside rather globulus to sabotage
You think you understand
Far as that goes I wrote down a bunch of stuff I'm a little nervous.
Listen you're probably right
We'll see what he ends up doing
Yeah
Malleable be like that you know I mean
Alex
Scrooged
Any casino owning
And a big slumlord
Economy
But you have to defend them because what he's saying is true
Office
That's why it's catching on
The other candidates should be saying it as well just more smoothly as dumb
Booksmart
Shark
Casino opening shark
But you got them
Ideas man those vaccines right
We're going to be covering one more day
Okay
Necessarily
The Friday
And
August
16th comes around
Mentioned in past episodes
My experience is that Sundays are for
Doing a trial balloon the new narrative
The new narrative on Sunday
And I'll just
Of August
16th 2050
Call Geico
About Donald Trump
Because he is
That are not what a scripted controlled candidate
Machine irrevocable
An absolutely massive scale
Because he's support about parties in the past and
Own casinos
Has his own list of problems and has been part of WWE wrestling
Jesse Ventura
Long-term politicians like Donald Trump
People think he's an outsider
To certain point he's made his money though off the service economy
Alpha products
Stealing money
Statement right there he
Contradicted his own Knowledge from past episodes that we've seen
He has stated before he's a front man
4 Consortium
Doesn't make his money off
Of service stuff
No he doesn't make his money off the free market is part of the mob
Alex
Is
Making his pivot
This is the turn right
Are we say is he
Full-throated I don't think so
What happened on the moon
He's going to get to it a little bit in the in the next couple days
Earlier
Couple of days I would
Eclipse cuz it'll sort of come out and then I will give you my sister
I'm right here on air
Wrong
Bulshit
All the time
Yeah that works
SeaWorld
This is written up prefab
It is unscripted so there's mistakes but
I rarely fundamentally Miss Gage
Major geopolitical
Because I've been doing this year's on air over 20
And I've learned the players are the different clubs are the different Power structures are
I didn't last 20 plus years it's been the same group of
So you're not getting too much information there about
Well he's just saying that he's never wrong
This person that ever was
Enough
Stand up and
I got the date wrong
Did that one time
Even though that stuff is deflection area bulshit
This is unlike Allen
The idea is undoing all of this
All the stuff he's been saying for the last 2 months
Very weird
And it's very abrupt
It is really abrupt
Cuz the ended
The 14th show which is Friday no show on Saturday
Saying negative things about Trump
Still giving him the benefit of the doubt he's a liar he's floors
Even though like
The the trajectory that we've seen hasn't been
Hasn't been
Flat and then there was a change today
There's been there's been some little motion of like
I just he's a distraction and we don't even want to talk about I'm Turtle like
Let me tell you he's a
Yeah
Well I like what
What is this
The shell
Or I know things about him
We're going to get to the other statements
But first we got to pay the bill
Got to do a little bit of a super male Vitality commercial products about
A different people
Is what happens in the morning when you wake up at 6 a.m.
That job
I was be honest
I don't need Cialis or Viagra
What is a man 41 years old
Once the doctor had a checkup
Anaya bottles about Cialis and Viagra used
Recreational
Either it's just
Idea what it does for everything else
They call the boner is a metaphor talkin about
You going to have a mind boner killer is a metaphor
Dropper
Yeah we can put
It's better for
Somehow yeah
From the woman
Yeah
This is the last Cliff I have his statement on Trump
Where he's at on August
16th and
I mean one of the pieces of our investigation is to like what are these things you sell
And our long-term
Contention
To use the word properly
That was our penultimate
What
Changed his mind a little bit
By then we get on the other side of it all
Romance
Klitschko strongman
Napoleon Bonaparte types
William the Conqueror type
I'd like to point out that within the last week of these episodes
It's in the timeline
Alex Jones is unfair unfavorably compared Donald Trump to Hitler
Seizure types
Would try to come in
But if you shut up other people in control of other power
And that
Because we have three centers of government
That would not allow a dictatorship
How sad is it that in hindsight
His analysis is right and why we're f*****
In hindsight how sad is it that Alex Jones
The only branch of government that is under the sway of 8D crazy out of control
Yep
How
Hey come on
Don't forget
They control the Supreme Court also
Nothing I control the still some issues with the a plays out
If we're going to help us
Rodger Stone
There's another Supreme Court
Yeah that's what I like
Alright
Alphabet Corporation
But still attached
McDonald's
Money off having a rich economy
Off people vacationing people
Russian slang for salesman
How much Freedom we lost in that we really nowhere in a Long Cold depression
He speaks to that he should look our borders are wide open
For free
Not for you
He'll come on somebody
They thought it was a joke at first
Double cross people are I tell you he is going to be
He's going after the clintons now which is a big deal
Wants to be president
NFL leaders in history that weren't perfect
That's why I Like A Boss Hog management control
Montag was not the hero
The Trump doesn't want
He is a capital at the end of the day
He's totally different then
Barack Obama and a cloward-piven
Executing
He's got some major problems
But it's nice
This is Trump on Clinton emails
Problem this is bull
Because
This will destroy you
Because it'll make it safe for other people to do it
This is a general election problem
No problem
Proverbs 22:28
Gmail
So that's what happened
Trump said a couple negative things about Hillary Clinton
Trump
That's it
Wanted to jail Hill
That's pretty much it
That's it
Let the big thing
That's what
That's what happened over the weekend
Yeah but that's all that's all Alex needed was somebody to come out and say let's put Hillary
Basically
But I actually think it's much bigger than that
What you would have to
Well I think
It turns out our theories are both kind of correct cuz this is very close after the first of
Get him
On board with Trump
But it opened the door
And
I don't have I don't have the exact audio of it but even on this episode
I'm not endorsing him
That he is a serious
You spoken out of
Against Clinton
Fully on board
I know what's going to happen
The thought the thought that
He was having the reason that he was
Holding back
Was because he thought
That
The real the real reason was because he
He thought that
Trump was owned by the
Yeah
Now
That
He knows
To put Hillary
Jail
Exactly
No nobody
Well
I mean maybe
But so so bye-bye getting rid of that
All of his other objections
Bulshit
They work though
I mean
Well they were just
They don't matter as much as how much he hates Hillary
Exactly he hates her so much
But the thing is
Internalized
Massage
Like
Externalize
Well it certainly comes out
But
I know I know exactly what's going to happen
Like he's okay with the idea that Trump may lead us fascism
Because he hates Hillary Clinton
I would actually stated that was
Dirt during the race I think most Republicans would have agreed with
I'd rather have fascism been a woman president
Exactly
Like I can predict 100% what's going to happen
Cuz Alex is now open
The door
Then the door is
The door was being held shut by his concern that Trump was a shell
Ford
Right that's specific fear
That he's just there to torpedo Rand Paul
Right
Publicly done this trial balloon on this Sunday show
What's going to happen
Now that Rodger Stone isn't part of the campaign
He's going to show up
Kick that door wide open
He's going to
Reviews Alex
So Rodger stone is not part of
No
He's not involved in Infowars at all
Alex
Is going to be used
Like a f****** puppet
By these people a very willing pup
But
It's going to
Tubi
Harshest
Exploitation
It's going to be a combination of forces
Like my prediction
That it's the
It's the pechenik
And the Rodger Stone
Forget him on board with Trump it's just after the first debate
Are both
I think going to be accurate
And bumped me to f***
Yeah I don't like the idea
That what led to everything
Is just hatred of Hillary
Because that's f******
Boring for me yeah but
You know that
That is
The Jaime that's boring but that's also
Really the only conclusion
You can draw
Like like that wouldn't have been in my first couple of
Even suspect when we first started
I mean of the election
Oh
That's really the big
Yeah but he thinks he's on some sort of external I'm above The Fray I'm into
Cover stuff
He just hates Hillary yeah he's as bad as anybody in any conservative
Media Outlet as bad as anyone on Fox News
He's as bad as anybody is as weak
He's as
Lame
In terms of what
Drive him
Really
F******
Chimeras
Or something like that
How fun would that be
If it turns out that was his sticking point
Like baby Trump says something about chimeras in a speech
See that would have
Perfect amazing
Trump ambivalently said that Hillary Clinton has a criminal problem
Brett
He didn't even say it that forcefully in that interview
And that interview was terrible that's very bad audio and very short
Yeah this is before they kept
Saying lock her up
That's part of the whole
Yep
Sunday shows
16th
Caught up with a narrative yet
A lot of them
Doing the
There mirroring is
Dialogue
As opposed to what he's already shifted the narrative
There's there a bunch of people were calling in music
He's saying this about the clintons
You're still working
Together it's the same thing as when he said that Barack Obama birth certificate
He was working with them
Because man
They released
The fake birth certificate
The other foot fake birth is a
Convoluted
But at least his callers
We're not at least
But it's fascinating to see like
They haven't picked up
And I guarantee within a week
Or so
They will have
I downloaded the new operating system will be following exactly what he says
And it's not because he screams calls obviously
Obviously not
We've seen
The kind of people who get through
It's because
His listeners are so malleable
They're so stuck in believing whatever he says
But it doesn't matter
Trump is a shill
Trump is a slumlord
Trump is mob-connected
Either Pied Piper who could lead the
Alt-right
Not even called that at this point but the Tea Party folks the Patriots
You could lead us to fascism
All that stuff is being mirrored back to him by collars
You shift the narrative
They go right back
If they're going to follow him
This this thing like
It's so much
The the exact
Fun of cancer
Like you and I both were like
There's something there maybe there's some invest
More than just put this
Yeah this pivot is the thing that bums both of us out
Super bummer
How much better world are how much more fun world we live in
Seattle is like a black
Or something like that
No
But it does speak to underlying societal issues
Right but like most conspiracy theories do
I still think
A hundred percent
The fact that Rodger
Gaston hasn't shown up yet means
He probably shows a very soon
Hates Hillary Clinton
And has forever
Hate the clintons
Insanely
Are I predict Larry Nichols is going to show up real soon again he's been absent
The program for a bit
I predicted now all of these
Influences
Will congeal
I will start using Alex as their mouthpiece
Tricking him in some ways
To not
Really
B anti-clinton
If they'll shift it to Pro Trump Rodger Stone nose
Like
You can listen to Alex a couple times and know basically how to
Trickum been around for decades doing it
You could listen to a couple episode
Tattooing
You can find like a couple things that he knows he can sweet-talk Alex with
And what's Alex's open the door
That like
Maybe Trump is for real I got to get in there
This is going to be our PR
Campaign this is going to be alright
Machine them longer with the Trump campaign this is how I can
Serve the interest of us
It's still I think
Conspiracy but
It's not nearly what I want
I'm sorry Dan
It wasn't
Showtimes
It's not closed
Not yet
Cuz he still not
He still not on Trump
2.07
Yeah he's not on Washington come back
So we do still need to figure out
Pretty quick
I think our next episode might have
Him turning into
The false prophet as it were but
There's so many different things about that
Like
This election
Is going to be
One of the most studied things
Also many
Stillman differ
Reasons
Like it's one of the most faceted like if it weren't
Going to end the world
It would be super fascinating to read about it
Like whatever our
Fish-people progenitor
Project
Study
That the mistakes
That led to their creation
Or the Anunnaki come back
It is going to be like
Maybe
One of the biggest things with
The Democrats
It not not like a
Sanders would have won or any of that narrative or
You know they didn't talk to the people they didn't go
Campaign in Minnesota
Michigan or Wisconsin
Like that maybe it really is the Democrats
Under s
How much people
Yeah
Personally
Not not like
As much of misogyny as a part of the
Hillary
It's metastasized beyond that certain way
Like you can hate women
Hillary
Clint
Piece of it
But it it's not
It's not like the people who hate her hate her because she's a women
The dental
It is what it is is it led to
It was the beginning of that
Yeah
We need to hate
Somebody
Hillary is an outspoken woman
Next to the president
Claiming that she was one calling the shots and stuff like that
Please narratives around her
Which are easy to push
Because of that
That's a great point
Just kind of sits in the background
Do you have Vince Foster
What the f*** are you talking
But all of these people
Hillary Clint
Yeah
Comparatively
I would say that
Like
If there was a
If it was if it was Elizabeth Warren
She has a better
Because they don't hate
Her
Personally
Hillary Clinton
Person
Trump would have a field day with it still like calling her Pocahontas and what have you
Stick nearly as hard
Because she's not
Hillary Clinton
I think they just underestimated how much
People-hater I think that's a big part of it and I think Benghazi to the
Fallout of Benghazi is going to be
Maybe a hint hint
Japan history
I think because of everyone thinking that she
Was running guns and
Man killed Chris Stevens like I think that might be the turning point
In terms of
What's f***
Everything
Propaganda campaign about
But he already didn't happen
It's hard to say if the hatred of her would have been his fresh
Because a lot of those other scandals are so deep in the past
And a lot of them were pretty easy
Like a lot of those Clinton Body Bags
P0131
141 through all those murders alleged murders
No debunk
A bunch of almost all of them
Suspicious circumstances
It's certainly are not evidence of murder
Arkansas side
I'm really bummed out
Redback Iced Earth
Appearance
But we'll see you next time
Score fight on Twitter
If you want to go to a website though you go to
Collegeboard.com
If you'd like to become a policy wonk
Put your name
You're able to give whatever you'd like on a monthly basis
Give as much or as little as you like we appreciate it
Great
Tunes libreview
Cuz damn f******
Is it right now
Bummed out
I wanted something
No I meant I wanted something other than the most
Basic acid
Explanation
Cuz like
When we started this investigation
Someone I could have conversation with somebody
On their way
Cleavage
And then we find all this weird stuff about him talkingshit on Trump
And it seems like there's going to be something
Natural talked about Hillary Clinton I like I like that
Just assumed correct
Again you're right
They're still investigating to do we don't know why he became
A cheerleader
But yeah Leroy Illinois to leave a 5-star review that says dan we hope you feel better
Android Facebook
If you want to join up a few things on there
Thank everybody who is already started to like
I know you
You've just taken
I'm really really bad
Some good news
Please anything
I know this is
Going to really cheer you
Damn
What
Alexandra Thurston color