Important
I have great respect for its knowledge B
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
What's fight.com
Search for the altar of Selene and Doug little bit about Alex
Emmerich
Jones
We are.
Question what's up
I've gotten back to make
In these buttons
For folks
Quite quite a response
Cranked out and sent out to people
But I've used this also as Anna
Excuse
Text Mike recreational time
While I'm sitting around making button
Sure I've been watching a bit of Survivor
Okay when I ran to
I'm starting at the beginning
It's better getting yes but I'm not putting a time frame on it
Episodes of The Tick
I realized well I've got this Amazon Prime account now I've never had access to whatever is on
And so I was like I loved season 2 of Survivor
When I was a kid
Season 1 to season 2 stuck out in my head as like being really great
I watched a couple other seasons
I missed a lot
And I missed
The time
And I really am curious where did it fall apart
Lie cuz I know who they've got
Everything got too complicated everything
The total mass
Yeah
It was
Good I think
Oh and so I started watching
From the beginning
And I have not gotten
To where it's terrible
I'm in season 2
And
I want to talk about it
Non-Stop
I have a million
Yeah oh wow okay why I'd started a little bit before
Like I have
I have so many thoughts
About all of this
First of all
Season 1 is amazing
Okay it's it's a very
Well done
There's an earnestness to it that like
There's a recognition that what they're doing is a little bit goofy chordae mean it
Sincere right right very nice
Season Two's A little bit
The little bit of a departure
There's a there's a little bit less of that to genuine
That Curiosity shoes
Well I think that I think that
If you cut like a first season really wasn't that
Like everyone being like who am I going to
And season 2 it's just like
Is it already is jumping into that
I'm going to throw this out
Coucher when people get to aware of
The metagame
I think that there's a lot of conversation
Wrong wherever we know how to plan for this is the right move
What happened in season 3 or whatever you do
Yeah
I think that is beginning to happen already in season 2 not overwhelming but it's
Like it's very different than the kind of conversations they're having in season 1
Yeah I realize wow
And the other thing to was
I don't watch any of these that's like
I mean what would it been like
This is pre 9/11 stuff
Yeah straight up I think that we're on like he's in 2000
Yeah we're on the season 13 hours
I was like 16 or 17
Remember watching it in like I had
Various feelings about various cast members
Re-watching it one of the things that really stuck out to me with those two things
First
Elizabeth
I really like Elisabeth filarski she was great
And I realized re-watching it that I liked her because she reminded me of the girls that I had a crush on
In church okay alright to really sweet kind of word
Track
And the other thing I did I didn't realize
Watching back is that there was this guy Michael
Who fell into the fire
And ended up getting evacuated got airlifted I watched it when I was younger he seems like such a leader
You know received like a somebody who's like
Is outdoorsy
Watching it now
Increase
Total weirdo so weird sucks
I had a very negative response
To him watching it
I am too I was
Just looking out for these people now
Turns out he got arrested
Good for running a Ponzi scheme
And in the process of the investigation they found c********* on his computer
That's what I've always dreamt of Survivor being more like those early years of Sasuke the the Ninja
Warrior
Just because like they would make a huge deal of like this is our 25th
Season
And there's only been one person who made it to the top of Mount Midoriyama
And it's like I've always wanted Survivor to be that where it's like we're on season 40
Two people that survive winter
Yeah yeah I think
I think in order to do that you have to really rich people's help
Steal the other solution is like
People died this year
Taken aback by it was like in the first season berries
Is not a lot of problem with food
Totally fine on rice
Richard is out there fishing you catching all kinds of fish
They have rat traps that they've created the eating rats
Yeah it is not a problem
Events season 2
It's a bit of a problem
But it's only a problem because they miss ration the rice
I feel like
That takes away from this
Being about surviving
That's it
So funny just because I remember reading this huge like
Oral history of kid nation or whatever that MTV reality show was where they put
Town of kids and they're all like 30 kids they're all like 12 years old
And the oral history behind it was they built a functioning Society
Producers will like we can't
We were going for Lord of the Flies but in real life
Looking everything up for these kids osher
We got garbage pickup why are you guys throwing garbage around like awesome
It's so funny to me that they can build like a we're rationing appropriate
Adults do it
A reality show there like 1 all the food
Yeah there was also like real fingerprints
Weird manipulation
But I didn't recognize
Watching it initially
Like there's like
1 levels of awareness of what's going on at the other camp that like people shouldn't have
Oh yeah
Producers are talk
It was a little bit like
All right I see through a little bit of this
More but anyway it's fun and I'm excited to see where it really falls apart
Buy like season 7 or something it's going to be a disaster
My aunt before she died watch
Every season of Survivor
Loved it so much she watched
Survivor and big brother knows where the two for her
And I just remember watching like
I think it was like season 23 with her
And just going like
How
Do you not want these people
Shot into the surface of the Sun and she's like that's why I watch
That's why you watch that you watch
Pool for summer
We talked about this too much already but blast point I want to make the experience that I had
Watching season 1 is that I like
Both of the tribes
Aiden watching season 2
Cuz I don't like either of these
Which is weird
It's not definitely not how I experienced it as a u
Anyway I will talk more about this as it goes along I'm sure
The Creator's new album
Friday
Fantastic
Absolutely fantastic
Jessica's last album scumfuckflowerboy
Was
More of an R&B album almost like a Frank Ocean album
And this one he gets right back to
Just doing straight-up hip-hop and rapping and he's so good
It's amazing
Especially his career Arc can you imagine being like four
14 years old and and then becoming what he becomes like a weird
Is wild
Look forward to an oral history of that one thing
That'll be great
I'm sorry to not spend 10 minutes on your brights
Thoughts about
I could have complexed thoughts but they might be very boring they could be
It will not be boring Jordan is all right
Episode today we're good we talking about June 24th
Oh s*** we're doing present-day episode I thought we were going we're doing
Present-day episode because I wanted to give Alex
The chance to have a more developed
Conspiracy theory about John McAfee staff
Call report is emergency brake
I was not compelling
But let's give him a shot
What's going on on the 24th Thursday
I meant it will get down to business on that before we do
Hello
Thorndike as much your nail polish
What is my spirit animal chernow policy wonk
Very much danger butter that Saturday about all flop thank you so much
Thank you so much
Jana banana
Yep yep
Basically 49ers at year airpods
Can't even start a podcast without getting a million dollars
You got to be a millionaire
Also
You know
Got to get heavy
Before we get episode
Is someone life is giving someone death
You can say that
Life is good
Yes you can
Is honestly every time you play I could
Could see it being automata Monday episode like you just says that exact same thing every new episode
2021 all right here's an out-of-context
He hasn't said it as much but there was a little stretch
Like a week or two ago where he was
Articulating that talked quite a bit
Cade
Got a golden birthday coming up
Golden birthday
Number of the day Renee Lynn
What are reach
Jack wanted us to wish
Cade happy golden birthday
My golden birthday I was 24
And I was a mistake
Hopefully KD let me where I am today but
Anyway hope you have a good one
My golden birthday was 8 and it started me doing stand-up
Aaj Ka Rick
Got a birthday coming up Ashley wanted us to wish happy birthday
Also is a sandwich
He's a sandwich sandwich
Elsa has a birthday
Happy birthday is a sandwich sandwich
Irwin Kansas Moses this is
This is important
Birthday
And a wedding
Coming out
There's a very important request
This is not guaranteed
But it I checked in on it
And Selene does give her blessing
Nicer yet there was a chance that Selena be like
Hallmark says is a good wedding gift
What's up
40 years
Also Raymond Joe
Baby newborn
And we like to congratulate Metal Alchemist I think that's a Fullmetal Alchemist
But I wanted to wish this
Baby
A welcome into the world and the congratulation
To ran into although unfortunately to give life is 2 kg
Let's get in today's episode Jordan
Today we have
Contacts
I don't have to imagine really don't that's kind of regular
Pretty Dura lyrics
Thankfully like sometimes you jump you thinking like
Is it going to talk about
The thing that I'm interested in sure
Namely
McAfee
And sometimes he doesn't
In this case thankfully he.
Well we've got the Red emergency
Radar scan
Background up
I need one thing
Assassinated
10 days ago our style that we talked about
Very famous
Emmy award-winning
The Grammy Award
TV news
That expose the tarmac meaning
With Bill Clinton and then attorney general Loretta Lynch
We shouldn't even tried to kill him
Commit suicide
And then he was found shot
In the head inside of Home Alone
Married man with two children
John
McAfee you I do very well
20 *
We haven't talked in the last few years because he was in a Madrid jail
Awaiting extradition
They will suicide myself they will kill me
Episode we discussed the immediate coverage of McAfee is death
Story in the context of Alex's coverage of the death of Chris
A sign
Because I want to lay the groundwork for a narrative Arc about political assassinations when he talked about sign
He was prepared to tell this exact story no matter who ended up dying
And regardless of how suspicious the circumstances of their death
Really work
Alex looked out in a high-profile person who is sort of associated with died not too long after signs coverage
We would be seeing the outcome that we're seeing now
If no high-profile dance fit the bill Alex
Could easily
You know just get away with pretending he never made a big deal out of signs no pretending
But it was a professional
You can really tell how dishonest that works
The coverage is because of the intentional MS
Reporting he's doing
Surrounding these two cases
For instance Christopher sign as far as I can tell never said that he wouldn't kill himself then
The comment that he was getting threats
That came from a fox interview from
From February 2020
He was specifically talking about the rights that it come quote
Shortly after breaking the story
Which is to say back
In 2016
You never specified who the threats were coming from and it could have easily been from mentally Disturbed
Pro Clinton or anti-trump individuals
Completely disconnected from
The two politicians
There's no reason to jump to the conclusion that it was
F****** Hillary making the threat
Alex's disorder distorted this to fit his narratives because it Infowars world
Anytime anyone dies by suspected suicide we wants to paint is the victim of a Murder
The same script as followed
I'll testify to the details of this case would neatly fits the ark
What type of he's already established with past case
Also sign had three children and many of the details of his life that Alex is getting wrong or just things that Alex is assuming
Ryan making out
The same Dynamic existing coverage of McAfee
Some of the details that are
Completely wrong included
McAfee hasn't been in jail for years
And it wasn't in jail in Madrid
The daily was in was in Barcelona
More importantly though is Alex's lying but the timeline of McAfee
The tweet that Alex's referencing where McAfee said he was quoted getting subtle messages from us officials
Posted on November 30th 2019
He said he wasn't going to kill himself was from
8 months ago
Alex needs to take these tweets and make them a lot more current than they are because the in reality there
Completely rational explanation
Nothing to do
With the notion that McAfee was the target of a globalist hits
By combining these sentiments that McAfee is Sheridan
In the course of the last few years
And pretending said them just
Before he died
I was just trying to create a persuasive
Eviction cell is audience
And that picture is exactly how Alex's started the show
The point in the messages that the globalist are entering the part of their endgame where they're going
In the stage high-level political assassinations of their paper autonomy
This mentality is so dangerous for Alex to be playing around with
Since it's one of the things in the past he said is a sign that the cold Civil War is going hot
And it'll be very easy for his listeners to take this as a sign
That is killing time
You've already got your list I've told you to get your list out there now it's time to enact
Spell playing
Ethically speaking this is yelling fire in a crowded building
No matter what the outcome is and whether or not anyone gets hurt this is just Reckless endangering activity
It's fine to yell fire when there is a fire
Cuz there's a fire people
You know you can help them avoid the fire right
In order for Alex to metaphorically create the appearance of a fire here he has to lie about multiple details of these two men's death
This isn't someone responsibly covering the fact of a situation it's someone lying about reality to suit his purposes
Which is making money
Not caring at all who gets hurt
He's a real
Piece of s*** like I really like whenever I used to work
Customer service you can have those macro responses that you
He's pretty written responses it's almost
When McAfee died he was almost like
Boom Madlibs I'm already ready
I've been doing this for 20 years
Is pre-written
You know it's like fucoffee bottles that are like
I can't afford that well Lord if I told you
Is it safe
It's sort of a branching
Video already knew was going to go down
So what are the interesting things about McAfee is death that isn't actually a
Nothing but some people on the internet
Having fun with it is the idea that
Alex's found it
Basically as you already know
Found dead yesterday
Pretty amazing and he said he got a dead man switch
Sound
The Deadman switch buried in
Talking about that
Coming up here on the transmission today this is all made up
It doesn't look like McAfee actually had a dead man switch setup because the way he's described his failed to become a real
Madea doll
He told an interviewer that he had a choice
Daily check-in switch
So if you ever missed any of those check-ins the dirt would all be sent to the media
That's not the same thing as him burying something somewhere in a bizarre and complicated
Cryptomages John McAfee is so
Aware of time that he's never
John McAfee has never missed a date
I've never been drug it out
Hungover
What's actually going on here is that after back if he's dead someone posted an image on his Instagram with you was just a big
Q right
After this happened qanon folks started
Speculating that the image
Continue the key to a cryptocurrency address
Show a map where all the goodies were
This is made up out of thin air and completely not true
There's meditate on the picture but from everything I've seen about the situation.
It's not a crypto key
McKay's Alex is just taking bulshit he or his staff read on a conspiracy blog or Messi
Message board
Pretending that he got it from
Some kind of
Navigate of process or imaginary high-level source
But he's trying to pass off a sanitized version of it to his audience
This is essentially Alex's role at this point
Find dumb s*** on the internet and tries to laundry to the point where it can pass is a story he could
Pretend to report
Inevitably this dead man switch will fail
Materialize and Alex would probably say that the global is somehow
Recoup dead or something
Then there's going to be this great
Magoffin out there
We could totally prove all of Ark
Conspiracies are truth only Mac if he's dead man switch
Hannah been received by the globalist or whatever
See this is a problem with the internet conspiracy theories they don't know how to have
Have fun with it here's what you do
You don't have any evidence that this isn't
The case say that they found trace evidence
Of John McAfee dick in his own stomach
Then why everybody's like a human leg out of a shark's stomach and everybody's like
I guess he actually followed through with it forward
The man who had one big left
Do on this
That was either though dick it's been done
News story of the day there's also talk
Fauci
Doing covid
Grouchy one month before the cupboard
Outbreak
Covid
Covid-19 vaccine program
Windows exact sequence
Understand
Premeditation
Total complete open-and-shut case
Everyone involved
Is lucky or they end up in a supermax
Frozen
Arrest of their lives
I decided to play a little game with his drop okay I was going to treat this story as if I was just a listener of Alex's show
Like what would I know about this story from the information that he's present
At this point
I guess that a month before the pandemic started
Fauci Direct
Get someone to begin working on a vaccine that's mysteriously a perfect
Covid-19
That's
Mysterious
And this is being presented as definitive open-and-shut proof that there was premeditation with a development and release the virus
I've not heard this
So I'm going to
Eagerly await Alex telling me more about it
He doesn't
That's surprising yet seems like a big story ruined my entire game but not
I'm going to act like a Alex's listener experience
B******* and you have no idea why or where
But I have no idea
The back to McAfee
McAfee
Mine really smart individual true American rebel
Why does gel cell in Barcelona Spain
It's 75 years of age infidel
World
U.s. government is
Suicide
Commit suicide
And I believe him
Wishing a lot of suicide lately of people that challenged the clintons and others
A lot
Not that it's a Clinton
Call Dad
Call it
My immediate response when my friend texted me about this was
Somehow Hillary I got bingo
Of course it was
I mean the other
One thing that I would expect
From John Mackey
The day before he killed himself to claim that he would never kill himself like
But even so
All of the stuff that Alex is talking about his old tweets but he's pretending happened a week before
No he is not
Neither is Alex does not matter if he is his best friend or something
This is like when somebody in your high school dies in the most popular kid is suddenly like
I was their best
Friend please everybody feel bad for me
God you're evil
So Alex plays a little clip hear of McAfee talking about the Deep state
I have some thoughts
Cheering from the grave
Talking about the political process on this planet
The Deep state
Is a
Conspiracy
It's defined as the people within the US government military who are in C
Secret
Please people
The Deep state
Is those peep
Within
The US
That are
Career employees
Cannot be fired by
We
Elect
By the Congress
The president
There are the FCC
The CIA
Securities and Exchange Commission
All of them can be fined RS
Control
Can they enact
Laws
No kiss
The cold regulations
I understand that Mike if he's a real hard-nosed libertarian in the
Nothing more than government regulation idiotic
Apparently the
Deep state of these government employees who can't be touched
No matter who you like
These people include according to McAfee the CIA the SEC the FCC and the IRS
And every single person who is headed those agencies
Is it for the past 10 years has been fighting there's a little bit of nuance to it
The CIA is headed by director who is nominated by the president who we elect confirm
Who are elected
CIA director reports directly to the Director of National Intelligence who is nominated by the president who was elected
Nothing confirmed by the Senate
Who is our like it
If the president who was elected
It so chooses they can replace even the CIA director or the Director of National Intelligence
I guess it would probably be improper for the president
To fire an individual CIA employee but through the chain of command if there was a
Specific legitimate Direction
The president wanted to take the organization they could do that by picking
The new director
So assholes but just
Data entry in El Dorado is the president fire gif
No reason he just wanted to see if he could Obama thinks you're up to
The SEC the security
Exchange Commission is run by a Board of Commissioners are appointed by the president who was elected and confirmed by the Senate who are elected
They're put in for five-year term
When he was running for office John McCain threatened to fire the SEC chair which sparked
The conversation about whether or not he actually could
It seems a bit unclear whether president could fire them without Congressional approval but
It would be a really big deal to try to remove one of these people
The SEC is supposed to remain very independent seeing as their tasks
With dealing with Market manipulation
To be best not to allow people like a president to be in the position where they could fire them without a really good reason
It's almost like for retaliation towards let's say one of their super rich
Which friends that might be something that you would
The SEC to be in Independence
Yeah it's something that you'd really need to
Try to create
Safeguards against the appearance of impropriety willy-nilly firing an SEC
Dinner would be
Imagine if you were is Senator with
Early information that a pandemic was coming
And you sold all of this stock before everything happened whenever we still at a higher value
That's something that the SEC would investigate and take care of
If they were an independent organization as we all know they are
ICC is run by a board that is appointed by the
President who was elected
Confirmed by the Senate
Or Alexa
This is also an agency that's meant to be independent so it's widely understood
The president could not just randomly fire an SEC commissioner
Interesting article from 2014 and Politico brought up a way that a president could still
Work to shape FCC policy
Well it's accepted that Obamacare
Could not fire the SEC chair he disagreed on policy
Zephyr teachout made an argument that he
He could still remove the chair from that position
And replace them with one of the other commits
This would keep the same board intact
But still shake up the power Dino
So while there's good reason that the President should not have the sole authority to mold and penitent
Agencies are there will there still things that
Can be done to affect change
The irs's Run by a commissioner who's also appointed by the president was elected in
Confirmed by the Senate elected
Arsene
Some arguments that suggest their president
Actually fire the IRS commissioner
In a lot of conservatives are really pissed off
The truck didn't do just that during his term went John tashkin was in that position
Similarly there now calls for Biden to fire Charles Reddick who's the most recent person
Fill the role
Being appointed by Trump into
Neither commissioner was or has been
Been fired in the reason again is probably the doing something like that requires a really strong just
Occasion or else it'll just look like severe corruption
The idea that the government is secretly run by these on elect
The people is a popular refrain among folks like McAfee but it fails to take into account that each of them serves at the pleasure of people who are alike
And the choices that are made
In elections can have
Drastic
Implication
On any one of these are
Renovations what are the big
Failings of our government is that
Trump appointed an incredibly corrupt person to run the IRS and then it would look like corruption if you
Just fired up
It's like Jesus there's just no ass
It's not
How you would want it to be it's unclear what level of Elections and how
I don't know
IRS
The Midland management or whatever with that need to be elected
Satisfy Maccabees complaint
The reason that it's confusing because it's not a real
Compliant you just doesn't like regulation and government doesn't want to pay too
A fine position to has but the framing of this argument
Modesto Toledo
Dishonest if you're if you're being like all their own elected deep State people we should reform it but you're
Your actual plan is like a we should just burn down the IRS forever and the building is gone and the government's gone
Just get rid of all of it
Don't frame it like you want it
And the point that you're making about like eruption still existing within even organizations that are
Intended to be
Independent
What is is
Is very fair
The different it's a different
Complain
Then the complaint that McAfee is bringing you and I are not in agreement
Mia
So
You know what else you're not in agreement about
Just about everything
Your resume
I'll give you the inside scoop
On
Good idea exactly was I was doing
He did work for
Guava different spook agencies
Including the CIA
Masa
Including Shadow government
While
He was recruited into it as young man
Intelligence level
And good luck sweetheart all
What
The rest is history they killed him
Debtor
Man
So what's the what's the agency you think he was in those above the
The CIA aliens Bradley
Treaty with the aliens in which case I guess they're kind of
Coco equal branch of universal government
I'm excited for Alex on on a
Very
I mean it's sort of facetiously but
McAfee is somebody who Alex can makeup
So many stories about
Yeah totally he can have a field day
I would buy would buy most anything right
Couldn't have
It's almost the ideal person for Alex to have
Die cuz now you can take total control over the narrative my best friend
Cooper let's do it all man you imagine how many things Alex can make up that McAfee told him
Conversation
I couldn't tell you before because he's alive and now I got to Spill the Beans
Government systems
I drop is going to be Alex's imagination
It back if he does
Three times a day Alex will claimed he's killed everyone
So Alex is a
Is is OverWatch
Teeth poleaxed you might sell
Let me just try to process this
Reason I'm going to be a I am here today
Because I am Pole
Trying to really cut to the heart of the matter so let me just
Put this out now
There comes a moment when the Tyranny really lodges is full of tact
It all the window dressing Falls away
Do you learn more in a daily alarm the previous year
More in that Zeitgeist that quickening
That acceleration
That
Apocalypse
Everybody is dying
New ideas coming forward
Death Rows of
The Old World Order
It calls itself the New World Order
Wanted to control the future of humanity
Everything I say is an inverse
They say they're the new age they are the Dark Age
So do you want a new world order
I think that's what he's saying we don't want the old world order to be the new world order we want a new world order to be the new world
I just grow weary of listening to this
Over so many different time periods
I and Alex constantly saying
You learn more in a day than you did in the year it's so many different times
It always
Seems to be like
Everything is
Isn't it
Intensifying now
Alex is the voice of the
The person who's like
This is the most important time in history ever
Everett healing that every generation has
Yep
Nobody nobody thinks the world is going to exist after the
There's a certain solipsism to every generation
That is kind of
Just so standard on Alex's broadcast-style it's
It's annoying
Yep
I'm so about a year-and-a-half ago it was
Declared over for Humanity
There would only be Lone Survivor
According to Mike Adams the health Ranger
Can't argue with the truth
Apparently vaccines are killing everybody now I don't know anybody who's got the vaccine and it's not dead
Alex makes a
Bold
Prediction
About what the world will look like in a year is it over
It feels like it might be
The mask
I bet 20 million extra dead people than a year
And this is just the start
It's all coming up today
Any year I guess we'll check back in and see if
20 million additional people are dead
In the United States
From vaccines and such
And then will I consider all of the people who are like you got to you got to just
Do you know how often is Alex Wright
Ivory
Ty Wilson right about it being a summer of Rage Devers on its over $40
Collapse
Gold is the only thing to buy haha yeah I think he's been right
Obama is going to declare himself
King use the FEMA provisional government to bring a Muslim caliphate
After the government before that was Larry
True that was agreed with him
That wasn't Alex original.
Yeah the ring in ballots from North Korea
Trudog
Through the Panama Canal and nobody
Check the North Korean shifter
That sounds true
20 million additional deaths in the United
Spaceman
He just can't even moderate the you know it's over for Humanity I mean I guess 20 million is a conservative number
Walter's over for Humanity right
Sure
Yeah I mean lone survivors versus 22 koosman
The escalation
Deescalate
Subways
A little bit later this route
Maybe more than 20 million specific number will check back in on that new year
How long it last
Alex talked a little bit more about Chris
A sign and get some of the details about
This guy Ron
11 days ago
Versailles
Christopher Stine dead 45
So they were coming to kill him it was threatened to kill anyone today
TV
Emmy
For those reporting on
What kind of sense does that make
That doesn't make any sense
The story about the clintons on the
Bill Clinton on the tarmac meeting with Loretta Lynch is so damaging to the globalist
That they have to kill this guy 5 years later after he reports it
But it's also supposed to be a story that would win an Emmy
That's kind of what I'm struggling with attention to the story
Entire media is like wow this is so good we're going to award you for rice
Shrek the whole media is
Controlled by the globalist an independent thing
That is a tough reality for me to
M2 don't match up
The reality is the Christopher sign won an Emmy in 2040
2 years before the
Clinton story
Bruise coverage of the shooting of two police officers in Phoenix
He also want an Edward Murrow award for some of his reporting on serial killer
Larson Phoenix
Alex just read a headline that he won an Emmy and he's assuming that it must be for the Clinton
Story even though that makes no sense when combined with other narratives that he's trying to push it at all
Cuz that's all we got
Just go after any winners is that like their secret duck there's a serial killers with that one weird thing you know
Exactly they got the treasure they all think they're doing it
That makes sense
Lookout Jon Hamm ever went one
Probably do Cranston
Stop with the Enemy Number One
That's all I know
We're just going to lose the Cranston
That's it
Yeah don't worry about Godzilla or
How many how many Emmys did Modern Family win
Alex talks about his own coverage
Of crisp
Resign staff
Jordans
In this
He wants to he wants to sort of change that the landscaper
What is prediction
Yes Papa
In the near future
Another prominent anti-establishment individuals
It's a message to everyone
Myself
Matt
Sound clip of himself saying that
It's not quite
He was saying that like
Maybe 2020 Patriot weirdos will be dead overnight
Me and Tucker Maybe
You're going to be a little bit more specific then
Anybody who
Might be
Hershey Everly related to a show
Right rice
In the past
McAfee does not
Outfit the
Image of who Alex was talking about
In that
That episode
Please clap
Man this is it this is where everything falls
And so here is
The clip of myself
Talking about this
A boy
10 days ago
The coal mines this guy was a big one
The next few days next few weeks
It's a message to threatened everybody to shut up
Tomorrow
Welp
I'm not sure what's going on with the control room today
Hell I don't even have an idea at this point
You know for me
Back up that clip
This again here I am
10 days ago with sugar on top
Okay so real quick
Before you respond
Gary's him trying again the Q that card back up
I am
10 days ago with sugar on top
This guy was a big
The next few days next few weeks
It's a message the threatened everybody to shut up
Tomorrow
Oh I understand I sent you guys a full clip and somehow you didn't download them
Get here earlier I got a review
Every single clip
It's your job
You're talkin about doing your job
That's all your complaining about having to work the job you created for your
There's that but I think there's a secondary thing and that is that like he's recognizing that the people use
Delegated these tasks
Doing their job except they are
I sent you a 10 second clip that he's 10-second
Maybe it doesn't feel like it to him
That is clearly the clip that you sent them
And if it doesn't say what he needed to say in the moment and is really mad he's laughing out its
He needs a time machine to go back
And tell himself to say what is going
To be best for his narrative because unfortunately he was talking out of his ass then and he's talking out of his ass now
Buying his bath heino
Oh I understand I sent you guys a full clip and somehow you didn't download them
I just got to get here earlier I got to review every single clip
On this show
There aren't many reset the show
You're the worst
I'm going to try to come back
Is all hell's breaking loose the wheels are coming off everything and
Cuz of this clip that you played
Really really really really really really really trying
My bestie
Alrighty then
Well that is not how long that was
It was
It doesn't matter I'm here and I went over all this and I've got all this news
What does it even matter
What
Does it even
Matter
The General Public
They don't care at all the time.
Wow
That's up from 20 million now
Whiny baby
Please throw in the Middle East throwing a little fit because the clip didn't say how he set it up you set it up to extreme
Extremely
Didn't match those expectations
I know
Instead of dealing with that being like well you know maybe
Baby I miss that that up or something used
Throwing a fit never was going to die
He's trying his best
So funny
What
I mean
How can you do with that
Fast how can you do it that fast how can you go from being like
The strongest we're going to fight this to Disneyland
This clip
I thought it was different
Everybody's got
Going to die
I think that
Good comedians
On stage
Will be able to respond to changing Dynamics in the audience
It's really fast it's almost like your job
Yeah it's like if you're on stage and you're in the middle of let's say a b or a story
And something happens in the audience so you need to respond to you can change
What you're doing in order to respond to that otherwise
It'll cause a wrench in the gears
You'll be doing a bad
Experience doing stand-up
Like don't know that
Don't get how it's even possible that someone could do that
And I think with Alex he has that skill but in this world in this realm and that is covering up the
The appearance of that doesn't make sense
With an emotional Outburst that's really severe
And seems real
2 people who are tricked
Take a decent to your bed
We're all going to die that covers up the fuk up
Yep. The dynamic in the room changed in
He's responding
Blaming it on the staff job
So talking about who cares we're all going to die anyway
What's what's great about it is that
Part of you if you are a listener like if I'm
Part of the Infowars listeners
Living through this clip
I am assuming
I like I like calling it living
Exactly
Alex
Does have the actual clip
But unfortunately couldn't
Play it because of
The impression that he wants.
It didn't say what it is he wanted
To have said
And part of the conveying that to the audience
Is the
Of the little
Petulant meltdown
Totally
Has nothing to do with it
It is nothing nothing nothing
What you guys
The same one
Actually get that out do that
Maybe I'm not supposed to be on there anymore maybe the show's most
Walkaway
Disappear
Yes
There's a hold it up
Do it
Play all people to fold out the system
Quit play love the death they love
Destruction I love being full
Because their followers because they're idiots because they're more on it
That's really what all of this has
Come down to
What is that
Literally there's nothing you can read into that positive than him thinking
People are going to assume I was mad about the quilt
I was mad about the clip
I got to tell people I wasn't mad about the clip
The progression of thoughts
You can hear while he's silent
You can hear them
In his brain
A hundred percent
Wow
People are definitely going to assume it was about that clip better say it wasn't
Is clearly
100 / 0
Unprofessional
Let me see if I can get out in front of me
Low Drop because he stole my food
Not about the
So he wants to cover the big
The globalist declaration of war against humanity
Going to do a good job for everybody
Comeback
No one interested in Rio
No one come in here it's almost like a
All day long
Once there's something going on it's like a
Asking for is to be left alone in the studio
Muckleshoot videos
Dial everybody
But I just I need to just focus
In my own little cocoon
My show
That's what Imma Try to do
Is the present now that he's like to distracted by things that are going on in the studio
Discover his
To do is drive I don't know
It's so now I'm not mad about the clip let's pretend it's not about the
The clip and it is actually about him being to distract
Goodbye things that are going on
That's still his fault
He's cultivated the work environment that he has if it's not conducive to him getting his job done
That's on him
Absolutely
I feel no sympathy
Just bring it back to to Comics like that that's like if you got the light in your likeness
I can't do stand-up
I can never tell a joke again
Or people like in the audience
Eating
Food affected by you eating I can't tell jokes
Subject drop happened and now it's
All over the show end but it's actually different
Because you didn't
Start the
The club
You are the person who made the menu
It made it so these people would be eating while you're trying to perform stand-up
Why did I get so many cracklins
So much
Yeah that's the way to make that analog
I don't know
I think that this is sad
To trying
Lanza he's got this this clip
He's trying to use as an argument that
Joe Biden
Threatening to Nuke
The Americans
You notified made that comment about our you know if you're going to
Having guns to fight
The government makes no sense
Build this up quite a bit about others like you
He's going to Nuke
Can people
Wright has going to require more congressional oversight
Firing let's say the head of the IRS or nuking the American city
Probably IRS
IRS2Go
Alex builds that up any plays the
The clip
Obiden
It does not say
Eclipse again
No Alex does a different move that he usually does
Mexico
Like sort of an argument at the beginning
Play music
Completely different argument weekend because it doesn't say what he says it said
Here's by The Imposter the stooge
The puppet The Pretender
Destroyer
Death Rides a Horse
Figuratively and literally
Literally rides on a white horse
Basically
Admitting interzone senile rage
That we want your gun
Don't worry I already wise we've got the news
Military
Is separate
From the American people
And that their plan is military action
As if you use a nuclear weapon
On a rebellion
Yeah that is ridiculous
The cities are
60% Democrats
Dominic thiem
Unless you meant new car major power production sites
Turning off the apartment access
They're already turning off our pipeline
Destroying our borders bringing in
Dependent populations they control
We got nude your separate from us
Second Amendment from the day of
Limited too
What type of people could own a gun
What type of weapon you could own
You couldn't Buy Canon
I was just say the blood
The blood of patriots Eno
C-nile rape
Move against the government
The tree of Liberty is not water in the blood of patriots with
Enter
Never been if you wanted you think you need to
Have weapons to take on the government
Uniden 52 maybe some
The point is that
Abilities unlimited rationally limits
What type of weapon that can be on
Buchanan
So there you go
The Democrat
You see a completely different
Point being made after the video because I had nothing to do
With the story that I was telling about
Always
Act militarily on the people
Add point that Biden was making
That there's always been limitations
To what sorts
The Weaponry people can own for safety reasons
Yeah that's just a
Mental abuse stay to do that and then
Make that Whiplash change as if you didn't
I think honestly I was just review the clips before he comes you know he should listen
Every clip
You just have all this dissonance going on
Sounds kind of realizes after pivoting to the side what fighting sexual point is
It's a response to that I'd
And of course you can
No crime is that
1 G
Readysub
Alex is trying to define a 50 caliber as a
And even though he even refers to it as a rifle
I think he knows that this is a dishonest Ark
Also in terms
The crimes being committed with 50 caliber rifles I was actually able to find a House of Representatives
Newport from 1999
Specifically about crimes
Committed with 50 caliber rifle
This report.
It's time to track with Alex's narrative
But part of the reason for that is it 50 caliber rifles are very inconvenient
In terms of committing most crimes
Most of them are so large that you need to have them propped up on a stand for
For shooting purpose
Which is why most of the instances of crimes associated with 50 caliber rifles in this government report are related to disrupted
Criminal plot
There's a piece of a West Virginia Mountaineer militia member was plotting to bomb an FBI office wedding
50 caliber rifle in his home
When it was searched
Exam
The majority of people mentioned in this report had the fifty-cal at home but would use smaller more convenient weapon
Pens for away games
Yeah yeah
Cuz cuz
Said Alex is still just lying
1 case
What happened in 2015 what a man and his son
Greg and Jason niedermeyer fired on a sheriff's office volunteer
Enid him three times
The officer lived but it's unclear if he 50 caliber that was being shot at him worthy bullets that I can
We hit him but wouldn't not unclear is at the 50 caliber definitely was shot at him he's at
Christ in his when he was fleeing in his vehicle
Is that is
That is functionally the most terrifying
And Candice ever existed
That officer had been part of an interagency group at it uncovered a marijuana grow site
Arizona where they also found a ton of guns and pipe bomb
An ATV was seen speeding away from their location and this officer followed it
What turned out to be the neidermeyer's home
As soon as he exited his vehicle they started shooting at him
I mean
It's upgrade tracks the only reason that you would have a gun that big is to commit
A big
Crockett right so it requires more planning
Not always snow I like walking into a f******
7-Eleven over with the 5th
In 2013 a man named Adam wickenheiser was arrested after shooting his ex-girlfriend's new boyfriend
The shooting the victim had called the police to say that way cuz her was on his own front porch with a rifle
And quote well cops were on their way dispatchers heard a shot and a scream and the connection shut off
So what happened is that he had a 50 caliber it and he was pointing it at this guy
Allegedly just trying to scare him that'll scare you
Wow that's not
Scary 2004 guy named Marvin heemeyer bulldozer with a
Caliber mounted on it
He was mad about zoning issues in city code so we went off in quote plowed the armor-plated bulldozer
Townhall
The former mayor's home and at least five other building
I mean in some ways
I respect that he shot himself rather than get arrested and the fifty-caliber wasn't actually use specifically in the crime
Mounted on his armored bulldozer so I think that couch
You're the only person running the bulldozer I mean you would need somebody up there
Evernote
There are plenty of other examples but I think the point is made and nothing
Is going to top a crazy homemade armored bulldozer
It just doesn't get better than
Just2good 50 caliber rifles are rarely used in explicit
Violent acts because other weapons are just as effective and easier to wheel
However they are very often found in as part of the home collections of criminals
Been there sometimes used in crimes
What Elsa saying is just an old NRA talking
Pinpoint that he's internalized is truth
Because he's an idiot and a zealot
Has brainwashed as ever any claims up the on the left
The bunch of Dante
I get
So tired of
Same argument
Being convincing enough
These types of
Like
If here's the thing
If somebody gave me an argument that I
New
Was the exact same argument
From the 60s
That they tried
I would say
We don't care about that idea anymore
We tried and it didn't work and these people are just like
I know
It didn't work last
But maybe it'll work now
And next year and the year after that and the year after that and the year after that and then they've been so brainwashed by it there's just knows things
I love hearing it they love
Tahir
Guns are the best
I think that's how you change a little bit of
Little bit of aesthetic
You change the shirt
That the wiring or whatever you can pass it off as brand new
I think Alex does a bunch of that
Leprechaun
Conspiracy
Culture like really
Does a lot of that work
Yeah
Yeah I mean though you've attended
Again it's just that macro all over again you know
You switch the Black Panther fatigues for a BLM shirt and you're just you're still like a their communist infiltrators
Did the Democrats are bringing in from other countries
To replace us
Sure we said that in the 90
Sure we said that in the 80
Are we said that
Shore we did that
Now it's
If you bring that example up and that's very fitting
Cuz at this point Alex
Gets into critical race Theory
God no I'm not even taking this seriously as legitimate
Argument
That is being made
What Alex is responding to is that clip of General milley
Yeah saying that he wants
To understand white rage
Yadunnadi understands you know he reads a lot of things about theory is whether or not he necessarily believes
Is there true
Shores value in understanding
All kinds of
People's perspective
Yes he said education is important
The conservatives
So Alex
Has some real problems
With
General milley
You're at some of the other
Brass
Anybody who does
Some say white people are the best and everybody else should die
Apparently they're putting a bunch of black generals
In charge because they're going to take the guns
And then you're racist if you resist
Black
Across the country
And the national
German 2.0
Is General Honore on record
War on white people and gun owners
Matter what you'll be a white supremacist
You don't turn them over
Always always
That's what you said
So yours didn't say any other
It's so funny it's just so funny
How obvious this is just because
The moment
People started talking about critical race
The conservatives
Reveal exactly why it's important
By reacting in such a white nationalist way
Immediate responses you're trying to kill white people hit send your likes to get why we need
The theory
Two little telling
And I think honestly
I would ask
Any of these people who are complaining
Sing about
This idea this Theory
What is a
They don't get an answer
Reference to what
The Theory actually is
What weather roots of it are
Anything other than white people are bad
That's all that's only thing that he thinks
This involves
Nonsense
You know Millie
Austin
Is generals
The traitors
Trader
They're planning false flag
Nothing
This country
250 years history has never
Traders
Exonerate
And Nelly
Austin
These men once they've been politically
Call Shirley
Economically
And he's in the criminal justice system defeated
Will be known as
The new definition of Benedict Arnold
Call Slugterra tax here in America
They're spoiling
They're spoiling to overthrow
And they're getting ready
To carry out Terror attacks that is there
Can be blamed on those of us they're loyal American
So yeah we got
I just
All the time
Conservatives are just
Empty of everything but whiteness and guns now
You do like
Dare you disrespect the military
Generals are all Traders and we should kill them like Jesus
Christ there is nothing
Is empty of whiteness
And just
What does a gun
I agree at least from like the perspective of this
This branch of the media absolutely
Insane nonsensical
But primalix specifically like
I just don't understand how he feels like he can get any purchase out of like predict
False flag
It happens all the time
NeverEnding
Prediction
Ignore that you've made last week and the week before
Outrageous
It's a it's like you got to update you know it's like when you've got an album and the release date
Keep getting pushed back it's like he's hitting the smooth alarm clock that is exactly what it is
Business news
Cuz that all just plays white nonsense
We need to get members of Congress in the military
And then
General milley General Washington General Honore
We want to start out with the American people
Frustrated trying to get business capital
Is that what Alex was
Maybe commercial
Somebody to work
He's fake mad though
So it's a Marxist plan this critical race Theory
God Marxist even argue that Alex is making a compelling defense for
My point
Which is that if you don't read or engaged with critical
Call Sierra Reis Siri
You probably
If you responded this knee-jerk
Then maybe
They're only because we immediately react in a way that would suggest we believe in
The supremacy of white people
Its side
It's sort of telling on yourself a little bit
Any continues
Seen it
General milley
And general Austin all the rest of these guys
Up there with just such demonic looks on their faces
Hateful towards Congress
Critical role
Siri that is a marxist-leninist globalist
Liberation theology
Did you read it
This is pure poison
I meant to say
AR white members of military have to be asked whether they're good people or not
That is so racist show evil
Was that
I just see the enjoyment of Millie and the enjoyment of Austin
Knowing this is our takeover plan in there in on
Conquerors
To see them abuse their position but
It's just it's it's it's
I mean
That that f****** refrain of everything they say we're doing is what they're doing
And then he says that all the white members of the military are going to have to be asked how they think
Not true in Florida all the students are going to be asked what they think because of the Republican Governor like
Stop saying that you're doing
Blood-curdling
Frustrating to be guess what on a national stage so you know what you know what gets my Goose all say
You know I have a line
In the sand
Critical race Theory should not be
Preschoolers
I honestly disagree you got to wrestle with those Concepts from the
Get eggs
You know you do
Clifford the Big Red Dog should be entirely about race relations people learn Edition
Preschool
Critical race Theory to preschool
How I do I don't know I don't know
Well I mean
Alex doesn't know what anything is
You still mad
True
Then we.
Preschools
That they're bad because they're white
Abusive
Infowars.com
I'm sure
The General
The capital was
Oh I don't think it's hard to figure out
Text the froggy election are right to do it
Help
White supremacist
All of America is
And you're the big
U.s. military
You got the nukes in the F-15
The shows the gun owners
I think Alex just embodied that thing
This is an example of why this is important
There you go
Critical race theory about teaching children that it's bad to be white
We were talking about
But this
Particular brand of Rage that Alex
Drawings of bodies
It is not all just racial
Sometimes
It's homophobic
Military
They're controlled at their enthusiastic
Fetishize
Nelly
And others
When they were all working against him just like
Dog Mattis called mad dog is he such a homosexual or whatever
But
That's who these guys are
What
They blackmail him with that
Mad Dog Mattis
Everything they say about a frog
Dog sees a madtree
Would a coup against the president their sacks
All American
Really was a Green Beret
Convince me by their fruits
I would say that if you apply the standard of judging people by their fruits to Alex's guests
I don't think he would like it
You probably have to disown all of them
I think you should
How old is Steve
Connect stand up to the
Judge a man by his fruit stats
Apparently
You can't judge him by his fruits because you will be killed
Write his Global team
World shatterer
Fruits
But he's taking responsibility for literally everything every never happened to geopolitics
Assassination
Tons of that
Overthrowing governments
The coos
Not good fruit explain to me imaginary fruits of my
It's like
Steve pieczenik is the only person who is actively claimed to have already committed koos
And I'm here
Supposed to sit here and be like
The people who work for the government are starting a coup
Me and the person who commits
Coues rap
He's doing a koobits only because the other two
Counters are we on now
Who knows
How about Leo zagami has his first
We got the popo
Yeah it's so he is a Jesus apparently that's true
Good fruits that mean nobody's born better for its Benji's
How about Rodger Stone in his North Korean ballad boats
You don't even need the imaginary fruits of Rodger Stone
Enough about how evil that
Alex's recently made friends
Mike Lindell
He's got some
Interesting fruit best pillows in the world
Haha
Shark
Hello
Fruit salad
Is not not a not edible
Passion fruit and kiwi
Together to the problem though is V the army and
The services
Is that the problem
Wokeness
God you're just
White yes all you're mad about
Yeah
This is one of the satyr add pivots I've heard in awhile
It's just you can experience
Is a bummer
Cuz you're the one
Person with all the corporation
University
And a whole system in Hollywood behind you to mess with our kids
Text censoring everybody in the rest of it
Totally disgusting
Alright I have a plugged yet I'm just going to tell you this right now
Wow
Yikes
Oh yeah that's the other part of understanding white rage
Which is ultimately when you get down to the bottom of it
You just have to remember it's a bunch of people whining
That white people aren't running everything and everything is
For that
Yep there seem to be a bit of that
Talking about McAfee
Exciting
Immediate video that you put out the evidence that Alex presented is all that
Tweets
Just treats
Suspiciously
The next day we have a new piece of evidence have Alex's attic
Do I do well
He personally told me the last time we talked on the phone
Couple years ago
Before I leave strong in that Madrid prison for no reason wedding
Reset my brain
A.m.
Barcelona
And I said go check his Twitter
Siri said he would never commit suicide
Wait
You said
Yeah he told
Do you don't need the Twitter
He told you first
What does the van that Alex now gets to have with taking over the certified personal stories
There's just enough
Connection between them.
Plausible that McAfee and him have had private conversation
Just say whatever you want to be like you said that to me on the phone
We are gradually getting closer and closer to my best friend
We've been together for 30 years I was in Belize exactly
Define well-being
I'm really well we were close
We texted all the time
We were in a rotisserie baseball league
Houston survivors veterans
Yep
So Alex Compares this of course to the death of Andrew Breitbart
Alex is not brushed up on the Breitbart death narratives
Eddie confuses some of the details
Breitbart
2 hours at the hospital
Never say that they didn't say that
The media lie
He had information
Absolutely horrible
Motor good friends all the time
He said they might kill me their answer me
Follow me but screw them
Tell himself
Ugly to Breitbart didn't kill himself he didn't kill him know I'm saying he killed him
Alex is screwing up the details of
Conspiracy theory
The story was the Breitbart was killed because he had a video that would take down Barack Obama
Presumably evidence that he was a radical communist
Extremist
The conspiracy was never about Hillary but the real version of the Breitbart
Conspiracy isn't going to move the needle at this point
Hillary is more interesting in the satanism
MacGuffin
Breitbart had that needed to be silenced
Bounces just completely screwing up even what the
Does the stories were
I think it's kind of funny
I think it's kind of funny how most
Conspiracy theories about Obama have just
Faded
You know like they're all in the background now it's
Its back
The Clinton somehow yeah you know like that
Obama was President at your short while ago and you hated that guy but I think I think that they've been
Transitional lot of the Obama conspiracies into actually being Clinton
Yeah
It's sort of a sub-branch
Bostwick Landon has a connection to both of them so you can kind of triangulate there
But I mean it's just
And Bill and Hillary are secretly running me biting Administration
As well
Like the only people who f***
I hate Obama now or the left
We're the only ones who've gotten together and re-evaluated men like
We were
Still very much dislike Obama passionately
That the left
Have
Critiques and criticisms of a lot of policies that Obama
Infected
You could have done better about
And hippos
Presidential life as well
I don't think that
Any president is going to have
A real great time after their present
I think
Well I think his life to helping others
But I also still think that he took it on the chin quite a bit about
Denotes the economic
Impact as an officer I think that you're not going to ever have
Smooth sailing afterwards
Probably not
Mary middle maybe that's how many people should expect when they when they get in
Totally I get you get you get
Khushi speaking gigs but also
A lot of people are not going to like you if you're the president of the United States
So generally speaking it's something that maybe we should have our President should be in the
Sure
We are I just I think
I think
Your ear comment is is
Cool noted
I think the left doesn't
Hate Obama
They have
Critiques of him
But some might border on strong dislike and I'm sure there are some people who do hate
That's true
I'm just saying he's not the Forefront of the
The Brunt
Have a special place in their heart
Man
Yeah
Well it's because
Like the clintons were the big bad guys
The time when
Things were pretty fun for the bad guy Grant was really popping off at
Limbaugh was going ham on everybody all the newsletters and everything kind of secret
And they were in their clubs yeah and the groundwork has been laid so for so many years that
But they're still available
Easier to actually be a white supremacist or Nazi back then yeah cuz like
Didn't you just got away with it you and your buddies hung out in the garage and murder
Yeah you talk
The good old days
Alex seems to believe that
Pentagon has declared war
Shawnee American people
That sounds weird
Just a conversation about a guy having read Theory before but also
Dojo
Well that's a good idea that's a good idea
Boron
Yes
Be cool okay
That's really comforting to know
Sit out
Speaker
So a 9 is starting to kill
Anybody promise everybody to shut up
I have the real take over
John Didion South Vietnam before they had a big offensive
I'm not picking sides in that war I'm just saying
Wait what you're not today
Vietnam
When they thought was sympathizing
With the North Vietnamese
How do you say killing everybody Grandpa
Made the Vietnamese go get the fetal position and cry to Mommy
So
There's a difference you're not going to have
It's going to be here
Weather now
And they think we're such cowards
And when this attack against us
I don't want
I want this to stop
They're all Munoz the official battle doctrine of US Army
And the military is not America
I hope
I hope to stop at the last thing we need is any offense of violence
Wow
Well done God has declared war on the American people
Military to get mad about it
I don't want you to eat
Just keep your mouth shut
But understand this
2 minutes to exit
To sit there
We killed 50 million babies
We let pedophiles teacher kids in school
We how we worship the devil maybe it's God's plan
Wait
This is this is a mess okay
Alright
Okay
Pentagons declared war on America
He said that multiple times multiple times
He does point out he doesn't want offensive Island be cool
I don't want any offensive violin
2 minutes execution
The Pentagon has declared war on America
Okay
Energy Services
You don't want to you don't want to let them know that you're going to take over your car not absolutely not
It's 9:58 so what I want you to do is wait a minute and a half
45 but that might be too long
Okay
Just
Dissonance
To the point of
How can I how can I live in a space where I
Being actively murdered any moment now
And also also I should just wait
Be cool
I know it's
It's been an emotional state that he wants the audience today
It's just a
Beatdown
So Alex almost started the show covering news about how covid-19 Italy created in a lab
He's really close to do
I'm now back to my adventurous listen
Coming to this Azan
Infowars listener is this the story that Alex is talking about earlier
You know I almost started all broadcast today just wouldn't leave
Over the top news on covid being cooked in a lab released on purpose
It is over the top
Depending on who you are politically you won't be allowed outside
Wor
House under future lockdown
Has martial law digital passes
Caught outside without your phone tracking where you do what you do
You're permanently
Martial law.
Hell on Earth
So is this
Story is I don't I don't know if this is
This doesn't seem like
The same story but it did
The beginning of the key
I don't know
I don't know anything
This is a tacit admission
That the mark of the beast
Because he's even just pointed it out
If you're outside without your phone
They can track you and find you at any point
That's what he said
Oh so weird
We're done with the mark of the beast forever
He's proven it the mark of the beast is happen
When did happen
When the iPod first came out 20 years ago everybody go back to flip phone
Having a better understanding of what that story was
Bobcat
I don't know
How much time on it cuz he's got to get back
Do McAfee
Conspiracy like more details on how I
Deemed politically
Play correct enough
Okay 100 step-by-step process
Well the first thing is you've got to understand
The McAfee was murdered
Madrid
Yesterday
Walmart
What
Just so happen to happen
Homeland Security
Barcelona
Elizabeth federal prison that he had billions in b
Pointer
But we do know is his lawyer says no indication of suicide
He just talk
Talk to him
Hayes before
Alex is actually correct
Activity head of Homeland Security was on an official state visit to Spain at that time so I guess that
Improves it well he was in Madrid
Ed so naturally he had plenty of time to just sneak down to Barcelona murder McAfee and then
Sneak back us to Madrid country therefore you murdered him yeah absolutely no instructed I have no response
Noah murder happened in Austin and I am here in Chicago or in the same country I don't drop it yeah I did it
As far as Maccabees lawyer goes this is another classic case of Alex reading a headline in
Pretending that he's read the
There was a Reuters article with the headline quote lawyer saw no sign that software mobile McAfee would kill him
And Alex is assuming with the body of the article must be about how the lawyer saying that it wasn't
In reality who's lawyer Xavier villalba was the person who made the initial statement to Reuters
Maxis lawyer Javier Villalobos said that the antivirus software Pioneer died by hanging
It is 9 months
Prison Broad
Him to despair
This article is just villalba commenting that he didn't see any signs
Is that this would come
The pass
Villanova and Maccabees widow or pursuing an investigation into the circumstances of his death but
According to an ABC News article about the case quote
Although vilaubi said that he had no evidence of any Foul Play he blamed the death on quote the cruelty of the system
We're keeping a seventy-five-year-old behind bars for economic and not blood related crimes
After a judge has refused to release him on bail
It seems to me that's the approach that he's going with
In terms of re-examining
The death fine I mean in terms of
Incarceration
Let's take a look at things
I am not not for Mcafee sake but for the sake of the larger
The larger issue in
I mean I think that America certainly has some issues
With that this was in Spain
I'm not entirely sure how the
Spanish prison system is I don't know enough about it
Me neither and I don't know what I personally would
Be able to do to make an impact
Yeah I mean this situated
It's so unique just because yes I know I don't agree that a seventy-five-year-old should be in a
Prison
For financial crimes
And at the same time
It's John McAfee
If you let him out of prison
He's not going to be in your ear country anymore is going to be able to quote
I'm sorry
I don't know what to tell you
It out like there's no solution
Open for John McAfee
I don't have
I like a light.
Circumstance
That's with him
You don't like that
I just don't I understand that
You know there are crimes and
There are rules
Somehow those crimes are
We want to talk about
Different ways in which
Law and Punishment
Works
I'm open to that conversation
If John McAfee had gotten out of his Spanish prison
Because they didn't want to extradited to the United States Penny ended up back on his boat
I don't know if I would think that was the worst
He's a crazy old dude on a boat right
Play grated Maybe
He did kill his people
Baby
I don't know I think my my just immediate reaction to anything about this is just like
Everybody
Made their decisions and I have no input and I wash my hands of this
Specific circumstance
Is its own circuit
Smell if
The conversation that the lawyer is bringing up about
How Financial crimes are dealt with
Particularly in the case
If somebody was 75 years old
Maybe there's a conversation to have there
Just need to be because of McAfee should be because of
All-weather chameleons of people have been f***** over by the person
So Alex brings up the tweet
He wants to go over the evidence
Really just Refresh on the evidence of McAfee
And this is this is a really read between this is a pretty sad display on Alex's
Remember he said
I am content here
The food is good all is well
Know that if I hang myself I lie Epstein
No fault of mine
Refers to that prison
In October of 2020
So this tweet is really the Keystone of Alex's argument dishonest but Alex doesn't strive to put the statement in
The proper
For instance if Alex were an honest actor just trying to present the
You should point out that this tweet he does say that it's from last October
But he doesn't point out that on April twenty
Play 5th of this year
McAfee also tweeted quote
I've been imprisoned in Catalonia nearly seven months
I speak no cattle Annie and little Spanish so human contact is limited
There no entertainment
It's no escape from loneliness
From emptiness
From myself
That tweet alone presented
Departure from the map
Call Sadie was in when he posted
Did that tweet in October
I would never bring up this other tree because it calls into question the certainty of his predetermine
Conclusion
And selling that conclusion is
If the certainty is ever question
It wouldn't survive any kind of scrutiny and less you enter into the
Active scrutinizing
Already decided of the conclusion then
Yeah so they just
Do you got this
Yeah it's like hey eight months ago he tweeted I'll never kill myself for months ago he tweeted
I live in Despair and life is meaningless for me and I don't want to go into Escape From Myself
Actually it's like well
So Alex wants to read this more recent
And
Doesn't come up with
He's saying
My wife. My sack I guess I lost it
8 days ago
I want to go back eight days ago
Where the most important one is about
They may be planning to kill me cuz that's
The last known communication from him
Is that an age cutoff
Selected files on corruption in government
For the first time I'm aiming names in specifics
All began with the corrupt CIA agent
And to Bohemian official
Coming today if I'm arrested
Or disappear
31 + terabytes of data
Will be released to the Press
That was June 2000
19 South
There's a big
Motive
For him to die
He's trying to find this
Creep from 8 days ago the rice is queso he find something from 20
Because the 18 days ago was just like I like to the new Rick and Morty episode
I mean look
This is so important to Alex
He has to find this
I'll do it myself cuz it's my fault
I had it last night shuttle report on last night
Today
There was a message for Mcafee
Last week
And for some reason all the king's horses
And All the King's Men
Pull that up so I will find it
Just go to the garage
And I will give you
That information
I mean it's his last week
But did I take a sweater.
And it's just honest Twitter
My bad
Sounds like you're mad
That's it I'm done today
Let's go ahead and
Choir sings about vaccines that's the real
Important news for the body
What
Happening
I don't know the life
Is it this
I'm done
Time it is show this to pay that is like I'm f****** done
I'm getting to the point now where I'm fairly convinced
Text that your Truman showing me like this whole thing is b******* Alex isn't even real and their cameras on
Show me all the time because this did not happen
It's this is a lie it's outrageous likes me like I'm done
Twice in the same day is unprecedented
And then
Almost like
A parody of Alex's show for him to be like alright I'm leaving
Play that clip where the gate why are you can't you can't
Like
Apparently it's supposed to be an escalation and you can't parody
I can't I couldn't have thought let's play the game choir sings about back
I can't write that up with that I'm writing a satire
Situation he won
Aziza
He's defeated
So now he's he's transcended Beyond parody
Only the end of the second hour
Oh God
Twice in two hours hours ahead of blow up and threatened
Believer
Like okay does the end of the second hour I guess I'm going to go back in
1/3 hours just going to be special reports he's done for the day
He's back
That would be
I wish I did but it has
This all before the many hands of team
Your belief is not required
Remaining assets
Association
Yeah I regret.
It's not proof of anything
No it doesn't say that McAfee wouldn't
Commit suicide
You just saying
The US thinks he has hidden cryptocurrency not because they want to
Kill him for it but because he walk
He was wanted in the United States were Financial crimes related to fraud
Cryptocurrency
Speed isn't a slam dunk away Alex's pretend
This is little
Ransom
Thread to go off air and then convalescent
This is again
Again it's a nut it's a pattern of behavior
This tweet doesn't match what else is building it up
To be right
He had a lash out
Almost as a distraction
From
The reality being presented to his audience
What is narrative doesn't match the supporting Evan
Happened to Bocce
It's basically
Keep angling it's absolutely
And it's just so
Harmful it's
So harmful
I mean
How can you
What's you're trapped in that and that works
Like
What what argument could
Be made like if you want it's like a cooler keys I mean kind of
Didn't send it to a certain extent like if you want to communicate with somebody you have to communicate in their language
And if their language
Is consumed by this
Then the only way you can communicate with them is through this
You know what I'm saying
Depressing thought conversation with somebody who's willing to just be like
These keys were jangling so I'm going to let whatever information that I was going to talk about go
I think the humans are susceptible to distraction
And a lot of times
Then up we go on autopilot
A lot of a Time
We don't engage
The critical thing
Skills that we do have
Access to
When we feel we don't need
Right and I think that a lot of the time
The people who fall for stuff like this
Fall into these traps under
Distracted by these dangling keys
Or capable
Of thinking their way out of it
And recognizing oh this is what he
He's doing total I think it is possible
But generally the stimulus
That's required to get them to activate those critic
Thinking
Tools
Are they
Start ever engaged
I think it is possible to maybe I'm
Overly optimistic
Decor
Or naive
But I do believe that that is
I agree
Wholehearted and my best evidence for your point
Is that if it weren't possible
They wouldn't spend
Billions upon billions of dollars making sure these people
Never engage with
Constantly Reformation
What I would argue against your point
With
Angle other keys
The only thing that ends up happening is you end up just choosing a different
Laying of b*******
Like
The Alex keys are jangling
And then the qanon keys are jangling over here and
You get distracted by those
You don't really get distract
Did towards Reality Bites
Did that methodology
I don't think
It's unfortunate
Or at least we haven't figured out a way to distract people with real
Yet I think it's a losing strategy to try it's fine that
Don't seem like it's working
So
For the third hour Alex interviews a guy
From black guns matter
And
Okay I don't care
Okay there interview was
I mean the guy
For the most part there's just a bunch of
Complaints about guns but then also
Talking about
Black gun ownership in
Whatever
Find
One last thing that we have to take care of those that
I still don't understand that.
Story
No as a listener of his show
Going in
Right information that's provided to me by Alec
I don't
No
What the proof is
The falchi created this pandemic what you're missing
Is that the proof is
He said fauci created the pandemic
And then we talked about John McAfee dying all the time
So then you just know that's how she created the pan. Now it's would have gone to it if he had time
But he was too busy
Being pissed off about all those clips
He didn't say what it was he
Okay
Us confirms removal of Wuhan virus sequences
Database
Comedy channel
Questioning bluebird
Here
It is yesterday and I hate
Are sequences that request
Balance read any of the stories about this you would know that it's the policy of the NIH database to consider data to be the property
Of the scientist who submitted
They hold the right to withdraw their data if they want to and that's what happened in this case
Also that dude is still available online and do removal of it from the NIH database will probably have
Zero impact on any investigation
The virus
This is just like a catchy headline I guess the Dozen
Really is it sounds like it's
A bigger deal than it is but
I don't what I've been able to tell this is not
Necessarily a huge deal
Speedway
If covered by Outlets
Like New York Times like the story isn't something at
It's being ignored or
Or anything it's interesting
No I mean once it's on the internet
It's out there
You know it's not that you're not happy you can
Can take it off the nih's website but it
They're still f****** way back of it on the nih's website and the story in the New York Times
About the scientist who used
Google Cloud 8 a.m. sound
By all of these old
Things that have
Been taken down
No sure it's interesting but I don't think it
I don't think
It proves that
Fauci
Created the virus
So if I understand correctly the researcher
Took down his own
Research off the NIH website
He requested to be taken. That proves that fauci created
Did the virus
As a listener this show that's the conclusion that I'm black
The only thing I can think of
This is dumb
Man
What an episode
Beaches
F******
Non-stop bangers
It was like it was like an early Radiohead show just non
Stop it
All the time
Damn I got the Bands
I think
Okay so like most of this episode obviously is
McAfee nonsense
And
In terms of evidence
It's presented
Still just all those tweets
And then
Mysterious conversation that Alex apparently had on the phone
Definitely happened all of the conversation about that
Are misrepresenting them moving them around in the timeline in order to make things more suspicious
All of this is just total b*******
These blowups
Outrageous he's having a bad day
It's a real bad thing really pathetic
It really is like
When we get past making fun of it
It's so sad
It is
Hey man what are you going to do it's not our fault
He can't f****** handle is emotional
F****** impulses whatsoever and honestly if
The conversation that he was having wasn't about how like
The pentagon's at war with white Americans
Look at that wasn't the subject matter that he's discussing it would just be straight-up hilarious
Incompetent lashes out to such an extreme that when there's a technical difficulty
Dead boarded babies
And it's so fun to me to be like living in 2000
Free on his show as well
Because you get the like
Technical snafus that happened then and he's just like
Outfit trying to make it in a ton
Descend into these everyone's going to Diane.
Find a tweet be like an emotional Benjamin Button
Yeah he's
Aging backwards
Intuit child
Yeah man
I'm excited to get back to the past cuz I have grown weary of McAfee conspiracies
Oh yeah but it was a fun little dip
I will check back in and see how things
You're going down the line
I wanted to say one thing really quick without the button
The button
Situation
People
We're two tone sky
Skinny suspenders about tone situation up
What's the email address to send
Addresses to is K F business
Biznes
Yes
At gmail.com
The business right if we will send a request to other inboxes
Try my best
Make sure everything gets taken care of but
That centralizing the point where things are futile
The second thing that I wanted to say is this dawned on me when I was thinking about
It
We're not
Building an email list
We're not saving your emails not saving your addresses or anyting I was thinking
About like Rodger Stones weird website where you know I just want to reassure people that like we're not
Any information or
Are you not going to be getting any you're getting a button then that's it
I'm sure that most people listening to the show would never even
I wouldn't suspect it right price but I wanted I wanted to reassure people because
I got worried that someone might suspect that it never even occurred to me
Despite knowing everyone doing that
It never occurred to me for a
I started to put myself in the position of being someone who would
Send up email across my mind maybe
Is I'm going to end up getting spam or
I assure you that will not be something that we are
No every time we've done a comedy show and there's been somebody at the door like your email address we send out free tickets
It's like
Oh I f******
No you guys
See through your lies
There is a lot of promotional
Reason to gather those hit and we have no interesting
Made it abundantly clear by now
We just still
But
Also tickets for goddamn wizard her on sale at Saint Eventbrite you can find the link on
Twitter find it on Facebook
Thursday July 1st at 9 p.m. it'll be a great time we'll all be there talking and haven't
No autographs
Website.com
Please find a local charity or bail Fund in your area to help out people
Doing God's work until then I'm needle I'm Leo mdzs
Text Clark I'm Daryl run this one time John McAfee told me on the phone that he was going to eat his own butthole
Alex
First in color with huge fan I love your work