Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for this knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
We are the bad guys
Knowledge fight
Fight.com
Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones and Alturas away
Autopilot baby
Hey hey it's okay it's okay it's okay we got to speak
Don't have to come out of my mouth
No I didn't hear it at all I heard you say worship at the altar of the ciliated and then just let it go
So many buttons
Whistle
The pets that's where that live unspoken
Actuation
For you
What's your bright spot
My bright spot today Jordan is a lot of messages
With the request for buttons
So many that I cannot possibly respond to most of these
Yeah so please just know that I have read these messages and I very much appreciate them
And buttons will be sent as there
I've ever seen
Also here's your response
Send the message
Yeah that's right I'm taking a weirdly aggressive tone yes that is a how I'm feeling and also
Something that has come up a number of times that people wanting to pay for postage
Particularly international walks
Sure I'll pay you or pay something for both really nice thing but I want this to be a gift
Her folks
So I don't want I appreciate that but I don't want to accept that
Respectful to the generosity
And so if anybody feels the desire to here's what I would say
This is my blanket response
Feel free to give a little donation to a charity that you support or you think that Selene would support
And do it in the name of my cat
We will all worship at the altar of Celine eventually because that is the name that will be.
Donating to every cause from now on
That'll be good for the postage
For everybody
My bright spot was thinking about that
Imagine if we were like as
Wealthy is Bill Gates and you were just like our foundation in the name of the cult of saline
Conspiracies at all
Billion dollars in the name of the cult of saline
What's up with your B
What is Wimbledon
I don't know if you noticed
The past year has been rough
Yeah I see this year the French Open and Wimbledon we're only a month apart and I will tell you this
Inspiring s*** Dan Andy Murray
Andy Murray
DND Marie former member of the big four back when there was a big four and then
Andy was not kicked out of it former world number one destroyed injuries
He's old as s*** now
Back in Wimbledon
For the first time in years
One is first match
So did Federer
Coming back after his injuries
Wimbledon my friend the big deal
So anyway that's my boy
I got a lot of energy Andy Murray is in an amazing person
I understand that was like Charlie Brown
Debate that was just wow I could not understand a word you were saying
This is why I keep my love for both of us
I wanna care
Am I want to I want to join you the things that make you excited but I
I could not like my
Eyes glazed over like I should listen to you talk about Christian scholar podcast
Cuz I've interesting talk about it I'm like
I'd like me about Survivor if you're interested
Jordan instead of
Sneaky Snake
Wednesday episode here
What is the going into the mailbag it's been a little while they have a little bit of catching up to do
I'm so Steven London O2 give you a Thang
Thanks for the Department of Truth graphic novel
Also Jace
Some cool shirts
Cute shirts from Infidel meme where
And I went over their website to checked out some of the designs
Yeah every cool I think
I think there's one I may end up getting a hoodie
Olaf
Is that so
This is not sponsored this response
But thank you for the shirts and cool
Thank you very much also Keith and Laurel centacare package while back and I have been
Horrible
About getting a thank you and I really appreciate it thank you
Folks horrible intolerable and thank you very much
You so much
Also this is something that we forgot to do any I felt a little bit guilty about it
That was when we were given
Ukulele
Steven Universe
And I got it
Green's ukulele
Right side because a plant
I forgot to do was Beck's requested that I give a shout-out to Quicksilver on the Discord
And I forgot to do that and I would like to right that wrong by saying
What's up Quicksilver
Quicksilver on the Discord
I've no idea what any of this means also
Hemming someone life is hitting someone death
You can say that
Life is death
You good
You're good
Happy birthday Gigi.
Hope you had a good one also Dexter reached out wanted us to wish happy birthday to Zoe
Oh okay
Zoe
I would like that you can't be named Dexter and wish you a happy birthday after opening with giving someone life is
I've never watched that show the referee
I do he kills serial killers
People
Cool I heard the ending was bad
I never watch the show you their also Renee check
Happy birthday
And this is this is one because Rosemary recently reached out and wanted to wish you would have to go pick
Also Renee says she's the best friend I could have it thanks for putting up with me happy birthday Rosemary unfortunately
Life is death
Do you like the password digging into the past
And we're going to talk about May 22nd 27th
Dealer got black
Knock knock knock
3rd grade stretch of time
If I'm going to be perfectly honest with you
There's some funny things that happened but you're looking for anything in depth I am
Afraid you're not going to find a few May 22nd not the best day of the year
22nd and 23rd a lot of it is talking about Bilderberg
Talking about the same sort of Bilderberg
Conspiracies that we've discussed over and over again
It's very boilerplate
Fairly boring
That's Thursday and Friday
Alec doesn't have a Sunday show at this point
Monday is a repeat
Michelle from the past week day
Back on the 27th
There's a little bit of
Interesting collars maybe but like there is nothing going on it is a
Wasteland
I like how we've gotten so far into the show that a Bilderberg
Conspiracy were like Jesus that's
Quaint
Back-in-the-day whole Bilderberg yeah they were scary back then no man Bill Gates
Bill Gates dyrberg
There's one thing about the
The people that he has
To talk about Bilderberg that I think is
But the actual conspiracies they're all just
The exactly
At the same stop
As always
I feel like a pertinent question that every
Opening of the shows
Just getting into blood libel today Dan
Yep 3 I'm guessing
Anti-semitism
What come quicker than you think
So we start here on the 22nd and
Not much is going on until Alex takes
You take some calls fairly early in the episode
And Alex
I think he's trying to he's mr. Brightside
He's talking to this car
I just wanted to tell you like what I do so like your father
Are people listening they'll do the same
Like I make like
Like both with
Stories
Your movies
+ 9
That's amazing
With wild apparently
People who
Open stuff for likes
My friends
If they even start talk
Me about it like they're girl
Girlfriends or wives
Give him a look
You know they're not allowed to talk
Who's my friend
Man
Don't blame the girlfriends
Yeah everyone's waking up and now they won't talk to me anymore cuz their girlfriends
That's very sad that is unfortunate
Pet his fat
I need
I need corroborating evidence on we're getting 90% wake
Survey response rate
Rasmussen polls look I remember back when I first started out my job
Ways that we marketed was with direct
Mail campaign
And you get like a .5% response that was BS
90% wake up out of this I got to know what you're doing
Yeah it's like if you're getting 90% response
Do something it's got to be like heroin
Totally sophisticated brainwashed
Actually do have a little bit of insight into this cuz Alex was talking to another caller
A&T gives out DVDs to people and he's like I'm getting a hundred percent response
From people hundred percent wake up
They talked about it and
The way the disguised
Defining that is that
Everybody who takes the DVD
Seems happy about it
But still there's a lot of people who are not taking which also means
Didn't necessarily
Watch it
Yeah I don't know if there's follow up with these people about
The content of it
I don't know
This color in particular this first one
Is it really bumming me out because
You can really see what this looks like in real life
You know what this looks like in real life yet
It's a friend telling me weird s*** and then their girlfriend like look
We can't have him a party
Are you really freaks out my normal for him totally
Totally
He said something incredibly rude because somebody challenged him on this freaked out because you're not awake
We can't live that way
That's not how we is that guy wants to be over there by himself
Listen to Alex
Also apparently extends
To digital
Stop with this collar
I emailed stories like when
Husamedin stupid emails with
No it's forwarded 1000
Sometimes
Emails
Email
Trip stories
Anna
Links with your movie on there I mean
You know that's a p
People I probably email.
Can I play go back like
20 respond
And most people yawn
I'm crazy or where'd you
My email from
You know that's about a half percent
Call
Definitely a weirdo
Is getting chain emails saving people's email addresses
Then when they respond how did you get my email
You keep sending them Infowars stuff
I would say that's an interesting
I will give him this
That is an innovation towards chain emails that I had not even considered
That you could essentially turn those into your own mailing list
Bother people for the rest of their lives
Yeah I mean
You could do that
You don't have to recognize if you do the your piece of s***
Yes there is that there is not all informations are good
Map South gets another call
Because got a bad question and answer
Outkast
Quick question before they break their it
Number told me that
The 9/11
User appointment World Trade
Employee to work that day ever hear anything about that
Go to work
So f***** up
I don't think it needs to be said that Alex is completely wrong
Lending credibility to Annex
Explicitly anti-Semitic
Conspiracy theory about 9/11 here
This is lazy sloppy behavior that only serves to validate the complete bulshit this caller is heard from his bigoted friend
Using his platform as a voice of Authority or certainty on the subject in a way that is
Torrid
You can very easily find the names of many Jewish Victor
Themes of the United live in attack
Somewhere on playing somewhere firefighters who died trying to save their fellow persons lives and Benny worked at the World Trade Center or at the
Pentagon
I can name specific names
Because I can
Find out
Graphic sketches
Many obituaries
I'm not going to get into specifics out of respect for those people's number
And it wouldn't change anybody's mind
This narrative was a baseless claim that is made to demonize the Jewish population
The United States
And imply some kind of complicity in the attack
How it should be deeply ashamed
Elvis
Can't believe we got to the very first
It's time in 2003 the
The Jews were blamed for something that they had nothing to do with
I don't think this is the first time even in Alex
The show 2003
And we've got there I thought that was
Bad
I I just think
He saying
Hey is it true that the all the Jewish people were told to stay home
Yes that is true it cost you nothing comes back
No no actually that is not
Yeah there's there's no other I mean there's just no interpretation of that that doesn't wind up with
The Jews were involved in the planning and the attack
And it's specifically
The
Capital V capital j
The juice
It's not like
These people
Not a group of them
The entirety of Judaism
So weird
So Alec
What's gets to First
Guest here on the 22nd
And the Bilderberg experts
I remember
So I never heard of this dude
Tony gonsolin
Yeah I wanted to learn a little bit more about him cuz he's not the Bilderberg expert that I'm used to
Tavern on
Wasn't in The Notebook
Other is his brother
When later time by Alex Jones is trying to look into a Bilderberg a story he pretty much always
The Big Jim Tucker
And then in second place
If you're available or had died by then
Alex to talk to Daniel estulin
Tony goslings not a super elephant name in The periods that I've left
Listen to of Alex's show
Tony runs a website called Bilderberg. Organ I will say that this site pretty quickly deteriorates from
Being about the Bilderberg Group at all
Oh if you scroll down his homepage you'll soon find a pic
Picture of Jesus as Che Guevara I was just on a shirt that he sells
The Lord's Prayer okay okay weirdly religiously Centered for what appears to be aside about the Bilderberg Group which
If I'm not mistaken and based on this interview that
I'm hearing on Alex's show was supposed to be
Political conspiracy
Things really fall apart when you get to the section titled quote my spiritual beliefs
Message
That is that should be
On a
Everybody's wall
Things really fall apart when you say
Here are my personal belief
This passage stood out as not sounding great
Any problems have been caused by some of the Jewish people's refusal to acknowledge Jesus as the Messiah
The root cause of many problem many Jews for example even Old Testament
Believing they're still God's chosen people
It seems clear to me that God cut off the Jewish hierarchy from his favor after they pleaded successfully for the unjust death of a
It's only fun
In the Bible the Bible where they wrote letters the rest of the New Testament is
Reading writing letters to Jews Jesus there's a there's a lot of
Conversation about who is or is not
Real Jews also on the website
Solo
Convoluted and
Not good
Do I say sausage is weird
If you scroll down a little bit further you find a list of Tony's 30 top movies
The Life of Brian
Sorry like that f***
My personal beliefs
24th favorite movie stupid they are
Great comedian I'm not kidding there's a big sale
What is wrong with the humanity it's a really poorly lay down
Confusing website and I don't know if it would even be helpful even if you did assume that he had evidence of something
Listen religion is the center of all of our problems in this life
This guy
Is my favorite
Anyways here by personal beliefs number
Four or five on his list was they live
Oh boy well that one actually
Play Tracks I didn't recognize a lot of the names of the movies and I am guessing some of them
But we're not good I'd be funny if they were all over it's like they live
The Life of Brian and then a bunch of weird seventies are for like Harold and Maude is up there they Shoot Horses Don't They
Everything Lee Remick is ever been in all of that everything by like
Sure sure
This way I don't know it's read over everything but it's
Seems like
This guy's a little bit unwell and he's a bit defensive about his positions
Razavi Judaism
So
Welcome to Bilderberg. Org 30 movies today
A lot of the stuff that he has to say about Bilderberg is all kind of
The same stuff you here
From just about any of these
These folks
You know just
Straight Talk
Powerful people are there
Let's let's
Imagine what they're talkin about
I'm sure I'll do this
A little bit of a fun Twist on it and that keeps kind of like a birdwatcher for Bilderberg
Members like is he teasing to get really excited when he was talking about how one day
One day
No one day during the Bilderberg conference
All the people all the Richie's
Who are attending the conference
Prince decided they were going to go to the Palace of Versailles
And they were going to just go with that or
And so he was like
Gawking it rich powerful people
He was really excited the David Rockefeller actually answered a couple questions from people into didn't seem standoffish or bad
I think you just enjoy this
Special really I don't see
Spirit security
I think you like
Following around
He's like a like a powerful group of people and I feel like we're in a situation where
Like
The Continuum is there's something
There's a very thin line between David Hayter and
Fanboy
You know like
There's a very thin line between like and I'm going to follow them everywhere they go and hope to catch
You know you like he was on that why he was riding it a little bit more than a lot of the other folks
Like the tacos are astelin
That seemed just to be
Either insane or full of hate
This guy
I don't know
Your Spears just a clip of in his own words
Let's hear Wilshire
The US entered World War
German
And
Any any other
In the future
It is true that for a brief time before the war prints Barnard was a member of the writer SS amount to division of
This is definitely not cool and I'm not making any kind of in
Excuse for a butt
It's usually a good idea when you're looking at a historical figure like this to judge them based on
The measure of a person's Act
Tiny
Not a tiny
Detail but a specific individual deep
Clearly did not support the Nazis in World War I actively fought against them when Hitler invaded the Netherlands in 9
His track record is fairly clear and he was fighting Hitler's forces before the USA
Even was
This is an instance of like something that's a true enough fact
It's been used to create a dishonest image in the listeners had
The goal is to portray Bernard as somebody who fought alongside the Nazis in the war and it's someone who's
Part of the cell
Division of Hitler's organization that's just not true
There's more complexity to this
Them
Yeah that's
That's got cirrhosis
His dad written all over it like
Fine
I get what yes
Your your fundamental basic
6 fact is correct and by leaving out literally everything else you can support your narrative
But that's not the only fat
Yeah Improv
Blueprints Barnard's a little bit less
Of a sympathetic figure than fourteen-year-old George Soros
Ben is much as he was older and he was a member of the
Writing SS
But
The totality of his actions during the war speak to somebody who wasn't not
On the side of
On the side
Of the Nazis
Ann's
I think
I think that at that point you can
Say all right this was a blimp
You're on your history
Deterministic of your character
And that's what this guy want
To present
That's because
You know he hates the Bilderberg Group and
One of the people who co-founded it
Canby just portrayed as
Man I want to Hitler's higher-ups right
Right now
It's one of the most annoying things because
You don't
Like I don't need
Help
Being prejudiced against
A prince like I'm fine I'm fine with that I'm not arrive don't like royalty
But you can't
Make me hate him based on b*******
That's not fair I like to correct myself Barnard
Don't know why
No I'm an idiot I don't need I don't need help
I don't need help there and you lying about him makes me then have to defend him which I don't want to do no
I don't want to defend a prince Royal teeth
Makes
Makes you need to
Hold on a sec
Secondarily it makes me
Very wary of
Whatever information you're putting out
Whatever information you have about the Bilderberg Group seems kind of
Sketchy
As if this is the level of
Backpage
Detail
Contextually right then
Why would I believe the rest
What you have to say
The rest of this is just you know standard Bilderberg
Conspiracy nonsense
Gossip
And
Bird-watching of
Rich people
Can't argue with a good bird watching
Skip back two calls
Discolor
Relevant to my interests
Stamatis of course whether or not Alex was
Fighting the literal devil
In 2000
Good good
Demons are loose
And their app
And they're in there doing the work
I mean Alexander have a direct response to that but the they're loose
I don't know what happened but demons got loose humans we had listened we had
Amanda Corral
Northwestern Montana we've kept all the demons there that's how we developed this great nation
One of ours and somebody tripped
Ruined the summoning Circle and now the demons are loose since there's just nothing to do
Someone someone's got to get a lasso
We got to go get a drive into a demon
I think we need The Regulators I think Nate Dogg and Warren out of
Need to mount up
I think
That this is an indication of some of the
Conversation
It is
Clearly just pretty OrganiCann
The natural on Alex's show
This time
Talking about demons being loose and what have you
Still doesn't
It's still kind of a nebulous picture for me
Yeah I'm leaning more towards
It's like they're being a real
Literally just religious
Bible agreement closer to that
But I also don't have
Merely the amount of information that we do from the present
Alex legit thing
The shoot devil
Is is there if you pulling the strings of the enemy
REI mean
This guy
Sounds like you definitely believes that the literal demons are loose
This dude
They're doing work I mean you could still see that as a metaphor or you could if your Alex and your respond
That you could see that as a metaphor for the Demonic impulses of the
Elites are given free rein
No longer having to be corralled moderator
So Alex
Gets a lot of mileage out of people pretending that he's been right about so many things
For 27 years older than he is wrong and he's not
One of the things I was really going about this next clip
Is he makes a bunch of predictions about gun-grabbing
Everything he says is wrong
And they're going to expand
The most
He likes a lot of those people now
Yeah loves
At all those predictions are wrong
I was I was trying to keep track of my road no
Nope
And also no
Nope none of those happen
Yeah
That mean he's
Bright most of the time
Sure this makes 12 Alex goes back to calls
This dude
I tried
To trace this down
I got very little on this
Yeah
Okay
You're on the air.
Text Mars in
Over there off Highway 6
About the island
Arianism
I do not understand that
And I want to know more
Hawkeye haircut
Removed
And the old man walk out cussing like a sailor
George Bush
And up above
Pictures of
So I'm out
Hobby Airport
So first of all this dude works for a moving company and he was called to show up at a backwards hidden
Church to remove pews but somehow the only person there hadn't called them to move the furniture was confused. They were there correct
This is a little fishy
My second issue was that this was a 1988
This point George h.w. Bush was coming to the end of his second term as vice president
And was about to win the 1988 election for
I still flew back to Texas
Every Sunday to go to the hidden Church on rhetorics everybody knows
George W bush hadn't even become Texas governor yet
Even bought the Texas Rangers at this point
I don't see how that either would be in either of their interest to be running a secret Nazi Church in the middle of Texas where they
We're spending most of their time at this point in DC and campaigning
Iron device
President of the United
State and have been for years one of the most
Looked at
Observed and known where of person is at all times I people's schedule
If it's public
But on Sundays
Blythe Baxter taxes heads to the hidden not too chicken to church no one knows about it
Except for this guy but U-Haul mover who accidentally showed up there or something
Okay okay so you're telling me you're telling me
That this moving company
Shows up the guy is
Cussing like a sailor says you know whose churches is the bushes Church
And then
About grass of attitude wipes away and he's like come out back in the office let me show you George Bush in the Nazis
No one will ever find these pictures despite the fact that this guy seems willing to show them you literally anybody who walks in
Yeah it seems to be real neighborly
Hey this is the hidden church around 6:12 let me show you the vice-president Nazi memorabilia
George h.w. Bush and he specifically told me when he left it while I was watching over the place
I was to tell everybody. Everybody. Be sure you show the pictures of me
That's why I go to this church
Ridiculous
Also text Mars Izzy
Extreme Pizza
So yeah.
Hey
First person I got to get this information to
Not good notes Alex wants to know where this church is important question
Now where is this
What the problem is he wrote a hit you wrote about me and it's buckhead's are in the rainbow
I don't want to inform you about he didn't know enough
And
Okay is going highway 6
Right outside
Sugarland
Wright's only Eastside of Houston
Look man if you find the vice president's Nazi Church
You do always know where the vice president
If you will drive people by its
Pretty big
It's a pretty big thing
No I would
Find
Waze
Be like hey look
The main highways been torn down we're going to have to take the long way through huh
Oh by the way I met
George Bush's mouthy bastard he's got pictures of George Bush with a Nazi Bowl
I find it difficult to believe that if you did find something like this you wouldn't go back yourself
Not all the time please do go back if you like
Did I really see what I thought
This is Brigadoon
Outrageous
This church
What
Like I want I want to ask you like how you're picturing
How big is it what do you what do you imagine it but give me some give me some like physical attributes
But you're all right
I see it's eating maybe 60 to 80 people there about
There's a smaller congregation creation there's two rows of pews on either side with a walkway there
Where there's a Pulpit and directly behind it hanging is a
Let's call it 20 ft tall Nazi flag on his description you think that it's
The place that's in like
Good repair
Do you think it's something its dilapidated what are you what are your feelings on the
I think it has to have that feel of being absurdly
Clean for the area that it's in like
The walls are painted absurdly white almost as if they're immune to the
Nature around operating room in the middle of a swamp
Absolutely
I think that's probably about what I thought
That's a lot.
Talking about
Your call
Farm
Guarded
Bohemian Grove and there is a top
Terraria
I'm so proud of Alice
That's one of the few points
But I've ever heard him be like I can
Accepted
That isn't it
How great would it be to be like I'm on the phone with the person who found George W bush is not censored
I can't break this this is no good night sorry
Yeah I'm calling you a liar but I don't know about this
That's a that is a level of pushback I rarely see from them
True but I mean at the same time it has pushed back is not based around like
That's ridiculous so much it is like
Okay I get you think there's enough to base on the moon
But it's on Mars
I can't accept this
Nazi base on the moon can I never mind I have to actually push back on what you're saying
That's not fair
I think that would Alex is saying the reason that he's he's pushing back on this guy
Is because you think there are
Little Nazi enclaves
Nnn black worship
Ship centers or whatever
They're heavily armed
It's like you can't get into the Skull and Bones area where there's the big Nazi flag
Right there's not going to be one out in the middle of like
It is church that you get welcomed into
It's not it's not that it's like okay it's on the moon
It's all ours
It's the context surrounding this doesn't make sense
Psychiatrist and would not be that easy to accidentally stumble into
I broke into Bohemian Grove that's how I know there's you didn't break into this chair now you're welcome
And that would never happen surprisingly neighborly.
It Alex is narratives
Require
That
It's hard
To find the secret room
Answer that's why he's pushing
Don't think that it's
Spit least
I mean functionally it serves the same purpose as saying that this is ridiculous
No that's that's definitely true
That's definitely true
And I assume it would feel like it'll I like a bit of a personal attack on his manhood if you
Just got
To get Secrets by walking into play
Bohemian
U-Haul truck
I think it would just be so much easier to be like really
Seat 800
Why there's
There's a what
People who know that the entire Bush family is not these no no no
1 800 Bushman
The only bush
Church there's ever been
So
Here's a here's our last clip from the 22nd
Alex is talking about the situation in Iraq
Tuesday saying that
Confiscate weapons
From people
So Alex still think
On the 22nd of May
That the bath party is
Being put back
I came to power
And that's all the CIA operation
Isn't reading about how they're confiscating the bath party sweat
Well I mean I think
I have to assume that he just thinks
Stats
Window dressing
Suspect that the bad party is still running right right
I still think we have not reached
A point where this
Is interesting
It's still sort of rising it's crescendoing
Reality Alex
They're on a collision head-on collision
Traveling
Directly at each other
Interested to see how that how Alex tries to
Virar around that
That looming accident
Writing straight I can't hit reality so I'm going to turn off
And then it hits a bus you're like way to go
So a large portion
Of this episode on the 23rd is Alex talking to this Belgian doctor
Dr. van marter
Mortar farter I'm not entirely sure
He's a witness crimes being committed by our military against Iraqi civilians
There's taco
Bringing charges against military leaders
In foreign courts
Yeah that would be nice
I have little problem with this interview as a whole
I think this guy is bringing up
Fine points
But also it's not a very good interview like I don't think that Alex
Really
To too many of the more important
Issues in it seems like
The grandstanding and what-have-you
The subject matter is covered better by
Almost anybody else
Even in 2003 there were much better commentators
That you could find
Discussing
Human rights abuses on the part of our military in the Rye
But at the same time I'm not going to I'm not going to sit in nitpick
Because it's mostly this dude talking
Frightland
Perspective is like
Keith's awesome
U.s. soldiers shooting at an ambulance
Yeah and like
Yeah that sucks yeah that's
So so you think
You say that this interview is Alex like letting somebody give legitimate criticisms of the US military in order
Order for him to
Be like see the military and the government is all evil despite not actually giving a s*** about the war crimes and just
Exploding that the government is
Somewhat and then also using it to translate into like they're going to start a police state
I don't think that he's use of this stuff is
Great
So think like
The US commits war crimes we got it
If we should do something about it now it's hard to listen to 1003
That's it
Really weird to me it's really weird to remember 2000
And hear that Alex was having a
Belgian doctor on to reveal us war crimes and was
Is not
Like cuz I remember how bloodthirsty everybody was
Everybody was so f****** bloodthirsty
If you said if you went on TV and said like hey the American government is committing war crimes
There would be another talking head being like
That's the cost of War
You know and people would agree
Yes sometimes you have to
To commit war crimes
F****** have to live in a world where
Unfortunately despite his exploitative nature Alex was one of the few people putting on
An agreement fast about the u.s. committed war crimes is wild
Yeah yeah yeah it is
I'm sorry I just needed to not just feels like really strange to to live in both the present and the past
At the same time it's worth
It's worth pointing out
I don't think it's worth
Discussing this interview like actual clips of it but it won't work
That is a reality
MMA
Again
I think you can say hooray
To an extent
To him for that
Sure but there is still other voices
That exist that were talking
Think about these things
And they weren't doing
Things like the other things but Alex is doing
One of those things
Yeah I mean just in the context of that it is it is kind
And it's something that I think about a lot just because
That's part of how Alex got
To where he be
He got two
Is that
There were shitt tons of war crimes going on and be
Because
Theseus
Is correct
You are sucked into the rest of his bulshit until he just
Gets rid of even any pretense of giving a s*** about war crimes and then you're trapped in this place of
I neither do I
You know
It's weird
Yeah it is weird
He cares about more aren't those
They aren't
Exactly issues that he cares about for the sake of them
There's about the mezu
Is it means
And it's it's an important thing to point out that one of the big reasons that we are here we're propagandist
Can destroy everything is that
Cyclical nature between a
Corrupt
War crime committing governments and a propaganda Outlet who's creating that like
You can't trust these War crime committing people for good reasons until it spirals out of control and now
You can't trust anybody
Or anything I am sorry
I got
Lost on a panhead apologies apologies
No worries
What are the things that Alex does care more about one of the things that's really consistent like I said is that Build-A-Bear
Tony Gosling
On
On the 22nd
Talked about Bilderberg end
Go check out his website he has some
If your opinion
I would like Alex to put his top 30 movies
I died out
I think it would all just be Bolivian 1330
He has another expert on on the 23rd
Big Jim Tucker baby
20 years with
Daily News
Newspaper
Without me knowing
Willis carto is a Nazi and white supremacist
The Spectator was the paper's editorial position was anti-Semitism in Holocaust denial
Jim Tucker was the editor of that paper
In case you forgotten since we talked about him in our endgame coverage
Here's one of Willis cardos famous quote
Is Satan himself with all of his superhuman genius and diabolical Ingenuity at his command
I tried to create a permanent disintegration and force
For the destruction of the nation
You could have done no better than invent the Jews
Describing his motivation to start the spotlight
The ATL says in a bio of cardo quote
Cardos chief aim was always to mobilise opinion against
Jews
Liberty lobby with his chief instrument to bridge right wing
Constituency
Hard right or paramilitary libertarian
Conspiratorial anti-communist braces
Fighting flaming Durante government did nativists fears
And identifying Jews as the country's Chief threat
Willis carto is a bigot who wanted to sway public opinion against
Jews of his media
Entities
Jim Tucker work for his big media entity from its
Beginning in 1975
Until they folded in 2001
F*** him
And f*** whatever he has to say about Bilderberg
Yep even more insulting that he
Didn't know about them until Willis
Pardo told him about it
Goddamn
One of the worse
F*** gym tuck
Makes you want to invent a bow and arrow that can shoot arrows into
The past it's really funny to be those like
Alex is like a gym.
Climb fences and get in there
Is a real Intrepid journalist
You look at the videos of
Jim Tucker and he's always drunk
This is not a man
Man who can jump offense so without
Severely injuring him
He seems like he's exhausted reading a paper
Or at the very least
Continuing to breathe
So anyway Alex oxygen Tucker it's all just
The same
S*** except without the
Excitement at seeing David Rockefeller
1 things that I think is is is worth pointing out about both of these interviews
This is the gym Tucker
Is
Somebody who I don't
No
Well I and I don't care
What his personal positions are
He was the editor of a f****** whites
Supremacist Holocaust denial paper
25 years
Tony Gosling has a lot of question
Is about who is or is not Jewish
And thanks a lot of the problems in the world come from
Except
Jesus as the Messiah seems like
You wouldn't know that
From listening to their interviews
These guys are concerned about politics
Really powerful people getting together and talking behind closed doors
You would think that these are just guys who
Have a political love position that maybe is
Anathema with what the media
Wants to report
You know that's a maybe
Lot of anti-Semitism is what drives
Yeah you know a lot of people don't
A lot of people don't sympathize
With
This much
But what you got to understand is
You used to be able to just
Tell people that you hated the Jews all the time
And now you have to hide behind all of these things you know like that's hard
Let's just think about the knots
Fees for a second now they can't even say
Openly
Open the radio that everyone should kill the Jews cuz
Their faults
Brutal four-wheeler
Anyway we go to the 27th because
Both of us
Show is just that interview with Jim Tucker and then the interview with the belt
Doctor Who
Like I said discussion of the mistreatment of arachis
All that is
Find anything good
It's something that
There was
Probably
I don't know probably the right word I would say definitely
There should have been more space for
Republic conversation
But
What are the reasons that I find it
Kind of not
That
Interesting
Not that relevant
To give Alex
Too much of a pat on the head
About it is
He takes these stories
And he discusses or reads headlines about mistreatment
Of people in a rock the the civilian
I meant he just makes it about himself and the United States
What's the song
Horrible
And
Wham
Re-education
Wiring propaganda
Forget none of that
Came to pass
Here
Pesi suggesting
He's covering here at this is on the 27
And I we've jumped to that to Tuesday
Who is covering conversation about Guantanamo about the possibility of like a Military Tribunal statement
Place there
Saying that you know that plan before the war for
Do here in America to have these new detention centers and Machine Gun Nest
Now it is
Hold the conversation about
The wrongs of the war
Exist
In order to facilitate his narratives about his fears about what's going to happen here
It's not on its own Merit
The people there their pain
And what's being done isn't wrong because it's wrong
And I have a difficult
See with that
Yeah I mean you know
It's tough
The good thing
Is that
If I recall correctly in 2,000 and
The 8th
Obama fulfilled his campaign promise to
To close Guantanamo Bay right
That was like one of the first things he did
What
So Alex Goes to calls
What is pretty upset about is seatbelt check
Really
Really don't know
Yep he's not a click it or ticket
The devil with all of his might
Is a RAID again
And I can't
Text and a $70 ticket
Heetsuki
Talking here another another instance of him being totally right
But his predictions of what would
I'll check
Control
Melton
4 minutes
Gray uniform
BB High School
Inquirer
Reported last year
Building clearing
I don't know I don't think
One of the things that's wild is like he go back to 2003 in the world was so
Topsy Turvy
Because of the aftermath of 9/11
Probably could hear something like that be like
F*** I don't know
No I mean
The only thing that I'd like the main argument I would have against that is just like
That seems like biting off more than the government can chew how like
There's not the infrastructure in place to get everybody to wear gray uniforms
A Monumental effort of manufacture
I think he was talking about the conscripted use 1 uniforms
Do you got an outfit all these kids with submachine guns.
The gun manufacturers in the gun sellers are all
Used to explaining fears about the
People having
I don't think it's going to happen
No
Kernels are some of this stuff is stuff that I remember
Not being not sounding that crazy
You cannot hold on I've got their National Dress totally I remembered him saying people having that conversation
About like is there a possibility
That address to Maycomb back because of
The world circumstances
That
Level was like okay.
It's not that nuts right then attach all this nut stuff on it
Get someone to
I don't know
Except the nutstop
Because of the if I can buy something that is ostensibly not switches the reinstatement of the draft
Then
It's not
That much bigger of a stab to assume that there will be
Gray clad children with submachine guns patrolling my name
All of this because a seatbelt
Sure
So another thing that I was talking about
A bit is a there's a mad cow situation in Canada
Canadian beef Market is taking
Because of
There's at least a few cases of mad cow have
Fence covering is a fear of an outbreak
Answer Alex's is
Complaining a bunch about how you know you need
To get can't be feeding
Animals
Other
Dead animal
Especially sick animals
You can't be feeding herbivores animal Prada
Define pedigree
Yeah but I don't know what the answer is other than regulation
Well we can't do regular
I don't
It's not you just yell complains about like how people can't be allowed to do these things
How do you deal with this
Play my funk
General standpoint
He never brings up a solution other than people shouldn't do it
The free market
System if everybody wakes up if he's got a 90% wake up rate
Then the free market will I assume account for the fact that people know that believes businesses shouldn't be doing that
So all of these people won't patronize these businesses
That is
That is unfortunate
Seems like government regulation might be the only way to really could work
Barry Alex I have a call from a guy and he says Jesus a couple time
Just relax
Steel electric Wizard
Exclamation
Alex end the call
And this is just taking the lord's name in vain not because of that but
It's definitely what's on his mind
John
Call Ferb
Great points made out of
And we're on a Mini
I know we have a worldly audience
Be very careful
I don't want
Repercussions
What did you say
In the lord's name in vain I don't want divert people off
That's important
That is an important point
Wow cut
Jesus saves you got to buy my products
I got a trick deck
Boy
What
F****** red
Ridiculous thing to say
I worry about God's Vengeance when a caller says Jesus Christ
Yeah I think that's performative
Maybe
That's a little bit
So Alex thanks the audience
Here for
Cutting its content out
To the world make copies of his videos and stuff
Cuz if those things are going to spread themselves 94
Percent success rate 90% wake up impressive
Search that cuz whatever he's doing
Command you
Milwaukee
Myself
F*** you
Wow I'm a fan of that kind of framing of things you know
That's always really fun like if we hadn't
Been doing this week actually you you're supporting my show and spreading my materials
Has actually made it so the globalist
Can't pull off another
Yep yep
That's
So great that's why Mark why that's why Mark Wahlberg flies
On every flight he can all day everyday because he's trying to make sure that no more 9/11 will
Will happen and the only way to stop it is
To put a Mark Wahlberg on your plane and having Alex tell you how to stop it
We did it
I think we just fix terrorism
Can you imagine
What kind of a s******* you'd have to be to
Act like this
We could be like okay hey
Thanks everyone for supporting our podcast and actually I'm certain that there would have been another Oklahoma City Bombing total
Another Patriots federal building bombing if if you hadn't been supporting our
Who the f***
Play Lissie
Your support for our show
Made it so January 6th
Was not as bad as it could have
What could they were secured problem but we did it the problem is something that did happen
Alex is making up imaginary things
That didn't happen
Because his show is funny so what you're saying is
We successfully stopped
The attack on January 7th
That would be how you would have to bring okay
Okay
There's people who are saying that
The the war
Is a
Is kind of like a holy war
Yeah that's not good
No
6 that's bulshit
Good however
This is a holy war
Crew
Okay
Alright
Okay it is
Scientific
Fact
That God removed his
Texan over the United Way 911 Avenue
And that is why it's not a holy war
No
Because it's
Divine retribution
Also Alex
Does say now the people who are against
Tamara with the Devil
So I
I guess it's a holy war now
Right
Okay
I'd like him to scientifically prove that God protection was removed inactivate 9/11 happen
God's protection doing
Around the United States prior to that area
Did we never have any terrorist attacks prior to that.
None
Another call from a guy brings up scripture
Clunky way
I just found this to be a muse
Belleville New Jersey you're up next to Howard go ahead
Leaving reading in
Chronicles
Save the King you know
2311 Woodlawn
So
I don't know
Second chronicles 2011
Okay okay
Alright
Okay got a weird vibe going on don't know what's happening
Maps guys talking about Kings
Well the Chronicles are about the I mean their literal Chronicles of all the cool ship that the Kings did
Sure sure
So
Easy caller
Easy
What do you want to talk about
Story of the 7th and lion
The British crown
Oh no
Pictures of the mother and
Queen
Mother
Really
Well if possible
No he's not
But that's interesting
Because that implies
Is that Alex knows very clearly what British is realism is
Alex is aware of it as a concept he knows it
The thing
I'm saying
A complete ignorance
About
Which is a problem
But this caller what he's talking about is a book
Is about Prince Charles's brother
Is younger brother
The 7th in line for the
It's not Andrew to the other
Edward is the other brother whatever I don't like Royals
Biography
About him I don't think it has anything to do with British Israel
I am glad he's going is that the bushes are related to the British royal family
Well
I don't know where he's going exactly
Fair.
Bear
Color brought up the scripture in he's talking about anointing of Kings it is in the Bible right
Read this book
About the Royals and daddy look like bushes or whatever right
Mike down for this
I want I want you to help me out here
I can't tell if what this caller is bringing up as a satirical suggestion or if it's sincere
I'm not sure
You don't
In the Bible
It talked about
The testimonies
Navigation to manipulate
Constitution
Ditto in Germany to do I don't know why he was a complete bad
About
You know
23:2
I don't know what's going on
I can't tell like
I think this is a sincere suggestion that the caller is making that he's real
Poorly expressing
Sort of a point of satire like
Hey you know it's in the Bible do we have Kings why shouldn't we have Kings
Like being
Presenting that is like an over-the-top argument
But then again I don't know what the point of that would be like what what's the movie underneath that satire the satirizing the Bible
No I
I view this
As him being 100% sincere
Kind of feels
And I think the main reason for that is he's been reading about how great
Great Kings have been and how a philosopher-king is perhaps
The best type of government that they're possum
And that's decided that democracy is
Who's failed us
The Constitution is meaningless
And we should have a king
Also
And Alex
After a little while
Is going to agree with him
True
Yes I do think that Alex is come around on the idea of monarchy
At least
Specific sort of monarchy
Yeah weird weird that those guys were that'll to Alex being like should we all just
LiteBlue
High School
Lot of people didn't I would say I would say probably a significantly larger number
This is this is some kind of problem
For Alex
Much like the Republic of Texas callers
His craw
Fancy goes to another call and he's got to bring it up he's going to bring up this idea of making Bush King
Yeah yeah that's another
Don't put down
Just because he
What is a good
My family
Have two lines of Royal Blood
I don't know
Fought in the backyard at a house
This didn't go away Alex wanted it to
Chris is spirals out of control real quick buddy I kind of got the sense that maybe you'd back me up on this whole maken-ki
Anything is bad actually I am to Royal bloodline
Yeah that's that's definitely not what you would be expecting at mean if your Alex
With your Alex audiots I can't imagine you would get to
Pro-monarchy people in a row
That would be surprised
2 m
It's just like wow this is
Bad luck at full moon or something I don't know
Smoking description of Kings is literally
Don't hate the player hate the
The game
Something like the two Bloodlines I come from
No
But George Washing
You can park my backyard
My blood
I dated if the tutors heard I was bad-mouthing behind their back Alex
And said that he's related to The Tudors
Maybe they're related
Hey Kirby
So
Coming into the end of this
Is here and 27th Alex gets into talking a little bit about some new news stories about
Some SSRI
Issues who are literate literate
Becoming conversation
One of them is about
Dangers of withdrawal
For some SSRI medication
Although Alex
Portray it as just
Being on these drugs will make you kill people and I
Have you
I thought this was
Bizarre
Because Alex hasn't updated any of these talking points
These are all the same things that he says
When they did that
Mind control
Pittsburgh
Open
This is just
Exactly the same sort of stuff that he says all the time
Anything that I think is really interesting is that story about the butcher knife on top of a roof is also the specific
Example that uses yep
3 years and years
Is this one
Image that he has
Of of a case of somebody with a butcher knife on a roof
I think it was just deeply response
The definition of a nun nuance
How to take on
Psychiatric Med
Yeah I mean there's a
You know there's not much to say whenever it's like
Man when I was
In 2003 I was unmedicated
Just coming into my own as a type one Bipolar person you could see reality manned like
You know you weren't really walking just reading about it back
Then it was legitimately like
In the literature of bipolar type one was just straight-up like
1/5
It's the view don't make it for whatever
And its related to your mental illness
I'd like that idea of somebody being like well
You know what
Better than ssris
I'm feeling it's just like
I just don't know how you can
How you can talk to somebody who's aware of the death
Toll just being alive
Yeah
Yeah it's
It's a real shity giving someone life
Is in fact
Yeah there's a lot of factors and variables that Alex isn't taking into account here
Obviously any medication that people take isn't without risk
Living without medication
Pittsburgh
Some people is also
A great risk
And it's unfair to attack
Is medication because of the risk
Well not accepting that there is a great risk
Do not take
Can medication
And the f*****-up part of it
The f*****-up part of it
Is what one of the biggest
Contributors to that is let's say you were on an SSRI
And then you listen to a f****** radio show and suddenly decide to stop take
Taking your medication
And then your withdrawals f******
Blue light you up and you become part of the statistic
Did Alex is going to use the next
Sheer dry say that people who are on SSI right should immediately stop them
As part of his Avenue
I have to correct you cuz it is Alex does
Bring up that
Stopping taking
King meds he's dating
Well that's good
I don't know if it's enough
Dissuade his listeners who
Hear him say the taking meds
Make you have a bad trip or you're just be brainwashed
But he does
Actually say
Is that like you need to
Take a like a
Decreasing dose.
Wild fear-mongering about the meds I just couldn't let
That's not be sad because he does actually
It's good to say it's good to point out
Now unfortunately
Properly
So apparently
You should just pray
Well you know I feel like I'm worthless in like I'm a drain on every single human being around me in that
Every
A part of life would be improved if I were no longer here for it
But actually know what I should have just done drug gone for a run
My bad
While I was running
I definitely wouldn't
Fixate
On those very same repetitive thoughts that I can't get out of my buddies just pray that God heals you
REI
Man fights really worked for me when I was growing up on YouTube
It solved a lot of problems
Look I don't want
Like give any credence
Stewart Alex is saying but
Piano exercise
Can help people feel better exercising meditation are great
8 ways to cope
But that is not full
Help regimen necessarily
Dangerous kind of bad
I think
You know obviously it's not what I'm looking
Four in terms
Figuring out if Alex believes he's fighting the literal devil
There's a corollary here that does seem to think of that
Health can be achieved
By God giving it to you
Yeah so there is at least some kind of
Weird
Religiosity here
Yeah I mean there's there's definitely a an escalation
From metaphorical to
Jesus
And God having a literal effect on curing you
Which
It suggests that
They are real
Literally
And if they are real literally than his cosmology suggested
The devil is real literally I'm not positive that is an assumption that you can make
Because I think I think that a lot of people can believe
In
Literalness
Of God's existence
Without believing
Literally in an antagonist
Sure that's why I agreed with you that's true I think the evidence presented so far in 2003 of Alex
Celebrate such that you can't be like
I'm guessing his
Belief in the Bible
Is it does not include say
I also think that you can believe in the literalness of God and not necessarily believe in the literal
Wellness of
Prayer is a healthcare plan
You know like
I think
I think that there is a difference
Between
Those kinds of Engagement
With diligent
Absolutely
I think
I think you're seeing that Alex is at least
Clearly in the
God is better than Single Payer
A 2003 but I still haven't found a more like single pray that's what we do
I still haven't found enough evidence of
Literal Satan
Keep looking
Although this episode was
Bizarre I mean
Beyond just the boringness of it
Very boring
It's just standard at Bilderberg
Put behind that you have two guys who are
Appearances of anti-semitism
Who are the experts that Alex has on to talk about the Bilderberg stuff a problem
And it definitely merits attention
Next
The other thing that I'm seeing here
Bizarrely
22nd
27th of May 2003
Alex isn't talking about Putin
Well
Is conspicuous and a types
You talk about that
F****** Apartments
Instantly
Episode that doesn't come up
It might just be that he had other things
Talk about but
I mean I would get distract
To do if my guest
Notorious anti-semites in my callers were
Oddly pro-monarchy
I would get tossed out of my regular
808 Mafia Church in the middle of nowhere
That would cost me from my regular boots
Self
Yeah
Another other fish to fry at least I've distracted by those dangling
Sure
Will be back on Friday we have a show on Thursday
We do Thursday July 1st at 9 p.m. at the link
Collage
Available
Holdover button
Anybody wants to come out
Afrobull
Are in Chicago
Route something
I think that
We will have a feeling of
Is there an interest for sure
Face. Like if no one comes to this recorded in my apartment
I don't want that to be a threat
But
No that was very good that was a very good plan
We are attorneys that knowledge has revealed that go to bed Jordan Facebook if you would like
Bogota lost my mind
There for a second and then find a local charity will be offended
Until then I'm Neo I'm Leo I'm dzx like I'm Daryl rundus actually sound
Barack Obama's
Secrets
Baha'i Church
In Evanston
Text me just to Baha'i Temple in Evanston
It's not Secret
I don't think Obama ever went there
I just found this really cool velvet
Holding
Alex
Kristen color my huge fan I love your work