Air Jordan X swetik
I have great respect for its knowledge B
MoneyGram
I love your room
Acknowledge
Dot-com
Little bit about Alex G
Jordans
What's up
Which baseball today
Is forthcoming actually recording this
Sierra Leone is on Thursday and so this evening we have
You show
And a little bit as I was getting
Today's episode ready
And
It's so cool to be able to go back
The Lincoln Lodge where we're doing
And I was thinking back to my Early Times doing stand-up and what are the things that I feel really grateful for
Is that I was able to perform at the Lincoln restaurant
Were they moved
And
I just wanted the greatest
What a great like
Vibe an experience that was that room
And The Ivy
The chaos of
Going to Reggie's afterwards for a mystery beard
That was just a great great I feel very lucky to have been
You're just timing base
And I never did the Lincoln restaurant to be fair was a little early for me to have done
I might not have been fully
Might not have had a tight end there is loose
All the people at the lodge had more than a Titan
Tuesday value
In my memory
Anxiety nice to
To be able to get back on a stage for the first time in a very long time and it be
Heather new venue
I don't know but I've heard it's a nice place
Yeah I'm in my bright spot is the same little bit of a different
Performed at the Lakewood Lodge before it's kind of funny that I I did stand up
Chicago for 10 years in the only time I'm going to perform at the lodge
Just because of my
F****** D&D ship
I'm excited just because it's my first time back
Chuck because you started a trivia night
But basically
Your Escape calling bingo
Oh man
That would be fun
Marty behind me Swinging a mic stand around like a dick saying B24
Derail
It almost done almost two years now it's longer for you but two years is a long long time until
I'm nervous
You know I'm one of the things that make me kind of
Just stop doing it
You know slowly over time just
Stop going it's cuz everytime I would have a show I wouldn't be nervous or excited I be like
It was like I became one of those old Roadhouse
Just like I'm just
Resided where the office
Is dumb I shouldn't
Be like that store this is a new this is back to that you know
No it's cool
I don't feel that way
No I mean like I just barely have a pulse
Until like
You know
You're at your cool under pressure
I get it you're level-headed
Whatever
Self control
So Jordan today we have an interesting bit of content
Batman
And it will be talking about is a little bit
June 28th
I think that was really your lips
Spirals out of control
We go to
Just a total
That's alright total Max on Alex's part in the present
I'm excited to get into a 42 let's say hello
Does the new Wok
So first thank you so much
I believe that's a side character on peaky blinders
Wiggy figpin
Peaky blinders who haven't seen that you just know the reference I just know the name cuz it's a hilarious name
Mixed stovetop Stovall and his kid Mighty miles
I forgot to peaky blinders characters
The cat and I'll probably want
Rabbi Dave thank you so much and I'll probably walk
McKay is for Kentucky
Thank you so much you're in a policy wonk
That's the only Kentucky and Marxist I believe
The next person
Is that they challenged me to pronounce their last name cuz I think
Impossible
Charizard
Charizard Charizard
Like like a Pokemon
Alright spell the little bit differently
Charizard
Okay
Gave Michelle in our new baby Ellie thank you so much and I'll probably walk
I do very much to the family don't have any birthdays
Do today button
We do have a happy anniversary
To wish to Paul and Christine this weekend anniversary weekend
I was thinking about it
Alex is at given life is giving dad
Giving love is taking it away right
Literally all marriages end either in divorce or death
Forever This is Alex Jones's waves
No matter what your marriage will fail
I-17
Glad you asked
This is a good one
Actually
Let me pull up the list to see if I can give you some
Includes from around
That
At that point well at this point I guarantee something for anniversary of pool supply
15th is Krista
13th is Crystal
Yes
I'll give you this 18
Appliances
An appliance
I'm going to have to go with the light bulbs
Light bulb does a good guess
Longboard
Oh no
Wine or spirits
That's
Every anniversary
30th anniversary
Alright I got you survive
Sirius Scotch whiskey is what we're going for
Happy anniversary Paul and Christine hope you have a great weekend
Let's get down to business
Perfectly honest I listen to b of the show that
I just lost my patience for it
Entirely
Do Wednesday the talk about that because there was a big nose he had
Spell dying
Gabe Cosby
Just getting out
It was like this is going to be in Alex's wheelhouse
Because these things are
Are kind of difficult for Alex to work
Prevailing narrative
John Mackey
Kathy was killed by Hillary rights and Hillary also kill Donald Rumsfeld I hope so
Well but I mean like how is this going to work the gas is going to play
Yeah I don't know if it's going to be tough to fit into the
The matching game that he's
I've been playing up to this point
Yeah it's like I'm one of those XY axis you have that data point that's just so far away from the curb that you're like
There's just nothing we can do about that one
It's so important
Elsa as a person
Who is dying
Until I was
I was interested in
He seen that so I just jumped ahead to the 30th
Our hub
Play restart on the 28 years where Alex is at
Joe Biden is globalist Joe Biden wants to sell the country out
The Pentagon is
Major pressure
State to get
Is Allah doesn't kill you ice cream sandwiches
By the shutdown a bunch of our pipelines Biden's open the borders up
He told the illegal aliens as soon as he got in
He's working destroy the country
At least for now when it comes to stand
Administration came out
There's no reason to be there we are pulling out
That is good
Report
Good news
About Dubai
Yeah that's to be couched in he's also destroying the country.
There's so many people at the Pentagon who are tired of this
The American people that's a different kind of
That's the Deep
Satanic cult
Is the Patriot pentagon
This is a good guys
Compressor on bike
Right
Alex can't even enjoy like a good this is positive
Nono whenever
Are you have cast your enemy is the
Servants of literal Satan they can't be like well that one's a win-now what is the devil doing
Exactly what I have encouraged people to do
General
Yeah
So
Alex also gets into a trip
He's going to be taking this guy is going
All over the
It went to New York
Sure you'll be on a podcast
Or maybe talk
Talk to the attorney general he's gone from sea to shining sea
To be on podcast
Another trip
It's coming up just a next day on Tuesday
Critical
Information so we're going to be going to the Border but I got a call from my accountant this morning I went live
He said will you please
I know you got a Dory cost lot of money
Because you are going to the red
You need to really explain to listeners that
Hibachi shirts anandibai books films water filtration
Ocean
Or you're going to have to
Stop doing this
Not your fault let me have the products and the supplements you buy them
Herself
But we're not able to
Most the time
On the covid lockdown still the supply chain
Because we give you high quality vitamins and minerals in
We could get crap from China
But we're not doing that so somebody products we normally have a stock or sold out for
678 months
Supply
We're running the July 4th super sale right now double Patriot Point
Listeners fault
How are they not doing
Exactly what you want them to do
100% real conversation that happen
Alex
Tell your listeners
Money for you to go to New York need to buy T-shirts I need to buy products
Flagrant 2 did not translate to enough Salesforce to justify that to
So Trump is coming to the Border Trump is going to get
I do his Riley down there
I've got to go and try to get some attention
Everything will be fine if we knew how to operate our
Supply chain
The problem listeners is that
You won't allow us
To get through these covid embargoes that keep us from getting the products that you guys have already bought for us
This is all your fault
It seems like Alex
Is is
Trying to
Looks like
Solicit sales
By way of saying
You guys always buy everything
Except we're always out of stock
To the change should be the stocking
Aspect of it as opposed to
Trying to push sales
Well if you need to do have stuff in
Excel might be a bit of a
Might be what I believe
Bulshit
So
Little bit into the show something happened that really threw me for a loop
This was
Weird
This is something I don't think I
I've heard
Very often
At all Beyond
Does one take me to Driftwood instrumental introduction
What
Let me just get this out of the way
Because I'm 47 my mind still pretty Sharp
10 years ago my brain wouldn't have done this
A lot of things on my mind I was thinking about other stories
I'm just not really
Fixating on
Joe Biden
Mostly what I said
About
Pulling out of that was true
Trump policies
Trying to get the different warring factions to stop
Killing each other in Syria at least on paper
That's all tomato
But when I said that he was saying
Normalize relations with a side of lb station that was completely wrong
Pull that up and I was real
I was incorrect and I don't know why I said that
Sanction he was cautious Arab States and its normalising ties
With Syria's Assad
I don't want to water War least on the surface
Hoping for peace
Thank you optimistic
U.s. 12 allies of sanctions for those
Other always there so that
Is corrected
Real-time we are not like Brian stelter
Weird
That weirdo weirdo than the Undertaker coming out on its Wicked
Beats Pill
A lot of product to serial we see a lot of very
Pro-assad things from him in the past and this one seems really weird it's it's strange
I don't think that is all that weird that he has a pro-assad kind of mentality and editorial
Given a lot of his other beliefs
It makes sense
Like where he's at Evel dick
This is weird
This makes
Very little sense
Need to correct
Icanvas
Almost the immediate
Totally
I think it's probably just cuz
The glaring and ridiculous
Wow
Here is actually from earlier in the show him making this
Mistake and you can see if you listen to this
He even gave himself an out
He didn't leave the correct
Just last week
Biden told Saudi Arabia
Call Steph
We're going to put sanctions on you
Flip-flop next week
Like what is happening
Even says like you are going to flip flop back next week or they could be could just use that as like a way to ignore the
Never said that
Yeah
This is weird it's very strange
So one of the things I think is important to
Big noise about this is how this mistake
His maid
There are plenty of things that you can get wrong
In different ways
Princeton
Could misspeak
And this is your brain totally Kyle whatever
It happens
Another way you can make a mistake cuz if you get a fact wrong
Like you can save it
Played for five different NBA teams when in fact he played for 6
You could forget one of those teams or have got the wrong Statin your head and just never corrected
We all have tons of inaccuracies floating around in our head
Times we don't realize them
Until we speak them out loud and then we get
There's no real shame and make
A mistake like that so long as you're able to integrate the correct information when it
It's presented to you
I don't get defensive about like now
5 memes
No I understand I forgot that he was on the sons too that have
This is not the sort of error that Alex's make
You're nor did he miss speak
He read a headline
The story and then he went to commercial one of his employees
But he made up of
Complete
Eddie realized I better
GardenWalk that back
You can tell from the headline Metallica's working off of
Quota sighting sanctions us cautions Arab states
Against normalizing ties with Syria's Assad
Beer that Alex is making here isn't a matter of a fact being wrong he's got an entire concept wrong
The framework of the story is completely false
He read this headline wrong
Anywhere
From there
Talked a lot in the past about how is real gift is when it comes to analysis is being able to
Connect to the.
So I would guess what happened with the follow
I like to read the bible plan to withdrawal
Troops from Afghanistan
I have these Kim's other headlines Alex is trying to make connections to this story that could work for him
Pulling out of Afghanistan
Supporting Assad or two things that Alex
Can say Trump would do so he can praise Biden for doing them
And presented his Biden ripping off Trump in that angle can
Play on info
This headline announces reading is from an article out of al-arabia and there's no conceivable way that Alex
Could have read the article
And Come Away with the impression that was about Biden demanding countries normalize relations
Facade
Al-rabiah is a media Network that's run out of the egg UAE by a Saudi own company called the MBC group
Saudi Arabia and Asad are not on great terms and the paper is an editorial position that easy
Not favorable
Suicide
The only explanation for Alex you know haven't
To come out
I'll do this correction for this headline.
It is that he
Skims
I skimmed this headline in the news made up a story about the this mist
That would fit with the other stories that he's covering that.
And this may seem like a trivial point that I'm making but
It's not
When you're dealing with someone like Alex
Exude disseminate
Consistently shity information
What are the critical things to pay attention
Shinto is how the information makes it from the start
Pinpoint in a primary source
To destination is a thing that Alex is reporting on his show
If you do pay attention and read the primary sources that he's using
You'll almost always find it underneath his outrage
There's nothing more than him not understanding the subject he's covering
Often due to his unwillingness to put in the app
The epistemological process that Alex uses to create his content
He's completely unreliable
It is correction really well illustrates how this
Exact same everybody made here
It's whether you make stops
This one had to do with the idea that the globalist
Play nice with Assad though
We need to make a correction about it which is the weirdest
Yeah
The mistake
Isn't weird
Read a headline didn't understand it and decided to write a story that he tells his audience
This
Direction is f***** up did he feel the need to correct
So quickly and so immediately
Cuz it was
Technically
In some way complimenting Biden
No because I think that use is
Qualify
Your complement of pulling out of Afghanistan A reduced pension Afghanistan is there too
What is this white
Regular situation
If I had to
Put forth a guess I would say
That's not it
I think that Alex might be keenly aware that his audience is full of a sod
He knew that he would get corrected on that by people who were listening like
What are you talkin about
It does seem like this is something that he thinks
People will
Catch
It is audience and he's aware of that
And as such
Eunos
Bad like I bungled that one
Corey I bet he didn't even know I bet one of his employees
Correct
Wow I mean I'm just saying damn if we start
Kowtowing to Assad fans as part of our editorial position
I think we're going to make it
I think we're really going to turn into a big show
I guess this is what it takes to get hours to collect something
Yep that's
But halfway it'll first hour here he is
China build
Suspense by
Talk about how he's not building
Suspension
A story that he hasn't explained yet
In-store sure promise
Netherlands
Do you know I'm not trying to build up
It's on this but if I just cover this
Special Report on this after show today
And then
Nearby battalion
But I'm not going to release this information now
No big deal
Bad news
This is going to go nowhere no matter what
Cuz it's not
Wow
I was like okay I'm ready I'm ready for another dud
Sometimes it sometimes when you say he's
Building suspense
That's without actually do I feel like I should just be given an opportunity to like see if I can
Pull exactly what
He's going to say we've always
We've always heard this exact
They've like
I'm not going to build suspense here
I'm just saying that this is a big
Story if you guys want this big story to have an impact
And that's what we need to do this big story has to have a big impact yet otherwise
Bible need to let everybody know how big this is going to be
Yeah you could do that speech
Probably in your sleep you could predict what
The story itself
It could be any
Yap's
I'm not going to build
That's actually I'm just going to get into it now
Alright
Checkpoint at the
Car park before I get to work everyday and that's
I wish that was what it well
This report is just really really really big with a Time
I just hope this goes viral because it needs to this is such a big deal
If you read Klaus Schwab
5 books
And yes I've read all five of them
Bulshit
And the reason
Get so angry
I think you just don't like reading
Les Schwab is written more than
In five bucks
The most recent one is covid-19 the great reset which of course is the book that Alex has not read but is Bill plenty of conspiracy
Theories around
But he also wrote stakeholder capitalism
The fourth Industrial Revolution shaping the fourth Industrial Revolution
Modern Enterprise Management in mechanical engineering
2021 Global 19 covid-19 predictions
The aftermath of the covid-19 pandemic and then there's the annual
Report
Global
Competitiveness report
In a bunch of books is edited compiled and co-written
Alex
Now he would do better with Harry Potter in
Reset read any of the you like
Reports videos on likely
Lockstep
Document
Read a book
No you
This report
Whatever Alex is going to get into it something to do with Klaus Schwab
I guess
I'm not sure that it is
This morning's Dallin Barnes is almost as well
Stop it
Jeremy Barnes
Country in lockstep with the new world China
A major
Province of Canada
Healthcare
Hoop group's from gathering in order to stop the spread of unauthorized information
Criticizing
Love it
Breeders one dress
Information they were putting out is because they refuse to
Comply with public health guidelines during a pandemic
Killed million
Some people that'll do it
Also whatever is going on I have no idea how Barnes is going to be involved in lawsuits
Stop it like I don't think
License to practice in
Canada
Now he's he's a director of legal strategy
A bunch of Canadian lawyer
I bet he is underlying story there was a video that was going around from Nova Scotia
Dr. Robert strank the chief medical officer for the province was taking questions about the pandemic
A reporter asked
If there was still need to have an injunction
Cancel large Gatherings given the trajectory the cases were on
Bringing together
Continuing to keep an eye on it and
Situation
He also did say that the injunction is useful for public health because it was preventing the Gathering of quote
Groups that are deliberately spreading false information that creates
Risk
This probably was a bad way to express his point so I'm going to call this one and unforced error
Here and the surface appearance of what
Sakrete suspicions but
Anyone looking at
Contacts to your appropriately would understand what doctor
Whispering was saying
Yeah I mean the ultimately it's
So hard not to think that
There is a
Quite a bit that
Gatherings
Designed to spread both
Bulshit and covid
Of which there were some
Have a lot in common with our cells
Also this clip is from May 31st
DeSoto about a month old
This point
It was posted on a trump meme Twitter account called new Granada on the 27th
I got picked up by qanon blogs
Banda media Outlets like Alex and Steven Crowder
In the recent days this Twitter account is promoting the idea that the Q posted to John McAfee Twitter account was a crypto encryption key
They're also blowing Minds by talking about the Georgia Guidestones
Plugging Auntie mask
Shirts that they were selling
Sure basically this is kind of just a meme
Attention-grabbing account
That's a bit light on
Editorial rigor
Play some Alex sees fit to basis big Bombshells on their tweets
Yeah that's not good
Yeah you get one sweet you got a story that's all you need
I actually went and I found the full Daily Briefing on YouTube from Nova Scotia and it's
Pretty easily access
Very easily
All of them
From this the government of Nova Scotia are available
You can find them regularly
What are the things that's really funny about taking this clip and insisting that it shows some kind of evil government desire to
To control the public
Is that if you watched
The full briefing
The number one question is about their recent decision to reopen
School
Most of the conversation that's happening is Doctor Strang and Premier ranking
Defending the decision to reopen
Where is the feedback of the receiving is mostly about concerns that it might be too soon to write
Nova scotian officials words
The progress that
I've been made and how to keep that progress going
All the contacts that bigger picture is ignored because of that short clip that Alex can play
Includes one of the official saying something that's useful
The s*** head to want to derail all the work that's
Identify pan.
And
B b
Snooze
I mean
You almost want
That clip to also it like
If you want to say something like that
In a daily briefing you also have to
Did you start with
Goodness we're ending our tyrannical and Draconian measures
We are ending them there no more tyrannical or Draconian measures
0 tyrannical or draconian
Reminding everybody
No more
Alex
He will also want to talk about vaccines
Viet evil
And bad
And
The clip from official at the World Health
Innovation
And then
Clip of his own
Here's the UN director of The Who admitting their plan for more face masks that actually don't work
And then from 11 years ago
My analysis and others don't we're really facing
So the Clippers Alex plays of the World Health Organization spokesperson is just them saying that a vaccine alone isn't going to magically solve everything
Actual piece of the strategy but not the entire pandemic
Strategy on its own
This isn't evidence that lockdown to last forever or whatever
The f*** Alex is trying to say
Now ask for his own
Clip from 11 years ago
This is exciting
You sounded heard there's an entire agenda afoot to force the population to undergo
Different type of Medical Treatments vaccine we're seeing a medical parenting thing setup
Worldwide under the UN and the world
Organizations behind the Bilderberg Group
Carry out their population agenda and they want to do it through the medical system and that's why vaccines are so important
We know that many of these vaccines turn out that serious adverse reactions and this is being done by Design
They kill you slowly over time
I think you should really talk to doctor Reema Lebo she doesn't live inside the United States
Come up here and talk to you some medical doctor and she really understands what's happening on
Where's the doctor now
So Alex is evident to the stage conversation that he had
From Jesse Ventura conspiracy theory
It is a little bit like
The Undertaker showing up I will say that there's another Super Body
The funniest thing though is that Alex is telling Jesse Ventura to go find arima labo
If you don't recall Rhema labo is the anti-vax advocate who is married to General stubblebine
And the two came onto Alex's show to sell their laminated don't vaccinate me cards
Switch work grossly overpriced
Real good they were like 50
18 bucks or were they supposed to be about the evil the vaccination but couldn't
Stay on track
Can started ranting what other was a genocide against the white man going on
That was pretty early too in terms of like the right-wing adopting that as a talking point yeah
Trailing far behind
Supremacist to been on that tip for a long time
Rema labor recently gotten
In some hot water with the FDA and the Department of Justice issued a permanent injunction against
Enter to stop her from selling her nanosilver
Is a covid-19 cure
Associate outside similar tracks
Permanent injunction it takes it takes quite a bit
For those dudes
Get to work like that Alex's big
Bombshell was this nonsense
Small clip of a Canadian
Briefing
And then is evidence covid-19
Becoming Sewell I knew that Barnes was coming up and I don't want to listen to
The barns in Lake
Alex
Evidence of his Bona fides is
Jesse Ventura TV show clip
He said it was like I hate this
Can't take it away from him what about Rumsfeld
Is because the 29th
I was Alex
When's check in on the 30th
Guess what
Still host
What
Call
And gives a big Brie
Alright
Ladies and gentlemen
Awnry
This is going on
2 miles from me
42 minutes
3 boxes delivered
At least 7
Building one of them is 80 yards long Warehouse when
Tore something you just see hundreds of women and children inside
I'm standing there as a bus pulls up
Another bus around the corner.
People in cages
Do I get to that
People in cages with
Private Mercenaries
Catholic charity outfits driving border patrol buses with guns on their side
Really
3 minutes
Walking around here
Looking around little where they are
Mothers
And get this
Blonde-haired
Blue-eyed children
Without them
Without their father's coming up to the security guard
English
Mother
Please call 911
Wow
Wow that sounds like
Some pretty shocking video that Alex
Scott
So I immediately I was like all right Alex isn't in studio
Maybe he'll call in at some point and do a little dance but Rumsfeld or something
Sure
For his response to Rumsfeld
Recording right now we we do
Know if it has come to
There's talk of charges against the Trump organization
Supposed to leave imminent or somebody
The cfo's turned himself in today
Did you know I know that I look so probably haven't
You know how we're able to process stuff
But I heard this as like I'm not going to wait around for Alex
To call back in
Say something
Watch this video
Check out this video is Alex as evidence
Kids screaming for their mom
I mean I'm not going to not
Say that the idea that he would
Only say that there were children in cages at the border
Children
Steve
I'll just I'll just
Spell this out for you
The cages
I'm not actually
Mackage
Yeah a boss
There's a
Big boss that people
We're being transported as a door
Between
Where the passengers were
Yeah the the
Okay okay
And the driver section
Open up to disembark people for
From The Bodyguard
And that's what I was referring to
The cages there's no cages that he actually has
Any evidence I was in this
In this video
Him saying
Can you believe this
You will not be
Leave this right
Would like blood
Yeah
It's infuriating and honestly I think
This
Turned my stomach a bit
It made me very sad and fairly angry
At the same time
It's my job
And I'm not not disassociate from that sure
Get past it a little bit in order to provide
What I think is a really important
Teachable moment about this video
And I think that there's something that you can see if you pay attention
That is super in Port
So this is the way that Alex's setup
The clip
To our right this is 42 minute video this is what they
A lot of is exaggeration and embellish
But the selling point of it
Is he saw
Blue-eyed blonde hair children
Who are crying for their mom
Anime get with
Into the spider hole that is this charity
Does he not realize that he is
Is prioritizing literally the Aryan Master race in his mind as a
He has to know that
At least he knows that this is what he's trying to use as a trigger for his audience
Play there's no way that you do
So Alex is down there in
McAllen Texas along with his buddy Tim
I believe the guy want the gun store
I'm not sure is it one of Alex's weirdo Buddies
What may get there there is or what the video start
There's a family that is being taken to a vet
Out of this Castle
For charity
And
There's a bunch of people around
Short and Tim
Is
Complaining about how many how much is a
Security they have
You folks are going to be Tran
Transported
McAllen international airport
City of their choice
This is the third load being loaded up
That interesting thing is this is supposedly a Catholic
Security personnel
The dirt bringing out
To put this family into the van
You got one two three four five
Seven security personnel
Horton cargo for Democrat
Farm and milk the welfare
They're going to sign this human cattle up for this
Imagine 7 security
Okay on an hourly basis
To sit there
And transport these people make sure they're protect
They have all that security because Alex Jones and his goons are there
Is there to keep you guys from being like
Villager song
It's absolutely disgusting for people like Alex to antagonize people and create super tense unsafe situation
And that when people calmly responded provides
Security to make sure that he can't escalate situations
Do that security is now evidence
The people were being a mega Niger up to no good
The security is there
Because of you Alex
They're there because you showed up in
Bangun someone's car for attention months
This is the same place where he went out
The Catholic charity of Rio Grande Valley security is there because
Alex encouraged his listeners to show up to the charity and harass them
Who knows what they've been dealing with since then
Alex is the reason that these people are there because
He's a danger
Also I hate to be petted but if you watch the video you'll see that at least
Who are the people in the video who Alex
His friend Tim
He's calling security are wearing shirts
What's a Heartland Disaster Response
These people are volunteers who work with a group called Heartland response
The texas-based quotes
Compassion coordination
Center
You consult their website you'll find their mission is described as this
Heartland responses in emergency and Disaster Response organization focused on
Parent training and educating
In the disciplines of Emergency Management Disaster Response
And Recovery as well as other forms of Compassionate Care
Further the mission is
Facilitate Unity among disaster in crisis response Anthony's church
Synagogues
Businesses and individuals throughout
The faith community
People people putting their faith into action and helping people in a desperate
Situation so
It's not too surprised
Embassy people like Alex make them out to be filling
Yeah there was so they're doing that thing where they help people and that just doesn't sound like Chris
Anime
Not that nuts
Yeah that sounds wrong
Yeah so what
Some things that I'm actually I can't prove this and I I don't know
I kind of
Suspect that Alex
New when
Arrivals
We're coming in to the station
Because there are a couple bus
The show up in the time that he's there not as many as
You would like you to believe
But I would guess
That there is a certain time
Intake happens
Sure some of his listeners at least have like sending emails it sit out
Okay at noon is when people show up
He shows up at the time when he is most likely to get the video that he needs
To make it look like it's just
Constant floods of buses
Too lazy to stay there all day
Absolutely
42 minutes
The shirt is just wet t-shirt
Anyway
They noticed something is a little bit different
From the last time
That stay where at this place antagonizing and bothered
Covid testing
Area
And I would say that
Might be
Explained by another friend
Ramadan the BCP
Now the interesting thing is
When we drove in we noticed that
The covid testing site had been removed
Okay
So before boarding
Controllers dropping them at the
The covid testing site
Then the Catholic charity here would walk up there
Marshalltown
Marching into their facility get them plane tickets
And put them on planes to the interior of the United
State that covid test
Seaside
Is not removed
Which tells us now to naughty
Leaving testing for covid-19
So
Hundreds of thousands of illegals coming
Cross the border
Not being tested no background check be
Bean.
Turkey Point at
A few months ago around here and we see the man putting
Now
Reloading which is illegal
Again without child seat
The other vehicle
Go as well
So yeah
Dishes
Play total
Waving of the law
Really impressive how much of an upstanding citizen Alex's and I care so much about
Carseat accurate
Bringing in
Children
Border to replace the white race
And they're not even using car seats
Weird that you would think that he has a right to physically strike a person's car because someone wasn't wearing proper seat
It's particularly considering how in our last episode from 2003
He thought that car seat regulations were Trojan Horse and recreating gestapo teams of Greg uniform high school kids with machine
Seatbelts man says God damn seatbelt that's was going to do it I guess in the past 18 years he's just learned
Now you super in favor of micromanaging other people's decisions
I think it's great
Also
Everything that Tim is saying but the covid test
Thing is made of
He has no idea what policy these people are following and he's just assuming
No one is getting tested but he couldn't demonstrate that at all
Also shouldn't kinako
Care is anyone is getting tested
Like their whole pointed if not worth of the pandemic is a Hokkaido so I think it's a little disingenuous
Give a problem with immigrants not getting tested for something that you make money convincing your audience not to take series
You dick
Yeah there's that whole clip is just like what
We doing also
One of the other Hallmarks of this video on the main point
He's that
This Catholic charity
Has rented out a whole nother building
Big building Arizona Hollywood fashion or something to eat
Store across the street from their charity
Not possible that there
Who is running people through covid testing in there
No they can't do it really
No
Today's all the way across the
You could get covid on the way
To their they
It's got to be right off the bus there just making an assumption and Reporting it as
They're not testing anybody for
Anything it's it's outrageous that the sort of just leaps
But they're making an order to justify
What they're doing I mean the only difference
Between this and pizzagate is
I mean I guess slightly less
Implication of pedophilia
Or less
Close ties to Hillary I think I do know like this is I think
The other thing about pizzagate and this that is different
Is
What are the reasons that I was saying that is really difficult
Go to watch this video made me mad
Is because you see the
Yeah like with pizzagate is very abstract
And sure
Should I put crime scene photos liked Instagram post
From like Comet Ping Pong
Like had pictures of
People in them
Those were used as props for the conspiracy
GameStop
This video is really
Alexander using these people who are in a desperate
Situation A props
To make his narrative
End
Dehumanizing of it is is really
Bastard
By Alex
And that is really difficult to experience
Yeah I mean he's he's
Exploiting pain as
You know like he's he's just
I'm pretending that he's the one who's trying to help
Oh yeah yeah that's its really really really just
Taurus
Alex notices that
These people have
Disaster relief
Leaf written on their shirts
Answer keep side
It's to write a story about
Building
Disaster relief
So you know
The Texas governor has declared emergency
What do you bet
Imploded border
That
Biden
Created
We're going to have to look into this but
Again
They created emergency
And then they get all our tax money
To credit even bigger emergency
That's the plan
Exxon
Quotes
Disaster Zone
Ozone
On the back
Of the vehicle
Emergency Response Team
But disaster Zone
Set the Ender Alex on a placard that's in this vehicle this Advance back window
Response Team state saems
Support vehicle
I checked the utexas transportation
Encoding this could mean a number of things and none of them are
Suspicious
For instance of vehicle Gladys placard if it were a quote
Vehicle use for law enforcement purposes that is owned or leased by a federal government at
Or if it was quota county-owned or County least Emergency Management vehicle that
Been designated or authorized by the Commissioner's Court
You know it just gives the vehicle certain rights
Like the ability to park places and not get ticks
Or there's an actual emergency they can
Exceed the speed limit or turn left in Notre Dame
Intersection the vehicles likely owned and operated by the state of Texas and the
Catholic Charities question as well as volunteers
For helping with the process because we don't allocate enough fun
Keep refugees safe for people like Alex
This isn't a big mystery and the only thing suspicious in this equation is Alex
Said his behavior
Let me put you on this idea
Alright I'm going to throw this out there
What if
Alex
Is the literal Christian death
Okay wouldn't it be
Just like the literal Christian Devil's convince everybody it's crazy
Expect somebody would be trying to fight the literal Christian devil
See what I'm saying this is next level
Well I have a I have a reputation to that
Cuz we know from the Bible
The devil can quote scripture
And Alex cubis quote scripture quite a bit
So
Leave me to think that you could be wrong idea may have some holes
So there's a bus
The pole saw
And there
Alex and Tim
Stand
At the door of this bus essentially waiting for people to get off the
Wow there should be security
Get off the bus
People don't disembark
This could be the case you can see the one of the people inside the bus
One of the guards or
You know people who are escorting them
I'll have some paperwork
And it's possible there is need to get a couple things and get out there is some sort of a process
Need to go through
That they would have done as people got off the bus but because of
It's raining there doing it on the bus
There's all kinds of explanations literally have to have a customs form
That does happen is a someone from
Aviva the Border Patrol shows up
Is the people getting off the bus
They were waiting for someone who would basically be like a notary public
All these peoples arrival
It's because they are there
And these people on the bus who are the evil globalist
Don't want
There's something secret on this
Bus that they don't want people to see.
Something that I think is legit dangerous and awful
They were doing it in the
But now that we're here filming
They don't want to open the bus
13 don't want to dbus all these illegals
But that's why it's so important for America
They're going to wait because
We're here in April
You can tell that the media has not been cover
Illegal operation
And nobody
But now we all on Sunday
What they said
But now we show up
And now
To follow through with their plan
Now they don't know what to do
And that's why American
Need to get out of their home
You need to get in the streets
Need to come down
No
Alex says absolutely so
Totally signing off on this
Call for people to
To come stop
Yeah
Which certainly is not the kind of behavior that
It's a good outcome
Snuff
Also just
Spoiler alert whenever the people do end up getting off the bus and they do not go through the back doors at Alex appointing to just made
That up entirely off
A bunch of bulshit
That sounds like basically would have ghosts
Hunting show sounds like
You know like them just wandering around being like
See they won't tell you about this this is a cold spot that has been
Ghost hunting show
They're never liked now we need a million people to come to this house
Haha yeah there's more Danger
There's an excitement
That is involved in the improvisational storytelling Metallica's doing
What he's doing is he's coming how do I take the
The pieces of the things that I'm seeing
Create
What I would
Do if I were trafficking people that's where they're going
Him to traffic people and then assuming that that's how people would do it right and then ignoring it when
The actual reality
Is counter to what
Predicted Emily ignoring V
Tunis of how he would do it successful that dumb plan with
Definition
So I would say that watching this video
It's
Seems like people arriving
At
Compassion charity Center
Bedlam
Computershare this
You are the Paul Revere
Regal
This video doesn't in any way to fix what I would call Total bedlam
In fact
Around this point the video I was starting to wonder how it could be possible that this whole thing
It's like
Conveyor belt
Human trafficking where they deserve his huge flow of people
Alex has been standing
Yelling outside this bus for like five
15 minutes
And no one else has shown up
Junior be like a bottleneck forming
I mean if there's total Bedlam shouldn't you have in some way and inconvenience along the way to
Minor inconvenience it's raining
Somebody shouted 11-11-11
This is all coming off intensely desperate if you so much attention the last time
And bothered these charity people so I can recreate some of that magic to drive traffic to his site
But this just isn't a click
And one of the big towels
About how we could attempt is to be seen Alex
Does constant need to reassure himself that these people are doing something wrong because they don't follow seat belt rule
Here's he's there
Just hoping for a dramatic confrontation that makes him look like a big Brave strong American loving boy
But he's not
No he's just getting rained on
And the people were trying to help refugees are sick of his bullshiting are not engaging with him
My black walk back into the gun shop and apologized
It appears Morgan all over again that's good let's do that again
Maybach
Come on guys we all did good on that right you probably got some more donations and I got Drive everybody
When everybody wins let's make a fight so Alex exaggerated
Let's hear a little bit
We are here in McAllen Texas to 20 minutes
We've already seen more than six boxes for the Ford van
Deliver
And pick up
Holding a few minutes ago
Ali room into a huge facility that goes for 80 yards down
Leaving come out
Go to the bus station
That is right down the street
So
Dawn
I forgot there's another part of this video that like it doesn't play on audio well but like
Someone tells him that a bunch of people just went down to the bus station
I'm so there's a bus station that's like across another
Street catty-corner from the charity
And so he and the cameraman go down there like what
There's nobody there
They got away
I don't know what's going on exactly but I know that nothing that he's saying actually match
Matches the video that they're presenting
Courts
Alright
Immediately border
Disaster Response Team
Arm
Driving these buses
Children
That seems pretty extreme to be reporting based on
The
What what he shows
It does not does not match
That doesn't sound
No Heartland response teams are in armed
These children probably kidnapped
Yeah and you can even hear him kind of struggling
Describe it as you know he's trying to stay he's trying to improve his way into like an awful description of the
Horror that he's seeing around
And he's like
Car seats the Optics of it doesn't match what he needs and so he's trying to escalated
By way of Storytelling
And it's just
It's just saw that
This week
Alex finds the second bus
And it's around the corner on the other side of the building and this bus has people getting off of it there's is worth
Door back door front door
Fox News
Fox News to send a team down here
We've been here 30 minutes
Disappear out of the country
Busy people
What barefoot
Disappearing
That's a blond-haired blue-eyed little boy
Hispanic
Waiting on a baby
This is a place where Alex has spotted a blond-haired has decided to assume that the woman he's with his ass
Really nothing to base this on
Mother's wearing a mask and he barely even looks at her as she walked past him so this is absolutely
Sense of Alex just
Deciding
Improvise a story on the Fly where a white child is being smuggled by immigrant
There's another child that our two saying is alone is
Is there two different child
Children
But if you watch the tape you can tell that he is actually with a woman and another child he's just a little bit older the kids
He's walking ahead of them by the time Alex season
Hey decides to use them as a prop for white nationalist propaganda
Yeah that doesn't get much more white nationalist then just instinctively being like white kids stole
Going by somebody else
This is a humanitarian crisis
On the level of f****** every
Knox
And you know here's where this gets teachable
So this is something that Alex sees
And he's decided to make a big deal out of based on assumptions that he's making
That are not based in anything
Other than races
Well yes
But if you pay attention
You can see the story changing
That's a blond-haired blue-eyed little boy
Hispanic
Waiting on a baby
I got it you got already
Gentleman
You just see what I just saw it right there
Wow
We need to call the police
Get over here
We got to call the police
I don't care what the
Call 911
Blonde hair blue-eyed kid
Hispanic women
Waterboy
He gets convinced not to call the police
Because they're like
Can I do that
Ephod enter 100% smuggling
Radon details that Alex
And keep straight
Yep that are based on
Again nothing but his
So now if you look
Immediately again
The story changes
IJustine
Fluid
It's not based on anything real
Discord
Women with him
One of those kids was barefoot
Barefoot
Barefoot you name it
This is where paying attention is really important
Jourdanton helpful
What's the story is already changed twice
Summer span of minutes after he witnessed this non-crime but he want
How to call the police over
Initially it was a blonde haired blue-eyed child who was with a Hispanic woman who couldn't possibly be as much
Then it became a blond-haired blue-eyed child was with
Nike women who couldn't possibly be his mother
Now it's become a blond-haired blue-eyed child who was
Unaccompanied minor arriving scared
At the center
The story is changing because Alex is trying out different versions of the story to see which feels best
See what you can use to incite the maximum amount of fake outrage
Satan is audience
He does this a lot and it's absolute
Gut-wrenching to see him come faced
The face of people who are in desperate need
And then for him to use them as fodder for his dumbass
Here's what's going on with this video and I should point out this
Is painfully obvious if you just watch the footage that Alex posted
There are two kids
But Alex is talking about in mixed
One of them is wearing a red shirt the other is a blue shirt and that's how I'm going to do
Distinguish between the two cuz they're both
I guess
Blue
I don't know. Can't tell what their eye color is good
I don't really know if it does hair
To the end of the story
The kid in the red shirt is the one that Alex initially started yelling
The one who was he was convinced was with a Hispanic woman who couldn't possibly be as mother
Alex just made this up and it's based on nothing
Thing at all this is a
A group that goes in pets
But that's with a red shirt
A couple people in front of that kid in the red shirt is the kid
In the blue shirt
Use the child to be alone when he entered the charity building
Sing because he was walking separate
From his mother
If you roll the footage back to earlier you can
Can clearly see them walking together
Is a woman carrying a child and
The kid in the blue shirt does not act in the way that Alex is describing
What do you approach has the door the charity he looks up as if to make a greeting to the guard who's holding the door open or have lunch
And then continues in showing no signs of distress or
Confusion
Alice's version of the story is completely made up and he's also mixing up these two different children that he saw walking to the charity because
Because he knows that no one watching this is going to
Care they're not
His audience isn't going to Lake
Hey we just
That's not what happened was it matter
Does not matter
Yeah I mean it's good that you can watch this
Because it did you just hearing the little bit in the description I have blood dripping from my ears and I think that maybe that's
What I have to offer
Is the visit not yell at
I'm doing great buddy
So at this point Alex's
Gotten
Something on tape I guess
Any decides
It's time for people to
To follow seatbelt
Alright
Login
There's just another box
Is this a
Everywhere *
Do some people came out of the charity and went to get in a taxi
That was Park
Tim decided to bother.
After their desperate pleas to follow
Seat belt law fell on deaf ears
You could actually see in Alex's face the wreck
Recognition that he needed to try and save this thing
The publicity stunt
Is the U.
Dishonestly comes off look for looking tremendously week
Around 7 to constantly Retreat back to being a seat
Spell snitch
And that's where things got really depressing
Information
You can kind of see Alex make the decision to Waddle behind this taxi and try to block it from moving because the last time he was bought
Bothering this charity
You got a ton of attention on social media for blocking that dude's car
You can feel him trying to recreate the magic
Pretend he's having another heroic moment
It just Falls
Completely flat
There's a little bit sad but what I feel more is
F*** his dude
Is a 47 year-old man is putting all of these people's lives at risk
Prophet
Do you know somebody saying is b*******
He doesn't care about
Seatbelts and he's making up a narrative about this unaccompanied white child in real time
You can see him making it up
He's betraying refugees arriving at a charity as an invasion and whether it's his
Explicit gold or not
He knows that his actions are helping create a Target on this charity for harassment or violence
Planets
F****** unacceptable and if the moment that I get to
Enjoy is Alex
Thinking that he's going to have a big moment waddling behind this Taxi
Is it being very sad
And I did not working out I mean that's not a win but I'll take it
Some sad music over that and really get some
Pesos at the shop
Freud of that pathetic
I think he's trying to get these people like a mobster on tax
Excavation elx reveal all of the other crimes app
Alex
The Eliot Ness
Outlaws
Yeah definitely
Anointed himself seatbelt cop
Collapse of the USA
Mortal children not even seatbelt
Just disappeared
It's okay
What about
It's honestly pathetic how much of this is Alex trying to pretend he cares about people using
Seat belts are car seat
Political beliefs actually require him to be strongly opposed to seatbelt laws which are really just an overreach of the
The Nanny state
Recognize here is that Alex knows that what he's doing
When is wrong
Do you know that he can't prove in any way that anyone he's in her acting with his doing anything illegal or even untoward
He can't prove that anyone is being trafficked said he can't prove any kind of malfeasance on anyone's part
Everything he's doing is about making assumptions
In creating
Suspicion
And baseless
Being thrown around
However
Car seat laws are real
He should be philosophically opposed to them but they're the only concrete thing he can
Come up with to justify why he's there then why anyone should listen to him yelling
The reason that he brings it up so much and this video is because it's legitimately all he has to work with
And honestly I've seen no evidence of the video that Alex released that suggest that anyone is doing anything wrong
Even in terms of car seat
Earlier in the video
Rob do is gawking in the window of one of these transport van
Alex keeps insisting I tell me that there is not video evidence of people in
Car seats
This one actually does have it looks like one baby seat at least goddamnit
Broadview what's again f****** taking sup
Corporate representative do
The official Vehicles barely do so I'm at least have appropriate car seats
So don't lie one they looked in the window of apparently does have
Alex is just going to have to file a complaint with the taxi company is blocking is insisting doesn't
Is that it is that is that the end result Southpoint taxi company
And I got somebody's Medallion taken away
On the front lines against McHugh and the New World Order
Bothering a taxi driver
This is just overwhelmingly pathetic
I want to bring this back
Full circle because I think you might forget a little bit
Of how this was presented
By the time who now we listen
Alex describe this video
20mm
Ladies and gentlemen
This is going on
2 miles from
42 minutes
3 boxes delivered
McAllen has
At least 7
Bldg 180 yd long Warehouse when the
For something you just see hundreds of women and children inside
I'm standing there as a bus pulls up
Another bus around the corner
People in cages what do I get to that
People in cages with
Private Mercenaries
Catholic charity outfits
Driving with guns
30 minutes
Walking around here
Mothers
And get this
Blonde-haired
Blue-eyed children
Without them
Without their father
Security guard
English
I want my mother
Please call 911
Spider roll
Closest with armor
The complete fiction but it
If the end product of what Alex
Did out on the street
The raw video de posted on Infowars is actually the recording of a rehearsal
Alex went out there to cause a scene and hopefully get a ton of attention again like he did last time
Nothing really happened so he started raping about a child that he saw go into the charity
Gradually he worked on the Beats of that story whether or not it worked
You know for it to be a white child with a Hispanic woman or a child alone or with two women he was just trying to figure out what we
Work best
And he came up with the optimal way to sell it to Azadi
Having the whole I want my mommy thing is a really nice touch and go
Completely made up but it doesn't matter
Anyone would believe anything Alex says it's going to watch
The video and not pay attention or not watch the video and just believe
But he captured whatever he claims he captured
It's just
And and you can see by the way that he's focused
Sing this
Biddies
Very much
Whiteness there's a waypoint
Yeah that's that's a really great
Description of it that rehearsal idea because yeah you can definitely hear the on the call it's so much
More polished
Like the the actual video of all things
And what's more important is
Appetite
45 minutes 45 seconds on of
Yeah it's unfortunately it in some ways you know you take away the the evilness of
You take away the disgusting
Exploitation of these people out of it
And you do see that there is a little bit of a creative processing
Involved
When Alex Witnesses a child go in
I can work with
Any start
What's to try and figure out how to
To do it and then you see the B
Being presented
To Eleanor
This is this is kind of
What I mean by the teachable moment
That is available within this disgusting
A mayor of a video
You see this process and I seen Alex do this
A number of times
He doesn't on the show sometimes
He does it when he's trying to figure out a way to spend something
It's
It's important to recognize
How disingenuous
Dishonest
Transparent
This is a huge just pay attention
Yeah it makes you ain't make it you know it almost makes me want
Okay so there's
About 10 million
Podcast
We're creative people in La talk about how
Great and creative they are
And go through their creative processes and kind of like
Where I come from
Imagine if there was a right-wing f****** liar bulshit podcast mother likes well this is how I work
Workout all of my b******* you know I'll take it to the border and I'll just kind of wandering around and scream for a little bit
To be after all of their careers are over
Yeah that would be fine honestly don't even know if it's a conscious thing
Like I am I'm not positive that Alex knows
That what he's doing
Is drying to heighten an Escalade
And imagine scenarios that would be
Exciting or enticing to the audience based on their picadillos
I mean
But it's tough to really
Get into like that idea of somebody with
Almost instinct
Tradecraft
To them you know that that like
I've just done this so much I've never actually been able to intellectualize it
I simply do
I think I you know I don't know I think
I think a lot of
People who do stand-up
You go to open mic
Again you perform and you like that didn't work
Not necessarily your writing down on paper like a conscious process of how to fix the
The joke you just kind of brute force it
Just go over and over again and this b*******
10000hours Andres valdovinos
Full of s*** a****** ironic that the best way to describe his growth
Is b*******
So one of the things that I wanted to
In some ways
Is the last time Alex went down to this charity and harass them and bothered them
A lot of people posted videos of it
Out of
I am
Doing this
In a lot of the traffic that he got out of it was people being like look at this monster
And such
Seem nearly as much
This time around
A part of it was because the Optics that Alex had are not useful for that another thing is is
Good
Help him
Yes is a trap
This is a trap
And unless you're going
To take the time
Do
Experience
Understand
And help an audience understand
What he's doing
Don't post an out-of-context clip of him
Bothering charity people and be like look at this a******
It's only it only works
To his advantage and he's aware of it and that's why he does things
It's a game and a trap
People like Alex Hughes
Yeah I'm proud you have no idea that he was at the border
That says a lot you know like people Roberts people share a lot of information with me and and
You as well you know and that idea of it
This whole thing happened with me completely unaware of it
It's like back in the old days dammit when I just had no idea what you were going to tell me I would guess that if Alex like broke some
I'm on the window or something like that you would have heard about it
Actually succeeded in a lot like
Finding the
Temptation that he wanted
Then there's a chance that people would have fallen for it
But this was just so Bilk toast in boring
That
No one cares
Yeah I mean his next stunt
Has to be well it at the the start that you would
Think it's the correct
Escalation if I'm
In the writer
Your stone is going to get arrested
Needs to do if he wants to pull a stunt
And he should do some kind of minor bulshit that he knows he's not going to do real-time for the real question though is is
Sewing ready
You know is is is there anybody who can be a temple while Alex's doing
However long he's going to have to do like a week
Before he gets released or now we do now I'm asking later this to another love
Bible alright Owen
Live in Folsom kind of situation has already whenever Congress
While Alex is in prison
Bohme
I don't
Albino about prison is I learned from Mark Richards
I don't think they let you bring
Podcast
The freezer
Hey if Johnny Cash could do it I would love love love it
Owen started doing things work you would go visit Alex and prison visit
Well they let me bring a pencil
Alex's in touch with some reptilians and
Full circle kind of closure that we could ever get Alex was telling me the other day but I was married to a rafter
Princess Anne
Can you imagine the narrative closer that that would provide that would be the end of our
Ride off into the sunset
God I want that door seals
I think it is an interesting thought those like in terms of like what would
Student escalation it would really have to be some kind of
And Alex doesn't attempt on Alex's life in jail for something
I got the rest of this stuff is kind of
Italy
Like you can go and get drunk on podcast and talk about his dick
And like
I don't know
Before
He'd go on Rogan and gelato
Done that before 2 I think it's diminishing return
I don't know what he can do
He went to the border and he got
A publicity stunt out of it
Back in April or month
What's ago whenever you did it
Trying to go back to that well it's
Dry
Ironic cuz it's raining
But it's dry to dry well
I don't know what to do
I mean
You got to go
You got to go somewhere enforcing
You got to you got to go to to like
Amaris house would be easy too because you
Could protest something
Totally
I mean people
On the left get arrested for protesting all the time
John protesting itself
Yeah he could be good
You know he has a lot of
Wrong ideas
He could protest
In a legal fashion
Peaceful resistance
It's it's a sad school
Could drive a tank down Main Street
They work out okay you know it's legal to own tanks
Yeah I think we'll see I think it'll be interesting to see where they
Things go in the future
And
It is it is woefully transparent
I would say that anybody who's interested go watch the video and watch the kids that he is specifically talking about
And see how that does not match up at all
With the public face
Narrative that he landed on
After spitballing and trying to
Figure out exactly how
Best salad
And if you can understand that you can understand a whole lot about how Alex
Creates the narratives that he creates
And why
And about how the
The entire right
Wing creates their proper
Change shirt
Translate
Oh yeah
Will be back on Monday Jordan
And I'm excited somewhat
To see how Alex deals
With Rumsfeld
Excited to see
I mean he should hate Rumsfeld
He does
Yeah so
I just don't know I don't know I could see him giving a glowing
Eulogy to
I don't think I don't think it'll be a glowing eulogy I think he doesn't
There's no way
You can like rocks
But he also has
Built-up Rumsfeld is a giant global
So like
There's no way for this to be another Patriot assassination or whatever
Impossible that would be like trying to rehab Karl Road
What does end up transpiring what's Alec
What's gets back
From the border
I will find out but until then Jordan Twitter
Please find a local charity or bail Fund in your area
People doing God's work
But until then I'm needle I'm Leo I'm dzx barkingdale rundas I am
The Punisher of seatbelt law
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work