Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for Tenaya Lodge babe I'm sick of them posing
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Looks around and talk a little bit about Alex
June
We are dancing
What's up
But today my birthday
Skittles gummies
Just discovered these at the store and I dried them as I
You're better than Skittles
Probably
It's hard for me to tell me though I am a fan of
When is Skittles going to get into the THC gummies
Yeah it's a bootleg one I'm sure
That will be good people who enjoy that
You know it's funny what I like
But I don't like sneezing
Not funny
What's your red spot
Jordan
Save me
Bok
I've got to be
I finally
Got a new coffee maker
Do you know how much I care about coffee
$15 Mr Coffee
Copious amounts of coffee
At least
Because I got the new coffee maker
Cuz I only work
Set timer
Because my coffee makers so garbage I haven't I didn't
Use that coffee
Because it would have
Just come
Garbage
So the first thing I did with the new coffee maker had some of that Kona coffee that you got for me
Fantastic
They make it over there
Is it good babe
Antoinette Folgers Bolshevik
I like
Good coffee but if I'm going to drink a pot of it you know you might as well drink
I guess I mean I disagree but I I guess it's next
Where you want to be at
It's like drinking PBR
July 20th
July 1st
You're still you're still ahead
This is Thursday
Down by the border
Hey we're checkin cuts
Say bye
Trump
Organization
Talk about a little bit of
Yeah there's there's news
We do a little bit of a z I like that
Thank you very much
To Lisa
Erotic dinosaur bath bombs I'm excited to give a try
Appropriate for your coffee maker these Cthulhu a Starbucks
Smuggs cool I love
Awesome
And they preserve the Earth with its reusable Eco mug
Book sokullu
Destroyer hell yeah it's about time yes
And then also I want to say a very special thank you to Tom
Who sent a couple of guys
Propaganda posters
I have got those are really cool
Unbelievably awesome I've made a point that I do really enjoy that art style
And I think of something really cool about communist propaganda posters and also answer
Communist propaganda posters
And if
Just so cool thank you so much time I can't wait to
Get those framed and put up on the wall
Something if you put those right next to each other there's almost like a
Duality of man
Metaphor there
Pro-communist
Posters themselves
Although I do have some that I found
Various places
Is there antique
Particular I think we're both
But communist
Destination
Thank you Tom
Today Show
Mi mi mi mi mi mi mi
What, what
Fun
You can tell he's having a great time
Mama mama mama
My fight song
He didn't even have the energy to do
Brutal
We start off the show with Alex
Just getting back to Studio A
If I understand correctly he's so he made great time back from McAllen
Implied that you made it back of this morning
Yeah
Owen is in studio with him
I think because there was a chance he wasn't going to make it in time them
Shotgun for the first bit of the show and that
Does not
Doesn't make for good listening oh no
But they do touch early on
On the
Indictment of trump organization
CFO
Now
Beyond from company has been indicted
But not guilty.
During a divorce
What might have let one of his children
Who's getting divorced
Stay in a condo
And maybe they really use company card maybe company pencils to Owen
No and if
You know cut a check it may have been a pain Alex I mean God forbid
Alexander Evans
Some fun here but the reality of this case is a little bit different than the
Picture there painting
The case has its roots in some questions about the Trump organization CFO Allen weisselberg son who lived
Apartment in paid quote far below typical Manhattan prices for it
This was
Between the years of 2005
June 2012
Oh I thought it would have been like the 9th
1830s when he could have been like 60 bucks more
It was not
More recently
Additionally they found that weisselberg
Self-report
Headed to be a resident of Long Island
But in fact lived in a company paid apartment in Manhattan
Thereby avoiding quote
Paying hundreds of thousands in federal state and city income
Come taxes
About 133,000 in refunds
For which he was not entitled
Prosecutor set
This is essentially an allegation of committing
Fraud by paying someone under the table so there's a bunch
Two things that are alike
Your payments and kind
Not reporting on your entire thing of like we're not going to pay the government
Well do anything we'll see how it shakes out as more details
A tray of this is
Complete nonsense
Yeah
I mean I just
I I don't understand even from their kind of
Ideological
The perspective
What is
The percentage
Do you think of businesses
At bat
Size
Don't have some sort of criminal
Indictment
Available
Eligible for one
Teams in all this stuff going on all the time even if you're even if you're retarded
What you should be like
Is hay
This is the cfo's been doing all this stuff the whole time Trump is clean
These clean mayonnaise businesses clean the cfo's embezzling man
Really is he
That's an interesting
Angle that you're taking on this and have a kind of similar spin
Obviously there's the you could indict a ham sandwich
Define totally.
And then there was the also
Rodger Stone comes on defense
Basically their argument is that like
Bruise that Trump is
The cleanest business man ever tells me about Trump he's got to be one of the cleanest people that has ended
Everybody doing
Something wrong
I mean it letting people use a condo during a family problem or letting someone use a company car
We have a couple company cars does that mean
Company car
Does that mean that I paid you off in some criminal action I mean
This shows me
Yeah I mean if you use the fake version of the story that Alex's
Does television does look like
Such as driving a company car it's
Payment in the form of
That's not report
Yeah it's it's also a little bit like
To your question
It depends
Right but it's the context of is giving Owen a company car payment and time
Well if you gave him a couple
Pretty car in order to avoid tax
Pictures of some kind
Howard Ward is the company
The car is huge and it's a payment
Exactly
Maybe
Analysis of this case
And it does not
Takeout mugshot
Almost no conversation conversation
Pass
I was kind of shocked actually like to dance on the graves of the people he doesn't like when they die
Yeah
I didn't even hear anybody bring up that Errol Morris documentary where he just talk directly to Rumsfeld through
It was
Like you know with terrifying genocide all Psychopaths you know like George W bush
He still got that kind of charm that down-home folksy charm
And when you are just listening to Donald Rumsfeld talk
And looking into his eyes your life
This is the most terrifying serial killer in the history of this place
Can plan it like that guy is
Verify Marissa's is feta
It helps him and it's just like that
Space don't rub smells go ahead and talk
Present yourself to the world
Old and he's just like
I am a very normal person and I have of course
7 million Muslims
It's no big deal sometimes you kill
People you know like he's just terrified
Yeah I know I would have thought that I would say something to bring up buddy I got nothing
Then that's kind of because you know this Trump indictment along with
All sorts of other
B a business
They are
Indications
In this clip
I think if you read this very unfairly
It's very unfair reading of this globe is inciting people to Suicide bomb
Dracula's lunging arthro right now
So the analogy of
The flame of Liberty
You know
People going to drop whatever the numbers are
The Communists going towards the light of Liberty that torture
Freedom on a Kamikaze mission
Do the
Flame of Liberty to do anything to keep it
Going even at that
That means jumping into it themselves to spontaneously combust
Because we know we're about to
To do end of the tunnel we're about to be under
Take over
We education Bachelor playing
Very ungenerous reading of that
What is Owen saying people need to
Commit suicide bombing attack
He's just basically saying freedom lovers
Suicide bomber
Duh
There's nothing more free than
Your body being
Small bits all over the
But not
Not an impossible one from molarity
No not good no that's not good
Not good
You know that's one option
You could throw yourself into the flame of Liberty
Or
I don't know do a show on Saturday
Special
Transmission
I'm seriously considering it so much news is breaking
I'm coming in Saturday and doing a special
Broadcast on Sunday
Damn baby but on Monday
Understand
Last July 4th ever in this country affect you could stay
Last year was we really are
A conquered Nation or not
Honest with ourselves
How much trouble we're in
We have no hope so I'm just asking was realize that
This Is The Moment of Truth
Last 4th of July
Yeah this is definitely all about
Having our last Fourth of July and not at all about exploiting a holiday for sales
That sounds good Fourth of July sale going on
The irons
Pretty severe
So I don't know
Pride before the parade yes absolutely
Sometimes
Alex
Interesting thoughts about what
What might or might not go down
Suicide
No
Gross
And it's just gotten too over-the-top disgusting
We're going to hit this coming up next
Yes kick belongs
Pride
I want my kids to see it
Eating feces drinking urine
Having sex in public
That's what goes on at the Gay Pride Parade I never been to one but I've seen the videos
Maybe.
What group far-right propaganda videos
About it so I'm pretty sure I have a clear-eyed view
Wow
It is so
Heartless
That
Everyone turns into Footloose
John Lithgow
The moment gay people are like let's have a party
They're just like no parties
Listen
Even he's even just like it's gotten
Too over-the-top like hey
I used to be a huge Pride fan
15 years ago no way I do my God
Oh my God there's an op-ed in the Washington Post
Furious
They eat poop
The pride parade since its Inception
Now it's just gotten
I'm too excited I've been real chill
Anais
Whatever anyway Alex
Is a report
I'm going to Pride for the first time
I barely have a great
Time
A terrible time on air but
Keep the whole time until I got you fracture an entire
Situation where you saw a blond blue-eyed kid
That's true being kidnapped that's true you would make up if you went to
Isn't it amazing how short of
Time. Ago we discovered that blond-haired and blue-eyed children were being
Kidnapped at the border and now it seems like we're not talking about it at all I don't think Alex is even talking about it on this episode
Nothing so important was yesterday for the Delta variant covid-19
Because
Well that's the problem is you know just like the media is 10 or 20 years
Find Infowars
Play just because they don't
Want to be fully honest with
Their audience
Did Alex talk about on air
The person the average person on Fox news or whatever we'll talk about behind-the-scenes with their
Family at the bar at dinner whatever they know it's all going on
There is not going to talk about it on TV so that causes the public
In 20 years behind
Why they're so stunned when they see Infowars reports from 10 years ago or whatever they're calling out everything that's happening now
No we're just being real about what's going on it's not
That hard to predict
The Ava
White papers 10 years ago
Watch this virus will have new variants to keep people lockdown
Didn't get any of that from
Some kind of evil globalist plan that he's red
Anyone could predict it if an outbreak isn't
Contained quickly the underlying virus will evolve as
Everytime it replicates is a chance for a mutation that could result in a new more dangerous version of it had that something that pretty much
Everybody
Was discussing in the early times
The covid pandemic
Biological reality around
When the inevitable variants arrive
If you prepare the audience
Interpret
As opposed to what they really are
A tragic reality of us not dealing with
Does Public Health crisis in a responsible fashion
You know if you let
Anything reproduce
Trillions of times
It's going to make a new very
Thanks kind of how everything got
The odds of it are greatly in
Increase
And I mean obviously not for nothing
Alex is rhetoric
And the worldview that he's espoused
Greatly
I'll contribute towards
People behaving in ways that
Increase transmission
So
I don't know
No it's not even it's about self-fulfilling prophecy
We make sure wanted to express something
Close to that without using
The term selfie.
Quite right but it
It's in there it's in the ballpark
But it is it's
It's an outcome that he is warning against
Wasp
Torts
So he is
Essentially saying
Don't respect the lockdowns
Yeah and they're going to create more various
But by not
Acting lockdowns you create more varied
And so on and so forth Lee at very least the odds are increased that outcome will be
Exactly
Creates the feedback loop that lie
Lead us to where you say that
10 years later Fox News is finally catching up no my friend
It's just an open Rebellion now
Bien
So Alex went down to the Border
Cuz he was looking for some
Footage the stereo is in a bind
Is way behind
I can't do this on the Fly
So you went and got that video and
He has a
Appointments
Right now
The Border Patrol
They are involved
Did human smuggling
That's what they need to go
On strike
What what's this
What is happening on a meditation app
The Border Patrol
I become the facilitator of the smuggling
We need the Border Patrol
Completely walk off because right now
They're the ones that organized it and bring it across actually
Or find a bus or go anywhere
How much the border patrol does it
And so the border patrol needs to have a strike
Because because
They are facilitating
The breeze
This is a tough this is a tough thing to workout
How to because
Get to the larger issue of the Fiat
Currency and how that used to control us a new study came out
It's not what
Obviously it's like I give the trillions of dollars
Eschew a week
To themselves
But what I'm saying most Americans are still living paycheck to
Paycheck and
Shmoney
Illegal alien you get $15,000
I'm saying
Some border patrol agents probably going on strike and not getting that paper
Paycheck is not an option they've got
Family that got mortgages
Is the fiat currency slavery
They're all enduring right now
Interesting
Is an interesting Prospect
So what he wants
Labor to do
Is organized
Collectively
And take
Action
Against management
Swishes
Which
According to Alex the management has a human smuggling which I disagree with
Naturally
Yes in his
You would like to use laborers power again
I guess the manager
My class
This is a real sticky situation because
You know these people need
Evil job there
So their power as workers
Threatened by not being able to collect
Actively Act
Yeah this is
This is like
Conversate
Asian from anyone
Who's not full of s*** this is Drew Michaels bit about
Being so racist you go to the other side
You know like I've just
Spin I'm so
Furious and racist in mad at
F****** s*** that now I'm a
Collective social
Goddamnit yeah
Yeah what an awful
Well I mean it's the same thing that happens so often with Alex's rhetoric he's like you know
Complaining about stuff that like government regulation would solve
Nope
I don't have a solution for this problem I'm just mad at the solution is the prop is the thing that I'm telling you is bad
And I'm also telling you that the thing is bad and the only real solution
Is give me
Complete and total power over all
Anyway Alex Hudson white papers
Sure but he's he's found
These are all public
Available on the world economic forum's website
And
And I could tell immediately that he did not read it
Global governance toolkit
Mental Health
Building Trust
Indestructible technology for mental health
Control them and help them
You don't understand what you just read
Wither disrupt
Pokemon takeover they're going to make you feel good and enjoy
And love your servitude
Alex obviously didn't read this papers
Technology even meme
He's interpreting the word in a way you might if you didn't.
Understand the concept and then you were just cold reading a headline had to come up with a meeting for it on the
Applied technology technology that disrupts things very simple if you actually read the paper you would
This is about a specific
Ectopic mainly disruptive technology and it's possible applications
And helping address mental health issues
Disruptive technology is a term that's used
To describe things
Almost
Upending scale
Logitech startup same to be disruptive
If you look at something like uber that's
Kind of an incident of really
Disruptive innovation
Famous previous status quo
The taxi in Des
This white paper is looking at ethical implications and other issues surrounding the emerging
Disruptive Technologies aimed at Mental Health
Quote
From simple Edge
Educational websites to Virtual Reality avatars delivering cognitive behavioral therapy
Who's the wide-ranging subject and honestly some of the stuff I think is a little unnerving
Like a conversation about using digital phenotype
Quote where phone's watches
Computers measure everything
Thing from Behavior language facial expressions and post
Tonality
Been helping to make diagnosis
But that's not
Being forced upon people
About tech innovation in the mental health
Fright
Another thing that they bring up his how quote augmented and virtual reality are enabling
Consumers to experience and practice real life scenarios with
Open the safe confines of a visit to their psychology
Which seems like a pretty amazing possibility for a disruptive technology breakthrough
Then Mental Health
Incredibly helpful
Pulling a lot of
Circumstances
Anyway
Alexandria this paper
He has no idea what it's about music making up a story based on what you think
What's the headline news
Which is pretty much what he always does
But in this case
The headline is far too complex for him to even understand
I need to watch him drive
Yeah it is it is like giving a child a cookie and being I'd like I've never seen a cookie before what do I do
My mouth technology
Somebody who really likes Alex to take a look
And be like
Yeah he read it
Like defend defend him doing any preparation based on
Is that reading of the headline
Guest on the show
Rodger Stone
I just dropped in for a couple of minutes to be like
Buy trumpsc
We're all purse
Security
Gaston this is a woman who
For Congress
Failed
It is now
No
Lauren whiskey has been a
Presently on shows. Infowars as well
All over the place jobs standing up
The freedom
No freedom
Freedom
So she ran for a senate seat in Delaware
2020 GOP Primary but lost the general election against Chris Coons
Probably cuz of cheating
Globalist
So there's a
This is an interesting incidents of a basically like an Ouroboros have an eye on Infowars
Our Alex himself probably had a huge handed radicalizing Lauren
And who he's now interview
As if she's some kind of an independent expert in things
He wants that in the podcast that watching Loose Change 911 documentary that Alex
Produced was her quote Great Awakening
They had a 90% Awakening out of that
Yeah
She was a big qanon booster and an article in The Daily Beast by will summer does a pretty good job of racking up some of her greatest hits
From the past
Princeton she stated that you believe the Earth is
B flat
I also she posted an image on Pinterest
Over 600
20000 white people died to free blacks
Slaves and still to this day not one
Thank you
Wow it's another appearance she was asked if she would be into Trump being the king of the United States
This was her response
You know that would be really cool because I really think that he's a man who puts America first
Who's the first president I've seen in my lifetime it really puts America first
People of America first
I guess I could get behind Trump
Life long-term I guess
She's either trolling or she's a lunatic
Right-wing extremist
The matter really care which it is it doesn't really matter to me anymore
Sure sure it well if she really was she would have suicide bomber according to Owen so
I guess he's not really fighting
For freedom
The reason that she's on is that she had her bank
Account closed by Wells Fargo
Apparently recently
I don't know the details of this
I have no idea
She is made
Accusations that it
It's political
Sure I don't know
She hasn't she has a reason
This happened
Haha it was because she had
Guest-hosted
Good for Rick Wiles
All-night prunus show
Yeah that sounds like one thing that a Wells Fargo is always monitor
And she said something on that show that I
She's think
Retaliation
Warren thank you for joining us give us the latest on what's happened to you
Play so much for having me back on
To listen
It's no coincidence that they did this to me.
The same day
That I suppose the equality act I was filling in for Trunews
Host Rick Wiles
And I went on
Their show and I talked about
The equality act now
There is a war on Christians they did this
They targeted me and they made an example out of me
Because I'm an outspoken Christian
Vocally opposes the equality Act
I don't know if you know much about it
They're trying to legalize
Jesus Christ
But trying to legalize Jesus Christ I mean I'm surprised
It didn't work
The first time
Yeah I don't
A right-wing ding dong
Showing up on a right-wing ding dong
Program and talk
Talking about how Christians are under attack
And equality Act
Is evil I don't think that is going to
Raise anyone
Pulse is going to notice
Cuz it happens all the time Wells Fargo
Donate to right wing ding dongs all the time
I'm so it's like
Can you show me in like finally somebody's talking about there's a war on Christmas
Rick Wiles
Is wild one
He's out there
Do we get restart to get the science of his Maybe
This Saturday
This lady was Lauren
Is just a little bit
G b t q b b
Edit pictures mad about pride month
DeBary map
Deposing the left taking away free speech authoritarian
The churches will stop groveling mostly churches institutions aren't on board with evil they're just
Bully
What do you say to that
But also they've been
Cowardly they've been spineless they've been so afraid
The evil vile people who hate us and want us dead
Calling them names
Do they have refused to speak out against things like
Gay marriage
And now look at this
What do we have what if we seen all last month
I know 10 years ago we talked about the slippery slope
Purchase remain silent did nothing but
But in the end we saw that the
Angle with always the children
Please watch
Plies pedophilia they're pushing that normalization of pedophilia
In children shows
Drag queens
Blue's Clues
I with Peta
Paraphernalia all over
A discount this little clip in Blue's Clues for children
Yes yeah they did and they're not even hiding it anymore
You remember how when Alex is on a podcast flagrant 2 he was trying to
He pretended his problem with things like
The pride flag in Black lives matter where they corporations are
The master evil actions
But hiding behind socially-conscious signals
Remember how we had a conversation about that about now
That's something that is used in public
Because it makes sense
Better than just being an out-and-out bigot
Right
Right here
I miss you
This is what Alex actually
This is what his actual content to entails and is made up of
Blue's Clues put out a clip on their YouTube channel where blue sings alphabet song where
The pee and it stood for
Propride
There's a bunch of flags on the screen momentarily like the asexual flag
Trans flag pansexual flag
Intersex
Swag princess
Alex is not concerned with
The corporate Corruption of lgbtq
Q+ identity
He just uses that as a respectable mask
Hydrazone / bigotries Wendy's
Conversation
Like it would come off as being wildly unacceptable normal
Yeah like
Flagrant 2 is
A podcast where
You can bro out talk about I got a trick
In what have you
But if you start going down there like
Gay people exist to corrupt our children or something
Chords a little too much
And so you hide behind this respectable facade
That is I'm just not into corporations
Doing this pridemonth thing where you
You put up a logo and then all of your past sins are forgotten
This is this is the real face of what
I do like the
The Reckoning
A video
Christian Movement
Reviewer refusing to speak out again
Landscape marriage
I remember when gay marriage was trying when they were trying to legalize gay marriage
That was that the churches were also
The Christians didn't hear a people silent
There were too cowardly because then somebody might call them a bigot
Hushed
And that's why that's why they were so silent gay marriage was passed without any objections at all
Call and then now look at us we got Pride we got slippery slope
Argument and it's all because
Christians have been
Quiet
About lgbtq issues
It makes sense
Yeah
Nope nope
So Lauren is a big news
Actually
I think it started
Let's dominate Alex's coverage
Smell up for the end of the week
In regards to the vaccine
Did you know that likes I just
Percent
Miscarriage rates
Why is nobody talking about
Deletion agenda this new variants are going to be pushing fear on the American people again and us
Sensory information about these
82% of women are having miscarriages
Killing babies is Mormonism
Dead babies
They love that baby alive dead babies
So lifesitenews is a pretty bad out late with dogshit editorial standards and I don't usually
You trust them for s***
Damn you always hear things being side it's like natural news and life cider
To like headers always
I don't know about that
If you try to find this article that Lauren is telling Alex about you'll find the headline
Huge red flag medical researchers
Berry data showing 82% miscarriage rate in vaccinated with
This is followed by no actual article but
But instead there's an editor's note that says quote
This article has been temporary pulled
Temporarily pulled
For further review so life's I can make adjustments and provide additional clarification regarding the data
We apologize for the inconvenience
You could do for your understanding and patience as we speak
Maintain accurate and honest
You can leave that
Headline up apparently
Wow
Unfortunately the damage has already been done and the talking point is reached Alex by way of this Flat Earth qanon homophobe
Even though they've taken down the article gas what it's still the number one article listed on the sites must-read list so that's
Cool
Article in the way-back machine and a relies on comments from an oncologist and a quote reader who described herself
Self is a teacher of medical research
They insisted in New England Journal of Medicine paper was lying about the
Conclusions that its data found
The paper is easily accessible if anybody wants
Sarita
What the researchers did was use self-reported information
Come to assess the outcomes of vaccinations on
They found that quote preliminary findings did not show obvious AP signals among pregnant person
Who received mRNA covid
They also found that there seem to be very low-risk
Biscayne people who were
Vaccinated in later terms
Like third trimester
Wow I mean 82% miscarriage rate is low-risk
That's the cover up what they said in the paper was a cover-up
There's some concern in the data about how many people who got vaccinated early in her pregnancy did not end up in a live birth however
The data is unclear about exactly the circle
Everything was self-reported there's
There is a possibility of user error for example
Another issue is that this study that we need to wait
Need to get more info than obvious read
People who are vaccinated in their first trimester might not have reached
The point where they would be
Be giving birth yet
And that's this day does not going to be particularly useful in terms of assessing those outcomes
In terms of people who are vaccinated in their third trimester most
Those pregnancies have come to
The term so there's a more useful metric
For the purposes of what
What is paper good hope
The capture
The paper literally says
Whereas some pregnancies with vaccinations in the first and early second trimester have been completed
The majority are ongoing
And the direct comparison of outcomes on the basis of timing of vaccination is needed
Did you find the proportion of spontaneous abortion
In this cohort
I'm going to wait and see what comes out on this subject
Because he Fuller scope of information becomes available but for now
I can say with some certainty and lifesitenews seems to agree
The diversion it's being cuddled by Lauren is
Talking nonsense
This so dumb
Yeah I mean
Even if it was
In the sky
Even if we weren't
Studying
82%
Of pregnant women
Getting this
Vaccine
Having a missed
Would already have been very
Very very obvious
And everyone would know about it everyone would be
We talkin about it constantly because
The government and science would have been murdering children
At an 82% clip
Yeah that would have been an issue
Yeah it'd be very
The impossible to hide
Just at any given moment how many women are pregnant
At any given out any given day how many women are pregnant
Varying stages of a long enough time that enough of them worrying
Actually White
Winding up in a miscarriage
I can explain this to tistic and I will
Get to it
The Order of the Phoenix
But just
Bearface
You cannot trust that
Even a little bit
No no
Silly
It's it's a it's an exaggeration 22nd
It's a parody of
Avast at
Hideaway
This is all this is all about
Well
Yeah
He knows that the easiest way to destroy something is when it's in seed
That's why they try to murder babies in the womb
What
Yes
After that then they tried in document doctor enables children by smearing their identities we don't really know if you
Your boy or a girl hey you're a boy that identifies as a girl.
That's smearing the identity apparently
Who much I hate it when people
The slander my gender by me saying that I don't like it
Fairly convinced that she's not troll
The cheese just
Not so this is this is like
This is the exploitation of an insane person
It does seem that way
This is not a person that can be taken as anything other than completely deluded
I think that one of the issues with Alex's
Like she'll be coming so
Stupid in the present day
Isn't the conversation that other way other circles are just be like
Alright I can't listen to this because you think I'm really wants to kill babies alright I got to go
Totally normalized
It's a totally like
It fits in no context that this person is
Even crazier than what you could imagine
Yeah
Can seriously as a commentator on
Dismiss that idea Satan knows
That the easiest way to
The kill thing
Is when it's a seed
What are you
Walking talking about
F****** talking about
Why it's actually harder to kill it whenever it's inside a woman cuz that's a full-grown woman there to protect it
That's true you just throw a stone at it no problem easy to kill their outside
They can't fight back
You need to talk to the devil serious problem
Lord I will get
To you
When we
Figure this out Lauren brings up this study
Alex and he has not heard of it
This is the first teaser
And he understands it
Sowell
Ladies and gentlemen
Mainline Federal numbers
Journal of Medicine 10 most prestigious journals in the world
Population alert the article from infowars.com
Shocking study reveals
Treatments
Five pregnancies
Be a spontaneous abortion
So what's going on here is that the anavex folks have glommed onto his
Specific data
Point from this report
Madison and they're using it to argue that covid vaccine results
In 80 or soap
Percent death rate for brake
This New England Journal of Medicine article include the table where they list the number of spontaneous abortions
Observed as a percentage of the total price
Penzeys
Completed captured in the register
There were 800
27 total
Four of which resulted in spontaneous
This number is in line with the expected incident
Just based on
General population
The mix-up intuitive
The reason why it's a little murky
Lookie here is it it it comes from the definition of spontaneous abortion only being relevant until week
Of pregnancy
Past that point it's
Considered a stillbirth
So the folks like Alex and said Steven sister what should be done
Is to not consider the
The total number of completed pregnancies as the denominator of the
The fraction
Instead it should be the number of people who got vaccinated in the fur
First trimester
So there's never one
You guys should use the numbers that I choose
I'm not the ones that you
Specifically designed for this study
And since you didn't use the numbers that I chose
For the study you designed that I was not
Involved in
That means you're lying
Both are also being
His friends are also being kind of dishonest
About what these numbers
Capture because bees Arkham
Pleated bregman
If you want to use the argument that they haven't stay honest with it you can scroll up
On the paper and find that 1132 people were vaccinated in their first trimester
So
The proportion of spontaneous abortions there would be lower than the figure that they usually actual paper
Is a 27 as opposed to 1132
Issue is the 827 that number is all completed pregnant
Which includes no live births and spontaneous abortion
Stillbirths
Many of the people who are vaccinated in the first trimester have
Have Nots
Completed their pregnancies are
The point when the data was compiled
So the stats look a lot worse in that column
For reasons that should be really obvious
If you think about it for any stretch of time longer
The one of Alex's stupid commercial break
Makes total sense
Later there will be
More
Full information we can make a better
Assessment
This paper is useful in as much
As it captures
Some
Information
About late trimester
Outcomes
In vaccines
Stuff about the beginning of the first and second trimester is a little bit murky
Due to availability of information
18 complete
And this isn't something that is address
They mentioned it in
Biscotti
It makes
Total sense
It is
Hard to learn information
That you don't
Have already
It takes a while
It's not easy
You have to
The time to spread it out
To learn overtype and these people are just like
Reaction
I wondered why this would be report why would this be
Be published as it is
With
The other information being forthcoming
I think probably the
Just because the what
Profound
Third trimester
Outcome
Yeah I think that might be part of why they're like there's
Strong indications
Instead
That this might be
You know what sign that we're on the right track
We'll see one more information
Alex reporting this is 82% miscarriage ratings
Mike Adams wrote an article about it
I think it's all natural news so I assume it's like Adam
A that amount in Alice
The study authors apparently sought to deliberately office.
The truth
About the vaccine
Causing spontaneous abortion
Calculations
Science news article
We checked with our own science
Contacts review the data and double-check
And doing
Yes the study shows that 82% right or spontaneous abortion
Mothers giving covid vaccines during their first
Second trimester
Give me the lucky ones
Yes the study authors either deliberately sought to hide the fact
Dishonest obvious Casey's Pueblo or they are incompetent
That brings into question The credibility
Another word for study
Was almost certainly
Animated women
That actually shows the opposite
A lot of a lot of assumptions in there that are unfounded
There was a lot of claims that I don't
He could back up with
Hard evidence
Snow
The Story Goes Around
It'll be
You know I'm sure a lot of people have been bombarded with chain emails and
Social media post
Surrounding
Miss talking point
And it's a load of b*******
I mean I really feel like it must
Chocolat
To just not know anything about science
And actively
I hate it
Just to the point where somebody can be like
These scientists were clearly obfuscating deliberately this information and just say
Sounds true to me
You know just like that reactionary
Hatred of people who have dedicated their lives to learning
Pizza it's a
Strange response
Just be like
This makes me angry
Deliberate obfuscation
And therefore
It is true
Yep
So Alex gets a surprise guest
Sherri Tenpenny
Okay do you know Sherry 10.0 know she might have talked about her too much weirdo
She's pretty Promenade
She's pretty big name in the anti-vax game right now
Wow I think he's got kicked off Twitter
A f******
British Barrister is huge in the anti-vax community
No I think your name
Moneypenny
Protect native area British
Type
But she does have a webinar
You can hopefully still keep people from getting the shot
Keep them from getting the second shot
If they start to have side effects
You know what to look for
We're going to talk about
Tissue modification
Oh boy
She's into magnetism
Just pretty big into the vaccines make you a magnet
That thing
I cannot have a webinar where they do
Discuss becoming a magnet
I guess that other the two things pull
You know towards each other
Or away from each other without touching
So that's
Got to be the highest
As for magic that she
How do they work
So is cheetahs got kicked off Twitter and I don't know exactly why but
Anyone's guess
Invested
This idea of
Teaching people how to teach other people to be
Oppositional
Defiant again
Text medicine okay so she's she's got a bulshit pyramids a pyramid scheme of b*******
It does feel that way yeah
Alex
I took our webinar the first time
I had no idea
So perhaps
Keep more of them from being injected
Education technology
That will permanently the irreversibly change your genes
Give us the Prelude of the
My point you're going to help me come back
Okay
Alright
I would I would talk about the genetic modifications that will forever will destroy the genetic modification
That you're going to turn into a f****** mind
I don't know you know that this is what I've been saying I'm fine with GMOs as long as I can glow-in-the-dark like
Scientifically superpower out of it become Magneto
She doesn't really talk too much about the actual
Science behind
Correctly I cooked this is me being stupid
The vaccines end goal is
It's two teacher white blood cells
How to make antibodies
For a virus that you have another already
I undo that advisor heard we haven't already developed an immunity
Right
Amira magnets
I think magnets might be the only way you could do that
Perfect alright
That sounds right
Obviously everybody who gets vaccinated
Is going to die
This is everybody
There's also going to die on point
But that's not the conversation we're having
Tenpenny believes that everybody is going to die to kill off everybody
Except
Some people
And you know why
Because they got ceiling
Shots
Can you know it's interesting that we just got some
Vacation yesterday
And it's because
Good opinion
Category
420 mechanisms of injury schedule
Which is anaphylactic shock
You can have one of those so that doesn't mean
Free
Yeah you got to go through one of those
20 mechanisms you have to go through all 20 mechanisms to be fine
You maybe got a saline shot
There are a couple new stories that I was able to find people who are active
So that we were given
It does happen
Sometime soon
Add the numbers of people were very low
And
These news reports are saying
These people went back and got
Not on purpose
Was not to make sure they did
Died at the same time as everybody else
I mean look
Tenpenny got a meme about
I'm so maybe and argue with memes
Alex
It's for screenshots I'm looking at it on my computer right now
For screenshots
From Newsweek magazine
April 21st Wednesday
Group of Canadians
Accidentally receive saline injections
Covid-19
And the global still want to promote that stores injects people with saline
Number 360
Scene in South Carolina
Is that an accident or is that intentionally misleading to what you just said
Clusters are they sending
Boxes of files that are just normal
Places in
Cluster
Boxes
Of the places
So that they
Who has a senator and a special operation
We're just giving you saline don't worry
The exact same thing
Exactly
Oh yeah
Okay that's
That's probably
Vaccine
Tucker Carlson got the vaccine all of their Republican politicians got the wedding
Oh no
Brick shocked reaction on there to have her tell him about that
20 mechanisms that he's about to
To go through
Jesus
I was reading a little bit about these
These alien shots that have happened and part of the reason is
Speak Australian
Who's used as
Get to dilute the shot
And so some people
Accidentally got the unactivated
Yeah I don't know I don't know why this retired Colonel guy is son who's in Special Forces
Get the shot in the guy tells him don't worry we're just
Giving you sailing
Why would they even go through that the playacting of it
No no
I just don't know
Just tell me when you got a shot
Yeah
Yeah or just not tell book
You were just not tell them why would you give rank-and-file people that kind of information going to file any special force
Fine
Yeah I mean if it's
If you're giving this kind of information to someone who's
Special Forces
He's going to tell his dad was going to tell Alex
Got to be careful special forces guy if you don't ever
Alex
Jokes
People are being magnetized or saline shops
Are being given out in order to make sure that some people survive
Construction.
I have bad news for you
If you are parents
And you vaccinate your child
They'll Never Grow Up
Indiana came out with a couple weeks ago
If you're vaccinated
Engrave
Haven't even got
That point yet
Kindergarteners
The 7th grade
Did children who are now marked forever and forever will have
As they grow up
Adult
Haha
Children with these Technologies
Golden that will give them
Privileges
They won't be able to do any
It was really happening
I think the
I think that living through a global pandemic is just the subject of a
Nightmarish
Movie and we've gotta movies
Lot of movies and we lived through it
Yeah
I look there's a lot of tough
Tough conversations in tough decision
I'm really glad on
Some level that
I don't have any kids
And I don't have
Involvement in those
Those sorts of decisions
I'm not a teacher and I work at a
School
Any of that
Figuring out exactly how to navigate this is
Incredibly challenge
And I do not
I envy no one with actual power in this situation
I have zero nvim like
Yeah would you guys
Good luck I'm not even going to be like hey this is what you have to do you got to make that
Isaac
Conversations about it our challenge
And I think that there's a lot of
Morelos
Invoice has been Alex Jones
Tenpenny
Yeah
If you're listening
You're going out the window
That's defenestration
Going to grow up
I don't know if there's anything I can think of that's funnier
Then them believing that 10 years we're going to have a generation of 8
18 year old tiny people just wandering around like with their tiny little high-pitched voices
Experience of
Real life. I was honestly wondering if that's what she meant
Because it makes
It's very little sense
No and it turns out I think that is what you meant
It's what you said if parents get their kids
Dota 2 ever wanting to become a grandparent
Who's already started her periods
Is anybody going to keep to see whether or not she
If she hasn't started up yet
She will
About the little boy
Will never grow into
Is anybody
If we give this to 12 year old boys
Children's Choir
They certainly don't want to
Have their children these children
Humans
What
What the
Book are you talkin about
I don't even know what to do anymore like
There's there's a certain amount of stuff that can be like disgust
In terms of like okay this study is something with being misrepresented blah blah blah
Alex
Didn't read this white paper
And it's funny that he called read it and came up with a completely different version
I don't know what
To do with
Peter Pan
I don't know what to do
I don't know what to do with this
Because it's nonsense
First of all I don't know what you talk
Secondarily
What you saying
If this happens
Will anyone notice
I don't understand
She thinks that like science doesn't have a vested interest in keeping
Things
A data for longitudinal studies and
You know
This will be something could be closely monitored
Don't stop
Non-Stop
Don't stop even if even if it's 30 years from now
There's still going to be like we we got one study that's been going on tracking how vaccines work over 40 years
Will anybody notice if
There are boys generation of twelve-year-old girl suddenly stop having their periods at the same time
Are the boys don't grow and have no body hair
We've got a bucket
Entire generation of Castro's with beautiful voices that people are going to notice
Yeah
Seems like one of the more
Obvious
These
Also
Obvious anger
Cuz her ankle is f******
The obvious angle for Alec
Sixto
Is to say that the reason the elites are doing this
It's so they can have an infinite amount of head
Pedophile
Children around
You know they never grow up
That's the only angle that makes
Since I really I guess I'm glad that he didn't do that
Really glad that he didn't do that
That you did I'm not selfish about it but I mean what and what else is there
They're not going to let them grow up because they don't want grandchildren
I think that was more her saying that if
You get your children that you won't have breakfast
Maybe
I don't know
Well there's so many more
Easy ways to do it
Yeah like
Alex's talked about like Plan B
And it seems like it could backfire if it's giving people magnet powers
So bad what if it accidentally turns people into like they never go up but also they can never die
Okay here's what I would do
If this is what I thought my
Sworn enemy was doing
Would feel shame for them and
Inform me for having
This is pathetic
This is a dumb plan
I can I can end of this plan all tell you one way to end this plan
I'm going to tell the special forces guy
That I gave him a saline shot
Hanover
Defeated player
Silliness
Some of the
The attacks on
Vaccine
Reality
Growing
Of its
More nonsensical than usual certainly check
I was shocked
There's no no real rum
Conversation on this app
Episode butts
You know when you get breaking news like this study that Lauren witzke brings to his attention and sometimes it'll catch you off-guard
Ignore the whole room
Spell
Special drop in
In from
No that'll that'll take up
Talk to Tenpenny whenever 10 pennies around breaking news about
Grown up
So I can't get out of my head
The idea that
When I'm like 90
I'm going to be hanging out
With this child
Who is
80 South
With all the weird world-weariness it comes with that age
Perfect
Skin
Just perfect child
Ibtech
That's going to happen
I guess we'll see you
70 years old
This is the end of this episode
2 nonsense
Project Camelot
Kind of semblance of reality
Deteriorated
Like even without us knowing
Like it's just gotten nonsense
This is too much
Just say is aliens trying to keep our children the same age and that's
It's the same
It would it would have the same amount of grounding
And support
Zia
See what happened to in the future with Alex but I think he's going to be talked about this 82% number probably for the foreseeable future
Which will be annoyed
I wonder if it's going to make it all the way on on the talk show
I don't know I think
I think someone would be able to
We can't back this up
Yeah it was taken down on life
A little bit
It's cuz also wanted
One of the problems with it is it's pretty easily explainable based on the context
The conclusion
Trying to be pushy
By Alex
Incendiary
That like
If you actually believe that 82%
People who got vaccinated
Lost their pregnancy
That's
I don't know what you would be drugging to do
Yeah I know I mean resolved
To fight back again
Baby jump into the fire of Liberty
I mean
Okay million pregnant women who got the shot just
Let's just say that number
And you're going to tell me
Everyone now knows
820000 of those women will have a
F******
Miscarriage or abortion
And
That it wouldn't
Start a war
That would that there's no way that that wouldn't start a war
How incendiary that idea is Rebecca
Conclusion is
I mean
I've always been wrong when I say
People will have more restraint
I would
I think the Tucker would know enough to be like
This could get somebody
This is I don't I don't like Alex
This is what this is What Separates Me from him all the little bit
I don't know
Where the right-wing
We've killed abortion.
We know how this works
If we go that hard
It's
Bloodbath
For any doctor
Yeah I don't I don't I don't know I mean like I said
That I hope you would have the
Restraint to realize
Like the danger of playing with that kind of fire but
Very wrong
About sibo and the
But everything
Jordan will be back
Another episode
We'll see what's going on in
Alex Jones world
But until then we website
Yes we're also
We are available
Please find a local charity or Bell found in your area to help out
People doing God's work
Emilio Emilio and easyxplore come Darrell rundus
Alex
Birthstone colors
I love your work