Damn important swetik
I have great respect for its knowledge B
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
June
Jordan
What's up
I was going to do laundry I went down to the laundry room and watch it fly past me but I think
I thought it was a bat
Rights is pretty early in the morning I was like
It's in a basement got to go down to set of stairs just fact
Bat
I looked a little birds nesting underneath the staircase
I remember seeing that like a year ago is when they was really delightful
I don't know if I brought to mind feelings about you know
Pandemic waning a gas a little bit or like returning to a little bit more of normalcy
I ended the birds are in on it too
Birds
Clearly different bird I got to know these birds pretty well these are different
Are there be nice if you had like a whole intergenerational things starting and in the laundry room I don't think generator
Visions of birds last a year
I don't
I don't have football a player but I think it's longer than a year
Yeah
My bright spot Dan is DJ Dan arti has made me and
Send all of us something very cool if you could please
Wizard
Faster and faster and faster
Worthy podcast that will be coming out
Next week
Oh wow very sorry originally state for you're going to come at 1
It's going to show up
You'll be able to download it listen to the whole thing and then if there's a second season we will let you know
Jerk what is on now
It seems almost like we're obligated
I'm not
I am not good at acting or playing along with things
Thank you great
A compliment wasn't beautiful
Snake episode where in Pasay
We're talking about May
And 29th
Okay
I was I was I didn't know what
Going back to this because
* a little confusing the last time we went back to the past
I found it to be a little bit
And I was little bit worried like I don't feel like there's any progress that I know are actually
But today we we we
Business picks up a little bit
And I'm very excited about a couple of things that happen
But have nothing to do with how important
Like
Stories from 2003
Nothing to do with that
But there's one caller in particular that blew my mind
And I spent
A couple hours researching this call
And I'm very excited
Let's talk about it
I will get to that
Before we do
Jordan
We got a little moments say thank you
2 as opposed to signed up
And our new Wonka
Dave it's good ideas be vamping while I pulled up my sheet
Mcfucking gauge
Anna Kelso
Me to do the entire Steiner math promo
Way too long
But
The Cryptids thank you so much
Uniball parachutist zero-sum
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you
It is time to get deep
Giving someone life is giving someone dead
You can say that
Life is good
You could
It's true
Happy birthday
BBY Maddie Maddie
I also
I apologize
I think it's gorrell
Goral
It's either this is one of those names that hasn't oh that is a flash through it I don't know what to do with that letter
Who is that girl I never remember what the flash that's not one of the characters
Where is that I'm aware of how to pronounce English
Totally that one I don't know what to do with I stare at it and I'm like
Spiral on top notch
Just get it out of here I don't understand
This is from torstein in Norway wanted to wish
Possibly go wrong
Michael T happy birthday
Xdw status
Also haven't happy birthday happy birthday happy birthday
Joseph send a message
Got a birthday but instead of
Wishing a happy birthday to he wanted to spread this to all the community of long
And wish everyone else
In the world
I guess even if it's not your birthday happy
Have a good feelings of someone wishing you a happy birthday
I like that very very very nice inter-communal
So thank you
I guess
That's right that's why I think we should celebrate the way that they
The Giver did
Do you know where with what was that Lois Lowry all right
Everybody has the same birthday once a year
Everybody
Same birthday move on with the rest are his birthday day
I like
Might be functional
So Jordan are we going to get into business on this episode of years and out of context
Episode
Alex Jones is the grandchildren Nazi
Children or grandchildren
I know but it's funny that we're in the present-day on our last episode
The Next Generation
The grow into adults
And then we go back in time and they're still going to be no grandchildren it is something of a preoccupation for Alex
Seems like an obvious it's not being formulated in the same way that they will all not grow up
Good to know there's a lot of ways to get to the
The same
Destination ideas
Who started May 28th and
I will say the beginning is a little bit slow
I'm lying
Heats up
Okay
Got me
Very interested
Very quickly
Whatever should be
Criminal
Moratorium considered in North
Carolina
Furniture
Hardly seems a kind of
People don't
Counting out
Immediately I was like
I am so fascinated
I got completely thrown for a curveball here
Is this a new one
Take
It's not
It's something for now
No it something it's trying to have the appearance of a nuance
Let's take that actually isn't
And honestly I think this is the first time I've ever heard Alex give a definitive
Position on the desk
Penalty
I'll till this point I've gathered from contacts
Excludes that he didn't support the policy given that many of his other ideas that appear to be based on principles
Have to do with the government not doing things to individual
The position is putting forth is absolutely the definition of not having a
There's a lot of reasons
To be for or against the death
Based on an emotional appeal you know like people who commit certain crimes deserve death
Utilitarian calculation where you determine that
If you have a death penalty
There's actually a significant effect on crime rates and you make it
Whether or not that is actually
Do other positions can be based on ethics
Swear there's an intrinsic moral character to sentencing someone to death
And that consideration guides your position
And then there are sets of political beliefs
That could include a strong position regarding the relation
Between the individual and the state
Which would impact your views on the death penalty
Obvious ways
Alex seems to only be operating on the most Elementary level here
He's appealing to an emotional desire for an item
Be taken for an eye
This is really an impressive stuff from him and I once again regret that I gave him more credit than he deserves
Terms of this position
The other cowardly thing Alex is doing here is that he's claiming that he's for the death penalty but not when the government is
Corrupt
The level of corruption is of the government is it
Completely arbitrary and sub
Objective measure
For Alex
This actually means nothing
According to his feelings the George W bush government and obviously the Clinton one before it they're too corrupt to responsibly
Play handout desk
But it would be impossible to formalize this into any meaningful
Scale that you could guide
Things on
Literally anyone could just counter his argument by saying that they believe that the Bush Administration was not too corrupt to hand out.
And Alex would have nowhere to go
He could rattle off in
Answers of governmental corruption to try and build to a point that still doesn't handle the subjectivity
Of his assessment of
Of which government is or isn't
To corrupt
Descendants people to die
It makes no sense
Was he I didn't realize that it was in specific
With the level of Corruption of the cover I thought it was more of a blanket like
You wouldn't trust the government to do that
Just because there's a good chance they are corrupt in some fashion or another cuz they always have
No so he's he's like
In specifically
Okay well now that doesn't make any
By presenting his position this way Alex is effectively making it seem like he's taking a position when he's actually not
He's in favor of the death penalty but only when it comes to some imaginary ideal government
They could be in place
My planting is flag there he can manage to not alienate either side of the debate while getting each to think that he's actually on their side
What does a pet weasel
There's an additional problem here too and that's that there's no reason why the logic Alex's using should apply exclusively to punishment
Involving the death penalty
If your opposition to the state imposing a death penalty has to do with escaping to corrupt
Responsibly give out that sentence
Then it should
Stand to reason that they're also too corrupt to responsibly incarcerate somebody
The reason is using Intel.
Complete inability of the government to enforce any laws
Because they lack the moral Purity or authority to do so
Yeah the way he's presenting it I understand where you're coming from
And I actually think that
It does get closer to
What the point should be
You're saying that they did buy by the very nature of it the government is to corrupt
To mete out the death penalty
And I think I think that
That would be a position
That you
Could call
I guess functionally
Anti-death penalty
I think that that would have much less problems though but Alex is a
Because he's
Not saying
If there were somebody in charge
Who was cool
Right right
No I mean if you wanted to if you wanted to get into it like what's the level of
Nazi war criminal
There should probably maybe the death penalties fine there I guess
You know that's
That's an
Whether or not you can trust the government to single single out individuals is an obvious
Opening
Close Quest
From
The government can't do it
Without eventually abusing it
And killing a bunch of people that they just want gone
I think what's going on is that you're giving
More Credence to what Alex is saying then
Merit
To work when
We'll see more as we go along
I always thought there be a blanket opposition to the death penalty
Because of
The relationship
Kipling individual and State
That is implied through all of his
Political beliefs
I was surprised
He says that he's for the death penalty
I was also surprised when I heard this
More drugs more people in prison
What is not how I've heard Alex explain his opposition to drug laws at other points in his career that I've listened
M2
Every other time I've heard this.
Discuss the issues that Alex is not in favor of drugs but you have the right to take whatever you want
Who is literally one of the main selling points of Ron Paul
The people on the left
And one of the major tools Alex tried to use to insist that he wasn't a right winger
He was cool. Drug should be legal you have the right
Individual you're an adult
Freedom
You clearly doesn't actually believe that
His opposition to drug laws
Is purely a consideration of trying to break up the cartel of globalist We Believe shipping all the drugs
Legalization is in essence a strategic move against the globalists not something that Alex supports because of
The political beliefs
Adult should be able to use drugs if they want to
Which is the way that he presents it
Pretty regularly
This is super weird man I'm like 5 minutes into this episode and already Alex's explain to his positions on things that I thought you would
Irrational about
Positions are all wrong
I'm starting to question
Is there any position
But he and I would agree
I don't think so
Even even with you agree
He's wrong about
I hold out that last bit of hope that somehow like
That the conversation about like
Civil asset
Picture won't somehow turn out to be like
His position on ivis Baisden
Some kind of like
Alien
Comfy or something
I'm more like we need to get way down on a base level of like you guys in a room with a mediator just being like
Who's got the best
Just like start there can you even agree on it
This grinning so did nothing
Your is or is not
Yeah yeah
Something the death penalty
And this is this is kind of gets into like
Alright
Kind of see what you're saying but it's still incredibly stupid
But
Place
But no there could not be a federal death penalty
Here's an interesting statistic that I'd like Alex
The chew on
Do you know the answer this I'm not sure if you do
How many people were executed by the federal government during the eight years that Obama was in office
From 1958 to 2001 only four people were executed by the federal
Timothy McVeigh
Three of these game during George W Bush's presidency but none after March 2003 complaining about
Federal executions
He's talking about something that won't happen again
4 / 7
13 years
I meant
Trump became president
And 13 people were executed by the federal government
And I don't think I ever heard Alex bring it up as a problem because we finally had a government that wasn't
Corrupt right exactly kind of why kind of why I get this
This is
So if there's the right person in charge I don't think this is actually a problem
Giant
Issue during Trump's presidency
The shift
Intone from
The previous
Decade
Two trumps
Four years in office in terms of federal executions
Insane and the fact that it wasn't a major breaking point for Alex
If
This is actually what his position is rooted in
That all states doing it
Then that's I don't know
I don't know if that makes sense but I can't I don't trust
It doesn't that that
Idea of the different that federal government shouldn't be able to but state government shipped that so stupid I can't even
Even breathe
There have been
Few Federal executions chair for Trump
For many years
But conversely according to analysis from usafacts
Between 1977 and 2018
There were 1490 execution
Carried out by state
During which. The federal government only carried out
How much is beloved state of Texas quote accounted for
37% of all executions in this. Or approximately 500
The states particularly Texas carry out the vast
Majority of executions
I want to say that he's fine with that which makes absolutely no sense based on what he's
Dispositions on earlier
If he doesn't believe the federal government to be able to send speed
Because the government could be corrupt
It's absolutely idiotic.
Pretended the same
Cancer doesn't exist in
Slightly lower levels of governmental organization
Being opposed to the death penalty but only on the federal level is the very definition of a meaningless position
It only becomes more meaningless when you explicitly support state
Executions and you live in Texas
The state with the
The government seems most interested in killing convict
He's a downright farce when he also go on to support Donald Trump president who presided over 13 Federal X
Executions
A total reach in 4 years that surpasses the number of federal execution sediment carried out
For the preceding 67 years combined
My phone is at Alex's political beliefs are idiotic and they're not based on anything
But a very least
This kind of brings things into Focus
You know at least I you can kind of get a sense
Because he's giving us
This little piece of information
It's just a state's right
It's kind of argument that doesn't have anything to do
With ethics morality or even
Opposition or support
For the death penalty
Okay
It's it's
Meaningless
I mean well because here's a big problem
If you want to abolish the death penalty in Texas
Citizen Alex's eyes
What it should do is secede
Then it will be its own federal government
Cuz I can't no longer be able to perform executions
Wow
Yeah and then I guess the state of Austin would have to choose their own executioner
Stupid thing to say it is beyond I mean
It's interesting to me because like you just hates
The federal government
I hate the federal government so much that he's willing to like
Except how many probably innocent people are being killed in the
Texas by the government
Yeah
I don't I don't understand this
It's
10 Things I find most remarkable about it is that I could you have listened to
Hundreds of hours of Alex's show
I'm still have like this Bo
I had I had
The Baseline position that you had wrong I had way too generous of a
Assumption
Cuz I've heard him talk about not being in favor of the death penalty
I just didn't realize that maybe it was rooted in
Something is really stupid
Yeah
That means it's just
The only way to carry out the death penalty in Alex
Exercise is if there is a I suppose philosopher-king
Who is choosing each and every individual personnel
Can we talk about philosophers we're talkin about
Drop Donald Trump
That f******
Trump
So at this point
The process
Same policy of the pacification is in place
Sprite and Alex
Still is not addressing that or dealing with it in any way which
Will end up being I think
Gigantic
I think he was wrong
And here is another thing these Ivy the Iraq war that Alex
Is very wrong about
I want to take
But don't worry they're going to find
I hear prey
Now in
2021 look
Going back I did not believe they did
Find
Yeah you know that
Alex almost on the almost under estimate
But Alex being like well you know
They wouldn't just straight-up
Elias into a war right
Yeah I mean like if his
If his ideas were correct about how the globalist operate higher level of control over everything
That's exactly what would have happened
He's writing that novel
Cuz that would have been the way that they are like seaweed proof cuz we set it up the whole time it up
Really not grasping
That they could just
Slice into a war which seems weird for guy whose job is to turn lies into money
Yeah
Wow
A bat bat
Conversation though about what
What you need to do or how you should wear
Respond to the reality of the the Iraq war in the lead up to it
That
It's right it's not super easily turned into and that's why you need to buy my tapes
This is
Kids operating with
Weed impunity in lying to your face is about starting a war
For this reason
Buy my pills no that's like
Let's do something about that to be fair Alex isn't selling pills at this point but it would it is
Is kind of like
Here is the science
Fiction
Conspiracy Intrigue spy novel that's going on
And if you read all my information to be able to
Mexico
So I think that these two things if you
If you were to listen to this episode one of the things you would definitely take away from it is
Position on drugs
This position on the death penalty
Are things that Alex really wants
To take calls
I think it's a slow news day for him I think he's trying to solicit
Calls
Now at the same time
I don't know if I
Can get a sense
That these are
Fictional version
Visions of his position
Like I don't think you saying these things to
To try and antagonize people short like
Someone
Bite on a shity
Call intoxalock it does seem like
This is this
Makes sense that you
Could believe that
Stupider than I thought your
Interview takes calls and this one guy who calls in
Do you want stuetzer to distinguish
When we're talking about drugs
We're talking about it like
Knotweed right
And Alex is not chill
Cocaine
Heroin
Spell marijuana I don't consider to be
Personally drug
People understand
They were put down
Not really made
But
Nightshade grow
Wow
Good morning
Kind of feels like
Trolling with an argument that good
Wow
I feel like from Alex's Brandin that he wants
How to put forth about himself
Didn't seem like the kind of guy who wants
Equivalent about whether or not we'd the drug
What he's talking about being against drugs
Yeah well did you know poisons exist they grow
Close to the present day in Alex's smoking blunts
Evocative hypocritical
I also look like this tobacco
No man would have jerk
Yeah he definitely cut him off before he said
You know these drugs were legalized because of and then the answer
22 that was going to be
Criminalizing underrepresented groups in government
But he also this color brings up the
And the Alex's position on it
Has a interesting reason to be against
The death penalty is coming from utilitarian perspective
He believes that the death penalty is not at the church
And now you can't believe
I guess Alex got his wish
Coming from the moment he said those words that would literally zero Federal executions in Delhi chosen god-kings
Trump came into office
And started wantonly killing people they gotten the death penalty abolished at the federal level
Also consistently research has shown there's no discernible deterrent effect
And having a death penalty
Statistically violent crime and murder rates are lower in states that do not have death penalty
And a 2018 study reported on deathpenaltyinfo found the countries typically see
Reduction in murder rates after they abolish the death penalty
The study looked at murder rates for 10 years
After 11 countries got rid of capital punishment
Any found that six of them had lower rates
All 10 years
Forehead one or two years above the Baseline and then saw a downward Trend underneath the previous level
Only the country of Georgia had a higher murder rate after and explain exactly why that might be the case is beyond me
Or the study
Anyway the point here is that no credible data that would back up Alex's conjecture the
The death penalty is a good deterrent for crime
Exist it's not a good deterrent Dan it's an incredible tutoring
Almost like you can't believe how good a deterrent it is
It feels like it would
Since you think the people would be less likely to commit crimes if they knew they might get
Kid killed for them but that feeling is not based in reality
According to the cdc's numbers
The states with the three highest death rates from homicide in 2019 were Mississippi Louisiana and Alabama
All three of these dates have active
This should be the case
Safe without you saying is true but
It's not cuz
He's not living in the real world
Yeah it's
It seems like
The death penalty exists almost to justify an emotional need in
I guess voter
I think that's what you see when you when you
Here I was talking at the beginning but he is
Support for the death penalty comes out of the emotional appeal to people deserved
Todai
And I think that that is the lowest level of reasoning
Bet you can approach the situation from other than I guess
Randomness
Flip a coin
Appealing to emotion of like I think that this person deserves
Posted I because they committed this crime
Is not well thought through
Obviously
People's feelings are
Find about different crimes
Get yourself in a lot of trouble price
Everything was organized that way
Does seem to be with Alex's is basement on
This caller has a slightly more evolved
Position than Alex
And Alex is telling them
Yeah that they're wrong
Yeah I know I mean it
It is that kind of feedback loop of yes it is the most
Bass
Thank the most base form of reasoning is that appeal to them and emotion of this person did bad
Bad habit
Consider this person
You know and
That's why so many prosecutors in the end elected
Attorney positions
Are f****** running on those like look at how tough and look at how
Crewlife
Because that appeals to that emotional bass in it
It's we're on order it's how we get to where we are
Is they can exploit the lowest form of reasoning to
I only
PJ Max
Worse
God
That sucks
Because I
I think that the other thing to that is part and parcel with that is
Is that the appeal to that emotion
Of this person deserves this
Because they did this crime
Is also an appeal
To like your feelings of security it's
Stability
Because if you were the person who was here in the politician be like I'm tough-on-crime
Really how it at how it hits
You and how you experience it isn't so much about like they deserve this
I get the feeling that I will be safe from crime because this person
Taking care of those
Write those things
Yes the bad people who get bad done to them
I think that that's
Security
Is
An artificial
Emotional
Crotch
Selling to eBay
So these callers are not great
Alex has another caller who's
Hey man
I got another idea about what we do about crime
You know America
The most technologically-advanced
First Nation on the planet
Engaged
Barbarian Savage
You know like
I figured
Criminal
Amenities
For whatever
Put them on the island
You know
Where
What
Haha I was with this guy until he got the island idea
I think
We should send all of our criminals
Around the world
21 Island perhaps
The continent even a big island huge island
And I'm sure it'll never come back
No
Feel like this guy had some points
That's like we have a barbaric system in place
Kratom listening
People should be given due process and that makes guilty before being punished
Here's what I think we should
Restart the state of Georgia
I feel like that clip is a really good towel that Alex isn't coming in with any real position that has an app
Application in the real world
Because in the modern-day the idea of creating a penal colony is stupid
If he just wants people to call in to discuss how they would like
To punish criminals I guess that's fine
Is not a productive use of time
Seem like everybody's having a little bit of a fantasy likes here's how I would punish
Criminal
What I would do is I would fill their room with
Cupcakes and then cover their hands in plastic bags
The mouth real wide
Cupcake everyday
Female that's interesting
Thai soft rock song.
This color does not have an idea that it is
Is your approach criminal justice
This one wouldn't
It only have the power
And wicked and I
Prison
All that Doug
Create a situation
McGrath
I put non-violent people in prison
Exactly
I too feel like there are too many people in prison but I strongly disagree with his entire conversation
This is the unhinged position that would not stand up to the smallest amount of scrutiny
So if I were talking to this guy is a guy who is taking calls on subject
I have a couple questions that I would start off with
I think the death penalty should be for everything
Well
Where's the lion
But you got to kill him
Apparently
So you're not for that okay
Offense would qualify someone for the state
To commit
All violent crime
So okay
Interesting
Like what about
Assault
Like what if
I just came up to you and I punched you
Wow you got it
I don't know man
I feel I feel the hamster be chopped off
For property theft
If we're going to be brutal not have the power to do anything except
I don't know this is a completely untenable
Way to organize Society
If you think that white-collar criminals have it easy now imagine how they would do in that call my God
It is death or nothing
I guess maybe this collar
Has an unstated position
About
What states comes your criminal justice system
But the federal government can just kill or Alex would have to disagree with that cuz he doesn't think
Federal government should be able to kill what about a Hunger Game scenario if we're going to get bad
I just have the federal government with the right to
Kill or zero kill
I say we may have a have some fun with it this is the problem with people who think they can improve Society with their terrible ideas they don't have
What the government
Kill people know making a show about
Alright alright
I would like to know what this person thinks about fines
I would imagine this person has received a great many finds in his day
I think that these conversations are so stupid you can't be in my office anymore sir this is $100
I'm listening to this Alex's articulating his opposition to the death penalty
And
Drugs way he is
Idiotic
Are completely stupid
Absolutely absolutely insane
Somebody gets another caller and this lady
I don't know what to
I can't make heads or tails of what she's talk
I think I can
It's just a long story
Long story about
From what I can
Until the details of it
That there was some police
It showed up at her house
Because she has
Some acres of land and there's maybe something suspicious going on on some of Acres of the land
Lychee
Allow other people to use
And they wanted to look into what was going on
And so she let them in
And they said thank you for letting us look around
And this is a giant
Conspiracy of salt store
She's under attack okay
Escalated quickly
Turns into Alex
Like this
Well you know they were real nice
Nice again we appreciate your you know
Your cooperation out
I told the children all the
Your homeschool my children
See my children read better
The front
Well
That's a little bit of an extreme response to the story that this person is telling him
Like a cheetah
70 acres of land her husband passed away and she does say that she allows people to use like
6:30
Acres of it
Sure and there's not really a good sense that he has an idea what's going on
Enforcement showed up wanted to look around like I said cuz they had reason to believe there was something suspicious
They didn't find anything
Cooperation
And now we've done this
I fully understand standing up for your rights and if his lady a chosen to let the police look around or told them to come back with a warrant
I think either is an appropriate choice to make and her situation
It's one thing to be mindful of your rights and protect them it's another thing to do with Alex's doing
Where he's turning
Trying to take some very benign details this collar is giving him and escalate the story at the hospital's keeping
Kidnapped your kid
This is a sick person acting out it is audio
Even back in 2003
UCF career but
Pretty clear this behavior is still part of Alex
The psyche even backup back at this point
Yeah
That's that's great that's a great way to calm someone down his just had a bit of a scary experience not used to having
Cops show up at their place
You know that to have some things off of like
Hey DCFS is following you and they're going to steal your kids at any moment I want to call me down
Steal your land apparently because this color also brings out
That one of the police that showed up new her husband
Your late
Alex takes
This to be like oh he knew you had lamp
Of course
There's no indication
Pretty women and honestly she's lucky she survive
They come out the only way that you know that they're the law
Because I have the shiny badge
I'm walking to the house
Your head off
Marijuana
He would not take a 911
Tyranny type I mean
What you trying to do
They have a 90% wake up on that day
Howard's power
So apparently the police were look at the squat on this land or
I don't know
Various
Stream turn
He takes a lot of time
30 gallon
Give this lady a really good time
It All Leads
Inevitably exactly where it's supposed to go
God bless you on to Alyssa
You don't know how many
People out here you woke up
I give your tapes away
The only solution
Everything bottled
To promoting Alex's cell
See that takes me back that takes that's good old-fashioned religion is what the lady at right now
Listening to that man you being part of them and you giving them the spirit of God and then at the end of it
My friend what you need to do is
Evangelize
What you pay for your sins you can hear Alex sweater
Cycle
We need 100 tapes out of you
It comes back
Exciting
Now go
Appreciate
Joining me on
Short notice
Friend of mine
Does water sponsored by the US distributor of black Berkey water filters
I'm afraid that I just don't think it's going to get much better than
The soap guy
No it's just not
No I have not yet heard another guest
He's so clearly abusing alochol
Just forcing him to
Set up
The limericks
Marty Schechter
Is
Just
Just exist as beautiful as an awful person
In terms of somebody who has bullied their way onto Alex's show with money
Forced him to broadcast limericks
Freddie Gray
But this is not Limerick level but it is still pretty funny that this is what's going on in Alex's
And it's anime
And
Great deal
Oh my god of Howard fell over
What kind of
Used car salesman
We got a pallet fell over so therefore
I thought that was pretty amazing
I was thrilled
Hey it fell off the back of a
Food Truck Sale you walk up you take it your give
Bkash and you go away no questions asked
I mean low-rent is the
Almost mint condition
Eu's
You probably wouldn't even be able to tell if he's fell off a pallet might actually suspected we just have too many
I can't believe you got so lucky that you got the one Goodwin off the broken
Palatable
Goodbye
Do the 29th
Haha and Alex
Not to himself has another gas
Episode of the DTs
Beginning of the show
Another guess coming on
Georgia
But now
Literally
Andover Andover
We're again and we got to go
Biscuit wants
Seat belts click it or ticket is about getting cars to armories to ransack
Weird stretch of time for us
Specifically so much seatbelt related melodrama happening
Yeah it is weird it is weird it's another sign of my witchcraft
In the present-day Alex was going down to McAllen Texas
Doing the
Seatbelt snitch
Sleepmelts
Add a little bit of hilarity that these things are
Bananas to I don't spoil anything for you
But this
Caller doesn't
Actually
Have much to say
This next clip gets into a little bit murky
A good bit of explanation that I need to
Attract
On this one
Alex starts talking
Confused
It took a while to sort of disentangle
Some of these these threads
Talking about
Yesterday so I went and got the
Remind people
I can remind
Security
Report where
Of the third world
Free birth control
And my friend
Amazing here's the headline Brazil Washington
Million sterilized
Night
Journal
Directly off
Library of Congress
Infowars
So just listening to this I started with a little bit of confusion
Because he's talking about a report out of Brazil we have this report
Does he have
Is that report it
South
What is the
Port makes sense to me
Because he's
He claims he's read this thing he's posting it it's
The 30-page report of population and Homeland
Security
Okay so
I'm starting to put the pieces together
There's no such report that was not a report out of Brazil that something else this is just National
Security report
I know what he's talk
Talking about it this
It's not doesn't match what he say
Therefore he's referring to his National
Security study memoranda
200 from December 1974
The subtitle of the report is quote implications of worldwide population growth for US security and overseas interests
The problem is that
123 pages long not 30
I don't know what
He's talking about maybe some
Report about that report
Yeah and you would say like all maybe he only read 30 pages everybody didn't read 2 pages of the 30 pages that
He didn't read as124 page
Yeah
Know what
The specific report you talk about it but I do know that underneath it
Is this nssm
And we've talked about it in the past
Particularly in the end game coverage in South what to give a brief recap of it
This is not a plan to sterilize the world
That's a fake version of the document that Alex's imagine because it's really
About providing foreign aid in the form of healthcare and reproductive
Assistance to people in less developed countries
And Alex is
Super again
He's smart enough to know that he would look like an a******
We spent his time passionately yelling about how evil it is to provide Healthcare to people in developing countries
So what he does attack policies and proposals to do just that by pretending that they're actually plans to kill everyone
And he's a hero for telling you about the evil
If you actually go read nssm 200 after having only heard Alex yell about it
One of the things you'll be surprised by how much of the document is not about providing reproductive option
The people in the developing world
At all
In reality
About the implications of the post-world war population growth
That's been seen around the world
And how it could impact the general stability of the world mostly As Seen through the prism
Of US enter
Even as it relates to fertility the document place is equal importance on programs aimed at quote
Improve Healthcare nutrition to reduce child mortality
Education improve social status for women
Increase female employment
Improved old age security and assistance for the rural poor as it does on issues surrounding birth
The word sterilization is used to time so the document in the same paragraph when it's listed as one of these short-term
Consider available to provide improve fertility control
For people in the developing world
This is a list of options like oral contraception IUD and even teaching ovulation
Prediction and the Rhythm
But yeah and sterilization in this context
They've been used
Is things like
Tubal ligation or vasectomy
That's the thing
Sterilization is a word that's a bit load
On the one hand course they're pressured sterilization
Can is definitely hugely an ethical and unacceptable and there is a history of it in the world
And I'm not minimizing
On the other hand there's a long history of people using voluntary sterilization as a method
Control in Brazil is a place with a
An interesting history on that
There's a much larger picture here in a bigger
Your story to unpack then what Alex
Does doing
He's pitching a made-up version of this document from the seventies combining it with a recent headline he's read for Brazil
And declaring his work done
In reality he's done nothing
And he's covering up with actually going on under the surface
The actual news headline here that he has is about an investigation in Brazil into the history of sterilization
Which was said to have been prompted
By reports about nssm 200
In Brazilian Outlet
Instead of talking about the
Details of
Brazilian sterilizations
Actual news stories about
I was just rattles off his normal talk
Talking points about the memo and he passed
Himself on the back
That was unsatisfying for me as a listener
So I decided to look a little bit deeper into the
A little background on the situation that Alex
Important to understand
Tree in Brazil
As discussed by Jose Alves professor of the national school of
Physical sciences
Anthony Brazilian
To geography and statistics title quote
The context of family planning in Brazil
From the early days there was a moratorium on any sort of birth control
Federal decree 2029 one from 1932 quote establish that doctors are forbidden from indulging
In any practice whose aim is to
Prevent contraception
Terminate gestation
In 1941 was passed making it a crime to even advertise processes or substances that we meant to
Acreage
Active choice
As you can probably imagine this didn't stop
Republic
Control options
Navigating a 1965 a group called family well-being Civil Society started providing some Family Planning services
Though they were unable to meet demand and
Even if they could
The ability to provide things like oral contraception was nearly impossible
In the context of
Brazil's laws
The country was playing from
Behind
And it didn't help that in nineteen
64 Brazil is the locality us supported coup
That led to the installation of a military dictatorship
The last until 1985
Over the course of that. Opinions
Begin to soften on Family Planning with it becoming Seymour's at
Matter of individual rights
Some health decision
By the time
That the real progress was being made on the issue of Reproductive Rights
There were already a ton of people in Brazil opted for sterilization is a means of birth
And many of them were women who already had kids
It's and didn't want more
That predates
The nssm
200 Shiloh that Alex is talking about show
What are the primary drivers I've been able to
How to find a identified
Is contributing to a high number of sterilizations in the country
That's due to. Just after the end of the military did
I have the country went through the process of democratization what are the moves that was made with the
Decentralize the medical C
So there would be more local control and responsibility for
For the providing of healthcare
This was a decision to cut it
Into Direction
Particularly in higher poverty less
Developed areas of the country
As explained in an article from the journal population
Development review
From March 2000
M4
Quote
Well efforts to improve and decentralized the administration
The Public Health Care System undoubtedly led to
Number of larger municipalities
It is possible that decentralisation actually fueled
Clientelism
In smaller in 4 minutes paleti's by providing an additional source of assets
To be used for political
Purposes
Decentralisation resulted in a two-tiered system in which the better-off segment
The population Ogden
Good for private
Managed Health Care
While low-income groups were left
Depend on public services
Of uneven or poor quality
In which preventive medicine as well as contraception had long been undervalued
He was in this context as politics and Healthcare provision became deeply entangled
And the demand for contraception Rose Among low-income groups with few alternative options for birth control
It's sterilization acquired importance in
The Client List
Exchange
Of medical care for vote
This paper interviewed many doctors politicians and
And 281 women
In from the Northeast region of the country
Undergone sterilization to understand the Dynamics that we're at play
From the paper
Quote
Considering all are sterilized responded
It's 71% debate said that they took the initiative of ask
Imprint surgery
About 22% reported that the position it's a
Suggested procedure
Ray provided a medical in
Indication for
People want reproductive Healthcare that that they just didn't have access
One doctor they spoke with
Explain the prevalence of sterilization
The reason
One of them is that there's a shortage of other option
Even if something like the pill was available it's only available quote on an irregular basis
Prevents
In this climate where there is demand for birth control and no access to it
People who are in positions
To provide some access
Pop up
The authors of the paper talk to another surgeon to explain quote
In the region there are a lot of Physicians involved in Polish
The mayor is a physician
The ex-mayor to the ex State Deputy elected by the region is a hospital owner in position
Therefore they either perform the operation themselves or they ask a friend
All these mares are friends of physician
Essentially the way it would work is that because
The state
Reimbursed
The doctor for performing
Tubal ligation
They would do it in conjunction with another procedure application
Can't request in order to gain the bureaucracy
Of the 281 women they spoke to 159 had personally asked the politician
For a favor to get a tubal ligation
And 100 said they quote
Turn the favor by voting for them
78 of those 100 even quote
Tried to obtain additional votes for their benefactor
It's a compelling
Snapshot here this mutually beneficial yet
Inherently exploitative system
That arose out of the inability of people to access reliable self-directed reproductive Healthcare
It's always so fascinating to me how I can
I can get curious about a sub
Alex is talking about
Scratch the surface a little bit
And find the exact solution to it is the thing that he opposes the most
Wild
Nothing that I'm saying is meant to minimize or pretend that eugenic applications of sterilization have not been used many times
That's absolutely true
Of course there's a wider story that exist
Austin terms of Brazilian history
Then Alex Karras
To even be curious about
The headline news reporting on at is about this investigation in Brazil and it's nothing new
A parliamentary Commission of inquiry was open
The 1967 to explore accusations of mass sterilization
And another was launched
The 1983
There's a third open in 1991 quote to examine the spread of female sterilization in Brazil and identify persons
Organization
Responsible for AIDS
Miscues
This was followed by a national
Congress investigation in 1992
That was to examine quote
The possible racist motivations behind the provision of sterilization
The role of international agencies in interest
The availability of alternative birth control method
Let's do low-income women
Andy politically-motivated use of tubal ligation
The result was that quote in its final report
The Congressional CPI Echo device
The state's investigation by noting
The pervasive poverty
And the lack of reproductive Health Services
Contributed to women's depends
Sterilization
Haley birth control method
Shocking
No one
Not really
This is been a matter of
It's widely discussed and it's something that has been investigated
And talked about in terms of Brazil
For many years
And I'm fairly certain that Alex doesn't even know about these
These previous investigation
He just think
But recently in Brazil someone found nssm 200
And like the whole thing's
Blowing up an exploding now which is just
Dumb
Alex provides his audience with a dumb butt easy-to-understand story that leads them to accepting
Bad position
If you're opposed to sterilization being used as a birth control method then
Waging a crusade against the widespread access to Alternative birth control methods is exactly the wrong way to do it
Or
You could have
Draconian Crackdown and remove all rights from women
There are two ways to go yeah there are two ways to go I'm not saying that one is better than the other
Yeah and I found really difficult was that like
I
Don't know
Like obviously I would never say
That
The use of sterilization or
Tubal ligation
That wasn't
It wasn't as widely
Yeah it discussed in the sources that I was able to find
I wouldn't ever
Pretend to be naive enough to think that there was a
Any abuse
No even the system that that that one paper that I found
Discussing the clientelism aspect of it.
Poor
Less-developed areas
Like that is intrinsically exploitative
Is f***** up never happened like this
If everyone had a
Exactly
Aunt Angie what is available to be offered as an unfair Exchange
Of course
I wouldn't
Bat
That there aren't in
Instances of also
Abuse
It's people
It's just
The stories that you hear about
Sterilization campaigns
Being used as methods of
Of genocide are eugenics
Or what Alex wants you to think every single birthday
Control
Executive ever has been
And that's unfair because I think it's a disservice to the campaigns that have happened
Yeah
No
It's
It is it is
Typical Pharrell
Simply because
You can't
Before any kind of birth can
You you just can't like there's no way for Alex
Text to square being like okay it's okay for sterilizations if there's no other available birth
Control method
So it always has to be wrapped up in something else
Being
A murder
That's the only way you can talk about
Birth control through his eyes
Politics don't allow for you to be able to dictate what someone can do with their own body like if you say
Play I want that person
Things a woman they do
It can't ever be someone's
Rational choice
To engage in a birth
Control
I could always has to be some sort of a conspiracy where you at
Intuit cuz if it is 1 time a rational Choice then that means that there are other people who can make that same rational choice in the
Then all the sudden there are a lot of things that you have to reconnect your license maybe that's a ration
Call Joyce 2
Until it becomes reasonable to assume that some forms of birth control
Are rational actors and then your whole argument about how everybody's trying to kill you
Is kind of a god
It hurts
So this
This conversation is
About birth
That's about
Reproductive
Brights and how
But Alex takes this story about Brazil
You can
Season pivot it
Because he doesn't know really what anything is about me has a certain amount of talk
3 points
Any makes it about vaccines
Because
He also believes that they're going to sterilize the third world through putting Secret
Put stuff in vaccines and stuff
And so he just takes the story and makes it about that because it works
People wonder why the mail
Thousand Island
The come out years after
Dissipated report
Who don't use drugs
Europe
Percent
Third world
Do G
It is still about vaccines that he's yelling over and Children's Museum
Has anybody getting to White
Fear there
Quite a bit
Yes we will grandkids I have not heard of any new grandkids
It's now I mean technically in the past two years I have had three combined nieces and
Nephews appear into this world
But
Who's grandchildren look stupid stupid
Stupid
I don't know I I don't want to
Speak too much
About like
Not believing a lie
I feel like I do it too much
I wonder I wonder if these people that he knows
You can't have kids are made up
The lieutenant colonel's he talks about all the time
Country made up
So I got to tell my I got to tell my family to start back
Connecting their kids
I want him to stay at that babe you know how some people are like all I wish they could stay this age forever
Guys
Covid vaccine
Now three years old forever
I ate your Nutella
Terrifying moment
Oh no
I said that Alex mix things up
After I forgot
Infowars.com
Out of
Now is the time
For America
We could not wait any longer
Certainly can't wait eighteen more years
Got to be done so I'm sorry I'm sorry that I
You've got a good case for libel
Probably
So here's something that Alex is making out
Only
Only a few
What
Alright escalated three levels very quickly
You thought it was doctor's bulshit military industrial complex
Chirp
No you thought it was real Terry dustrial complex
300 people know the real truth
About vaccines
What's that you Pikachu 300 people know it's 300
Literal Nazi
I just also like to see this in
Turtle relationship with Alex
Complaining whatever and calling him a Nazi
Because everybody not to the Past
Everybody
Seatbelt through problem
Well that's because they are
That's alright
His history has borne out that you can't get much more seriously in the present
It seems like it
As we discussed on pretty much every 2003 episode
What are things I'm most interested in
Is trying to figure out if Alex believes he's fighting the literal Christian devil
I'm still not sure I'll vote
This gets me a little closer
Believe
And so close to the I got to quit
It can be described
Titov hell forces
Quite there
And even though he said Massive Attack
The song is named the angel not devil so we can maybe
Also teardrop
Yep yep there was that one theme song from
What was the did they do the entire soundtrack for a Jet Li movie where he was a
He's a dog that he was Jet Li was captured by a British gangster
Dollar Tree
Oh they're on the smash soundtrack by friend
Don't you dare say they're not even if they're not they are
Spiritually snatch soundtrack to talk about seatbelt
Stuff ending up in ransacking at the Armory but
We're about to go to
The whole nine yards
Enduring
Guard Armory
That sucks
But it's also like
Alright
There's no passion behind it and hopefully early pay
Programming or whatever it's clearly an ad
I don't I don't think that unethical
It's a little bit
Disjointed
Somewhat
Whatever it's at how you would
Expect ads
To work
In a radio show even though it is more like
Here's a topic we're going to get into before we get to that
I want to talk to you about a sponsor
Like I'm playing that because that's not how he does it
Bellator * 8
So eroded TV show where they would cut in with a
Actual actor from the show me like we're having a grand time watching this thing first let me tell you about
Thompson's
Yeah I also think that Alex's sales pictures of
A little underwhelming
They have
This thing
Capri catalog
It doesn't feel like you feel like someone who's super familiar with
Super X
I like whatever you're doing it ad rated the middle of it
You get mad that you have to
Continue doing
100 Pages catalog
Guy calls in or this gas
Cuz this guy might as well be a f****** call her p**** is a gas
Either
Handsome
Experience with the click it or ticket
Campaign
I guess
That takes you to the armory
I don't know if this guy actually
He did
What I would imagine that would be hard
So
Who's listening to the details of this guy story everything I can tell you
There was just
Like a traffic
Stop sure
He didn't have to stop
But other people did
Okay
Alex makes it a little bit Ray
We were allowed to pass through
Although we drove very very slowly after
Stop
They stopped the Volvo with a very old
Chloe passed out
Emmanuel
Ground
That Middle America was a little tell a little America
Middle America
Eclipse
Is about a minute-long and it begins
With this guy who's the caller saying that he went right through the checkpoint
I don't I didn't hear the part where you said I was wearing a giant turbine
Well I mean bats
That's assumed with all of
The avelle conversation just because if you are driving through Austin you know the only way to avoid the conflict
Turbine this guy's not in Austin
To be fair alright he's in Alabama
He's in Alabama
Traditionally I have not seen turbines treated well in Alabama
Thermador click it or ticket Alabama
This interview is
The definition of
Why is this happening yeah
I don't know you went to a checkpoint you saw
Couple of people
People's over
Adele
Look I have a small percentage chance of receiving a ticket so Alex is going to turn this into a vest
Rachel conspiracy to destroy White
Basically
Another story that Alex is trying to make people scared about to do with fingerprints
Scans being used for school lunches
We'll talk about that a tiny bit
After he
Pretends to be very emotional
Imagine the movie
And now there are dust
Call home
Grocery store
New York
You want to fight
Wow
The only way to solve these problems
Sparta promote Alex's
Product I just seems almost too easy
Too easy to defeat the global it all put all roads lead to that bottleneck
The solution
Is free publicity for Infowars
It's really convenient for him
The story about the the fingerprint this wasn't mandatory
Students could choose to use a PIN number instead of their fingerprint if they wanted to and from a 2005 article about this
Graham quotes
About 4% of students have chosen that up
They're right they can choose that they want
Apparently this is a really good system for school lunches for a couple of reasons
The first is that it streamlines overcrowded school lunch line
Which is a problem
And in May
Overcrowded schools
The second is that by making the transaction to uniform in appearance you completely eliminate the stigma that many kids
Fila Theron launch assist
Program
I haven't been in school in a while but when I was I do remember that the kids got free lunch got picked on
For being poor
And that system that you have their eliminates that possibility which I think is a really good thing
Yeah it's a shity system where you just by being born or made fun
In terms of privacy issues there definitely something
But they were discussed in the positives outweigh the
The concerns and the concerns were addressed
A copy of the students fingerprint is
Connected to a unique identifier but the stored data isn't the actual finger
Also quote parents who do not want their child fingerprinted May obtain an opt-out form
Upground of this
I don't know I just don't
Yeah
I don't know why
This is
The most pressing issue in the world to me can never be can you imagine
Making a
Sci-fi film in the seventies and thinking
Oh they'll use their fingerprints to get lunches
What's that smell
Things to make
If every time I use my f****** credit card I tap it against
Nothing and it references
Ridiculous amount of information about me in an instant and then comes back and they know it.
No one cares
The notion of
Creating a database
Of children's
Fingerprint
Is a little bit
F***** up
Sure and that's not what they were doing
And I'm secondary relieved it was all so f***** up the idea
Like this is a concern that I think
Is very
It is
If you keep that all on file that seems like something someone could hack
Totally
My concern is also addressed and not storing the
Fingerprint
I bet
Storing is like a numerical identifier
Affect
It's not like
These concerns weren't something that
The people who put this
System
The place
Didn't think about
Yeah
Yeah it does seem like all-too-often many of the complaints that Alex brings towards any kind of system Arthur
Things that you could just
Address well
Instead of being like Walter Mitty
Flaws in the system they're just like
Bugs
Broken workout
The real complain
But he has or the ones that are based in reality are things that people are aware of
And other people are conversing about in
Reasonable rational towns reality
The things that are nonsense
But he's yelling about are all just things too
The appeals to the emotions of the audience in order to bring them closer to that bottleneck
Gets them to making 100 copies of his movie Cheese's
Have you got to do it man or else
Epr
Get in the fight by reproducing how has to give to people as free promotion
Or it's over
Just awful
A man for an initial investment of $50
Just $2 a day
You can make
Sure
That Alex Jones
Will be richer than you can imagine
Can you
Can you just open your heart
This sales pitch is not compelling can you change it save in America
It's going to wherever you don't
Make this $2 a day Sacra
Click it or ticket
Soldiers oh my God
Rip your children away from you how you come to a snugglers high-schoolers with submachine
Guns in Greg uniform
It's
Chaos
For just $2 a day though
What does talk a little bit about 9/11
Stuff during this. But not anyway they like I feel like we're going to go ahead and cover this now
But what's really fascinating
Is listening to how his tone is so different
From the present
Wendy's ask Direct
Questions like
Like what happened with 911 now to be like
You know what I don't know
I know everything I know now he made a movie about
Multiple multiple movies
I know everything
Look we got a
Dead to rights we have all the proof
Yeah I think I kind of forgot it is interesting that he's easy to place where it's like
Somehow he existed in space where we've learned Less in the intervening time
Broke when he started
Somehow forgotten about what should be the most important thing that for him to under
Stand inside and out
Your entire career is based off of
This
Thing I find myself
Every now and again remembering
King bed in the present day
He doesn't answer direct questions
It gets really funny
Things that makes this very tolerable
Another thing
What's that mean
Xmas tolerable Jordan
The caller that you're excited we have connect
The fuk down
Control
I was recently
Surrounded by the military
Bonsai
I'm raising
I was lured away from
Chargers
Why was there
Tigers on my Cropper
While I was there
The military
Skating
The military were high
High-fiving each other
And laughing
No
Okay
Are you are you telling me that all that happened is we just missed out on Tiger King by 20
Years because nobody would listen to Alexander show is that what's really going on isn't this is not Joe exotic
Yeah but I was like
Holyshit
You can't get calls like this
Home regular shows
You can go to have a crazy show cuz you're not get this call
From Howard Stern
And if you did to be an actor
About this that I just
Couldn't resist getting to the bottom of
I was like I've already spent a bit of time preparing this episode
This is towards the end of May 29th July
Bucket starting over I don't care
Here's the color on Alex's show
Who had a Siberian tiger
Taken away from una raid hahaha
That's got to be in some newspaper somewhere right red alert
I had absolutely no idea where to go with this but
I use some Clues
I was able to find something that look promising
Listcawler says that he is in Minnesota and honestly how many Siberian tiger seizures could there possibly be in Minnesota
Every year I don't know
I found an article in
Albert Lea Tribune from January 2003 about a raid on a house where female baby tiger was taken quote
Because the owners did not have a permit
For possessing the wild animal
This seems like a wiener
It seems close
It sounded right
Problem though is that the owner of this tiger is a seventeen-year-old kid who said that his fifteen-year-old sister is
That's the owner
I don't know I don't know much but I don't believe this color is 17
Then I read this little nugget in the Tribune article
Quote
Peter also emphasized the past record of the child's father who is also lived in the house
Sing it indicates the families inability to provide appropriate care for the Tiger
The father was barred from having a pet by the court in October 2001 as a penalty for cruelty to animals
However the child said his father is not living at the residence anymore
I'm intentionally not using these people's names because
Was as I was getting into this I have no idea if
If they are the people who were
Call the doctor
How many raids resulted in the confiscation of a baby tiger went down to the first few months of 2003 in Minnesota
I can't imagine that the numbers higher than one
And
Now we know that this is a family business
I found a follow-up article that include some other bizarre details
Apparently that whole thing the tiger seizure was set in motion
Because the child quote head
Scratches and B Martin was falling asleep in class
When asked what was up
Quote tool.
Teacher that he lived with a tiger and it smelled bad
Police searched the house and found a malnourished 35lb tiger cub as well as a bunch of urine and feces
Porcine I was completely obsessed with the story by this point
So I had to keep looking around
Yeah I've if this was the story that this person who's calling into Alex's show I can match the story to the
Caller
Hey was very excited yeah yeah I can see I can see it's palpable
Put up by Peta of all tiger cub related incidents in the United
Midstates and guess what
This was not the tiger case that prompted this call to Alex's show
Wow I was able to find Grant
This caller on the list from PETA
So that means in the first five months of 2003
There were two tiger cub incidents in Minnesota
What are the f****** odds
To be fair though I do want to make this clear the guy who's keeping
The tiger cub at home with his kid the story we just talked about
Did by his tiger from this caller
So there is a connection
I
New
That there had to be some kind of connection
You had to know there's a
That's just
Awful guys name brand
And he ran a business called tiger Zone
And he's also pretty full of s***
About others didn't make any news outlets
The reason he's in trouble here is that in March 2003 one of his Tigers quote
B a sixteen-year-old girl in Grafton b a pregnant woman on the wrist
Tiger zone is a place where people could come and look at the product animals
Reports of people being attacked by his cats
The past but people have been reluctant to press charges until the sentence
Would you like to the downfall of tigers own
And a police search of Grant's home where they found some
This would not be the end of Grant trying to hurt people of tigers
In 2005 he was arrested after a woman whose
Employee cleaning up after some of the Tigers was attacked and seriously wounded
Anyway this guy's lying to Alex about the circle
Stances of his run-in with the police
And yes
Stewart you brought up Tiger King
After the success of that documentary Grant's nephew tried to kick-start a documentary up about this whole thing but it apparently didn't
Takeoff
But also in the kickstarter it says
This is not just because tiger can't happen
Yeah I did say it sounds like that's exactly what you would say if it was just because Tiger King happened I think that there is probably
Interesting story to what
Done with this guy
The trailer for his documentary
There's probably some
Experiences of people who are involved
That are worth hearing about like
I don't know if it's This Guy's daughter or who
In the dark in the trailer giving
Currently about how hard it was to watch
We will take away these tigers
You know like that she knew and cared about
As friends or pets
And how they work
Treating a very harsh
Sweet I think
Valuable thing to hear about
Help people
I don't know
But this guy is not
Bye.
Where will the military looking for bombs
Took his tiger cub
Anyway
I would say that the fact that he's sold the tiger to this person who was keeping it in their house
And the tiger was peeing and shiting in the house
And recklessly around this child
It means
He's not
Necessarily
Due diligence
Invading
Who is able to
To adopt
Yeah that's a red flag
Along with the multiple people who were attacked by
Saint all kinds of s*** the red flag I mean just just like
Pte exam
Exotic animal zoo
Is a the biggest red flag I can think of
I don't know if that's
Actually the case
I mean I can understand why you think a lot of times it is
But I don't want to stigmatize people who do actually take
Take care of
Animals
Yeah but a lot of times in order to make
Enough money to provide care for some of these animals
You may need to like
Have people will be able to come look at them
Because there are people who do that responsibly and within
In the parameters of
Not
The nuts
Grete and I would say that it's probably more than the others I would say there more people who do it responsibly then
Irresponsible
At the same time
Still reply
And it's not even like I think it's evil or malicious or anything it's just like
There should always be somebody there should always be a neutral third-party Observer on the ground at all time
I'm being like
It's one of those Industries those where it's
You can't even have
Like that but any self-reporting is just not pause
Our regulations needs to be better
Reasons of human safety and
The welfare of the albums that sells
What that guy was doing to that f****** tiger
Randy's kid
Justice f****** disgusting
And again just to be totally clear that is not the color although the guide itself
Animal
You know that
You're implicated a tiny bit your not being like if you're f****** selling a tiger in
Minnesota
You should
Do a lot of background work on who are you selling this
Possibly take care of
It's a goddamn
Are they a person who's going to put the Tiger in their
So you don't get a tiger
Excited about the story
Snow
Media coverage of it or whatever
He thinks like I got a fresh lead here on time
Government abuse what's going on
Guy tells his story or his version of it and Alex just accept it unquestioningly
This is
Kind of bad
Activist
Open
They have to
Graft
Industrial lighting
5 * on the
Grabber
Yes
So yeah
16 year old who got attacked by what
Cats
Just lied
Yep yep she lied in court five times and in writing three times so the story was exactly this
The same every time and that's how you know she's lying
Well I mean like a
This is
An interesting wave
To present the story to Alice
What's Jones
Alex should not just
Except immediately all their lying about what happened
Cuz maybe
Someone got attacked by a lion
I just
Unquestionably accepting this guy's version of the story only serves to use them as a prop
To push your the government's out-of-control in one take your tigers
Yeah I heard of which is
Silly and there's a bit of a credibility gap
There's a bit of a credit credit
I think also there's a Justin
Issue with
I know that it
It's 2003 and Alex isn't as
You know grosser figure
In the public Consciousness as he is now at this point
But this guy
Soffit
Call Alex and talk about this story
And that that's an indicator
Yeah that tells you what kind of reaction he's looking for it the very least
Yeah or where he would go to Astoria positive spin on this story
Because it won't be anybody legitimate
Got to get those tigers
Fun little
Path of
To figure out like a
I had
So many walls I ran into trying to sort out what happened here
And the issue is like
There were too many
Kernels of information I'd like
There's no possible way I can't figure out who this guy is
Look at how this has to be
And there it happened four times that's
Not possible that's not possible
So weird like there's not other there are other years where multiple
Instances of
Tiger into the Cabin Inn
Minnesota America has the most
Concentrated number of tigers just because of private ownership but
Not not
Felt like a Minnesota thing
Writes like I'm looking over this list and like in 2000
Clear 2000s from PETA
There were two incidents
Regarding
Tigers in
Natural Bridge Virginia
But that's
Because they both happened at the same Zoo
That makes sense
It's so nuts
But there's two different
Separate
Stories in Minnesota
I mean granted I guess the fact that he sold it makes them
I'm connected stories right
I mean you know but that it does make sense if you've got a disreputable Tigers who operate
Who is willing to sell car
You are going to find out you have more than one incident about tigers it in your region
Very soon
That is that is
Probably a truism
So Alex complains about that how you'll be arrested for pissant Stuff
Like in Germany
Yeah if you don't open your mouth at the dentist
Your parents a rest of the public
And then Alex said something really f***** up
Ohio
Five-year-old
A what
Tell what
Yeah what is that caught me a bit off guard
For what purpose
To whom
Also
Even leaving aside whatever the reality of the story is a articulating it
Silence says a h plus
Interview with a guy named Michael Hagan
And I don't know who this guy is
A book that I can't find even by Googling the name of the book don't know how to spell is
Last name that's not great
Could be anyway number of different yelling
Eh
And
I tried to figure out just like what the bottom line about him was
Was but I wasn't really that interested so I don't really mind that I did
Figure it out because he's just kind of a guy with the standard newworldorder tough
Just kind of someone is playing a game of boring ping-pong with Alex
Hitting the ball back in
Until I find it fitting
That he didn't get enough traction from being on Alex's show.
To penetrate the Consciousness to the point where he's even Google it
So it makes more sense for him to definitely not even penetrate onto our show
And I think that I probably would ignore his appearance cuz it's really boring until they end up taking calls
Now you're talkin
Go well
I fell for handling the mutual funds
I took your advice
I got all the market when I'm setting
Cordell Jones
On 400
7-Eleven
Text back and forth
Montpelier books
The right beside my copies of voice
Planet Earth
You worry about several years on the peak of the market
Infowars.com
Mainstream Publications
Stuff
The 35,000 are gold
Have you been watching
Ringgold
I've been watching and I've been watching
And for the last 9 years
Recommended
Play religious
What the
Mian
I wasn't even back on the airbag
Freedom
Do a talking point
Yeah it's this caller is not happy with Michael Higa
Flappable
No. Seem to give a s***
Hello
I listen to your show I know I know that you said
Come on now
Nice try I've been you been lying to me for 9 years I have several
Dollars worth of gold to prove it
Don't let them talk too much more it just heard a bigger
About gold a little bit
And address the question more like once
She is gone
Maybe I was a little bit if you look at
Know whatever
Fun I like I like to stick around if you're going to have a have a little conversation
Take another call
Protecting mr. hege as you did from the last caller was Noble of you
Bartow we read his book
Department of Syracuse University
Syracuse New York
Hagar's book and used it as a reference
Oh that's a one-two punch that they were not expecting
Another caller
Do you like Alexa
F*** you I was going to be at 4
Go f*** himself
So I wanted to play more of this collar but there isn't much of it because it's just
It just deteriorates
Into yelling
Yeah
Just yells over and doesn't allow any points to be made
Creates a false version of the things that he saying in order to be like
How do you know what that guy was saying Pat nuts
Guy was nuts
Baby
Just maybe
Still being very
Nice
To Michael haga in this interview
But maybe
Some of that negative response
I had something to do with why we don't know who you could have some
Something to do with that
Maybe the audience
Not thrilled with the idea this guy being on and Alex will take note of that I'm not come back on
As much
In the future, I also honestly if I were Alex I wouldn't have them on and not because
Just
Strictly from the negative reaction but like
He isn't bringing much else to the table shake you don't get from
What Alex's or anybody else he could have on the Federal Reserve is bad
My God I can't get a hundred other people to say that
The benefit of having him on is
Is kind of
Dwarfed by clearly
The negative phone calls
I thought that was pretty fun
Selfie
The 29th
Just being this like
Pylon Michael Hagan
And a Colorado
This f****** tiger taken away all good watch fun what a good day good day and he doesn't think it is
You but it's a great day
Can't like
You can't prepare
For what you're going to get
Alex Jones in 2003 like a box
Chocolate
That is so vital I would almost imagine like if I was
Planning a show where I knew Alex
Was going to have a gold guy on
I would have a giant
Button with an x on it for if Annie
Econ professor
Just like I button I could run to press
Technical difficulties just a thin line just I agree with you but
Trump Michelangelo's presentation of himself he's not like a super gold guy he's not one of those guys
Do the like a lot of Alex's other
Buddy
Apparently
Had some
Opinions about gold over there
It's unclear
Didn't let that one call or speak his peace
He's fully and I think if they had I'd have a better sense of
Or is this guy was googleable at all he was invested in the
Dial when I was up high and the guy was like it's going to collapse right just put it all into gold
Gold going to Skyrocket up to $3,000 an ounce or whatever it is and then you'll be a billionaire in the guy was like
I was at 11,000 dickhole yeah a little bit
But it didn't move nearly as much as
That's the sense that I got for sure
Seem like
The kind of thing
Things that people in the right wing
Space specially
It happens to him a lot
Like Alex in the Nigerian princes
Right-wingers and gold scams are always
They walk hand-in-hand oh yeah
So
We've come to the end of this
Adventure in 2000
3 +
Some of that stuff
But I also think it's very valuable to recognize these little glimpses where Alex speaks a little bit more about his
Positions
That we kind of
Got the sense were admirable
Like his opposition to the death penalty a preference for drug legalization
These things are things that you can agree with
I guess
In terms of like
The end result of them
Sure
You can't agree with how you get
Yeah because you can't agree with how you get there you are
Actually can't agree on the end result
Because for me
I think the end result of opposition to death penalty
Execution
Opposition
Intuit.
For Alex
Clearly that is not
Because
You can see
But his opposition is based in
I distrust
Cast of
Some people who are running
In the federal government
Damn if those circumstances changed and he is now
Totally fine
With a
Excuses
State-level
There isn't actually agreement
He is for all intents and purposes
Ipro death penalty person
Just to get some
Doesn't like bull sharks
Yeah
I mean the the thing that gets
Me about that though is that it's like
Because he's so malicious
And so
I expose fungible
Anon
On just about anything
Like no matter what it is you agree with him on
She doesn't
Care about anything
Other than
Finding a way to
Give himself and do white men more
So even if you were you can't like
Agree with him on an issue and then
Come together or even work together or or anything towards that because if he's given
Eniac
He's going to take whatever access he's given
And funnel it towards
The point of a white male
So even if you can talk
They have about
Because he's only issue
Beyond all the take
Sun on the news of the day
Is like the end result of all of this should be white men running
Be specific
Yeah and I'll even get that like from other the other issues that he ends up covering
During this
X Equis complaining about these click it or ticket thing
Yeah yeah yeah
Why is talking about immigration
Is it is concerned about immigration rules like they're going to
All of your jobs are going to be
You're going to make lassi
All of it does
There's ghost towns in Germany that they're bringing immigrants into to run like
They're even said they'll replace it you know you're it's like Cheese's
Christ we get it
You're awake Nash
All all
Bottlenecks of his ideology
You go there has bottlenecks there
Add everything about action
7 specific things
Stop
Any of this is
Promote my shed and then eventually of course once they start selling pills
There we go
Only solution
Into
Globalism is
Supplement
Bad documentaries
We're also on Twitter
Please find a local charity or bail Fund in your area to help out
People doing God's work right
But until then I know you I'm busy X
No grandchildren for you
Alexandra Thurston color