I have great respect for knowledge but I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Dot-com
Everybody welcome back and I'll try to sit around and talk a little bit about
Alex Jones
Jordan Jordan
Jordan is the continuing of the button
Sending them out
What are things that I mentioned that a previous episode was the guy we're taking care of the postage and everything
So inclined
Because a lot of people have offered
Paper postage
2 number of people in foreign countries
I understand
Meson on people's generosity
Metaphorically
You know why you sneeze there but be that as it may
Are we could do is find a charity and donate in the name of saline
My cat over the world
I got a really
Awesome thing
That I wanted to share this is my brights Bach
Frederick h
Adopted
An elephant
In Kenya alright alright I'm listening I'm listening
Meet my cat
Celine
Is now the foster parent of bond any
Baby elephant
Oh my God
That's that's one of those moments where you're like I didn't realize the scope of this
Your cat is fostering a baby elephant and then you're like okay the world's got great something so great about the creativity
The Listener is like Frederick as well like this
I got taking the ball and running with it
It's a doing something really
Cool lands
Overwhelmingly beautiful
Yes those are personal message
Which came in with that that is my neck is
Ashley large
From the elephant
That's true so thank you for everything was really awesome and really bright
My my
Yeah I just
My mom is a huge elephant person
It was a nice Coincidence of the
Parent relationship
Now we just need
Now we just need to
Unite them and have
Celine stand atop
Offended all time we're heading to Canton I think we have to
Absolutely
What's your bright spot is far less
Sequential kind of makes me feel a little embarrassed at this is my bright spot
Have you ever had a cutting
Candy grape
Stan
No I was trying to think of what they did
Flavor God
I see now this is the opposite
Cotton candy flavor grape
It taste like cotton candy
Cotton candy really is just
Sugar
Sugar grapes
Understand alright and this is why it's my bright spot
Judging is a
Exactly as defensive about that as you would imagine it's not just sugar it seriously
Cotton candy and they know that your is your first reaction is going to be like
Oh okay so they're sweet grape
And then you eat one in your like s*** this tastes like cotton
Candy and there
Judging is so f****** divots like
Do you think it's just sugar
Give us a chance give us a chance
Weird yeah I know
Fantastic
Candy grapes
Well that's cool. I'll keep my eyes open
Great
Also I saw that someone posted a picture of
These Skittles gummies with weed in them
Samsung mail them to us I think that still with federal crime so you should be able to find them no based on
The legality here in the city of Chicago
Episode to go over
What about
4th of July
Which is Alex's Fourth of July honestly
You know it metaphorically it's his
Big Daddy
It's the it's the Christmas in July sale
Christmas
Yeah it's a little bit something else entirely
Work before we get to that
We're going to get deep
Giving someone life is giving someone death
You can say that
Good
I'll never get tired of that just the
Heavy simple
The simple-minded confusion
Whenever he lands upon you know
Life and death are one in the same it's just perfect
Text ya just love it I love it so much he is a philosopher
Also Elaine newzealand happy birthday
Sweetapple listenership in New Zealand
The surprises me a little bit I love it and
That is something that I definitely would consider
Going to do a song
Excuse to go to New Zealand in order to get citizenship in New Zealand you need a sponsor in
Hey if you are a walk
I might need it
Also Jeffree Star Anna a happy birthday so happy birthday Diana
Diana brother Sean
John the brother of this person
Message didn't want
This brother
I didn't know how to braid
Happy birthday happy birthday
Jonna said quote
I don't have to say quote primary source
The Washington Post
Thank you for helping me become the Wonka a day or perhaps I should be asking for an apology
Unquote
Yeah I would I would very much
Be disappointed if you didn't and those brackets otherwise we got to make sure I got over
Slanderous
So Jordan out on the 4th
Was over the weekend
Put out a special report
They put out a report on
On the 4th
I thought was
You know
Underwhelming okay
Think about
Captain's hat
I got to stop right there early
But he is wearing that captain's hat that may or may not be the same one from his Halloween store
One from his
Halloween store
In order for him to be like
I wonder.
Is that bad
Thanks I'm going to try to charge my
Believe CNN
The New York Times
Fauci
Example
I'm declaring
Independence
And the globalist
One person one household
1 State 1
The big interview in emerging
Broadcast
That
Podcast
Can you do 1
Demonetized
Because their cover
This episode of Rogan's podcast but Alex is referring to came out on June 22nd
And didn't feature to scientist covid-19
If you did one scientist make a quarry and what member of the intellectual dark web named Brett wine
If you don't remember Bret Weinstein
I envy you
You Rose to problem
It's because he was a professor at Evergreen State College and got really mad about the 2017 day of abs
Have you forgot about that it was
Are minority students
Some faculty members confused
Stay off campus has a way of celebrating
But things they bring to the
Yeah I remember
Decided to try to reverse the experience and ask
Tobacco Tita voluntarily stay off
This guy so much out of this and took it upon himself to enlist the help
Fox News
Turn this into one of the most
Pressing matters of free speech in America
This national attention Charlie made the situation on campus more intense and protests began escalated Wichita
Culminated in Weinstein and his wife resigning from the school and suing for 3.8 billion dollars
Climbing at the school that failed to protect him from Stu
Shoes for 250,000
Dollars each
Which is a ridiculously small amount for the couples
Except unless they knew they were lucky
Need to get anything yeah they were very
Gaston Rogan a few times and it's just a general dumb dumb hanging out with idiots like Jordan Peterson and
Dave Rubin
In the 2020 election he uses position to try to drive Tulsi gabbard
On the unity2020 ticket
Well that would have done it that would have solved that better
Because that's what would have happened on that one
What ticket would appeal to the left and the right order nobody can't think of more of an oxymoronic
Statement that emergency
Podcast
Yeah that is weird sort of joke
Also Bret Weinstein brother is another
Remember the intellectual dark web
Who's one of the managing directors at teal capital
That company of course is run by Peter teal who famously made giant donations
The trumps 2016 camping
Boca the Republic
Intervention that year and of course bankrolled Hulk Hogan's lawsuit that took down Gawker
Yeah there's it there's very little difference
Between teal
Capital and the Legion of Doom
The weinsteins are
Super cool
The Great
Lately Brett has been getting some covid territory and
Been widely rebuke
Republic promotion
Ivermectin
The cure for the virus
He was going on Rogan
Didn't show to discuss this along with
This doctor friend
Pierre Corey is a doctor who's been making very suspect claims about Ivermectin since at least late 2020 calling you
Get a quote wonder drug
Even though the actual evidence for such a
The claim is very lacking
There are some studies that appear to indicate slight benefits that
Could come from Ivermectin but they are far from descendants
Other studies showed no Bennett
The drug the drug
There just isn't consist
Good data to show that it's a qrm people go around promoting it is such a
Acting in ways that are
Super dangerous for the General Public
Anyway
Fourth of July special report and he decided to open by talking about her Joe Rogan didn't episode 2 weeks ago with this doctor
16 overhyping Ivermectin
And that's a declaration of
Independence or something this sad
Yeah that's
That's great
This is a mess
You know July is history about the 4th of July episode
Listen to The History of the United
Midstates I just want to say that one of the big problem
Sunset really is coming back to bite us
Is our long history of loving
Snake oil salesman to the point where now you can hear the word wonder drug
And I go
Oh you mean snake oil and other people are like
I love Wonder drugs in your leg while we're just stuck with this forever
This is just how we live we made a mistake in being like
Like
Cheer it rooting for the the scam artists needle
Phil Hartman crushing the monorail song we would be way better off
You think that's where it's at all goes back to the Sims
Everything goes back on this episode
This special report to Brogan
I guess.
That's what the 4th of July the bout
We got these are too big scientist
Censored demonetized
YouTube
To have them on
Discouraged
A few days ago
So I guess I want to watch the whole thing and didn't realize the bright wines
Seeing isn't day censored covid doctor
Cuz weird courage it
To bring
To dum dum scam artist onto York
100 million dollar podcast
Spray listened by the most number of
People in the world
Also sent to come out and before this Fourth of July report that I was doing
Rogan
Quentin Tarantino on his
The gas what you did
Infuriate Alex
Alex hates Quentin Tarantino
And Joe should know better than that kind of a globalist on his show
I'm going to get people to travel an emergency episode
Oh man I'm going to try and get back on
So we got a little headline here so that way
The defender had a
Robin's emergency podcast question
YouTube Center
I'm content
You hear the defender
No
That seems like an interesting citation I didn't really hurt him toss out that is a place he got news from before
I thought that was just like a person
Who is defending
Tweet to Twitter Defender Defender is Ableton Outlet
Turns out it's an online publication put out by group called The Children
There we go that's an anti-abortion group
Christian bulshit
I love defending the healthy children know everybody does have
Children's events
Anti-vax outfit run by Robert Kennedy Jr
Baby Gannon 2016 being called the world Mercury project potential
A name probably because they want to try it
Obscure the fact that they are out Now intent
Anti-vax
Advocates as opposed to Independent providers of information
To reseed them
Nonno's got to Mercury being in the vaccine
Axiom propagandist it makes
No sense why they would call their Outlets up the Kentucky with like the defender
So you can say their articles about sounding like you're the kind of person who takes forever
Kennedy Junior seriously
Cuz that's one of the sources
Consider is not fake news
Pretty sweet
That's real great
Graton real great
It's kind of funny how they get like
Hated by people who are anti-vax people who get
A money from being anti-vax people
And by putting this out
People are less likely to take vaccines and more likely to give money
To the anti-vax people who pay
For the coverage in the defender
Some people
I'm starting to see how this busy
Model work
It is it works it doesn't work
So we have one last clip of this Fourth of July Special Report with
What is italics in the middle of a field or maybe his backyard I don't know
Chavez had on
Probably taking a break
Europa BBQ barbecued hamburger around
Call Rob do passed out on a chair
Got it Buckley is fixing on the ones and twos they had to ask him to turn off the music
Look for a little bit Special Report
Yeah this is this is the last little blip I have
So I hereby declare
From the New World Order
Again
I pledge my life my honor my
Find
Everything I am
Tommy Oliver Liberties Thomas Jefferson
Over every form of tyranny
So I mean like your response
Is so right I mean
Discussion about Jefferson and Alex
Scalded himself
I don't I think that we've gone into this a little bit in the past but I want to read you the larger context of that Jeffers
Quotes
This is from a letter from 1800 that he sent to me
Monroe
Quote
I promise you a letter on Christianity which I have not forgotten
On the contrary is because I've reflected on it that I find much more time necessary for it then I go
At present
Disposed of
I have a view of the subject with which ought to displease neither rational Christian or dies
And would reconcile many to a character they have too hastily reject
I do not know however it would reconcile the irritable tribe of prophet
It's who are all in arms against
Their hostility is onto interesting ground to be softened
The delusions into which the XYZ plot
Shoot it possible to push
The people
This whole experiment made under the prevalence of that delusion on the cause of the Constitution
Well it secure the freedom of
The Press covered also the freedom of religion
Given to the clergy affair
Favorite hope of a
Obtaining an establishment
Of a particular form of Christianity through the United
States
And does every sect believes its own form.
True one
Perhaps
Hope for E-Town
But especially the episcopalians and congregational
The returning good sense of our country threatened
Is abortion to their hopes
They believe that any position of power conveyor confided to me
Will be exerted in
Position to their scheme
And they believe truly
Bribe sworn upon the altar of God Eternal hostility against every form of tyranny over the mind of man
But this is all they have
You're from me
And
Slavery is every form of tyranny over the
Google well it is true that Thomas Jefferson said essentially the words that Alex loves to quote the reality is that
Everytime Alex repeat
That's saying he's using it incorrect
The contact the Jefferson said those words and had to do with an opposition
To Christian churches using
The first
Freedom of religion
To establish what would effectively be an official religion of the United States
Around 1,800 he would have absolutely been one of the irritable tribe of prophets who were at war with
Jefferson
The irony of Alex using this quote to pump himself up in his quest to bring about a Christian theocracy in the United
That is not lost on me
It's understood the primary resources he uses I honestly think that this would be a plus troll
Using this quote in the way that he uses it while pushing
For the things that you push
It's analogous exactly to their form of Christianity insofar as
It's like
It says what we say it doesn't God damn you if you read it
Terrible idea you'll realize that it doesn't mean what we say it means and that's why we tell you not to raid
I found this video message really confusing
The title of it is we're winning
Alex Jones's 2021 Fourth of July message
It's kind of flies in the face of his routine Outburst about how we're all going to die whenever you have Tech problems
Studio right but whatever
Considering he's wearing a Nazi hat while he's doing this they are we have
Itself was basically just a
I'm trying to pump himself up
Open talking about a recent episode of the Rogan podcast
He spends like a third of the video suggest
Austin guest the Trojan Azan
Did he suggest
No
That's surprising
A number to preemptively reject that invitation
Let's be clear will never come
Go on if it's Tim J Dillon and Joe Rogan I just get the s*** on them all the time
I'll do it
I felt like this video is just pathetic
And it was
The energy that Alex was bringing on the 4th of July which
Should be this day to shine I just don't know how interested
I could possibly be to see what he's doing
On the 5th or talk about
I just like
If you can't
What get it going on the 4th
You a you have really disappointed
Yeah I really thought that he was going to come and when you said there was a July 4th
Special video I thought he was going to come out
Critical race Theory
That's the thing in my mind that was like that's him going to be patriotic
Something
So
I just was like okay
You're on timeout
I'm going to look around your website
See what I can fit
Figure out if I can get
Get the temperature of Infowars
Based on bam. Video see what's going on
Everything thanks
First thing I found was that all was Alex's shows have recently been
Been pushing Nick Fuentes
Quite a bit
I suspect one element of this as I think that Nick was recently liked in
So you just went did all the shows
Also I think that Nick might be realizing who cares
Do I have to lose by trying
To steal Alex's audience are putting already an out-and-out avowed white nationalist
What's lower
Best I can do is probably a co-op to Alex's audience
Get them over on my side
The worst thing that can happen is
Kicks off Infowars streaming platform
Cuz I'm too right but then I get
Call Alex's Zionist
Best caulk or something no matter what
So also the other thing that I realized it
Is bad news
For them
I compared the The View totals
Of
Of the other main shows
Harrison Smith American Journal
Man
But for some of their clickbait titles of they're like little videos little little clips
Some of my bouquet views
Man
No one
Is watching their actual shows
No man's land
Over there in terms of their they're full
Full videos of who
I almost want to go back and see how many old David night View
We have now and just see if he's really like kicking himself just going
Oh my god dammit I've got Harrison Smith
Boring people with his white nationalist garbage
I think the David Knight had
Appeal to a different
Segment then
Any of these shows do I think so too
Terrible decision from a business control
The noodle Stevens on show yet
So I felt like it was time like I said take a little bit of a day
Little Bear
Honestly though
Harrison we're looking like real disa
Appointments
I realized
They're featuring Nick Fuentes
Ocelot
And then I remembered that Nick was just giving his own channel on Alex's website
Bam dog video God he has his own America first channel on there maybe it was time that we
You check-in
And see what kind of car
Alex is signing off on
And hosting AutoZone website phukmi
No, why are you making me do this so mad what would happen
I honestly
I think that when I started this I was like I was before this will make Jordan
And as I got through it is like wow
I can't believe
Even more overt than I was expecting
Wow cool cool cool cool cool
The first video that I
Let's check this out
Title of it is
The purpose of Juneteenth is white replacement
If they changed it to that
I'm fine with it
Also that have to change it to that
Fine with that this
Starts
And here's our latest
Piece of s***
Sean R&B
B singer and I'm sure
The sentiment shared by a lot of black
She says why stop
Today we should have a new America
Working flag
This is an op-ed
She wrote she said
The quote
Confederate Battle Flag wood
Which was created as a symbol of op
Opposition to the Avalanche
Mission of slavery
Is just recently tired
We don't see it much anymore however on the six
When the stormers rained on the nation
Most precious
Is hot
Waving Old Glory
The memo was
Receive the American
Flag is it
Replacement
A little disappointing that the underpinning of Nick's argument is in
Op-ed there was written by Macy Gray that was published
Not in the New York Times or the Washington Post but on MarketWatch
No disrespect to Macy Gray or MarketWatch
But this isn't the level of thing that I would expect to sell for
Respect
Nationalistic series
No disrespect
To Macy Gray
Bookmark
If you pay close attention to how Nick is discussing this article you can see a couple of really important to sumption
And Fabrication
But he has to make an order for this to even be something
Can use for his Naruto
The first is that he has to take this op-ed written by Macy Gray and presented
Present opinion that making sure is shared by a lot of non-white
I guess if what Nick was responding to is a giant Groundswell of support for this outfit specifically a non-white communities
We might be able to make that rhetoric
Call trick work but as it stands he's just responding to one person's opinion
And then pretending he's responding to Atkins
Consensus View
He's doing that because he knows would come off as a little sad if you were
This upset about an op-ed written by a singer
Who's biggest hit came out just after his
First birthday
He has to make a much bigger deal out of this than it is to
To justify his out
The second thing he does is escalate the argument
It's being made by Macy Gray
Nixos quote
She says why I stopped it Independence Day we should have a new American
In flag
This op-ed says nothing about replacing Independence Day with Juneteenth
Just
Adapt to the argument the greys make
King of the Peace
This is just about the idea that maybe we should get a new flag
A bunch of s*** also DC and Puerto Rico should be States so we should add more stars
Grade does even bring up our flag hasn't
Consistent through the country's history and the current versions
Only like
Better things you can agree with or disagree with you can think of
If a good idea to make a new flag or think of
The bad one
But in order for your reaction to rise to the level of racist outrage that Nick wants to engage in
You really do have to
Create a strawman version to attack so that's what he's doing
This isn't just an op-ed written by Macy Gray she's speaking for large groups
Non-white sure about a flag redesign
Secretly about replacing it
Ended stay with Juneteenth
Nonsense and he will not like my interpretation.
Lisa Left Eye and
The correct
Miss of burning down house
Is it snowing out right now because
I'm pretty sure I read an op-ed by Lisa Left Eye has ghost said burn down
Nick Fuentes house choose + bathtub
Equals
Prison benzinga
Or whatever f******
In finance website there are heroes Nick talking about
The horrors that will happen
How because of this idea of
Possibly updating
The fly
After
Is Regis
It's final.
Destination
What do you have left
Probably not
Maybe nothing
Before the 21st century
How long before they
They say that
Anything before Barack Obama is the new Confederate flag
Anything before Barack Obama
Is the new Jeff
Jefferson Davis anything before Barack Obama's
Ku Klux Klan
How long
Before Juneteenth becoming a national holiday
June 19th 2021 is our new ended
Father what
That seemed
Used to be where all of the
And tell me
That it's
Me
And and
Pat Buchanan
Amazon login and the paleocon to Donald
Trump fighting
To preserve
Are white
You're a young Western Christian identity as a nation
At least people
Trying to destroy that in
Replace it with a
Black foreign
Non-whites
Liberation
Theology
Postcolonial
Identity
On the same side
Against who
All these
Jews at all these intellectuals and all these other people that
That I don't believe in erase all these
Boomer idiot conservatives
Racism
Identity isn't real and we all
Build a new country on
The fact that we buy Nike and we listen
Anna popular music
Holyshit
That was an
Astonishing amount of racism compacted into a very short. Of time
It is I mean
These conversation
And stuff like this is
Start unfamiliar to places like Stormfront
This is this is what's on Alex's site
Straight up
I've realized I think this is what I've learned
Is that there's just no way to talk to
Do people like
Text Nick Fuentes
What we got to do
All right here's my new play
Cesar Millan
Alright when whenever somebody's nearby and he's like saying some racist s*** you just
Until he stops and then whatever little training treats like you got to do it the old-fashioned
Skinner
Straight up behavior modification
It's the only way
I think that
What you just said will be interpreted by someone like Nick as being like I want to put us in camps
I mean
I just think I would have put you in a dog
Alright
This is Jordan's opinion
So I think I was watching that as a guy
Is pretty
I made this is it this is a distortion of
What was
Spell being
Sad in the op-ed
That's being used specifically for the reasons of being able to create this
Backlash arguing
A distortion that turns into wholesale fabric
Location on top of that
I thought this was this was pretty bad
Just like as a first
Vale
What else is going on over here on the old
Winters Channel
And then I saw this video that
It's a
Screenshot of it
The image
Is Matt gaetz
And
Marjorie Taylor Greene
Arrow pointing back Gates's grifter
ArrowPointe Marjorie Taylor Greene says fake
These people are not a merry
And the title the video
They wake up
The Holocaust religion is antithetical to America first
All I got for that
These people are not them
GTE Tampa America
The first and go out
Weeping and apologize
Sing about the hollow
The Holocaust happen on another continent
There's a genocide problem and no one even cares
And you think that's an exaggeration
Marjorie Taylor Greene was called out
Compared
Washing mandates of the Holocaust
Do you think it's a little bit
Copper bowl that today in America
White people are not allowed
To get covid
Stimulus money from
The government
No
A little bit comfortable
You call your bank
And say I'd like to
Reply
For the personal paycheck Protection Program loans
For self-employed people
And they'll tell you
You're white
You're not eligible to apply youth
I think that's a little similar
You think if you're a farmer or restaurant owner and you call up your bank
How to apply for
Does the government
The economy
And they say
You're not eligible to
To apply because your wife
A little bit the same
I was unaware that white people couldn't
Get covid stimulus money
Actually no many white people
Some individuals
Susan's in some small business
Sounders
We did get the alone to the stimulus money back
I tried to look into this a little bit I found a couple of stories a kind of or the opposite
What makes
Talking about
LA Times reported in April 2020 that US citizens who are immigrants
Send are married to non-citizens worse
Specifically
Excluded from Trump's Financial relief package
That's a cupboard over 1 million citizens
For cut-out I was going to say
My problem with Nick
First
Thought that white people
Can't get it is that
It is mathematically impossible but the mat
Vast majority of those funds did not go to
I'm saying like
The vast majority went
Two white people
What make is talking about was a provision of the covid relief bill that provided 5 billion dollars in relief to quote disadvantage
Farmers approximately a quarter of whom are black
From an article in the Washington Post
Farmers in America have lost more than 12 million Acres of Farmland over the past Century mostly since the 1950s
A result of what agricultural experts and advocates
It's for black farmer say the combination
Systemic racism
Bias government policy and social and business
Practices but if
Denied African Americans
Equitable access to Market
Yeah the farm version of red
Discrimination started a century ago with a series of federal Homestead Act
Text that offered mainly white settlers deeply subsidized lamp
Local US Department of Agriculture offices
Charged with
Distributing loan to frequently been found to deny black Farmers access to credit
And to ignore or delay loan application
Many black Farmers don't have clear title to their land which makes them ineligible for certain USDA loan
To purchase livestock
Or cover the cost of planting
And they are seldom benefited from subsidy payment
Mentor trade mitigation
Asian
Almost all of President Donald Trump's
28 billion dollar bailout for those affected by the China trade War
Went to White farmers
According to the assessment they cite the average white farmer received
$3,398 from
Drops bail out while the average black Pharmacy
Affect
There's a larger problem regarding how independent agriculture is treated in this country regardless of
And that's something that we do have
Absolutely after work on but it's also
Completely absurd to look at the history of black farming in America and not recognized
Concerted attempt
Apps to exclude black people from having access to
And participating in that market
You can be against
This if you want
Isn't it clearly does want but
To frame opposition
The provision of the covid relief bill
White people are being genocided cuz they can't get covid
Would stimulus
That's a little bit much
Considering this is also just a five billion dollar provision in a 1.9
Million-dollar bill
I don't know I don't know
Something else we're all like
People couldn't get covid
Brooklyn
They don't know what that is though
I know that this was a big
Big talking point
Amongst his
Community proud
Yeah I really despise
I really despise that the piece
People most obsessed
Messed with
Portraying themselves as like
Self
Sustaining
F******
Amazing individualist
Only ever seem to follow whiny cowards
To pick the tiniest
Bulshit
Then tell them that every Vic
Victimization that they've ever imagined is true
And they're all a bunch of morons and I hate it
I hate it
It's infuriating
And I think you're going to have a real bus time
With us
The rest of the stuff we talked about
Might be a good idea
This might be an instance of an episode where it's all Mike down
No Interruption overhead Eclipse I feel like an eruption
But from afar
Is I'm pretty sure you're going to yell over a lot of them and I would like to present Nick in his own words
Cuz I don't want to
I don't want to show like a distorted version of Alex yelling over Brian stelter show
You and I'm not saying this is a failing on your part I don't know I don't know if you'd be able to stop yourself
Be heard no matter where is the microphone in this room may be a little bit away from you is all I'm saying because
We are about to get it too
Oh my God Mass
How is this possible
So Nick put out a video that is
Real emotional music
Behind it
And it is a pulley
About how the system
I hate to White
Super 8
The system of my heart
The system
You just got understand
Okay so here's where we're going to begin on this
Very little
From this the 7 Minute report
A couple of little
B I did but they were worried
Here's the beginning and
Oh boy
Lexus
Call what it is
The system
Paige White
I just wanted it
Everybody wants
To call it every
Other than that
They want to call it ever
Everything other than what it is
You may hear conservative talk about
Call TruMark
Critical race
That's the new one
Critical race Theory
Trt
And critical race theory has
Marxist origin
Is socialism is communism
It's anti-western
Western Civilization
Conservatives even will call it anything other
Then what it is
Because
It's not politically correct
To say what
You can order it in polite Society
What is its ratio
It's racial hatred
They hate white people
This little boy
Cash Garden was
Murdered
Dragged out of his bad
The middle the night in his home
In murdered outside his house in the street by a black man
Because he was white
That black guy killed a white boy
Because he was white and black I hated white p
People that's why he did it
It wasn't acting Patron it wasn't random it was an act of racial hatred perpetrated by a black man
And why is everybody so afraid to call it that of course that's what it is
There's one really important
Anything that needs
To be kept in mind
Entirely as we discussed
Situation in that is
That this case is pretty Reese
At this point there is a suspect has been arrested and charged but he's not been found guilty
Well it may very well turn out to be the case that this eighteen-year-old Derren Brown
Gilda's four-year-old child
Nick Fuentes is making a lot of assumptions
Circumstance
In order to make this child today
Death
And emotionally resonant centerpiece
For his white identity propaganda
Woman taking care of the
The child
The circumstance here is basically that
The woman
I was the girlfriend
Of the child parent
And the child's parents
Father had
Yeah town
Okay and so she was taking care of the kid
Okay at the time
This woman she identified Brown
From a surveillance footage of the child being taken from
Is crab
And tachinu
Brown was friends with her son
Additionally police have stated that sunglasses shoes and hoodie
That were taken
A brown after a search
Tested positive for child's blood
So it does look like there's a decent case coming together today keep made
AP Celtic short
I Court will determine what it determined
But the case is being built
Sure
That's it
Even if you are to break with the American
Tradition
Nick loves America
You break with that tradition of presuming innocence until Court
Find someone guilty
You decide
He is definitely the murderer
It's still super unfair the way maker
Is presenting this case
Mickey Singh the brown killed his four-year-old child because the child was white and that he hated wifey
I've read a number of pieces about this case
And I don't know where Nick could possibly be getting that
That from
What seems much more likely is the Derren Brown is somebody who is experiencing
Terrifying and awful mental disturb
In February of this year Brown was also alleged to have broken into another home nearby and appeared to be in the middle of a burglary
When he was confronted by the homeowner
They got into a quarrel and brown was removed from the house
Re-entered and attempted to take the man's
2 year old granddaughter
The grandfather fought Brown off and protected the young child but decided not to press charges at that time
CBS article about the sea
Situation quote
Two weeks after the incident the man ran into Brown at Walmart
He told police the brown approached him and apologized saying he was sorry for breaking into his house
And trying to take his grandchild
Additionally another name
Neighbor Jose Alvarado decided to check his
Security cameras after the murder to see if he could find any
10 weeks prior to the murder he found video of brown quotes
Skulking down the street
Opening Alvarado's backyard gate and
Appearing in before quickly walking away
Alvarado has multiple Young
Brown's mother has also stated that he's a patient at an adult
Treatment Center
And there have been some speculation
That he may be
All the details of the story are absent
From Nicks version
End of it because
Those are indications that maybe there's more to this case
Then just a matter of relative skin colors of victim in alleged
Perpetrator
Nikki doesn't want to tell people about the multiple other in
Instances in the neighborhood of brown appearing to be
Be trying to take
Children because it would overcomplicate the story and make it no longer useful for him to use as a prop
City Meats
To justify his white identity anger
And that anger is
He's felt long before this case ever came along
I'm all for humanizing victims of crime
Times and I think that what happened here is it
The complete unqualified tragic
From all available evidence I just don't see any support for the version of the story that Nick is telling
Where this is a racially-motivated crime
By insisting that this crime is motivated by racial hate towards white people from black people what Nick is attempting to do
His take the adjuster
Certifiable and understandable emotional reaction that a listener might have
The hearing about this case
He wants to transform that into anger at black people and a defensiveness about being white
He's effectively trying to use this child's death is fuel for his racism machine
Which I find repulse
What are the main points I want to make your is that all the information that I reviewed
I can find no indication that would lead me to make the assumption that Nick is making
Sing about the motive of
This case
Articles often even include a comment from
The son of the woman who was watching
A child at the time
Cameron also went
To school with brown they were they went to the
I was saying I think there was even the same age
Cameron was asked about a possible motive and he said quote
Random yes
Random out of nowhere for no reason
There's no reason for none of the
It's not from Revenge not for
From hate not from none of that
Nothing
To get back at us
Directly indications in the Articles and primary services from people involved in
In the situation that they don't
That it was crying motivated by hate
But this is the exact opposite of the story is reported by Nick selentis
Because the reality is the Nick doesn't care about the
The story at all
Outside of how we can use it
The push is Worlds
He doesn't care about this child or his family he doesn't care about any of the pain that anyone involved
This feeling
That's just a facade that Nick puts on in order to give his bigotry some plausible deniability
And make it acceptable to behave
Yeah I wrote
This is
It's fun
F***** up and it's an assault
It's an assault in the sense that
The way that I'm
But the way that you interact with the story if
If you are at all a
Empathetic purse
Is 2
Hear the story
Feel nothing but heart
For everyone involved Terror
It's just absolutely nightmarish end for somebody with a mental illness
Is that that
Other Terror of like
There but for the grace
You know what I'm saying
But
Whenever Nick Fuentes gets involved
You can't
Experience that MP
He blocks
Forcing you to feel nothing but
Rage either at something or at
Him it is like if you are wonderful
If it's like it's like if you're wondering up to somebody who is bleeding out on the
The f****** ground
And then you have somebody just barge in and tell you why it's okay for them to be
Be dying and you don't have time to help that person out because you're too busy trying to
The fight off have f****** awful this person is trying to kill them
That's a fascinating thought and I guess I kind of that kind of gets into like
I guess a little bit of the difference in our react
You know because
Get that anger at Nick I mean I understand it
But that's not my immediate reaction
See what the details are understand
I I think that there
I think a lot of people probably to respond the same way that you're talkin
I'm about probably why you act like such a big troll is to elicit that angry response
That's at does not allow you to deal with the reality of this
Situation to discover can't go I can't do any good
All I can do is feel Fury at this human being that is exploiting people who I also
Can't help
And just feel rage about it it doesn't help anybody do anything and it's simply an assault on everyone who listens
It is an assault
And that's what that's what
Drives me so insane we're talkin about like
Illegality and freedom of speech and all that s***
This is an absolute
F******
Override
Yeah maybe that
Maybe that's the lesson or something that's good
That is okay too
Feel but in a minute abs
Its meaning
Playing into the hands of the people
Like Nick Fuentes
If all you do is
Is feel like a girl
You at him or whatever you can't help that person who's Bleeding Out
All I have is
Miss Fury
Hey there Denise
To be like a recognition of not a not a
You can't
Feel bad at yourself because you're angry at them
Is there needs to be another layer to it and that brings you to a resentment like my first reaction to him.
Talking about the story is that I
Can't allow myself to
To feel that
Full open
An empathy towards the
Check to his story
Cuz if I do
That's History
You know and so my reaction to that of course is
Fury
Because you're taking away my ability to even be a human
You're forcing me to focus on your boat
And then I feel resentment that
Doing being angry
This anger doesn't
Solve any doesn't help us it doesn't help him it doesn't help the person is suffering
It's a f****** a song
Goes on I'm doing great I'm going to put my bike down for the next 2 or 3 hours
Sounds good sounds good
So why the saddest video guy continues
Very
Dramatic music
What is been engendered in the population for the past two years what's the population for the past
30 years older than anti-white hatred what are people learning in the school
Would you go to grade school can you go to American history class what do you learn about
Howard Zinn curriculum
You learn about how
White people genocided the indigenous Americans white people enslave black people and
Brought them over here once freed by Whites Whites mistreated blacks by being racist
Plan segregated making them drinking we are about how
White supremacist Nazis try to take over the whole world
Weather fascist ideology in WWII with Adolf Hitler
Real quick
So far this is just a list of things that are
Grill
And it's not like
In school that
Oh you know you also learned other
All
His argument is people always always only talk about how bad why people are
Why don't we get rid of that part into talk about great white people are
I guess
Aryan it's because they were white supremacist because they
They believe they perpetrated the Holocaust
And that was by far and away the most have seen worst genocide ever in the history of the world
And then what all was said and done white people racist to the Muslims that blew up the World Trade Center
Are racist to black criminals in the police basically people are bred from cradle until Ray
Thinking that white people are uniquely evil people
White people there a special guilt for all the problems of his country
All the problems
And really like all the problems of humanity like legitimately indistinguishable from like white
Us propaganda that was coming out like
10 years ago
This is
Identical to videos
That you would see
From like
White is Right groups
Like 50 donut
Yeah that is
I also just that f******
From when they're very young
The kids are white
People are bad
I just want him to follow that up with
And I'm here to prove their right
Listen
Here is all the stuff White
People and the fact
That he said
That he said this is the
Sequence of events
Is
Black people were enslaved White
People freed them
Then why
People started to treat them poorly
That was it and then it's an interesting that chain of events
Interesting.
So this goes on
Unfortunately
And it's as a consequence of these things are becoming more and more common
White people are being dehumanized and when white people are Geminis black people are going
People because they see them as less than human and other people are going to start killing
How much do you want to bet that this song whatever his name is Dara
Brown whatever was radicalized by the meeting up into thinking that white people are racist
Responsible for his suffering
And then he committed this crime in retaliation for that perceived Prejudice precedes hatred against him
That's the consequence of all this anti-white hatred and dehumanization the media education system
And it's even tried in the lot systematically through the government and what do you think affirmative action is
So Nick is just making up
Details circumstances motives
For this
It's murder and
Using those assumptions
Has Justin
Application
Like a proves his
Why people are being to humanize
P
This is nonsense
I do love
Full and
Complete admission that
They are aware of what they're doing
And are doing it on purpose
Just that like
Black people are trying to dehumanize white people and when you dehumanize a group of people
They start getting killed
Immediately after being like Oh everybody cares about the Holocaust like it's a big to you
I f****** hate him
I hate him so much that I don't think he was aware of
Nick Warren
Is it because they said the humanization against white people as having
Give me a problem
When
This country is no longer White
But here's the problem this is not going to be a white country forever and it's not going to
For very much longer in a lot of places it already isn't
And in a lot of ways it already is it to white country more and is the percentage and proportion of
White people to finishes in America relative to non-white people it's going to become more and more of a
Problem for white people that non-white people don't like it it's just that simple
Pink
White and non-white people largely don't like
Why people like Nick
Is everything to do with
Position
His beliefs
Better rapport
This goes back to a few conversations that I've had with the terrible comedians in the circle of The Joe Rogan
Haha
Kind of thing where
Ultimately like what he
He's really boiling this down to
Is
A theory that he's not going
And he doesn't want to say
Straight out
Basically
White people
We kind of have it coming
And if they have the numbers
They'll do what
We would do in this situation
Which is Caleb
Ultimate logic of light us if we are at any moment event
One of Nick's primary political
Motivation
Isn't one of the things that is like a prime primary goal
White majority
Overall levers of power
Because he thinks like I do as soon as
We're going to do what I would want to do
They've kind of actually have internalized all the
The guilt that they're blaming other people for
I'm recognizing that
You know what
White people make up a little bit coming their way I feel like that is something behind it
Is politics so much like
It's it's
If I guess he's complaining about the education system in critical race Theory
He's just listing all the things that white people have done that are evil
And he's not even bringing up like
And here's how to balance that out
He's not doing that all he's just throwing the great replacement Theory out it
With the underpinning that
White people are genocide of monsters who maybe have some coming their way like that's his that's his understand
He's also a mean
Resent is like
Notion
I call you learning
And school is these negative things
About white people
Anybody who makes that point
Is willfully ignoring all of these very positively to learn about
And all the negative things you learn about other cultures
You know you learn
Old sorts of things
It's cool if you actually do the reading remember all too often
My elementary school history books hearing Barbarian apply to United States citizens
Yeah it's the same
Kind of
Thinking that leads you to be like
Uc-one Gillette commercial with a interracial couple
Why are they trying to push this on me there is
He's bitter in every commercial
Did selective
Attention
And they definitely don't put in all the times that white people are propped up and told about how great white people are whenever
The real history you look a little bit further into it and it's like
All the work was done by
Video ends
The media attacks white they say that white people caused the suffering of non-white
People don't like white people nobody talks about increasingly know that non-white people
Largely Ricard white people with fishing distrust in some cases just don't like to pay them nobody wants to say that
You are very comfortable talking about racism against blacks or other non-white but nobody talks about the
The distrust nobody talks about the resentment that non-white people have for white people in the country
Everybody but it is a lot of people and everyone knows that as the population becomes
Less and less white as the people in charge of the country and the people enforcing the law
Positive people the country they charge of the country become less and less white that's going to matter a lot
These are not foreign ideas to the rhetoric that Alex uses it's just way more eclipse
Said it is over
Hey you saying
The parts that Alex likes
Obscure way
Yeah this is not the quiet part loud this is
This is the quiet part scream through a bullhorn on top of a f****** Mountain yeah
For sure
Wow
Nick
Posted also on here on this on this band. Video page of his
They posted a video a little clip
Of him giving a speech at the America First political action conference
It's so funny
Because in the real world
If you heard a video like that
You don't hear about a follow-up video it's not like
Like this would be like if this is immediately after Michael Richard then we were done discussing that clip in your life
All right so the next night he was back at the laboratory booked again
Yeah
Yep cancel culture is out of control
Control control videos and giving a speech
Play this
Entire clip and it's
If its totality
Is a two-minute clip that he posted
Titled we are the American
This is terrifying
Like
This is what him might as well
America
Is a party
Secular
Particular
We are the American
In America is the home of the American
That's what I mean
America
America is
1 people
One nation
Discontent
Forge
Over hundreds of years by shared experiences
Descendants
From
In English
Cultural framework
And influenced by
European
Civilization
America
Christian Nation
And that's not just a slogan when I say that America is a Christian Nation
I'm saying
That Jesus Christ is the Son of God and this is one nation under that guy
America ceases to
If America ceases
To retain
That English cultural framework
And the influence of Europe
Loses
Demographic
And if it loses
Space in Jesus Christ
Is not
America anymore
That is about
In terms of making
Orefield
Speech Where You Are advocating
M4a
White
Ethnostate
That is a theocracy
She can't you can't you can't Henry Ford
I think somebody's really been going back to those
Sweet old days of
Why Don't We join the Nazis come on where they're good people were good people parentheses White
And it's great person interesting
Things that I wrestle with
As I as I was sort of watching these videos and I was like
How much of this is Alex aware of
And how much of this is just like
I don't f****** care Nick popular
Put this videos up I don't know it
It's it's
It seems like
If I were him I would think this is bad for business
It's a little too over
Scnow
This is kind of Harrison was doing that ship to my vibe on this is
Is this is Alex
Fully dipping that toe into like Ana I so if
Nick Fuentes
Is clearly trying to steal my audio
If there's one thing I do believe Alex is smart about it snowing
People are stealing his money
Yeah it'll at least some Elementary
Assertive work with
And Co-op thing
It's it's looking like
To me that Alex is putting that stuff up to
2 gauge wire
Cuz look sure
Owen and Harrison
So let's get you what level of out now white supremacy will do for us
Maybe we have a whole new wing of the show
Yeah I mean I think that a while back
We had
Sort of ascent
That like
Deplatforming has a decent chance of Alex
Eventually just realizing f*** it
Yeah suck it
Speak freely you bet
Just us here know if
I don't know if
This should be taken as a sign of that
Put it feels like it could be
It really does
Because this is
This is a bit much
And you think about like Okay so
In the day
But in the
In the old Salad Days
The 2017 we were young and fresh-faced do you have Alex Jones
Put into a sew-in Shroyer
This would not have
Flown
Here's what we do
Deterioration
Chords
Alright
Clear throated articulation
Of white nationalist position
But I mean it's been if that's the
That's America
Like as we've Alex's
Is Alex's dominated the United
I genuinely believe that
At a certain Boyd Alex
Overtook
Is is
Why wasn't propaganda
No not really but that like
Straight up
Conspiracy Laden
White nationalist only
Is
Absolutely
Just taking over that way
You know like though as we as we watched Alex go from having Jakari Jackson on his show
Now where I'm pitching him a jhacari
Nick Fuentes
Double hander
We see how that goes
IMDb
So is the culture
Largest done the same thing
Yeah
Bucked up
Now that's f***** up
One last video of Nick
Oh God this one's about Pride parades
Well I'm upright box
You know these people just
Crystal Light
In terrifying us with us
I really think those are Christ is King Jesus
They love that s***.
That's creepy
The merging of
Sort of
Ethnic
Demographic anxiety and anger
The the hyper nationalism
The Christian
Extremism
Very similar when Thomas Jefferson was talking about definitely doesn't
Lead to bad out
Also Nick is a big old homophone
Somebody giving a speech that whines up having a crisis cream King break
Beat like
Yeah I would say that this video even surprised
It starts off with him
Complaining that
The country is being
Clark hunt
Being stolen from
And that's not just rhetoric
Our country
Neighborhoods are play
The business
Our economy
Our sovereignty
Our country
Azar's
Skip a long story
And now it doesn't belong to us
It belongs to
The foreigners
Hey.
Our country
Do not underestimate
Made what that mean
When it comes to the
Agenda
They would have if they
Did all of you
Children
Would be a doctor
Transit J ideology
Think about a purse
James younger
8 year old
Who is being
Horse
By his mother
Potter the order of A4
To undergo chemical castration with hormone replacement
Therapy
To prevent
I'm going
These are the kinds of
Or shows
Tragedies the Abominations that are occurring
We talked about the younger queso while back it wasn't about a child being forced to take hormone replacement
There's a situation where the child disagreed on the bus pass
Steak and turn blue
Transition with the father
Going to take a more gradual watchful waiting approach
Anna mother wanting to engage
Social affirmation
I looked into the case and I don't really feel comfortable about how much of the conversation is wrapped up in a clearly ugly.
Divorce between the two parent on I'm not getting gauge with this
The child as a proxy fight
Between the two adults
It's important to notice that and recognize this case has nothing
To do with 4C
Sing a child to transition or take Peabody blockers
Stairwell this is just
A prop again that
Sneakers using another white
A child
But he's using as lice look what they're doing
It's it's almost as bad as
The blue-eyed
White blond haired child
Abducted at the
Which totally totally happened
This goes on
This is
At what point are they good and
Decent and Christian
Stand up
Questions
And I have a civil debate
And I'll be polite
But to say that
This cannot go forward
One more
The conservative movement is broadly
And you can't find
A lot of
Devout Christians
Socialcam
Conservatives
Anything remotely like the Conte
Within the leadership of the party
Like this
We're talking about sick
Stop
And I'm not going to be respectful
Of what they're up to I'm not going to
Both are anti-god anti-spam
Anti-human
Anti
Conservative agenda
We have to say no not just to
Trans kids and girls
And I just noted the
Forcibly transitioning children
We have to say no.
Transitioning
.
SA node
Trans.
You cannot transition
Addition to other
Genders
How to say no to homosexuality
We have to say no to lesbian
Do the whole thing
What they're pushing
Is something that is the antithesis
Obey traditional Christian moral world
Okay
So now we have spiraled
Listen to
Say no 200
People at 8
Yep
Yeah
God God
Pretty far down this road here
Yeah yeah yeah right
Old
Non-straight whites
Should be eradicated is not a good starting point for
Consensus
I would say
I feel I feel like holding these sorts
What positions are going to make people not like you would say maybe they would make everybody not like you and it backs
Would need to have
History books specifically written about assholes like you to get people away from
So the issue is that the family right the family is WhatsApp
Important end
No
Next Friday
Tried to be tolerant tell me about it
Tell me about it
There is no meet me in the middle
Between families with biological men and women
And men and women getting married and having kids
And whatever the hell
Going to put up
Call Ray
Some of this
They were willing to say maybe
Okay people want to get married that doesn't have anything to do with me
Fast forward 15 years and the governor
Telling people will transition your children and cut their penises off
And put them on hormone replacement therapy and not tell their parents
And you have to be okay with that you go to jail
Well you're pushing the limits
I'll people
People have
Darryl Lenox and Derby
And the person who's going to stand up
Say that when they run for office that person
It's going to be a very popular
Politician
I love the idea that you brought up
Episode 2 is that like
Did the rewriting of
The Christian position on gay marriage
Yeah
We're giving it our best
Go
We've done that mean if you think about
Christians and gay people up until this
Very moment you will notice that there has been nothing but tolerance
We've killed them and hunted them Thursday the legal Tuesday
Opposition
There was massive opposition to not
Being allowed to fire someone because they were gay
Not even gay marriage just not being able to how and out destroy their lives
Just for being gay and that's being re-written as Christians being tolerant
Ranger only push people so far
Kind of amazing how
Quickly conservatives forget things
It's almost as though it's a
Expedia almost like
Just a matter of convenience and whatever will make the argument
Yeah you know and then we talked about this
Is before I hate it when people are like I'm going to challenge you to a charity box
Match that stupid
What I am going to do
Is I'm going to challenge Nick Fuentes
Into a charity
I'm going to pee directly into his eyes
Spot all right never wins
To donate $10,000
Glasses
I do have glasses
And also I will be the only person peeing into his eyes and that's the whole game you better watch out
He is from the Chicagoland area
He'll accept my challenge to let me pee directly into his eyes
For awhile I drink a lot of coffee and I would
Mai-tais true enough for a 24 hours fan if I were you I would be more worried about him
Corner of new and telling you opinion
Physically I don't think you'll be
He's the type
So this goes off
Really what it comes down to it
The horn
And the Pitchfork
It's not easy
The rainbow flag
Do people that just love each other
It's not easy
That's why conservatives now tolerate and support homosexuality transgenderism
And a number of other social ills because they say
They say if it doesn't hurt somebody else if I'm not force before taking it
What if you stand against
The time
How funny is that
How
Funny is that
The entire
Message of your religion
Is so
Difficult to follow
Because you have
Basic human empathy
Has nothing to do with your religion he's putting those two together
He said that your religion
Demands you overcome
Caring about other people in order to eradicate their style of existence
Stop using version of Christianity is Todd
It's hard to overcome
What we would have to assume
God gave you
Which is an instinctual need to care for other human beings around you
Demands you override that
It's a f****** test kill as many people who disagree with you is boss
Great
It's not a race is also like
To be clear
Good God this isn't just
Just Nick being mad
About
Lgbtq plus issues
This is this goes far beyond
The time
It doesn't just end it
Transgender bathrooms or girls locker rooms
But not just friends
But you know what else
Promiscuity abortion feminism
It all has to go because if you take our world you through to its logical conclusion
Transition transition
And the differences are real and significant and they matter and if the differences matter than they have
Differently
Open Society I told women are are bored with
Reproductive apparatus
Insofar as
Human population
They have to be making
The babies
They have
A certain disposition arrays that they've got a raise them too and that's a
Full-time job
What they're doing is marginalizing
Normal
They're marginalizing anybody
That is not
I mean
This is beyond just being outrageously bigoted
Towards all sorts of
Battles are just dumb
It's really dumb
I would
A follow-up question about this and I would say exactly on
What you can and can't change about how God Made You
You take medicine
Can you dye your hair
Can you cut your hair
There are a number of things that seem to run afoul of his can you get any kind of like cosmetic surgery apparel
I can't get tattoos that's even in the
So I would
I would ask
About that
About the idea of
Changing how God Made You
If we could figure out exactly where the line on that is
Then I would ask what is prom
Acuity mean
How do you defined that
Exactly
That would you
Do you want to make sex illegal
It's so it's so insane to me
How these dudes
These are dudes who are absolutely
Screaming
Absolutely screaming about returning to these Christian values
That were their society
Ever to be implemented
They would be murder to me
A joke
The people make about the fact
Nick Fuentes
Is a white window
It's like no matter no matter it's it's one of those just
F****** classic
F*****-up brain stories
That have been written about
So much as that person who's like
But my last name is fluent
But I want to be white
So bad
I'm going to try and be the most White
Love you too white
You know what I'm saying
Classic f****** it's goddamn
Greek
Yeah cyclists is bothering me now
You hear stuff like in that life
Best clip
The implications of actual
He has none.
The positions that
He seems to be espousing
Looking for Lincoln Hub dumb they would be in their application in the real world
Ideas are not really
Something you should take Serious
Promiscuity
Should be outlawed and unacceptable and simple normal people like the 50% of marriages that
End in divorce simple normal good condition can I ask also
I love to that he comes out of the
Sort of conservative Wing that generally isn't favored a smaller government
Anti promiscuity laws
Soldiers on the streets
Children you would outfit by giving them tickets
It's them taking them to an Armory
I'm saying is like I think a lot of these
Beat the ideas themselves are stupid
But they're really dumb and they're not
Coming you should take Siri
But he still someone that you
Should be taken
Seriously
Outside of
Whether or not his ideas make
Make sense
Thank you
No he's really nightmare
Even
Really shocked
The
Amount of
Escalation and elevation
He's been able to
Engage a short. Of time
He's
He's somebody who I
When you first showed up
On Infowars
I was like
YouTube dick hole is it
Alex is giving him a little bit of a platform
The
Is the PAC Center
Lana is not something that people should
Should ignore
Yeah and Alex
8 getting involved
To the level that he is
Is playing with fire
I know that you know Alex thinks
He does have some
From skeleton term
Co-optional
Recognizing
Ways to make things work
Best for him
But
I don't I don't I don't know if he's met anyone like me
Nick before
Well I mean not not
You know there's a part of me that says
This isn't exactly that he even brings up
You know like
This there is an audience for this and they're always has been
Steven was a presidential candidates
Allowed
And he was straight up white nationalist and let's kill gay people all the time you know you know
Nation space that exists now is so different every time you can
Buchanan wasn't old
But by the time that you would never
Quote unquote cool youngboy
Niketalk
I've been in the 50s
It was so cool to hang out with ex
Penny was a mean
Subway
It's around 2 talking
About how
Quick transition
Is Justin Poss
Not even trans-exclusionary
Just a big old fobe
So
Full of hate
This this clip is where I really think
Turn
I can't believe he's actually even
Just saying this
I do not think
Gender
And transsexual
Should be normalized
I think it's morally wrong
I think it's Morley Bank
Transition from one gender
You can't do that
Yes you can
And there's no cross
Passing over you can put on a winner
You can put on lipstick you can put on a dress
It doesn't make you a woman
What does not happen in our society we shouldn't have it on television
We shouldn't have an elected office
And we should be passing laws
And the same goes for homosexuality
And the same goes for abortion
These things are wrong
And we shouldn't have them in our society they shouldn't be glorified
We should not get too comfortable at them they should not be normalized
In fact they should be marginal
And people should see them as what they are
Gravely
And disordered and misguided
Damn
I mean like bigotry is awful
And it's really too
Support and calling for legislation that would outlaw
Trans existence
Outlaw being gay
Outlaw abortion
Pretty
Pretty serious I've got some brand new idea
Brand new ideas 2021
Hot off the presses never before
Try ideas
Like legislating against the exist
Sense of human being
And when they did do that which I'm not saying they did it went great see the reason that people don't want to
Engage with people like naked
Because they're afraid of this this kind of
Brand new Visionary pink
Visionary
Really cutting-edge lotta f****** genius
Here's what I think we should do
Very clearly
Racist homophobe
Transphobe
Bark
It's almost like he cares more about the bigotry than he does whatever the bigotry is about you just love
He probably feels really good so happy
Get the ball out of attention
I get some angry
So I bet you have that merging of all of these disparate bigotry
I desire to advocate for in work
Towards
A governmental system
That is Buick rattikin nature
And
Operates in such a way that would
Public laws
Against
Being gay
Public laws against
Strands
Existence
Public laws against
Feminism
That's a terrifying Prospect
Of what
He is
Explicitly
Calling for you
Yes
One last clip here from this
Report a little bit of a breakdown
The foundation of the civilization is the family
Where do children come from they don't come from factories
They don't come from the government they don't come from corporations you don't come from farms
They come from the womb of women as they come from men and women
Listen lie within marriage he don't have any
That's the only way to degrade the only way that you get baby
The only way that
You perpetuate a society
Is by men and women getting married and having children
Society that is society that is how Society propagates itself
That's how it perpetuates itself
Elemental foundation of the sea
Society
And in order
For that process
What happened
He created and for them to be raised
And inculcated
With the culture
And to learn what they need to know for the transmission of knowledge
You need to have
Marriages
You need to have men
And you need to have
And by marriage
Do not misunderstand
First and what I mean you
The Union
Between one man and one woman
That's the only way that you get
Everything
That is supposed
Anything that tries to
To confound that or
Refuse that are office
Escape.
Pure Evil
And that is
The enemy of society
I mean
I just don't even
I mean this guy this guy needs to be stopped
How do we stop this guy conversation
Let's have a dialogue of times and stories like
Fictitious that you'll see something like this once it's too late
Exactly exactly is already risen to power or something
Video is played in Times Square in the horror movie he thinks he's living it
Clear Lake
Cute saying need to stop
It's not a matter of hurting him or
Anything like that it's a matter of
Dealing with what he's doing it in a
In a in a way that is response
Recognized
Hit you very justifiably should have
The other response which is like
He wants you to be angry don't be that Angry Dragon recognize
How stupid a lot of these ideas are there's an empath
Hey. And
I honestly think that there's a
The huge resentment that he feels that most
People don't actually agree with
Except that gay people exist
Most people
Aren't
Most people have the basic human empathy that his religion demands they ignore
Or his version of his religion
Make sure people don't
I think you're Christianity like
Google Alerts
Very clearly
Christianity is not a Blog
Religion
Not a monolithic
10 million types of Christianity
So
I was surprised
Honestly cuz I don't Nick
You know
I know that I know what he believes and I think it's a little it's got
Probably
Maybe even a little bit more over it seems some ways from the last time I checked in on its content
And it was it was bizarre to just click on
Banned. Video there's a section
Tortilla man
These videos are pretty easily accessible and whether Alex wants to
Take ownership of this or not
He owns that website he's promoting this he's platforming this
He's tacitly accepting us and he's profiting off
You know
There is no other way around
And it's like
Is there tags or it's like
If somebody search
Looking for white nationalists this will show up here saying just awesome that out there it's going to be at the Google search results
I think that Alex is aware that the video doesn't show up in Google search
Might have been d-list
That's fair
Like I guess like I guess this works for Alex as long as Nick doesn't
Put out any videos that completely undercut the basis of Alex's entire can
Conspiratorial worldview
Uh-oh
The try guys wanted
Destroy America from within
I texted this to a good friend of mine
I said these Boomers
They're talking about
Try to watch a
To destroy America from within
Good friend of mine
What is funny
I would give anything for the chai,
Destroy America
True
What
A hole
Hilarious
Just
So funny good luck with this guy Alex
Wow
So I texted my friend about the guy whose website you're watching the song
Dumb moron who thinks that pichai comes there a problem
This a****** I texted
The person who is
Hosting this content that you are watching this video on
I texted Mike funniest friends
About the jumpship the person who is hosting the got that you are watching we all left about how
He believes that on the side of the bad guys are naked.
Oh okay well maybe Alex doesn't know about this
I don't know I don't know what the deal is
This is this is
Pathetic and not good
We might be experiencing cancel culture
I am. Video from this van. Video you know who's going to come out ahead
Nick
Anyway
I wanted to take a little bit of a break from
Text for a day if so
I knew that the Nick had this Channel and I wanted to give it a little bit of time for some content to accumulate
For we took a look at it and this
Is a cross-section it's one of the stuff that it's there it's
Extremely
Bucked up
It is over
It is
It is not making
Any bones about what his position
Cazares
Unbelievable unbelievable
You can have a video right now
Next to another video and then one video you say
Whenever they dehumanized
People
They think we're less than human and that leads to White BB
White people being killed
To the next video being like
Trans people aren't actually people
God demands that you get rid of them until log
They are less
Then human
Sorry I was terrified by this and I don't know I'll check back in on his thing event
Actually we'll see how
How this works out for these job down this
There was a two-hour debate about the Middle East and Barnes
And
I tried to watch a bit of it and I was like
Ono Barnes
You don't know how good Nick is at the Barnes is a shity lawyer even in the face
Face of a lawyer
Nick is
He's the debate cap
You don't need you don't want to
They don't mix up with him
Barnes
I don't give a s***
Dog stick to the IPA
But until then Jordan
We do have website is knowledge
Dipbrow on Facebook
We are on Facebook if
You like dogs so active
Please find a local charity or Bellefonte in your area to help out people doing God's work
But until then
The sex robot
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work