Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for its knowledge B I'm sick of them posing
Dot-com
Blues Licks it around the altar of Celine and talk a little bit about Alex
Jones
Jordan
What's up Jordan is worth checking in on bees Survivor re-watch
Continued and I have more thoughts
Did you hear the news out today no
5S project
Veritas has been using a former Survivor contestant is a Honeypot trap
What's this
I think it was 38 season she was allies masquerade yearly so that
No I have not
I do not know I know there is a later Survivor contestant who is
Become like a trump
Person
The same one but
It's definitely not Elisabeth Hasselbeck from Elizabeth
Filarski / Hasselbeck
April from the Australian season who I thought was great and then
So I've been watching it
I think this is an interesting Dynamic that goes throughout like some of the early Seasons that is like
They start to realize that they need to make the show
Familiar enough
That it's like the same but also different enough each season
That's it it's not
Stale
Exactly
Tension a little bit and I think it's really well done
Infer about the first
Four Season
You're already past Four Seasons how much farther
Through those
And then I got to the fifth
Season and I could not watch it
I don't know what it was I was just like
I
Don't like this
It stinks
Okay
No I wasn't really worried that like okay
I guess everything fell apart the fifth season
And I like I can't be too sure what I have to do is
There's nobody forcing me to watch
I was skipping
I don't care you don't have to immediately I was like I love this again
It was the cast about what was going on
Is actually
Fantastic
I really enjoyed it
7th Season great
Rupert
Is the Miami efforts this year passed into the actual zeitgeist
Survivor comes back
And such and I don't know if things
Turn bad
I've no idea
So if I
If you did end up becoming like a real.
Dick head or something please don't judge me for it
At this point all I know is that if you was also in season 7
Spoiler alerts for a thirty-year-old joey
It's amazing how immediate is food like
This guy is
Oh okay so everybody just suddenly passed to the king like okay
Hey f****** let's do it
People on the island of the show is
Clearly like
Presenting him
And I like that I think it's probably partially sincere that he's just a big-hearted guy
But I would always watch that season
Everybody f****** love in this bearded hippie dude and I want to like older I get
Is a very Magnetic Personality
One of the things that I've recognized
Is is that
Season 6
I think
Is where things
Sword of Begin to Fall Apart
And that is
Because season six has be first instance that I've really found
How somebody who's really relishing being a sociopath
Oh those people yeah maybe Greg and season 1
Or Rob Boston Rob maybe even earlier
Those two guys are
Kind of dicks
Right and there are people who are dicks
6in black Richard hatch's
Is a dick
You'll be polite to each other but
Rob
On season 6
He seems to
Take
Pleasure
Audi
King with people is kind of characters
That felt a little bit like okay
I know that a lot of other people past this point
Aronov Lake
And it's become
My confessionals and all of my talking to the camera is just like
I lied to this guy and I love it
From then you could have a trophy room filled with ears
Who clearly was
I like lying
I don't play
Yeah that's really worried that there is now this
Trend of like
This is how you get attention this how you rise above the
The Fray
Maybe you don't win the show but you
You become a character and that to me is like a metagame that I'm not interested in and I think is actually
Destructive to
The enjoyment of the show that's what happened to everybody you know everybody knows this about the bachelor now like
At a certain point
All the sudden stops being about whatever the
Jeff is supposed to because it never really was what we all crazy
And then it starts being like
I'm jacking to become the neck
Next Bachelor and then maybe that'll turn my into a career you know so everybody always
Fifth episode conversation with
For the right reason you like all my God we do this every year
Yeah that's kind of why I think
Fake baby Eva
Season 8 is
Does like actual beginning of the end
Yeah because season 8 is All Stars
Oh yeah people back
I think that incentivised some of that
Behavior
Of like
In this
As opposed to
Like no you're one-and-done
There's nothing coming from this ya play the game dammit
I think that awareness
Is a little bit of
It's something
That is within
The game itself that
Doesn't belong there
Not sustainable
And I'm worried I'm worried that we've already reached
The point where it's like wow
I think it's going to get a rear end and we haven't even gotten to the point where they're hidden immunity idol.
Where the game becomes hyper complicated
Yeah you know I wonder if that's kind of a very similar trajectory that wrestling took as as like that
Kayfabe started a break and everybody was
You know that people knew about all that stuff in the mad but then it became part of the ACT
Actual
But Global watching of the the Show wrestling is now also including the metagame
And I think the same thing happens with Survivor where it's like
Once everybody becomes aware of it there's that loss of everybody's like
And all that stuff
And then it builds back up again when everybody's like well now that I know the metagame is part of the game
A better game is on top of that metagame
That's just another day
You know how you
A beat back again
And I don't know how you do like
30 more seasons of the Mist
Without it completely becoming
Unattainable
Marvel movies we had
Half the universe die
True Religion
I know you're tired of tennis
So I won't give you any tennis bright spots and in fact I don't have any Barrio tennis
The Wimbledon again
To tie both Rafael and Federer with 20 most grand slams of all time
Djokovic is undoubtedly going to break
Those records and then probably beat Serena's open-era record 223 because he's a robot
And I heard
So he's either he'll the biggest heel
But I will say my breakspot Dan is
The night at which you are listening to this on Monday night
Is the Home Run Derby
All of it
Normally I never watch the Home Run Derby I don't really care last year or two years ago
Hit the
Salute ever-loving s*** out of the ball and it was amazing
Shohei ohtani baby
Take the picture
The picture who is leading the league in homeruns in 33
That's not
I look picture
Outrageous
Wow he's a god
Well I am I'm excited I may watch this Home Run Derby 2
He's going to hit
Are you going to hit a ball
Well over 500
I always liked that Home Run Derby me and Nikki get
Nobody naked gif
You still sit around and watch the Home Run Derby
Yeah
It was fun for a while but then they added this new like you have a
Time limit
And if you hit enough homeruns you get like bonus time and all that it's 11
July 9th
I exploited that this is Friday's episode
I thought I would check in at the end of last week
See what's going on I know that my Friday was very
We put out the episode
Alarm show and then
Yeah and then you texted me in the morning and I get the same
Nothing to do with our episodes
Intensely weird timing
So probably going to
Address the fact that is
Little baby bigger
Friend got the boot
It is no longer necessarily profitable throughout have on the network
I thought that might be interesting and nothing to do with that
Azimut to think things to go over so we will do that but first
It's a little moment say hello to some new walks
First Noah also happy birthday Mom
You are now policy walk
Happy birthday Noah welcome to the wall
Is a better offer than JK Rowling
As if possible thank you
Unfortunately that is not possible
So Hillary website
I don't know if these are codes
Messages that are like activating something
How's your 401k
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
Before we do the episode
Get into this
Are we going to get
If we have to
Giving someone life is giving someone dead
You can say that
Life is death
You good
Happy birthday
Also Christopher
Reached out this this might be
I love
Giving people a birthday
I got to be honest this might be excessive
I swear to God we are just
Not trying to do that we may have to end the season of
Birthday shout out and not because of Krista
For anything like that pictures
We might have to to real this in a little bit it's definitely getting out of control
Control your butt
Elana and Brian just had a birthday so happy birthday also Christopher's best man
Sweating
Robert
Robert has birthday
I don't know exact code is that
Activating some sleeper cells at work
Happy Birthday to everybody
So Jordan here we are
Ammonite
Begin the show
Some severe covid
Last we heard
Alex talking about elevator cause 82% of people to lose Brakeman seats
Turns out there is more trouble
Basically
These vaccines are straight of killing
Everybody
Mom 45
A job at John Hopkins
Hospital dies
John Hopkins Hospital
After she got the
And I said yeah the vaccine reaction
Until all the blood vessels
Along
Horrifyingly painful death
Great shape and totally happy
Then a doornail
Within a few days
So the case that Alex is covering is about a person named spring Saunders and there's a number of problem
The way that he's reporting
In the story
The first problem is that all of his primary sources
It's just limited
Screencaps it someone took
From Facebook post
That's not
Exactly accurate to be honest
The story from a Blog called the Empower or which intern just took all their reporting for
Facebook posts
Great name
It's all good and well to take some open-source
Information from Facebook
Proposed
Suddenly aware that anything you read might be intensely by us
Only telling half a story or could just be completely made up
In this case the woman in question does appear that existed there's a memorial page
You can find online
Conclusions that Alex's jump
You are completely not damaged
Castrated by the primary source
Nothing available present
Presented indicates that anyone
It said that her death was proven to be from a vaccine reaction
Nothing in the article indicates
Their brain swelled until all the vessels pop
And Alex is just writing a compelling story to tell his audience
Some of the other details here don't match up
But the primary sources that Alex's article presents but I honestly feel like bringing up to
Specific
It kind of feels like
Splitting hairs and it might come off as disrespectful to the woman who passed
Tanner family
Which I don't want to be
My only Point here is that Alex is jumping to a conclusion they can't prove any of
Is that he's reporting
Also if you try to find this story just by Googling the words in the headline you'll find another interest
Recent story
Another 45 year-old woman Trisha Jones died this week
From covid Delta variant having refused to get vaccinated
Her mother told the local news quote she was afraid of the side effects I think
You hear a lot of horror stories
I myself when I had the shot it was rough
So it scared her and freaked her out
So she didn't want to do it
I couldn't convince her
Also there's an article in the BBC from my April and it discussed the incidence of people having Cerebral venous sinus thrombosis
After having received the Pfizer or moderna vaccine
This 30 reviewed electronic records
Of 81 million us patients and found that the risk of this thrombosis quote
He's 82 10 times higher in people with covid
Then those who got the vaccine
Of course it should be pointed out the drunk hard conclusions from this study isn't really possible and there's review that needs to
Indications
Pure to show the people have a far greater risk of this
Condition metallic
Does making his audience
Really afraid of if they get covid
Then if they get back
Just playing game
No I mean
If you
What is it it's like 90 it's at least 98 to 99% of all covid deaths now are
Unvaccinated
Play
Alex has the exact opposite staff who have talked about later so hold on to that
Version of reality that sound fair
I can be in this
Of somebody who died
Blaming of the vaccine.
Beautiful young Italian girl killed
Brain surgeon
Said he's never seen
A brain
I've never seen anything like this
Thrombosis
A neurological trauma
I know this for me it's a red flag when a headline do you know you're talking about
Discusses how the subject of the story is beautiful
Right off the bat
That's the Hallmark of a
Journalism
Turn the 1940s
This is a headline from citizenfreepress which is another attempt at making
King Anu drudgereport.com right-wing link aggregator
Headlines meant to be attention-grabbing at the
The expense of journalistic Integrity so we're off to bed
This story is about a young girl named
Camilla canepa and comments that are surgeons
Gian Luigi Zona made after her death
I have never seen a brain that was effect
Goodbye such extensive in
Severe thrombosis
Seems slightly unethical for a doctor to make comments like that but actually a world-renowned
Maybe things are different in Italy I don't know
About their number reasons to think the kidnappers death was not directly caused by the vaccine even though that's how it's being reported
Boarded by people like out
Was it because she was hit by a car
Oh okay that would have been in
The first thing is that you got vaccinated on May 25th and only died this
This past week
It's a little bit of a long time to have him between these events in order to make a definitive connection
6 weeks right yeah the second reason
To be suspicious is far more
Which is that there's some reporting going around for medical officials that can make my headache
Chronic condition
Called familial autoimmune
Thrombocytopenia
Which affects the ability of the body to create enough blood
It appears that this condition was known prior to vaccination but investigators are trying to determine
If it was known to the people who administer the vaccine
Since we probably shouldn't have given the increased risk that her condition would have put her in
Can I receive the vaccine at a quote open vaccination day so it remains an open
Question about how
Bulova medical history was known as
The time door if
There was an awareness
The people should have had and then ignored
Conversely there's also reporting that says her parents have commented the quote she had no disease
I'm not sure what that, does it
Response to or any of the surrounding context
Isn't finding information on that has been
Challenge
This quote is the only thing that they were cited In Articles and Outlets
Where they
Casually called
Can I beautiful
Icna there headlines
Stop
There appears to be a bit more to the story than we know at this point an important thing to remember is that
The previous story about the woman who work
Route to Johns Hopkins
That had to do that that was in America and then had to do with the Pfizer or moderna vaccine
Theirs has
To do with an AstraZeneca vaccine which
She's not an mRNA vaccine it's not used in the United States
Blurring the line between a pretending that the
Different things
Completely different
Vaccines are having
The same
Side effects
Killing off everybody and identical
Fezzari
It's not
Yeah I just don't know how we're ever going to deal with this it without a certain
Kind of like
Reckoning of like hay
Ninety-nine percent of people are dying because they're on back
Vaccinated
40% of Republicans refuse to get unvaccinated almost
Entirely
Because of this level of prop
Opaganda.
Their face
So
In no way is the propaganda not responsible for at this point in time
Massive percentage of Coke
That's right
Like it can't be
Cannot be said any other way
Like that
The influence
Seems very direct
Very understandable
Drawing
A concrete Linebaugh
Between the individual disseminator of the information and the people who are
You know making me stress is to not get vaccinated a Barrette that's more of a challenge
But yeah it doesn't it it seems it seems like it's pretty hard to argue that
Like that influence
Is leading people to make a lot of bad decisions
Sprite that are having consequences
Canby Ferry
Yeah it can't be a I'm not going to say like oh okay every night went
Tucker goes to sleep he is responsible for another hundred.
Cats or anything like
Like that as part of the right-wing ecosystem
It is the right wing
Again the ecosystem that is killing
You know as a whole
All 99%
Constable yeah it in the largest part
You know it definitely it definitely seems like that and it seems
Also add additionally
Difficult to figure out exactly what you do about that elderly on an individual actor bases held because of
You know how do you
Prove a concrete mixer
Yeah
Spongy assholes
So Alex has some bills that he wants to talk about
But have fun number
Okay
Well it's official
Legislation has been introduced in the house and
To create a new law enforcement body in the Justice
Track everyone's medical record
United
That means whatever they
What about your body
You name it
Add
The bill is 666
Contact tracers coming
To your house
Chose
Robert
Your face a little
Calling card
I'm so HR 66
6 was the testing reaching and contact
Everyone activity
The trace Act
Foreshorten
Who's introduced in the house on May 1st 2020 and it died in committee before even receiving
NFL 2016
Even come close. Alex is talking about
Close to being committed
Committee
Don't even vote
This is what that Alex talked about a lot you made a big deal out of the number being
But he didn't even follow up with it or care enough to notice
But it died in committee
The other stuff is just kind of
Madoff
In the 100s
16th Congress which was last
Are there were four bills
Also the number 66
None of them even received a vote and one of them was a senate resolution quote honoring the faithful and unwavering service of
Civil Air transport and air America to the United States
Civil Air
Transport
Cat
And air America
Put that around at a knesset probably Satan
Sure
News the Senate resolution that was just like good job Civil Air transport and that didn't even get a vote
F****** Congress we have a new 666 bill because they count
We're now in the 117th Congress and in the house ayonna Presley introduced the anti-racism in public
Health Act of 2021
This seats
Quotes to amend the Public Health Service Act
To provide
Research and investment
Structural racism and police violence
This doesn't seem like what Alex is talking about
Unfortunately also it'll almost certainly dying
Do anything to help people will die
On the Senate side we have another very Sinister Bill 6
Quote
Ability to modify the criteria used by the Corps of Engineers to dredge small ports
Devil Rays
This will also probably won't pass and it was introduced by Ram
Paul
Real numbers don't hold some kind of secret signific
Alex never really take the time to update
It's past the point where they have gotten
Very stale
Is a great example of
Stampy's forgotten
To check in and see if that's
666 overpass
I I just
I know it's
Stupid
But if we're going to live with hotels not having
13th floors let's just live with congress not having sex
Let's just do it just skip 666
660-520-6422
Let's just get it out of the way I'm sick of people being like Oh it mean something
Well I think that it's okay
To have superstition
In the private
Sector
I would feel worse if
The government
Change their behavior based on some people's weird version to a number
That might that might be a little bit
F***** up you know Stones get worn down you know
The Rushing Water will wear Stone down over time
Eventually you just go underwater
I guess
So Alex is mad about this
There's something else he's even more mad about
The
City-sponsored in San Francisco
Corruptor children were coming for your children
We're going to recruit your children
Giant
Porsche
Well now they come out and say
Oh they were just baiting us
They don't really mean it
Who is a couple of important points about the video Alex is talking about
The first thing is that the Men's Chorus
Did not remove
The video from the internet
It's still very much up on their YouTube channel and you can find it
Incredibly easily
Alex is claiming that they took it down because that makes it seems like there's some sort of guilt or it's suspicious in some way
What is audiences
I watch the whole video I'm just going to play you the first verse here bike down
You can hear it
What they're doing
As we celebrate
Fight on the progress we've made over these
Last year is there still work to be
Still working against equal rights
Read the message.
Respect
Corrupt
You're correct
Making
Will make them tolerant and fair
If they're doing there
It's a hundred percent meant to f*** with people
Yep yep
Yep
Mad
Did the response though people like Alex or the right-wingers
Just so it definitely predictable and it's a little embarrassing embarrassing
Bigotry it's actually hear what's being said leads to shortcut
It's in the big shortcut here
Is it
This song is actually about cruelty to children
At the lazy hateful it's also just
Dumb also it leads Alex to desperately try to pretend not to be a homophobe because he wants to attend
This
Specifically Hazel
Okay
So how am I going to do this
I might have to dance around this
I guess I'll use identical rhetoric to the stuff that Nick Fuentes was saying on our last episode
Oh no no no
People who are
Homosexual in the world
You're not tell molesters and
Not bad people
Recycle child molesters in there
You need to not let
The pedophiles
Claim that they run your boo because they do that
We're getting threats
Perceptual
Choices because
A bunch of creepy men singing a song about your coming for our children
Elementary students how to masturbate
That was
What teachers need
The peanut
Alex was lying about Jocelyn elders and she said
You know what that has to do with her just tossed in there for some reason he was grasping at straws
That's not good they should just sing
Anytime he says something like that turn it into a song
Glen Elder
Peaches York
Children who masturbate
I feel like it would be tough to get Alex's
Voice in
Any kind
Note
Downloaded song
Yeah I think
This is another one of those
Assertive
To strawman
Arguing
It's the same sort of thing that Alex does with
You know at times with Muslim
Sounds like why won't Muslim groups
The cry
Tons and tons of examples of it that he has just ignored
And it's
The same thing with lgbtq + community
Having to fight
Do not be associated
With people
Who like children
Trying to game
Level of
Acceptance and
Association with
That Community they have to
Hush
Against that
That Association
Because if that co-option is always
A part of it it goes back here years and years
And Alec
Will not accept the
Multitude of voices
Love people in the lgbtq
By a community
This is not
This is not part of our thing
They just pretend to feel like I'll run by
I know.
That's your
Smear
Exactly that's that's what you've decided to accept
In order for you to
Pretend to not hate gay people
Wellbeing again
Any
Modicum of
Right that the community
And this is this is just ridiculous because it's essentially sharing an onion
I mean that's basically what it is if you being like
I can't believe that died that this publication
This is a f****** onion article
Do your f******
Stupid
Yeah I was watching it and I'm like this is a little bit
Maybe
It's a fun song in
And what have you been
It white when you're making it you kind of have to know like
This is really going to piss off
So
Unbelievably tailored
Just for these people they're the only
Show me people who listen
Do it more than once
Everybody else was listening to in their life
Give me an anger boner
Thinking about while I was
I don't think that they
A wrong
To make this song
Worried about like
Review make
Something that is this
Kind of pointed of aperitif
And satire and like
F*** you and whatever you're stupid
But beliefs are about
What's coming to corrupt
Your children and stuff
If you do that
That could be
Put people in danger like
I would not be surprised if
It leads to an increase in harassment of Cisco gay men's chorus
Or whatever I hope it doesn't escalate to violence
It's it's
In the landscape that we're in right now
Seems like
Rave movies
Even more than it is like
Interesting
Funny video movie
It would be
It'd be like if comet
Pizza like
Built
But seller under their place and then made a recreation of all the conspiracy theories
The ball pit exactly the same that people were expecting to find out there
They gave tours
Maybe like yeah
Okay you guys maybe have gone too far with the center
I get it.
MMA like a music video of them
I'm creating the bass Hillary Clinton
Whole thing
But Sir Alex is pretty mad about this
The entire show on it cuz there's other
Equally less important
Things to deal with
Best footage
A comet
Running around in
California
Up the side of
A building
And setting
The cross on fire
And then jumping
From building
To building
Someone out of
Dr. Jekyll
What
I would have gone with Spider-Man
Spider-Man dad and if Spider-Man
Climbs up a church building building
So this week
Just boxers and socks
Fox climbed up a church Roofing
Set a small fire
Hero hero
It's probably someone on drugs
Newsweek quote the Los Angeles Fire Department
Confirm that these small Church
Rupphire was fully extinguished in the LAPD
I'm sorry lafd arson
Is currently
Conducting a fire-related
Navigation to the guy was apprehended in other real.
Details are known about it
This time
This could be
Be a story that
Includes a whole bunch of
Different details like
Baby
Who knows what the actual story
I think it's pretty clear how Alex is going to cover it is like this
There are
Hundreds of churches
A week in Europe main burn the majority have been burned to the ground
Wow the Muslims and a Consortium of devil worshipers just spiritually
Go and burn them down the news covers up
Oh
Other media coverage
So after the 2019 fire at Notre Dame
France embarked on a two-month investigation which determine the cause of the fire was an accident
With the leading suspect the cause of being an electric
Short circuit or an errant cigarette the most likely things to happen to one of the most protected landmarks in for
There's no evidence whatsoever that this is a target
And Alex couldn't defend that claim if his life
Ended on it
Reality
The fire that happened
The Notre Dame could have possibly been a miner event but there were a series of mistakes
That were made that led to the fire become
The crisis
The first issue was the attic where the fire broke out at no firewall protection and no sprinklers
In place
The second issue is that the person who worked at
The cathedral who is response
Communicating with firefighters about where the fire was quote
Was only on his third day on the job
Smokey been detected but quote according to the report when the fire alarm went off at 6:18 p.m. the guard sent to
Check on the Fly
Went to the wrong building
The Sacristy not the Attic
Seriously delay the response effort
These variables are unfortunate and they combined
Blood result in a really bad fire but none of it proves any Foul Play behind it
I remember watching the show Infowars that is around the time of the fire
The only evidence I remember being offered to prove that it was arson was the
Paul Joseph Watson black people with Muslim sounding names reacting with heart emojis
Auto Facebook
Book stream of coverage of the fire
Is unconvincing stuff but Alex knows that his audience doesn't remember that he never proved that one so now he can do
Is playing the media covered up that Notre Dame was an RC
Whatever
Just sofa
Funny
Your third day on the job and Notre Dame is on fire that's just so goddamn funny
Anna movie
,
God that's so fun
Brutal real world
That's a nightmare I'm sorry I don't want no turd
What happened on our first or second days of work and just imagining global news story
Awful nightmare
JCPenney's
Stole a couple shirts and it was like a big deal of it
But that did not make the news not not Notre Dame fire
Square your boss your training bus
Just like listen we get it
It's your first few days
It's going to take a little while to settle in everybody makes mistakes
But it's Notre Dame on
You are so fired
We're putting you
In the burning building that's what we have
Have to do.
Turns out these people like the guy who climbed
It is boxer is onto a roof
Open California
The next mayor of La ever set fire to Notre Dame
Taken over by demon
They are drawn
Winning that lowered state
Conscious mind
Spirit has been removed from the control
Nothing more than Avatar
Driven by a force
That desires to burn down churches and rape children
And if you go to any Democrat event you go to 185 and are even go to a main line
Pro-choice
Women in
Will tell you they love Satan
Start sticking their tongues out and licking their lips
That sounds true
Countless times
Doubtless
Zurn
So yeah I mean
You know it's it's a little bit
I resent
The idea of demonic possession has become so boring
Notable
Itsfunneh
My my partner loves
The Conjuring franchise
How do I fall asleep during every movie get the black
Oh my God they're possessed again
Confine
Whatever you was at work
I don't care
Like you
If any other
Like
Respect
Edible news Outlet
Anchor
Suggested that somebody was possessed by a demon
It would be
Amazingly huge
Oh and Instant Fire
Why is he saying that that's outrageous
Alex is like oh it's
My God
He's doing that again
Because I think you also meant probably handmaid's Tale
Instead of a Stepford Wives
Text Maurice
So Amigos Pizza Ventnor like bad word a v
Whatever is that sometimes he also goes to events that are about
Himself
Like there was a panel in Austin Trump and fake news
You crashed sure
And you know what happened there nothing there but sit him
When when they got it
Call Donald Trump
Alex Jones in the fake news they shut down part of downtown a few years ago
Horses uninvited
Add
Men came over
Began to
Tell me that they like to have sex with children
Choir
Children as they're everywhere
I told you around these people
They're pathetic
They're stupid
Are usually White
And they're all very very now
Fake feminine
Cover for what unbelievable
Monsters they are
Peter ugly gross men
Who are driven by spirit
That absolutely wants
Destroy innocence
Add
By shaking their butt naked man and the looks on their faces and how they act
They are enslaved
There is a spirit in control of them
And it's hideous
Doesn't wife on this Earth
How to make sure the children
Buy chickens
Swallowed into a satanic
Best Buy
So please remember that any signs of
Femininity
Andaman
Is definitely
Wow. Remind me when I used to run an open mic
Early on
You know the always have trouble with people running the light for whatever reason you do people sometimes
My Gmail
Every time that would happen you know I've seen so many shows where people would walk up and it be
An altercation or they would just not
Take people up
The stage you know Inlet
Certain people go for 20 30 40 minutes you know that kind of thing
I always what I would do is I would slowly start dancing through the middle of the
The crowd and just kind of
Get everybody paying attention to me and just dancing really loud not being mean or anything and then by the time I got to
The stage
The comic would just be like
And then just leave
If you know sir that is how you get rid of Alex Jones
Cops involved
You get a bunch of people to just shake their butts
Sit him until he goes away
But you can't you can't make a demonic video where it's just a bunch of dudes shaking their butts and your likes
I see it as being like you get to like a March
Yao Ming height
Big conga line I'm just like are at work we're done with this b*******
I just follow Alex
Susan couple tuba players goat
Auto rental ban
Totally just do that
So I would say I don't know who these people shake their butt at Alex R I don't know
That happened if they did his own
Almost certainly
Without me
I hope I don't know they look like
But I do know from the video of
The San Francisco Court
Those people do not look anything up
A group of a lot of men who look very different
I don't know what
Unites them
Except for they're all gay gay choir is responding to
Lakeview allege demonic
Possessed
But shakers
Is Austin experience
F***** up yeah I think you might just not be able to perceive reality in any given way so
Anything he just likes
Just turned gray Mass he hides his intense bigotry behind the presentation of not being a
Experience reality Kelly Trail
Living in an alternate reality is less
Socially abhorrent then I his actual belief
Kind of it is really really sad that's a really sad thought
You just had
So this this is this is very on
Unacceptable
Organization of men
Meeting and saying we're coming to corrupt your children were coming for them were coming to go
Highest rate of suicide highest rate of hurting each other
Because of the
The culture in and around it
That is so
Incredibly
Disgusting and Anti-Venom
Add
View
Give the FBI rated the
Gay San Francisco
I would bet that
A large percentage
CalPortland computer
A large percentage of them
Sex offenders already
Wow.
Just made that up
I mean that's
That's actionable
I guess you can I guess saying I
That is such a
Speaking very intentionally
Seems like it wouldn't be
It's something you get sued for
I think you should call the FBI because they're all pedophiles
Yeah that's
Look
I guess you can say I bet in
Between there but your
Because I think the
The context of what he was talking about
Before
He's like
I think what you saying is a pedophile armies talkin about all like LGB
More specifically he's saying the chorus is probably
Sex offenders
I just
I can't I can't I can't I can't
Anyway acceptable
Now this is an outrageous level of
Incitement towards
Homophobia
Drawing a conclusion based on the only information that you have
Is it someone is gay and you've decided that there probably is
I just
I can't
I can't I can't say
But is it strongly or cleanly enough
Is explicit
Yeah I mean there's no other way to
Deal with this other than to say
If they get
Hey
Significant amount of power and continue with it
We will eventually have laws again where you can't be gay in your own home
You know cops can knock on your door open it and if you are
Quotes engaging in homosexual activity you can just be put in jail obviously wants it
Alex's having naked
He has Nick on his
His show at the on his Network
And
You know
His rhetoric is really not that different
They're compatible rhetoric
But anyway
Oz of meatloaf
Well
Lesbians because I like women
I've been around the block a few times
Ladies and gentlemen
The women
Black women
Chip on the shoulder
Okay so if you're a lesbian you support the police
Apparently
That does not
What sound verified
No
Is it sound like something
Can or will be verify it doesn't actually even seem like some of the makes sense for Alec
Seems like something that he's just
I get
I get the sense that he's address
You know he doesn't even know it's stereotypes anymore he's make
Picking them up now
Just suggest but
Even even weirder like just being like a
I don't know why but all black people like Luxembourg like that's not a stereotype I don't even know what that means
I think that you had this
Sisqo gay Men's Choir
Chorus
Play come out and make this video that is
So a meatball for hallux
Tekitsu
He can't resist
The way that he wants to respond to it or they way he'd have to respond to it is
Bees
F****** gay people
Can't really do that please try to find a way to have that response would be
He knows that the audience needs
Try to do it without being like
Ital gave you wants to say
Gay people are making fun of me and I hate them
Then pour it like that's what you why are you going off about pedophiles you're just mad that you're getting mock
Yeah cuz your child they're taking this smear campaign
That I have
And making fun of it in a way that is embracing of like
We recognize what the f***
You say about
To flip it on its head
Power away from
And
I think Ikea
Take that is largely what Alex is wrestling with
Bigots usually don't like it when they have the power taken away for
From them in my experience you end up calling people a pedophile Armada
Maybe a little dance a little bit
Continue to do so
These are just blast
Beyond hell individual
Spider-Man
Weather Juneau like
Alfred Hitchcock
Like his mother
And now
The schools are having talks with your Elementary students
You're really a girl where are you you want attention because you are going to send you
In most jurisdictions doubt that they will take
Your children from you
The CPS will
Another home with a bunch of these perverts don't just want to stay
Their members in your children
Top
Testicles
Shop little girls breasts.
Because the end goal is to mutilate
What God created
Got cut off by the breaker
Very similar to the rhetoric
Nick was putting out in his video where he was advocating
Before the criminalization of lgbtq folk
This is not any this is
This is a mess
This is incredibly
Inciting
And an awful
Yeah
Yeah it's fun
So you know
This is all satan
Really
And Alex comes back from that break that he got cut off
F*** it
I'm going to discuss Satan's plan
All the news and tied together here the satanism.
Pedophilia
Declaration of war against humanity
Externalization of Satan's plan here on this planet the spiritual battle
The church is rolling over to doing nothing to fight it
Very very
And just how hellish things are going to get
We have free will
Only further please remember it is viewers in Lester's that key
This independent
Media operation hours
I got a plug before I get to Satan's plan
The tease you guys Satan plant coming up but
Before we do that it is your viewers like you get into all of the nitty-gritty
What the devil is up to
We have some pills
So
Apparently
I mean you know we have a lot of people who are possessed by the devil
Running around
According to Alex
And two of them you made a wreck
Recognize
The news
Possess
And also Michael avenatti
Devil possessed
I would have thought about him in a while
They want to destroy innocence
Like a man in the desert
Water
Like a starving man needs bread
When you see
Michael avenatti
And you see Hunter Biden you see these people and they look like these
Look like
Not them
Gone
Something something is repulsive about them
Because your Humanity fees
But nobody's home
Chestnut
So
There isn't a place
That you can buy
Products
Where
Dynamite
Iron products
I am hurt isn't it remarkable that that was in the middle of his sales blog
I think I
Broke my neck broke my neck on that
Sudden left turn
I bet I forgot to wear my seatbelt and I went straight through the side door window
Bearing sales pitch
Said he's doing any sometimes
Gets back into stuff
It sounds like it's
Contact calculator
What
Alex
Is plug and this is the
First time in a very long time that I'm about to
Secure my voice
Okay
All right I know
What was going on
As like
This sounds like if there was ever a way that Alex would end up using our content
Could be at
Spoiler alert it's not I was a little bit nervous
Did you guys find that comedian face
I don't just run on you
Comic relief
I guess someone hearing this
Is like wow this sounds crazy but
It's really true
What's in high in fish oil in Anaheim
This will give you the Fishburne
I don't like
But if you're not getting fishberg folks it's not the world
What is an out there that stood it's telling us the real deal.
Guinea Pig BBQ
Bring Darkness good
Never Say Never picture like this
Alright here
Gold
Believe me look it up
Baby
Please do it just you
I like that
Yeah what
Okay
I got a couple of
I got a couple
Okay one
I have never heard fish burp
What's before in my life
Yeah we even talked about it
Still refuse to hear
Outside of here
Is Penney's fishburg something that other people say
Maybe
Maybe I guess I have not really spent too much
How much time in the
Comparative fish-oil game
Comparative omega-3 product
Conversation
Maybe they do talk about just burp
I it's not
I've taken omega-3 before and it's certainly not something that I
I've seen as like
I need to be mindful of
N2
You just can't
You can't parody
No can't do it
That's that honestly
That would have been like a low-level Alex
It's not a parody that now
That would be that's
Any day he could have said exactly that reason why
It's safe to use this as you know like something he can use in his address
Talk about comedians
Stalking
Oh no
Anyways we get to
Plug-in plug
Commercial
Because of course now two minutes of plugs
One minute of commercials
Now you get to the nitty-gritty of the devil's play
Apparently it has something to do with
Ali wants
To get into space
By the way folks I've always wanted to do, nicho Rogan tells me I really need to do it
And I guess
Y'all get to go on Church
So
I've got to go ahead do it
Is a joke CNN
I'm supposed to tell you who you can talk to me
Brian stelter
Will get jealous
I open up
Say you're from now for Joe Rogan
No he will not
Are you ready
Review
10 minutes
In the works
See because I decided the stuff so serious
Authority control
That we also need to really screw it
Fun
At the same time
What the f*** is happening
Anymore
The stand-up Eddie opening for Rogan will make smelter jealous
Weird people for my time doing stand-up
Who had various reasons for wanting to succeed
And I will say that that's the most unhealthy one I've heard
Bull boy
Unhealthy ones
I want to fuel a Coke habit
I want to get my parents love
These aren't normal motivations compared to
I want stelter to be jealous even I want to crush my enemies in comedy is less destroy
I want to make stelter mad my dude 15 up top 40 Brian stelter
He was doing
Average
Eventually start to realize
How little
Goodwill
Being a video figure
Cuz once you actually start
Presenting yourself as a stand-up stand-up with Doug Stanhope you would think I got him two in Austin
Years back
That video is
Grimm hello man
Yeah I think
Coast for about a minute and a half
2 minutes
Whatever you're saying eventually audiences will be like
I want a joke
Right
I've seen this happen
It's the last time
So many time
Diagnosing to happen at local shows when people have dropped in
And it says it can be a real
Surprise
For folks who aren't used to do inside out
And indefinitely not used
Easter failing in front of that many people all at the same time
Unique
Schadenfreude to see somebody
Infinitely more famous than you at ASAP like for year in comic and do five viches wipes
It's the floor with that
It's a weird shot
Can you f****** imagine
A double-bill of Rogan and Dave Chappelle with Alec
Hosting our opening
I can't imagine it laugh
I can't imagine there not being massive protest outside and broken in Chappell both
Standing up and being like
No we can do whoever we wanted our shows and a few weeks later he's gone forever Grogan in Chappell would both be
Wise enough
To know like oh
Yeah if we do this this is all about a like oh yeah and we have
Serve
Used our position to allow him to use us
Yeah
I think they're smarter than that
DeBrands a little better
I don't know I don't even know too many Road hacks
Who wouldn't lose their f****** mind if they're opening a
Got more press than them every show
Yeah you know or if they're openers
Droid of the audience
Before you even got up stage
No no it's almost like if if they do that that would be Rogan's in Chappell just trying to
The flex and see how deep a hole maker
Could dig out of
Have you helped remember back
Wayback show I pitched a reality show called
Somebody is on stage
They intentionally ruin the audience you have to try and get on stage next
If you can save the show
I think a whole
Season of that could be Alex Jones
Is doing opening
Totally see if you could get the audience laid back to a place where they're laughing at things
Change too much in 20 years that we suddenly fit pillow
Pull that off with a sixty-year-old Ali
We can't do that I don't know if you'd have the
The Vim
I don't know another 5-10 years
Is going to do to him it's true
Especially if he
Consider this plan of
Fighting on Pay-per-view
I don't even want to I don't even want to engage with that
You know what my first thought was when he said that is like
Money is bad
This is a real Dustin Diamond vleck Golden Corral
Bitconnect
How long until we get that
I'm sure it's I'll say that there were very few folks
Who don't
Seem to be desperate
Who do did these are the celebrity
Fight
Things are changing a little bit now with the Logan Paul and Jake Paul's
I also think
Because of that
And they're able to get a fight with like Floyd Mayweather
Floyd Mayweather
Is like
Add appointment is career as nothing
Approve a giant paycheck is something that
You could see him doing he also did like WWE
He's somebody who's open
The booking
The idea that Alex think
Him fighting
Ten little
People is something Vick
Could be
Like
Interesting or funny or what
It's kind of sad and it feels like a desperate
MoneyGram in 2002
It's like when we
We can't poop
We can't be doing this if nobody's remaking Revenge of the Nerds man do the past needs to stay in the past
But I would seem like he's actually serious
Are you really going to fight
And the interest
They want me to do something like this for a while and I and I said what about
The fun of the thing
I am so it was for charity and stuff it's also good thing
This is no joke
Competition
This is not a joke
Brian stelter is going to
Challenge by myself
I
2 extra minutes
I'm Blown Away
I am in in the match
I thought we were going to get to the Devils playing
Alex is going to delineate breakdown plug and now he's
Drink to
Promote
A pay-per-view that is not going to happen and his burgeoning stand-up career
Apparently that he's going to do
Because
Things are so wild with the globalist
We need to f*** with their brains and have
Fun
Or
Trying
Cheaply kashian and make some money really fast
Blown Away blown away that you said that out loud to another person I want to fight ten little people
Using that word and nobody went
Hey man
Okay
You said it wrong one time over and over again time I'm in your earpiece just don't say that word again just
Do different words
Okay you said it again
2 *
Okay we're on 5th
I sincerely
You can't interpret this any other way than like
Money is tight yeah
Money is tight
I am being like I really hope Brian stelter would agree to this
I don't know why anyone would
Like if you were Brian stelter
You have to based on Alex's
Like Pablo
Good presentation
You'd have to be worried that you wouldn't
Stop punching you
Because Alex has said that he's a demon in a sanctioned boxing match
He's going to try to send arella Manning
Photo of course
He might trade up trying to Million Dollar Baby
Think that he's totally full of s*** or he's going to try and
Haein
Either way
What what is it what's in it for you
Totally
Anyway I was really wants to
Baby
I'm a manager of midgets
God dammit man
You know what I'm doing right now I don't really want to cover this news
I have responsibilities at no s***
Really genuinely freaked out
Are we now
Enjoy that moment there where he's like I realize it is getting a little too transparent that I'm not doing my
A job
Bulshit that I'm going off on
Yeah look I don't want it in my job so I'm going to on air fantasize about promotional stunts I can do to make money
It has the feel of somebody coming in late to work for like the fifth time that we could be like Leslie Mann
I slept in
I got a nice cup of coffee I didn't get her on time
Because you got me
I don't know what to tell you I just don't care
Yeah
To head to the Hills
Because this news is so
Severe
It's so terrifying
I don't know if he'll be able to do
Do Pay-Per-View boxing
From the woods but
Fly fishing
I just forget any of this ever happened years ago
Not going to let you do that do you know
When the contact tracers in all this
But they're going to come under political enemies houses
Already said we're going to Republican areas
Because they're the ones refusing
All being done that one
Strike forces
Horses
We're going to hunt you down quotes
We have all Bloomberg elated
Quote and we're going to come to your house
Whether you like it or not
Would you like me to play the video
He doesn't
So I don't I don't know
I don't know about
Trace down what I could but
I don't know
And who cares
When he gets into a specific
It's a little bit
It's a little bit of a mess
By the way even the Times of Israel reports
80 + percent
I know I sent that
I think I lost it
My stack
Kentucky
Photo of the Downriver
4% 85%
All the people in the hospital with covid and those dying
Covid
Have had the vaccine
People are dying of covid vaccine killed you and then they say it's covid
Comprende
See this is where we got the inversion of us at yeah
I have no idea what Alec
Is referring to to this article in the
The Times of Israel but interesting Lee
CNBC had an article that came out on July 8th that I was the headline quote virtually all new covid deaths and hospitalizations
They're among unvaccinated people White House
There are breakthrough infections that are being seen and it's inevitable C
No vaccine is a Hyundai
Percent effective
Apparently almost nobody who's been vaccinated fully is seeing illness that requires hospitalization
United's
This reality that vaccines are not 100% effective is
Being exploited by anti-vax propagandist by using real statista
6 in a manipulative way
There was a conversation last month
About how the proportion of vaccinated persons within the group of people who died
With covid-19 is rising
That proportion is rising
This sounds scary
And it's kind of statistic
Could be very useful for someone like Alex
But all you do is think about
Things for a few minutes
And you'll come up with possible explanation
For this phenomenon
The first is that data shows that people who are older are more likely to be vaccinate
People who are older also are statistically more likely to die than younger people so the unfortunate reality is
Happy pool of vaccinated people skews toward containing people who are more likely to die
Unrelated to the shop
The second reason is that the vaccine
Cannot be a hundred percent effective
An article in the guardian really well
Expresses this dynamic
Quote
Consider a hypothetical world where absolutely everyone had received a less-than-perfect
Vaccine
Although the death rate would be low everyone who died would have been
Fully vaccinated
In that scenario that's being painted total numbers of death would be low but if you only focus on the relative
People who died who had been vaccinated
You come up with an easily distorted narrative about the
I find it incredibly hard to believe that the Times of Israel is reporting anything close to what Alex is saying
On July 8th
They reported on the first two covid deaths in Israel in the past 2 weeks
So the number of covid deaths
I don't know how you get that number that Alex's saying but
One of them was a 48 year-old unvaccinated man and the other was an 86 year-old man who had
Been vaccinated
That same day they reported only 37 seriously ill people with covid
In the entire car
Country so
I just don't I don't know where these
These are the stats
Yeah I just I mean
It is such that vicious cycle of you convince people that the vaccine is evil
They don't get the VAC
More people die
And vaccinated people are like we can't let you
To continue doing
You're dying and to your incubators for
The eventual immune viruses we can't let you do this in the only
Way to do that
It's a coming to your f****** homes and try and convince you and then they're like Seether coming into your arms and trying to convince you and you like
Like not forcing people but
Doing Outreach
Yeah might involve knocking on doors
There are a number of people who probably would get vaccinated but don't I have the resources
Play horror have some kind of a block
Towards
Access
David and door-to-door
Awareness campaigns could help with that
And unfortunately they will end up probably
If they do put that in
2 plan
Into effect
Probably will be attack
Yeah that the door will
The shift kicked out of them by
Somebody
I foresee that
It is
It is like that
Talk to you and the administration or talk
Talking about that creation of to America
Cuz you know the vaccinated in the unvax
Estimated
That's just the literally
Expression of the two Americas
Vaxxers in
The horrible anti-vax propaganda that existed before
We're just seeing it happen
Physical life you know what I mean like it's just a
It's the same
It's the same thing we're just seeing it play out
Yeah it's at and the other thing too is that the vaccination
Opposition or whatever has
Metastasized unattached
It's up to so many extraneous political position
That it's being
Co-opted as a
Signifier like
Right-wing politics
And that's that's the dangerous
Reality I felt like a good proportion of anti-vaxxers used to be new age
Oaks and now even new-age Jose like
I did not see the Great
God dammit man
Ships to the prediction about these plans
About
You know I don't know
Door-to-door awareness campaign shadow
The nation
Keep keep this prediction in mind for the next
A few years
See if this comes about
So
Rolling out the contact tracers that they've already done it in Europe is it in Australia
Your neighbor said you were coughing
No I'm fine
My house
Well under the emergency code we don't need a warrant
Come outside
L
What's your name
They stick Lord knows what up your nose
Machine 2 months later says
Sorry
Excuse
The disappearing
Used to Vans driving around
Grabbing people in all the Democrats and all the leftist
It went to college
Everywhere
Certified School
Social workers
Americorps
Or to be in the Peace Corps
Now that's that
Set civilian domestic Army Obama talked about
Military
Make sure you take the shot
See if you're sick and go in your home and take you out take you away
Ago
Such thing as velox
What's that planning
Just making all this up and
Repeating is paranoid fantasies doing imaginary
Yeah I was born I was thinking it was a little hard
To believe that Obama's
Civilian Army matched up
Equally with the 900 billion dollar a year United States military but I could be wrong
You could be
This is just a fantasy that is not going to come
Come to fruition
Just a just a little like keep it keep this in mind for all the people who like Alex's predictions always come true
Can you imagine
People in Vans take
King people away
And everybody being like
It's just
Pandemic
It's so awful it's so awful this scenario where someone would
Have a neighbor that hears you cough
That would be off
Now
If somebody had a neighbor that hears you were gay
Of course the cops should come to your door and rip you out of your house that make
Perfect sense
That makes perfect sense these are people who have consistent belief
Stan
I mean let's talk about the implications of the desert of the Texas abortion law
Alex doesn't cover that so I have no idea about that I haven't actually heard about it
So he does get to another bill though
And this is actually the bills
66-63 was talking about
Did it actually was one of the bills that I already talked to her
Bhrc
Racism in
Public Health
Oh my God
It says here
Analyze data in research
And bring program
Racism the impact
Health and well-being
With all of your medical record
From the CDC
Center
So
Big 666 velvet Alex's chocolate is that a auto Presley bill
The anti-racism the public health Act
For some idea about the bill govtrack gives the prognosis of 4%
Ozio Panthers better than I would have expected on time
Alex hasn't read this bill it would
Create a new entity within the CDC called the national Center on anti-racism and health
The Entity would be tasked with looking at an address in the healthcare implications of our country's history of structural racism
Ranging from issues related to infectious disease to pregnancy-related conditions
Which are two instances of health issues that intersect heavily with race
Additionally the bills whatever CDC coordinate with
The doj to address police violence as a public health
A related matter
The bill was introduced on February
1st and
Like even though it does have imported
Points in it as it stands even Alex knows damn well this isn't
Antipas
More important
Just making up major parts of his analysis
To the Bell
There's no discussion about it
Accessing anyone's medical records
That's part of this
Free associating
Also the national Center on anti-racism in the bill is trying to create
It's not something that is as Alex's reporting it run by the abl in the Southern Poverty Law Center
That's a knee-jerk reaction that Alex has whenever something that sounds like it might be a social positive
This thing says that it's Auntie racism
Silver to make sure my Audis does
Field races for opposing it
I can't be sure to say It's associated with the ATL in the fpl-c I've already convinced the audience are Evil based on
Ganda
Street from white supremacist to the protocols of the Elders of Zion
It's a load of s*** but you can see how he needs to do that to cover his bases with the audio
Keep them in
In check
Also this bill is identical to
4533 the anti-racism in Pueblo
Look Health Act of 2020
Which was introduced by Elizabeth
With Warren last year and died in committee
It's also the same as HR 817
8 which is the house version of that bill that a auto Presley introduced last year
Which also died in
Bunch of bulshit
I would like
To know more about that
4%
I think that's a made-up
There's no way that you can come to
4% like it was
Like what did they 538 and they ran up million simulations and in 4% of them it passed
Any of those situations what happened
I want to know
I don't know
I need more information on their methodology I'm not sending it actually has a 4% chance
Things that gum track
I want to know that
I would like a widow would be interested in how accurate those predictions are historic
One percent by 3%
The number of co-sponsors
Like the number of people who have
Express
Support for the Bell the history of the bill as
It's sand
I think probably going to get her to Bill quite a bit.
Is the fact that we did this last year
Cuz we already have a running of this right right right you can see that it probably has about as much
What chances it did last year
It's it's a bit
But nonsense
So Alex tries to read this bill and even seem sort of riffing
Little bits
I was kind of confused by that
The Centers for Disease Control and prevention
Racism in health
Enforcement program
Kumon other activities
Conditioner must
What can analyze data on your medical record
Administer research Envy
Help
Health Department was set up a New York
Exterminator
Call Mike Kelly really love you
Bill specifically
The cdc's
Injury prevention and control and coordination with the Department of Justice
And other relevant law enforcement
Officer
And other activities enforcement
Austin Public Health
Contact tracers
Your medical record
ATL
Where the Southern Poverty Law Center
Northern Human Services
Local Health Department
Seymour surveillance control
Legalizing the surveillance State they've already had for decades
Alex is clearly cold reading this bill because if he read it before getting on areas
Conspiracy would be
He's having to make up all these extraneous details that aren't in the bill to make the
Square peg fit in a round hole but if you actually read it
He could do this as a white identity narrative without even thinking like yeah you can tell
Because he's trying to force it into a space that doesn't really belong
He doesn't actually know what it said cuz I was reading over the Bell like oh my God this is
This is
Pharrell
That's that
Do you know what that
Sometimes it really bites you whenever you never prepare for your job it's certainly it can really come back and
Hit you in the ass
Yep
Hr666
X-rite this thing
It's what it really is
Is an attempt
Chick-fil-A
Decriminalizing all
All the things that
All these evil global
Must've done
Right
Even from what he read
No no
And I know it's all coming out
Legalize It All
That they don't all go to prison
Horses
House resolution
Covid-19
Reaching and contacting
What is sake
Misaki
Bad drink a bad person
What's
White forces
Horses
So hr-666
Six did not become law Alex just made that up
Also press secretary sake relationship with the term Strikeforce
In a press conference on July 8th
Did she use the term
It was in response to a question about Biden
In talking with
Chicago mayor Lori
Lori Lightfoot about the gun situation in the city
Question
How is the doj Strikeforce going to specifically interrupt the networks that are traffic
In those guns
Answer
They work they're going to work with
The city they're doing them we're doing these strike forces in about five cities around the country
And they want to work directly with them to use legal authorities
The Crackdown on illegal gun trafficking and work in partnership with law enforcement authorities in the cities
And that add additional 2:30 and additional resource
In a press Gaggle the previous day's use the
The term again in relationship
The gun trafficking in Chicago
But on July 6th to discuss
Communities with the low vaccination rates and said quote
That's one of the reasons we initiated the strike forces to go into
The communities and work with them
The determine what they need
To take localized specific
Approach that work
Works with elected officials and community
Picture doesn't like the combination of those word ambulance
Hey weird take that straight
Forced out to 24th and Main because we've got a details like everything's a strike for
Certain people certain people have
Momentum with
Terms
She has like we have a
Team
Strikeforce or whatever I don't know I don't
I don't take this to be a sign that she's going to send it
Squad
The people who don't want Patxi's or something
Phrases that's how we caught the Unabomber
So the rest of the show is Alex interviews Michael malice who I don't care much for
A couple reasons I just got really bored listen
Be there in a few and I just turned it off
His name is Michael malice
His name is Mal
How is that not as equally as 666 his name is Malik
I should be I don't know the reasons why I don't care too much about him
He has his own show and he fairly regularly has comedians as gas
I've no idea if that means he's trying to do a Rogan type thing and if that's the case I don't know like
How much
I can accurately assess where he's coming from and what's meant to be take
Seriously
I don't want to I don't want to engage with something that might
B a b troll
Scroll through his guest list however does reveal that he's friends with a bunch of real idiots
He seems to like having them on his show
I don't look great
The second issue I have is that Michael is there in studio so one would assume that he's heard the show leading up to this point
If you're aware of the bile that Alex has been spilling up to this point and you still decide to associate yourself with it
Then I don't really care too much about what you think your decision not to leave is a massive editorial decision about what you stay on
If you don't if you
Caribbean
A part of the same episode where Alex
He's talking about
The gay men's chorus in San Francisco
Probably being pedophile
Who talks about his pay-per-view fighting aspirations all of this nonsense if you still are like yeah.
I'm going to I'm going to keep this booking
Then I don't
You know there's nothing about your own individual career that I think could even rise.
To the level of like wow you have
Made yourself discounted
Whoops I was booked to this Nazi rally and I'm the fifth
Speaker but
Listen
You got to do your time I was raised up in Chicago comedy you got to do you're a professional
I think the most important thing though is that in 2018 Riding High on Trump energy
Michael malice was one of the speakers at at night
For freedom
Did you go back and look at the list of speakers 8 losses with
Poorly disguised monsters just waiting to be allowed to see
Speak freely
Princeton's Owen Benjamin was on the panel this was while he was still just pretending to be an edgy comedian who like to sing song
Songs that the n-word in them
And just before he came out as an actual knots
And started making his career about doing live streams
Yard complaining about the Jews
Gavin McInnes
Still in that sweet spot where the proud boys were is still being seen as a harmless joke by most people
Ganador in Colton things I'm gone South to the pirate after
Pretend you didn't mean any of the violence stuff you wasn't really
The leader of the group and honestly they were mostly just about having a beer together away from the old ball and chain
Okay
I started a violent street gang and then they became violent streak I didn't have any intention of
Doing that whenever I told all of them that I'm starting a violet gone bad
What about Stefan molyneux ground being a
The creepiest libertarian cult leader
Prior
Dim going to Poland and realize the news actually white nationalist all along
Goofy losers like Jack pasovic and Mike cernovich were there to talking about how they were the Vanguard of culture
What a bunch of losers
Jared Holt cover the event for rightwingwatch in Hindi
Is article has a
Quote from Michael malice his speech haha
Quotes one of the ways the left is 14 decades is by beating the fun-size
That's where the parties are that's where the cool people are
And it's important if you want people to agree with you and come over to have a vent
Like this
Tonight at the social cost of being on the right and do enjoy life in America
One thing I take away from that is that Michael malice and I have very different ideas of what sounds like
Fun
Personally I don't think hanging out with a group of
Pathetic thinly-veiled bigots sounds like a good time
Apparently for him
It does let's not forget
Very unfunny bigot
Also Jared's article include something
Hilarious
Cernovich should take
Campaigns to rid the event of something
Explicitly alt-right media personalities
Leaving Pam hat
To prevent a sea of red make America great again hat
He created a space for a series of decidedly not family-friendly speeches that took aim at feminism tram
People and immigration
Turtle Beaches night of Freedom relied on cancel culture and banning articles
The clothing so they could create the right kind of
Text Buddy was looking for
He was that they like to have fun with a bigot
You can often tell a lot about someone by the company they choose.
Lucky Penny 2018 Michael miles is hanging out with the
The grossest pack of losers
And this week he willingly appeared on Alex's Show when he was doing
This kind of content
No matter what he does or says I don't think they might have him
And I was pretty bored by the
Beginning of the interview and
I just don't
Character
Rise the level of like interesting Danger
It's almost like
Nick Fuentes
Eddie doesn't
These social capital of Someone Like A Joe Rogan
That make them like a we should talk about that yeah
He's just kind of in that middle ground of
Audience
Spite
Pictures of s*** had great you're an a******
Yeah you
Surrounded yourself with more assholes
We have four for today
Just remember
Friends family neighbors acquaintances total strangers about the show
Pre-World news.tv right on the back of the card give it the folks and tell him here
Is it suppress truth
They don't want you to see
Can you imagine the conversation you would have coming if you told somebody wasn't nuts
What's the listen to this show and said it was the suppressed truth in the universe
Can you imagine how worried your friend would rightly be if you did that
It's one thing to TuneIn and somebody like Bill Cooper is boringly going over hoaxed
Discussing conspiracies
It's completely another thing of your friends has to listen to Infowars and get the
Truth and you're confronted by a complete idiot yelling about us a
Francisco gay men's chorus or probably pedophiles
Rambles about doing a Pay-Per-View fights Ten Little People then,
Instantly makes up details
About every real thing he covers like these bills
If your list
English it in three accidents yearly recommending it to someone
A rational response would be for them to be very worried about you
Also
Did he say write down free world news. TV
I think so I think that's one of his new URL is
So part of that conversation would be you handing somebody free world news. TV and then being like what's this and you saying
Infowars
Well then why didn't you write info
You know why
I did write Infowars
We both know why I didn't write it
Free world news. TV
The Trojan Horse
This a little bit even though it's
I guess I'm suppressing it a little bit
You have a little bit of awareness of this dick hole is
Yes what I found I found this episode to be
Disgusting
Honestly
Just overall pretty
Disgusting
Yeah
Especially coming off the heels of a Fuentes episode and hit
This is just
This is turning into a real free speech
Bigotry
Speak freely
Some things that I think we're going to learn
In the next week or so to is
How does the relationship
Nick getting
Kicked off Twitter affect Alex
Relationship
Nick Fuentes has with Infowars
Now Infowars maybe one of the larger platforms that he has access to
There may be a need for him to invest
More
And his prizes
Since on Alex's banned. Video
His ability
Need to come on the shows
Play Maccabeats
Rubble
For someone like Alex because
Nick
Pretty slick
I mean you know
Harrison Smith suck
Nick's not busy
Maybe you know and then
When does the show becomes more popular than Alex's and he has to kill him
Fuentes
I don't think
Is somebody who is
Comfortable being
Third banana on Infowars
I know absolutely not not think you would
Be fine being in the sad sad roll the Harrison
I am lucky to be so tired
Like I could do it on my own f*** out of here
Moving up and taking over
Yeah yeah we'll see I'm I'm very interested to see how that dynamic
Mcplayz out
And whether or not out so I have to cut bait
I don't know maybe maybe he goes pjw
You know maybe he just produce
Maybe that way I would like that get the f*** out of Chicago
Schleich videos in the place among the main they honestly also think
Picnic as a bit more ambitious then Paul has ever been
Paul I think also knows where his bread is buttered
Although he will probably
Every now and again
And give voice to support of her like Nigel farage are you kept candidates
Nick
Is
Somebody by the political project
True be the stuff that he does does involve
Action
Towards
Politic
Action towards bills
Towards
Organizing
And disrupting
Do things like Charlie Kirk event
Things like this are things that have
Real
On the 8th the real-world implications hidden folks
Like Paul and Alex
They don't really do as much of
That's a good point people like Paul and Blake Harrison
The kind of understand that sure they want to sway opinions on things
In the Infowars
Or whatever but
More about like
Creating your beauteous
Nick is up to
You got a good point
What are the reasons that I find Nick to be more of a dangerous
Person been
A lot of these other folks
You know I don't cover his
Show even though he does a show
Is because I don't think he's the same
Type of person
I think he is a bit of a grifter and he's scamming a little bit obviously
I'll put an ideologue yeah yeah I think you would
Sacrifice
Selling America First shirts
For political action
Yeah I think he probably would
But I think it's a someone like Alex I don't
Think that
I don't think that's
Yeah it seems like
Princesses trying to get to that kind of norquist
Place where he can somehow convince all of it cuz he's never going to actually make it into
Like Congress or something.
But he can convince them all even be like the white nationalist pledge of likes
Hey
No new people
You know like that kind of s***
Empire biotrack in the support a folks
Like Paul gosar and Michelle Malkin true
You end up drying
To expand the influence
Ants that human is
Groyper is having
Hit some
888 it's a bit of a different thing
Then what were used to cover in
Not to say that it's
The last serious because I think it actually is probably more serious then
Fun yeah
Maybe it is something that is worth
Exploring a bit more I know that his particular brand of content is a little bit more
Unpalatable
431 in audience maybe there is some value
U2
Maybe covering
A little bit more of his America first
Joe
An end one another one of the reasons why we haven't is because there was a limited amount of it was on it for what
And if it starts to leave more on Infowars
Then it becomes
More in our sphere
Directly
So we'll see we'll see how things play out but but
For now I just think this episode sucked
And I also think
But that too
Disco gay men's chorus oh I'm just pretty catchy
But until then Jordan website
Also on
Twitter
If you could please find a local charity or Bellefontaine your to help out people doing God's work
But until then I'm Neo I'm Leo mdzs
Text Clark I'm Daryl
Honestly if there was any justice in the universe Rupert should have won that season 2 survivor
Animated times he did actually seem like a little bit unhinged and he was screaming at people for voting at 4 then maybe
Maybe there was a dark side to him that wasn't fully captured in the show and that's entirely possible
I accept that's possible but
What a bright ray of sunshine. Dude was anyway
Rupert
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work