Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for this knowledge B
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Action for you
My brakes but today is actually it's been a little bit of
Challenging week
But if he gets around to my bright spot
And that is the beginning of this weekend I don't know I don't know if I'm
Getting sort of like Stolen Valor by calling it surgery
I'm not sure I call it surgery cuz it was cutting something out.
Because it's just cuz it's not like open heart surgery doesn't mean you don't get to call it surgery feels like I'm putting on a
Presumptuous
I know that's true I have dealt with
A ingrown toenail on my right
Big toe for the past 15 years
Long long time
I've had it cut out a couple times and it comes
Because lingering chronic problem
I've gotten to the point where I
Kind of made a decision in my head like while it's just never going
This is something that I have and it's for the rest of my life
Flight Club
Recently I started to come around on the idea of like that's a silly
Jamaican I started to think about all of the ways in which
It is impacting my life
Staff are there so many things that I want to do or I want to be able to
To do that I can't do because of this
Right like I can't climb a tree
Because of I do I'll probably bang my my toe on it and it'll hurt like hell
Can't do push-ups
The normal way because of the excruciating pain of trying to put on my weight
On the on my foot I can't run
Because of the constant
Hiding on the ground of the foot
I'm sorry I finally decided to bite the bullet
Take care of it
Now have
A wounded foot
Very nicely and
Yeah it was it was an interesting experience
It's to go in at
And I have that.
Things cut
Circle
I believe anything in the open wound and I like sometimes I leave for steps in something like that nothing
I don't think the wound is big enough to put 46 then but
No I think I don't think was any souvenirs
Synagogue
Oh man I can see now we're going to get into conspiracy theories
This was absolutely a patriot Dr and you have been implanted with a
Fine they know where you are
My apartment
Cool
Couldn't you call me
They told the beginning of this week I couldn't run
End until at least two weeks from now you feel well
Yeah my toe
Looks like it says right now not going to be running for a bit
It's a bright spot to come to a point where I can't take care of this guy
To move in a positive direction
Well obviously for years
Constantly
It's not like a regular topic
I just read up
Stuff you want
That's awesome
What are the best part about it is that like going to like
ICare afterwards a lot of it
It involves just Epsom salt baths
Matt Smith
Series of Doctor Who
You know whenever I first saw him I think it was like 2010 was almost
12 years ago or something
And it was immediately like
Oh
This would be like if I was a duck
That was it was just like this makes
Good sense to me and I'm rewatching it and it's still
Is allowed he's loud he is simultaneously
Incredibly fast-talkin very angry and also sad all the time
Interesting
Sounds like I don't need to watch this show live experience
Today's episode of a little bit of a Survivor thought
Is the new segment Survivor thoughts
I started season 10
I think it's harder to watch now
Because in season 9
Probst
Starts dating one of the contestants after the season's over
Still not cool with that little bit uncomfortable to watch
That's not okay
I'm sure that they had a fine relationship is based on like
Makes me a little uncomfortable
And then what was the other thought that I had season 9 is almost certainly where the first
Vale of the show being destroyed happen because something happens in the second episode
Square
They
Hypnotic
Explain
How this is supposed to go
There's a man in the women's tribe
Reward
And immunity
Okay
The first challenge as a tribe get a reward
I meant individually to get immunity
One-man or one-woman will win immunity
Then
Both tribes have to go to Tribal Council and vote somebody out
Bright
The person who wins immunity
Individual
It's safe
They go to the other Tribal Council and give you immunity to one of the opposite ripe
It's like
While the people were trying to explain what was going on is it like no no no no no no no you're trying too hard
This is it there's no
Nobody was like hey you know what the problem with Survivor was
Not enough Rube Goldberg machines sincerely like the people on the show trying to explain what was happening Steve
And I was like oh no
Not many people tuned into TV to watch 9th grade story problems from geometry talk
Talk to them
Yeah there's a lot of logic puzzles that go on in terms of the rules
40 miles an hour
Headed east and another one of your teammates
Infuriated
Quickly it deteriorates that seems to me to be like that
Just that backpack
Cracked
Spread we've run out of ideas windshield is going to break
Also last survivor thought I loved the deranged that they haven't earned their challenges
Elaborate
The job over there to climb this wall then carry it back over the wall
Heaven sometimes like f****** hold your breath
Bedside yeah that's such a favorite joke
All of Rick and Morty is
Rick sets up this like sausage we have to get
Through challenges
And then because he was
Two drunken of the third one of these just like I ran out of ideas
Three-pointers
Exactly what I was looking for
It does feel like that
Jordan today we're going to be going over July 13th 2020
That was a straight-up tide that was simultaneous episodes
Troubling in a number of ways and some of the stuff I'm excited and
Uncomfort
Get to that moment
Let's say hello to some new
The first bag creator of butt poop thank you so much you are now policy walk
That might be a code of some sort
Whatever whatever that is I'm sure it's
Neuromancer was a good book but all tomorrow's parties is William Gibson
All capitals basketball
Fight me
You're now policy walk
Opposition
I'm a policy wonk
Next
Yolanda pronounce Yolanda and not Yolanda thank you so much you are now policy walk
Orlando
Hello
You're not
I'm a policy wonk
We got to go
What's the business
Heroin
Large
Certainly we haven't we have a little bit of we got to get deep
But we have to get deeper than usual
Giving someone life is giving someone death
You can say that
You could say that
And I I I hate to say this and it pains me but
I think this is probably our last
Birthday sextant
I apologize to anybody who is that made a birthday shout-out request that has not been you not heard it on
On the show
We can't risk getting out of control. We had fun and I want this to be something that
We could all have a good time with and I think we did
I think
Between us
And we we ran this into the ground
You know you could say
Vet starting a segment
Is ending a second
That is what we have come to
In this farewell edition of birthday shout-outs I'd like to give
Shout out
So chemical Pleiades the cat
Where you at happy birthday Ryan happy birthday Ryan
Is b****** fantastic
So Stephanie sent me a message
Happy birthday shout-out to
My brother
So I know the birthday
Is on the 14th
Of July
I know that he's 31 years old his name
See once again
If you are accepted
Guess what
You got wish to happy birthday and if your Stephanie's brother stay with you
He was the one who emailed brother
If you're Stephanie's brother you never specified if you're somebody out there and you have a sister named Stephanie and your birthday
On the 14th and you're 31 years old happy birthday birthday
Happy birthday
Now unfortunately and this is true this is our last birthday segment
These are will also be the last birthdays for all people involved
I'm sorry to say that but I was how it works
I don't stay by that but
Whatever
We're going to do this year July 13th
The good old days
Whorehouse
ZZ Top
Indiana Jones
Parenthood
How how how
ZZ Top lyrics
Hey I love I love all Aerosmith songs when all the sudden he's just like
Aerosmith
Yeah I had to buddy who did we did do the lot of karaoke
Get together and he would do like
Play ZZ Top and you can just sing she's got legs she knows how to use them tires up
Is the m of fence
The entire time
Nobody ever claimed ZZ Top with
Position
Composition on the Planet of Women
Or slip inside my sleeping bag
I will never not be delighted whenever I
I'm finally get back to reading ZZ Top
Song titles are pretty good
Did you guys get
Owl.
How are we going to start off here's where Alex
About 5 years ago
Gmail already Boston ford.com
URL
Library
Define one that resists them
This really is the Holy Grail of control
This is a rare opportunity where you can actually do it
Experiment to test the truth of the claim that Alex is making and it is not true
I have multiple Gmail accounts
For personal and professional use tonight I tested sending various Infowars length between them
Not got censored at numberblocks
Even links
Student homepage not even hiding behind some dummy you redirect URL just went and went there just fine
Visitors more agreement bragging that I was just trying to do
That's so funny cuz I saw the I saw one of the test email
Onr I looked at it and I was like
And then two seconds later I was like
Oh Alex must have claimed that you couldn't email his leg
I immediately knew exactly Heather
Before we get too deep into this episode I want to mention that there was a really severe tone
That you'll notice
Throughout the show and
I don't see them before I started listen to this episode over on banned. Video
Heather's preparing things
The featured video on the homepage was a gris-gris video titled quote
This Is the End
Oh that's a horseshoe start
The episode of recovering today from July 13th has the headline quote
The globalist must be arrested now or billions will die
As I was looking over the video titles on the site I couldn't help but feel like this was just kind of end of the world theme
One video was just titled quote New World orders official announcement by government shocks
The planet
Think about how many times Alex's run that headline in the past
How many times has reported that finally the New World Order is come out into the open
Almost a joke at the
The thing that really stuck out to me was how low Alex's view count though
We're on these videos
You think of this we were telling of doing would be the kind of thinking employee to gain attention to drive traffic and if that's the plan
I'm not convinced that that plan is working
August actual episodes of you count
Between two and three hundred thousand views which isn't bad
Way below what you'd expect
For someone like
In Alex's position
It looks like Alex is Saturday shows which have a guest heavy format
Who seem to be far more popular than his usual show
And I can't help but think of it
That's at least partially because his normal show sucks
But even the audience
Maybe getting tired of this are getting really ready to be like
You can't carry the show by yourself
All the king's horses men and Sensational headlines Camp makeup
Or how tired this act is getting
I want you have these Saturday shows that are like
For guests
Deep
Alright let's see what
Nick Fuentes is going to bring to the Mayo Clinic in your barn
Yeah like you do that and if I go out at least that'll be different than Alex
Rambling on about bulshit yeah
If I were him a Alex I'd be a bit worried
About this
Phenomenon
Like you still pulling way better numbers than Owen Shroyer and Harrison Smith butt
I was looking around and he's pretty consistently getting beat by Greg Reese's Sensational last
Little video essay
To be the leader in the clubhouse
You know what he's got to do
Get a Coho
First show
But don't go in The Patriot
Sport
Talk radio
All those guys are crazy
Conservative insane and they are they all know how to talk non-stop without actually saying anything
I think Owen Shroyer has some history in
In sports journalism perhaps I think back in Missouri he might have been involved
Attache please switch to just being an old Texas Rangers
Talk format
Why not
Couldn't
Here's where Alex has to go from he's already made the claim that the Gmail blocks everything
Show nonsense
Amazon to be like
Text Sarah block your email
I'm glad that
Sake talking to Preston
We're getting ready to start
The DMC is
National Police 47 Oz that's actually who
And the Pentagon
I would
To read all of your text messages
Have them stand by AI flag
Block your ability to say certain things
Going to go into the autofill function and not let you
Certain
Even before
It's been scanned
When you try to send it
What
This is the power of AI Control
So first of all up to this point Alex has not specified what article his employee showed him that
Spelled all this out
He's made reference to how important it is a couple of times but I have no specific
Fix to work on other than I think it was in Politico
Now what's really break down the claim that Alex is making here because I think if you look at the constituent parts of this conspiracy
You'll see how desperately he's just grabbing it
Straws trying to make stuff up
So press secretary Jen sake said in a press conference that the dmc's new police force
Is teamed up with a pentagon and their enlisted
Trainees from the abl in the Southern Poverty Law Center
History literally everyone
This will be achieved by
Through an unspecified
Then I guess stop them from being delivered
Wow human review takes place like us
This is also going to somehow affect the autofill function of every different phone companies operating system which is going to make it so
So you can't type certain
Now autofill apparently will no longer just suggest words
That you might be typing
School force you to take their suggestions
It seems like a user experience nightmare waiting to happen
I think
1 people might notice
Before we go any further with what they can do
If there's a DNC police force teaming up with a pentagon already a prop
I don't need further conspiracies
This is stupid
Even if you were an evil all-powerful cabal bedtime
This would be a dumb dumb way to do it
For one reason the autofill thing would cause an uproar in the consumer base
We've seen over and over again that in the realm of digital communication if certain words are banned people will try to find ways to use
Go to replace letters and symbol
Getaround scanning
If a company were to impose word restrictions to the b word affect the customers
Ability to use the product
People would adapt
Communication or stop using
The product
What's going on here is that Alex's just evolved disc
Conspiracy about that bill we talked about in the last episode
That anti-racism in public health Act
The 2021 the tablet isn't going to pass
Not just about the adln splc reading your medical records now they scan all your text messages
All thanks to this
Politico article I think
Yeah I think what's funny about that is
More
More than anything else
More than any of Trumps
Sly's or the conservative propaganda
A massive amount of consumer inconvenience would lead to an overthrow of our
More than
More than like all they stole the election everybody's like politics is corrupt
But if you're like I can't text my friends anymore
I mean you took down my spaces yeah
Who's huge MySpace created that you cook people forget that deaf course they do
Course they do we never would have had to orgasm
Or any of those movies he was in
That waiting
He wasn't waiting Ryan Reynolds yeah yeah yeah yeah
At 1
Mr. Brooks
Yes
I was going to mr. Deeds
Button-down evil twin Nevada
So Alex is already made the erroneous claim the Gmail blocks Infowars Lakes
And I told you ten years ago there Holy Grail will be
Certain voice Prince Will now
Facebook doesn't allow the uploading
Any Trump clips
Unless it's by a handful of Select
Control corporate media so
This is authoritarian system
That you could ever imagine
Just a quick search on Facebook of recently post
Did Trump Clips returns many from Newsmax
To I wouldn't
Call anointed by the mainstream media
Fox News as well as local news channels posted speech at CPAC
Also this is really bad news
For Donald Trump jr.
For him to learn this way that he is one of the handful of anointed mainstream media Outlets
Outlets
Are you know that you that you suck your and you think your anti-establishment then you become the establishment at
He has a page on Facebook with 3.2 million followers
He was posting
Videos of
What just occurred to me
What just occurred to me more than anything else
Was with that email thing
How could you listen to the show and believe him
When you almost certainly have
Email links to your family
That day
Do you know what I mean like they are always sending links to each other always sending out emails with
Maybe they just think that they're one of the lucky one
12in Center
Tuesday or maybe they use me like
Whatever his feel like you're getting around
Man
Alex gets to talk about this Politico article and I finally am able to sort out what he's
What is covering
Story about it yesterday
And it was posted infowars.com
And then of course the Great
Carlson
Add with it
And now it's all over the news today
Where where is Congress
What are they doing about it
Are some of the headlines breaking
Private text messages reports Politico
Okay so that was enough to help me figure out a rock
Couldn't do when I have my bad toenail but now that I have applied
But I found a grip
Politico by Natasha korecki
Entitled quotes
Potentially a death set
White House goes off on vaccine fearmonger
The sentence from the article that causes intense backlash from Alex and Tucker and all their ilk is this
Including the Democratic National Committee are also planning to engage fact-checkers
Terriers to dispel misinformation about vaccines that are sent over social media and text
That sounds pretty scary but if you read the entirety of the article at
It's pretty clear that what they're talking about is not individual users
But organizations that use text messages
Send a messages that are directed towards a road in public health
The article brings up Charlie Kirk
Turning Point USA
Turning Point action a 501c for affiliated with tpusa
It also send out SMS messages urging people to sign petitions on the top
In what message viewed by Politico Kirk content quote
Find ascendant goon
The door-to-door to make you take a covid-19 vaccine
Sign the petition no more no medical raids in America
This is obviously a problem and when you're in a leadership position do you have to choose what you're going to do
You can try to address the problem of people like Charlie Kirk literally profiting off letting his audience die or you can do nothing
And accepted a certain subset of the population
He's going to be misled off a cliff by this type of messaging
I don't know what the right call would be here and I have no interest
Being in a leadership position because I couldn't solve a problem like that
I can say that I would be on
I'm comfortable with the government
Itself taking action and reading people's text messages and such
If that's what they were doing
Even if it were mastex
It's being sent out by clearly bad faith actors like
Charlie Kirk
Thankfully
Natasha korecki the writer of the Politico piece clarified on Twitter what was meant by that sentence
Pittsfield a couple days
Is right wing
Media outrage
As the story points out it's
Allied private groups that are working with SMS carriers
Not the way
Even then there's no ability for groups to read individual texts
Aside from ones they received themselves
Disable auto complex
Listen to the story
So these are groups that are allied with the White House that are trying to work with text messaging providers to enlist them
To limit the ability of people like Charlie Kirk to spam this information over the phone
They wouldn't be able to read texts prior to them being set it would likely result in the system
If a recipient complain to their text
Provider they look into it
Ask her whether they decided
Was in their company's enter
Contrite
The version of the story that Alex's reporting is entirely dishonest
But there's a kernel of something
Probably
Should be discussed underneath it I think
I don't care about Alex's position on it but it
There's something
There's
Something important
There's a really tough question they have to wrestle with and that is should speech that demonstrable put people at risk be as protected as
Is any other kind of spy
And if so at what point does that risk become a problem
It's hard
It's a hard question
The courts have held that you can be charged for encouraging Harmon someone via text message
Even though it appeared that that's just you engaging in speech
Michelle Carter was sentenced to 15 months in prison for involuntary manslaughter after she encouraged her boyfriend
To commit suicide
The appeals court upheld her conviction in the Supreme Court decided not to hear the case
Which implies that they didn't consider the ruling
W true infringement of the First Amendment right
This may not be in a
Exact parallel but there
Has been a willingness from courts to rule the
To certain extent
Encouraging harm can constitute speech that is not protected
The direct Armand Carter's cases much
Clearer but when almost everyone dying in the United States of covid is now unvaccinated
It does feel like directly discouraging vaccination through dishonest means
Could be argued to be an attempt to cause harm
I don't know where
I don't know and I don't know where the line would be
But I do think that there's probably
Discussion to be had
Sparrow far more insightful people than even myself
Certainly more insightful than Alex
Yeah
I mean
So I be if I was looking at it I would say the
First thing that you have to
To do
Before you take any action is prove that it's
Malicious and repaired
So if they're constantly spamming out malicious
Lies
Then that seems like a much easier way to deal with it than just being like
Hey
Blanket you can or can't do this
To allow for error
Say say if you get caught spamming
Flies
Wichita
Hard to tell if they're lies or not
Repeatedly after being told that you can't lie to people anymore then you get
F****** Destroyer finder whatever it is
Did you know
Kind of thing it's not it's not necessarily A
We can ban or unban
Speech so much as I would almost even add in a qualifier that there needs to be a profit motive
Live to
Because I think that people can be misled
And sincerely
Do harm by way of
Plumbing system
You haven't the wrong information or whatever they can
I think they're doing the right thing
I am do something that is is absolutely involved
Totally I think at least in terms of misinformation
In the case of that girl and her boyfriend
Then been misinformation this early
Do tissues there is that it's not protect
Causing harm
Right it's directing harm
I mean it's it's
It's very
In that situation
Personal and 121 and in this
Vaccine situation
MedStar creating a mask
Culture
Around
Encouraging harm
Yeah and it's tough
It's tough.
It's tough to know what the
What the right thing to do is to
Protect
Speech the same time
Not allow
Devastation
I'm going to go with
Harris is playing in The Rock
I haven't seen The Rock
Disgrace
I've heard that
That implies that I'm going to watch it and that implication
Is wrong here is Alex being wrong about this
Article
Just save lives
With covid
Criminal
But really the election
We can't let Trump
How to speeches on Facebook
Election
That's not something you're allowed to do that's terrorism
This article literally says nothing about Alexa
Misinformation
Outages
Completely Magnum at all
It's almost
Is entirely about ways the people are trying to fight back against the right-wing misinformation campaign about Biden
Proposed door-to-door awareness Outreach about the vaccination
Campaign like people saying it's going to be
People coming to your door with needles and stuff
People
From the community
Coming around
You know it's easier than you might think
To go get a shot
If you think that there are hurdles
And you would like to get a shot
No I mean it do you think it's too expensive guess what it's not
It's not
Yeah but that's
That's really what the campaign is answer this article is about
Dog just
The what do you do about the incessant
Misinformation surrounding
These things
Dressing up as Jehovah's Witnesses
That's the trick
Everybody expects Jehovah's Witness to come to your door sooner or later
That's what they've got going on
I don't feel I don't I don't feel like you're going to get
The warmest welcome true
But I guess you're probably not if you're not going to
Right away
Probably not knock on the door
Election misinformation
I also lies a bit more
That's what scares me the most of time
It's hard to break the big story
The debates fines were there
Calling something out quietly
SMS messages
And that of course ladies and gentlemen is it such a loss in ATL already reading ever
They want to announce it and normalizing
The edl and sblc you're not mentioned once in the Politico article
I guess Alex
Could just read the term Biden
Allied groups and assume that's
Which groups the Articles talking about but that's no better than
Just a guess on his part
He's reporting this based on nothing
Yeah it's just
That's a straight-up bulshit since talkingshit
Might as well sblc natrez enemies
The audience's prime to think demons
That why not
So Alex brings up a clip that he covered a couple weeks
It's back here
Man
This this is metastasized
What did the Canadian Health minister
Martial law
People will protest our government
No speeches allowed
Apply
DDC the
Authoritarianism
They're just
This is a complete mess representation of what Nova scotian Health official Doctor Strange said in a clip Alex covered whew-wee
Respect
Just made an offhand comment about one of the advantages of large Gatherings not happening is that it limits the ability of people spread
Misinformation
From Gathering and disseminating dangerous public health messages
The broader context of the video is
We talked about is Strang and Premiere ranking Fielding questions about whether or not it was wise of them
To open up schools and businesses
Which they were doing
How to completely making up all the surrounding context of this clip most likely cuz he does
Steven actually remember what was said
You get the strong sense that
At a certain point only remembers the fake version of things that use repeated
On his show and that's kind of troubling
Yeah there's there's definitely a pattern of life
Eventually he convinced
Is himself and it goes from short-term memory into long-term bulshit a self-reinforcing
Artificial
Facade
He's his own fee
Back loop it's weird
It is weird
Terrifying the irony though that entire press
Friends really being about how they were opening up and people were concerned that it was too early
He's never going to end
Add stats
You know I mean he's right
Come out and say it's martial law and no one is allowed to speak offline
Would be tyranny
Wow he was talking about how he had already relaxed martial law haha
Yeah we're free journalists were concerned about public health are we ready
Earl is there like a man I don't know
So
This is staggering
More covid-19 vaccine deaths last week
And he lasted covid-19 deaths
That's it official number
Doesn't sound right
Whatever he brings up something incongruous
That doesn't sound like a good happen
Don't seem like he ever entertained the possibility that it actually could
I was waiting for him to explain what the f***
He was basing this off of
Until about the end of
The show any just make a passing reference to Gateway pundit article
I tried to find it basically all that it it's rooted in is
That there are reports of like 9,000 people who have died after taking
The vaccine
Okay that doesn't mean the 9,000 people died from the back
Actually now that doesn't sound right at all
40 *
I like only one in 40 vaccine side effects
Whatever numbers
Elsa
It's a little bit dumb
Yes
So we know that Alex
Believes that
Bulshit
Except when people
30 likes with
Not b******* never
Got in fraudulently
Being elected
Merkel has been installed macron has been installed
Johnson got elected posing as a patriot he's as bad as they come
In the UK
Didn't take long
I'm going
To cover
That in the last segment of this hour
The fact that
We are not
Anymore
Things are not going to get better
Loretta
I got to be around
So on politicians Alex doesn't like
Fraudulent
Tucker power fraudulently
Now
He does not like
The UK Boris
Boris Johnson
He did really well
Pretended to be a patriot
I do I do appreciate that
The far-right
Like the only possible way to be like me
Immediately hated
If you do one thing they don't like like that that idea of Boris being like hey
Even I
The sociopath I am
I'm like we can't let another
Ton of people die
I can't do that
I'm not bolsonaro bolsonaro will let everybody died Trump will let everybody died
Talk about people for one moment my conscience existed and now the far-right thinks I'm done
You're pretending exactly
It took 60 seconds release
Surprising how many chances
Trump has been
When given a million billion
Thanks
Bike racks
But
The other thing too is there like
I think that Alex just doesn't know anything about what bolsonaro does or State score
Because of that he gets a million chances
Themes of power
Described as a few Rambo
Official database
More deaths from vaccines last week
From the supposed covid shot
Covers
They're making their move
And I told you that
Icon with more control than before
And now that's being done exactly as I said
Because it's an enemy plan
Everybody legislators
And governors and Society
And shoving corporations and businesses
Does the first vaccine passports
Once they get their world ID
What you can do
What you can eat
Mobile
Internet
Ideas for social Credit Control
It is for surveillance
It's all be shoehorned in under the name of covid
And Center Spencer them for covid
Another news
Bombshell over-the-top
Unprecedented
Also not true
Yeah boo you know it's just sometimes you really want to like grab these people and just shake the
Them by the shoulders and be like
The whole point
Is it despite how awful you are
I am still trying to not kill you
Birthday idea
Where You Are
Makes me not want to care if you live or die
And I think that's one of the things that makes
This question about these
These spam
Messages that are detrimental to Public Health so
Challenging is that like
The alternative to
Trying to find a solution to it is just cutting your losses and
Just being like wow these people are just going to die
Far right is just going to lose
I guess 3% and then we'll move on next f****** nightmare it terrific disagree with
Fundamental
Difference
That mean even
The piano as far as
They could be tenable the different than ideas about reality
Walk them to
Be healthy
Why is this hard
Yeah
So
Alex
His big thing here is as I got to read your text
That's just right
Joanne so in order to
To strengthen this he needs to harken back
Do when he was kicked off Facebook
At the time there was an interview that Oliver Darcy
We did I think I'm CNN
And they're discussing him being King
Kick-off Alex
Who kicked off
Instagram and Facebook
Cuz they both owned by the same company at the time there was some question if Alex is going to be
Kick-off WhatsApp cuz it was also owned by Facebook
And Oliver Darcy said they didn't know if he had an account
Salix Place necklace
Greatly exaggerated what he say
Almost 2 years ago
Talking about what it's really all about
Silence
Did everybody ever figures out that
I'm telling you this not my opinion
Over
Taking you to a hellish
Dystopian
You're seeing him for two years ago
3 Banning Alex Jones and Infowars
For now only there
On Facebook but also from Instagram
Am I checked in also to see if these people would be banned from WhatsApp
Which is also owned by a face
What the heck
Person cannot say immediately because it's
Unclear
Whether some of these people have
What type of
Text message
Do you have a house for children to be on a gun
Next
Olivia couldn't buy a house on Facebook
Yeah there's another
Whole section of the internet
There's always find all kinds of stuff
You could use your
Also I don't know if Alex didn't have a WhatsApp account
No I think this conversation is stupid
Don't care you completely misrepresenting this has nothing to do with this guy can't privately text you both
You know I think he realizes that like that
That clip is not as damning as
I remember it being
I have built it up by repeating the story over and over again to myself
That it said something far more damning than it does
I think this is Alex's attempt to save it
Text messages
Yeah Alex Jones is getting around as his fans are
Still on air via text message
We've just got to get in those text messages we just
You know you're right
He just got to get in that private email those text message
Just yeah where's a good guy
What those dirty Americans talk
Shut them up right now don't worry we will though
Are the bad guys
The damn shame we can't find that clip
I feel like
After a certain length of
The time listening to the show on the regular
Eventually you'd go
It is strange that they can never find the clip that says what Alex says the clip says
Weird play the clip
Doesn't say what Alec
They can find the clips that don't say what Alex says yeah
But they can't find the clips Dulce with Alex
It's weird yeah
Or suspicious
Almost always
Desperately crying out for context
Eclipse that can find it like
And then
So Alex is like maybe
They clear the lake
Stuff coming up
Come up
Getting real and yeah
Get up
You know it's going to happen
In America
Everybody
Wow
Looking for work
Not in the next segment
Explain
And slowly destroy us
Going to look like
Man if we don't turn this around
I would suggest you record this
Because you were unable to stop them very soon
To hear
About to be on the Garry Moore and that's in the coal mine
Really for the end of this phase
And there's going to be a horrible future
For Humanity
I really tried to warn everybody as best I could
This is a forced disc
I've got a recording
Also it's
So funny to me that Alex is pretending his any room left to claim that his enemies are going to
Close some metaphorical Neuse in the next few years
Like 6 months ago back when he was prowling around with David Icke
Can trying to see if there was money to be made and just denying the covid even
Existed
Alex became enamored with a metaphor that I could
Could use regular
I could describe a room
It's a bad room you don't to be in that room like an interrogation room
Somehow the globalist to lure you into the room
Which seems
Because the door is open you can always good I can run away
According to David Icke
It's through the release of a completely
We made up a virus and I guess for Alex you somewhere close to that
Dolittle
Less absurd
Get you in the room and another door closes in your trash
Alex's deploying with
The closing of the news
Burberry long stretch Alex Wood
Consistently repeat David Icke metaphor about the door being closed now and how we're stuck in the room with
The globalist
It was months ago
There's a zero credibility and I'm playing this game now with slightly different words
Like did we find a way out of the metaphorical room only to end up in a noose
Is the news in the room
Well what happens is
You go in the room they lower you in cuz the room is filled with chalk
Chocolate all kinds of good chocolate all kind of bonbons
Close the door behind you
Boom what pops out of the two-way mirror
Raptor and we know what they do to you if you
F****** chalk
Chocolate man
Chocolate mousse
Chocolate News
It wasn't great.
Alex makes a claim in this next week that he cannot backup
You understand
Double din
This isn't a Zombie Apocalypse movie
This is a controlled demolition of the planet
Please substantiate.
Please
Prime is double triple and quadruple all over the place
Where's the data coming from
How do you define crime what is going on here this is a meaningless
No it's
Basic questions are things that he should be addressing
Unless they are
The Listener should just feel free to just ignore this cashier
The temperature stalking nonsense
Yeah I don't know if
I don't know if we can live in
2021 now and listen
I mean read and watch all of these people
Redo
The f****** late 80s with super-predator
Do not immediately go like
Oh this is all massively races
This is horrific
All of this like all crime is getting out of control s*** despite
The fact that it's been lower than it has been
The f****** 60 there whatever
There's no way you can't see that is like
We're trying to get more black people in jail
We're running low on fire fighting
Slaves
Like that's
So
Alex's got some plans
For dinner
I wish I wasn't how I was going to set up this Cliff face Alex's dinner plans
This morning
I got my parents coming over for dinner tonight
I'm just going to tell him
How we protect ourselves
Because we tried to stop.
Lockstep
We tried to stop the initiation of this they did it anyways
I would give anything to be there for that dinner
I would watch that watch that for sure that would be way more exciting than my Dinner with Andre for sure
I liked my Dinner with Andre but this is the s***
This is like the Fast and Furious version of My Dinner with Andre I don't believe that this conversation happen
Yelp
Absolutely.
Absolutely
That looks all better off we got to I got to survive
Alright so whatever pizza tonight or what
What the hell
Just have another beer
So I dude
This is this is where things get very interesting
So we've got a situation on our hands right now
And you know the globalist
They plan to do all day
Everything is happening is playing
But the timeline
Who is the five years behind we tried to stop the initiation of this they did it anyway
Why but
Just to give you a Prelude
They had to because we expose our long-term strategic plan
We're always going to do what they're doing
All these countries around the world
They had an accelerated program
Are all in their committed
Yeah as soon as I heard that one balloon fell from the roof absolutely
Look up to my apartment
It started playing episodes Ramos in 2017 and 25th
Teen in 2009 and here's 100003 they ten years behind their always ten years behind
So you why coming up after the break
That's because Alex is expose their plans or something over the last 30 years
Push them back any further than 10 years behind it's kind of been more status-quo thing
He's fighting the f****** devil
Grifols
Devil does not care about 10 years
The devil has existed for 10,000 years and less than 1/10
What percentage of the devil looking at his watch in the tapping his hoof
Call man
Really scary in this neck
Going to stop
Just go ahead and get this out now
Bio weapons
If we tried to overthrow
You did
Give me type
Populist
Christian group
They're always planned the depopulation regardless later once they
In an attempt to maintain control
One way or another Associated plan
Okay
And succeed or your makeup do it next year
Maybe next month
This is one of the more f***** up things I think I've ever heard Alex
Suggested I mean that since you're late because ultimately there's no art team of villains that are being antagonized by his
Nope I find a challenging to even come up with the right words to condemn this because honestly
What can you possibly be advocating for other than vigilante action against his imagined enemies or
Acts of domestic Terror
You're about to be murdered in 10 years or you can die fighting now
I know that we heard Alex discuss how the globalist
Prefer an orderly killing of everyone but Alex and his friends are screwed because the globalist have plan B which is
With superb Iowa
What I haven't heard Alex Advocate is that his audience should engage in actions that they would
Think would
Escalate things towards
Plan B coming into play
That is a bizarre and terrifying version of fantasy-based accelerationism
There is no group.
The threatening to kill off the public in 10 years or possibly a year or a month
That's a creation of Alex's inability or unwillingness to read
Combined with his intense breed
Any psychotic worlds
No actions that Alex's audience
Takes can make it any more or less likely that a worldwide biotech kill-off is going to happen
Because that's just a paranoid fantasy that uses to make money
But people are real
Any actions that his audience could taken in Tempe
Disrupt the global is supposed to plant
Kill everyone in an orderly fashion in 10 years
Could have severe implications
For the General Public
I'm somewhat comforted by have ineffectual in an active Alex's audience seems to be but even so
This kind of rhetoric is
Completely unacceptable and
I think it's even a departure from the norm for how
Now that's crazy
Alex's introduced the idea that the global civil plan that has been tonti populate
He also introduced the idea to that the listeners of his show are as good as dead already
But I haven't really ever heard him do
Is what he's doing in the
Which is combining those two ideas
It would seem to be an appeal for people to force the government
Kill them
In order to accelerate the standoff he wants with his imaginary enemies
Annette's
I don't even have the word
It's horrifying
Yeah I mean
There's no there's not even like a
Zales
Politically
Or anything like that
Hey they're coming to murder you
You have the choice to sit there for 10 years and then die or you can fight
And Dino
So the only thing that you would think
If you were Lynn his audiences it's time to f******
Kill people
And two options are you can wait around and be killed in the orderly fashion in 10 years
Or you can do something to force
The globalist and out
How to do it now but we're all going to be dead no matter what it's almost like you don't you want to take them down with you
Exactly know like the billionaires are trying to escape
Can kill us all and then they'll be fighting what if
Hey at least we're going to take out 10 of them and you know who gets hurt by that
You and me not knowing me literally but everyone
Yep
Just people get hurt by that.
The real one
Yeah these like attacks on the Federal Building
And like the Oklahoma City bombing
Destroy the community
The community
People
It's not it
I'm not saying that that's what
What's going to happen but this kind of rhetoric leave them at Direction
I don't
I don't see how this
Kind of talk
Can possibly be directed towards
Awareness campaign
Let's get a little past I mean the reality the reality is after the 6
And nobody who was
At fault
For it
I took any
Punishment or
I mean
It doesn't even seem like people are
Anymore
Why wouldn't you keep doing this
I thought you didn't work last time but nobody's going to stop you from doing again I saw some pictures of the six
Again I seen some in a while I thought likewise
Holyshit
Even I have like
Do you settled into a place of like that happen
And some of the images that I had yeah I don't want to move
Godlike
Rihanna plastered over you no like
It didn't nothing happened
There's tons of people in Congress still
Can you imagine going to work everyday and like knowing
Through any kind of intelligence report that you have access
That guy
Across the f****** Hall from you
What's ready to murder you
Picture of how do you go to work like that
I will be tough
So Alex has it easy going to work cuz he just
Whatever the f*** you want
Doesn't matter and nobody's going to hold
We're going to be to Meijer
Dallas downtown
But I'm just telling you
I'm probably obviously not going to be there that's okay
Michael forcing instrumental
Pull punches
Cuz you know what's going to happen I'm not stupid you're not either
You know is all this happens
I'm going to go for
Allow me to be walking around very soon
But that's okay
Because I've lived a life of resistance and I can stand before God
I want to know you I do
I want to be
Alex is essentially like predicting his own like
Holy martyrdom
I am this is just
F****** mess
I will go from being trustworthy to being your secretary
Messiah all that I say will be
Be true
All that I say will be at
Accepted by the universe
As reality it's
I thought this was about the Federal Reserve man Federal Reserve
Like there's a grandiosity
On today's episode that we haven't seen quite theirs
This is intense very terrifying
And you know
He's Enemy Number One
If Infowars goes down that's
The canary in the coal mine where you really talk for a Merica
He's literally the f****** truth-telling Messiah now like this is delusion the Messiah but like a
John the
Just type it legal
Everything
I told you everything that's happened up until now here's before
Volume settings
Next time
Understand to tell you once this goes through
Your wife
Your children
Your dad
Explain how they've already done it
Which is why I did
Not going to let us organize against that
Figure out they're all dead
Almost
Almost every school teacher
They're coming to kill you
.
Human Slaughter
Warehouse
UK
Yeah this show man
That is a jackster
Deposition
Is Tim holiday listening I need a new phone
Understands the worship of capitalism but do they not see
How
F****** pirata kitties
To go from
You're all dead
All of you
Specifically
You're all dead if you need a new track
You're coming home I got week forklift
We can't do this
The real messaging of it is something that is so dangerous that
I can't I can't be dealt with as just like hahaha
In a fake reality looking a movie that kind of
Side-by-side is hilarious
Incredible
It's like
Cult leaders
Have to sell their Cults their own s*** you know they have to have their own books they have to have their own s*** their own
Forklift cult leader Latta goddamn Nike
What is a f****** Libras soccer player like he's got
No I mean it's not
It's not Stu Alex wants
He wants to get into
The intricacies of the plan right
Probably not
Master plan
The intricacies of this
So you understand that I'm not blowing smoke at you and I know you know that
I mean
I don't want to say these things
Hurt me really bad to say these things
I don't like myself
Something to you
Billions will die
Moves that one second closer on the clock
Ashley flowers
I don't enjoy
Messing with
But let me Translate
Putting out a headline that says a transparently desperate attempt
Nasionalisme cards left
Play
If his insistence that you do what he says now or billions will die doesn't move the needle how much louder can he possibly screw
The sky is falling
If I were him
I really wouldn't be too concerned about it
If there's one thing that the Infowars audience is good at it's being distracted by shiny new things to be afraid of
And I don't think it'll be that big of a
Did the swing that we're in right now is a pretty protracted
Pretty severe pretty long one
Terms of his career
Walking of this bag
Might be hard
If it brings them one second
Into taking him down
Every time he says that
He's got a lot of sex
He is got an insane amount of seconds over the past 27 years
I have not heard him
Not say that
They're ten years late to squash it
Jordan
I regret that it's gone
Come to this
But
Unfortunately
It's time to discuss the rainbow.
Dildo butt
You do yesterday
Rainbow
Dildo butt monkey
Athan
With a fake
Butt naked with a fake vagina
Turkey gobbler
Fake woman's breast I wouldn't even show it on
Little kids came up
TV station
I regret to inform you that the time has come
To discuss
Rainbow dildo butt monkey
Don't want to live on
This planet
No rainbow
Dildo
But
Yeah I mean I was listening to this episode and I hear him saying some of the more dangerous extreme things that I've ever heard
Ferdinand a couple minutes later he's talking about a rainbow monkey
It really boccio business donkey wrestler it exact
Andre translate Coronavirus
What happened at goodmayes library in London
Which did appear to include what
You might unfortunately call a rainbow
Dildo
I am not an adult this is part found adults was part of a carnival act by it put on by a group
Called my dick goddard's
Monkey
Keep business where they some of the members dress up as brightly colored monkeys
Stikbots and
I regret to inform you faked
This appears to be a situation where this our group heading
Activated they got booked for a gig that maybe they should not have been booked for
The library's events are booked by a local charity called Vision RC L and it appears that's where the real break
Breakdown happened
They booked what could be argued as a reputable Arts group to do a performance for an event
And they showed up with some pretty f*****-up costumes
Is considered the audience
Everyone is up in arms about this and there is internal investigations open it
The how it ended up happening but suffice it to say that I
Completely fabricated version of the story
The outrage the audio
There's no indication that I can tell from any of the articles that I've read about this incident
Do the monkeys have contact with children
Let alone with Alex's describing
This is just as grotesque imagination
I'm trying to push the listener
Buttons we can override their rational Minds
And get them into a purely reactive state
Yeah that's a real bummer for them that really thought I mean I've been booked for I've been booked for a show before by somebody was like
Man you're really funny weary like if this is going to go great you're going to be great for the show and you get there
And then they're like Okay so
It's a church youth group
And you have to work clean and you got to do six and a half hour
Yeah I do like
No
No just no
There was one time that I don't know where it was but is always out of town is at least an hour away me and Nick Kroll
Comedian Nick Rowley got to book
4 gig neither of us very clean
Get me at all you're doing half an hour or you're doing 15
45 carbine
No no
So we were panicked
Family
What do we do until we I made a bet that I could talk about
The chicken finger
There were on the menu for the first 5 minutes
Peanut that's what, to have to do in those situations
All of every, cuz had that story where they're at a show and they're like well
We got to find a way to make this fun for us that's what's going to happen here cuz it's not going to be fun for that I was like Nick give me a light at 5
So I talked about everything I could think of about that
Chicken fingers
I was like I don't know
Start telling jokes I guess I can't do 50
And so like my first joke
It started with asking the audience
If they have jobs
Yeah and so like
I got job
Play what I eat those chicken fingers like it's about a job and then I Saw the Light
Nailed it
Clutch
Like identical Oppo
Blocking a alley-oop is right there at the buzzers
Kind of thing on a show you should not be booked
Another time
When I first moved to the city
I was trying to find
Gigs on like Craigslist
Oh yeah yeah back Squad anything any kind of stage time I sound
Who did a show that was at like an art gallery
And so I went and I did the show.
It's kind of funny another is
McNeil not too many people there but he was in
A little art
Installation
Bambino no microphones do nothing
Is a good time
This person booked me for another
Thing
And I showed up to it
And like
It was all kid
It was like no it was like at a kids art fair
There's literally no way I'm going up on stage didn't agree
Any jokes there's just no way
I think it might be a crime
It might be a time so I had to work out like some
Some sort of a bit where I would panic and run off stage
These kids don't know what's funny how they got.
I feel like
Maybe there should have been
And some kind of an audible
Foucault in terms of
Rainbow dildo butt monkey
But unfortunately
That's what that so many. Like that
The booker like it has so many times that you know I've done a college show before where the booker is like so
Some nineteen-year-old kid they're like
We're so excited we got like
This is so cool and then you get into like I've nowhere
Can cafeteria without a micro anything in there like
Okay hear all the things that the school says you're not allowed to talk about any like you could have
Set me an
Email and I would have said
No organized and there's often times miscommunication
What happened
Between parties and easily see this being something along those lines
I don't know I do agree on the most basic level the discussion was
I don't think it has anything to do with the
The devil
Think nope nope
But this but
He also tells
A story
And this story I actually found really fast
It's real folks
It's one thing
To be knowing it's coming
Slow motion
I thought Corvette driving on a 25 miles an hour
Race on Highway
Wait what
Explode
People's head
Got caught off one person Farm Parkway
Botana pulled over the truck
Second chapter
I'm watching
The Bible trying to get up
The body was flat so personal
We were in a truck
Nobody saying I'm not speeding 120
By the time that take blue out and then
Fine and all that happened
By the time that happened we pulled up it was just instantaneous and I get out of the car
Flipped over onto the railroad trestle
Right there
Can I watch that
Slow motion that Corvette spinning
Watching those bodies fly
Slow motion I really just killed twenty million people
This seems like the kind of story that would make it
The news
You know
See if I can find any instances of drag race related deaths of Youth
In Corvette
Trim around the ears when Alex
Would have been the right age
But he's describing
I was born in 1974 so I looked at cases like
Flying from
Between 1988 and 1990
The first case that came up was an 18 year old named Chris Taylor who live in the suburb of Dallas so right near Rockwall
In the area
In died in a drag racing accident while driving the Corvette in what's the
Described as a quote fiery crash
This was on the night of Christmas 1989
Certainly in the wheel ballpark
If this is who Alex's talking about the nice one with a wild since Chris's mother is currently in prison for hiring
The guy that killed woman who was sleeping with her estranged husband
It's a it's a pretty
Big murder case
Alright alright
This is actually the only case that I could find it fit the details that Alex
Describing
Actually proved that it
It's the one he is talking
Whatever the case is
He's either making this story up or
Describing a life experience that would leave such deep scars in a person that they would
Tons of therapy
10 years of work to process what they've been
Been through
Seeing anyone die as a team is an immense
Trauma but seeing a friend die in a grisly fashion like what Alex describe
I will be so hard to deal with
Even with appropriate helping
Kerr Lake
The imprint of that would be
Almost unfathomable
Not too
You know like
Of course there's the bias I have because we
We're dealing with Al
But if anybody told me that story The Way Alex told me that story
That sounds like you stole somebody else
That's not
Yours I'm not saying that that's there was
True there was a flatness to the way he's delivering it doesn't feel emotionally resonant
It's somebody else's story it's one of those situations where you
You've seen that before where somebody I don't know if you've
Bentonite experience
Get caught with it but you've been in that
Situation where you been
Wow that's a really good story and then later on somebody's like you know that's not
That's not his story
It's possible that would explain it or just a complete detachment
From emotions that he was
Experience time
Completely made up I'm not entirely sure but
Like
My pictures now that's just
That's why
Yeah
Brutal
Alex gets into a weird head
Really just killed twenty million
All the Facebook workers all the Twitter workers
All the YouTube workers
All of you
That that block
Hydroxychloroquine
Can you help murder the 20-something millionaires starve to death
On top of all the other dead people
You did that
You don't even care
Modern Warfare
Turn the economy off and all you got to do work at Big Tex about it
Call me a racist what the hell does that even mean
And
Time off
I almost feel like my mission is complete
I really do feel like
We're here now
And if people don't do anything about it
Don't want to keep working I don't want
Why do I have to go find
The Politico article
Why
Cuz it's your f****** job
Why do I have to go do this what do I have
Have to provide information in the information
Wow
That's a guy does not give a f***
That's a meltdown on stage right there that's
Spencer me standing out there just being like
Why do I have to tell you people jokes you guys can tell each other jokes
I've had moments
Dark moments where I thought
This is so stupid that I'm chasing down this thread that Alex is talking about why do I have to read this thing or whatever
Never once have I been like
Why does it fall to me through the thing I've decided to do
Frustrating sometimes but
He's not just your job either it's your entire creation
18 Euro Pizza uniform vision
Created by one man
Who is now bitching about why he has
To do it
Whatever I do think there's something to be said for like the idea that his mission is done and when I hear that I think like
This is kind of him just recognizing that there's nowhere else he can take inside
He's I mean he's yeah he's already saying that it's millions are going to down to reach
The point where it's like people aren't shooting now I can't do anything else
Without getting myself in
Actually
Legal prison trouble
Not civil
Who's the movie Criminal
I helped kick the 6th off
Nobody got into any trouble
So I'm going to try and kick off the next one and if it doesn't happen
It doesn't happen more articles and political exactly exactly
Play I want the second one to happen I'm going to try and make it happen and if it doesn't then that's my mission
Yeah
Call center
And everybody's text messages I told you that
Running at all spying on you
Nelson Rockefeller
Let you send messages
Inderal
Ugly weird
What days are people that came up with
Rainbow dildo
Monkey man
Say it again
Funded by the UK government
Your creature dressed like a
Are the clowns dressed like that
Bring their children to the money
What
Ryan's Buffet
Demons released
Norway weather
Confident
Acquiesce
We open the gates of hell
We're all going to die
Holyshit
I don't
Verizon
I got is the same speech from Event Horizon rainbow dildo but monkey wants
What's the tear you limb from limb
I think
It's a carnival Act was poorly book
I don't understand
The level of
Douchebag
And why me like
Oversensitive lunatic you have to be to not immediately laugh
At Rainbow
Fildo
Butt monkey
Would be like listen
I'm sorry
Me and Luke Skywalker can agree on that. I'm not talking about the Star Wars character I'm talking about Uncle Luke
Fuckingawesome if I do from 2 Live Crew tried to call himself Luke Skywalker
Swig of a sabre with that one but
Luke Skywalker
Awesome
Yeah also I was waiting for Alex to drink
Completos with drag queen story time
It took him this long
This event had nothing
To do with even that at all it's
Sissies
He's just trying to get
Getting weary camp
Anybody dress differently around kids is annex
Excuse for me to call somebody a pedophile
File
At 1
See now that's a Nicolas Cage
Right there
Yes sir
Star Wars
Luke Skywalker
Scientific
What's your favorite science which
TV show
My favorite science fiction TV show that's a good question
You know you could you could say something classic like
Firefly you can do one of those
You know but I don't think I'm going to do that
You could go with one of the early you know one of the newer stuff like Mandalorian mandalorians great Mandalorian
Just because Luke Skywalker does show up spoiler
I have not yet watch the Mandalorian too much Survivor
Eventually
The survival or buying
He's probably The X-Files
I have a lot of fond memories of watching that with my parents
Ma
The dude's very long video essay on YouTube
Try to convince me that the Act was bad sour-faced
I've made peace with it but yeah I was convinced
This Is the End
Gloss for what it was
Watch The X-Files
Was growing up at
Star Trek the Next Generation
Terrified of The X-Files
It seems like
It could happen
Like a lot of the stuff could happen and people are getting
Hurt by things smoking cigarettes
Could show up deaf underground all the time I always took solace in like
It almost never happens
To a kid
I'm a kid
True like
SafeLink
Set up a little bit
Anyway
Maxwell's was created by Chris Carter
Alex and
Chris Carter
Isn't Western
And Chris Carter said some nice things about us we talked to Christopher
And the Chris admitted the CIA came to him and told him what to say
Episode
Wasn't sure why he was asking me why
But it's inside predictive programming
Injection with Spike protein
What is the destroy people's immune systems
And slowly kill them with a soft kill weapon
TI-84
November 11th
Why did they do it
For now
This is just Alex wrinkling the same day I'm seeing it there
I've seen it in my mind's eye
Why was the CIA want that out then
27 years later
Because there's
Accrual
They got a post
In the newspaper
Turn on TV
Right on the wall
What about before writing
What's going to be done so you got a chance to change your future
You got a free here longer than a local law
Run an ad every month
Guide
So save it like if this was something it was you no revealed and X-Files episode in 1994 you
You guys drop the ball on warning I did a really bad job
Seems like
Plot from an X-Files episode of there were hundreds
I bet you could have even gone to the Twilight Zone for a plot very similar to that
Chris Carter didn't say things out with the same
This didn't even have to do with the X-Files it's it was a claim that is made by Dean haglund one of these stars of The X-Files
Turn off the lone gunmen
Pilot episode of that show involve elements that were somewhat similar to the events of 9/11 but
And haggling to use this to make a bit of a foray into the 9/11 conspiracy world are heavily implying that the
The powers that be injected
Blocks into their show
None of this necessarily prove anything
Also with the globalist really felt like I needed to make a pub
Good post of their plan
Why do they choose to do it in the spin-off show
More people see it if they did it on the X-Files like
If it satisfies The Intergalactic law to put some predictive programming on
Pilots of spin-off shows that
This dude is an episode of some dogshit showed no one watches on the depth
Deep cable is there a ratings
Limit
In this Galactic rule
I mean this is something I would like to actually discuss because like
You know this thing in The Hitchhiker's Guide is like
They have the the post of
The destruction of Earth
Yeah they could somewhere we would never see it to go into the office building you have to go down three
Flights of stairs and it was play with last week
It was posted yeah you could have gone there at any time it's your own fault right so like why couldn't
They reveal that 9/11 was going to happen until like
What Aunt like
What's up telenovela that no one watches in
In Spanish
I don't know it's
It seems bizarre
Also after learning as much as I can about this Haiti situation
I think the CIA
Is 100% used
Because it appears that some random doctor in Florida can just hire a hit
A-Team and then successfully murder a president
Wow CIA is useless
Huh
I need to dig into that story a little bit more
Alex on this episode about it
There are some similarities between the plot of that episode of The Lone gunmen
And the events of 9/11 are also major differences that are just ignored but Alex
Into the show the attack is a single airplane and its remote
Controlled
Lone gunmen a game
In control of the remote control plane and save the day which they do would shouldn't happen to the real world
Also there's a whole subplot about a powerful computer chip and whether or not the lone gunmen Zena's any good
Hey I like the younger I thought they were pretty cool
Back when I was
Watching The X-Files
Deliver those
The side characters level
I just never ate missed me by I think cuz my parents were so like
Now we can't be having this time 3 conspiracy theorist
Sewer friends with Mulder like publish a zine
And secretly in on a whole bunch of comic relief
Put the elements of the show that are similar to the events that happened in the real world later actually not too surprising if you think about it
There's been a previous attack on the World Trade Center so that wasn't completely unheard of
The idea of staging such an attack in order to boost weapons sales that's a well-conceived plot which makes sense
Considering the Chris Carter and the future creator of Breaking Bad Vince
Gilligan wrote the episode
Also I need to get out in front of this
Just in case there's any kind of f****** s***
Fourth episode of the lone gunman was written by someone named Colin freezing and as far as I know I don't have any relatives named Colin
It is spelled the same I don't know Collin Friesen
Okay
The episode of The X-Files Metallica
Who's pretending was about the covid vaccine is titled one breath
Episode number 8
Season 2
Essentially scully's hospitalized in Boulder and list the lone gunmen to help him figure out what's up
They get her medical charts and find there's a protein chains
That appear to have been part of an experimental tracking system but they're inactive
So they've become toxic
Inside her
He doesn't die in
It's not a soft kill weapon
I was just cherry-picking
Details from pop culture shows the impression that he wants
But it's all bulshit
Also
He's creating a very inaccurate perception that the lone gunmen were basically the stars of the Xbox
That's not good
Scary characters that many episodes
Sure
Sting at they got guest starring credit
That's in the Yeah Yeah Yeahs
And at the end
He like I remember his name I don't remember the other two guys who are the lone gunmen
I think I like the other guys better probably
Yeah seen haglund is a very memorable name
He was the one who had like
Long blonde hair
But they all had kind of a distinctive look one clean-cut one soda from P1 long
Long-haired
Pennywise
But I don't know
I don't think the X-Files predicted that I covid vaccines
I'm so bummed out I'm so impulsive
Spike protein
Yeah yeah
Of course not
I like I was very disappointed by this
This Theory
Bums me out so hard
All of that kind of predictive programming south or or somebody being like
The CIA came to me and told me what was going to happen with the World Trade Center and then
After a
Decade of just believing s*** that people told me about it I read up on it
No he attacked
Before he said why
Simple
Conspiracies
There's not the CIA involved
This was the whole point how did I how did I not know the very obvious
It's in.
The other the other ideas of kotoko Truth are far more interest
You can start
You know I think I think one of the most pressing questions in the world right now you might think it's like climate change
Oh yeah no I mean the rainforest is emitting more CO2 than it's absorbing so
Real real problem
It's a bummer is a real bummer shoes that we have
Like to deal with but I think of one of the more
Pressing issues even than that
Is whether or not we're in a simulation
And thankfully
I think Alex has an answer
Jacquees
You're held in some alien simulation is Vault
Actually listen right now
Alien simulation
The simulation on the guy that knew about it on the guy that warned about it
Joe Rogan podcast
Talk to him all the time
TV host Tucker Carlson and we're Buddies
Developing a plan to fight the New World Order
I'm like okay
Is this a simulation
Cuz that would be a lot better
Got killer bug in Africa
Henry Kissinger is not real
Prince Philip's not real
Simulation
My mother's not real
Not real
Life's not real
You're getting it
My crew is it real
John over there running the Boom is not real
John Deere real aren't you John
John thinks he's real
Stupid assholes
Imagine being Alex Jones
Live in a simulation
How about some people say off
The third Dimensions real
Made this as a genetic
Real world real life
Simulation
So then we are in a simulation but it's a god simulation
Cool
Coco cool
How do you answering that question about whether or not
Existence is real
It's not but
It's not aliens
God or some
Yeah I mean I think the the more important
Though is that
Regardless of whether a real
How real or not it is
Is it doesn't really matter you're just
Going to keep going about
Your day
So
I am outside of the possibility of having telekinesis if you can break through the simulation or something
And if I can ever find any evidence that anyone has ever done that or that's possible I'll get very excited to hear that
Super
Let's assume that we are in a simulation
The worst case scenario of
Acting as if
It's not a simulation that we are in the real world where there are consequences and everyone
Existence
We have responsibilities towards each other so is at the end of it you're like
Boy I was foolish for thinking that
That's not that bad
You know the thought occurs to me and I haven't I haven't really answered the opposite of Pascal's wager
It is going to lose
Eeyore Winnie their way
Pascal's
It it's it did occur to me when you just pointed that out that if you see through the simulation you might get telekinetic powers or whatever like going
Director The Matrix
Even if you weren't Mio you could still do giant ass jumped
Some s*** you know you could
Could you still had special powers never occurred to me that I would rather
F*** the stake-bed Johnny talking about
Johnny Leguizamo Johnny legs
Lower body
It's like the steak and all that sound I'm going to stay in The Matrix
Because I can jump
Across roof building
Lakeside School
Can't jump across roof building
Unless you've
Been taken out of The Matrix
Right
Oh that's a good question
Yeah
Betrayal
But still want to take me home
Alex at this point spends would have time taking calls
And I want to address something really fast because I do believe that somebody called into the show was maybe a listener varsho
And
No no y no harm no foul no I'm not mad at anybody but I would like to take this opportunity to read
Reiterate
That we discourage people from calling into Alex's showed messing with him
I am the primary reason for that is that I don't believe that it is ethical
Or us
To do this show where we go over his content
If there is
A possibility that we are directly affect
Think is content
And I think that somebody calling and it was one of our listeners
And bringing up things from our show
Or something
To him is too much of
Incursion
Into his contact
Becomes a situation where I can't really know what is what
I believe we were talking before the show
And I was like wecantstudy him in his natural habitat
If we are at the
Affecting the natural habitat
Interacting with it and I try to
Keep that as a
Asbestos
As possible
Now we did do and we agreed to be in the New York Times Story show what are the reasons that I felt that was kind of
Okay was that
We were
It's not
Totally
Affecting the content just the awareness that we agree
And we already knew they were aware of our existence
Sure
The Following on Twitter
And what have you
But the direct interference I just I find it
Attributes makes me kind of uncomfortable
I can't make anyone
Bay Haven
A certain way like literally I can't say
Don't call in and expect anyone to care
But this is a curd
To see if you if you
About what my position is I would appreciate it
If people didn't call it is much
Phone is it might be
I don't think
Kind of
Serves
It works across my purpose
Yeah I mean
To go to to go to Survivor
You know eventually whenever the metagame becomes more important or as important as the game
Then it's just a day
It's a different thing and it's
Eventually
You know and 4
We're doing a show about him not a show about
Him talking about us
Talking about him talking about
You know we didn't go over the episode where Harrison
I was talking about
It's not that's not something I have that much interest
And for the Survivor metaphor
Alright Propst
Can like stir up drama
At Tribal Council
But if he were like on the beach
Vietnam
And then at Tribal Council was like
So there's some conflict today
Onyx
So I am no disrespect to the person who I believe was
A listener varsho called
Actually I think they're called
Fine but I'm not going to play any other on the show
I do not want to incentivize that behavior exactly now that's your another call
It feels like we're no longer
Peaceful Revolution
Vaccines virus maybe it's just cuz he's telling you you're in a violent War
Open borders with demoralisation
America Center
Does it mean people are
Revolution already
Yes I mean like I think that this caller has accurately assess the
The tone that Alex is bringing to the show at this point
He said everybody could have died 15 times on this show many times
Feel like there's a violent revolution
I want to look to your side and see Rainbow dildo
Adele
You need a little levity if you're in if you're in a foxhole you know sure
So what last clip of a call that Alex Gibson
Troubling to me
Hey how you doing Alex
Are The Apocalypse of Abraham chapter 29
Donald Trump makes
Very good appearance and they're just say
Could being not all I'm doing is asking questions
Physical into exist
Quantum realm that means that everything
Saying every law that apply
Eyes in the physical are world
I mean that you look at Isaac Newton where every action has an equal and opposite
Reaction the same would have
Alright
We're at right now
1988 because if you look at revelation
3.5 years rights
Revelation
35 and there was given unto him a mouse speaking rate
Things in Black
Even power was given unto him to continue forty and two months that would be three point
Years Jesus was ministering for 3-point
5 years
You go to Revelation 20 Satan is bound and I saw than Angel come down and having the key
He laid hold of the Dragon
Thousand Years Jesus Christ
21 years old
Going to be the beginning
Who are the globalist
In 2029 that they say that
That's official
Yeah I would
I would have a difficult time being a radio host hearing this stuff and be like
That makes sense
At the struggle
You know somebody somebody put out a question to a bunch of people I think is on like Gizmodo or something like
What's the most
Hamilton conspiracy theory
And
Like
Everybody had some fairly good responses you know like five of the normal ones but when you really
Get down to it man
John of Patmos hold out the worst conspiracy theory in the history of the world and it's
It's killing all
If you think if you think about it in terms of like longevity
There may be some truth
Yeah I don't know whatever conspiracy is like
Makes it so easy to accept all the rest of
Exact that's the one that yells dangerous as the lowest bar
Bulshit
First one is any con man with a smile
That's the worst
This episode sucks
I would say I think of it's a Alex's town is a
Extreme
What would make you say that then I don't I don't like the development of the
Idea that you have to escalate the globalist
The Killing you or else
They will just kill you later
Yeah that to me is something I'm going to keep an eye on
Cuz it worries
No he when he was talking to the
The f****** Boogaloo boys he was trying to push back on less incendiary s*** than that I wonder I wonder
Alex even understands the implications
Listen to the things you saying
They sincerely Wonder
It just seems like he's having a mad day
Having a bad one
LaGrange
But until then Jordan River website.com
A local charity or bail Fund in your area to help out
People doing God's work
Omniome Lido MDX
The sex robot
Holding
Alexandra first in color with huge fan I love your work