Damn important I sweat it
I have great respect for Tenaya Lodge B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
MoneyGram
Knowledge vype.com
The Beverages and talk a little talk about Selena
So I thought I saw it was all my fault I was there in the beginning
I love a two-button
Don't do it again don't find that magic one more time that's always go back to that well
Did I have a quick question
What's your bright spot
Today by breakbot today is an email that I got from the WWE
Ask gifts not the wrestling guy the worldwide life
Maybe Sue's shoes
Susie in order of the
The altar of Celine
And inspired by the elephant that was adopted
Celine's child elephant has gotten
I'm liking this now we do
How inexplicably adopted
Delete a message I feel like the elephant needed a sibling
It's pronounced kwakho by the way
Thank you so much that's so sweet I really really appreciate it
Absolutely I think that's
Just exciting and really cool yeah it's really cool that's your bright spot
Has a new album out there
Tacular really really good
He's on a streak of like
Four straight albums that have been spectacular like you can go back to big
Big Fish Theory and that's still
Second grade
It's it's really really good
Nice really good let's check it out cuz this is the second time someone has recommended
You know that's kind of like alright fine I apparently need to be conversant in this
And a plus-one it you can't just have meat
Yeah I got you
So Jordan today we have an episode to go over and I'm going to give a little bit of a warning up top I guess
I already told you this because you need to emotionally prepare
Episode that is about a video that Nick Fuentes posted on his website banned. Video
I totally understand that there are some people who hate
The sound of his voice and can't handle it
And I fully respect
If you are that sort of prisoner I promise
We're not going to become an acquaintance
But
If you would like
To skip this at we will be doing an episode on Wednesday
Think hear that merited talking about
And so I wanted to to play this
And to have a conversation about it
I am apologizing
Hey if you don't want to listen to Nick Fuentes voice
You Are Not Alone we are doing this professional
Before we get to that bit of us
Pretty unpleasant business
Looks like a little moment to some
So first
Jordan's life is wholesome and I have a lazy eye too but I'm a hot chick thank you so much you are not follow through on
Thank you very much I appreciate that
What's good next 14 calling never will thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk from Virginia
I'm a policy wonk
Terry from Virginia and Nathan rhymes with Satan and also have
Big what's up too big and Eugene
Thank you very much to all of that but
And finally this this one was
I wasn't sure
Is another person who thought I couldn't pronounce their name
Spell out the first name
Vayla
Okay bela-bela Viola I could go I could help you
Well if it's Bela and she says you can't pronounce
Their name
Then
Viola
You're now policy want
I'm a policy wonk
Okay
Souderton today this episode I was a little bit on inspired by some of the
Stuff is going on Iran Alex's world that so
Poking around the website and posted a new video
This video is
Nick Fuentes on why we must preserve America's majority-white demographics
Well
Is
Extreme
That title
Is racist
So if your titles racist I imagine the thesis is far worse
It's a shocking blunt
Racist clickbait I found this to be bizarre
I think that
One of the things that I find the most interesting when I look at Infowars stuff and one of the things that keeps me
Engage is when things change
I've always been kind of interested in how things can change
Because on some level they shouldn't
Is yours shouldn't change
Decades-long conspiracy
That Alex understands fully change that much
From Trump is a con man is mobbed up and all this prove he's the greatest person in the world is going to save the country
That's interesting to me
That that sort of shift always is something that that sticks out
And I kind of feel like
We might be
Kind of in the middle of
A chain of the Tabernacle
Text Big I'm a little bit worried because of
A title for a video by
Like that
I mean cuz there's just no way to interpreted that anything other than
White people should be in charge cuz they're better
They're better in charge then other non-whites
That might be part of what his argument that you can make which is already silly and race
So
We
We're going to go over this 10-minute video that Nick post
It's a clip out of his speech
But he gave it his
Political Acts
Can committee conference or whatever
And I believe the title of it or at least something that's on the the the logo is America on canceled
Part of the reason is because
You know that sort of the theme of CPAP
Throwing it in their face that he's not allowed at Sea-Tac cancelled everywhere
I think that that framing is also going to be
Bit of an issue for Alex
But
Football here we go all right let's go to the white nationalist happy hour and everybody
Getting ready to sit down
Say that I'm a wife now
That's Ryan
We have another
Were there that's right yeah
Run
Econo's out-of-work erases room a little bit
Yeah I know where you're sitting there was a little bit of
Moment
One of the things that I want to make clear is that like
I could have probably found this entire speech and we could have gone over issue but I don't think that that's really
Why I'm talking
About that okay
I'm talking about this because it's on Alex's site
Right we strictly Infowars
Podcast you do like we've talked about project Baker
There's other things
Nick Fuentes in and of himself is not somebody that I necessarily want
Stood fully
Devote
Too much time to
However
He has entered Alex's fear in a way
Becomes very relevant
To what we're talking about far more horrible things throughout this entire speech
But this is what is posted
And tacitly approved
By Alex Jones Infowars
Right it provides a context for Alex that cannot also you know like Alex Cano cannot go
Go anywhere cannot go on Joe Rogan to be like
I don't know why they call me white nationalists this is why
This is on your side incontrovertible you are a white National
It's maybe not because Nick has an interesting definition about
The reason they call me a white Nash
I am aghast
Transformation
America's
I want a white Nation
White
White people in America
Which is
Never said anything
Multiracial country
Unstoppable
We is a nation
Figure out how to navigate
Living in a very big
Diverse
I wish it wasn't that way
That's the way that it is
So the first important to note here is that Nick is very clearly saying that he wishes the United States wasn't a diverse country
He doesn't advocate for a whites-only country because it's an impractical goal
It's Logistics issue not an ideological want listen you can't shoot for the stars every time man
If it weren't an impractical things pursue it stands to reason the base
Lakewood wanna eliminate that diversity that he doesn't seem to enjoy in our society
The other important thing to note here is that Nick is creating a false definition of white nationalism in order to pretend that the label doesn't fit him
What does it mean to advocate for a country with no non-white people in it to advocate
For white nationalism
Some among the crowd probably do wish to see a whites-only country but the definition of white nationalism is a bit broader than that
What are the trademark beliefs that defines a person's belief as being white nationalist is the belief that white people need to retain
An absolute grip on power in this country
Particularly by retaining a firm majority in terms of population
Mix created a false version of the definition in order to avoid the baggage that's associated with it but then that everyone's calling him names
But don't apply but this is really just an elementary rhetorical trick
It's nonsense
Well I mean the thing that is undercutting everything he saying is the idea that we need to stop
These Trends and then saying they are
Virtually Unstoppable
Which okay so if the birth rate and such are virtually Unstoppable how do you expect
To change the trend
And it would obviously be getting rid of people try deportation or whatever
Obviously violence for them is on the table but apparently has something to add
K40 because like what if
You know people
Don't want
To leave well I mean this is a majority-white country I don't understand
And I hate these
People gets into a little bit of a history lesson that is
Not fully
We as a nation
You're going to have to figure out how
Very big and died
I wish it wasn't that way
That's the way that it is
Singer Janis Ian
Like that
They call me back because I'm opposed
The
If you don't know
America's
Minority
Probably with
Less than 50
Percent
Population
Pretty incredible
Not incredible
What
Master
The transformation
Such a short.
It was just recently
When the demographics
90%
And 10%.
And that's how was
The beginning
Country
Colonies
It's been roughly like that since
The 17th
The order of
Population is being replaced
Wow
In fairness the US population was 205 million in 1970 as opposed to / 320 million now
Little bit different
Also
Based on US Census Data
It feels like it's a
Exaggerating a little bit
You know if you go back to 1972 census shows that the country was 87 point
5% White
2010 that's 72.4 /
Additionally
I don't think it's super helpful to go back to some of that like old census data
From like let's say I don't know prior to 1954 The Colony days
You know the terminology
Classification that was used to describe races very different back then
If you go back to route
Some of the ways people are catalogued are slurs
It's outrageous the weird
Open Mixer be a little more careful because if you go back to far you might find numbers that constitute a problem
For the argument
For example if you look at the 1790 census
Sleeves made up
43% of the population of South Carolina and almost 40% of the population of Virginia
I don't know what he's I don't know what he's talking
I mean I mean I do but
I suppose be very simple argument against that of course is
You know the country
That we that land was here before even the 17th century
Boy that's a second quite a drastic demographic shift
Since that demographic I understand completely
So
Yeah maybe you should shut the f***
Yeah probably
He's concerned about this changing of population beak
Cuz
The United States really only is the way it is for a particular reason
This isn't good
Malaysian is being replaced
Prince Andrew
Children
People hear that
Like that
The problem
The problem is this
The problem is
The problem is that
Just like men and wear
People
Are not interchangeable
Country is right now
Lived here
This country as we know it early says
What's an expression of
European
People
Civilization
And wasn't
Way because of
European people
It was a certain way because of how European people
The ability to understand American history
Lost just like
Yellow like
No
But just no zero no just zero. Do you know why you can get from one side of the country to the other
Chinese people that's part of the game like
Is everywhere everybody is everywhere the point of the country is that everybody from everywhere
And that that is a big part of the contributions that have been made by people who
Have roots
Stay in other parts of the world have made America what it is there's so much of the frappe the fabric of what we
What we consider important and culturally relevant
That is not from
Hahaha
I don't know even
What
Strict definition
Naked try to use I mean go back to the go back to the f****** colonies you do think that they thought that I
Worst people in Italian people acted the same European way of
Probably probably not I think that is a difficulty for this Ark
The relative definition overtime
Yeah
Did United States exist
Yeah I just
I don't I don't like this
Because
You know the saying the people aren't interchangeable because based on
Your roots where you come from you act different
Your culture is not the same
Great
Sure
You know what I really do hate that I can get Ethiopian food if I want it it's awful that I
I don't have to fly to Ethiopia
That's the problem which
I don't I don't I don't know what he
No Depot are great
Okay there
Another animals
Lance
The more complicated
Technology
Subtle
Subtle but significant
You might think that somebody
Buy Nike shoes
Assimilated
Not the case
We find it
Superman
Create
The same conditions in a
Fans created
No
They don't
This is a matter of fact
I don't even know what he's expecting of
Immigrant
Okay that's okay
So
Don't know how you gauge that when immigrants came here
They start their own country and take the land from other people
Then they didn't create the same conditions that the Europeans created here
Everybody knows that wow okay well I don't think
Like that's the only one that makes sense from the word teeth
Yeah he seems to just have a problem with
I guess the idea of
Neighborhood
I guess he just doesn't like the idea that there are non-white neighborhood
Yeah I mean
This is so transparently b******* just like that
This is
Clearly
Whatever is whatever the word is whatever it is immigrants or whatever
It experienced words
Incitement like that's all that matters to him if it was if we were in
Different times he be like at the Irish if you were in different times he be like
We we got to hate to love the Mongols like it doesn't matter all it is is a tool
To get people
Do act for him
What's power out of this and I'm terrified
Map
So I wanted to be terrified of is that the he's from the same city as us
Chicago
And they create the
Same conditions and
Created before
No
They don't
And this is a matter of
If you look at all these
Different communities
I live in Chicago
Chicago is a third wife
When you drive
Gas
Redlining
I don't want to live in Mexico
And when I drive through the Southside
It would look like
Somalia
You should go there maybe you should check out the Southside you dumbass
Dial at that time White Sox stadium is
Basically the middle of box why not
Pretty sure he lives in the suburbs
Of course
Yeah I don't understand I don't understand what the
This affects his life in any meaningful way other than
He gets mad seeing people of other the backgrounds other communities
Living
Prelate
That takes me back to that joke that he said in the last Clipper two clips ago or whatever where he's like
I like them
As long as they're over there and everybody laughs and he's like just joking and gesturing
And then he literally says you know the same thing but
Deadly serious
I don't go to the South side right and that there was no I'm joking they left
Did the joke is that he does mean it
He's deadly serious.
But he also doesn't mean it cuz he's also not fine if these other people are over there
Ghost of us outside
I don't know man I don't even know how to set up these clips
Cuz it's just rolling
Going through the interview
And I just
Just find everything in it disgusting
You know what Detroit looks the same
Many cities
Tinseltown
Where are the Democrats
Consummate
What
Policies work in Haiti and everywhere else in the world
The exact same way
And they put it down right here
Becomes a problem
Country happens to be
My home
So one of the things I think is important about that clip Beyond just the
Covert
You know bigotry that runs throughout everything
This is counter to the Infowars narrative
Yeah this is counter to the larger conspiracy that Alex cells because
He's saying
What is it in these countries where are the Democrats in those countries where are the Socialist policies in these countries know
Intrinsic
These people
Come from other places
And
It's within themselves it's not even the devil
Right
It's people with big human spirit that I hate
I think I think that one of the things that's important to recognize is the
This is
Not compatible really
With the diversion of the world that Alex tries to sell
That conspiracy is undermined
Bye
Knicks
Rhetoric
And that seems to me to be
Enough of a reason not to have him on your website
Well if you're if you're fine with the other stuff that comes along with it
I would think it's probably bad for business
For you to be yelling about how
It's the global is to the left of China and all this
And then have Nick Fuentes be like no it's not it's just right
Alex
Skin color my man
The problem is the people look different
REI really so
Again
Now he's mad about people packing up their country and moving it to America
At what point in time are we ever going to deal with America only being short number of years old
Bad never
I'm going to go with never that was like
Fine up until like 17
79 that's what those the cutoff
Fair enough
Now we enter the portion of this clip that is
The fear tactic space
America
I don't know
Where else
Coming to coming to your neighborhood
Your place
And your people
Look at all the way
Utah
Number two
You're not sending them there
Southern border
Where are they
Nevada where they sign them to Minnesota
In Michigan
Wisconsin
And they're flying them
To your neighbors
Cities and everybody sees it
So I mean it can't get much clearer than the
They and you like Autumn me that you portrayed here and it's
Gross just say they're coming for your white women
That's it just say that
They don't they don't need any more than that they don't need rhetoric they just need to hear that they're coming for the white with
Even like be fine with that
Where classic
Remember this song
You do a lot of people think that segregation ended but I think
Bring it back
Okay I have these folks coming to your school's your neighborhood
Yeah
You do a lot of courageous chill
Broke
Through
F****** ranks of National Guard members
Just to go to school
And you're like they're sending them to our god I
It's pretty bad Bruno it's from the past man
This is this is kind of where this next clip
Elevated into like
I cannot believe that Alex is allowing for this on his
Platform
I know this because
America is not
We like to go to work and
Are we like to go to Mars
America is
Supposed to be
Nation
Which is constitutionally
Regions
Communities
Neighborhood
How are you
Real community
In real neighborhood
People don't even speak the same language on your
A real community
If people don't
Religion
But this is a fact of our nature
Can you have a community
I mean
That is outrageous
I just don't even know
Your head is in your hand
Very very much breathing through it have a community of people look
Wild
Just want you know what you can you can I've lived in so many of them. They're way better than all of the
All white ones I've ever lived in
It's insane I honestly don't even really know where this logic
It could be grounded
Like at what point do looks
Like where it where is the relevant difference in looks that you can have a community with somebody
Skin color
Facial hair choice
I think is it how much how much uniformity is required in order to have a neighborhood
Where somebody across the street from you eat
Honey Nut Cheerios when in your home you are eating plain Cheerios
Exactly you can't have those in the same neighborhood I need segregated Cheerios neighborhood
I want the Jets in the sharks in different neighborhoods
Get them all out of here I want
White sole
What you really seeing is that there is there something going on with Nick where he doesn't feel like
He's capable or able or anyone is capable
Of having Community with people who speak different languages who have a
From religious belief
Or whoever
Different looks
Great he thinks that about himself he has universalized at everybody else
Switch is stupid
But he's saying that in terms of like
His own ability to make a community matter in other places where he is not
Other people are existing totally fine
But what's fascinating about this is he's trying to make both arguments
That not only does he not want to
Live or is it he's unable to live
In a diverse community
But the communities
Are equally unable to exam
That's the one he never goes to
That's really f***** up
And the fact that it really comes down to
Being so over that like 82 looks
How can you have a community with me
People who look different than you
I cannot believe
Did Alex
It would be fine with this
Cuz I think it's true
I think he's our two similar but
This is so optically bad
I mean even Alex takes great pains
Needs to go out of his way to be like it is
Not just like how you look different f*** off light up you look different you should be in a different Community also
So I don't want you in that Community because somehow I believe that you can't coexist with my fellow whites
Be back in a different community and guess what
I'm going to need to take that land later that's going to need to be my community as well it's
Yeah
God how can you
Cheez-Its made it there's only two ways to go for them
Is if they win
It is
The country then becomes a f******
Non-stop conquering country trying to steal everybody else's s*** to
Or the whole thing falls apart and they just
Separate into smaller and smaller groups that hate each other like it's bananas house stupid all of this is it's pretty.
But yeah
McNichols
This is a fact of our nature
Can you have
Community
Who's the courageous man there
And that's the question I do
And if we want to preserve
Communities
Bring over
Different Valley
Different ways of life
But they are still
I need to buy
What
Do you really want to bring
Nashua
And you would be in favor of cohesion
But the cohesion and the communities are in
Possible if you look different
So you have to have uniform communities that's what it means to be an American nationalist
Snap some of these people who are not white who are coming over these immigrant Folk
They may seem totally the these changes for these differences are almost imperceptible
But they're there
Guess what even white people you see
Secretly they might be harboring some imperceptible difference between the two of you
What kind of
Might be where the next stage of his Workshop
But I say
Yes it's it's a it's a way of being a I can't really make this argument but I'm going to go ahead and
Well I mean
Fundamentally the the biggest issue with his argument is it is
Thoroughly intrinsic
You
Can not change
Simply impossible
No there's no way that if you did move to a let's say
Non majority white neighborhood
You could change your behavior
He does not allow for that possibility like not not even
Not even like you shouldn't have
2 or anything like that he's saying this from a place of
It is not possible
Ulta coexist so your country of origin is deterministic of what
Kind of
Behavior you're going to
Yep manifest
Any circumstance
It's
You are not an individual you are a block
Now what people are just white people have a lot of individual things that's why we can create a country like the United States
Alicia
Brutal
Yeah yeah it's pretty bad
Now at this point explains that once
Deep there's a no longer a white
Majority in the country will be a worse country
An inferior country
Nation
Lucy.
Do they call me away
Because I say
Truce
The nasty
America
Won't be a wife
And America will be
Country
What ignorable
And then when you begin
The question is
The country
I wonder why it is we get it
The same
Or will it be
The conscious
Worse
Hey
I don't know
Hey if we end slavery
Is the country going to be better
The same or worse you will have changed the balance of power if you allow black people to vote will the country be
Be better
Or the same or Worse cuz it will be different than
Desert these arguments eBay
Very similar
I mean like I think I think it's just that this is kind of these dancing around
Defining anything yeah
What is it mean for the country to be better or worse right
Fortuitous
On the grand scale or for you
Individually
Guy who can't deal with people who look different right what change is
Acceptable is any change
Acceptable
A progressive tax
Like what if what
Change towards
America isn't acceptable
Like within the boundaries of possibility
Stuff to say
Right so if this is the end of his speech and I have some thoughts that I want to share
If we get it
Will that country be
B Team
Or will it be
The conscious
Very simple
Country is changing
Born not interchangeable
We can't just take one guy and
It's going to be different
What we know about where they
America
We don't want that
Happens
I want to live in the
My ancestor
Creative
I want
Ancestors
Nit
Stories about
Divider Grandpa
Cigarette
Please don't ride the Subway at night
Ride the bus
And can you imagine something
Like that
Look at our cities
What's going on
At the end of the clip has lived in Chicago for the last decade
Preco videos I could
Imagine riding buses and trains after Dark
Did all the time
It's awesome that was how I got around
And you can just hop on the train and you'd wind up somewhere in Chicago
And sometimes you didn't get to the right spot but the powers
Video Jordan is disgusting
And it's a pretty clear articulation of white nationalist beliefs which are being presented with a nice pre-emptive explanation that these are not in
In fact a lot of people say these are white nationalists beliefs and that's only because I want to wait
If you look at the beginning of the speech and the things that he ends up at
Expressing
What you have is
I'm not racist but
Basically in speech for NASA
This in itself
Isn't really that groundbreaker
Contact you can expect from someone like Nick but now it's being posted and hosted on Alex's own website which is pi
Kind of amazing Attaway
Who's representing looming problem for Alex that I don't think that he's going to be able to navigate very well
And that problem may be coming to a head much quicker than he expect
At least if it's can of the comments on this video are any indication
I don't spend too much time in the comment section on his website mostly
Why's mostly cuz a lot of it is incoherent anger slurs and
Anyone can post whatever they want anonymously so it really feels productive to assume the individual comments mean anything
However the comments on this video or fascinating and that they seem to break down into toucan
The first group is people who seem to agree with Nick
They seemed pretty mad
Pretty comfortable with just wearing their white nationalism on their sleeve like this one
The differences between races isn't just skin color deal with it Boomers to each race their own nature
Was that Boomers that
So some of these people on Nick side let's say are a little more blunt
But what I find far more interesting are the people in the second camp
Which is the camp that recognizes that this kind of content represents a bit of a departure from what Infowars is supposed to be about
One person something up pretty well
I can't believe how many racists are in this community
I thought we were better than that
I hated the libtards call everything racist but this guy is actually racist y'all we don't want this s***
Scaring our I think they might scarring the name of Infowars I'm more right
That's
Right on man
Another commenter makes a good point except for the part where he's like I can't believe I mean man, I didn't realize
I'm all about it
Man another commenter makes another good point
If I sent a family member a link
Banned. Video hoping to that for them to educate themselves about covid vaccine election fraud or the cabal end
Wo agenda
And the first thing they see featured up top of the page as a headline like
Why we must preserve America's white majority just doesn't look good
Even if you're in the Infowars world you believe the narratives and everything
You can recognize that this is something you do not want to be associated with cuz it's on its face
A little bit
F***** up
I like Infowars
It's because he says globalist instead of Jews and then I don't have to think about it okay that's why I lie
I can forward you can't just be saying white all the time
There's a number people in the comment section to bring up things like no wait until the media picks
This up
I got making it clear that they know that this is going to be something very attackable which Alex chosen to associate with
And now the audience of the show is going to be associated with it to unless they clearly reject
That's a tough position to be in and you can see a lot of people decide that they're just going to retreat
Intuit comfortable assumption that Nick is actually a Fed plant drink
Check the bacon in floors look bad by making videos that are transparently racist so Alex will look racist by extension
That sounds great
There's a deep division in this comments section and it feels like this could be hiding in one of two directions and neither I think look
Good for Alec
One possibility is that Alex keeps Nick around and let him have his channel on the web
Mix clearly already testing the waters to see what he can get away with it if this video is any indication
But he should probably feel no trepidation about pushing even
In further
If things go this way it seems like there's a contingent of listeners who won't support that
It could lead to them questioning why Alex would distribute this
Kind of contact
Particularly given her naked Alex disagree on the very basis of the conspiracy they're fighting
Who is Mick rejecting the China Democrat socialism big Boogeyman
But Alex uses to scare the audience
Tell me other Road you have the option of Alex kicking Nick off the channel
Which only serve to alienate the more extreme elements of Alex's audience
This is a dangerous game that you get into when you make so much of your political identity about how your viewpoints are secretly correct and everyone said
Answering you because of it
If you ever need to censor someone you really put yourself in a difficult position because whatever arguments and attacks you've used against
People censoring you can now be used against you and make no mistake
That's precisely what would happen if Alex
Get your neck off the platform
Situation because he left
You letting it get involved
He kind of has to deal with the association
Or
Go against his
Banned. Video principle
And I think either way you're going to have a certain amount of the audience be like
Why are you doing this
It was actually kind of heartening to look in the comments section and people like what the fuc
Like I believe
Does Federal Reserve sugar see I've been there for a while
3 cm
Got the FED we got it man I'm with you
I like to see I am fine with going to the same bathroom as other people I wanted to focus on things that were created
Goodbye people who worked on George Wallace his campaign
Perfect
That's well done.
Like it's so bizarre though
Honestly I think that I might be making a little bit more of this season than actually exist like
There's a decent chance that this will just be a
Little bubbling thing or comments are always a vocal minority
You never really know because it could lead to no chaos on
Play Infowars front door
I also see this as kind of a difficult pickle
The Alex
If not addressed
And handle
Fairly well could end up with
Lot of
Lot of negative
Dicey material being posted
On on Alex's own website
This one's free
Alright
This is the only good advice I'm going to give to Alex
On purpose
Get Nick
And Doctor Stevie pees on the same show TV peas is not going to like what's going down there cuz Nick is knocking
Can I handle b******* those same way that other people probably not
Get that as the fight
That would be Alexa
Exact
That's how you do it
Yeah I mean it was great to have Nick debate Barnes
Let's get let's get speakers at math you want to get rid of them
You know that's going to be a fight you you got rid of David night and nobody really bad it and I there in fact people were more in this TV
So even the racist will be like
History is boring I mean it's boring white nationalism isn't it
Okay let's exterminate non-whites you know like it's banal but that's a Stevi B's
He's in control of white nationalism
Pick up people in betting it all the way to the fullest self
True
Countries over here to kill I don't know everything
It would be nice
Be nice to just see how they would interact
I want it
I want to bed anyway visible shorter episode like I said to take a little look at this and
Will be back on Wednesday with a
A normal episode Hindi but until then Jordan
Do we have a website like we do
We are on Twitter that knowledge underscore fighting that go to bed Jordan
Find a local charity or bail Fund in your area
To help out people do it.
Pitbull
And now here comes
The sex robots
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color