I have great respect for knowledge by now I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Jones
Indeed we are
What's up
My bright spot today is Monday
The conservation journey of the tributes to Celine
So so far and
A baby elephant
Oh and today I am thrilled to announce that
Got in touch
And has
Protected for M2 of forest area in Belgium
In honor of Celine
Do we need to be we need to overtake Rogan
And we need to carve out
Part of the world for just the walks
I think that you're getting into unhealthy
Call T territory a little
I think it's more amusing that this is turning out to be like people are just going to take the ball and running with it in the direct
Directions that they come up with
Some really cool conservation tape ideas
A supporting
Call charitability
I really think that's cool
I think so thank you so much
Celine
She says
Meow
What's abortion for the altar of saline and now we have
Adopted
People out yeah I know this
Wildlife
Corkcicle
Just donating to
Preserve wildlife
At no point in time has anybody sacrifice
What's up my bright spot Dan is early in Layton June I think released his
Documentary stand up special
Tastic it is so what he did was he
Did six nights
Improvised stand-up
At this at this
Kind of like
Dilapidated / amazing incredible holy Comedy Club
And it's fantastic not just because it's really really
I mean he's very funny onstage obviously
Scuffles
Really really great
But because it shows him analyzing his sets
The afterwards
Like you
Committing to
Doing an improvised hour
Are you now
The comic
You know if you're doing that there's a good chance you're going to get at 5
10-minute stretch of like
Oh this is nothing
Yeah this is nothing so there's that
Fear of 20 minutes
There's that double-sided
Did fear for him of like
I don't want to go into a joke
But that's what
Comics have always trained themselves
To do Drew
You're ripping 45 minutes you the rift runs out your like
If things are going bad the way you save yourself would be like well I got to pull out of jail
Or or you know that kind of thing and so it was that constant fight and then the way that he analyzed it afterwards
Like why is it always it why is it getting sexual too soon and he's like well because I've never done this before it's just like when you
You start out
As a comic it starts out real blue and do nothing
Psychological deconstruct
By way of
Analyzing your own stand-up sets of your own Tendencies under pressure
I would
I would recommend it
And also there's the story of the comedy club and its
This guy is
The story is amazing
I'm so done today we have an episode from the past
We're going back to the past I was sick of the bulshit
Here's what happen
On Friday we will have
A present day episode will talk about f****** Mike Lindell and all this nonsense
But ice
Got to a point where I was sitting here I was like
Alright
No matter what
If you get into if you at
You open up an episode of Alex Jones Show
You're going to find something
You're right you're going there's going to be something
To talk about
What is it going to be like something bizarre like maybe
A new species of animal or is it going to be a body
Right
There's a cornucopia of possibilities yes that is one thing that's an advantage of present-day it's always upsetting
Max is going to be a bummer
Turn up that cover and see
I found myself resisting doing it where is
In the past year you might find a new fossil
You do something you might add to the
I don't know I don't know if his metaphors making any sense but
The point is I I didn't
What I wanted to put off someone's birthday
That's what they're for us in the past was here in the present is just everybody's going to die
Yes yes
Yeah
So today we're going over
May 30th
2003 before we do let's take a little love and say hello.
Paul
Easy walk thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Hey I hate to say it it took me a second
Going to get there
But thank you very much
Reruns on top thank you so much
Next
Rogue Pelican thank you so much you and I'll probably walk
I should say also I believe it was
Season 9
Is when the Pelican makes
Its first appearance
Listen to Survivor Pelican referee
Not
The case on Survivor
What a great power
Want to buy a tiger
Thank you very much
I'm a policy wonk
Yeah
Catherine
I'm a policy wonk
Where's the best co-worker I started buying pills and trips from Alex on becoming a technical text
To bring balance
Thank you so much
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
Started buying fails and there's a myelogram pick up Annika developing Advanced nurse
Thank you very much
That was not quite auctioneer
Seattle
All right and also for helping us out with this special project
We have a new Raptor princess
Joanna
Barbecue your ass
It's over for Humanity
You're Beautiful song
They're coming for your balls
It's all over your God
Very few people
Their babies
Make it a practice
Calling people
The garbage when they are
Hey Jude
What's the weather
From now on
Episode
Interesting little glimpse
Into where I was at the end of May
Obviously
Still looking to see
If he believes he's fighting the devil 1003 true still trying to see his relationship with the
Iraq War
This Thread that we didn't expect
Find where he's in denial about the application
Yeah
I'm fascinated to see how this plays out and there's midget
Pink stuff
In the mix
For today
But the lead story
Holyshit
Bill Clinton coming back
But Republicans
George
Run again
For those in our audience outside the United States
It's the 22nd amendment was added to the Constitution
The douching in 1947
Essentially
To make sure that someone could only serve two four-year terms as president
This is just kind of understood that this was the norm with George Washington setting an Unwritten precedent by not seeing the third terminal
This man was ratified when it was in 1947 because the presidency of Franklin Roosevelt
Route to just end it
Who served three terms and it won a fourth election for
For the presidency but died in office
People kind of realize at that point that this Norm that everyone just assumed everyone would accept was
Was not actually a rule that maybe we should
Put it on paper
Propeller
It's more of those things lately, down Roosevelt Amendment
That was the first name of it yeah
Presidential been bound by these term limits also the wording of the rules is often caused some
Debates pop-up
For instance conversations often happen about whether a two-term president could run for a third consecutive term if they were
President on the third term
Who serve two consecutive terms to run again at a later date
Essentially making the term limits only apply to the
Consecutive
Sure
He was giving speech at the
Probably not a coincidence
John F Kennedy Library and Museum in Boston
Speculated that given the people were living longer quote
There may come a time when we elected president at age 45 or 50
And then 20 years later the country comes up against the same kind of problems the
Then face before
So that's basically you know
Look at the John F Kennedy Library
According to the article
Is Beto's in the BBC quote
The former president said such a change
Probably would not apply to him but would benefit
Future Generations
The kernel of this is yours
Berkshire in 2003 representative Serrano introduced to house joint resolution
What does repealing term limits for the president
He did this literally every other January from 1997 to 2013 and ever
Free Bill died in committee
Between these years of 1995 and 2005 representative steny Hoyer also introduced bills to repeal the 20th
Second Amendment
And both of these dudes did this
Regardless of which party held the presidency
Like people
Are doing this in order to get their guy more turds right they're doing it because they don't believe it should
Return limits for the president
Is there doing it even if it does bite them in the ass Reagan gets a third term
Yeah yeah
So the prospect of a l unilaterally
Declaring they want us
Establish term limits
Do not apply to them
Maybe be seen as a warning
Anxiety but for Alex to report this news about the appropriate context
I think is a bit of a lying by omission
Yeah
Yeah specially when we live in the present and you just heard everybody being like
I don't think there's anything wrong with y'all getting the third term he didn't even get a full one his first sermon you like I don't even have whatever that
Going around with serious dates
Nubian presidency forever
And also that argument
From Clinton is really really stupid
Really stupid because if you're saying to me that twenty years after a president we find ourselves in the same problems
The president was a shity president
Maybe maybe there are problems you can deal with
But you can't deal with permanent like
Recur
I would say in
Relation to Clinton's argument
That is
B were the case
President was particularly good
Add dealing with something years later the same as you popped up
There's a really good chance we would have studied their response
To the issue probably and maybe somebody else could Implement a lot of the same
Things
You wouldn't need the exact same person
To deal with it it's not like
They have a magical individual power to
Maybe not
The most compelling
Although I do see that some people
Who are opposed to
Term limits don't have
The worst ideas ever has valid argument to be made for and against
Yeah I'm not saying that
I think what's funny about saying it at the kennel
CityCenter is just like she could also be like and your entire family should run the country forever
Why do people problem
So Alex has he studied
Prediction
Haha and I want to say this like this is this is why I going back
What's the password
It's particularly fun
Because there's so much going on now with Alex trying to be like I've always been right
I predicted everything down so many people online to argue about
It turns out I was right bro but I got to tell you Alec
When's you been wrong
Every time he shows up they only talk about the times when he's right
About
This is hilarious
Secretary-general
Predictions of these are s*** they worked out exactly any more wrong about any of
Hillary lost in the 2008 primary to Obama and Bill Clinton is not nor has he ever been the secretary
Terry general of the UN
Also there aren't established 8-year terms for un secretary-general
Their terms last
Varying amount
The time over history
But
Since 1971 has become tradition that a persons elected to the position
For five-year term
And they will get a second term unless it's vetoed
Buy a member Nation
This is only happened once
Boutros boutros-ghali not getting a second term
In 1996
The next to secretary-general Kofi Annan and ban ki-moon serve full 10-year stretches
In office
For someone who's big villain in the world as the UN Alex seems to not have a very good grasp on how they operate
No clips
Years of study to bring this analysis
What's also also just on its face
Can you imagine the United Nations
Electing a former United States President as the secretary-general
Talk about just how unrealistic that is a little bit later but unrealistic
I would be very comfortable with saying that we will never see the day ever that not only
Former president
But a high-level us Diplomat will never be
Be Secretary General of the UN
There is a lot of distributed power among the security Council
And such a totally organization that you and B
There's there's really something important about
The representation
That is given by having different regions of the world
Represented by the secretary-general absolutely and so whenever there is
New
Appointment coming up
They'll generally be
Conversation of what region of the world is
Resistire
State belong
A group that has had a lot of time
Being up the number of terms in the secretary-general's at Petro
First of all you're not going to probably see anybody
From the United States
Express whatever second before there's not another
Person probably from an Asian country from Eastern Europe has never been someone from the East
Eastern European region
Who is Ben in the secretary-general.
These things are important
832 the countries
But do have those veto powers
Over the process
I know somebody in hungry who's really looking for that secretary-general job
Just ridiculous if you have any awareness at all and I like I said we'll talk about it in more detail later but like
You have any idea about how any of this stuff works
Like this on a
Structural basis
You couldn't
Possibly think the
Hippies were
Anyway reasonable
Conspiracies to have absolutely not just no way they could ever happen
Know some of them
It's some of the member nations of the UN I have been like
We just had the United States invade us
We can't be having them run the UN
Yeah
Again
Really
Why does will never happen will get through a little bit down the road
You'll notice that these predictions no matter how bad they are and how wrong they
Continue to be they often don't change
Hey more recent days we've heard Alex try to reuse this exact same conspiracy but with Michelle Obama becoming president
Barack becoming the Secretary General of the UN
It's overloaded s*** but it's really effective
In terms of terrifying the audience
The Alex can constantly just recycle this stuff with just
Slightly different details
Change to suit the times
It's all
Bulshit
If the president of the United States
And a former president United States was a un secretary-general at the
The same time
I think I might believe in the global
You know what I'm saying
If the president was married to the
Secretary General of the UN and this they also happened to be a former president
Even if it isn't a conspiracy
Just now
Whatever's going on is wrong there is it there is a structural problem with the organization of what's going on and we cannot
Hey Robert you been doing a great job
I need you to do a SG job at the UN even us would be like look
No more Brothers in politics
Sure
Eclipse
Save people who I have
Mostly positive feelings
Barack Obama and Michelle Obama
Dude about their prospects
Pretty flexible
Honestly laughable just
Pavestone
What things would need to happen in order to get to that point
It's just ridiculous
Both China and Russia agree
Clinton will be the next secretary chair
It's important
To understand
When you're talking about something that is this
Conspiracy bike
Clinton's going to
Become the Secretary General of the UN
Kind of
Have to discuss how one becomes the Secretary General of the UN
Or at least you have to give me some kind of an item that you understand that or else I'm going to say that this is
Bad analysis
And that's what Alex himself on that this is real analysis
Listen to this horseshit
Brian stelter
You know you can't smile like that unless you're possessed by a commitment
Through the false left-right paradigm
Flash forward to a little bit earlier in time I'll come back I hate it
Can we fight all the time
Everything is fake I don't get bogged down in the
Conspiracy theories every shooting didn't happen
Call someone
Okay whatever
But Alex has a little bit of a
Complaints about the bush
He claims that he came into
The the 10-year of bush in office
What position effective see what happens
He was disappointed immediately
And
This is so interesting the way that which Alex's
Have the consistency in his desire to
To see his political enemies prosecuted
Yep
For crimes that he's imagine they've committed
He imagines his enemies committing our ones his allies are committing openly and off
Yeah
But they're not
Another problem
With bush
It comes down to the senate election
Okay and 2000
100 Bush came into office
This really confused me
But I think I figured out what I was talking about but I still am not 100%.
George Bush
So they admit it
What exactly did they gave them 50 50
Bush gave them a
Receipt
Here's the jump ahead to that
That was sort of what I was going to explain last
And I think
He's getting at is that
Bush stop the recount
In Florida
And Florida was a previously republican-held
Old searight retired
The Democrat ended up winning
The election
Maybe Alex thinks that if the recount had gone forward right that the Republican would have won the seat
But based on the percentages I don't think that's
The Handlery ahead by like 5%
Involved in stopping
Yeah I think that that's the only way that I can look back and make sense
Yeah I think that's probably what he's talkin
Cuz they gave it yeah it was and he would almost be a problem
Hopefully it's like a trade of like something like that I got the president so they got the Senate
Not all senate elections stick out in your memory but
That was the election where John Ashcroft lost the Missouri Senate race to Mel Carnahan who it actually die
Prior to the election
As someone who is in Missouri at the time this was gratifying.
And 52,000 senate elections the vote was tied 50
50 with the vice president casting the tiebreaker
V
2001 Jim Jeffords previously a republican decided to go independent and he started
Caucus with the Democrats
It'll book you would later released Jeffers explained that he began to feel alienated by the GOP
Particularly in their refusal
Support and fund the individuals with Disabilities Act which has been a major priority of his
Or at least
Decades
Before this
Hurry if you hear from a statement that he released after he decided to switch
Increasingly I find myself in disagreement with my party
I understand that many people are more conservative than I am and they form the Republican Party
Given the changing nature of the national party it's become a struggle for our leaders to deal with me
Me and for me to deal with them
Indeed the party's electoral success has underscored the dilemma I face within my party
In the past without the presidency the various wings of the Republican party in Congress have had some freedom to argue
And ultimately to shape the party's agenda
The election of President Bush change that dramatically
We don't live in a parliamentary system but it's only natural to
To expect that people such as myself
Who's been honored with positions of leadership with largely support the president's agenda
Looking ahead I can
Tibor & Morgan
Instances where I will disagree with the president on very fundamental issue
The issues of choice
The direction of the Judiciary
Tax and spending decisions
Missile defense
Energy and the environment
Host of other issues Largent
Small the largest for me is education
Which Loops back to the individuals with Disability Act issues that he
I was very passionate
You can make an argument that there was like so backroom dealing involved goes duh
After he switched parties and gave the Democrats a slight advantage in terms of votes he was given the chairmanship of the Senate environment
And Public Works committee
We could also kind of make the argument that this was making up for the chairmanship that he would necessarily lose
When he leaves the Republican Party
Frazier said he had held for a long time
Yeah yeah I don't know I don't know
But that doesn't
Feel stage to me
I don't see anyone admitting it
And I don't
I don't know what was staged
About
The ending of the recount
I don't understand how any of that stagedoor admitted
No interesting about losing to you
Yeah yeah
That's one
It's alright it's always fun whenever
We we hate
Somebody so much we'd rather have a dead person in their spot
One more. About that ultimately none of this matters at all because you remember it like
He died for the 2000 election
His wife Jean filled that c for two years then in 2002 there was a special election where she lost it
Jim Talent
Anderson was under GOP
Control once again
Jim Jeffords defection was a big deal on paper but ultimately it only mattered for
Stretch of months
Yeah we are actually in the past by the time I was recording
The show
Three witches strain
Wow
What
It's an interesting way of
Recasting certain amount of failure guess
Look man
Any shows
Competition
How long is it on a substance
He doesn't have competition
Because they don't have sex
Exactly
Moron
It didn't happen
I almost would rather listen to something that doesn't have substance that something that's
Pretending to have Subs in Chinese
Drastically wrong
Yeah yeah it would be like
Substance
And is
Convincing you of inaccurate
Conclusion I would rather not have a pie
Then have a pie that he baked out of
You know with no feeling no nothing it's just
The paper is a paper plate I would rather not have a pie
Then have somebody give me a paper plate
Because I'm taking that paper plate that he's trying to give me using it to serve up a nice pie which is our podcast metaphorically
I would love that paper plates
Manipur has lost
So
Totally going to become secretary-general
F****** stupid
In Beaufort
You're they're going to have Hillary Clinton or some other
What
President
Okay
Wawa
For the
What
In this episode alone it's almost impressive how much of a lack of awareness about the UN Alex seems to be displaying
You been wrong about the way the terms work for secretaries General and he's come up with this fun story about Bill Clinton trying to solicit
Set votes at office
Alex is wrong with those details to though
He's at the Clinton needed eight countries and he gotten the approval of six
But that's not
True
ICandy for secretary-general needs to be I have the backing of 9 members of the UN
Security Council and not have any Vito's from any of the
Permanent members
Who are the United States the United Kingdom
France Russia and China
They're 15 countries on the security Council at any time so you need to have support of nine of them
And not be someone who'd be vetoed
Bill Clinton
Would absolutely be vetoed either by Russia or China and I'm already brought up 1000000% not even a question
There is no
Pho King way
Ever happen
Not
Oh yeah it's a Putin say hello to you mister Clinton
Way to work with you going forward
It's it's it's an honor
Thinkable Prospect
Russia or China would not veto a former US president as a candidate for the UN secretary-general ship
Nonsense
What Dick Cheney could get
Probably.
Alex's Basin that a country's thing like you said off the
The G8 but that has nothing to do with the UN Security Council is deciding the secretary-general
The G8 is a yearly Summit that was held among the group of eight countries until 2014 when they
Kick Russia out and change your name back to the group
France the United States and United Kingdom are all G8 countries that have a permanent spot on the UN Security Council
There is a little bit of overlap
They're sure
The Security Council is made up of
The five permanent members
And 10 rotating
Non-permanent member State representing different regions of the world
In 2003 when Bill Clinton would supposedly be trying to lock down these votes for un secretary-general
Positions
There were two even 6ga countries in the security Council
There were the permanent members France the United States the United Kingdom and Russia since then
Been kicked out yet
And that your germinate was a rotating member
Does g a country that was in the spirit account
Of the G8 countries that would it be
Didn't even a factor in the
The decision about the selection of the secretary-general
Canada Italy and Japan play
Who
But maybe Alex is talked about in 2006 when the whole thing would go down not 2003 right
Bill Clinton was just trying to plan prematurely preemptively
This doesn't work either
In 2006 is no longer a rotating member of the security Council so the number is actually
The decider
The balance out it wouldn't work
It's really a big problem how little Alex seem to grasp about this stuff that he's talking
I'm making these grandkid
Conspiracies about
He's pulling out numbers and making up fun scary stories for the audience but it's pretty embarrassing
When you consider the reality how the UN works
Even if
A candidate makes it through the selection process in the security Council
They still need to be approved by the general assembly afterwards
Don't no one has ever been rejected by the general assembly after being selected by the the the security Council
The awareness that certain candidates would be rejected as a critical part of the
The security Council selection process
And part of light off and ends up dragging on
Pretty long
There's zero chance
That Bill Clinton or any former US president would be
Not be voted down by the channel cap assembly
Outrageously Snoop
I am going to tell you this right now
I refuse
To take
The predictions of subway
Hoop report
To be an ex
Expert in international affairs
Who would absolutely be destroyed by any ten-year-old in the model un Club
Definitely
Murdered by a ten-year-old simple basic ten-year-old would be
Disappointed to have that conversation with an adult it would rattle their entire perception of humanity
And they would learn too young
Adults are just bigger chill
And how is your confidence and you know amass enough false credibility
People will just go along with what you say
Like
Beat up the notion
That
Like
If you're in the security Council in here discussing like who should we put up for the secretary-general chairs
It would be
Fairly obvious
That it might be seen as insulting
The rest of the world
To nominate a former US president
Would probably be a consideration like it would be in the front
Generally speaking
It would give the message that the United States
Actual Primacy
In the world that is not
We are
The body that represents a large number of nations
Who all have some sort of tension but
Between each other in some form or another so we tend to elect somebody with a neutral perhaps
Stephen distance
View of how to deal with this on the
A global scale
Or this time
We could elect one of the guys causing all of the tensions all around the world
I can't imagine that like
Never be like you
Let's do this
Yeah yeah
Obama has a Peace Prize and we will all want it taken away we don't want him
Anywhere near the U
Alex
Is
Able
To confidently assert these things
Because the space is so stupid
Like there
Like it at people who are giving voice to the
That's not how this works Cher Cher Bono
It's Magic his co-host might be a ten-year-old in the model untf
Yeah they'll be devastated
I'd be awful
So Alex goes on a little bit
In the in the present Alex is totally fine with a new world order as long as it's a
New World Order a collection of
Christian nationalist States
That all work together International Coalition of nationalist States who refused to view
Do International Coalition does being valuable and we're also going to buy Greenland or going to take over
Nationalism colonialism
Two new world order new world order
World Order
New World Order
Smith secretaries-general
Gaston
And this person is barely a member of
A school board in Akron Ohio which is where they were having
The discussion about the finger
Thanks for lunches
One of the large Arguments for is it
The bureaucratic nightmare
Some sort of an organization
The large
City School
Also there were a number of high number of
To Iran
Assistance programs
Had to take away the stigma that
That students real
Your eye and I reduce bullying
This way you wouldn't have to have a ticket
Signal singles you out as
Alex wants her to say the boring interview
Alex wants her to say that it's
Mandated
Ride the government the federal government is making them do this
Because it's not
Anthony and David the way the fed's Mandate water things by saying
You can have this money however you can only
Spend this money
In this way
So what they don't tell you exactly
What
Your limited on what kinds of
Scanner
Yes they're not mandating it
It's a grant
So so it's like okay
Okay so it's like somebody's giving you a hundred bucks
For you to buy this thing
Right
They
That you need
And you can't just go spend it on drugs
Stop
Yeah it's the federal government telling me what to do with their money and I hate it
Don't some fun trivia
What is woman that Alex is interviewing is the mother of Patrick Carney the drummer from The Black Keys
Team Trivia
That is very fun trivia
It has legitimately nothing to do with his interview but I was so bored then
I was like who is this person can I find out anything about them and it turns out she's The Black Keys drummer mother
In the process of looking at that I realized
The Black Keys drummer Patrick Carney is married to
One of my favorite singer-songwriters Michelle Branch
Hippie mother-in-law Michelle
It's a Small World
Small world everybody has love and will travel
So they're talking a little bit more and this is the only other thing I really think was
All that interesting and it's I think Alex
Thinks me solution to
School shootings
And what have you is
Beating up kids
They make me run around
And then you have parents that that you know
They come in and I think their job is
Be there kids stuff
The kids best friend and they take the child
Hardness a nice to know if parents are ruining their children because they're uncomfortable with being parents
Throw up
Ma'am
I don't know if I have much
A comment for that but it's kind of
Sad you know if you don't want bad things to happen you should psychologically and physically torture your kitten
I don't know why everybody doesn't get this
Yeah you know you physically and psychologically tortured children into behaving good as a do
And then later on when they're adults they'll torture children into behaving good as an adult
An owl
We have our perfect
System
Of all of those people can't we see that dude I think that
Makes a lot of sense
That you should give card blocks
Do people who are in an educational capacity
To enact violence a stranger
To beat my children I want them to determine what is and is not appropriate and then respond with Viber
Yep yep
Yep I infect
You know what as a parent I want
Let's say over how my kids are
I would also like some of that violence to be tortured
Crisco absolutely until you vomit and if you have a paddle
You better Innovative way to make it hit harder
Cuz if you don't what's
The point
Yeah
I don't like this position
Alex ever talking to this gas
God the mother of The Black Keys drummer
He goes to call
I listen to
In the evening
Here locally in the shop
Call Gloria en.
There I forgot to tell him
After work this morning I forgot
But I know the name of it
Video
It's called Monopoly man have you ever heard of it
What do you think of it
That's pretty good
I don't I don't think Alex has seen it
Sort of response is always
Snyder no
Monopoly man wasn't an actual documentary it was the title of an episode of it
The conspiracy show called The phenomenon
The series was hosted by Dean Stockwell
This one had to do with
The theories surrounding the Federal Reserve
Sure
Freemasons go back and look at this episode and see who they chose to talk to
Here are some of the experts
But they consulted
Here we go give me give me a call give me a ride or when I didn't see them
Andrew Arnold was interviewed who is he an editor for the spotlight
Which is that anti-semitic rag published by Willie cardo
Hey spotlight
Oh they also talked to William still
Whose film The Money Masters contains historical inaccuracies about the Rothschild family
Anti-semitic propaganda most notably the Nazi film
The Rothschild sharrett Waterloo
Clearly this is the kind of hard-hitting TV episode that does their homework
Work on the possible crypto beliefs
But they're supposed experts might be secretly pushing
Woobat job Dean Stockwell
Yeah
It really bums me out cuz here's what they could just
I'm tired of all the Conte
Just every couple of weeks
Put out another video of somebody Straight Ahead like in Ahoskie
Situation just going
I haven't used it and then we all got it
That's what they all say
It's the same documentary a million times over
Well they would never do that be
Because
You can't really persuade people
With that you have to
Couch your beliefs Indies crypto
Talking points is essentially what
This documentary about the Federal Reserve
You know boils down to
And you can try to tell by the guest election that
I don't know if the people who are making
In this documentary series
Hey the vested interest in
Really giving the spotlight
There
An unchallenged position
It seems like it was at least
Dad
Straight up
Nazis in here
Very silly
So Alec
Talks to a guy named Frank
Adorable
Is another gas
Alright
And
Activist
Doesn't seem too bad kind of just seems like
You might not know who Alex is entirely right
Legends about 911 himself
Sure
You can see Alex
There's a really fascinating thing to happen
Concierge
Whenever Alex tries to relate to somebody who doesn't actually relate to right
Who was off tracks so fast
Calling the paradise
Republic
During all these Wards as
Republican
Democrat
Can you play some years ago
Anything that we do
Direct deposit
Organized crime
Terminology
I can't speak for everybody else
Yeah that
Was weird
Huh
Longtime activist who made a film called what I've learned about US foreign policy the war against
The third world
Does released in 2000
It's not really an original documentaries and a lot of it is clips
Two speeches by Martin Luther King jr. Jimmy Carter and Amy Goodman
Minute section
It's just clips from a different documentary about the Iran-Contra Affair
Course
It seems like Frank has a mostly level-headed anti-war fellows
I think that he is talking
Into the same sort of person
Just like they have a few different political idea
What happened there is what I see happening
When Alex tries to find this common ground
What happens is
The common ground is established
In the pay believe that the problem of militarism is not unique
To the left or the right
And then immediately Alex will start ranting about some other bizarre talkin boy that has nothing to
To do with what's being discussed like HIV in the corn
Who's the complete curveball and it's meant to disorient for
Or at least put them in the sort of Defense
Some posture
Yunnan situation for Alex's drink
Rosetta agreement with somebody who's
Ostensibly on the left
Still needs to assert dominance
And honestly it comes off a really weak
And confusing
Yeah and there's always the moment
Where the person
Did you know that
Is when he just went oh no
Iron Man
With a Bluetooth
Or maybe at least
You start to get worried about it
Alex backs off on that a little bit maybe just
So talk about Warsaw Cannon
Sure
I'm so Alex
Centerview and
Concerned about Bordertown
No
Junior High School
So
There's a couple issues here
Activists and all the sudden he's like
You know kids are being sacrificed to the satanic cult sound what do you think about that
I think I
Took the round looking
Idea about a literal devil
It still doesn't help to be misdirect
Exactly could be worshipping a God that doesn't
Exist
A Alex in the present-day we know he believes
Hook
Pitchfork literal corn
Getting into people's heads and making them
Morph into
Places to go black
This still is like
I could see somebody being like
Fight in the street and I don't believe what they believe
Alright
Look what they're doing right
You can still have that
Though and there's tons of people still on the on the right who do Rekha
Acknowledge that the
The Church of Satan
Aiden is not actually worshipping
Their literal Christian
Disagree with that
This doesn't do it for me in terms of that
Open question
Now I will say that I've been to Juarez
And I did not get sacrifice
Not once
Not even one time
No
Now
How can I get some of that
Corn
Oh no are you okay
Street vendor at some corn
Spice on it real good little Mexican street corn
I don't know
Sacrifice to the devil
Damn
Alex has been wrong about number of things
And
He continues
To be wrong about something
Other we mentioned earlier
Is a ongoing theme
So Alex is
Still as of May 30th
I convinced that the bath party is being put in power no change in that status quo
He is still
You still
Looking to make that picture I don't know if he's even look into it but it's still
If there's a pivot it's in the future
Yeah
How are you
That's a weird thing to that the weird Hill to die on
You know like
Because you don't have any vested into there's no but there's no real part of the
Conspiracy that requires them to put the bad party in there
You could just say that the CIA took over the other people
Cuz they were all CIA
I imagine that might be the direct Migos eventually
Fight Against the Grain on that one
Like the idea of still having
Conspiracy it seemed salvageable because you can just say
This person also
CIA
But this this abject denial of something that is going on is a major issue is
Strength
Any idea that you your audience is going
To have a an interesting
The view of the differences between Sunni and Shiite is maybe a little silly
There's one thing that you can't into generally
It's not
Quite quite applies to the bath
Party narrative
But in terms of Saddam if you look at the way Alex's discussing
Situation here
These later perfect track
In front of him we're like no matter what happens
Try and pretend he's right
I also know
Where are you at
What they will
So now we have multiple situations
Where we find Saddam or we don't write if we don't Alex's right there never would find him and if they do find him then
Mr. Bullard
So you've created a situation no matter what
Do you have track
Week
To be ripe
It's very lazy strata
I think the only one that you really
Probably couldn't f*** with you
Just yet is that
Saddam actually died 1994 it's been one of his novels.
Well I don't know how big a part of the show Steve is in 2003
So that narrative has not been brought up yet
So Alex
Has a story here it's about how there's a death camps being announced in America
McKay's
She's going back to a headline from three talk about a previous episode where there was discussion about the
Possibility of military tribunals that would lead to executions of prisoners
Animo
Relating that and turning it into a thing where it's like well
That's going to be in Omaha or whatever
And so he's got that
Look how smoothly he turned this into a plug
It's a plug but it's a plug for free publicity
It's a plug for the early days when we when I used to be
Be like oh man I didn't see that plug coming that was back whenever used to be able to to do that
What kind of snack kind of stuck there was a little bit of a natural organic
Whatever from murder to buy pill
At least connective tissue between like
Here is something bad
Here is
My plea that you watch my documentary about something bad
Service
Free advertising for 8 everybody
Tell everybody
Economic sense
But it's still like
Pretty transparent
Egregious a great you know what I like a good I like a good 95
To 120 minute movie that's about as long as they should be
187 minutes
For that s***
Froedtert sequel
I like to the way that this is like
Also everything is just the same as ever like
We have this
Un conspiracy wax
It's Bill and Hillary as opposed to Michelle and Barack
We have
This
You know the death camps and what have you and also I'm being shadowbanned on the internet
You got to send it out there emails
UVM shadowbanned in 2000
Amazing that he was able to like reach the levels of C
Success with people blocking him in 2003
Either there was no way to grow into a massive International fostertown for some sort of contest
Text like at one point
In this
Episode
He's on in 30
States in the car
He's not even on
In 20
There's just no way to grow a business
This anymore if you're a white man
Just you can't do it when you're shadowbanned there's a number another thing that never changes everything
Always the same
Nose answer your
The resolution
Resolution
Memorial Day Parade
You do this all the time in 2009 there's a big initiative
To push the
Yeah Amendment resolutions
Constantly trying to be like hey we still believe in this thing that's the law
Yeah yeah yeah
It's everybody
Everybody's Bound by it it's nice that we've always been hated by monsters
But what
Especially nice to know is that they're also very very lazy and just say the same things for years
Pretty interesting the way that there are those like
It just
It's like a band it's like Boston will always Play More Than A Feeling
Without to have to
And Alex will always
Have some of these things that are just like
Just how to beat Center that's a hit it is it is like people listening to the same song on the radio over and over
Over and over again it's just like yeah give me that hate
Give me that
Jorge
Look at it I can listen to FM
But they don't make me hate
Stuff
You really give me that freedom to want to kill my neighbor
And the other thing to like it's really really
Weird
Notion that he wants to
To constantly be passing resolutions
The affirm the Bill of Rights
Is is
It's Saturday
Trap do duplicit
That's because it's like okay first of all to waste
You're wasting everybody's time
Just fed up with a like we did this a couple years ago why are we doing this again
You don't like the Bill of Rights Act
It's just
Such a stupid game
Constantly playing it
Yeah
God's annoying the worst part is even if it doesn't go anywhere the waist
Time is also a win for the
Just wasting our time is a win because it
It's time not spent
I don't know
Improving anything more like hey let's fix roads or something it's just now
We got to spend
Three days in session saying
I think the Bill of Rights is good
Smothered
This is a pretty guess
Field episode
The person named
Furman who's a Belgian lawyer
And I don't know I think
More or less okay with the
To like you
Alright might have a little bit of a
It's hard to tell
If there is a politeness for an inclination towards conspiracy
Enhance
Kind of tough to tell and I couldn't
I couldn't quite read it quite read exactly how the dynamic was
But you do you have
We have this person who's
A lawyer in Belgium
Who's
Part of bringing these charges
Against military US military forces who have shot at civilian
Belgian Court
Order to try and get these
I think
Address
When you have the anti-war activist guy who made a documentary that's just
Just a bunch of clips of things
I don't f*** I don't totally hate him
The lady from the Akron School Board I think is
Wrong and
I think the issue is meaningless
Black Keys are great
She's the mother of one of them
Interesting set of gas
Yeah when nobody knew who he was you could really get a diverse
Series of people that come on your show
Pretty bizarre
But we we talked about this a little bit because I mentioned on our previous episode that one of the people who is going to be a witness
In this case
In Belgium's was on the show and so now this lawyer is on
Amendment of the law
The Belgian government has
Sorry to pass over the file to the US
Which day
Before US military Court
To go into
Committed by
U.s. troops
Good well and I fully support Iraqi civilians having their day in court
Being given a voice
I just have a bit of a problem accepting that Alex can credibly have this conversation
Because
I'm not sure what his solution could
Possibly be
This gentleman is
Pretty clearly expressing the problem with expecting countries to hold them
Themselves responsible for the atrocities that they can bid for
Particularly during wartime
Yeah why would they want to do that it would make them do less war
How could these Iraqi civilians ever get a fair Hearing in the US
Military Tribunal
This is where having International bodies can really shine
Oz world do is diametrically opposed to any kind of infringement on the sovereignty of the United States
While preserving Hardline version of State sovereignty there's absolutely no Safeguard against
Insterstate Act
However they want
Provided they have the might to back up those Acts
Can say like while we just shoot
All you want
Play yeah
That's not that's not
Like a good
Weight organized
Thanks
No absolutely
Just look at how every
Self-regulated industry the United States were
Very unregulated
Know what it like
Every month
Mysterious or every country that's acting monstrously
Is not going
To check themselves
Turkey still won't admit to a lot of
I don't think they're going to be like a
Look
The genocide never happened
But we will discipline the people
Definitely didn't commit that Janice
Checks and balances don't work when you're doing all of it you're
Why would you
About this conversation with this guy
Doesn't make sense to me
Because what he
He saying
Make sense
I
Did you appreciate on some level
Alex's willingness
To have this guy on sure I certainly don't think he's the only person
Who would be willing
Going to I'm sure people like
Amy Goodman would maybe through be a less stupid conversation
I just don't see I don't see how he
You could possibly
Have a solution to this problem the Dozen
Involve
Amount of
Kwebbelkop
Yeah yeah there's just no way reflects
How how would it is babe
What what
Military is going to be like hey
We are going to let like they don't do it they don't limit their options for murder
That's just how they work
And even when they say they do that doesn't mean I'm going to do
Japan
Like like I'm saying I'm sure someone like
Democracynow would have
A conversation with somebody like this
Or are there other options but I'm sure
Tipping like a majority report
Talk to
A person who has this
Kind of position
It had today
Existed at the time
Somebody like Amy Goodman
Wouldn't talk
Like this
Did you know the people to download music and stuff
Music chairs
You never
You wouldn't be
Be talking about Bill
Clinton becoming the Secretary General of the UN and then becoming president again and
If you go on Napster you going to get it
Executed or haven't life in a
F****** hard labor camp
Man I'm stupid I think he really took those
You wouldn't steal a car would you
Commercials a little bit too seriously
Remember is that like a whenever like movie piracy was kind of
A real good before movie review like Ben Affleck
Any real life
Hey guys
We need to support the industry
You can't be taking
I don't remember him saying or we'll kill you
Or you're going
Intuit labor camp
Hey hey
We understand
Difficult
It's it's a lot easier to pirate movies maybe there's some distribution issues that week
Couldn't fix
But
Don't do it
It's an industry that could die without your
And if you don't
Supported
You will die
These
Sorts of things
Make
It really differ
Buckle to take seriously
The actual things that Alex is talking about like interviewing this Belgian is trying to advocate for
Civilians caught in a warzone
Like it
It's tough
To see this is
Worthwhile
Even
The things that are valid
There worthwhile use of time
Because
I guess if you're the sort of person who thinks that you're going to be killed for using Napster skin
I don't
I don't know what you can bring to the conversation about this Belgium
Well I mean bye-bye elevating the steaks
Of a Napster download
You you're like oh no
Human trafficking is a huge problem in the end all this s*** in your like
Yeah but the stakes are the same as
Pirating from Napster man like your devaluing other problems by making just
Torrent
Describe make a farce out of just
About everything
So Alex gets another call from a guy
This was
This was weird I didn't know what to make of that okay
Started coming out with any
3 days
Today's date
Newspapers
Is
Being ran by
Starcom
Would you the website
Very similar to what you do
This morning
The Rave
Organizations
Okay
Okay well I didn't
Don't judge Porter
Not on my show what is this
The fuc
Girl from Wilderness.com that's what he did that's what he just said
Who's confused
So I went to check out the wilderness.
Something
Different
It's just like an
A survivalist
Store
Online they sell like gun parts and things that you might need
For the outdoors
The only thing that really
Stuck out to me is that they very prominently support the NRA
And I think that that might be Alex
Cuz bone with a
Maybe they got into a fight
Because in 2003 our tape the NRA I forgot about that
You only like more extreme gone or go
Translation
In 2003
Other than that I'm like I don't know maybe it's personal
Like it maybe it's personal between the person who runs that site and Alex
He supported the NRA where is Alex prefers gunownersofamerica
Andrews for the preservation of firearm rights
Yeah but
The way you said I'm not going to talk
About people do that says
Spiraled out of control I can't imagine why I mean you would need some sort of anger
Addicted is some sort of man who
Control his impulses
To elevate an argument about the NRA into a friendship ending
You know what those still is indicative of a level of control That You Don't See from Alex in the present day
I'm not going to talk about this
I do want to talk about people
Not something we here today Brian stelter look weird
Exit
Strange
What are the things I've noticed
Going back on these 2003 episodes
Is there I think the Alex views his job
Here's how it works
Some guy
Headlines for a couple minutes up
Sure just read headlines like a news reader
Couple minutes at the end of the show
3 hours in
Read some more headlines
It's about how you open and close strong in the open
Reader Hitman news but I am a journalist diabetic care business you can take whatever calls you want
Talk to
The drummer from The Black Keys mom
Do whatever hey in an hour set usually you can only take about 20 minutes off in the middle but it's
If your dude Infowars you can take about 2 hours and 45 off I think I'd be fighting kind of enjoy that but I have noticed that
It seems very intention
Now
This is one of the news stories that Alex
Decides to hit
At the end of the
The show
We don't get involved
Report
Because the only
Squabbling
Rum
When it was
William
Your launcher
And it goes on and on there will be a massive
About 20%
Legos
That's not a news story
No
That's a gold plug
Yeah guys
A news story
X2 not at any point
Declare
That he is syndicated by Ted Anderson who owns Midas resource
He is at 100%
Affiliated with Genesis communication
That work
And
Is that kind of a protracted thing
You know what you're talkin about gold news
You should be in Gold 5% you're crazy if you're not
Like
Financial advice
That's a commercial
For gold that is being masturbated
Is a news story
That's f*****
That's a commercial in 2003 they get too little pat on the head
From Ted Anderson in
Bobcat
Men's ears start to get a little bit hot
I might have a job soon
Right cuz you don't want on the show Alex isn't talking about Vitus resources but guess what
Commercials
That might as resources puts
Send forth himself
Alma Street yep
So like if you are Alex
And you're talking about
How everybody should be in gold
Has people who are listening to the show
They will hear the commercials for Genesis Communications
Put two and two together
As good as a commercial for
Fremitus
At the end of this
I just think
I think it's sleazy
Infowars was ahead of the game on hidden
Spawn con
You know is it took awhile to trickle up to the New York
F****** times but we got
#this s***
About the future everybody made it worse
So you know if you look at this
You got you got a pretty interesting
Dynamic
You have the
De-baathification still not being a real thing to Alex
That's what I find
Bizarre you have
The devil question still be up
A bit open to little bit open
But
You have
Bees
Prediction
Stuff
Like I'd I just ate it's very gratifying to me when you you live in a time when everyone's trying to
Hero-worship Alex's past belief
Yeah and you just go back in you
Your Glimpse and episode where he has no idea how the UN secretary-general ship works
You makes
Sweetly stupid prediction
About the other political dynamic
Paradigm
That are going
Going to evolve
There's a bush got re-elected in 2004
That is true good on a
Buddy
Sad sad display
You know what you listen to Clinton
Like that's the thing that does get to me like
That Clinton being like you should come by
Maybe we shouldn't have those term limits
Like I hate those people so much
We already have the clintons around every f******
Corner
In the conspiracy world
Since they shut the f****** in Arkansas
I've always had
The clintons in my life
Causing problems
I'm tired of them make them go away if you are Bill Clinton
And you're giving the speech at the John F Kennedy Library out of notably
Young Presidents actually have a sincere belief
That
Organizing
Then I was the political system could be done better if
Someone were able to come back
Sure Office later
Why should you have to not
Say that just
Because conspiracy theorist will be weird about it
I'm saying that they should be
God
Just go into an island
Forever Epstein got one open
You guys have already been
I'll be back
Movieweb.com
Go to bed Jordan
Omniome Leon dzx Clark
And now here comes
Alex
Birthstone colors