Alexandra Thurston color
We had a little hitch there
Don't know what's going on in my head
Alright podcast professionalism
Cut this out and redo the intro
God damn do that now you're calling me out after split
Stutter
It's not you
What's the round-trip novelty beverages
You know everything about
Pretty much
I don't know anything
There's another one of the bottles of juice
Very tired
Which is the whole point of getting this
So tired that I dropped
This is excuses
I forget the coconut juice and now I forget this
It is organic
Hibiscus
It's a Chia Vitality colloidal
Disgusting look
Okay
To take this out dropper by dropper and put it underneath
I agree I think so
This is the Alex Jones beverage
The fiber I'm going to take a sip of this
Oh my God
I don't want to try this
It tastes good but
It seems to me like a drinking yogurt
Just swallow it
Not chance
You have to get you
You to swallow your tongue
Seeds every time
Hindu
Anyways
It's it's like tiny boba
June 23rd 27th
Episode of The Alex Jones Show
Oh boy
The president's been going on
Skip
Last week of listening to him in the present
Megan Kelly interview I was like
I don't want to listen to him brag
I don't want to listen to gloat for a week about the main stream media
Until I retreated
The 2015
Right time in my studies of 2015
As opposed to listen to him jack himself off on the air
However we got to check in
See what's going on
Guy
I checked in today
And recording is on Tuesday
Owen Shroyer
Summer and they were talking about the CNN video
I'm assuming that
It got a name like James O'Keefe behind it it's either
Painting of a vagina flower or it is b*******
It is
That there isn't any evidence of trump
Russia collusion
Higher-ups
Are pushing those stories because of rating
Made it to James O'Keefe production
You know this when he's involved
Project Veritas is involved it's not true
Is justice
Good through-line
So
Alex called and talked about how
James O'Keefe has just
Killed
Alex is calling into the show.
And I can hear tropical birds in the background
So I'm sure he's on a vacation he's not
Calling a
I went back to Monday
Mission to stay exactly
Do birds learn to talk
Spoiler alert
Talkative
What if you yell globalist of the tropical bird what happened
Empirical Studies have shown
They are globalist
So who trained them to y'all globalist
It's obviously Soros exactly money
Turn soros's going into tropical
First thing that they say
Introduce each other
Short valisure Japanese Global absolutely
Respectful of course me what you do is
If you
Go up to a bird
And you say globalist and it says globalist
No big deal
But if you go if you go to a bird and its globalist first
That means you're close to one of their word out
Okay there are murdered out cuz it's already
That makes the least amount of sense of anything I've ever heard in my entire life
I'm thinking of the dream-quest of unknown
Cadet
The Lovecraft
Echocardiogram
Today
Well good to be back
So I went to Mondays episodes
You see what's going on there
Steve Alex
Was there or if he's been gone
He was gone it was Owen Shroyer hosting
Episode for us to cover
Sunday
Has been gone all week
Right so I go back to Friday
This is Friday 23rd
2017 we're going to be covering
Discovered in the first hour of the show
Lunacy
Hellboy
Really irresponsible and very dangerous
And maybe not as funny as I want this to be in there
But I listen to the whole thing and you know he doesn't interview with a guy named Max Keiser
Is another one of his
Faulty intellectual
The economic
You know he has his Gerald
Valente's and
Harry dent
Peter Schiff
These types
You come in and tell everybody that says it's about to go bad
The real twist
He's so boring
But I didn't
Cut any of this
This interview
Ball from the buy gold
Cuz he is
Ingles pretty cool
What does Max Keiser guy
What do you also say
Is
Hey
Get my
Now that's a good move right there
Excel Mac
Coins
That
Publix
I didn't realize you could just do that
Worth something like $0.20
But it
Came up from like
Be that as it may
If you responsible to sell gold
Get on your show when you're fear-mongering about an economic collapse
It's very irresponsible to tell your own currency
I know but
That's I love it I love it
Go f****** b****
Yeah now it's like coins coming soon
I'll look into it
I don't want I don't want to make my own economy
Like a lot of work
Camarones
That's what we've always want
Digital money
I just feel like it's more hassle than it's worth and then if someone falls out of knowledge fight coins
We are responsible for
Screwing over so many people well it was only usable at Disneyland
Nations in Disney World
Look and feel like we lost a lot of money on that traits right
Disney World is
Globalist Disneyland
Small big small this f****** say
Episode
I'm going to start
We'll just go exactly where he begins the episode of fun thing whenever I choked
To death on chia seeds
Wow Friday Waging War on corruption is Alex Jones
Do You Love by Gwar
I want to stop there because I
He says that every day
Well first of all hell's breaking loose.
Breeze's it's hard to believe it's already blank.
He says that all the time I kind of think that's Charming on a little that it's kind of like
A little broadcaster
All this time has passed
Another Day Has Come and gone and we are still alive and I kind of like it
All hell's Breakin loose
All right you've smelled breaks loose
Switch very fast
He's starting to show what he wants
They're scared right now
Globalist
Going to start calling Disney World
Previous records
Each one of the four failed special election since President Trump sworn in on
January 20th
2017 from Washington
The people
Deliverance in
Royals page
And the globalist
Russia
Re-entry freakout mode
35 million
Special election
How much are the Republicans Birdsboro
Spoiled brat
Power
Is Awakening
Klingon to the host the parasites are in a
Insane
That is a run-on sentence
Oh absolutely
I have
We're just we're just going from okay the globalist
Because they lost four consecutive special election
HD Democrat
Farro
Performed previous election
Far closer than they should have one of them
Wasn't one of them a bit too
Georgia was the Asif race was very much
Everybody kind of predicted a far better
Yeah but you know you got to pick this other lady who hates gay people
Ya got to do it
She doesn't think they're real
Fine
Put her in Concord
I'm trying to find
Just how much the Republic
Install the Republican Spectrum
Now the problem is
They have so much
Because their best
Are billionaires
Best friend
Billionaires but not as many
And Union
I don't have a whole lot in the coppers
There are a few billionaires
How did we get to they have our kids
Public School
What
I don't know but that's
Betfair last
Chance
I guess I guess
Maybe
That doesn't sound like a bad son
No
I mean we're full of a lot of bulshit
Straight Out The Gate because he's misleading about all these special elections
He's not dealing with the fact that like
If you look at the actual
Statistics on the Republican should be worried
About the turnout
About
Results
Even though they want it does indicate
Bad thing
A coming because all of those were heavy
Republican-leaning areas
D I swear to God
I've been sitting here I wanted
I want to listen to the last
You said replicas
I know I didn't
You totally.
No
I could not be
Oh my God
And that
Is my favorite thing to refer to myself
How can you be sure I'm very confused about I might be reading too much Phillips
That's what the Republicans
The replicant
But Alex's high-minded
He's talking politics he's talking taking our kids
That episode
What a meeting
Potato special election
Sims were so close
And how it's a really is
A good thing for the Republic
A-1 Auto
When you expect
This huge
They would have lost
Even that he's going to spend it as you know if you want to look at the truth Republican should have one major
And all of them
Light a fire under Republican 2A.
Complacent after the last election
Nope punch
He does not deal with me
A meth head
What's some other Waterhead
And they stand up there and talk about how
A dream about killing the president
Another piece of Filth
If you don't love it get out
Classic
There are more countries besides
North Korea
The think global global
Yeah probably has houses in Malta
Principal Alex North Korea
Text Billy
Came out
I'm stuff
Last week
Alex
Might spend most of his show.
He is furious
For those of you don't know what Johnny Depp said I will play the clip a little bit later
Labadee
You saying that
Donald Trump needs help
He's responding to a question clearly and
Goes on to say
Practice is it by saying
This is going to be in the present
It's going to be terrible
He says I'm not
I'm not saying anything
But when was the last time
An actor assassinated the president
That's not bad Pizza joke
It's not a good joke that's not bad at all
Homeless looking
Which is what you think of when you think Johnny
He goes on to say I'm not an actor
Ilife
But you know what it is
You picking on a lot of
The traits of Hunter S Thompson
He has he's using all restaurants in sort of
Younger mannerisms
He's just acting like Hunter S Thompson
Yeah that's all he's doing for a life
That would Hunter S Thompson dead
His spirit
For good or bad
Seems to live in Johnny Depp
Hey you do what movie with him in and there you go
If I had to like trying to that headspace
To do Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas
Maybe I'll go crazy too
And maybe that's not the point you went crazy
Beautiful
Like it's a joke it's a dark joke
Plays on the fact
Like I said
I'm not going to
Ticket Club
There's awareness within a
It's not like a
Threat or anything like that
He refuses it by saying I'm not an actor
I'm not saying anything I'm not going to do
Stories about it
He takes it
Real art
And we'll get to you some of his reaction
But I think you're a little bit over-the-top
He gets to an article with Paul Joseph Watson has written
And he makes a very interesting offer
To an unknown
Named woman
Yep some spoiled pension fund government-funded
College scholarship
First class tickets
Remove
One year
Libya
Are the Siri I'm sorry those are Total War zones Thanksgiving people
Come on without the Pay-Per-View
Muslim
Muslims
Globalist minions
Daughters
Anna Sun
North Korea
Invaders
Play the end
Horrible end
To that
That piece
Chunk
Vets
To be heard.
That was the most
The cost of living in Saudi Arabia
A decent to a one-bedroom apartment but $700 a month
So I mean
Copper bowl food
Little donut
11:00 or something like that
Hell it's going to take him up on the driver
I feel like it's actually safer there right
I would
Probably go
Yeah I'd like to travel but also I don't
Because I have my job and all
Would be difficult but presuming I was
You know fancy-free and careless
Don't do that
Phuc yea
I like my job
That's weird
That's pretty weird
Yeah Walton why did he
Why did he put it in lb
I think
Paul Joseph Watson
So Alex is not going to
Target at a Quran
You should stop offer
Clearly clearly he doesn't have $30,000
Throw around
But
You made a very astute
Observation
Took his brain Force
I am
I think he definitely did
And this clip
I'm in my Infowars uniform today
Sports
Because I need to be
I got my balls on the table
She'll get ready
He just called himself tuck buckford
Oh yeah he called himself these bacon character
Because he really
Reclaim it
That's a smart move
I think
Recently Alex put out a video
It was convoluted
When did receive
Played a character named tuck buckford
Now I'm again
He had a wig on
He was a liberal guy
Who Alex Jones ripped off
Alex Jones ripped off the original tuck box for a character
Personality or whatever
I meant Stephen Colbert
Is ripping off Alex
But there's a Realtek buckford who is a super liberal and very angry
Hey it so he brings out a pinata of trump
And starts attacking
It's creeping
It
Convoluted
Wait so I really encourage people to watch everything he's done
But because it's such a mystery I do support people watch
Okay so
Stephen Colbert
FaceTime Alex
Yes
Alex Jones
A liberal
Trying to murder the
Pinata
Yeah
Yeah I see no problems with understanding that at all how could you have a
And its construction I think
I think he
Now I don't want to disparage his writers
But I think it's possible that not a lot of them are good at,
Possible
RAB do
Write me a sketch
Libertarian
Paul Joseph Watson tries to be
B status
Take a note
But it's the same time
Him just calling himself tuck buckford on the show right there
Is a little f***** up but you're right that is kind of reclaiming like
Do you think you can make fun of me I have
Absorb your insult
Can only become stronger because of
If you hadn't made that video 100% agree about it
That one doesn't support that
Not much
Every gets back
Screaming about how
The next few
Things that we have to get through our like straight-up ramp
Was it these on he's in Rambo today
Really going after the
Pinata or was he just kind of like a
And then he starts
Hearing Trump's face off
Like in a way that
Hi interpreted as
He's mad at Trump
He's actually very mad at Trump for having to do the things that he's doing there is a level of like type
Something getting out yeah
It feels very cathartic
There's a textual analysis we could do of like
That's real you really mad at that pinata
It's also really dumb
Either that or either
Has anybody considered putting them in
Hollywood Feed
I think one guy
And that's about it
This next clip he misleads more about those special election
Mni's really tries to wind up as audio
I don't put a good face on things
That's reasonably true
- say something
Unnecessarily
Now things are kind of roses
Yeah I can't remember the last time where is like everybody
Don't worry about a thing today we're all good he does a bit withdrawn
Numbers are in Snowflake
Results
We've defaults to the negative
Globalist
Benewah Vista
But
Right now
Wishing for special elections
Will the Democrats spending more money than other elections
And they lost
People voting with
Illegally
Call David confirmed on coming out the last election but still they lost
Debate questions
Weeks before to Hillary
Trump called it out but still on
Forget to the Superbowl for NBA basketball this is the real game of life
For the future of America and the world
How about hot versus slavery
This is such an amazing powerful
Transmission today he really thinks it will be
Mostly just talked about Johnny Depp
But
Did the stuff in there that
Looks like
You got to really take away is
His examples of trump being like
A man that we must
Emulate
Brave
Someone gave Hillary Clinton questions ahead of time
Announcers were mean to him
That's not
That's not really that great
I'm a big fan of how
Borradaile of winning that election
Also that
Oh no that's terrible
Really hard very hard he was completely and utterly
An oblivious of what the responsibilities
Illegals voting
If you really number comes from
Actually really fast
Million illegals voting
A dumb tweet
Was insane which still hasn't that guy on Twitter still hasn't to back that up
How did the number get higher
It was done by Old Dominion
Sound like 36
Respondent
39 of them responded that they were illegal immigrants
Who
To have photos
So
There's a couple pieces of the
That are problematic
Interviews
Showed a bunch of people I think there were 20 in
Instances
How people do in the initial
Survey said that they were citizens
I'm going to follow up interview said that they weren't
Which is statistically impossible
There's no way
That the respondents
20 people would lose their citizenship
So it indicates a lack of
Care in the people who
We're filling out the survey
It was like a hundred plus question
On the survey
People speculate
That the methodology of it was
Was flawed
And people weren't giving correct dance
So forgiving
100 correct
Never
I've never paid attention
To 100 question
7 million is a high-end estimate 100000 to 5
7 million
That people have speculated
Based on this 39 respondents
So they just multiply
The population at Large
Statistics
They're I don't know what the
How they got these responding
But I do know that a lot of people who do surveys
End up doing them
Through these services
That are available
Through Amazon
They have a system called
Twerking
Where you can sign up
A user
MMA pay you like
$0.30
To do a survey
Tractor like bounce your ass up
Sundown
No
No that's something else that's something else that's twerking
Oceans is closed but
Universities a lot of research centers
Have
Conn's
Responses that they need
And they pay people like a nickel or a dime to fill out surveys to psychological
And prescription work
Work on this Amazon portal
But they have
I don't know for sure
If this is what they use
But if it is
I've seen studies like it
On on these
Hummus perking site
And I also know
Because they're getting paid
Like $0.10
For survey so they speed through them
They just
Fill out bubble
So they can try and make a living wage
On it or at least make a decent amount of money
Possible based on the anomalies that are found with the
People reporting
That they didn't
They lost their citizenship and stuff like that
It's entirely possible that a large section of the people responding to the survey work
So that's entirely possible but be that as it may even if it is all sincere respondents
39 people out of 30000
Is not a large enough
Sample size to be demographic
We interesting
And many many professors
Have written
About how this study is not something
To be cited
It's not it doesn't pass muster
Statistical ethics
There's
How could that many
Illegal
Citizens
Possibly vote
2%
Of the total
For what
It's two and a half 3% of
The total population
7 million out of
It's more like 200
Right
So that means that you
Gaunt
To the voting booth
With an illegal
Many of them probably
At your polling station
You Are by like
Raise your hand if you're an illegal citizen
Citizen
That's why your migration
Chicago is like
2 million people
Two and a half million people so that's like
25 of the entire population of Chicago
Across the country vote
It seems
It seems ridiculous
It's absolutely
People
Like if you're using this this
Debunked
Statistic about the last general election
Curry point
With the special elections in
Vicarious
Aurum in Atlanta
But be that as it may
Like it doesn't
You have no statistic
Nickelback this up
You're just too
Really work is audience
Send you a fever
This is freedom vs. slavery
This is the most important Battle of all of our lives
I'm at something important
Because that sort of ethos
Fatheads
Is where he lives
Right now
Today
The current date
Jedi vs Sith
The current day of the show is not fun
Because
He's legit at War
Like anybody anybody listening
Who's crazy
I think they would
They could really could really hurt somebody
It's not like he's saying anything illegal
Football
And we're going to get to some of it it's just
Hey listening to this bum me out especially after listening to 20
At least in 2015 he's
Not trying to get people
Interesting idiots
He is oh no.
So let's get let's go
He wants to talk about some headlines
WWE style promo
About the global
Property
So real quick the lady who said that Trump is like a suicide bomber
Was saying that you shouldn't cuddle up to him
Because he's going
To destroy
Sort of a warning to.
This is a dangerous thing
Dante is literally, everybody is aware of
Nobody in the GOP is paying
Much of these bombers
We were following them
Be that as it may
The other thing you talkin about is
MSNBC analyst said we should blow up Trump Tower
Again that was
That was that same one forwards like
If I were nominated
The first most likely can
Malcolm Nance was just on Realty
With Bill Maher
Breitbart editor was on with him
They were disgusting
Effective fake news
Stuff like that
Story that Alex
Talking about
Malcolm was like
You know
Something you posted on your site
Head Called Death Row
I have gotten
And my family have gotten death
Because of something that you lied about on your side
And the guy was like
Well I'm going to have to look at that I don't know how early bulshit
Tootsie bear look into that
I don't know every story that goes up on the site that sort of Dodge
Actually don't know what his position was or anything
Was Bannon
Be there
Yeah but be that as it may Alex is like on that same tip
He's on the same story
And for all we know he might be the one who's responsible for Malcolm Nance
I mean it's not
True the story
Dickies telling is not true and there's real-world harm that comes from pitching those parody
Play how do we know
That it's not
That's a really good point
Considered that Malcolm Nance
Is
Sending his family.
False flag
Could be that
It's possible from all angles
If everything's works whenever you feel like your wife
I could die at any moment.
Monica stories
Is saying are not really true
How many the Mika Brzezinski did say that Trump has established
Take a lot of people feel that way
He mischaracterizing
The bombers sort the suicide bomber story
Mischaracterized
But even then is mischaracterization of the suicide
How many years like a suicide
Like I would say even
Out of contacts if somebody was just like
Trump is like a suicide bomber I be like yeah he's trying to destroy the entire country
Or blackmail whatever
Situation
70 f****** years old
Done everything it needs to do anyways
Play sing about Trump Jr
Professor
MB
Professor from Trinity University wrote a blog post called let them f****** die
The blog post if you read it is about
There are a lot of
But it's but it's basic
There are people
Well I got Trinity behind me now little more eloquent on the Fly it's like
How to write something down I'm sure it would be every
Actually would probably just be
The bug
Assets
Is about how there were a lot of people who are up
Can people by Race by gender
He's laying out is really an argument he wants to make
And that is that you will not get any brownie points from big
It's for saving their lives
Call f******
No you will not you are being
If you
Let's say run into a burning building
To save a bigots life
If you were a doctor and you save a bigots life
We live in this fantasy in our head
That like I was saved by a black person
You know
Hallmark movie
It doesn't
Work like that generally in the real world
We're coming to a crisis
This point and you if you are in a disc
Franchise class
Should never put yourself at risk
To help someone
Who hates you
You there are black.
In hospitals
Specifically pointed out by people
I don't want that doctor to hell
Turn higher
There
You should give out a questionnaire like do you want to Black.
Emergency rooms
With black doctors in the
Just let white people
I'm totally fine
People
I don't know the argument that he's making tell from the from the stomach
The argument is laid out in that blog is not like
Actively go murder people
Don't
Don't exert any effort to save people's lives
As I said
Don't give a s***
Again
You're not happy that he got shot
Cineworld
Could not have been shot
Yeah I wish that were I wish I were pause
Yeah
He has held architect of world
That has led to him getting shot
The world is a better place without him
Yeah
Because of mass
Mental illness
Re-education camps
Third culture bombs
Implosion right now
Bumpers
Who released the bio-weapon
Set
Insanity
That's that's
He's already said that we're against the globalist
Bye-bye new Alex Jones Brandon Walker
Only with
Deep Earth
Steel
What's the stopping power of a 9 mm
Never really experienced for college
So I
Discount is a penny
Quite a bit
This situation with this
Professor at Trinity
And people are pretty mad about it
And I wonder I wonder what
The situation at Evergreen happened a little bit ago
Like within the last month
That's a day of absence
Situation I think that's a little bit more nuanced than the people are really giving up Reddit
I think there's arguments on both sides
The professor did not
I have the obligation to leave
But I think
He's being a f****** a****** for not
Has wavered and then changed to
Come on
Yeah they also I mean sure the administration at schools acting a little bit weird
But also
I don't I don't really care I think you could have left campus
F****** come on you don't have the right to not
I have actions that are dickish that you do not make you a shitheel
Like you are kind of an a****** you should be treated like it
Even if you make a principled stance
Again
Something that is
The reality is
Come on man
The reality to is
That those schools that had to be closed
Because of bomb threat
I am murder
Devastated
Quite literally are devastated
I will give them
Call
Is a culture bomb only in the Sun
But when you go to it you're exposed
Things you would not be exposed to otherwise
Challenges
Your growth
Those are the things
That happened on most college camp
Not liberal indoctrination
Or anything like that that's a load of horseshit
I think the best liberal inductive
Of course meeting
People
In a homogeneous
If you meet people on a global scale
You start to have a global world
Yeah absolutely
The reality of all this is
You know more nuanced
Maybe slightly controversial things
People are saying
That
Strictly speaking racist
Or I would never call the guy the professor at Evergreen races
For his actions
Like I said it's kind of an a******
A butt
The reaction is decidedly right
All the threats that have made these schools closed down
Are not because
Liberals
Yeah it is liberal kids finally waking up to the
Patriots and so they're finally getting out of it
And the way that they express their
Threatening to murder lots of
What you do you know what I was going to think about you I've come to realize that on a certain level every generation
It's kind of like a new operating
System we have to reboot a little bit
It's so
Maybe it's not strictly speaking every generation
But every now and again
Fairies like a cultural
Upgrade
To our system that happen
Racial understanding
Another one was
Homosexual
Lifestyle understanding
Another one
Trans understanding
And it's not always as cut-and-dry as those thing
But I think that we reboot a little bit
And we we have to integrate our worldviews
Is a process that a lot of people are resistant to
Cuz they're like no I love
Nintendo
The original
No I don't want
Super Nintendo
But there are everybody
Sundials are arguably very reliable
There's there are people who hold on
To like no I don't want to be taken away from the old operating system but I'm very comfortable
I have to learn
To be accepting it
Understand
View of humanity
Avocation
Easily had that response
X
Stop and
Think through it
Before I special
It's part of the system upgrade is
Resistance to grow through that
I was fine and it was the first time that somebody is like we don't say that
Has like that come on and write about it
That's a part of the upgrade
It's better it doesn't hurt
But some people are like 5 upgrades
Like
The thing is
College students
Are kind of like
They have a beta version of the Opera
I don't need beta-like
Beta Alpha I mean like it's
It's not it's a little glitchy
They run the program put their Hardware is
And so often they end up being really bad and bassadors of a good thing
Yeah I'm so you have these college students come out
And they end up getting on TV
Let me say crazy
Where what they mean is
But what they're saying is
Really unpolished
And bad for television
So
People like Alex who's resistant to cultural upgrades to a
Instagram
See these college kids saying dumbass
I defend the spirit of but not belittle letter I was right
White people
He's just making fun of the
Like it's like someone playing an early release of the video game
Everything like
Not realizing that the polished version of it isn't it
Credible game
I am not entirely certain whether or not
Amazing metaphor or a
Tortured metaphor that you really ran through the ringer I don't know either
Either that is a
It's like either you hit the nail on the head with that metaphor
Through the whole thing you got from starts
Finish on it
Situation
Endless all got it
We all got an instant we all figured it out immediately
I bet I can move this run other Ted Bundy really wanted to get to was the idea of the college
Being a glitchy version of a good
It's really easy to make fun of kids
Not being adults
Due to certain degree
Will find out
If I'm an idiot
So someone who isn't
Alex
Most of this episode deals with Johnny Depp
I am
How can
Mediocre at best joke
Well your gums are at
Drug addict meth head looks like
Trying to act cool
Stevie Ray Vaughan to play the guitar
Is a joke stumbling around
Liberal
Listen to put up with
Drugged out so brainwashed
A bunch of
Moronic
My numbed zombie looking twit fan when he says
Just hold on God
I just said something
Jumped on the whole bandwagon of other
America
Muslim
Western Civilization
They want they want
It's such a pathetic
Just adjusting
Drugged out with Meth mouth
Politically
Dogcraft
Hollywood Cinema
Play johnnyswim ball death
I think he needs help
Royal Rumble.
Start places you could go
Doc Martens
Just a question I'm not insinuating anything by the way this is going to be
I like the last time
Mattress fascinated with president
Seriously
Elijah living
How does
Alex
Spiritually ripping off Hunter S Thompson 2
Except I'm not
So why we need another one
I was trying to keep up with
All of the insult
I don't
You look
He might have at some point
I'm sure he does a lot of Coke
Who does it matter
Is too cheap.
Also
I mean if you're going by that
Speed of speech
Definitely not doing meth
Caden
City Futsal
Dr. Gonzo Style
Yeah it's
If it's a version of cool to have
Just wanted to say you're putting on an SX station
You are not
You're not this cool
But you can
You can't get the child molester after
That's kind of an object
Do you like you look like a child molester Stevie Ray Vaughan to pull that off in Haiti
I don't know
He would not feel sorry for her not hateful political you do not
A little bit
Goodwill
Be the first to be like I love
I love Johnny Depp in
Elm Street
Breakout rue21
Let's face it
The first Pirates movie
Wasn't that bad
He did a great job
Epic I loved it bright
Sure he said some things that I don't agree with but
He's dead
We got a receipt
Fine the other thing
That I'm most
Defended by in there is Alex
He uses Dutch safe
Speech but he's threatening
Johnny Depp's wife
There's nobody else to hear that
Other than
I want someone to kill Johnny killed for running his mouth
He's implying that he hopes
Sooner also the
Someone can find out where you are and pump a bunch of bullets in you
I don't want that
Yeah
Alex
Is irresponsible cuz
He does not
Recognize how crazy
His fans are
Like
He knows
He doesn't apply the requisite caution
If we had
Caution
Have the fan
Right but that's irresponsible to humanity
Will ya
Okay well
Alex Jones is bad for human
And this next one
I wish
If there's
One thing that I
Think should be restricted
In his free speech
Is he's not allowed to say the word
No situation
He has said multi
They they screw up and they take advantage of America's open this
Kindness
Cute do not understand that that's
Are open
We're talkin about something and the thing that he's attacking
Is the cousin the only way you should be able to say the word kind
The first said
But people who are kind
We must abolish.
Anybody want let's open this
Restrict our borders we won't stop all this b******* like all these Advil
4 is closed
Except as a relates to God
And
And of course
He wants true diversity
Just means what
If you if you want to put the word truevine diversity that
Do you know what you could say I want Diversey
Which means I want all kinds
The people here
Yeah. Like
Good diver speaking of true diversity
Lookout cuz on our next episode where we're doing our investigation
Spoiler alert
Alex Jones
Does get David Duke on the show
Hey talk to him for 2 hours
Yeah
That's going to be a whole episode
G Dragon
Wild anti-semitic conspiracy theorist David Duke
Holy s*** I look forward to that also look forward to this
Alex
Raps
Violent rhetoric a little more
Look at
Kill his family
The Property Brothers
Add
14 killing people
You live in the lap of luxury acted tough and cool all day
I want to say like I don't know what like
I don't know what calling for someone's recovery is going to do I don't know how much it's going to help this isn't like a
Tinkerbell situation
Although I don't know how how negative
Calls for someone's recovery is
Also I mean if you're booing somebody's calls for
Recovery it's like
Well neither of us
Call Jill
You know what you know what I
Here's the thing
Just now
Realize that
That phrase
Running your mouth
Always
Suggest violence
Solutions
He's running
Like that's what
He's running his mouth kind of suggest
So punch him
Close his mouth
That you know if your if you say something like always
Talking out of school
Good-natured ribbing
Running your mouth
Is always
I don't know but at the same time running your mouth
Connotation
I feel like it's I think it's
I think it's in the realm of
This might just be you
It could just be
And it's because I
Starting to run your mouth
No idea
I go for David Brock in older people
About operation
We're aware of all the different
Scientists engineers the surgeons
And their sutures
And their instruments
Cast to get cut out
Enter the patient
Surgery
Pleasure
I think it's clearly fused into one
That's a lot of wars Civil War start is you never really have a demarcation line whenever shot heard around the world
7075 twin
The world
And
You can hardly walk
I saw a clip of a wall
How all of this works
And so
You're not calling you Civil War you're saying you wanted Insurrection Trump supporters
Publications by Obama's
We're going back to the rant in a second
Understand that one
New elections run by Obama
This is one of the
Fears that Alex Jones has that
Obama's National Security
It's only based on the fact that
Obama Russian meddling in
In the election in the lead up to it
Smeg
Our election
A piece
Of federal
Protected it's
Right
To push through
And Alex Jones
Interpreted that as
Bedroom lamp
Yeah I would say automatic voter
History and federal election
It's probably the best
Get rid of the Electoral
Pro-collagen
That's probably not a terrible idea
Alright alright
Guns
You take us from
Powerful to incredibly powerful
Listen to Martyrs you take us to the next level
Episode 4 Star Wars
We become more powerful
History
As long as we're focused as long as we have courage and as long as we don't you're going to lose
Korea
We have set up a dictatorship
Images of China
Under vassal control
Orthodox Christian
Get that music
Antichrist
That's a real f*****-up way. Wait wait
Alright well
I can't even deal with Hollywood everything
Is movie reference
Everything everything is movie or music video in this page
Reference 22
You know predictive programming
Really surprised
To me about the Run
Spreading
Like I
Occasionally talked about how
You know friends
Talk about how that
But
I don't understand why
He's saying that it's happening worldwide now other than if
Sing about he's talking about like brexit
Kelley's bringing up Korea is bringing up African-American or little
No goodnight in that
Since he's talking about how you
You can't take away freedom in America because we have your trying to oppress up as opposed to
Never had it
Much easier
To keep them in the
Depressive state
In North Korea
He was not
What the
Is going worldwide is
References
Is 2
Lappin brexit
You wouldn't say Russia but he does
They call that kicked out the oligarchs they're just trying to take out the global
Yeah that's why everyone hates Global influence
Imagine and inter
Another world
That
Believe
Russia
X Out etiology
Maybe they kicked out the old
And replace them with the new ones
That's Russia Alex's version of the New Renaissance
So these countries
Cdm's out as having kicked out
Or kicked out the globalist
Does it work
Fought back again
Like why would
But then we have to
Really get into Howie's
Globalist
Works we can't do that
Because
How can you
Be like
Look at these other countries they're doing things
Write any of the same time say
We don't need to worry about any other countries it's all about America
So if you're spreading
If you're spreading this like
Renaissance narrative going worldwide
Talking about is just the growing Mash
Analyst
Which is
B I don't understand why you think that's a good idea
It's like every country to be
Like their own version of America
The first
Country to be partially nationalistic in
Xenophobic and close their borders
Not realizing that the end result of that is
Everyone
Yeah it it will turn things back to like city-state
What parts of countries will secede
You will just have
Sweet destruction
Any kind of international cooperation which is
I mean I would be a positive goal
But
He conveniently leaves off the part where everyone
Interest will butt into each other in ways
That we do not
Have
At that point
Anyway to negotiate International bodies like the UN
Or the EU
They can negotiate and resolve issue
Issue before they turn into
You know all our war
Remember how Europe was always at War for forever
Is the inevitable result of his everyone should be harshly Nash
Holistic
Think he's right when he says Civil War
End result of that
At least what is the United States most Libertarian
Is kind of stupid
In terms of like
The outcome that you want isn't
The outcome that's going
To come
You know what
It just indicates of like a deregulation
That the conservatives and Libertarians want so
They think it is
Like a boost to the economy
But all you're going to end up doing is empowering people who already have
All of the businesses will be able to run roughshod over our enter
And we'll never get to this happy face
Eland
It's on the other end any historical
Where in
Regulation
Was Adam
It was
The 20s
Not a lot of Regulation back then
You know what I want to bring back those Coal Mine children
And you know what kellyanne Conway said about
Healthcare Bill 30 million kids are going to get kicked off Medicaid what are we going to do with them put them
Schools are Jeffrey education can wear
Work camps
That's not a terrible things moving
And then we take all these old people who are just f****** sucking off the government at nursing home
Why don't you work at the nursing home
Terrible idea
Alex I believe is that
I don't know it what I don't know what causes
I don't know what to underline
I don't
I think you thought through the reality of the things that he's exposing
Like the idea of
Free-market sounds
Good cuz it's free
You take to get there in the steps that he seems to encourage are all things that will have disastrous consequences
The problem
Withstand
Fremont
Does the same thing
Free market
Is that
You don't realize
How much
How much work goes into
Keeping it
Natural state
No
The natural
It's abusive
It's very powerful people crushing people who have no power
Kind of a thing that you
You get into with with
Just understanding language
Is that to me the idea of a
Free market is everyone
Having
An opportunity to kind of compete
Yeah you know like I think that's a good idea
Equal access
Free market more than that new trial
Everyone is capable of
Equal rate at an equal level
Whatever you deregulate
And
You can charge for Fast Lane
You do not have a free market
You have a closed-off guy
Are already
Participated
Can do so at this level and it makes
Damn near impossible
Lower-tier
And those are
Concrete
Short-term examples
The
Hellscape
That exists on the way to a hypothetical Nirvana
Alex
In the same way
That every country even know if there is
Like a fantasy land at the end of
But in the interim it's just War
I think there is
Feudalism
Humans being eradicated from the earth entirely and it's allowed to grow which is what Alex
Forms are allowed to evolve
I'm starting to be for it
Well your globalist
Anyway
So I prefer the globe
2 what's on it
I like Globes
Civil War
But there's no shot that was heard around the world there's no demarcation line
Different
Demarcation line
Powerful
Pizza deals with other trying to start a Civil War and now we're already
With Congressman scalise get shot
Congress
Women
Republicans
3 years ago 2 years ago
But now it's official.
Demilitarized
Play
We can just hold
Respond
Sublease was shot June 14th
I'd say that's a shot heard round the world
You can argue already in Civil War before that and they're calling for violence and killing the president is family in every major publication
Overthrowing the government
Action Agency
June 14th
That's when the Civil War started
So In that clip Alex's literally say
Hot Civil War has started
Was Augustus
And then he's further saying
We could wait
And let them shoot us
He doesn't say or
He's very clearly
Define why it is
We don't want assault weapon
I think I think it's a great one
They used to say fire until you see the whites of their eyes
Suggesting you should know who it is that you are attacking
Stead
We're just going to hold down the trigger inmobi pulled out and I'm sorry for those of you who get killed
He in that was saying
We could
Patriots
His side
We could wait
Until they kill us
And I'm sorry about those of you who will end up getting killed
What would he conveniently dozen
Do is give the other side of that disjunct
The other side of that
He doesn't get to that
Any other side of that
Implicitly
Yep and if you were someone
Prone
Coming to Hammond
Like a white man
You have no other way to hear that then that implied other side
We can wait until they come and kill us and I'm sorry about those of you were going to die that's a really negative
The implied other side
Maybe
I mean this is really f******
So close to
Openly advocating people start
It's close enough to warrant
Like at the very least invested
I would say it's
Close enough for jazz
Is there a b a
I don't think Alex would like that expression I think he would think you were run
Open your mouth I'm probably
Run your mouth feel your hand
Better than him I don't know
And then just the entire what
Run your mouth feel your hands
On the front
The transcription of the Jihad about Adam Schiff
African grey
Alex
Reading
That's how you learn
Alex
Explains that a
His understanding
Does not understand
Twilight zone is authoritarianism altered so many of worship throughout history always
Liberalism
What is a weapon system
Johnny Depp from Kentucky
Posing
Frozen
Hoping he dies
Benedict Cumberbatch and if somebody kills you
Which I hope doesn't happen one of these other Hollywood
Turds
Wolf Blitzer is the most useless man in the history of the world
Johnny Depp
Ultraviolet
I don't know
A violet what if I kill Nicole Brown
Why do I hope nobody kills her
Sweater
The other thing is you talk about Wolf Blitzer interviewing the guy who knew the guy who shot Steve
The guy said that he was just fed up with politics news a good guy
He mad about that all he wants but
That's really basically what happens with any interview with someone who knew a serial killer
If you watch any documentary about serial killers generally they're like
I never would have predicted this from him
Quiet guy
Self
He was always
Talk
How's the weather
Good
Be the end of our interaction
Serial killer
Alex wants to like complain about like their friends better
But if you want
You know you're lying
I don't think he's broadcasting propaganda by interviewing the guy but his
Potentially limited perspective on the shooter
That's nonsense
Weird weird
Just heard wolves
Now you knew it was a murderer didn't you tell me
Someone get a funding so the other thing
Two though is you talkin about like you know if someone goes ahead and murders Johnny Depp
Or these other Hollywood people
Deterred
Hollywood or wolf
He's throwing Wolf Blitzer even and with that like
People who should be murdered
Yeah it's very dangerous
The type of stuff you saying is incredibly
Aubrey's not.
The Washington Post the New York Times
There
So uncoordinated
No shoot two cops almost killed him and almost killed a congressman almost kill another person
Johnny Depp
What a drugged-out
Debatable
From that club one more time
Somebody that wants to run his mouth and just because
You're going to be held responsible
And your publicist
Organized crime
Projection
How will you be held accountable
Well that's projection of guilt
He's using your massive platform to call for violence
You will be held responsible
I'm probably going to go down
For some of this
Like
We've seen it in the past
We've seen
Repeated instances of his listeners doing the things he says he'd they should do
The guy who broke into Bohemian Grove heavily-armed to kill people
Alex Jones
That lady last month or two months ago
Sending death threats
Do the Sandy Hook parents
Was motivated by Alex Jones
Literally
Reset it
The guy who showed up at Comet Ping Pong with a gun
Motivated by Alex Jones
That's not a hundred percent his
Fault
And besides that I don't think he necessarily should be arrested for those things but the fact that he's so flippant
And disregard
The effect that he has on mentally ill people
Means like
Scenario where that guy who had the gun
Easily could have accidentally
Showed up there to kill people
Accidentally killed
In that case
How does the conversation go differ
Is something that happened with that lady and the Sandy Hook families
If she gets shown up at one of their houses
Like that how is the story
It's only different based on how far you crazy person took
They took it way too far just not
To the extent where now there's death
Steve
I would say if
If we start going around
Recent hate crimes
I'm just started asking around like
Listen to Alex Jones
Bro
I wouldn't be surprised if
I don't know I don't know how solid the reporting on this but from what I've been able to find
Timberland
Tsarnaev one of the Boston bombers was a big in
Infowars
I know Alex is arguing
That he would make
Any of the
Is all this is how the media portrays me as
Crazy person
These false
And then they associate their Patsy with Infowars
In order to turn the public against me
Free meditatively
Okay great
Good
Catalog
You inspire crazy people to do Very Bad Things
That's a good argument
Yeah because you pay all of your enemies
As pedophile you paint them as murderers who want to kill everybody
Use a book you don't understand affordable
So f******
Sane
Every
Everybody is
Is the most evil
It's amazing
To me that you can't
Just criticized
Johnny Depp without bringing it in
He's a child below
You don't like what he said
You don't think he's a very good actor
We can debate that right I saw the revamped Willy Wonka
Yeah
Like you don't need to call him a child
Well and if someone were to like just
Strictly attack Alex
This physique or whatever
Why you got to send
F****** b*******
He would whine
So hard if somebody
If somebody was like
Look at this m************ brainforest mouth motherfuker
Has more to do with Johnny Depp
The news says Howard Jones
Kiki made a guy that has luster
Alex
He's talking about the song
That argument is
2Wire
Not his fault or why he has
Is no real
The gate
Recommend ever want to go find that clip that people should go check it out
Posted
Erroneous false
Information on his website
About the car
And he's just absolutely lying but even then if you just say go check it out
Us
Establish that it is a
Den of
Pedophiles
Traffickers
Murderers the worst
Human being
Available so if you're saying go check it out
What's implied there is
If you check it out on arm
You might get your probably going to die video
The Soviet poster
Of himself going
To Comet Ping Pong
Now you probably kind of drunk
Or hi and that video
Then his friend were even talking about being kind of scared
Going to a family Eatery
It's not that we are totally right. The implied thing there is you might die
So be careful
Alaskan hard-hitting Quest
Seems like it would be a better use
I've seen videos of people who went with cameras
James alefantis
Himself
Went outside
And talk to them
Answer questions
He took one of them inside and showed him all around
Music
Just took him around like
Nonsense
You guys need to be out there protesting
You want a coffee
Super nice to them
I don't normally do this you guys want
Selma by the slice here but listen
You guys seem nice
Night Kitchen
It's all nonsense
That would be the best
Like just
Okay go ahead
It's all true
You guys want some coffee
Witnesses that were there
Trump supporters
Who was an actor
On a already felony plea deal
In another state
Comes in
How does a month after I said drop the story it's a decoy before the Press ever targeted me
So no one ever said he was necessarily the author of A330 pushed it
He was guilty
Of the guy show
Talked about how he was influenced by Alex
Rat in Spanish
Who had other conviction
And the cops came to go do that
Required for that to be true are insane
The moving parts required for
The real version of a story that a crazy person game
Look around with a gun
Because you listen to Alex
Be very
On the air about the atomic bomb
Crazy guy
Just to be sure
Just to be
Be clear
We're
We talked about it
Mastiff
Conspiracy theorist
Triumph
The phrase Occam's razor
Out of it
Point Break with Occam's razor
That doesn't make sense there's people
Too much s*** going on how about it's just one dude
Yeah
I am really frustrated by
Characterization
Because it's always
100% support the
The police
That is
DC police
Making everything up
Sweeterman
And then you've got the
Police
Consumption
And there's always
You need to know that there are good cops
And bad cops
But you don't know who they are and the good cop
Splendidly
Black people
Yeah
It's it
Very much
Something where
You with you would think
Try to have some kind of through-line
Some kind of Baseline
For how you should treat
No jumping in the DC police
With the peace
Gay people
He doesn't have like a through-line of
What makes one good what makes one bad
Ketchup ketchup
Whatever the circumstances are
Through-line whatever
You does it serve my narrative
Exactly
We're not the ones running around saying kill everybody we're not the one saying bomb Trump Tower
Kill kill kill kill this person kill that person what's Johnny Depp
They're going to turn it into a horrible lightning
Supporters
You're wearing Trump hat
It's political
Clip but
Did you just
Before we introduce the next cut
Life clip
The previous flight
What are they going to do
So
The thing there is we get a real glimpse into Alex Jones thinks the world Opera
Deal with first
Johnny Depp
Cuz he's someone who's not an act
Who doesn't
Just talk
These are positive
Right but those are positive attributes
And these heard of world of
Macho Alex Jones
Implicitly what are you saying
Some real man comes on
You got a kill you
That's not good that's very irresponsible again
People are going
To hear that coded language
He seems to think
The globalist
Water Civil War
I'm so they're putting out these messages but no one else is really picking up Onix
Except for him
And that is the jump off
Let's jump off
Let's do this
Let's provoke the Patriots into attack
You're not the only person
I really think that is
Experiencing those things
Probably because of
Very it's very dangerous
I'm having trouble with his
Is language
Because
II
And I
Feel like it
Part of doing
Is podcast
It's hard knock
Talk in the
Okay
To do it there in like
Minions kill Trump and all of these things
Daenerys every
Thing is Viola
Every metaphors
Violin every
Everything that he's talking about is always
The threat of violence for the
Reply
Totally
All I can think of when he says like
They're starting a Civil War and all the s*** is that
Kind of
Blizzard reaction
Girl we are starting that's not good
It's getting into my f******
Consider that
Unintentional
But I don't think you will
My reaction doing all this like they're trying to start a civil war they're promoting violence
And all I hear is
You are trying
Not you Alex
Projection
I get I get
Cuz I look into the stories
Video sites I look into sources
And all of them don't accurately depict his rep
Presentation
So I know that either
He's unaware of the nuanced reality
Stop
He's intentionally twisting it
Service
And either way what you doing is
Speeding in
Separation
He's feeding into radicalization
Vulcanization the thing he's super afraid of
He's making his followers
So much further from the rest
The general population
Results of that much like
Extreme nationalism
Is just War
It's just going to be
Just rhetoric can't get ramp down
This sort of thing isn't
Something he can be escalate on his own real
There has to be something
What is a payoff
All of the economic collapse
Talk the payoff the blow off of the
The feud
Is
Person telling people go
That's to prep you for that
Now hopefully
All of the
This rhetoric is
Just leaving to a selfie
Hopefully down the line cuz the only other logical blow-off is
Actual
News hoping that something happens if you just waiting
And then he can
Spin his
Well if it's a minority I can say that they're attacking
He's just waiting
For something to happen
Validate his rattle
Yeah
Really f******
Bummer
He's talking to a
In the same way that he
Deescalate
DF
If he
Escalated even the Slate
He's out now
He's reached essentially his feeling
Obliquely
Threatening people like specifically
And not
Not far away
That do threading
The kill me
We're in a hospital started on June 14th
They're coming
Some of us are going to die if we don't get offenses
All of this stuff taken as a whole is
Bike
We not we know what you're saying
Yeah
Bad
So
Pei
Is really
Yeah
Find this
I almost don't want to play the rest
There's not really anything else
Other than theme but he complains about Joe Scarborough a little bit
Take me a job
All right I don't like
Forgotten
Mars Attacks aliens
Alien from Mars
Martian head
Famous Mass murderers daughter
Dictatorship
Removing so you with all your billions of dollars.
Marble policeman
Call Church
All right so just to take a quick break there
I like the Scarborough
Ghetto lol
When he was a senator
Who's the representative
He was in con
I don't remember
Cuz I don't like Joe Scarborough
He's probably butt on July 20th 2000 11 Scarborough's a died after hitting her head on it
Scarborough
Florida author
According to Scarborough allegation
Spread all over the Internet that you've been involved
There was an investigation no evidence
Foul Play
And what date
2001 is ripe for 911
Situation
Before 911
Yeah I think that obvious
Scarborough hell
Pepper Potts
Okay
What is
Evil face
Stole those
But Scarborough found
El kabong
Boom
Done it up the desk
There's no evidence of Foul Play like I said although
DC cops
Logical point
The life of that rumor on the Internet is far greater than
And the fact
Merit
What is the same thing with I mean
Gary Condit probably did Kill Chandra Levy
Right now we didn't
Someone confess
I don't remember
Didn't write for 9/11
Eminem
We're done with that
Yeah I mean the only good thing
To come out of 9/11 with
The blueprint
Is this
Fever to tell
The great albums
Okay
Gary Condit
Iraq
Solid
He's going to get to
He's going to get to economics
A little bit
Just like Starbucks
Precipitously
Purchases dropping
25%
And none of its right Michelle
Everyone just said you know what
Hotel
Coffee is Starbucks
Everett
Starbucks
You know I'm not booking with your hotel and you know that
George Ward. Not the other way around
Starbucks hates your fam
Is this is a freedom fries
Situation
And it's all just because
Stripes bar
Dan
How about those
It's all just because Starbucks said they were going to hire Refuge
Well they said they were
Did you not read
Presser
Starbucks
We will give jobs
Invader
You know this is lava
Everyone's like to play video games
The Vets I like
Flashback
8 months earlier
Hiring vets
Suck it
Totally right
Completely lying about calling hotels
What why would you even pretend
I've ever heard your dumbass
Even if you are against Starbucks and if you're an Alex Jones listener in there like
Starbucks is hiring Muslim
At best you're going to be like
Donuts
Starbucks
Is your only option
You got to get the
Make breakfast
Flat cakes
I'm done
But I don't even want to play it
It's just a dumb sales pitch
I'm just I don't hear his voice anymore
That's actually
2017 Alex Jones
Is just
He's not what I want
He's not good
It's really scary
Monitoring him and what have you
But
Boy 2015 is such a better time
Wendy said I retreated into 20
You are waylaid
Good long while now
Like
This is
Yeah
Like this is no fun
To listen to
And it's just
Very much
Elizabeth speaks
Killed
That's all
You know never sighting anything just saying that everyone's trying to
To kill the president
That's not accurate at all
If you're going to pull
Bulshit like that
Just look at the facts
Networks
Turn the TV's off
There's no law that can
No
Specific examples about people who are calling for
Bizarrely celebrities
3 celebrities
Cuz it follows up on the
Hollywood Elite
Right right there is that
But it all just feels like
Employees
Top-heavy
But like working actors
General ER
Commercial
But like
This gear is
If I had to put a bow a bow on
Got the feeling that I get is that we're watching
The beginning of
Something that is about to get out of
Like
I don't think necessarily that
Civil War is
Insurrection
But I do think
Activate the rhetoric that Alex is throwing around
It's probably going to
To get to a point where he can't
Control it anymore
He's going to radicalize his audience
Take on a life
Beyond him
Oh and he's already experienced that new
His career
Like he's responsible for a lot of people
Going down the
Conspiracy palette
Realizing
Realizing in like a quote on quote
Israel is
The problem
And then turning on Alex
It's because they think he's a Zionist chill
Rat he already have radicalized tons of people to out-and-out lights
Soupremacy because of that
Like because of because of
His actions
And because of the rhetoric that he uses on his show
He has had people like go to the go beyond
I know if people are listening to this
And they've had the lead up
Of the last
6 month
They're going to kill the president they're trying to kill him
We're on under attack from all sides
There always are
Beyond hello
Alert
The only outcome that can really come from it
Him losing
Control of his audience
Again
And in a much worse way
Yeah they just people going to storm front
Hangouts
The only thing
Genuinely
As far as
Like another
Another like Malay
What were the fox
Occupied
Snow park for some dumb reason
Cliven Bundy
Ammon Bundy
Really doing
What does the does the guys that I see is a
As a real three
Keepers are pretty big group
There a lot of folks
Like that
I mean you see it every time that there is a
One of these marches
There's always
Counter protest
The everything and
I mean it
Society does have a lot of problems that we need to address
Liberal problem some of them were conservative problem
And level-headed people could take a look at all of them
I hopefully come to a conclusion
They works for everybody
I buy professorship flying around
Impossible
But I see things getting worse
Preparing for it
Nope
Because I refuse
Is to buy a gun
Alex Jones
Which I mean again
That's the other angle that we're being remiss
In a little bit
What if he is difficult
He doesn't have an agenda
Really this is
Is just about Sal
You call first
It's like icing
Cialix
That we saw
Was
Yeah it's supposed to be a lot more like that then
Straight up
He's bought his own bulshit
Well I think in 2015 he was huckster with a philosopher
Like the globalists are still there but it mostly in service is selling
It is
Like he's barely even
Veiling
Globalist
Like
Easier
This episode that we've gone over possibly
No he's still talking about the Volvo
What's all the time
If somebody wasn't
Puyallup
I just feel like so far that the app
Target
The more specific ones
RN
Anything liberal
Yeah but is that
It's like I don't think it liberalism is authoritarianism in disguise
Liberalism is just b*******
The tries to get us to socialism
Which will lead to Communism which will lead to Authority
That is his world
Every liberal value
Is 1
Creeping step
Closer
To this
Communist night
That he thinks
We will head to her
So yeah it is
Still got everything liberal
Protocols of the elders
Zion
ISO
This has been a bummer but
If you want two more bikes
Yeah please
Or website
You can also follow us on
Twitter
Aetna
If you'd like to come
Say hi
Female knowledge fight at gmail.com
Look it up on iTunes download that
Send it around
Libreview
There's a button on the website appreciate it
Stop right there
If you want to
You can do it
You figure it the f*** out how but you
Good luck
Ufirst exactly
Soaps for
Reconciliation in Dayton
Our kind of dying all around us I feel like
It seems like that is
Cooperation is
It's on its last leg
But is there any silver lining
I can think of only one thing that will brighten our day when everything is looking
Dark
Rapoport
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work